Come on come on come on move it
Go
oww ass..
you okay?
oscar be careful
there is no fair
we go
be more carefull then
hey Oscar where are we
Sharken
yeah i get than sharke but where are we
Fort collins ,man
yeah we are in fort collins in this map actually where nowthe map..
all right you look the nail ,
its like i told you emily
when i by the heard on my little experience..
....... in the back easy
by run lunch time in the now you have a problem
see look its an anormal
so why?
Randy ,dont be ugly
this mee
sorry
i'm pregnant for there
because i got stomach
yeah i gotta go too
sneaks
all right ,allright....
thank you
ur welcome
it is hot
stick
that's just a joke
you must be polite to the ladies
she doesnt know u kidding
you too all right..
i guess not always sensitivity all right
what the hell man?
hey gotta guests and take some alcohol
thanks
how much
Thats five..........
Tourist Attacked in Collins. Lockjaw?
Fort Collins Mine Collapses.
Another Creature Sighting
LIEN TIMES! More Attacks Coming
actual footage
oh shit
holly shit
what the holly shit about?
Thats LOCKJAW
Look at this a few footprint
some people believe in....
thats right boys
expect you no idea....
u fucking mouth off....
out of blood
okay everbody just taken....
we did not mean..okay?
yeah no idea
guyss
u gotta check so far
sea the house that grimley built out of blood
Guided tours of LOCKJAW COUNTRY 5$..
go along ur funeral..
man,this is awesome , i love this
no relation, son
oh my dad wean all kind of stuff
no way
thats a fucking asshole
whats talking on?
is the house still here?
yup.....
Dont you want to see B.J_?
it that for
Niles
sure
yes sir
let draw a map
lets see u take the road here
so young
you guys thanks for we had a good time..
thank for the map
got damn its.....
okay hey
check that and wht u think?
read us , might become fun
all right
u know...
whats that
see the house that grimley built , he is grimley
but who is grimley
guess really wanna  know here
no
okay
story goes
i was this family call the btth.
deep...swamps
the family choosed the simple life,simple folk
like most families
around eighteen hundred it seems the boys family die
Curelyn and brother Grimley ..
wait u mean,oh man u know thats wrong
dont be s....
anyway
...destroyed..
..looking for any side the true love..
but Curelyn was gone now
grimley knows,he..
see ...animal planet and ..finish the story
grimley , he tracked...
in the darkness , ..so great,turned the range,
becoming change ...
and its madness..
he turned is so row , .. monster,that creatued it
he begin ,tweet....
oh my gush , i think im gonna be sad
this is story sugar
anyway
...he changed,beauty,become..one th.
they say he still up there,he swaps
looking for fresh meat....
thats the stupid thing i have ever heard
whatever
you know what yeah i mean this fun for me
everythings just one big event
shit
you love me?
all right
this is it..
ladies and gentlemen..
this is your captan is speaking...
lets go
here what we need
whats he doing
i dont know...
found it , come one guys whats waiting for?
come on , lets go , creepy....third,,third dishes...
im with you
speeders help
u oky okay come on sit down take it easy
here u got a....
thanks emily
ok guys im really sorry lets just building enough ths the road
no come on oscar  the camp is far,its just this way
hey Caroline  where are you going?
i wanna look there,..see,,
you come in oscar..
come on...pleasee
oh goodness , randy she cantt go allone she gets lost
make camp here....
im gonna in
Grimley are u in home?
grimley
all right ladies i think i gonna pie ...unless u think any help
No?
you sure?
greedy...
bless u baby
hey were we gone ,
come on sugar let me get the bed
yeah i'll help u...
thank you
ehm.. what are you doing..
u liked that?
its nice.. but i am..
...i know why
thats special...
hey sweetness how you're hot
sugar beth
shit
what the hells is going on here?
nothing
talking...
comfor....
its a beatiful area..
this is....
come on..
damn it Oscar
..what about me
what about me...
damn ,Oscar remember my brother
.... look?
everybody gonna give themself to line times
i know
look at me
i know swamp
all right ,speak to...
sons gone be upsoon
go get it row
shit
dont go far
whats that?
i heard somene over there
there is something there
what
its a pig
hello
let check it
oscar what the fuck doing men?
she was crying ,man..
who
look the f*ck..
who catched you
Randy...
u fucking delusional,,
hey Oscar Oscar! calm down..
okay stay here im gonna back to ...
thank you okay,im coming with you
why my brother not hurt anyone,.... kill someone
Emily , stay here
okay he smoked .....
probably having bad tripe,
but just in case something did happen
i wanna make you safe
im not safe with you.!.
ok look at him....
..shocked just put blank over arm just for..
all right?
hey trust me
ok
i love you
ok i love you
Oscar ,its okay
oh no no baby girl dont cry,
dont cry now darling
no -you stop that
this is an oner
yeah..true way
this used to big moms,and grandmother for her
it is along....
being the family long time...
now its yours
yeah ,im...
stop the bleed....
what the fuck,how the fuck 77?..
keep ur fucker....
oh shit
Randy ,Randy
Guys..
guys where are you..
whats that smell
this is not funny
god
drop it boy
why u running huh?
somethings ..us,okay  wee need help
See you .. happly boy
hey look us do you heard me
some big thing some animal monster things over here ,
so so must , you must gonna help us
w... the gett out our way ok?
you gotta boy i heard
but i gonna do that
he done choose you..
choose.. what the hell talking about?
what you think boy
god damn,he done choose you
that fucking animal?
he no animal
he...
we dont really wht u fucking say,why fucking get off way
shit up
u going back that house,,,right now
get up
you re right?
whats wrong asking my girlfriend..
emily
dont touch her
hey wheres emily
tell me you okay..
come on come on
we have to make this
come on
come on we gone take this
emily come on
im sorry
we take the boat we got a chance..
we got a chance
stay with me stay with me..
come on come on
this.. oner be doing for us , u choosed...
we think....
yes u will be make one of us,one of ...
Fuck you!
get up there
this will , will be done
like i was talked....
thank you
good looking boy too
turning is my baby's daddy
subtitle-JK-
Give me that old time religion give me that old time religion
It's good enough for me
It was good enough for mothers
Makes me love everybody makes me love everybody
and it's good enough for me
It will take us all to heaven
It's good enough for me
Give me that old time religion
subtitle-JK-