Go! Go! Go! Move!
Move!
Go!
This is yet another liberal attack on our values,
our families and on our way of life.
On the subject of gay marriage,
remember this, people.
This is not about the union of
two people of the same sex.
This, this is clearly the work of liberal judges
who are trying to force their will
on you, the American people.
Society at large is better served
by maintaining the sacred tradition of marriage.
As in a man and a woman joined
together by holy matrimony.
The people know it. You know it.
And I know it. This is Jim O'Bannon reporting.
Good night, everybody, and thanks
for watching The O'Bannon Files.
Yeah?
Arbor's gone, sir.
Missed his assignment in Seattle.
What happened? I'm not sure what happened.
He just vanished.
So the guy doesn't complete his assignment,
and you have no fucking idea where he is.
This is unacceptable.
Do you understand?
I understand. I'm gonna make it right.
I have Senate Oversight all over my ass.
And I'm meeting with the director tonight.
The last thing I need is a failed assignment
by a rogue agent who disappeared
and didn't follow orders.
He is your man. He is your responsibility.
Find him and fix it.
Yes, sir. Consider it done.
Good morning. How are you?
Good. Excellent.
This is Allan Campbell.
Hello, Allan. Do you know who this is?
Uh... No...
You're forgetting me already, Allan?
Listen, you know,
like I said, I'll...
I'll get you the money.
It's just a matter of time.
Well, that's great. Can you do it today?
No, no, no. Actually, I have a promotion today.
And after that happens, then I got it all covered.
The next time I see you, you better have my money.
Yeah, no, I understand. And I appreciate it.
Congrats on your career.
Thanks.
Oh, shit. Fuck.
Shit. God damn it.
You all right?
Huh?
Nicely done.
That's a good look. Don't laugh at me, Drew. Come on.
What happened to your eye anyway?
My eye's fine.
Just let me... Let me have your shirt, please.
What?
Just let me have your shirt.
I'm not gonna give you my shirt.
I can't go in to Gates like this.
You shouldn't have spilled coffee on it then.
Okay, well, I did.
And now I need your shirt, please.
Just... All right. All right.
Spill anything on your pants? You
want me to give you those, too?
Come on. Stop being like that.
Hey, everybody, I made it. Just kidding.
Big day, huh? Everybody pretty excited about it?
Hey, Allan made it.
Whoa.
What
happened with your eye, bud?
Nothing, man. I'm okay.
Yeah? Mmm-hmm.
I'm fine. Nothing, huh?
Doesn't look like nothing to me.
You got a new tie there, huh?
Classy. Gray. Didn't know that
was the new power color.
Strong choice. Thanks.
Mr. Gates.
Okay, fellas, we all have a lot of work to get back to,
so I'm gonna keep this snappy.
I've looked through all of your proposals.
And while I think all of you have
more than a little something to offer,
the proposal that hits the nail on the head
is the one that shows the most leadership
and vision that is gonna be required
to take this company into the future.
Congratulations, Felzner.
Thank you, sir. You are welcome.
And you can move into that new office
of yours whenever you'd like.
Excuse me, sir? Mr. Gates?
Yes, Allan?
Listen, you said that you liked my work.
You said that it was strong...
I said I liked your work, Allan. And I do.
Okay, so why am I not getting the promotion?
I mean, I've been here longer than Felzner.
Felzner is the future, Allan. It's as simple as that.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
Sorry, bro.
Hey, honey, it's me. Call me when you get a chance.
Come on. Fuck.
Where are you? Shit.
Campbell.
Brian, this is Allan.
You stole my idea.
And I know it.
And I'm gonna let Gates know it.
You can't get away with this. You hear me?
I'm not gonna let you get away with this.
Come on, lady.
Hey, honey. I've been trying to call
you. Why didn't you answer?
Where's Mike? I saw his car downstairs.
You all right? Something wrong?
Hey, Allan.
When did you become so detached?
What?
I'm gonna go.
Please.
Jesus, Mike.
I'm sorry.
I wanted you to know.
Hmm.
This isn't working, Allan.
You are always so distant, so concerned
with climbing the ladder.
For us, Syd.
It was always for us.
I believe you. I do.
But somewhere along the line,
you actually forgot about me.
I mean, look at us. We don't even
fight with passion anymore.
The hot and cold I can take, but
this numbness in between...
So does that make this all okay?
No, it doesn't make it okay.
But don't pretend like I'm the only one with secrets.
Look at your face.
You think I actually believe that was an accident?
No, I just was trying to get ahead, Syd.
That's all I've ever done.
Well, maybe trying to get ahead,
you just fell behind.
Okay.
I'll go... I'll go get a hotel.
Allan, wait...
Can I get a J D straight up, please?
Big night ahead?
Epic.
You okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Can I get another one? Preferably in
a bigger glass, if you don't mind.
That's the biggest glass I got, sir.
I guess I'll be keeping you busy then tonight.
What are you drinking?
Water.
Seriously?
If it was a joke, would it be funny?
No, no, I mean, to each his own.
We interrupt this game to bring you
this breaking news story right now.
Jim O'Bannon, host of The O'Bannon files,
a sometimes controversial news and
opinion show viewed by millions,
was found dead just minutes ago
outside a downtown restaurant.
At this time... Barkeep.
...police tell us that apparently
he was shot to death at close range
alongside two of his bodyguards.
Jim O'Bannon was 58. We now
return you back to the game.
So Jim O'Bannon, huh?
That's kind of crazy, him getting killed.
Him being a big TV star and all, don't you think?
Fame doesn't make you invincible.
Yeah, and I always thought he was a bit of a jackass,
but nobody deserves to die, you know.
I'm Allan. How you doing?
What is this, some kind of fag bar?
No, I was just... I'm sorry.
I was just trying to make some
friendly conversation, that's all.
It's like I got "Everlast" stamped across my face, man.
Like a human punching bag.
Can I have another one, please?
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
Whatever, man. It's cool.
When I spoke to you earlier,
I must have given off the impression
that I was game for conversation.
If I wasn't, I should have kept my mouth shut.
Name's Jonas.
Allan. Allan Campbell.
What you said about being a human punching bag,
you definitely look the part.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Corporate world's a bitch.
How'd you know that?
I read The Wall Street Journal.
No, I mean how did you know that
I... I work for a corporation?
How'd you know that?
Doesn't everyone?
I'm an engineer.
You like it?
Not at the moment, no.
Why's that?
You ever...
You ever have a really, like, a really bad day,
I mean a really fucking bad day?
Until recently, no. But recently, yes.
Well, my boss, he all but promised me
a promotion and then gave it to the new guy.
I mean, I've been working there for nine years.
I mean, I was relying on it. I had... Investments.
There's always someone else.
Our own expendability, that's all you
can ever really count on in this life.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Doesn't really explain the eye, though.
It's a bit complicated,
to say the least.
I guess some investments can really cost you.
Yeah.
Can you keep them coming, please? Thanks.
I've known her for years.
Since college.
I've known Mike... I met him just before.
And Mike is?
He was my best friend.
Your best friend that's fucking your wife?
Yeah, well, he's not my... Yeah, yeah.
Well, it's okay, then.
Yeah, son of a bitch was my best man at our wedding.
You know, Allan, what you said before, you were right.
You are a human punching bag.
You allow your boss to pass you
over like a Jewish holiday.
You obviously allowed someone to
work one over on you pretty good.
And you allowed your wife to fuck another guy.
I wouldn't say I allowed it.
Yes, you did, Allan. You allowed it. All of it.
You're the one who said it.
You're so afraid to stand up for yourself
no matter what anyone does to you.
That makes you a self-perpetuating
victim of circumstance.
I'm not looking for any sympathy here.
I just wanted to have some...
Shoulder. I get it. Your problem,
Allan, is that you're weak.
Your wife sees it. That's why she figures
she can sleep with your best friend.
Your best friend, he sees it.
That's why he figures he can wrap legs with her
and not suffer any real consequences.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I think you're... You're crossing the line a little bit.
Okay.
Who the hell are you
to tell me who I am and who I'm not?
As far as I see it, I'm the closest thing
to a friend you've ever really had.
I mean, we've known each other
for what, two hours? Come on...
How long did you know Mike?
Look how that turned out.
I'm your friend, Allan,
because I got the balls to be brutally honest with you.
Complete and total openness,
no skipping paragraphs.
Everybody else in your life is full of shit.
You know, for somebody who claims
to know so little about people,
you certainly got everything figured out.
Hmm?
It's part of my job.
What's that? You're like a...
You a shrink? You shrink heads
for a living? What do you do?
I'm a professional killer, Allan.
Bullshit.
Jim O'Bannon,
that guy we saw on the TV earlier?
Hmm. What about him?
Yeah, right.
When I said I wasn't much of a people person,
I meant I always work alone.
But I always know my opponent.
That's how I can read people so well.
Seriously?
If it was a joke, would it be funny?
Okay, fine. Let's say hypothetically,
you killed O'Bannon. Why?
I was paid to perform a job, but then decided
to come here and do O'Bannon instead.
Personal reasons.
That's pretty sloppy for a so-called professional.
I mean, you come here, you kill O'Bannon,
and then you give a tell-all to a complete stranger.
But we're not complete strangers,
Allan. We're friends, remember?
Here we go.
Here, I'll prove it.
Write down five names.
What?
Pretend you just paid me a considerable
amount of money.
I work for you now.
You want five people dead, and you're gonna
write their names on that napkin.
Okay, come on. Come on.
Everybody has names, Allan.
Especially you.
Okay. I'll play along.
So what, like, what specific order do you want?
What do you want?
Let's say number five dies first
and then I work my way up.
Number one being the priority.
Five, okay, so I'll put, five. Okay,
how about... Okay, five.
Fred Gates. You know, the boss
that I was telling you about.
Okay. Thanks.
Okay, Fred Gates.
Number four. Brian Felzner.
The guy that got your promotion.
He stole my idea.
He did. He stole my idea. He put
his little spin on it, whatever.
But he stole my idea, Jonas.
And this is the kind of douchebag, let me tell you.
I hate people like this.
They drive around in their little
cars, and they have these...
You know, the personalized license plates.
His says "Feltz" on it.
I mean, he should die just for that reason.
Okay, so Brian Felzner. That's number four.
Like I said, Allan, I can read you like an open book.
Number three.
You're gonna like this one.
Dom Escatdo.
Is that a cartoon character?
That's the one who, you know,
gave me the bump here.
The investment. Yeah.
Then his number's definitely up.
Number two.
It's a tough one. Mike Dodd.
Again, not without just cause.
And number one...
My sweet little wife.
Well, then that bitch definitely got to go.
Okay, okay. There you go.
There you go.
Now you can psychoanalyze me all you want.
It's a good list, Allan. No Dr. Phils.
I'm gonna take a leak. This is...
This is therapeutic. This feels good.
It's too bad you're not the real thing, Jonas.
What the hell!
As far as I see it, I'm the closest thing
to a best friend you've ever had.
I just wanted you to know we slept together, Allan.
We slept together, Allan.
You allowed your wife to fuck another guy.
Hey, Allan.
You care? You really don't care, do you?
Felzner is the future.
Congratulations. Thank you, sir.
It's as simple as that.
Your problem, Allan, is that you're weak.
Hey.
Yeah, trying to get ahead.
Is that the new power color?
Trying to get ahead.
Strong choice, man.
Trying to get ahead, you fell behind.
You are a human punching bag.
Look at your fucking face. Look at your fucking face.
You think I actually believe that's an accident.
I work for you now.
You want five people dead,
and you're gonna write their names on that napkin.
Fucking your wife. Fucking your
wife. Fucking your wife.
Oh, God. Hello?
Where are you?
Why haven't you called me back?
Maybe 'cause I knew it was you, Syd.
I've been calling you all night, Allan.
I thought maybe with the way your face looked...
Why do you care? Why do you care where I've been?
I care, and you know that.
I just needed...
Shit.
McKay!
Come on, boss. I just got here.
We just got another shooting.
Where? Out by Frankfurt.
Weird thing is it looks like it ties into O'Bannon.
Oh, yeah? How so?
Ballistics matched the slugs we took out of O'Bannon
and his bodyguards.
They've ID'd them as something
called a 5.7 millimeter.
Really?
You know something?
The 5.7's only been on the market a few years.
It's nasty shit.
Super accurate, screaming hot velocity,
kind of stuff you find on the battlefield,
not in your backyard. That's just great.
So tell me more about this new one.
Like I said, same MO as before.
Only this time it looks like he took his time with it.
Crime scene figures after the first shot to the belly,
he let him flail around for an hour or so
before finishing him off with two more to the head.
Okay, so this one's a little more
personal. Who's the vic?
Hey, man.
What the hell is going on?
You didn't hear?
No, Drew. What's going on?
Gates, man. He's dead.
What?
He's dead.
The cops are supposed to be by this morning
and ask us all some questions.
Number five. My boss, Fred Gates.
Have you seen Felzner around?
Number four. Brian Felzner.
Brian? I don't know.
I think he had a meeting over at Victor Rosen's. Why?
No, I was just... I was just curious.
You okay, man?
Hmm?
You don't look so good.
No, yeah, no... I'm fine. Will you
put that at my desk, please?
I just... I drank a lot last night, Drew.
Hey, do you work here?
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
Detective McKay. Hi.
What's your name? Allan Campbell.
Hey, Allan. Look, I don't know if you're aware,
but your boss was murdered last night.
No, yeah, no, I heard. That's...
Yeah, someone broke into his house and shot him.
What are you guys thinking, a robbery or...
Well, you can only be robbed
if something gets taken, right? Hmm.
Look, I'm here to talk to all the employees,
but now that we've already met,
why don't I start with you?
You know, Detective, if you don't mind,
I have a really important meeting
that I'm already late for.
So if I could come back anytime,
I can come back today or...
Yeah, yeah, sure.
How about noon?
Does that work for you?
Yeah. Noon's fine.
Let me give you this just in case. And...
I hope you don't mind me asking,
but where were you last night?
Huh?
Where... Where were you last night?
Oh, at home with my wife. Yeah.
Okay? Yeah, I gotta ask.
I'll see you back here...
Thank you very much. Appreciate it.
Hey, you've reached Brian Felzner.
Please leave a message, and have a great day.
Hey, Brian. This is Allan Campbell.
Will you please give me a call
when you have a chance?
Victor Rosen's office.
Is Brian Felzner there?
Brian Felzner?
Yes, the engineer.
Oh, right. He's actually with Mr. Rosen.
Thanks.
Morning, Allan.
Jonas?
What the hell are you doing here?
Waiting for you, obviously.
You killed Gates?
You're welcome.
Why are you doing this?
I'm your friend, remember?
Jonas, this is fucking crazy. Stop it, please.
Some people never go crazy. What
truly horrible lives they must lead.
I don't want you to do this. Please.
How are you planning on stopping me, Allan?
By going to the police?
Be sure to mention your involvement
as my employer when you do.
What! Are you... What!
I'm sure there's no legal ramifications
for something like that.
Listen, God damn it! I was just having a drink,
having a conversation, just friendly conversation!
I don't... This is a joke! I thought it was a joke!
Allan, lower your voice.
I don't want people to die!
What the hell did you think a hit list was?
Okay. Look, fine.
Fine, if I'm your employer,
then you're fired. Okay?
You're fired. That's it.
Let's just end this.
No can do, Allan.
I'm not the kind of guy to turn his back on a friend
when he sees that he's sick.
Sick? What the...
What are you talking about?
You allow the people in your life to walk all over you.
That's a sickness.
No. They have to learn
that there are consequences when they fail you.
Number four hasn't been crossed off the list yet.
I can't let you do this.
Then stop me, Allan.
Stop me.
Come on, Brian. Pick up.
Come on. Come on. Pick up.
Shit!
Come on. Come on.
Would you say he was angry?
I wouldn't say he was angry. He
was just really disappointed.
McKay.
Detective McKay, this is Allan Campbell.
We just met a few minutes ago.
You know, it's funny, your buddy Drew, here,
and I were actually just talking about you.
What?
Yeah, you and your boss had some kind
of disagreement yesterday, Allan?
No, no, no, no. Just listen to me.
I didn't kill him, okay, but I know who did.
Oh, yeah? And who might that be?
Look, there was a guy I was drinking with
in a bar last night.
His name is Jonas.
You gotta trust me, okay?
And you're saying this drinking buddy of yours,
he was the one who clipped Gates?
Yeah! And he's going after Felzner next!
Who's Felzner? Brian Felzner!
The guy who took my promotion!
Your promotion?
Listen, God damn it! I don't have time for this!
You have to come and meet me! Please.
Allan, calm down.
Why don't you come back into the office
and we'll take care of that interview already?
No, no. You come to me.
I'll explain everything to you
when I see you, okay? Please.
Where are you?
The Rosen building. Just please hurry!
Shit. Don't go anywhere.
This is Detective McKay.
I need a unit to meet me over at the Rosen building.
Come on.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm looking for Brian Felzner.
You called earlier, right? Yeah. Yeah.
You just missed him.
I did?
Hello, there.
Hey, Brian! Brian! Brian.
Campbell!
What the hell are you doing here?
Look, somebody's trying to kill you.
What?
Please. You have to believe me. Okay, just...
If this has something to do with the Gates proposal...
Listen, God damn it! It has nothing
to do with that, okay?
You know something about what happened to Gates?
Yeah, yeah. Yes, I...
Look, yeah, yeah, you stay the hell away from me.
No, no, no. No, please!
No! You stay the fuck away from me! All right, Allan...
No!
Time to go, Allan.
I'm not going with you. I'm not
going with you anywhere, man.
Let's go. Please don't!
Let's go. Come on.
What did you do... Get in the car!
Do you want to be here with Brian?
Get your ass in that car!
Do it!
Let's go, Allan!
Jesus Christ... Get in the car!
Open the door!
I don't want to open it.
Please, Jonas... Get your ass in...
Please, Jonas! Please! Get in the fucking car!
Hang on.
Shit!
Whoa!
Stop it!
Jesus!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Fuck.
No! God!
What about our uni? Is he gonna make it?
You got a 20 on that black caddy yet?
All right, okay, let me know.
So, get this, guy goes bananas
right out in the open for everyone to see.
He flattens Felzner in the Caddy, and then he hops out
and he double taps him for good measure.
And we're sure that Campbell wasn't the shooter?
Not according to witnesses.
And we got a building security camera
that shows a black male, mid-40s.
Witnesses say he puts a gun up to Campbell's head
and he forces him into the car.
Campbell mentioned another guy,
somebody he met at a bar last night.
Said this guy was the one that clipped Gates.
We traced Campbell's cell phone back to his car.
Okay, good. We need to talk to Campbell's wife
and anyone else who's seen him the last couple days.
I'm on it.
This just doesn't make any sense.
The shooter, you've seen his shot groupings.
He's a pro.
Why run him over and make a show of it?
It's like he's doing all this just for fun.
Let's go.
He had a family.
He still does.
How can you do that?
How can you just kill somebody like that?
God doesn't discriminate. I guess
he made me in his own image.
Life's a fluke, Allan.
A flash in the pan and then it's over.
A trigger's like a fast forward button.
I just skip to the end credits on other people's lives.
Or not.
The choice is mine to make.
Where are we going, Jonas?
Get in the car.
Number three comes after four.
Number three.
Dom Escatdo.
Ford here.
- Any news?
Not yet, sir. Just landed.
I know you landed 'cause I can track a goddamn flight.
Do we have a 20 on our friend?
No, but we have very good reason
to believe he's in the city.
So nothing has changed since our last conversation.
Do you think he's dead?
Possibly, but unlikely.
Well, he is a dying man. Maybe he'll
die before you fuck it up again.
If he doesn't, it's your ass. Are we clear?
Yes, sir. I'll find him.
Police are pursuing the suspect
who, according to witnesses,
murdered a man by running him over
with a car and then shooting him.
The suspect, who you can see here
in this surveillance photo,
was seen speeding away from the scene of the crime
with a white male in his mid-30s.
Ford is taking care of our problem.
It's unclear whether that man
is working with the suspect
or was taken hostage.
Did we get a hit from his cell? Okay.
Any Internet activity? Okay.
Check the local hotels and rental car agencies
using every known alias.
It's a small town. How hard can it be to find him?
Local law enforcement's on him.
I'm headed downtown to meet
with the lieutenant in charge.
Will you please tell me what's going on?
Just a precaution.
Just get in the car and we'll explain
down at the station. Okay?
I've told you everything I know.
Yeah, you did.
Except that everything you've been telling us
is inconsistent with what's been developing.
Your husband's boss was murdered
last night. Did you know that?
No, I didn't.
A couple hours ago Brian Felzner was also killed.
Does that name sound familiar to you?
No.
He's one of your husband's co-workers, Mrs. Campbell.
He's the one who got the promotion.
You're aware that Allan didn't get the promotion, right?
Yes.
So in light of all of this, you're still claiming
that your husband was with you the whole night?
I'm sorry, I can't hear you.
Yes.
He was.
What are your husband's thoughts
on Jim O'Bannon, Mrs. Campbell?
What?
I'm sorry,
are you suggesting Allan had
something to do with that?
Yeah, that's what we're trying to figure out.
You ever seen this man before, Mrs. Campbell?
Just from this photo from the
news. But besides that, no.
You've never seen him before?
You have absolutely no idea who he is?
No. I don't. Then why in the hell
was your husband in the car with him
when he killed one of my men?
I don't know! Look, I don't know
what the hell is going on!
But trust me, Allan would never
have gotten involved with something like this.
He couldn't have.
And yet, strangely enough, he does have motive
for at least two of these victims.
Okay. What about any disputes he may have had?
Aside from the one with his boss and Brian Felzner.
Any enemies, maybe?
No, just because he didn't get a promotion at work
does not make these people his enemies, Detective.
Not necessarily, no.
But it doesn't make them his
friends now, either, does it?
What about his eye? How'd that happen?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I'm sorry, Mrs. Campbell, but he's your husband.
I mean, I'm not a married guy,
so maybe I'm speaking out of turn here.
But I'd like to think that if I was
and I came home looking like
I'd been decked in the face
that maybe my wife would at least inquire
as to how the hell it happened.
Look, he just said it was an accident.
And I trust him.
- And that's it?
Yes.
You just left it at that? No further questions?
You and your husband having any
problems lately, Mrs. Campbell?
Trouble at home? I'm sorry.
What... What does that have to do with anything?
Hmm. It's just a question.
Everybody has problems.
Yeah.
Here we are, Allan.
Jonas,
this is the one guy
on the list I don't care about.
I mean, look what he did to my eye.
What's the story with you and that cartoon, anyway?
You don't seem like the degenerate type.
A friend of mine at work told me about
a fix. Said it was a sure thing.
Aside from death, there is no sure thing, my friend.
I promise you that shit.
We ain't open yet.
Let's get out of here.
I was wondering if I could talk to Dom.
And what the fuck do you want to see him for?
Tell him it's Allan Campbell regarding
the money he owes him.
I'm telling you, all right. You gotta come down here.
No, we got the place gutted. It still needs a lot of work.
But your money's being well spent. Trust me.
When we're through with this place,
it's gonna be the hottest fucking
nightclub in town. All right?
Yes.
I think these guys want to see
you about a little bit of money.
I gotta call you back.
I remember you.
Your eye looks good.
You got my money already?
No. I... No.
Hmm.
Then what the fuck are you doing here?
What did I say to you the first and
last time we spoke? Hmm?
You have two weeks and the next time I see you
you better have my fucking money.
Mr. Escatdo, I'm afraid Allan has
given you all that he has to give.
What are you, his lawyer?
Who the hell are you? What the
fuck are you even doing here?
I'm his friend.
His friend? Is this some kind of fucking joke?
If it was, would it be funny?
So let me get this straight.
You bring this Shaft wannabe in here
to intimidate me out of the money you owe me?
Does that sound about right? Some shit like that?
Yeah.
Do you even know who the fuck I am?
Mr. Escatdo, Allan is not a gambling man.
He had a lapse in judgment.
Made a mistake.
And I'm pretty sure
he had every intention of paying you
back once he got his promotion.
Oh. So what, I'm supposed to
just cut my losses? Is that it?
That would be greatly appreciated.
Listen, you little piece of shit.
I'm not afraid of this sly motherfucker here!
But if you do not get me my money,
I will fucking smoke you
and everyone who's ever fucking known you!
And when I say everyone, I mean every fucking body!
You...
Fuck you!
Fuck.
Whoa, whoa. No, no, no.
Come. No, no, no.
Jesus Christ.
Shoot him. What?
Shoot him, Allan.
What are you doing? Hey, come on.
Shoot him, Allan. No, no, no.
You don't owe me anything. All
right? The debt's cleared.
You said it.
You don't care what happens to him, right?
Isn't that what you said to me?
You think I'm fucking stupid?
No.
No. What was your plan?
I don't have... You put Dom and I in a room together
and then we just wipe each other out?
Was that it? Seriously?
I'm sorry.
No. Hey. Please don't make me a part of this.
I don't want to be a part...
You are a part of it, Allan.
Whether you like it or not, you're a part of this.
God.
The part you play is up to you.
Shoot him.
Don't! Don't listen to him!
I will fucking pay you! I will pay you!
Anything you want, all right.
Anything you want!
Anything! Shoot him, Allan!
Don't listen to him!
Don't you fucking listen to him!
Do it. Allan, do it. Please! Please don't!
Do it! Do it! I don't want to!
Shoot him, Allan! Don't fucking kill me!
Shoot him, you fucking pussy!
Shoot him! Please don't!
See, I'm not like you! No!
Fuck!
Fuck. You motherfucker.
Oh, now you're showing initiative?
I like it, Allan.
Yes.
Do it. Shoot me.
I'm not a killer.
Neither was I once.
But you'll get there.
Unless you physically stop me, this list gets completed.
No. Yes.
We work our way up. Number one is still the priority.
No! You don't hurt her! You hear me?
God, no!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Stop! Stop! He's inside!
He's inside! Drop the gun!
Drop the gun right now! Drop the
gun! He's in there! He just shot...
Drop the gun right now! Face away from me!
Listen to me! He's right fucking there.
Drop the gun! Face away from
me! Face away from me!
He just killed some people!
- God damn it!
- Get down on your knees!
Okay. Get down on your knees!
Get down! Get down! Get down!
All right!
You gotta believe me! He's right there!
Hands out to the side!
He's right inside! Hands out to the side!
Stay right there! Get your hands out to the side!
Bring your other hand back!
Sir, listen to me! He's inside!
Why don't you open the goddamn
door! Where are you?
Son of a bitch! Where the fuck are you?
Please, you need to help me find my wife. You...
Settle down. Settle down, hotrod.
We need to find my wife, you hear...
She's fine.
She's upstairs. She's fine.
She what?
Take a seat.
We picked her up after your little incident downtown.
I figured, with the body count you're
leaving in your wake today,
keeping her with us was a pretty safe bet.
What's your relationship to Mike Dodd?
He's a friend of mine. Listen, he's in trouble.
Okay, you need to find him. He's
number two on the list. All right?
You mean this list?
Jesus.
Don't worry, I'm sending a car
over to pick him up. Sit down.
Hmm? Sit down!
Now what the fuck is going on here, Campbell?
You got ties to at least two of these
vics and possibly a third.
I got one dead cop and you at the scene waving a gun.
Listen, I tried to tell you...
No, you told me a joke.
Two guys walk into a bar. Fucking hilarious.
The shooter, Campbell.
Who is he?
His name is Jonas.
You got a last name?
No. I... I don't know.
Well, how the hell do you fit into all this?
Because if I'm perfectly honest, from where I stand,
you could very much look like an accessory.
Okay, I told you I went into a bar last
night, and I wanted to have a few...
No, no, no. You told me that you were at home
with your wife last night.
And so did she.
She said that?
You better start cutting me a clue here, Campbell.
What's your relationship to this Jonas?
There is no relationship. Okay?
Please just trust me. All right?
I went into a bar. I got a little drunk.
I wanted to talk to somebody.
I thought all this was... It was just a joke.
Then I woke up in the morning
in my car. I went into work
and I found out that Gates was dead.
Now if you don't get to Mike Dodd
before he does,
he's gonna be dead, too.
I've heard some crazy shit in my time,
but that's got to be about up there
with the goddamn craziest.
I don't know, I think I believe him.
Seriously?
Yeah, look at this guy.
He's in way over his head.
His record's squeaky clean.
He hadn't had so much as a parking ticket in six years.
He doesn't have that level of crazy in him.
Well, we're not sure of anything right now.
And until we are, he stays here.
How about Dodd?
Unit's on its way to pick him up.
We're here to see Mike Dodd.
Come on. Jesus Christ. Come on.
What the hell? Excuse me?
What is going on here?
Are you Mike Dodd?
Yes, I am.
Do you know an Allan Campbell, sir?
Yes, I do.
Detective said somebody would be coming by
to explain something to me.
What's going on?
Well, apparently, he broke in here looking for you.
I'm afraid you're gonna have to come with me.
For your own protection, sir.
This is just great. Oh, my God.
I've been so worried.
I'm sorry, Allan.
You slept with my best friend.
And you want me dead for it.
No.
Oh, man, I didn't mean for any of this...
Why do you think Mike was there, Allan?
What's wrong?
I can't do this.
This was a mistake, Mike.
Allan, we never slept together.
What?
I feel like you left our marriage,
and you've been so distant for so long.
I just... I wanted you to find me with Mike.
I wanted to know that I still mattered to you.
What I did was a mistake, and I'm so sorry.
Yeah. Me, too.
Man.
Those people, Syd,
those people are dead because of me.
No.
No, if this guy hadn't found you,
he would have met somebody else.
But I did meet him.
And I wrote those names down.
No. Come here.
What do you think he wants?
He wants me to kill him.
Can I help you?
Lieutenant Harp?
That's right.
Special Agent Ford.
My agents and I are here to help
solve your little problem.
What's this about?
We're here regarding Jonas Arbor.
Whatever information you attain
on the whereabouts of him must
be shared with us immediately.
Then we'll take it from there. Just like that?
You have no idea who you're dealing with here.
You go after a man like Arbor, and
it ends only one way. Bad.
This is a direct order, Lieutenant.
Yeah, can I talk to you guys for a second?
You wanted me to check on Mike Dodd's ETA?
Yeah. We can't reach the cops
we sent to pick him up. They won't respond.
It's got to be Jonas. What about the spooks?
We'll keep them entertained.
Jonas works for the US government?
Did. Now he's just an embarrassment to them
with a little too much press coverage.
That's the reason these guys are here.
So the same guys that created him
now want to take him down.
Look, I'm not thrilled about the way it is, either.
But it is what it is.
I think they're looking for us.
Please stop now.
No can do, Mike. We got a schedule to keep.
Why are you doing this?
I saw a friend in need.
Please!
There are penalties to be paid
for our indiscretions, Mike.
Allan?
You've been a very bad boy, Mikey.
Nothing happened!
Sydney, it was a mistake!
It's really too late for all of that.
Please. Please. I need a doctor.
Some people are beyond saving. Trust me on this one.
Detective?
Oh!
Son of a bitch. He's headed to the station.
Look at this guy. What the fuck?
Dispatch, this is Detective McKay.
Son of a bitch stole a police uniform.
I think he's headed your way.
What the hell was that?
It's him.
Code red. Code red.
All available to Metro Police Station.
All units respond.
Hey, get out of the goddamn way!
He went down...
Come on. Come on.
Watch them. If things go bad, take them out the back.
Evacuate all non-essential personnel immediately.
Hello, Jonas.
Ford.
You vanished like a puff of smoke in Seattle.
Just left us hanging.
So, what, the doc gave you the
news and you just snapped?
Realized you're not a God?
I stopped having any fun.
Then I met Allan.
You figured you'd go out with a bang. Is that it?
Whatever it takes.
I don't have to tell you what a liability you've become.
I played my part.
And all I was left with in the end is this dreaded cough.
And they say depleted uranium doesn't kill.
Well, I'm here to speed that up for you.
I've come to terms with my own mortality, my friend.
All that's left is to finish what I started.
We all die with food on our plate.
What's on yours?
McKay.
SWAT's on the way, boss. Just hold him off.
What are you doing?
He's coming for me, isn't he?
All right, people, you all know what to do.
Taylor, check the hallway. Williams, watch him.
Cease fire! Cease fire! God damn it!
Down!
You son of a bitch!
Go. Get out.
Let's go. Come on.
Shit.
Freeze!
Oh! Fuck me. Come on. We gotta get in there.
Shit.
Attaboy, Allan.
God, no!
It's up to you how this ends, Allan!
Sydney.
I see you.
Shit. How do we get out?
Allan.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Sydney.
Jesus.
Sydney. I can't do it. I can't keep running.
There you are. Okay.
Okay. You're okay, honey. Listen...
Clear! Move up!
All right. You're fine. That's right.
Okay, that's all right.
What are we doing?
What are we doing, Allan?
He's not gonna stop, Sydney.
He's not gonna stop until he kills you.
Come on. Keep it moving.
Allan.
Only you can end this, Allan.
You can't hide from me, Allan.
This is what I do.
Sydney.
Whoo!
Where are you?
There you are.
You're number one in my book, Syd.
A trigger's like a fast forward button.
I just skip to the end credits on other people's lives.
Or not.
The choice is mine to make.
I knew you had it in you.
Don't move!
Nobody move! Let me see your hands!
Get down! Get down!
Stand down! Stand down!
I can't let you do this.
Then stop me, Allan.
Stop me.
The hostage situation
at the police station in Spokane, Washington,
ended early this morning
when Metro SWAT engaged and
killed the suspect, Jonas Arbor.
Arbor's hostages, Allan and Sydney Campbell,
suffered non-life-threatening
injuries during their ordeal
and are now safely recovering at a local hospital.
It could be several days until the full death
toll from the rampage is known.
At this time, 18 deaths have been reported.
Three of the bodies are still unidentified.
It's now believed Campbell is innocent
of any criminal involvement with Arbor
and was simply an unwilling participant
in Arbor's deadly game.