When I was a boy of nine, I read a book
called The Malay Archipelago,
by the great 19th century naturalist,
the co-proposer with Charles Darwin
of the theory of evolution
by natural selection,
Alfred Russel Wallace. This is it.
And in it he describes his travels
and explorations
through Borneo and Sumatra,
eastwards through the islands
that are now Indonesia
to the western end of New Guinea.
And in it, I saw one illustration
that thrilled me to the marrow.
It shows greater birds of paradise
displaying in the forests of New Guinea
and being hunted
by native plume hunters.
It seemed to me then as now, that to see
the greater bird of paradise in display
must be one of the most thrilling sights
in nature.
And it became my childhood ambition
to go and do just that.
Well, it's taken me 60 years,
but here I am.
(People chattering)
I first tried to see the birds back in 1957.
But then
I could only get to eastern New Guinea,
where the species Wallace saw
doesn't occur.
And there was another problem -
the people used the plumes as money.
These are wedding gifts - pearl shells,
mats sewn with cowrie shells
but, most valuable of all
birds of paradise skins,
prepared in the traditional way by cutting
off the legs and the wings,
to fully reveal the plumes.
There were 21 of them.
The bride seemed pleased, but for us,
looking for live birds,
there was worse to come -
a celebratory dance.
Each man wore plumes
of at least 40 birds of paradise,
of several different kinds.
Most astonishing were the sawtooth
quills they wore through the nose.
These came from
the King of Saxony's bird, that then,
very few naturalists had even seen alive.
There seemed little chance of finding
living birds here,
so we decided to go into wilder country
to the north.
The headman called for porters.
We got 50. Once in the mountains,
our baggage was taken over by people
who didn't wear feathers in their hair.
Instead, they had huge wigs,
covered with bark cloth.
We heard calls of birds of paradise,
we glimpsed them high in the trees,
but we couldn't find a place
where we could film them.
And then, after three weeks
one morning at dawn,
our luck changed.
Low down, in a casuarina tree
a plumed bird of paradise.
And there, his unplumed female.
With these pictures,
we had achieved something.
As far as I knew
this was the first film ever taken
of a bird of paradise
displaying in the wild.
But our film was not in colour
the species was smaller than the one
that Wallace had seen
and there were not
a dozen dancing birds,
there was just one.
This was hardly the fulfilment
of that boyhood ambition.
But now, 40 years on, I'm trying again.
Wallace arrived in the Far East in 1854
but it was three years before he caught
the first glimpse
of a living bird of paradise.
And even then
it must have been a very distant one.
For, as he wrote, the birds only display
in the loftiest of trees.
And they are doing so in this one,
right here.
I reckon they are at least a hundred feet
above the ground.
Even with modern binoculars, it isn't
easy to see exactly what they are doing.
As far as I know
Wallace wasn't able to climb the tree
to get a closer view of the birds,
but these days we've got ways
of doing so relatively simply.
You fire a thin line, with a catapult,
over one of those high branches,
haul up a thicker rope,
attach a system of counterweights,
then all you have to do,
is to clip yourself on, and up you go.
Down goes the counterweight.
And now, I'm leaving that dark world
of the forest floor
and really entering
a completely new one.
Now I'm getting up into the canopy.
Into the world of the birds of paradise.
And here's the top.
The birds are in another emergent tree,
just like this one,
and I've got an absolutely clear view
of them.
It's unlikely
that they're going to take fright
at my sudden appearance
above the canopy,
because they've been using that tree
for generation after generation,
and it will take a lot more than just me
to put them off it.
This, at last
is Wallace's picture come to life.
He was the first European to glimpse this
extraordinary spectacle,
and he knew well
in general terms, what was happening.
This is a female
and she's come to pick a mate
from among the gorgeous males
who are displaying.
A young male. He's dancing even though
he hasn't yet got his plumes.
They don't develop
until he's six or seven years old.
There are several young males here,
putting in a little dancing practice.
This, however
is almost certainly a female,
because the males are starting
the second stage of their performance -
the bow, head down.
The female has hopped onto the perch
of the male of her choice -
that's a straight invitation to mate.
Act Ill - the approach.
Head up.
Act IV - the first physical contact.
It looks rough, but presumably she likes
this sort of treatment.
She could easily move away if she didn't.
And that's it.
And now there's another
to be attended to.
Apparently, there's a queue
on this particular perch.
This is all he does as a father.
Now she'll fly away
and raise her young unaided.
The males on the other perches,
in spite of all their efforts,
have no success at all.
He's at it again!
But his partner is not reacting properly.
She's facing away from him.
He's got it wrong, this is a young male.
All the matings are taking place
on this perch, with this male.
But are the females choosing the perch
or the dancer?
It's difficult to tell.
But it's easy to see
why these wonderful plumes
should be so treasured by local people,
and why, when the first examples
arrived in Europe in the 16th century,
they should have created a sensation,
as they did.
Those first specimens
had been prepared in the traditional way,
and had neither wings nor feet, and the
books of the time showed them that way.
But how could such creatures
fly or perch?
This book explained.
The birds had no need to do either
because they floated in the sky,
feeding on dew,
and only fell to earth when they died.
They were literally birds of paradise.
Even 200 years later, the illustrations
involved a lot of guesswork.
For still no European
had seen the living birds.
This kind, for example,
had not only feathers,
but 12 long, naked quills
sprouting from its flanks.
The artist did give it legs, but he was
completely baffled by the plumes.
By the end of the 19th century, thanks to
the discoveries of Wallace and others
the illustrations are much more accurate.
This is that 12-quilled bird again.
But could it really have its strange quills,
or wires, as they're called,
bent back over its body like this?
It seems hardly likely.
Perhaps the artist had been working
from a specimen
that had been badly packed.
And what about this?
This is the sicklebill bird of paradise.
Could it, in life, have great fans of
plumes projecting above its wings,
like fancy epaulettes with a purple rim?
Even today,
some of these species are little-known.
Many display in the thick forest at dawn,
when there is not enough light to film.
That was what had caused us
such problems 40 years ago.
But now we can resolve that difficulty
with special video cameras.
And one of the species
I most wanted to see
is that bird with the improbable
epaulettes, the black sicklebill.
Its display in the wild
has never been photographed or filmed,
it hasn't even been scientifically
described.
But the local people say that a male
does display on a perch just near here,
but it only does so at first light,
just before dawn.
So the only thing to do,
is to sit down and wait.
He's there!
That dim, black shape on the sapling.
This really is seeing in the dark.
(Calling)
He's calling to attract females,
but also to keep other males away.
This is his territory
and he'll dance by himself.
Those things like arms are not his wings,
they're those epaulettes.
So that's what he does with them!
It's even more unlikely than the drawing.
It's getting brighter.
Soon we should be able to see him
just a little more clearly.
There's that purple line on the epaulette.
But there's still no sign of a female.
Ah, well, obviously time for breakfast.
A pandanus tree. Sicklebills
are particularly fond of its fruit,
and there's lots of it around.
That's what he's after - and there's
a female half-hidden in the leaves.
There's a second female.
A third!
All three are almost certainly his mates,
each building her own nest
and feeding in his territory.
Many birds of paradise species
have females coloured like this -
brown above
and speckled or barred beneath.
And looking at them, it's easy to see
that they're all related,
even though their males
are so very different and various.
The New Guinea forest
has an atmosphere all its own.
From one point of view,
it's rather disappointing -
you don't see many mammals, far fewer
than in Africa or South American forests.
But what this place lacks in mammals,
it makes up for in birds.
Not that it's all that easy to see them.
You know they're around
because you can hear them,
but if you want to watch them,
you have to move fairly quietly.
And there is one of the smallest
of the whole family.
This is the one with those extraordinary
sawtooth plumes -
the King of Saxony's bird.
There's nothing else remotely like these
plumes in the whole of the bird world.
He's calling for a female.
And it's not just his plumes that are
unique - so is his way of dancing.
(Soft hissing)
That hissing noise is his call.
You can tell he's getting
particularly excited
because he's erected the black feathers
on his shoulders into a cape,
another of those transformation tricks
that seem to be a speciality
of this family.
He's so worked up,
he's trying to mate with a tuft of moss!
A female, at last.
Typical female colouring.
And that's never been filmed before.
New Guinea is a huge island.
A thousand miles long from east to west,
lying between Australia and the equator.
It was rucked up from beneath the sea
some 10,000,000 years ago,
as Australia drifted northwards
and pushed against the Asian section
of the earth's crust.
The ancestors of the birds of paradise,
probably starling-like creatures,
slowly spread from Asia,
down chains of smaller islands
until they reached these vast forests.
And here, they evolved into
a multitude of wildly different species,
that, between them, exploit every kind
of feather adornment you can imagine.
But why did this great diversity
of species come into existence?
Well, New Guinea
as well as being an immense island,
is also an extremely varied one.
Up here, I'm at 11,000 feet, and the land
is much poorer in food for birds
than the luxuriant tropical rainforests
of lower altitudes.
And up here,
there lives a bird of paradise
that may give us a clue about
the ancestors of the whole family.
McGregor's bird of paradise.
And there's an obvious way in which
it differs from most of its relations.
This is a pair - male and female
look exactly the same.
The reason they do so
is connected with food.
There's so little of it up here,
that if nestlings are to get enough,
the male has to help the female
to collect it.
So he can't have a lot of wives.
Just one.
And since he can't, therefore
spend his time dancing in trees,
he hasn't developed an extravagant
costume in which to show off.
His courtship is no more than
this quick chase through the bushes.
At lower altitudes
things are very different.
The tropical heat and the heavy rains
produce a really rich environment.
As there are no monkeys to munch
the fruit or squirrels to gather the seeds,
there's plenty of food for birds.
Here the females can raise their young
unaided
and the males can concentrate
on dancing.
And since there are no cats or jackals,
there's little danger in doing so
on the ground.
The superb bird of paradise
does just that.
And this log is his dancing stage.
As well as his spectacular cravat,
he's got a long sheaf of feathers
at the back of his neck.
Extraordinary in itself,
but you wait till he unfurls it!
Here's the female.
Now there'll be some action.
This is the arena
of another displaying bird.
I'm not on the mainland
I've come to the island of Batanta
which is separated
by quite a narrow strait.
But it has its own species
of bird of paradise,
that evolved here
and lives nowhere else.
And one way of trying to get a look at it,
is to put some leaves on this arena,
because this bird is meticulously tidy.
This isn't him. This is a pheasant pigeon.
Maybe a trespasser on his patch will so
infuriate him that he will come down.
(Bird calling)
(Calling continues)
I can hear his calls.
There he is.
(Calling)
Wilson's bird of paradise.
He's got his own fashion gimmick -
the bald look.
There goes the first
of the leaves that I dropped.
He's really quite small -
only the size of a starling.
Now he's starting cutting leaves.
Littering the place up himself.
Presumably he wants to get more light
on the stage,
so that his colours show up.
That looks like a female.
She's got a slightly less brilliant
blue head.
But that's a young male.
He's not yet got coloured feathers on his
body, but his bald head is very blue,
and he's behaving like a male too.
ls he helping the boss
by doing a bit of the housework?
Probably not.
It's more likely he's come here
to practise the skills he's going to need
when he's old enough
to have an arena of his own.
She looks interested.
So does he.
(Calling)
He's clearly not much of a dancer.
But with a costume like that
who would need to be?
What an amazing bird!
I've seen lots of coloured illustrations
of them
I've seen mounted specimens
in museums
but nothing has prepared me
for the splendour of this wonderful thing.
It's as though it's illuminated from
inside, the colours are incandescent.
When Wallace collected
a particularly spectacular specimen,
he wrote in his book, "My heart began to
beat violently, blood rushed to my head,
"and I felt more in danger of fainting
"than when I had been in apprehension
of immediate death.
"I had a headache
for the rest of the day."
Well, I haven't got a headache,
but I think I know how he felt.
Half a dozen of the 40-odd species
dance on the ground like that.
To find another, we left the island of
Batanta and went back to the mainland
to the Arfak mountains
in western New Guinea.
The home of the Arfak parrotia.
This is his display ground.
Here too the forest floor
has been cleared
and the saplings stripped of their leaves.
He's dressed entirely in black, except for
that white disc on his forehead.
Though there is a iridescent patch
on his chest
that he can reveal when he wants to.
And he does have
those six black pennants on his head.
But he dazzles his mates
not so much with his costum' e
as with his choreography.
And that being so, he is particularly keen
on clearing his stage
of anything that might trip up a dancer.
Now he's miming, going through the
motions of clearing away leaves,
even though there aren't any.
The stage is now absolutely immaculate.
And here's another of those juveniles
who come to the arenas
of their elders and betters to practise.
Amazing! But how sad
that none of the girls are here to watch.
The master is back.
An audience is assembling.
He is going to show
how it should be done.
First, the warm-up - ritualised runs
across the stage.
A little more mimed leaf-clearing.
Mounting excitement in the dress circle.
And now, the performance begins.
The absence of ground predators,
that has allowed some birds of paradise
to display on the ground,
has been exploited
by another family of birds,
that used to be thought to be
close cousins of the birds of paradise,
but are now thought to be
somewhat distantly related.
and this is one of their constructions.
This is not a nest, it's a jewel box.
And these are not eggs,
they are blue berries.
The treasures of a male bowerbird.
And here is one of those
treasure-hoarding capitalists,
the flamed bowerbird.
He may not have elaborate plumes,
but his body feathers
could scarcely be more brilliant.
Those on his shoulders
have a gloss like spun glass.
But this is about all he does
to display them.
It's as if his ancestors
once had big plumes,
and although he hasn't inherited them,
he still goes through the motions
of displaying them.
Whether that is so or not
he now puts his faith in his jewels.
And here's another
to add to that collection.
Now he's chewing up leaves into a paste.
Perhaps he's trying to beautify
the bower walls.
The abundance of food in the forest
has had the same effect
on the bowerbird family
as it has on their cousins
the birds of paradise.
It's enabled the males
to become polygamists.
But whereas birds of paradise attract
their wives with plumes on their bodies,
these birds do it with jewels
and their bowers.
And like plumes, the bowers have been
elaborated to an extraordinary degree.
Like this one, for example.
This is a maypole bower.
The builder - a drab little bird.
But then, he relies even less
on his feathers
and much more on his skill
as an architect and builder.
And he's got something
to be really proud of.
He decorates
this impressive construction
with green lichen around the base.
And from the end of the twigs
of the tower, he hangs frass -
caterpillar droppings.
He does have the vestiges
of a yellow crest.
And he's a quite extraordinary songster.
And several of these males will build
their towers
quite close to one another in the forest.
The females tour them
make up their minds,
presumably about which is the finest,
and then mate with the architect
beside his creation.
They then go away and rear their young
entirely by themselves.
The father of this nestling
may never even see it.
He spends nine months of the year close
to his award-winning building,
hoping, no doubt, that yet another
passing female will give him her vote.
And this is the work of the master builder
among bowerbirds.
I'm in the Vogelkop on the far western tip
of New Guinea
and this is the bower
of the Vogelkop bowerbird.
And what an astonishment it is! Surely
one of the wonders of the natural world.
The bower
has been completely roofed over,
thatched with these stems of orchids.
It's been built
around the base of a sapling,
it has a stark pillar right in the middle,
and it's got two smaller pillars
on the side, to support it.
The whole of the treasury
is five or six yards across.
And what treasures it contains!
Or what a variety of treasures it contains!
On the far side, there are the black stems
of tree ferns.
Here is the lawn
neatly planted with moss, and on it,
the shiny wing covers of beetles.
There are orange fruit, there are these
glowing orange dead leaves,
These are the acorns of the tropical oaks
which are common around here.
Behind me, there are black fruits.
All of which has been brought specially
by the bird.
Bowerbirds are so dedicated
to their work
that even if you sit out in the open
beside the bower
they will often continue to work,
provided you sit absolutely still.
This Vogelkop bowerbird
is the plainest of his family,
with no sign whatever of a crest.
But the more spectacular the display
in your bower,
presumably the less need you have to
impress your mate with bright feathers.
And it's difficult to imagine
a more impressive collection
of treasures than this.
But they do have to be properly arranged
to show them off really well.
Flowers, whenever they appear
in the forest
have an obvious appeal to a bird who
has a passion for interior decoration.
From one point of view, these
adornments are better than feathers.
Individual birds of paradise cannot
choose their plumes' shape and colour.
They have to display with what their
genes have given them.
Bowerbirds, however, can choose.
If a male decides that he stands a better
chance of seducing a female with pink,
rather than blue
then he can decorate his bower that way.
So it's the tastes and fancies
of the females, single mothers,
who have no need of the help of the male
in bringing up their families,
that has led
to these extravagant exhibitions.
Whether or not the bowerbirds are
closely related to the birds of paradise,
both families have reacted in remarkably
similar ways to the asset they share -
the huge richness of this forest.
This really is a paradise for birds.
And the variety of bowers it has allowed
one family to build
is more than matched by the variety
of plumes evolved by the other.
One group of female birds of paradise,
for example,
fancied glossy throats,
and this is the result.
The splendid astrapia.
Tails clearly didn't impress them
to anything like the same degree.
But the splendid astrapia has
a close cousin, Shaw Mayer's astrapia,
and those females had different tastes.
They were hot for tails.
There's no wonder that the result of their
selections over many generations
is also called
the ribbon-tailed bird of paradise.
The female has to sit on a nest
and a long tail would get in the way,
but because of her
and her forebears' decisions
about what makes a male attractive
he now has the longest tail in proportion
to his body of any bird in the world.
The smallest member of the family -
the king bird of paradise.
He has yet another kind of tail -
two wire-like quills,
each tipped with a little green disc
like a coin.
Not so obviously impressive
as the ribbon-tail
but wait till you see
what he does with them.
Wingspreads and an extraordinary,
scarcely birdlike, call
are just the beginning of things.
Just attention-grabbing ways
to let any female around know
that he's on his perch,
and about to display his prowess
as an acrobat and a juggler.
What could be more attention-grabbing
than that?
But that's not all. When he's really
excited, he's got a final stunt -
the pendulum.
There it is.
Down in the lowlands
in the swamps beside the rivers,
lives the 12-wired bird of paradise.
He comes to his display post
in the early dawn.
This is the bird I used to think
had been drawn so inaccurately,
but the old illustration was right -
the wires, the quills,
are indeed bent back in a tangle.
The female doesn't have them.
But do bent-back quills
appeal to a female?
They're hardly beautiful.
Courtship seems to be
some kind of game,
a variation of I'm The King Of The Castle,
perhaps.
Only, with a very special prize.
He deliberately brushed her face
with his rear quills!
He's doing it again!
It seems that she prefers to be seduced,
not by visual thrills, but by tactile ones.
And after the quill flick, the beak poke.
It may be an odd technique, but it works.
I've now left New Guinea,.
I'm 200 miles to the west
on the island of Halmahera
one of the Malukus, the Spice Islands.
It was here that Wallace made perhaps
his most spectacular discovery of all -
a completely unknown bird of paradise.
On that today carries his name -
Wallace's standardwing.
It was only observed once more
in the hundred years that followed
his discovery.
And until recently, some people feared
it might have disappeared altogether.
So it is one of the least-known
of all species.
But we do know that the males
like the greater bird,
which Wallace made so famous
display in groups, and at dawn.
They've gathered in one of these trees,
and from the racket
I'd guess there are 30 or 40 of them.
(Many birds calling)
The standards -
those long isolated feathers -
project not from the tail, the flank
or the head
but, would you believe,
the front-edge of the wings.
These are advertising flights -
whizzing vertically into the air to show
passing females what's going on.
There he goes again.
I've been watching this perch
since very first light,
and I must have seen
at least a dozen displays,
but not one of them has ended
with a mating.
I think that's because this
is one of the junior perches,
the subsidiary ones.
The senior perch, where all the action is,
is over there in a much taller tree.
That's where males are winning mates.
A female.
This male is certainly putting on
a great performance.
ls she, in fact, assessing and comparing
the displays?
A copulation.
As ever, a matter of seconds.
Another! Same place.
There seems little, to my eye at least,
to choose between all
the several dozen males.
And I don't see how a female
could make a proper choice.
Maybe it is the perch in these
great assemblies of competing males
that is the important thing.
As it also may be among
the greater bird of paradise.
If that is so, then in these mass displays,
the males are not so much showing off
to the females
as posturing aggressively
to one another.
Using their plumes to demonstrate
their strength and vigour,
as stags do with their antlers.
That would enable them to establish
a ranking between them all,
and the boy at the top of the rank
gets the number one perch.
One of the mysteries about birds
of paradise, as far as I'm concerned,
is why, when they have
such wonderful colours
do they do so much of their displays
in the semi-darkness before dawn?
It's only now that the sun is up
that I can really see the full beauty
of these wonderful plumes.
The displays are over.
It's time to get smartened up again
after all that rough and tumble.
The white standards are looking
a bit bedraggled too,
and at last I can see exactly how
they're attached to the front of the wing.
ls there a more elegant cravat, in both
shape and colour, worn by any bird?
I doubt it.
So, after weeks of work and travel
with cameramen
Richard Kirby and Mike Potts,
we had filmed the displays
of not just one species,
but representatives of all
the major groups of birds of paradise.
And I had achieved
the ambition of a lifetime.
Wallace's emotions
on discovering such marvels
must surely be echoed
by all of us who follow him.
This is what he wrote -
"I thought of the long ages of the past,
during which the successive generations
"of these things of beauties
have run their course
"year by year being born and living and
dying amid these dark, gloomy woods,
"with no intelligent eye to gaze
upon their loveliness,
"to all appearances,
such a wanton waste of beauty.
"lt seems sad that, on the one hand
"such exquisite creatures should live out
their lives and exhibit their charms
"only in these wild,
inhospitable regions.
"This consideration must surely tell us
"that all living things
were not made for man.
"Many of them have no relation to him
"Their happiness and enjoyments,
their loves and hates
"their struggles for existence,
"their vigorous life and early death
would seem to be immediately related
"to their own wellbeing
and perpetuation alone."
Indeed so.