They say ignorance is bliss.
For the first time
in my life, I agree.
I wish...
...I had never uncovered
the awful truth.
I know now...
...once they find out,
they will try to silence me.
That is why I've written this
all down for you in this letter.
You are the only one
whom I can tell this to.
The only one who could
possibly understand.
Good luck, my friend.
I hope you enjoyed your stay.
Mr. Fuller,
nice having you here.
Your usual table?
No, thanks, Gene.
Her name is Erika.
She's from Toledo.
Ashton, would you do me a favour?
You'd like to meet her?
I want you...
...to keep this letter.
Somebody will ask for it.
A man named Douglas Hall.
Remember, it's crucial
that he receives it.
It's a walk in the park.
Going home, Mr. Fuller?
Yes, Charlie.
We're out of cat food, honey.
Yes, I'll buy some in the morning.
You've been smoking again.
Download complete.
Link to simulation terminated.
Martini, please.
One martini.
You forgot the olive.
We're out of olives.
How about pretzels?
No, thank you.
Please leave a message at the tone.
Douglas, it's me.
Listen, I've stumbled
onto something incredible.
This changes everything.
I don't know...
I don't even know how to begin.
What are you doing?
You have new messages.
You have three new messages.
First new message.: 5.:25 a. m.
Douglas, it's Hilary.
Don't forget to call Marshall.
Legal is screaming
for the contract.
I'll have a notary come
to the office at lunch.
Next new message.: 5.:48 a. m.
It's me again.
Please call me as soon as you get up.
Next new message.: 6.:13 a. m.
Mr. Douglas Hall,
this is Detective McBain, LAPD.
I'd appreciate a callback, please.
My phone number is 555-7876.
I'm Detective Zev Bernstein.
Sorry to drag you
out of bed so early.
This is Detective McBain.
Mr. Hall?
Thanks for coming down.
Where is he?
- Can I get you some coffee?
- No, thank you.
That him?
We found him in an alley
at Spring and Grand.
Looks like he ran into some guy
who wasn't just asking for a quarter.
Carved him up like a ham.
Took everything:
wallet, credit cards.
Got a kick out of it.
What's your connection
to the old man?
I worked with him for six years.
He was my boss.
My friend.
Hey, cigarette?
I don't smoke.
We found these on him.
Traced the prescription.
According to his doctor...
...Fuller listed you to call
in case of medical emergencies.
He had no next of kin?
No, he didn't.
You sure?
I think he would've told me.
Have any idea who killed him?
Everybody liked him.
Mind if I tag along?
Or we can continue in my office,
if that's more convenient.
That's fine.
What do you do
for a paycheck, anyway?
Computer software.
Would you mind taking care
of the car this morning?
- Must make some decent bucks, huh?
- I make a living.
- This was his apartment.
- You could be home already.
I see these signs
every time I leave work:
"You could be home already.
Apartment living in downtown. "
Never expected it could look
anything like this.
This company was Fuller's life.
He worked and lived here.
So what exactly
do you people do here?
You wouldn't be interested.
I'm paid to be interested.
Computer research.
Fuller was onto...
...a whole new frontier.
Very sensitive material.
Not at liberty to discuss it.
A lot of money involved.
This apartment must be worth
a few million dollars.
One of the perks of the job.
This job has a whole lot of perks.
Can I help you?
I just talked to him two days ago.
I can't believe he's gone.
My name is Jane Fuller.
Hannon was my father.
I'm sorry.
I'm Douglas Hall.
You're the one
he always wanted me to meet.
He never mentioned
that he had a daughter.
He didn't?
I arrived from Paris this morning.
I was supposed to meet him.
But then I heard.
My condolences, Miss Fuller.
I'm Detective McBain, LAPD.
I have to ask you some questions.
- Of course.
- Would you excuse us, Mr. Hall?
Sure.
Have we ever met before?
No, that's not possible.
You look very familiar.
Nice to meet you, Miss Fuller.
Hey, Whitney.
How you doing?
Sliced him up like an animal.
And for what?
He was the Einstein of our generation.
It's a waste.
What the hell happened
while I was away?
He was jacking
into the system a lot.
I thought you knew.
You didn't know?
We're months away
from the first trial run.
We are. You know, he was
taking a big chance.
What was I supposed to do?
You know how he is.
Were there complications?
None that I know of yet.
Did he ever tell you
he had a daughter?
- Why?
- Because I just met her.
You're kidding me.
John, I need the number
of that cab company.
No need, sir.
She went to the Omni Hotel.
Detective McBain.
Sorry to disappoint you.
I'll find Doug.
It's you I wanted to talk with.
What for?
Want me to catch your boss's killer?
Of course.
The whole thing's
a giant computer game?
No, it doesn't need a user
to interact with it to function.
Its units are fully formed,
self-learning cyber beings.
- Units?
- Electronic, simulated characters.
They populate the system.
They think...
...they work...
...they eat.
They fuck?
Let's just say that
they're modeled after us.
Right now, we have a working prototype:
Los Angeles, circa 1937.
Why '37?
Fuller wanted to start by re-creating
the era of his youth.
You see...
...while my mind is jacked in...
...I'm walking around
experiencing 1937.
My body stays here...
...and holds the consciousness
of the program link unit.
You think one of them units
crawled up an extension cord...
...and killed its maker?
Miss Fuller checked in yet?
Miss Fuller.
Glad I caught you.
Mr. Hall.
What are you doing here?
It's about your father, actually.
You said you spoke with him
a few days ago.
Can you tell me anything
about that conversation?
Did he seem strange to you at all?
He'd been under
a lot of stress lately.
He asked me to fly to the States,
so I could help with the company.
Help him run it?
Shut it down.
I worked with him for six years.
If he wanted to shut it down...
...he would've told me about it.
He didn't tell you about me.
But I wish he had.
It's nice to see you again.
Sorry I'm late.
Have you looked through the paperwork?
Yes, I have. And I think
we have a very strong case.
The company should be
yours in no time.
- Strong case?
- What I'm saying is, your father...
...changed his will
in favour of the employees.
In fact, you aren't mentioned
in the original will either.
But as I said, I think
we have a very strong case.
Who will head the board now?
Douglas Hall.
Not bad.
Owner of a $2 billion enterprise.
Strange, Fuller would amend
his will just before he died.
I was on an airplane
when it happened.
According to the security guard,
Fuller left the office at 10:30 p. m.
30 minutes after your plane arrived.
Autopsy shows that
he died around midnight.
- You had time to catch up with him.
- But I didn't.
- I went straight home.
- Didn't talk to him?
No e-mails, no faxes,
not even a message?
None of the above.
You know, that's funny.
We checked Fuller's phone records.
He made a call with
his calling card at 11:02 p. m.
Shit!
Your home number.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't
leave town for a couple of days.
And get that game fixed.
It's missing a spring.
You have no new...
Restore. Restore.
To restore messages,
press "rewind" now.
- Yesterday at 2.:45 p. m.
- I managed to reschedule...
- Yesterday at 5.:14 p. m.
- Hello, Mr. Hall...
- Yesterday at 11.:02 p. m.
- Douglas, it's me.
Listen, I've stumbled
onto something incredible.
This changes everything.
I'm here in some bar on Main and 7th.
In case something happens to me,
I left you a message in the system.
I gave it to...
How did you find me?
What's going on?
I'm trying to get
into Fuller's files.
For what?
He left a message for me
the night he died.
- He knew someone wanted to kill him.
- Did you tell the police?
Why not?
He also said he left a message
for me in the system.
Douglas, please.
This is my stuff, okay?
These are the units that Fuller
interacted with when he was there.
Maybe he wanted me to go in.
If you're thinking what
I think you're thinking...
...don't even think about it.
I need your help.
No, no, no. I won't help you.
- It's a serious risk.
- I have to get in.
You could die.
The cops think I killed him.
They may be right.
- What do you mean?
- Everything points to me.
To be perfectly honest,
I don't know what the truth is anymore.
Either I did murder Fuller and
I can't remember, or I'm being framed.
The one clue I have is in that machine.
I need your help
if I'm going to find it.
I'll set it for an hour.
Set it for 120 minutes.
Sixty is better.
120 minutes, Whit.
60 is safer.
I'm setting it at 60.
1-2-0.
120 minutes. Engage timer.
Preparing user for download.
Ready for download.
Mr. Grierson,
117 West Winston, Pasadena...
Transference beginning.
Download complete.
...five cents!
You owe me 12 dollars
and five cents.
Listen, young man!
I do not have all day!
Ferguson, anything wrong?
John, are you okay?
I'm terribly sorry, ma'am.
Someone will be right with you.
Oh, my God.
- Cigarette?
- No, thanks. Don't smoke.
Since when?
Listen, John...
...why don't you...
Why don't you break for lunch?
Get some fresh air.
You look terrible.
I think I look pretty good.
Extra! Extra!
Zeppelin blast kills 35!
You want one, mister?
It's five cents.
Hey, watch out, buddy!
- How much to Pasadena?
-90 cents.
- If I forget to turn the metre on.
- I understand.
This is it, 117 Winston.
- Do you mind waiting?
- It'll be a pleasure, sir.
- Tell me if you need any help.
- Thank you.
You own this place?
I mean, it's not much...
...but it's mine.
You looking for anything
in particular?
Interested in a scientist.
Wrote a couple of books...
...about semiconductors...
...and the limitations
of the 64-bit microchip.
Microchip.
Semiconductors.
What year?
Early '70s?
His name was Hannon Fuller.
Hannon Fuller.
1870.
No, I can't say I've ever heard of...
...Hannon Fuller, 1870, microchips.
But I'm not much of a
technical person, you know.
You been here before?
You look kind of familiar.
Name's Douglas Hall.
It doesn't ring a bell.
Guess you just have
one of those faces...
...familiar faces.
Oh, it's late.
I'd like to close up now.
Of course.
- Pleasure.
- Pleasure to meet you, Mr. Hall.
1257 Palo Alto Road,
La Cienega Heights.
I guess that's it.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for Bridget Manilla.
What do you want her for?
- I want to ask her some questions.
- She got a job now. I'm her mother.
Can you tell me
where I can find her?
You a copper?
Now, listen.
She ain't doing
nothing wrong no more.
If you don't cause her no trouble...
...you'll find her
at Wilshire Grand Hotel.
Welcome to the Wilshire Grand Hotel.
I'm looking for Bridget Manilla.
She's over there,
second from the end.
Bridget?
I got your name from
a good friend of mine.
Come back later.
I'm really busy right now.
His name's Fuller.
The manager's very tough on us.
You'll have to wait till I'm off duty.
I really don't think
I can wait that long.
Go talk to Ashton over at the bar.
Bridget, do we have
your attention now?
Thank you. Let's go.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for Ashton.
Right there.
Ashton, some guy wants you.
You're a lucky man.
I just opened.
Oh, my. Something wrong?
Bridget just sent me over here.
What can I do you for?
You know a gentleman
named Hannon Fuller?
Gin martini up, one olive and
likes them frigid as an Eskimo.
- Talk to him recently?
- Why?
I'm his friend.
He didn't come home last night...
...and his wife is concerned.
My name is Douglas Hall.
Concerned wives?
I can't help you with that.
How about something fancy?
So did...
Does Fuller come here frequently?
You could say that.
What does he do?
What everybody does:
drinks, dances, has a good time.
Especially has a good time.
He really goes for the girls.
Girls?
Thought you said you knew him.
Yeah, I thought I did.
Are you in a hurry or something?
Did you happen to talk to Fuller
the night before last?
Yes, I did.
Did he mention my name?
Did he give you something for me?
What would that be?
- A message or a note, maybe.
- No, sorry.
Did you see him talking
to anybody else?
I'm a very busy man.
Listen...
...if you like, I can arrange
something for you too.
You see anything you want?
Can you tell me where
the bathroom is, please?
Timer engaged and counting.
Douglas Hall! Hey, man!
You all right?
You sure?
All right, take it easy.
Hey, man. Take it easy.
I told you, 120 minutes.
It's too long.
You're really pushing your luck.
I need something to drink.
Some water.
Mr. Hall, you forgot
your coat and hat.
Name's Ferguson.
Johnny Ferguson.
Anything wrong?
Didn't finish your drink.
- What happened?
The memory transference
with your link...
...it froze.
Started overlapping!
Thought I'd be shooting hoops
with Ferguson forever.
You got a smoke?
Sure.
Thank you.
Mind if I ask you a question?
Can you tell me where I am?
It works?
Oh, it works!
It works.
How about Ashton?
- My bartender?
- He's got a better haircut than you.
Much better.
I wish I could see it for myself.
How's the lighting? Textures?
Colourization needs work,
but the units don't notice.
What are they like?
They're as real as you and me.
You see, the old man was right!
All those years of work!
Did you find out
what he was doing there?
He was having sex with girls.
You're kidding me.
Excuse me, Mr. Hall?
A man in the lobby says
he needs to talk to you.
Thanks. Have him call
my office in the morning.
He says it's urgent.
That he's a friend of Fuller's.
So, you're a friend of Fuller's.
You're Hall, right?
How can I help you, Mr...
Tom Jones.
You know, like the singer.
How about some privacy?
What do you want to talk about?
About the night the old man died.
I'll be right back, Joe.
So where'd you meet Fuller?
In my bar the other night...
...waiting for you.
Is that what you wanted
to talk to me about?
No, I want to talk about money now.
- Something in the seven figures.
- What money?
Come on.
You think you can
get away with it?
Get away with what?
You took the old man, asshole!
Listen to me.
He was at the bar.
You pick him up, leave together.
Next day he's an obit.
You do the math, asshole!
Oh, Jesus!
Crazy son of a bitch!
You're nuts.
I'll see you on
America's Most Wanted.
Omni Hotel.
How can I help you?
Miss Jane Fuller, please.
Hello? Who is this?
On the night
your father was killed...
...he tried to reach me.
He wanted to meet at some bar.
What for?
He felt someone was after him.
Did you talk to him?
I know how strange this sounds.
I can't remember.
What do you mean?
Did you talk to
the detective about this?
No, but the bartender will...
...if I don't pay up.
Christ!
I know how crazy this sounds.
You can't just plug your brain
into this machine...
...and not expect
to be affected by it.
Please walk away from this
before you get hurt too.
Why do I get the feeling
we've met before?
Maybe we have, in another life.
What about Paris?
What's that other life like?
- I don't want to talk about it.
- Why not?
I guess I don't want you
to lose interest in me.
Don't worry about that.
Let's dance.
- Me? No, no.
- Yes, come on.
I buy all my shoes in left pairs.
It's easy.
I'll show you the steps.
You're doing pretty good
for a man with no right foot.
Must've picked it up in another life.
You know that feeling you have
that we met before?
It's the same with me.
Why is that?
They say that déjà vu
is usually a sign of...
...love at first sight.
Go, go. Ready!
Don't make any sudden moves.
What's this all about?
What it's usually all about.
Murder.
Is that your car?
- Those are my plates.
- No shit.
That's from a security camera
in your office garage...
- ... the night Fuller was killed.
- I don't understand.
That makes one of us.
Fuller wanted to shut down the project,
and you sliced him up.
It's time I call my attorney.
You say you left at 10.
I was working late with Whitney.
Anybody with you?
You're picking up bad habits
left and right.
Must be the stress.
Then you'll need a carton.
Name's Tom Jones. Said he saw
your picture in the paper.
Said you looked like the guy
Fuller left the bar with that night.
We took his statement.
Said we'd be in touch.
Somebody reached out
and touched him first.
Looks like you found an alibi.
You're free to go...
...for now.
What did you tell him?
The truth.
We met for a drink,
one thing led to another...
...we spent the night together.
Your picture was on the news.
He saw you and thought
you were good for quick cash.
You should've seen the pictures.
The guy was slaughtered.
He was an ex-con.
Who knows what else he did!
Just because I don't remember it
doesn't mean I didn't do it.
You're not a killer.
Your father stumbled onto something.
He left me a message
having something to do with this.
So what are you going to do?
Jack back in and find out.
Downloading.
Time.: Two hours.
Engage timer.
Timer not engaged. Warning!
Timer not engaged.
Warning.
We're up next!
- Ready? Come on.
- What?!
What's wrong?
Come on, John!
What are you doing?
We're gonna be disqualified!
- Here you go.
- Thanks a lot, chief.
Come on!
Grierson!
I'll call the police!
- I need to talk to you!
- I told you!
I'll call the police!
Listen. Listen!
I know why you pass out
from time to time.
I know why you wake up
and have no idea where you are.
What'd you do three nights ago?
Any idea?
When did it first happen?
First time?
About four weeks ago.
And the last episode
was three nights ago?
It lasts for about two hours?
My wife thinks
I have a secret love life.
What about...
...memory flashes, déjà vu?
I was in World War I.
I'm still having these nightmares.
I'm talking about fantasies.
I do have them.
In these fantasies,
you're having sex with young girls.
When I wake up...
...I even have a perfume smell...
- ... all over me.
- Real or imagined?
According to my wife...
...it's pretty real.
I found this...
...a couple of days ago.
Your size?
I am married over 35 years now.
And not once have I cheated on my wife.
Not once.
Let's have a drink.