Central Sahara, North Africa
Base to Mobile 4
Jack, are you there?
- Still in traffic, Kat.
- What's your location?
ETA in...
about under an hour.
Is there any luck?.
You heard any news from them?
No one for the past 72 hours
- There's no time, move faster.
- Don't worry, Kat.
- sure does not become any problem.
- You be careful.
You call for help when something goes wrong.
- And you fallback safe.
- We will, God bless you, Kathy.
Hello?
GNE security here..
Anybody home?
Hello?
GNE security.
Open the door.
It's a help.
They drew markings right into the jackal...
writing blood on the walls.
You're fucking kidding me
What does it say?
I don't know it's in Arabic.
but it's nothing to get into talk about.
25 people vanished,
leaving blood and bullet holes...
- So when do we have hump?
- Kat, I'll be fine.
there are some other buildings I could check out but not in this
and it's gonna be dark soon.
Who's on graveyard?
Alex.
- Tell him I'm checking again at 2100.
- You bet.
and inform Caswell.
Over and out.
,,Emal Duwayce?
Professor Borman, would you mind sharing with us,
what is attracting you and your team...
... to research one of the remotest location in the Sahara?
It's not the Sahara that say, is attracting me.
-... but what lies far beneath it.
- What is it that you're hoping to find?
Genaueres should reveal more
at the press conference later this afternoon...
... that seismographic data has revealed
a fast geological anomaly...
... deep within the Earth's crust.
Welcome...
I expect you're wondering why I've summoned you this day.
Come in, yes you
don't be shy..
There are plenty of seats here at front.
I'll start again..
I've summoned you here today
to announce our groundbreaking objective.
To drill deeper than ever before human history.
to unlock the mysteries
hidden deep below the Earth's surface.
Jebel Afra is one of the remotest areas in Sahara...
and also the location of a former natural gas exploration site.
Seismographic data recently detected a massive
underground cavity opened 9 miles down.
Now that new techniques make it viable to dig deeper,
a much bigger crew...
...are put together in a team of international researchers...
and local workers to lease the site and resume drilling.
Some team members are looking to find
... new independent vehicled life forms.
perhaps extremophiles
such as hepothermials.
9 Miles Down!
...but you can trust all colleagues
in the Institute
I don't think it's the Isolation Room
they were all experienced to fieldwork,
as they used to have. No, no.
This is different...
There are bizarre expeculations and
soul searching about the ethics of what we're doing.
there were only local drilling,
that, I could understand.
There were supertitious Berbes,
who talked of having disturbed some spiritual realm.
But it's affected us all, I mean...
Dr. lvanov and I are engaged in long and
heated discussions...
... about the meaning of good and evil.
It's bizarre.
Oh, God.
Hello...?
- Anybody here...?
- Mobile 4.
Mobile 4...
- Morning, Kat.
- Any development?
- I'm just checking something out...
- Checking what?
Jack?
- Seems I may have some company.
- Jack, what is it?
I'll get back to you.
You gotta be kidding me.
Morning.
- It's about fucking time!
- What?
- Let me get change then we can go.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, who are you?
- What's been going on here?
- It's a long story.
The sooner we get out of here,
the better.
- Are you alone?
- Not anymore.
Hello lady?
Look ahh...
I don't know how long you're gonna pee,
but I need some answers.
And who are you?
Where is everyone?
One question at a time.
I'm Dr. Jenny Christianson. ,,J.C.
I'm a research colleague of
Professor Borman.
- What do I call you?
- Jack... It's Thomas Jackman.
- Poeple call me Jack.
- Please to meet you, Jack.
Yeah, likewise.
So they've sent you here,
to rescue me? That's wonderful.
Late, but wonderful.
I'm looking forward spending tonight
in the best hotel in a really big town...
... with lots of people and noise.
I'll throw you in all the details
on the way. It's a long trip.
Why don't you start now?
What do you know so far?
Oh, no one has heard anything
from you since Sunday.
- What do you know of our work here?
- Just let me ask a question.
- Who are you exactly?
- I already told you my name...
Thomas Jackman.
Yes, I know.
but by whose authority,
are you here questioning me?
- GNE Security.
- Yeah, this is a private project.
The company you leased asked
for us to check up on you.
So...
Well, the first thing you wanna know:
is that our project leader Professor Borman, is dead.
Dead?
He was shot.
By Doctor Ivanov, our chief geologist.
in a bit of rage.
How close was Ivanov to Borman,
when he shot him?
5 maybe 10 meters...
I wasn't there.
Does it matter?
Dr. Varga.
a Hungarian researcher.
- Apparently a heart attack.
- Would you forget about this one?
Look, Jack, I don't wanna be a hiccup
in your investigation...
... but if you don't mind we really need to leave,
as in now.
Yes, well that might be the case,
but...
... I'm gonna have to call in
for some instructions first.
We're gonna need a place.
Something weird is going on here.
Hold it there...
Linda, get me Caswell. The situation's escalated.
so what now, Jack? Protocol is
that you abandon the crime scene.
I know that. Tell it to the doctor
she's off to pack her things.
She seems pretty
clean to leave.
- She?
- Didn't I mention...
- Dr. Christianson's a woman
- No, you didn't Jack.
- What is she like?
- She's pushy or should I say, suspicious.
- Much like yourself.
- Well, you left out stunningly attractive.
Just get the authorities
out here will you.
Jack, Caswell here.
You and your doctor have to sit tight.
All available resources are being allocated,
to search in for the missing crew.
I want you there in case,
some of them starts to wander back in.
Yes sir, this is a suspected homicide,
the need to bring up further investigation.
All the more reason to stay put.
Police will send a chopper
the moment one's available.
You're safe where you are today.
You copy?
Yes, sir.
Hey, are you sure it was murder?
Looks like she was hiding to me.
We'll know if it matches with the evidence.
I'll take a second look
and get back to you. Over and out.
I'm all packed.
- You ready?
- Sorry, what?
To rotate out of here...
as in leave.
You said,
Varga died of a heart attack?
That was the opinion of our
IMO, Dr. Williams.
All I know is they found him
lying dead on the floor of his quarters.
Can we go now?
You want to be back
on an empty stomach.
- Jack, do be honest, I think...
- Great, coz I'm starving.
I took a wild guess.
- Black, no sugar?
- I drink tea, actually.
- You're not married.
- My wife past away six years ago.
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to pry.
What about you?
You have anybody back home?
You mean
like a husband?
I mean like somebody,
who might be worried about you.
- Are you interrogating me?
- Just curious.
- What, you a cop?
- Used to be.
What's out there?
But I'd stay away from there
if I were you.
So why the change of scene?
Doesn't it ever get to you?
I love the space.
Well, scale and isolation can bring out
the strangest things in people.
- Excuse me?
- Doesn't it ever get to a city boy like you?
Tell me about the project.
Well about six days ago, just under 47,000 feet,
the driller broke to the top of the cavity.
- It was great.
- And?
The truth is we know very little about what
lies before the outer crust.
even on average, it's only
15 miles thick.
If the world were an apple,
that would be thinner than a skin.
Nobody's ever seen below it.
Let alone taking samples of it.
Takes at least five minutes
to reach the bottom.
You won't hear anything
of that depth.
and when the wind blew...
... the driller sends a noise,
that was like the howling of demons...
- What? The SouthWest Wind?
- Yeah. Hidden superstitions.
Like all the garbage, they scroll
in the dorm walls.
- Do you know what it says?
- I don't have to.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm just a little dizzy.
- Why did they write it?
- I don't know.
Seem more like a ritual
than a celebration.
Why weren't you in the video?
Who do you think
took the video?
And you went to have their photos.
Oh God, Jack.
Are you okay?
One moment,
let me help you.
Put your arm around me.
There've been a lot of
strange accidents lately.
Here, lie down.
I'm gonna go get you some ice.
The sooner we can get out of here
the better.
Jack?
God, you looked like you've seen a ghost.
Come on, come lie back down.
It's okay.
Jack...
Do believe in the supernatural?
No. Why?
- Did you see something?
- No. No.
It's just,
there's so many things we can't explain...
... and I just thought I'll
get a scientific opinion.
The way believing the supernatural
doesn't explain anything.
We can't have any irrational thought,
just because we don't understand something.
- There is always a logical explanation.
- Says who...?
Some people fear the unknown.
And that is dangerous.
But some fear make sense.
As life of fear and pain...
- is a security mechanism.
- Sure, when we still live in caves.
Our instinct to fears
have become a liability.
They lead us to kill each other.
Khamsinia Base, Mobile 4.
Base, Mobile 4.
Pick up for me, Jack.
Mobile 4.
They found a guy stranded in the desert,
Dr. Ivanov from the drilling team.
Ivanov?
- Alive?
- Barely.
But he has some kind of gas sample with him.
We've sent it to the lab for testing.
When are the cops getting here?
Their priority's the missing crew
so they've asked them to keep you posted there.
- Did Ivanov say anything?
- Not much.
He's in bad shape, ranting in Russian.
- We got Alex to translate.
- Yeah, he was mumbling about...
... something evil being there.
I have no idea what he meant though.
That's weird. JC seems pretty
rattled by something too.
That's the other thing:
According to JaMc, the company leasing
the site, it was an all-Male team.
- There were no women on the project.
- What? Say it again.
They got no record of a Jenny
Christianson, doctor or otherwise.
Are you there?
Jack?
Yeah, yeah, I'm here, Kat.
Send us a photo of her,
we'll check her ID.
and the picture of that grafitti,
and I'll get Yousef to translate them.
I'll get you those photos.
Out.
JC?
JC!
Jack!
Where were you?
- Where were you?
- Please don't do that.
I couldn't stand being left out here,
alone again.
- I gotta get out of here.
- But we can't.
I'll be over this thing,
in case any crew returns.
- They'll never return.
- How'd you know that?
I'm sorry, I'm...
- How long before help arrives?
- I have no idea.
We're waiting for the police investigation.
- Why don't we just drive out on your truck?
- I already told you.
When did you join the project, JC?
Were you there from the start or you just signed up later?
From the start,
I told you.
My records said,
there were no women on the team.
There was no
Dr. Jenny Christianson.
You think, I'm lying?
Come with me.
This is dated July 12th to
July 19th.
The first shot the week
of our arrival.
When Borman leasing arrangements,
there were some concerns..
that a single woman
among men..
Union rules about separate showers
and toilet facilities and so on...
Our research budget was already stretched
and I would have lost my place on the team...
... had I not agreed to share with the men...
... so Borman falsified my name and gender.
There.
Do you still have doubts?
Just your not in the records.
Brooks.
I'm registered as Dr. Alan Brooks.
They found Ivanov.
Alive.
That's uhmm..wonderful.
Okay, JC.
What's the full story?
You know if I tell you, you'll be like us.
You won't be able to not know.
Try me.
Well, after we penetrated the cavity...
... we were very keen to find out
what was down there.
We stationed a number of remote sensors.
One of them transmits live audio data. Sound.
This is what we're picking up.
- It's almost like wind? Right?
- Yeah. And you agree with me.
- Thank God
- Wait. Wait.
All that sound...
Who are them?...
Like people in pain.
No one believed it at first.
That's just bizarre.
- I mean, it's like it's..
- That's how we all felt.
And for a time, none of us
wanted to talk about it.
This, the drilling crew they begin
mouldering we've released something.
They started seeing things
wandering around the corridors at night.
What things?
Spirits, Poltergeist, Genies...
And, who knows?
Obviously, some kind of mass hysteria.
But they believed what they were seeing.
What about the scientists?
Dr. Varga said, he woke to see
his dead mother sitting at the foot of his bed.
Carrying the corpse of a
still born twin.
I'm certain it contributed
to his heart attack.
I don't know about you...
but I think I need a drink.
Why didn't you tell me
this earlier?
I didn't wanna encourage the
same symptoms in you.
Visions.
Like at the shaft head?
And at the infirmary?
That's how it starts, Jack.
Sake.
Yeah...cheers.
and you attribute all
of these to...
- Like it's some...
- Why not just say the word, Jack?
What? Hell?
Is that what I'm supposed to think?
That hell is a physical place,
that lies just mile beneath us?
and that Borman well,
they drilled into it.
People once thought it geographically
real as Cairo and Jerusalem.
Those inclined to accept the literal
hell still do.
but hell is no more than a spiritual
creation used to instill fear in others.
It's all in our minds.
Hey Yousef...
Would you look at these?
Jack just sent them from Jemalafram.
Crazy.
These are characters from old fairy tales.
- Do they mean anything?
- They write to vanish evil spirits.
- Genia Duwayce...
- What?
A devil woman,
she seduce men.
It's a morality fairy tale.
So that's where you've been hiding.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah.
I should've brought my camera.
Love the way the light
turns in the Sahara.
while the air smells of sunset.
- I don't smell anything special.
- You don't know what you're missing.
You know
when I was a young boy...
... my mother told me that the sun,
was driven around the world
in a chariot roomed
by four horses.
And the wizards sprinkled the
stars on the roof of the skies.
My mom told me, the sun is one
of a hundred billion in the galaxy.
Which is one of a hundred billion
in the universe.
and that some starlight has traveled
since before dinosaurs roam here.
And made its journey...
Right here...
Right now.
That's not a mystery,
that's a fact.
Oh, don't you think that's
fancy, little clinical...
... unemotional?
I mean...
The math takes away the poetry...
sensiblehood.
Not from me. Science only adds
to the wonder of a sunset
... and everything else in the world.
I don't see how it can take away.
What about love?...
Jealousy?
- Phenethylamin.
- Phene... what?
A chemical the brain produces
when you fall in love.
And there's Dopamin
and Norephinephrine...
So the greatest of all human emotions
can be broken down to...
... chemical compound?
The greatest music on Earth can be reduced
to notes on paper...
... but I can still be moved by it.
- Smile.
- Hey! What are you doing?
Delete it.
I wasn't ready.
Oh, if you delete it,
I'm afraid, I'm gonna have to shoot you.
What?
Take two!
Well, it shall live this time.
Make me a copy.
There's a printer in the lab.
What are we drinking with dinner?
You wouldn't have a
Chateau Expensi around here, would you?
Why don't you try Borman's office
while I freshen up.
He kept a few nice bottles in
in his bookshelf.
Sue?
What?
Don't you like it?
It's for embassy cocktail receptions.
I don't get to wear it much.
Yes, it's beautiful.
- Are you alright?
- I...
You left the light on.
- Silly me. You hungry?
- Starving.
- I can do more than study rocks.
- Evidently!
Philosophy, Geology, Psychology...?
on top of it, you are beautiful.
Close your eyes.
I have something for you.
- What are you doing?
- Keep em close...
I know it's a little early...
but Happy Birthday!
It's on your ID.
Jack?
I used to think hell was in your head
and heaven in your heart.
Just looks like it's the other way around.
You wanna tell me about it?
About her.
You don't miss much, do you?
We we're married, six years.
With twins.
Ben and Anna.
She was unhappy,
I just didn't know how...
-... unhappy until she left.
- I thought you said she passed away?
She committed suicide.
Oh, God...
It was my fault.
I'm so wrapped up on my craft.
- I failed her.
- That's no reason for her to...
She thought that
I was having an affair.
Oh God... Jack...
It was my 35th birthday.
Sue and the kids arranged a
surprise birthday party.
I haven't been in the house
for two minutes...
... when the bloody pager went off
and I was back out the door again.
Daddy...
Some part of me...
... that some lived on you...
I swear I had this feeling...
... I was sicker than my life.
And for the last time..
but I just kept walking towards that door.
I could've saved my family but
I didn't listen to my gut instinct.
And I remained Jack the Cop!
Logical, rational!
You're being too hard
on yourself, Jack.
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to sound insensitive...
... but I've seen what can happen
when people abandoned reason.
You could get seriously hurt.
You're a good man.
There's no point in having
to take armor on the outside...
... if your own worst enemy's within.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- What for?
I like you.., and I haven't
felt that in a long time.
Oh, Tom...
Don't call me that.
Okay?
Stop it, stop it.
What is it?
I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
Susan?
JC?
Relax.
Put her out of your mind.
Take it off.
Hello Tom.
No!
Susan!
Did you enjoy fucking her?
JC?
It's okay, Jack.
It's just me, Jack...
You're dreaming, Jack.
Wake up.
You're sleepwalking.
- What?
- Whatever you saw, Jack.
It wasn't real.
It's okay.
Try and get some sleep.
Daddy...
Ben?
I Love You
You.
Mobile 4 to Khamsinia Base.
Come in.
Khamsinia Base to Mobile 4.
Base, come in, do you read?
Khamsinia Base.
Is that you, Jack?
Look Alex, I need some armed support
up here right now.
- It's 5 o'clock in the morning!
- I don't care. You don't argue with me.
You just bloody do it.
Call in the army, after.
I want armed support here now
you understand?
- Do you copy me?
- Okay, okay, I got it.
Good. Out.
Daddy, I'm up here!
Daddy!
- May I join you... God, Jack!
- No!
It was you!
You killed them!
Jack! Please stop.
No...
JC?
What have I done?
Jack!
What did the crew stuffed here,
before you finished them up, JC?
That's why you didn't want me to go
to the crust pit, isn't it?
- Those are animal carcasses, Jack.
- Were we close?
- I don't know who will find this tape...
- I'm thinking that we could both go together.
-... and make it that easy for you...
... greatest of danger
I cannot describe what we're
on against.
But I'm afraid, none will
go out here alive.
Seems we have released something
from nine miles down.
Something of unspeakable evil and cunning.
- Jack!
Taking all form.
Something disarming and unemotional.
Don't let his trance mislead you, Jack.
Behind these lies and deception.
It will trick you.
But don't be distracted by the spectacles...
Even pain leading us to..
It protest all abilities of techie trap.
I came here about you.
All cunning, the lies that
wash the consequences..
It will try to win your trust,
and before dashing your hopes..
- You're lying.
- It will trick you.
- You're lying!
- It will confuse you more.
- Show no fear.
- Base to Mobile 4.
And build on it the time is against you!
whatever it is,
it's going to drive the lives...
- Stay away from the radio!
- Jack! What are you doing?
Resist.
Resist the devil.
I know who you are now!
- Dr. Christianson?
- He's shooting at me!
- Dr. Ivanov has gone mad.
He's got some sample of this pure evil.
He proposes to carry out experiments...
- Remain calm, we'll get you out of there...
- I'm trying!
but he thinks I'm some kind of devil or something.
Kat, don't you listen to her!
Jack, we have to leave!
We got to get out of here now!
Don't listen to its lies. Never do what
it tells you for you will obeying the devil itself.
We have news!
The gas from Ivanov's sample, it's toxic!
- Resist.
- Lies!
Jack, we have to leave.
It's dangerous!
Dr. Christianson?
and may God be with us all.
Did you think you can get rid of me?
You know it's not good without the evil, Jack.
No darkness, without light.
They define each other.
See?
You wanna shoot me?
It'll make no difference...
No difference at all, Jack.
Ja...
No, Jack, don't!
No!
Daddy...
Daddy...!
Ben?
Anna!
Come and help Mommy with
the decorations!
We don't wanna spoil
the surprise now, do we?...
Daddy would be home soon.
Dad's gonna love this!
Is that you, Jack?
How do you want your steak?
Do you like it?
- Who are you?
- I'll come clean.
You've been right all along.
I was only testing you and you passed..
- You and Borman are quite the believers.
- Works for many.
It works for me right now.
I thank God for that.
Literally.
His very existence defines mine.
We have a lot in common.
We're glad when people just accept
what we lead them to believe.
No shepherd want a sheep
that think for themselves.
- What do you want?
- It's all about what you want here, honey.
Something about a second chance?
Still can't tempt you?
Okay.
I wasn't doing the freeze over.
Our father who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
thy kingdom, thy will be done
on Earth as it is in heaven.
lead us not into temptation..
I'm sorry, you can never keep a straight face.
I always wondered what people would do
had Christ been hanged.
Wear many knotches around their necks I suppose.
or is it knitches?
or knit?
I can fill and fuck your brains out!
Oh, Jack...
You're such a...
... Gentleman. At least now that I'm
coming out of the closet I can have a smoke.
Onions?
On your steak?
Onions.
Onions?
Jack... after coming so far...
... you're not going to just
throw it all away now, are you?
Last chance of getting...
... what you wanted most for the past six years?
I'm gonna give it to you.
Aren't you hungry?
It was Susan, wasn't it?
She sent you here to test me.
So, what is it you want from me?
C'mon, Jack.
- Think.
- Myself?
Is that what you came here for?
Okay... but then I get what I want.
Okay...
What will I do?
Repeat after me:
Lucifer, I sell you my soul.
Six times over.
Focus your full concentration.
And say it with conviction.
- Lucifer, I sell you my soul..
- One..
- Two...
- Lucifer, I sell you my soul...
- Three...
- Lucifer, I sell you my soul..
- Four...
- Five...
The last one's a difficult one.
Lucifer...
... I sell you my soul.
Six. I won't bother you anymore Officer Jackman,
you've passed the test.
- Is that it?
- I got what I want and so did you.
- Where are we?
- Wait outside in your truck.
And when Susan comes,
all you have to do is drive away.
Going already?
Don't leave us again so soon,
the children were so looking forward to it.
- but she said that you...
- Who?
Hey.. Hey...
- Who? The operable lies and deception?
- Daddy, you have to blow out the candle.
Make a wish first.
Yeah, make a wish Daddy.
Blow them all out or it won't come true.
Try wishing for something else, Tom...
or someone else.
I can't do this.
- Rather spend your birthday with her?
- No, I'm staying this time.
I'm staying.
Come on, Jack.
We have to go!
I'll ignore it.
- She can go...
- She?
You admit it?
It's over!
It was just one night,
just one stupid night, Susan.
- It's your last chance. Susan's waiting.
- No! She's here.
They're here.
She's here.
That's not Susan, Jack.
Look at her, Jack!
Tom, we must hurry.
We can leave now!
It's me, Susan!
It's me.
No!
Susan?
- Susan?
- Yes, Tom.
Thank God.
Come on, we can start over now.
We've been given a new chance.
- We did it honey. You rescued me.
- Daddy?
- But the kids?
- Dad! Help!
- Did you hear them?
- No, it's nothing, let's go, Tom.
- No, it's them. We can't leave here without them.
- No, Ben and Anna are at home waiting for us.
It's just the wind, Jack.
- It's just the wind.
- When is their birthday?
Please say you love me, Jack.
Say it.
I love you...
Go back to hell, JC...
We had a deal!
Jack!
You're hallucinating.
Breathe!
Come on.
It's oxygen, Jack.
Breathe, Jack!
Come on, Jack.
Breathe. Breathe!
Over here!
- Where's the girl, Jack?
- Who?
- Dr. Christianson.
- JC? She's not real.
- Yes, she is, Jack.
- What?
She is. She's telling the truth.
Come on, Jack.
She's right, her story...
Get down.
Look at me...
Where is the girl? The doctor?
She's one of the scientist!
- They had her under a different name.
- Jack, where is the girl?
- JC?
- Oh my God!
The cavity was probably full in over 60
million years ago.
and had trapped a huge mass
of compressed organic matter...
... tormented to early form of Psylocybin growth.
Now I think the only explanation,
that makes any sense:
Is that you are in inhaling an odorless
by product of the places.
It's a hallucigenic gas, which impairs
rational and cognitive functions of the brain.
So why is it the end of the world's longest joint.
It seems it disabled your ability to discern,
... between reality, memory and imaginative
creations...
To you they all seems to be one.
So what I believed to be real,
became real to me?
Yeah, what you wanted to believe
what you are afraid of believing.
And what about Borman?
Well, like you and everybody else.I think his own personal hell
was brought to the surface by the gas.
- What about JC? How does she cope?
- Well, a number of factors.
Everybody living up in the main complex,
was accumulating toxins.
- She was far as exposed.
- What about the voices?
- I mean, the screaming in the shaft head?
- Well, my guess would be:
Miles of Metal against stone.
Or the wind.
Merely by the power of suggestion
the mind is capable of creating patterns.
Even in white noise.
- But...
- Forget the noises.
Inspector Coolidgeman found two furgal forces
stranded 50 km out from where he come off.
Footprints leading up in all directions.
Realistically, there's very little chance
of finding any of them alive.
- Thank you.
Come on,
look on the bright side.
There's no hell
and she's not the devil.
That's gotta be something.
- I feel I'm just missing something here.
- You saw all the evidence.
Why do you throw away all rational
explanation for the sake of that 1% of doubt?
I don't know.
- Good morning.
- Hi.
- Forgive me?
- What's there to forgive?
Well, you seem pretty tolerant,
someone tried to kill you.
- We both got a little messed up.
- Yeah, and I'm...
How's your wound?
How's yours?
Which one?
Is it my imagination or did I...
... did I really sell you
me soul back there?
Jack!
You should see your face.
Oh it's just a chunk,
it's a...
I had to play along
with your delusion.
I would have played any character,
to lure you away from there.
- I suppose I owe you dinner then, huh?
- Yeah...
I should let you rest.
I've got it!
And this will prove she
wasn't there from the start.
The only image we have of her,
is on this footage...
... which was supposedly was
taken weeks ago.
- And...?
- My cap is in the background of the shot!
- What the hell are you trying to prove?
- That she staged all of this.
There!
- David, can you zoom in on it?
- Yeah, sure.
- It's like a safety helmet to me.
- Maybe there's something else further on.
Oh man, you're behaving as if you're
soring up to a thrown hell out there...
You're on extended sick leave
until further notice.
Jackman! your gun.
Well, speaking of the devil...
it's Jack.
Hey Jacko.
You alright?
- What's wrong?
- It's her.
- Jack, what!
- You almost got away with it, didn't you!
- Jack, what are you doing?
- I'm seeing you as you really are.
- What are you talking about?
- Jack!
Fuck off! You don't understand,
you haven't seen what I've seen!
- Jack, please explain.
- Explain?
- Yes...
- So you could twist the truth again?
No, not this time.
No, shut up!
Please. Please, Jack.
No, not this time, JC..
You've run out of lot
of explanations.
It is the devil!
Please, Jack. no.
- It's courage!
- No, no, no.
Let go of me!
You have to understand!
Who are you?
I don't know you.
You are laughing at me.
Oh, God.
Hell is in your head.
There's always a logical explanation.
Your anger settles right in yourself tight.
It's all in your mind.
I'm fine.
To fear the unknown is dangerous.
Stop!
Call the doctor!
- It's not her blood, it's not her blood!
- I'm fine.
Jack went crazy again.
He stole my gun.
- He ran into the quarter. He's nuts.
- He's gonna do it like Borman and Susan.
He's gonna do...
He's gonna do it like Borman und Susan.
Okay, Sue, you win.
I'll give you what you want.