Fuck you!
Oh no, not now.
Fuck!
APACHE LEAP
U TURN OK
I got a fire in here.
Who cut off my music?
You cut my music off.
Are you Harlin?
Is Harlin around?
I doubt it. He's dead.
- Are you the owner?
- Yes.
- Why do you call it "Harlin's"?
- Because Harlin used to own it.
Could you take a look at my car?
I think the radiator hose is bust.
It's going to be a hot one today.
Then again, it might not be.
You can't ever tell. When it's hot,
I don't even like to get out of bed.
- Nor when it's cold.
- Harlin...
- Darrell.
- I think the radiator hose is bust.
- Your radiator hose is busted.
- I know. What did I just tell you?
If you know so much,
fix it yourself.
If I could, I wouldn't be here.
Fix it, or I'll go someplace else.
Someplace else?
That's 50 miles from here.
The station downtown
closed some three years ago.
Okay. Can you fix it or not?
- Yeah, I can.
- Great.
I'll see if I have a hose
like that one. It'll take some time.
- How much time?
- I don't know. Time.
- What time is it now?
- 10:20.
Arizona...
- It must be 90 already.
- 92.
- What happened to your hand?
- An accident.
You've got to be more careful.
Hands is important.
I don't know if you can still
see it, but when I was a kid...
Interesting...
Where can I get something to drink?
There's a diner. It ain't much.
Us simple folk like it.
I'll be back in a couple of hours.
Just be real careful with it.
- It's just a car.
- It's a '64 Mustang Convertible.
That's the reason why you live here
and I'm just passing through.
- I'll just get some things out.
- Knock yourself out.
Just like a town,
only uglier.
- Hey, you there.
- You want something, old man?
Run over to the corner there
to that machine and get me a pop.
- You can't do that yourself?
- Hell no, I'm blind.
- I lost my eyes in Vietnam.
- Sorry.
Don't be so sorry. Just get me
a pop before I die of thirst.
- Got change?
- You want a blind veteran's change?
What the hell has the world come to?
Get me a Dr. Pepper.
Cola's nothing but flavoured water.
And open it. I can't.
If you do it, that's a good boy.
Unbelievable. Fucking...
That's for Mother Earth.
I'm about 50% Indian.
- Congratulations.
- Here's to all our relations.
- You want some?
- I'll pass.
The dog looks sick.
That's because he's dead.
I hope you wasn't patting him...
- What do you want with a dead dog?
- He's only just dead.
What was I to do? Me and Jesse
have been pals since the war.
Come on, Jesse.
See you later, unless
I come across something worse.
- Need a hand, beautiful?
- I'm just going to my car.
- That's right on my way.
- Mother warned me about strangers.
I'm Bobby. Now we're not strangers.
See how easy that was, beautiful?
- Do you have to call me that?
- I don't know your name.
- Maybe I don't want you to.
- Then why did you stop walking?
- You're full of yourself.
- I like that about me.
- It's Grace.
- Grace, can I carry your package?
- Can you manage? Shall I take that?
- No, it's no trouble.
- What happened to your hand?
- An accident.
You should be more careful.
It's just drapes and curtain rods.
I got so tired of the old ones.
My mother made them.
I just knew I had to have these.
Ever felt you had to have something?
- Yes, I have.
- This is it.
- Thank you, Bobby.
- You're welcome, Grace.
- You're not from around here.
- No, my car overheated up the road.
Lucky you weren't in the desert.
A day like today, you'd be dead.
When are you leaving?
Not until I get my car back.
And here I made you
all hot and sweaty.
- Morning, Grace.
- Morning, Sheriff.
- Got my drapes.
- You got yourself a helper, too.
Morning, Sheriff.
- Nice to meet you, son.
- Same to you, Sheriff.
I could use some help
getting these boxes in the house.
You could shower.
Get something cool to drink.
You're still lucky.
- Where are you coming from?
- All over. Detroit.
Chicago, Miami. I have some
unfinished business in Las Vegas.
- What is it you do?
- Whatever pays best. Bartending.
Used to teach tennis.
Used to play some competitively.
I never played tennis.
- I'm sick of your bullshit.
- Easy, easy.
- Bobby, I want my money.
- You got that?
You'll get your money.
You don't have to do this.
You have two weeks, asshole.
Take two for now.
Finger one.
Finger two.
- Some more lemonade?
- That would be great.
- What do you do, anyway?
- A little of this, little of that.
- Mostly I tell fortunes.
- Where did you learn that?
From my father.
Come here.
Sit down.
There's something in your past...
Something... There's a pain.
There's something you want badly.
It seems far away to you right now.
But you're determined.
And you'll do what you must
to get it.
- You can tell all that by my face?
- All faces tell me the same.
Everybody has a past. They have
pain and something they want.
- What is it you want?
- The same thing you do.
Really?
I want to hang drapes.
Can you hold me?
Tighter. I won't break.
There. Lift me down.
You can put me down now.
I'm safe.
I'm tired of hanging drapes.
- Now what should we do?
- I got an idea.
What would that be?
- All right, no more games.
- What game do you want to play?
You carry my parcels
and we go to bed?
- I'm going back to town.
- I like to know about a man first.
- Find out what he's made of.
- Thanks for the lemonade.
- You didn't answer me.
- You're still playing.
What is it you want?
Grace!
Jake...
I thought you were in Phoenix.
Who the hell is this?
- Who in the hell are you?
- Her husband.
Who are you? It had better be good,
or I'll break you in half.
I was just giving your wife
a hand with the drapes.
- It didn't look like that.
- That's all.
- A lot that means.
- Grace, tell him.
I suppose he just wandered up here?
I should paddle your ass raw!
You sucker me up here so the two
of us can beat each other over you?
Forget it.
You don't just walk in and walk out.
- You broke my nose!
- It ain't broke.
Get going, pipsqueak.
- What the fuck do you want?
- Hop in. You'll die in this heat.
You're not still upset over that
little love tap, are you? Get in.
- What happened to your hand?
- An accident.
- You've got to be...
- More careful. I know.
I'm Jake McKenna.
- Bobby Cooper.
- What brings you to Superior?
- Car overheated.
- Is Darrell taking care of you?
- He's dumb as a sack of hammers.
- Yes, he sure is a character.
- Where are you headed?
- California.
- Do you live there?
- A man wants me to sail his boat.
You're a sailor-man?
That would be the life.
Just get on a boat and sail away.
- A man could disappear like that.
- If I'd known she was married...
It wouldn't have made a difference.
You're a man without scruples.
I can smell it on you.
Yeah, that's the sweat of a man that
hasn't an honest bone in his body.
Don't be offended. A man without
ethics is a free man. I envy you.
A woman with her looks and a man
my age, what was I to expect?
Women... Can't live with them,
can't live without them.
Can't live with them,
can't shoot them.
I bet she had you hard as a rock,
wiggling her ass in your face.
You wanted to pull her pants down
and hog her out, and then I bust in.
You got a temper. I bet
you just wanted to snap her neck.
I bet you just wanted to kill her.
Would you? Would you kill her?
- Why would I kill her?
- I'm sick of her little games.
You could do it and drift away
on that boat without being noticed.
I'd love to split the $50,000 life
insurance policy with her murderer.
I've done some things,
but I'm not a murderer.
How do you know
if you've never tried?
You're joking, right?
That's right.
It's nothing but a joke.
Enjoy your stay, lad.
- You got a soda?
- Habla slowly.
- A cold soda.
- Something to eat.
No, no. Drink.
Keep it in you and nobody gets hurt.
The same goes for you, punk.
Give me the money.
That's it? Lady, I've got kids
to put through school.
What have you got, pal?
Beautiful. You're getting tasty.
Give me the pack.
- It's just books.
- I'm a reader. Toss it.
- It's personal family things.
- Give me the bag.
- No.
- No?
- This is no good. Come on.
He doesn't want to give me the bag.
- He doesn't have to.
- Come on!
- Not my wedding ring!
- Extra never hurt.
Murderer!
Señor,  you're hurt.
I'll call the police.
No. No police.
- Here. No police.
- $100, no police?
No police.
- What happened to your face?
- I had an accident.
Another accident?
You've got to be more careful.
What the hell happened to my car?
I had to change your bottom hose
too, but it runs like a dream now.
- How much?
- Let's see...
You got parts and labour.
Let's just call it... $150.
- How much?
- 150.
- To replace a radiator hose?
- A hose in a 1964 Mustang.
It's a Ford, not a Ferrari!
It's not just a Ford.
It's a 1964 Mustang.
- What's that got to do with it?
- I don't know.
But it's the reason I'm living here,
and you're just passing through.
You owe me $150.
I just got rolled.
Get out your American Express
gold card and call the guy on TV...
- I don't have a credit card.
- Then you'll have to work this off.
I've got a Movado. It's worth
$7,800. You could sell it for that.
- I can't see no numbers.
- That's why it's expensive!
Look at the gold.
No day, no dates. Far as I can tell,
this ain't worth a duck's fart.
I got this for $3.75. It's got lots
of doodads. I'll stick with that.
You son of a bitch!
- My lawyer will shut you down.
- No credit cards, but a lawyer?
Sweet talk me all you want to,
but didn't you read this sign?
- What sign? I want my car.
- I want my $150.
- What's the line on Dallas?
- You deadbeat. Lose my number!
- Mike, you...
- Mike who?
Cici, it's Bobby. I know
it's been a while, but I'm in a jam.
- You need money?
- $150.
No, you stole my CDs. Or was it
my ex-roommate, who you fucked?
Okay, where's my Mr. Coffee?
Cici?
- Rosarita. Bobby.
- Fuck you!
- Mom, it's Bobby. Your son.
- He's dead.
- No, I'm not dead.
- You are to me.
Hallo? Mr. Arkady,
this is deadbeat Cooper calling.
The motherfucker's calling collect.
Bobby, I expected to be seeing you,
not talking to you over the phone.
What a day I've had. This will sound
like a highly improbable story.
I had the money. I'm on my way
to Vegas, and my car breaks down.
I go into this store to get some
food, and the place gets robbed.
- And the robber gets your money?
- There were two, and they got shot.
The old lady shot them.
She kills them, and the money
in the bag gets shredded to pieces.
What are the odds?
So I thought maybe you could...
Can't you wire me $150?
I'd pay it back with the rest.
- Which you don't have.
- I can sell my car in Vegas.
Where are you?
In this little shithole
200 miles east of Phoenix.
Superior.
- Couldn't you send it...
- No! Listen to me, you punk!
I don't care if you got hit by a
truck and run over by a steamroller.
You owe me $13,000
and I want it on my desk tomorrow!
Or I'll show you what bad luck is!
- You understand?
- Fuck you too!
- What did you say?
- No. I'm sorry.
- There's just been so much stress.
- You've owed me for four weeks.
Now you want another week.
That's five weeks.
That's also five fingers,
because it's a finger a week!
Come tomorrow and be nice.
And maybe I don't take
the other three fingers...
Get your ass down to Superior.
This deadbeat won't see tomorrow.
You get three heads in a row,
odds are the next one will be tails.
Shut up and drink your coffee,
and stop flipping that damn quarter.
- Can I get you something?
- A beer. A Beck's.
- Ain't got Beck's. A-1, Coor's?
- Heineken?
- No. We've got Miller.
- Boyd thinks the odds are 50-50.
- "Genuine Draft"?
- No, just regular plain old Miller.
You can fucking take it or leave it.
I'll fucking take it.
- Flo. A cheeseburger bleeding.
- I'll be right back with that beer.
And a waitress named Flo...
Christ!
- He doesn't know statistics.
- What are you? A rocket scientist?
Fucking cat.
Got a quarter for the juke?
I want to play a song.
Got a quarter?
- What happened to your hand?
- I cut myself shaving.
- Yes, I've got to be more careful.
- Any requests?
- All country shit sounds the same.
- How about I pick one out for you?
Don't you just love Patsy Cline? Why
doesn't she put out more records?
- Because she's dead.
- That's sad.
- Don't that make you sad?
- I've had time to get over it.
You ain't from around here, right?
Where are you from?
- Oz.
- No, you ain't from Oz!
- Oz is from that movie.
- You are too quick for me.
No! I'm seeing,
but I'm not believing.
What are you doing with my girl?
I asked you a question.
- Toby, we were just talking.
- Shut up. Get back to our table.
Don't make me ask you again.
What are you doing with my girl?
- I wasn't doing anything.
- That's not how it looked to me.
- You tried to make time with her.
- Is everyone in this town on drugs?
- I just asked him for a quarter.
- Shut your mouth.
We've got business to take care of.
And I ain't never taken no drugs.
Maybe you should. I wasn't
trying to make time with your girl.
I'm calling you out.
You want to fight over her?
You don't know who I am.
The name's Toby N. Tucker.
People call me TNT.
- You know why?
- They're not very imaginative?
Because I'm just like dynamite.
When I go off, somebody gets hurt!
Fine.
I tried to make time with your girl.
Now I'm terrified, and I've learned
my lesson, and you can go away.
- Jesus Christ.
- Stand up.
- Or I'll beat you where you sit?
- Finish your pop and leave him.
Don't you never mind, Flo.
This will be over real quick.
One Touch Toby.
Come on, pussy.
You're real lucky this time.
But I'm going to see this through.
I think I'll make you walk home.
- What was that all about?
- Toby thinks everyone wants Jenny.
It's Jenny who wants every man
she sees.
- I can't open off-sale for you.
- It's the desert.
It makes people go bonkers.
- I'll help myself to some coffee.
- You be careful now.
- Son of a bitch!
- Look what you've done.
- I burned my gun hand.
- It's all red.
I'll put butter on it later.
Joe, get a mop and clean up.
Shasta, don't scare that nice man.
Sorry about that, sugar.
Let's see. $3.25.
Have a nice day.
I'll sure try.
Goddamn it!
Why?
Get me out of this fucking town.
McKENNA REALTY
Jake's the name,
real estate's my game.
What can I do for you, lad?
- I hoped we could talk.
- About what?
About your wife. About your
$50,000 life insurance policy.
- You'd split it with her murderer.
- I think the heat's getting to you.
You brought it up.
- I don't always mean what I say.
- You meant it.
You're a slimy bastard who'd
have his wife killed to get rich.
- What does that make you?
- The slimy bastard that'll do it.
You're a jealous man. If you can't
have Grace to yourself...
You're not the sharing kind.
I have what you call
a love-hate relationship with Grace.
- You love her, but you hate her.
- No, I hate loving her.
I hate having to tolerate
the little games she plays.
Like fucking half this town behind
my back and laughing at me. Bitch!
She wants me to hit her. She
likes it. She likes to torture me.
But after all...
She's my family.
She's my little girl.
My baby.
I couldn't stand to watch her
as she sucks her last breath.
No. Not me.
But you...
You've got a killing in you.
Let's say I want the bitch dead.
- What do you want?
- How do you put a price on murder?
I put it at $50,000
minus your cut, of course. Which is?
- 20,000.
- I don't have that kind of money.
- Getting the insurance takes time.
- How much can you get?
Maybe 10,000.
- I need 13,000.
- That's a bit much.
We're not talking about buying
a car, but about killing your wife.
It's 13,000 or it's nothing.
You drive a hard bargain.
But I had a feeling you were my boy
when I first met you.
It looks like
we've got ourselves a contract.
Do we shake hands?
If you can't trust the man
you've hired to kill your wife...
It's got to look like an accident.
If it don't, it's no good.
I'll be a penniless murder suspect
while you're living it up somewhere.
How do you want it?
- It can't be done at the house.
- I want some money up front.
Why don't I buy you a plane ticket
while I'm at it? I know you.
Listen...
You go to the house to see her.
Tell her you had to see her.
You sweet-talk the woman. A young
buck like you must be good at that.
Then shift the conversation.
Talk about the Jeep. She loves that.
Maybe the only thing she does love.
She'll take you for a ride out
in the desert, someplace quiet.
Riding through the red rocks
and mesas. She loves it out there.
So do I. We've got that in common.
There won't be anyone around
but you and some prairie dogs.
And then... sweet-talk her.
It makes no difference to me.
Put her at ease,
and then...
...do it!
- You could leave him.
- It's not that easy.
- Walk away.
- Maybe you can take chances.
You can wander wherever
you please. I can't.
I don't want to be alone.
I wish I was a bird.
Some of the old Indians thought
you could change into animals.
I wish I could. If I was a bird,
I'd fly to Florida.
Disneyworld.
I've always wanted to go there.
Then I'll fly to New York, maybe.
Then I'd fly to St. Louis
and all over Texas.
Then I'll fly to California.
Then I guess I would've seen it all.
Then I could die.
They say you don't feel anything.
That the shock kills you
before you hit the ground.
I've always imagined
it's just like flying.
I bet, right now, you don't know
if you want to kill me...
...or fuck me.
Stop! I can't!
- What's the matter?
- Nothing.
Doesn't feel like nothing.
Get out of town quick, Bobby.
Don't do this to me. I've been
fucked over by too many women.
You're the queen of hot and cold.
- It's such a mess with Jake.
- I know all about being in a mess.
Jake was with my mom.
After my real father died.
He used to call me
his "little half-breed".
He kept my mom on the side.
He had a wife someplace else.
He'd control me.
You look so pretty.
Put your arms around me.
- Why?
- Don't fuck around like your mama.
He was raping me the whole time.
For years.
My mom...
It tore her up 'cause she couldn't
do nothing about it.
She became an alcoholic.
They found my mama down here.
At the bottom of Apache Leap.
Virgil, Sheriff Potter, said
she was drunk and went insane.
I'd never believe
she ran off that cliff by accident.
She was like me.
She just wanted to fly away.
I'm so sorry.
What are you going to? Life, right?
- Have you ever been to California?
- Yes.
- Is it pretty?
- It's another world.
It's beautiful beaches
and blue water.
Clear sky,
as far as the eye can see.
Take me with you.
I won't hang on you.
You can dump me there.
I just want to leave.
I can't leave before I get hold
of the $150 for that crazy mechanic.
- Darrell? He and Jake...
- Do you have money?
Jake only gives me $20 at a time.
If you could get money,
I could get us out of here.
- There's money. A lot.
- Where?
Jake hides it in a safe.
In the bedroom floor. My mom said
there was more than $100,000 there.
- In cash?
- There's nothing else with Jake.
He sits there, he laughs,
he talks to himself and counts it.
$100,000... son of a bitch.
What do you mean?
- We need the combination.
- It takes a key.
He keeps it on him all the time.
So it's slapping up against me
when we do it.
Then how do we get it?
Kill him.
I can't kill anybody.
It's not like he's a young man.
He had time to live.
It would be quick.
He doesn't even have to feel it.
Do it at night. Come up
behind him when he's asleep.
Or when he's pounding me...
Bobby!
I see it.
It's in you. I see death.
It's in your heart.
Do it for me.
I'll do anything for you. You need
the money to get out of here.
It's three miles back to town.
It's a lot more than $100,000.
Where are you going?