Look at me! Calm down!
What happened to the others?
Look at me!
Fuckin' dead! The whole platoon!
The sarge totally lost it.
Went nuts. Killed everyone.
Get off me!
They're all dead! Oh fucking God!
Ah, you son of a bitch!
Let's get outta here!
Come on!
Luc, come on, man!
Sarge?
What the hell happened here?
They wouldn't listen.
The village was cleared.
These people are innocent.
They're all fuckin' traitors. You turn
around, they stab you in the back.
Sarge...
My tour is up.
I just want to go home.
Come on. Let's go home.
You're just like the others.
You just want to leave.
Like none of this shit ever happened.
It happened!
And it doesn't just go away.
You just can't walk away!
Do you hear me?
You're a traitor, too,
aren't you, farm boy?
No.
Prove it!
Kill her!
Kill the motherfucking traitor!
That's an order!
Get up, come on!
Come on!
Run!
No!
What the... Oh Jesus Christ!
Nice touch.
I'd hate to be the poor schmuck
who has to explain this to Ma and Pa.
Sir, how do we write this one up?
What do we say happened?
Nothing. Nothing happened here. M. I.A.
We didn't find anyone. Understood?
What? They're gonna call this M. I.A.?
Lincoln, this is Eagle. Come in.
I've got a code Zebra, do you copy?
Only a few hours ago.
At least ten bodies... Yes, sir.
Pack 'em in ice.
Ice...
Alright.
How's the picture?
Pretty ugly.
- Very funny.
Very funny.
I need a ladder.
Can you see me? How's my hair?
Let's go.
Alright, my size, yeah!
- Systems, check.
Next!
How's the focus?
- Check.
Good, let's go. Okay brother, go.
Alright, so we got 'em all.
We don't have much time.
Position 7, status?
- They're bringing the next one out.
Excuse me. I'll have a statement
for you later on, okay? Thank you.
They just killed another hostage.
Current status? - They're
all linked to an intercom system.
They're in the water.
Colonel, where'd you drop 'em off?
- About a mile and a half away.
1.5 miles? We got thirteen minutes!
Hurry up!
Hold on, ma'am.
I'm with the press. CNA.
They're waiting for me right there.
I'm canceling the remote.
- Oh, Charles, will you relax!
We're live in one minute!
- He's absolutely gonna kill me.
See, there she is.
I know, I'm running a little late.
- A little?
Well, that traffic killed me.
- We're live in twenty.
Where the hell were you?
See your mark?
- I got my mark.
Glasses!
Mic.
Nice shoes!
- No feet!
Cigarette!
With 30 hostages
inside the power station,
the gunmen claim they will not
release any of them until
some comrades are released
from penitentiaries across the U. S.
Checkpoint 3, all clear.
Keep your eyes open.
Shut up!
I said shut up!
Hey, do as you're told
and you won't get hurt. - Quiet down.
Checkpoint 3, all clear.
Colonel, they're at the tower.
- A mile and a half under 4 minutes?
They're 8 seconds behind schedule.
Veronica Roberts, live for CNA.
And we're out.
- See, what'd I tell ya?
No problem. - The network
does not revolve around you!
Are you saying I'm not the center of
the universe? - Don't get wise!
I always get you the story.
You think because you broke a few
stories that you're indispensable?
Well, I had a chat with the network
today and you know what? - No, what?
You're fired.
They're in the drain-out tunnels.
GR-13, take aim and hold fire.
Checkpoint 1, all clear.
- Checkpoint 2, all clear.
GR-44 is in position. Take aim.
Fire!
Move in and secure the objective.
Clear that image up.
Clear it.
Got it.
Interceptors are secured and powered.
Begin playback.
- Playback. - Rolling.
Checkpoint 1, all clear.
Checkpoint 2, all clear.
Checkpoint 3, all clear.
They're buying it.
Who the hell are these guys?
Okay, here we go...
Terminate objectives.
Activate interceptors now.
I think homeboy likes this shit.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Continue playback.
- Checkpoint 3, all clear.
Okay, we're inside.
- Begin phase two. - Initiate.
Look at this guy.
Hold it there, buddy! Hold it!
Two gunmen,
semi-automatic, fully loaded.
Main target to rear. Loaded pistol
and explosives detonator.
Shoot him!
You are cleared, I repeat,
you are cleared to proceed.
GR-13,
all clear.
- No injuries?
Gentlemen, I think everybody's ok.
Arizona team.
- GR-44, status report?
GR-44, do you read me?
Problems? - He's not responding.
- Well, try another frequency.
GR-44, status report, now!
Kill the motherfuckin' traitor!
That's an order!
GR-44, respond!
How many UniSols were injured?
- Just who are these guys?
I will address you accordingly.
This marks the third successful
mission for the Universal Soldiers.
Again, without any casualties and
without any injuries.
As to the UniSols' identity,
that remains classified.
But Colonel... - These men have
families. I won't jeopardize that.
Now I have
other matters to attend to.
Lieutenant, could I have a statement?
- There'll be a briefing tonight.
What are we doing here?
We need pictures.
Lieutenant, please, one statement!
Huey, I have an idea.
No, you don't.
Yeah, I do.
- I hate when you do this.
Ronnie, what are you doing?
This is too close!
They're gonna see us.
We shouldn't be here.
- All these guards.
They must still be in there, huh?
- Yeah.
Are you getting this?
- That's one hell of a mobile home.
At 30 below, lowering to
final stage of 60, sub-zero.
He just froze up. We can't figure
it out. - What do you mean?
At the end of the mission
he became completely unresponsive.
Did he overheat?
- He hardly broke a sweat.
GR-44,
why did you not respond?
What happened?
Innocent...
What do you mean?
The village was cleared.
That girl was innocent, Sarge.
Sarge? Who is Sarge?
That could be an old memory.
We should take him out of the program
until we find out
what's going on in his head.
GR-44 stays with the program.
But, Colonel...
- He just got mixed up.
Just give him the serum.
Okay, guys,
memory clearance.
Take your positions.
Activate injection.
They're moving
something else onto the tarmac!
We can't get anything from out here.
- Are you nuts?
This is a classified military
operation. You can't get closer.
I'll be right back.
You were confused.
- I was confused.
You must follow orders at all times.
I must follow my orders.
He's fine.
- If you say so. You're in charge.
This is pretty bad.
Soon as the floatation chamber's
filled, we'll have to put him in.
Great.
I always have to do this part
and I hate it!
Hey, Dr. Haines! Dr. Haines!
Can I get a little help with this?
Jesus!
No casualties or injuries, huh?
Power up the cooling generators.
He's almost ready. - You got it.
He's ready. - Bring him in.
- Yes, sir. - Thank you.
Prepare for floatation chamber entry.
Colonel, we've spotted an intruder.
Who the fuck is that?
She's taking pictures!
Huey! - Shit! What the hell has she
done this time? - Start the car!
I think we should leave now!
What'd you get?
- Redemption. - Let's go!
Do you think we lost 'em?
How you doin'?
Veronica Roberts,
CNA.
You want to help me out?
Thank you, thank... Hey, easy!
Take it easy!
You alright?
Okay, they got 'em. Bingo!
I want to speak to someone in charge.
You guys speak English?
Awaiting instructions.
Tell them to find that film
and bring those civilians back here.
I'm sure we can handle this situation,
if I can make a phone call.
- What's wrong with these guys?
The film!
Uh, fellas...
I don't know...
She didn't do anything!
Christ! GR-13, cease fire!
Do you read me?
Cease fire! I repeat:
Cease fire!
That's an order!
No, no! Let go of me! Oh God!
GR-86, visual!
What the fuck is he doing?
Stop the girl! Shoot if you have to.
GR-44, stop the car! That is an order!
He stopped the car.
- Cease fire!
What are you doing?
Come on, get out of here!
Jesus Christ, they're gonna kill us!
GR-44, turn the car around.
- Are you deaf?
You are simply confused.
I am confused.
- What are you talking about! Go!
Do not listen to her.
- What the hell is that thing?
Do you hear me?
- Fucking stupid piece of shit!
The bitch cut me off!
I must follow orders.
Bullshit!
On the road!
- Oh, shit!
Woodward, do something!
Traitor!
He didn't do anything!
Well, they're not gonna
get away with this shit.
Is he ready? - Almost.
- Take him out of the loop.
He shot a man!
- I need every soldier I've got.
We're goin' after them.
Colonel Perry!
We killed an innocent man.
Should we let that reporter
run off with one of our UniSols?
We can't just cover this up. We have
a moral obligation to tell the truth.
I thought
you were more clever than that.
This whole project is off the shelf.
Do you think those
wimps at the Pentagon would allow
the regeneration of dead soldiers?
I don't think
I can be a part of this anymore.
If this is uncovered now,
we're all going to jail. Understood?
Why did you do that?
Why did you help me out?
My tour's up. Just want to go home.
But I can't until you're safe.
- What do you mean?
My God! You've been shot!
Oh Jesus,
we've got to stop the bleeding!
Oh God, that's gotta hurt you!
The bleeding has stopped.
Secure your positions!
Secure and lock!
Why are we stopping now?
What happened?
Out of gas.
Sure, out of gas, why not?
Shit!
Oh, God.
Tracking system activated.
We've picked 'em up.
Moving due east, 7 miles ahead.
Estimated time of interception?
- 4 minutes. - 4 minutes and marking.
How you doin'?
You must be pretty tired
after all that pushing and stuff.
Well, I'm gonna go.
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
- To make a phone call.
You mind?
Change...
I need some gas.
We ran out of gas yesterday.
Refueling truck comes in the morning.
You want to rent a room?
Nice outfit.
Shit!
Hey, you don't look so good.
I need to cool down.
All our rooms have air conditioning.
I some with water beds.
Hey, the pay phone's out.
All our rooms have telephones, too.
Only 50 dollars a night.
I need a phone. What about this one?
Sorry, that's for employees only.
Since there's two of you, that's
double occupancy. Extra 10 dollars.
And a matter of
a small 20 dollar security deposit.
Of course, 20 dollars.
Have a nice stay.
Great. Maybe there's
already something on the news.
Commence UniSol deployment.
B and C teams,
take supporting positions.
GR-13, seek and destroy local
communications lines in target areas.
...one prays for the speedy handling
of terrorist situations.
In a related story, only hours
after the rescue at McKinley Dam,
news reporters become news makers.
Reporting live, Chris Garvey.
In a surprising development,
a CNA cameraman, Huey Taylor,
was shot and killed
in a motel room in Eagle Rock City.
Witnesses allege that
CNA correspondent Veronica Roberts
shot him after an apparent argument.
Cocaine was found at the scene.
No way.
No way!
I don't believe this!
They won't get away with this!
You must return to your room.
Mother, come here.
There must be
a phone that works in this place.
This area's not secure.
- You know, why don't you...
What are you doing?
It's not safe for you out there.
- Where are your clothes?
I have to...
I have to cool down.
My God, you're burning up!
I need... ice.
Shame on ya
GR-13, continue advance.
Target center structure.
What is she doing with all that ice?
Maybe I should call the police.
I've heard of cold showers before,
but this is ridiculous.
How you doin'?
I got all the ice that I could.
You okay?
How's your...
Your wound?
It's, it's healing!
Well, I'm gonna...
...make that phone call,
and call a doctor...
or something.
Heat and infrared, check.
Munitions and firearms identifier,
powered and working.
Don't even start with me, alright?
And take this lock off. Goddamn it!
Hey, lady!
What are you doing with the phone?
You know how much those things cost?
You got a lot of nerve!
- Shut up!
This one doesn't work either.
- Huh?
You women just don't know
how to use phones.
You killed it!
This is comin' out of your deposit!
He's got her in sight.
GR-13 has a lock on the girl.
What do you want me to do?
Tell him to wait till they're
together. - GR-13, hold fire.
And now, back to
"Nixon and the War Years, Part 7."
We will keep America the strongest
nation in the world. And we will
couple that strength
with firm diplomacy. No apologies.
There was no question about that,
because when I resigned,
later President Ford issued a pardon.
When I accepted the pardon,
in that I made it very clear...
I want that place surrounded.
- GR-86 and 61, take positions
at the rear of the motel.
How are you feeling?
The war is over.
Maybe not.
All focus to visual.
Powering alternate scanning devices.
Motion detectors locked in.
Something weird is going on here.
None of the phones here work.
I mean, there hasn't been a storm.
They're in the 2nd room now.
You better duck and cover!
Follow me.
He's in the 3rd room now.
The last wall is solid concrete.
He's not going anywhere.
I think we got him trapped.
Go on, knock it down!
What?
Get down!
Soldiers, move in.
Where is he?
I think we lost him.
- That's impossible.
Garth, get back to your station
and get me some tracking, dammit!
You have a car?
- Yeah.
Give me the keys.
- Hurry up. Don't worry. - Hurry.
Got' em?
- Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. Really,
I had nothing to do with this.
They're leaving the motel.
- Damn it!
Come on, Woodward,
I need you out here.
Way to go, Garth.
20 dollar security deposit, huh?
Woodward.
He's trying to cool himself.
Are you sure
they're not following us? - No.
You're such a comfort.
- Buckle up.
I'm fine.
- It's for your safety.
How can you be so damn calm? Your
buddies just shot enough ammo at us
to destroy Europe,
and you're worried about my seat belt?
Alright, alright...
All buckled up.
Alright, Mr. Top Secret,
I want some answers, okay?
First, you push a car
faster than my mother drives,
then you use ice
like other people use Band-Aids,
and then you just run through walls.
I'm sorry,
but this is not normal behavior.
Now, just who the hell are you?
Where are you from anyway?
Are you from France or Canada or...?
I figure you must be French
because of your accent.
What accent?
Look, you got a family?
You got friends?
Is there a Mrs. 44
waiting for you someplace?
Are you avoiding my questions
or don't you know?
What the hell did they do to you?
I don't know.
But I'm going to find out.
Hey, no smoking around the pumps!
- I'm sorry. - Come on.
Would you quit pulling on my arm?
Park the car.
Let's go.
Park the car?
I need some help. - Need some help?
I can't help you with this thing!
What are you doing?
Not this again, huh?
Could you at least
leave your pants on this time?
Great. Just great.
There must be a tracking device on me.
- Yeah, and?
Look for something unusual.
Something hard.
Okay. Alright.
You stay in shape.
What are you doing?
- Nothing!
What do you mean, "park your car?"
- You never heard of valet parking?
Do I look like a valet?
Does this look like Beverly Hills?
Is that supposed to be there?
Yes, yes, it is. It's very normal.
Keep going.
Right.
Update informational
computer scanning system.
They've stopped
in front of a single story structure.
I think I found something.
On the back of your leg.
Cut it out.
- Cut it out?
Hey, I can't cut it out.
I'm not gonna cut you.
Oh, shit!
You best hurry up and get outta there,
I got a business to run here.
Take it.
- What?
Take it!
- Take it? - We don't have much time.
Oh God, this is so gross.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Good. I gotta lie down.
I want a complete scan
of the entire area.
Enabling infrared.
That's his car.
- Scanning for body heat.
Got it.
- Arms?
Pistol, fully loaded.
Desert Eagle. That's him.
Motions and heat scan. Follow
tracking. Flanking advance pattern.
Three teams. North, East, South,
converge on my command.
Teams, advance. Surround target.
Teams East and South
prepare for break and ram.
Prepare and ram. Full charge.
Okay, guys, move in.
- Full charge!
No, no. He tricked us. Hold on!
Pull out!
All UniSols retreat immediately!
Evacuate! Let's go!
Get out of there!
Take cover!
- What the hell was that?
Oh, my God.
They're on fire!
Portable coolants.
Portable coolants, quick!
Put that out! Get him out!
Extinguishers! Woodward, Garth!
Garth, get over here!
Get this guy, come on!
Over here, Woodward! Get him!
Get those coolants ready!
Get that truck operating!
Woodward, get him over here!
Get more of that coolant!
Over here, over here! Get GR-74!
Put that coolant on him!
Got it, got it. Go.
Alright, hurry!
Oh, here I go again. I'm out of here!
We're gonna lose these two!
- At 250 million dollars a piece?
Buckle up.
- Right, seat belt. Okay, go.
Oh Jesus.
He should have buckled up.
He's getting up. Go. Go.
Shit!
They're pulling the plug.
We're heading home.
Everybody, back into the truck.
Come on, everybody.
Woodward, what the hell are you doing?
Yes, ice. Get back in the truck!