The Polish Institute of Film Art
ITI Cinema presents
A production of:
Co-financed by
The Polish Institute of Film Art
Starring
Set Decoration by
Editors
Music by
Production Manager
Cinematography by
Producer
Screenplay by
Directed by
Hi Max.
You can let the hostages out...
He's jumped.
Ok. Where are you?
In the centre,
I'll be at your place in 20 minutes.
But it's an hour's drive?!
I've got a new car.
Where's the mask?
What mask?
Balaclava.
Wow, are you going to wear one?
If I am to free the hostages,
I can't show them my face, now can I?
Get it?
Ok, guys, you're going home.
Do we have to go so soon?
Move it, move it. Your father
has done you a great favour.
Man, this car is a real toy...
Can I go for a drive?
Sure, no problem... but we're taking yours.
Why are we always taking mine?
That's not fair.
'Cause a hole or two more in yours
won't make any difference anyway.
- You were supposed to fix that.
- The garage's been fully booked lately.
Welcome, gentlemen.
Assholes.
Sorry.
I just feel uneasy in tight places.
Next time you're taking the stairs.
Well done boys. The loo's clean.
Even smells good.
I've only got one observation.
There is nothing to wipe your ass
with in cubicle two.
Hey, joker!
Do you know who we are?
We've even got a web site:
Www.gypsy.pl
Shut your gob.
We are a new gang in town.
My name is Gypsy
and these are my men.
Tell your boss that from now on,
I call the shots in this area.
Wow, that's what you call
a well-prepared self-presentation.
There's one problem.
I'm the one who decides
where and when I make friends
and I don't usually do that in the loo
so get the fuck out of here!
We've got ourselves a bloody clown!
I never repeat the same thing twice.
Any questions, you twit?
Attention passengers,
we are sorry to announce that today's
train to Zaosie and Tomaszow Mazowiecki
has been cancelled.
We apologise
for any inconvenience.
I repeat:
Today's train to Zaosie and
Tomaszow Mazowiecki has been cancelled.
I hate public toilets.
Get a move on, we're already late.
Assholes.
Mister Norman!
- What is it?
- You've got a phone call, Mister Norman.
Fuck off.
It's the hotel. They say it's important.
Drives you fucking crazy.
Bring it on!
- Is there anything else?
- That's all.
Screw off then.
What do you want?
- I think you should come here.
- I will. And I'll kick your ass.
The thing is... it's about your men.
Right now my men
should be in your hotel.
Technically speaking... they are.
Well... if they are, that means that
they have some important errands to run.
And you have to do what you're told to.
And if you disturb them in any way...
That's what I was going to tell you.
What the fuck
were you going to tell me?
They have already... been disturbed.
Have you been drinking?
If you hurry up you'll make it
before the cops get here.
Where?
Fuck!
Ta-dah!
What are you doing here?
Yeah, I'm happy to see you, too.
I've asked you a million times,
not when I'm at work.
Relax, honey.
Everybody knows we're together anyway.
It's no reason for you to come here. It's
going to spark off unnecessary rumours.
Take a chill pill, honey.
- Why are you here anyway?
- What do you mean?
I brought my son,
as you wanted me to.
Where is he?
He's in your office.
Don't be too hard on him, will you?
He's sort of sensitive by nature.
Not too hard? Not too hard?
You want him
to be a good cop or not?
He's my only son!
OK, OK. But you have to go now.
Pop in tonight, will you?
- I can't.
- Why not?
I promised my wife
we'd go out somewhere together.
- What, again? This miserable old cow!
- Stop it.
- If you promise you'll give me a call...
- Well... I will.
- I'll be waiting. Bye, honey.
- Bye.
Goodbye, ma'm.
Bye!
Stand to attention!
Sir, my name is Malinowski
and I'm in the rank of...
Shut your gob!
You only speak when I let you.
How come a beautiful woman
like your mother had YOU?
By the way,
who was your father?
Dad left us on the day I was born.
As soon as he saw you, I bet.
If it wasn't for your mother...
...you'd be a bobby on the beat
till the end of your life.
Have you filled in the application?
I've taken the liberty of putting my CV
and the application on your desk, Sir.
Taken the liberty?
Fuck,
what sort of language is this?
Do you think you are in for
a Sunday school session?
This is the big bad world. There's no
time for smooth talking. Understood?
Yes, sir!
Ok.
From what I can see in the papers you're
not the sharpest tool in the box.
But with me, you'll be making strides.
The first lesson, Malinowski,
is the following. Listen carefully.
If you want to teach someone to swim,
you throw him in at the deep end.
But I can swim.
It was a metaphor
to help you understand.
What I mean is that if you want
to amount to something in this job,
you need to start
with a serious investigation.
That's why
you'll be working with me.
Murders. Bank robberies. Muggings.
Are you ready for it, Malinowski?
I am, sir.
I promised your mother that
I'd make a man out of you.
And I do keep my word,
so if you blow it...
...I'll make your time difficult,
understood?
Yes, sir.
Come in.
Excuse me, Superintendent...
Get to the point.
There's been trouble at the hotel.
- Any corpses?
- Four.
This is what I had in mind.
Where?
Can you see what I see, Malinowski?
Are you paying attention?
I am, sir.
What would you call
what you see here?
Fucking Armageddon, sir.
I can see you're getting more
matter-of-fact.
At last something has come up
to liven up this bloody dull weekend.
- What the hell is this?
- Handcuffs. At least they used to be.
Makes you wonder
what they were cuffed to, doesn't it?
- Well, what on Earth has happened
here? - I know as much as you.
- Don't feed me lines.
- I'm not feeding you lines.
What I know is that Norman has been
doing his dirty business in your hotel.
I had nothing to do with it.
But you could...
am I making myself clear?
One of those four suckers
was carrying something, wasn't he?
Oh, I'm so sorry...
It slipped my mind completely...
What was it?
When they were going in one of them
seemed to be carrying a suitcase...
Well, well... a suitcase.
I can see two options: Drugs or fake
dough. Malinowski, what do you reckon?
I think it was dough, sir.
If that's what you think...
it must have been drugs.
- Don't tell me it is him
we are going to. - We are.
Fuck you, Gula. Is this supposed
to be the guy who's got our gats?
He's a fucking twat and piss-head.
You can't rely on him.
Borys's turned over a new leaf.
He only drinks still mineral water now.
For hangover?
Listen, Gula. We have to get the money
from four fucking Russian thugs, today.
And they won't be happy
to give it to us.
- Have you thought about it?
- I have.
So how are we going to protect
ourselves? It's four against two.
We need choppers
to get out of there alive.
Stop bitching out on me,
will you?
- What you hear is not bitching, man.
- What is it then?
Constructive criticism.
- Why does Borys have this nick?
- What nick?
Motherfucker?
They say he's done his own mother.
What do you mean?
He's done her.
With a hammer.
Go on, man.
- What the hell was that?
- Otherwise he won't open up.
- One more time.
- Wait, let me do it.
What the fuck!!!
Get the fuck out of here!
Borys, it's us. Gula and Max.
How am I supposed
to know it's you?
Look through the peephole
you idiot!
I can't see a fuckin' thing.
Move away from the door.
You're sure you're alone?
No, there's Santa here too, but he got
wasted and fell asleep in the sledge.
Really?
For fucks sake, man, open the door.
We're sort of in a hurry.
Paradoxically... I've been
waiting for you.
I've heard
you've given up the booze?
I have. But you know what it's like,
dudes.
A mate from the army
popped in and...
- Have you been in the army?
- No. Why?
- So where is he?
- He's having a rest.
Find yourselves somewhere to sit,
will you.
Right.
What brings you here?
We had a contract, remember?
Ehm... what kind of contract?
You were supposed to do us... a favour.
We've come to collect it.
Right... collect what?
Has your last grey cell evaporated?
Guns, damn it Borys, guns!
Guns! Why didn't you just
say so to start with?
It just... slipped my mind.
Paradoxically.
I'll get it for you.
Give me a moment.
I hope you're not angry
about the door scene.
I just need to double check
who's hanging round here these days.
Take yesterday.
These four funny guys looking like...
- Gypsies?
- How come You know?
I'll tell you some other time.
They said they wanted
to buy a piece.
Don't tell me
you actually sold them one?
I don't trade with just anybody.
I sold those suckers a dud.
A precise copy of Magnum 500,
half an inch caliber...
the biggest there is.
Might rip off your arm
if you try to shoot it.
Are you sure you've actually got guns?
Or was it just in your head?
One moment... I'm not quite sure...
where I've put it.
Guys! I love you...
We'll need help for this job.
- No! Not this gobshite!
- We have to. We're taking Johnny.
- I hate this fag.
- You and I both then.
Hello...
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
I picked up a new bird.
Pop in and meet her.
I'm telling you Max...
...the chick's hot.
Can't pull my dick out.
Has she got... a name?
I call her Chick. But I'm working on
a new nickname.
You have to call everyone names,
don't you?
Ok, I'll tell you,
but keep it to yourself.
I call her Chick cause I'm not so
found of her real name... Zofia!
- Zofia?
- I told you!
She was an unwanted child and her parents
gave her this name that to spite her.
She ran away from home...
cause her stepfather started
flinging at her. Pathetic prick.
- Hey...
- Hey.
Isn't that a bit too scanty?
Put something on.
And? Isn't she hot?
She looks even better
when she tries a little harder.
- How old is she?
- She's old enough.
If she's a minor, she's illegal.
This whole country's illegal.
You've already been up shit creek once,
because of this fifteen-year-old...
- She looked twenty.
- Right.
How was I supposed to know that
her old man was a cop?
- But this one's... OK.
- OK?
- OK, OK?
- OK.
Hey...
Well, I'd like you two to meet.
This is my friend Max.
Hey.
Hello.
Ta-dah!
Hello! Elvis's come to town!
- Lord, I must be hallucinating.
- Are you fuckin' nuts? You look...
Bitchin' awesome!
I don't know
what your plans are but...
I'm gonna mop the floor with
those fuckin' Russians tonight!
Got it from my old man.
Awe-inspiring, don't you think?
Made my willie shrink with terror.
I don't know what the Boss told you,
but there's no way you're going
with us like this. Is that clear?
When those Russians see
two grumpy tuxedos like you
they'll dig up what's going on
in no time! And me?
Ain't I grand?
That's what chill out means.
I'll pull the wool, and then... bang!
Get the piece out and...
Read my mouth.
There'll be no floor mopping.
- Max, say yes!
- Cut it!
Gula, do something
or I'm gonna have a fit.
No... no, no, no.
Same here.
Thanks.
Have you known each other long?
Ever since I remember.
Sounds like a long time, then.
I've known him for two weeks.
- I ran away from home, you know?
- Really?
My old man was pissing me off.
How do you like it?
I liked it more before.
I want you to hang around here a little
and keep your eyes peeled.
There's only one number
on contact list, mine.
Use it as a last resort thing, ok?
Why won't you tell Gula to stand
guard... I want to go with you.
Not this time, man.
It's never the right time.
How am I supposed to learn to be a gangster
if I never even get out of the car?
Scratch my car and you're dead.
I hope they scratch you out there.
There'll come a time when I get to
kill this poof with my bare hands.
Stay centered on
what we're doing here.
What do we do
if things start getting out of hand?
We'll do what we always do.
Play it by ear.
The last time
you played it by ear,
I had to take
a bullet out of your ass.
And trust me, your ass is not a pleasant
view. It's still giving me nightmares.
- Interesting. Have you consulted
a dream-book? - Focus, man.
We must be back before it burns down
to the filter line.
Or else we get our fingers burnt.
You always say this before a job.
But when we're in,
it's you and your big mouth!
Sasha, the Poles are here.
Welcome. How is it going?
Vodka?
Good Russian moonshine.
It clearly is Russian.
But we'll be speaking Polish.
Polish manners...
Hey, you, sit down and drink with us.
Is he always so serious?
Only today.
So, how do you like the house?
Not really.
We'd better talk about money.
- We've got the money.
- If so, I'd like to see it.
Fetch me the bag.
- Is everything ok?
- You were late.
- A wee bit.
- A wee bit. Two weeks.
And so what?
- Do you ever plan anything up front?
- Sorry?
Do you ever plan
what you do up front?
Just like everybody else.
You see... the thing is, we always
have a very precise plan.
Now according to this plan the money was
supposed to be invested two weeks ago.
And by now the amount
would have doubled.
The people we were to do business
with couldn't wait for so long.
I don't know what it's like
where you come from, but here...
we expect punctuality.
Get it?
If you're not happy,
get the bag and get out!
From what I've heard it takes
some effort to find a new supplier.
And you wouldn't be saying this
unless you have already made
a deal with someone else.
Do you know what I think?
I think the money here
is only a bait.
And you'll put a bullet in my
brain as soon as I turn around.
Let's take it easy, shall we?
I've done some talking here and
there but it was only... consulting.
I'm sure we can work it out somehow,
can't we?
What's up?
Guys, are you done yet?
I'm bored out of my skull.
You're not going to kill Johnny.
I will.
Are you alright?
Johnny, why didn't you tell me anything?
It's time to brag a little bit.
Brag about what?
Picking the hottest hunk in town.
What do you know about
a true male friendship?
So that's what it's called
these days, huh?
I didn't know that every time
I was banging a chick
I was actually... making friends.
You oaf.
My new boyfriend
is a very special man.
He's so sweet and understanding...
...and his ass smells of violets!
Look who's talking!
Our girl-lover.
And you guys, when it's over,
when you're getting out of bed...
...do you talk of art
and the meaning of life?
You're getting on my nerves.
I think the most exciting thing
about a woman is her brains.
Shagging a bimbo
is like jerking off.
How do you know?
Not only is she thick
but apparently blind, too.
I wonder what she sees in you.
Even...
if I was a desperate whore without a penny,
I would never shag with you.
Ditto.
Speaking of which, I've been wondering,
what is it like between you fags?
I mean two guys together,
how does it work technically?
Do you mean sex?
For lack of a better word.
The name's irrelevant.
When I'm with my partner...
...or, technically speaking,
when my partner is in me, 'cause
I guess that's what you want to know...
I'm trying not to think
about the discomfort
but focus on how beautiful it is
to give something to a loved person...
And that, naturally, at some point
we'll get to swap roles.
Jesus... thank God there's no such
issue with women.
Well, it depends.
Huh? On what?
You may come across one
who will stick a dildo up your ass.
Wow, at last, at last!
Seriously.
I know one who would.
She won't shag with you
unless you do it for her.
Everybody knows you've got
a whole lot of inspiring friends.
I guess. After all, I know you.
So did you... sleep with her?
Only once.
Damn! This bloody dildo was the size
of a baguette. Anyway, it felt like that.
I'll be stuffed!
A guy who calls himself a gangster
had a fake shlong up his butt.
- When send word to the boys...
- Say a word and you're dead, man.
I know now why you're so curious
to learn more about anal sex.
It was just this one time. I was young.
It was the experimenting stage.
Clearly the experience
has left lasting trauma...
There's only one perv among us!
There are more and more queers
and you can't do anything about it.
- There'll be one less when I bust you.
- Go fuck your new girlfriend...
- Stop it!
- Crypto gay!
- Faggot!
- I won't take it anymore.
- I said stop it!
I'm going to the loo...
Hey, did you have a good look
at his new lady? I mean her mouth?
- Her lips are full.
- Full?
Critical for a good blow job, man.
Trust me. I know what I'm saying.
I'm sure you do.
And her feet?
Have you seen her feet?
- I can see you did have a good look.
- They're gigantic, man.
I'd never seen anything like that.
I was even going
to borrow her shoes, but I'd drown.
Zip it.
With these feet, she could squeeze
cabbage juice in two barrels at once.
- You'd better shut up when
he's around, OK? - OK.
Max... uh,
have you heard that someone managed
to capture Yeti, the Bigfoot, on film.
You know, half man, half bear, living up
in the mountains.
Come on, Bigfoot's a myth.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Max, what do you reckon?
Hey, this isn't fair. You can't blame her
for having big feet.
Please, it's not mine either, is it now?
Ok, fine! You come out on top!
I almost forgot about her huge feet.
God, how can you be living
under the same roof pretending
that everything's fine when it's not?
Say one more thing
about her feet and...
I wouldn't be able to get over the thought
of this minor imperfection.
Shut up.
She's like an expensive sports car...
with bird crap on the windscreen!
I don't want to see the two of you
together ever again!
Take a taxi.
Why is it always me
who gets back by taxi?
Naff off man!
Ok. I'm getting the fuck out of here.
See you later, Max.
And piss on you, Gula.
Get in the car.
Now by the very fact
of being in this job
we often face the necessity
of contacting a specific social class
called berks, airheads, boobies...
and generally people less intelligent
than a dog...
I mean a dafter breed,
like a Doberman.
Here's a typical representative
of this group.
Now, hypothetically, let's assume we're
in the following operational situation.
This is your suspect and you're
carrying out the interrogation.
You want to get him to talk.
What would you do?
What do I want to know?
Nevermind... say, what time it is.
Oh, right, I see...
Excuse me,
have you got the time?
Go on, go on!
Tell me what time it is, smeghead,
or I'll kick your ass.
Act this lively and they'll
take away your sick benefit, son.
What's wrong with you, Malinowski?
He's even still got his cap on.
My mother-in-law is breezier than this,
and she's in a wheelchair.
It's us or them, Malinowski.
If you're not tough
they'll eat you alive.
Here, let me show you
how to do this properly.
The time, retard, tell me the time
or I'll bite your head off!
The time...
Get it, you son-of-a-bitch?
Like a fat cock bursting the cherry,
Malinowski. Knock him out.
Are you with me?
I get it.
If you ask a question in this way,
you're bound to receive an answer.
Unless the guy has lost his watch.
Yes, I can see your point.
Come on in, boys
please, take your seats.
Would you like some snacks?
How about a fresh, home-made
bread roll? They're excellent.
- We've just eaten.
- I'll have one.
I always pig out
when I have a shitty day.
And I don't give a damn
about putting on weight.
Quite right, boss.
So, tell me, how did it go?
They weren't too eager
to give the money back.
I hope they were the first
to start shooting.
Uhm uhm.
Look, boss, they wanted to fuck with us.
There was no other way.
Norman?
He'd made a deal with them.
This bandit is getting cheeky!
And what about Johnny?
Is he a no-hoper?
He was standing guard.
Will he amount to something
in this business?
He's got a lot of enthusiasm.
Fuck! I can't stand it!
Why is this
happening to me?
My own son being a... a...
...queer?
- Queer!
If he wasn't my son I'd personally
break his fuckin' neck long ago.
Shut the fuck up!
But tha'is just a side plot,
let's get back to the point.
There's a new door-to-door salesman
in town
who offers to sell loads of smack
at a very good price.
Who is it?
It's a woman.
Max! Max, wake up.
I've arranged for an appointment
in our office tomorrow.
You're going to buy
half a kilo to test it first.
Play for time if you can but
don't scare her away.
If everything goes smoothly we'll
close the deal in a few days' time.
Here's the money.
No, gentlemen,
you've got it all wrong!
I wish I'd been born thirty years earlier.
But what's gone is gone, damn it.
Now... where were we?
Right, I was saying how much
I hated to use names...
since it may lead you to get too
friendly with the customer.
But since I have to communicate
with you somehow
I'm gonna give you numbers.
Now note that the numbers
are related to your assignments,
so there's no chance of swapping.
Were you going to say something?
Now I'll take this tape off
but you have to be quiet.
My mum lives upstairs
and she really hates noise.
- Give me another chance.
- Are you going to give the money back?
That's not what I meant.
Let's make a deal.
What do you think? Should I
'make a deal' with him?
Ok, here's what we'll do.
I count to three.
If you can get a million bucks to jump
out of your ass, you're free to go.
Now if I was to squeeze
a million bucks out of mine,
I'd try real hard... so you'd better do
your best 'cause you'll only have one go.
Are you centered? Focused? Fine.
Ready, steady, go! One... Two... Three!!!
One!
Taking into account the case of number one,
does anyone else want another chance?
What's up?
- What is it? You're making my clients
suspicious... - You have to help me. Now.
'Have to'? 'Now'? Really?
Stefan, fuck,
they've gunned down my men!
Seems like you'd pissed someone off.
What have you done?
I have no time for bullshit.
I need to get the product back
before it gets on the market.
- And you're gonna help me do it.
- Why would I help you?
Cause you're one greedy bastard,
and I pay well.
What's it gonna be then?
I want 20%.
Stefan, damn it,
nobody pays that much.
It's gonna make you
the first one ever, isn't it?
20%.
Not a bloody penny less.
You wouldn't do that
if I wasn't in a deadlock.
In this industry,
everyone's in a deadlock.
I'll give you 10%.
15%.
And you don't interfere
with my sidelines. Deal?
Deal. But you're starting now.
If this shit is no good...
You'll be coming back for more.
You can thank me later.
Hey, Baldy,
someone wants to see you.
Baldy, get in the car!
- I'm outta here.
- Me, too. See ya.
Don't even think about it.
Why don't they
ever listen to me?
For fucks sake, Baldy,
I'm gonna get you anyway...
I was in a good mood.
And you've ruined everything.
Do you like my shoes? Ace, huh?
I think you should have a closer look.
They look awesome
but are fuckin' of tight.
If I had wanted to go jogging,
I'd have put on sneakers.
- Fuck off!
- Why did you make a bolt for it anyway?
I owe money, I run.
I thought you were here to do me in.
Do you, you plank?
You're a bloody retailer.
What the fuck do you want then?
Mind your manners!
What can I do for you?
I'm looking for merchandise,
and I need some advice.
I know nothing.
In a second
I'm gonna shit down your lungs
and you'll have bad breath
till the end of your life.
- But I might find out.
- Now, that's better.
Take my advice. Don't play the giddy goat.
Get in the car. Slowly.
My corn hurts.
I'm gonna wait one more minute.
If your buddy doesn't call,
we're going to the garage.
What the fuck is this?
- I got a text message.
- Where d'you get such ringtone from?
- From the web.
- Don't be such a whiz.
That's the contact for the bloke
you're looking for.
This much I can see myself.
Are you sure it's him?
This guy's tipped everybody off that
he was expecting a shed-load of drugs.
He's already got a line of
dealers waiting.
No kidding!
That's what the boys say.
They'd better be right or else
I stomp a mug hole in your ass.
Can I go now?
Baldy's done his job,
Baldy's free to do a bunk!
- Can I have my phone?
- You can get smacked in the jaw.
Listen carefully.
There's been some talk that there's
a 'big deal' coming up in town.
Big deal, like in the movies.
What's a 'big deal', boss?
Thick as two short planks.
You don't know what 'big deal' is?
You want me to tell you
what 'big deal' is?
You don't know what 'big deal' is?
'Big deal' is...
tell the man what it means.
In American English,
it means 'an important transaction'.
Big deal.
Trans-action.
Precisely.
We just have to find out
where and when.
And then we can get both drugs
and beans in one go.
I've got everything planned.
And if you screw up
like you did last time...
Boss, it was you
who screwed up the last time...
And the one the time before...
Oh! But it's gonna be different
this time, right?
And you know why?
Because this time
we're going the whole hog!
If anyone kicks up, bang!
Bullet in the head.
That's what I've got myself
a piece for, right?
There!
What is this?
It's a car.
It's a piece of crap.
You were supposed to get me a CAR.
There only was this so I took it.
Where did you get it from?
A special offer at the junkyard?
I borrowed it from my brother.
Boss, we'd better take this
one than hoof it.
Amen to that.
Who the fuck do I have to work with?
Get in the car!
Leave the bottle.
Don't get me wrong, but...
you've been coming here too often
and drinking too much.
Would you like to talk about it?
I miss her too, she was like a daughter
to me, you know that...
I know what you're going to say
and I appreciate it.
But it's none of your business.
You've got a very dynamic drive style.
Deep down we're all road hogs, man.
Don't step on it any harder
or we might travel in time.
Stop the fuckin' car!
Not right in the middle
of the fuckin' road!
Go back and park behind
that Mercedes, I know this car.
I'm picking up some
good vibes, gentlemen.
Look what you've done, you twit.
- What I've done?!
- Yes, you, you airhead.
You seem to be having
shitty day, amigo!
Do you always
make an entrance like this?
What, you're not scared?
If I were you I'd shit myself.
First you break my friend's furniture,
and then you threaten me with a gun.
It makes me annoyed, not scared.
What the hell???
But sometimes annoyance
may turn into rage.
I wouldn't like so I suggest you
pay for the damage and leave.
Are you fuckin' blind man?
Can't you see I've got a piece?
- Gentlemen, please...
- You stay out of it.
There's talk of a 'big deal' in town.
Tell me what you know or...
you'll have an extra hole in your head.
- Are you sure you know how to use it?
- What kind of question is this?
Prove it.
Can you see this teapot?
I'll bet you can't hit it
from a distance of one meter.
Bets must be your weakness, man.
One meter...
And... what if I win?
I'll tell you all I know
about the big deal.
I must ask out of curiosity,
what happens if...
...you don't hit the target?
- Let's assume that.
You'll have to apologise to my friend,
pay for the damage and leave politely.
You see, boys, that's what
hitting the right tone is all about.
Will you be all right?
Fair enough.
- Who the hell are you?
- An oversized dwarf.
No doubts about that.
Stop!
He's too high.
A word of advice. Don't act a hero,
just start talking.
Sooner or later I'll make you squeal.
I'll turn your arse into
a still nature painting.
This toy has five gears and that was the
low one. Start singing before I change up.
I'll make you die a painful death.
One gear up
and we're having a ball already.
I can see you want
to make it to the top.
Are you gonna ask him
about the suitcase or not?
Stay put, you back seat driver,
will you?
I haven't got a clue
what you're talking about.
A suitcase, filled to the brim
with merchandise. Does it ring a bell?
- I haven't got it.
- I'm changing up again.
I'm going to buy it, though.
I see. Interesting.
When, where and from whom?
- I only know when. In two days.
- Where and from whom?
I don't know that.
She picks the spot.
It's a she?
Yes. She. Female gender.
Norman, you never said
you got rolled by female gender.
Shut your gob and get the job done.
- In two days, is it?
- In two days. The day after tomorrow.
In that case, I'm gonna have to ask you
to cancel all previous arrangements.
You're spending the weekend with me.
What are you doing?
You've got to gank him.
Jesus. I am deeply surprised
with your ignorance.
What if he's dealing funk?
You know best how
to make him tell the truth.
I may do, but it's sort of hard
to verify at the moment.
There's nothing else to do but wait.
Fuck, whatever, do what you want.
What matters is the drugs.
But when it's over, you're gonna
do him or his men will go after us.
Don't teach your dick how to suck eggs.
Now, bring him down.
Stop. Down, man. Down.
Do I have to do everything myself?