# Under the sun, under the sun #
- # Under the sun, under the sun #
- X! Yo, X!
Hey, man, stop playing around.
For real, man.
You skating or what?
- Yeah, let's go.
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on.
South Side!
Attention, all you wallflowers...
and all you seat warmers.
This is D.J. Smooth Dee talking...
telling you, get on the floor...
and skate till
you can't skate anymore.
'Cause after today, the Garden
will be closing its doors indefinitely.
And if you don't know
what "indefinitely" means...
you shouldn't be
in here skating anyway.
You should have your ass
in summer school.
I say it with love, people.
I say it with love.
So get up out your seat.
We'll turn this mother-sucker out.
All-skate, people.
This is an all-skate.
# Rock, skate #
# Roll, bounce #
# Roller skaters celebrate
the disco wave #
# Give your feet the freedom
Let's bounce today #
# Roller skaters, one in front
and one behind #
# Bounce left, bounce right
It's disco time #
# Ain't no stopping
Keep on rocking#
# This funky kind of music seems
to take you by the hands #
# Bounce left, go on and #
# Bounce #
- # Rock, skate #
- Watch out, girl!
# Roll, bounce #
# Rock, skate #
Come on, Junior.
- Here we go. Here we go.
- # Rock, skate #
All right, fellas. Let's form
this train, y'all. Come on. Come on.
Whooooo!
Whoo! Whoo!
The boys is doing it!
Them little boys is bad.
Whoo!
Ooh!
Boy, hit my butt again
and see what happens!
Ooh! Ooh!
- # Rock, skate #
- Ooh! Y'all make me sick.
- Whoo!
- # Roll, bounce ##
Dang.
There goes our summer.
For real. I mean, y'all,
this is jacked up.
Damn, Naps.
I know you ain't crying.
No. My eyes just water
like this sometimes.
- I have a condition.
- You ain't got no condition.
Only condition you need to have
is some for that hair.
Man, we can't keep nothing
open in the hood.
How much of them dumb mothers
gonna go broke all of a sudden?
Shoot, Negro, you'll go broke too
if you had 15 kids.
- Sixteen.
- Fifteen, 16, 36, whatever.
That Negro got a whole football
"and" a basketball team.
Blue 42!
- Yeah, but I wonder what they're gonna build there.
- Come on now, X
You know what they're
gonna build there.
Same thing they always build.
Either a gun shop...
- Barbecue shack.
- Chicken spot.
- Liquor store.
- Or all four in one.
I hope they build that chicken spot.
Ooh, that'd be nice.
I guess we gotta go over
to Sweetwater to skate now.
Mike, you're stupid.
Look, I'm not going all the way
over to no North Side to go skate.
Why not, X? You're afraid you can't
compete with those North Side boys, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
- Who said I was afraid?
Look, bottom line is
I don't wanna go over there.
X just doesn't wanna run into that ug mug
he took to the movies last time.
- Yep. Mm-hmm.
- Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Naomi? Naomi the duck.
- Chick's so ugly, every time you see her, you gotta duck.
- Duck!
Watch out. Quack.
Hey, I heard Sweetwater has
some nice-looking girls though.
- For white girls.
- So? My mom's white, Junior.
It's cool. She got a black woman's body,
so it don't count.
She good.
She cool. Mm-hmm.
No! Didn't I tell you to keep my mom's
name out your mouth? Huh?
Man, get back on your bike, man!
She's got a apple shape.
I look sometimes.
- Hey, I say we go up there.
- Listen, Boo, all right?
I'm not... Hey!
Look at his wheel!
Man, I told you to stop rolling around
on those Buster Brown Goodwill skates.
- Didn't I say that?
- Uh-huh. Sure, you're right.
For real, X, man. It's time
to chuck them bad boys.
Hey, my mom bought me
these skates, okay?
Your mom bought 'em for you, and we
can't even talk about your old-ass skates.
Man, Harriet Tubman wore them skates.
She skated her way to freedom.
# I's be skating my way to freedom #
- # For freedom, freedom, freedom ##
- Look, man, these are not old.
They're classics.
Yeah, you know,
like your mama's hairdo.
- Whoa!
- He got you.
She still singing
with the Supremes, right?
- # Bald and beautiful #
- Bald "and" beautiful.
# Bald and beautiful
Bald and beautiful ##
Oh, snap! Later.
Oh, shoot. Junior, sorry.
Yes!
I made it. I made it.
Daddy! X is late again!
Girl, shh! Oh, girl, you better
not let me catch you. Come here!
Xavier.
- Huh?
- Boy, get your butt out here.
Man, I hate her.
You're pushing it, son.
Really pushing it.
What, Dad?
I beat the light.
Did I say anything
about a streetlight, Xavier?
I asked you to be home early so we can get
these gutters cleaned out, didn't I?
- Oh, yeah.
Boy, this ain't
a Kool-Aid commercial.
Dad, the Gardens
closed down today for good.
- I had to be there.
- No, son.
You had to be here.
Okay? Here.
Now, look,
I know it's summertime.
You wanna be running the streets
with the Mod Squad...
but I'm gonna need
your help around here.
It's just us now, son.
I'm gonna need you to step up.
You understand what I'm saying to you, son?
Yes, sir.
Xavier.
Xavier. Come on, now. Let's go.
Trash day. What? Did you forget?
Oh, shoot! The trash!
- Ahh.
- Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Don't try to move 'em now.
You know we don't like backtracking.
Yeah, we're highly
opposed to backtracking.
My fault. Look, I'll just bring 'em out
at night next time.
Bring 'em out at night? No, you ain't gonna
just bring 'em out at night next time.
What, so the German shepherd and the pit bull
puppies could snatch the bag outta there...
and have empty diapers
and cigarette wrappers...
and Snickers wrappers and Stayfree boxes
laid all out in the middle of the street?
Yeah. Then the neighbors call in
down to the plant complaining.
- Right.
- Talking about how we didn't do our job correctly.
And then we get complaints
and warnings from our boss.
- Then after the warning comes a demerit.
- Right.
And when you get to three demerits,
you know what happens then?
- A nigger lose his job!
- Oh, God, man.
- His house! His family!
- Yeah.
Get kicked out of church 'cause you no
longer got money for the collection plate.
- They want you out.
- Right.
- All because you bringing out the garbage late.
- That's right.
And I'm telling you straight up,
man, if I lose my job, man...
you're gonna put on a little Evel Knievel suit
and sell some dimes and nicks on a Big Wheel.
You're gonna get my money
some kinda way!
Yeah. Then, 'cause of our rock-hard bodies
we developed from lifting trash...
Right.
- We end up in the alley as prostitutes.
- Right.
Righ...
- Yeah, that's right! You too!
- I don't know about all that.
Yeah, it could happen. You end up
in the alley with the shirt off, sweaty.
- Selling.
- Right.
Not for money! Just for a bite
off the mars hamburger.
The point is we trying to make: Don't mess
with the Department of Sanitation...
or you will come up dirty!
Hey! Hey, hey.
Good God!
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Duncan Hines.
Mmm. Look at her.
Skin just glittering.
Oh, yeah.
Whoo! Boy!
Lord have mercy.
Is that a Lustrasilk?
Look at how her hair blows.
Look at her.
Look at the walk.
Chocolate city.
That must be jelly, 'cause
jam don't shake like that.
Yeah, I'm outta here.
See ya later, little man.
Hey, lookit here.
Why don't you check your package.
- You got a little fruit hanging out of the loom.
- Huh?
- Oh, man.
- Daddy, can we please go to McDonald's?
No, honey. It's too early now.
I gotta go to work. Come...
- Where are your clothes?
- Um, Dad...
Never mind. I'm taking your sister to Pam's
house to play, and then I gotta go to work.
Dad, shouldn't you comb her hair first?
I did comb it.
Looks good.
In the car, honey.
Anyway, I'm outta here.
Don't burn down my house.
And put some clothes on, boy. This ain't
Africa. What's the matter with you?
Hey, Curt! What's up, baby?
Mr. Astronomical Man!
Hey, Byron, Victor.
Boy, you know I wanna be
just like you when I grow up.
Wear the jeans with the whole sweater
tucked down in the pants.
Oh, boy.
No, man, all jokes aside, man, how the
airplane engineering business treating you?
Never better, brother.
Never better.
"Never better, brother.
Never better. "
Cool it, man.
Curtis Uncle Tom, man.
Damn! So what you think about me,
man, if you think he's Uncle Tom?
He ain't down with the struggle
like you and me.
- That dude voted for Nixon.
- You're right about that.
Can I take a message?
Sure. You can try back in about an hour.
All right. Thank you.
Yes. Good morning. Hi.
Good morning. I'm Curtis Smith. I'm here
to apply for the engineering position.
I'm sorry, but that position
has already been filled. Sorry.
- Good morning. McGill and White.
How may I help you?
What the...
Hey! How you doing? All right.
Ahh!
Whoo!
Hey, man!
Hey, how you doing,
Mr. Johnson? All right.
What the... Boy, what you doing?
All right, here he comes.
Arm yourselves.
Oh!
Hey! Hey, come on, man! Stop it!
Stop playing!
Get him!
Little punks!
Oh, sh...
Whew.
It's 97 degrees on the South Side.
Hey, Mr. Walker.
- Hi.
- Whoa!
- Oh!
- Oh, shoot!
- Oh, man.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- All right. I just wanted to...
- Yeah, I'm cool.
- I wanted to make sure.
- Just breaking in some skates.
Tori. My mom and I
just moved in over there.
Oh, okay. I'm X.
Oh, okay. I think I seen your mom
take out the trash last week.
Mm, black woman, skintight jeans,
wearing a top with no bra on?
- Uh, look, I don't...
- Yeah, that was her.
She know she be working it.
So, man, I see you skating.
Um, you a skater?
Yeah, I... My daddy sent these for me.
He lives in Atlanta
with his new wife... a white woman.
But I ain't mad. Shoot, she's rich.
What about you?
Do you have any brothers or sisters?
Well, yeah, I have a little sister.
She's five going on 40.
And then there's my dad.
Well, no comment.
What about the people here?
- What about 'em?
- You know. They all nice like you?
Yeah, of course.
I mean, this is a nice city.
- They're all nice like me.
- Oh, really?
Yeah. Better yet,
I'm gonna prove it to you.
- Hey, guys, this is Tori.
- Hi.
Damn!
Dang, girl! Did a whole silverware drawer
explode in your mouth?
I'm just saying, Amtrak called. They said
they need some of their tracks back.
Lay me some tracks. Come on.
Look, don't trip on him, all right?
He's always like this.
Oh, don't worry. I'm not.
I know punk rides
on the short yellow bus.
- Ooh!
- Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Heavy metal? I know
you don't wanna start.
- Yeah, you don't wanna start.
- Because I ain't the one.
- He ain't the one.
- See, look at you.
Your mouth look like a daggone
tin foil factory! That's what it look like.
Well, at least I'm getting my teeth corrected.
- Look at yours.
- What?
You need to stop chewing
on them yellow crayons...
and start scrubbing with
some Colgate, yuck mouth.
She called you yuck mouth!
What?
See, that ain't fair.
You can't say "yuck mouth. "
Because I'm allergic
to toothpaste anyway.
And I was eating Cheetos.
Look, look, forget you.
All right? I got you.
I got something for you.
Why you laugh at that, man?
- 'Cause it's funny, yuck mouth.
- Yo, X
We're going over to Sweetwater to check it out
and maybe even get a glimpse at Sweetness.
- What's a Sweetness? - Only the baddest
mo-fo to ever slap on a pair of skates.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, best on the North Side.
- I mean, not over here.
- Man, whatever.
He wins the skate-off
every year. Dude is good.
Hey, I heard he had his own
"theme music, like on" Baretta.
- He ain't got no theme music.
- And I heard that one time...
some fool challenged Sweetness
in the middle of the rink to a skate-off.
He made homeboy look so bad
that he went number two on himself.
- Stop jiving, man. You're lying.
- Man, I swear.
Number two in white jeans.
He boo-booed on himself.
- Nasty.
- "So, X, man, you coming or what?
Guys, how come we just can't skate
over here like we been doing?
X, stop being a little punk, man.
Look, we'll have you home
before the streetlight come on, all right?
- Yeah.
- Look, my boy's coming.
Cool. I'm coming too.
Oh, he-he-hell, no.
Junior, man, come on!
- Can you even skate?
- Yeah.
Yeah? Just don't fall on your face.
It's already hurt enough.
Boy, don't touch my face.
Hey, y'all, be quiet. Shh.
A moment of silence for her face, please.
All right. Amen.
Hallelujah. Let's go.
That's messed up, yuck mouth.
Let's do this.
- Oh, I'm telling you!
- Hey, man, we're gonna have a good time at Sweetwater.
I promise, man. Look at this.
My goodness! Whoo!
Hey, see that right there? They got video games.
Can I get your name?
Excuse me! Your number?
Dang, this place is live.
I could live up in here.
- Me too.
- For real.
I didn't expect all of... this.
What was that?
- I don't know.
- Was that a girl or a guy?
- Why you do that?
- Hey, man, this place has everything.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, everything...
but some real music.
Okay, I mean,
the Gardens used to bump.
- Yeah, that's true.
- What? Boy, this is a jam.
# In the words of a broken heart #
# It's just emotion
that's taken me over #
- She's crazy.
- #Tied up in sorrow #
"Emotion" by the Bee Gees!
The Bee whats?
Come on! Y'all never
heard of the Bee Gees?
No. But it sound like something
my cousin caught from his girlfriend.
I heard it make your balls fall off.
- Fo... For real?
- Yeah, so watch out.
- Yo! Check this out!
- What?
Whoo! Ha! Now this
is what I'm talking about.
"Come compete
in this year's skate-off.
"Show your talents in group
roller dancing competition.
Grand prize $500!"
You know what I could buy with $500?
Hopefully a comb, Naps.
Well, guys, I'm good.
I've seen enough.
- What?
- X, we just got here, man. What are you talking about?
For real, man.
Why are you acting all funky?
- Man, I'm not acting all funky.
- You are too.
Plus there's way too much new booty
for us to be jaw-jacking with you.
- For real. I'm renting skates.
- I'm with you, Naps.
- Come on. Come on.
- Let's pick up the pace...
and groove to the sound
of the real thing.
"Can You Feel the Force. '
Excuse me?
Excuse me!
Excuse me.
Y'all need something?
- Nine.
- Right, nine. Right.
No, man. These are 12's.
I asked for nines.
Oh, my fault, little man.
Well? Could you go get 'em?
Hey, man, I can't be wearing
these big old boats.
- You know...
- Check this out, young blood.
You're gonna wear whatever
skates Bernard gives you.
Dig that?
Don't start nothing.
Won't be nothing.
We cool? Be cool.
Oh, baby, you're so smart.
- Don't forget fine.
- That dude was crazy!
Really.
Look likeJimi Hendrix.
- Oh, damn!
- What? What?
"Diablo" mama!
- Damn.
- Ooh.
"Love to Love You. 'I do.
Be cool. She coming. Don't look.
Hey, baby.
- Hi, Xavier.
- What?
- Naomi?
- Yes.
How are you?
Oh, I-I'm fine.
- So when did you start coming here?
- Is that the duck?
- Oh, well, this is the first time down here.
- Damn!
See, the Gardens
got closed down, so...
They closed the Gardens?
I didn't know that.
Hmm.
Like it.
Um, are these your friends?
Yeah. Uh, this is Mike,
Boo, Junior, Naps...
and, uh, that's Tori.
- Hi.
- Can't call it. Can't call it.
- Hi. How's it...
- Shh.
- What?
- You're messing it up!
Those lips hit my neck.
You look great.
Yeah, so do you.
He ain't lying.
So I'll have to tell my mom
that I ran into you.
Oh, okay.
Come here.
Um, I never had a chance to tell you...
but I'm really sorry about your mom.
Oh, it's fine. Really.
- What she say?
- Shh, shh.
She said something
about a ham sandwich.
No, I know, but I just wanted you
to know that I am sorry.
Naomi, really, it...
Would you look at that?
Five hundred!
- I'm fine.
- All right.
Coming through! Coming through!
Move! Move! Get out of the way!
Y'all know what's going on.
Make room for Mr. Fantastic.
The pretty boy.
He's super bad!
- He's super bad.
- Super fly.
- He's fly.
- Baddest mo-fo on eight wheels.
Make some noise for...
Sweet... ness!
Chill.
- Sweetness, you're so fine!
- Yes, you are!
- Junior!
- I was talking to Tootsie!
- Hold yourself together, Tori.
- Cape.
- Lint.
Be careful, honey.
Towel.
Look at that chest, baby.
No!
Mine.
I'll skate now.
Sweetness. Aha. He's too cool.
Boogie on down.
See? See? I told you Sweetness
had his own theme music.
Damn the music.
Sweetness got the honeys.
I think Tootsie is scoping me.
Here, Tootsie, Tootsie, Tootsie!
Man, I hope she don't
got the Bee Gees.
I guess everybody loves
Sweetness around here, huh?
Not everybody.
Naomi!
- What, Troy?
- Come on, now.
You don't have to get
all attitude on me.
I thought we were cool. Hey, what's up
with that fake number you gave me?
Yeah, what's up with the fake digits?
It wasn't fake.
They just weren't mine.
Okay. Okay.
I see how it is. Okay, so you won't give
me... me... your number?
Instead you give it to a raggedy dude
with a crooked-ass 'fro.
Yeah.
Whatever.
- I'll see you later, X.
- All right.
Excuse me.
Hey, Roy. Roy, check 'em out.
Check 'em out.
I'm checking. I'm checking.
Wearing them hand-me-down skates.
I mean, come on.
Who y'all supposed to be,
the food stamp crew?
No, no, man. These are the welfare rollers.
Man, I know you ain't talking with them
American Bandstand glittery pants on.
What? What? You crazy?
These are the threads of champions.
Sweetwater Rollers,
group skate champions.
Five years running, baby.
Dig it.
"Sweetwater Rollers.
Five years running, baby. "
- Until now.
- Dig that!
- John Travolta!
- Is this a challenge, Mr. Mouth?
Whatever you want it to be, Kung Fu.
You just say when.
Right now, Cosby kids.
Come on.
Why don't you bring your old Salvation Army
rent-a-skate crew out here right now, punks!
Man, you ain't said nothing but a word.
You'll see, Jackson Five.
What the hell was that?
I don't know, man. Hey, look, let's
show these dudes how we do it on the...
South Side!
- Can I come too? 'Cause I...
- No.
Hell, no.
I didn't want to skate
with them anyway. Aah!
Yeah!
Oh, shoot! Come on, Junior.
Come on, Boo.
Dang, y'all!
I said size nine! Size nine!
- Dang, they're too far ahead.
- All right, X man. Cut through the middle.
- Come on. Come on, y'all.
- Hell, yeah.
Come on, y'all.
We gotta catch up.
- Man, that Chinese boy's fast.
- Let's get the train together.
Watch out!
Y'all go on.
You're all weak anyways.
- Uh-huh.
- A bunch of suckers.
- Yo, they was doing moves I never even seen before.
- Whatever.
[X
Yeah, they were pretty good.
- Whatever, man. It's home court advantage. Don't even count.
- Whatever, Junior.
- I'm about to go to the snack bar and get an Icee or something.
- I'm with you, man.
- Boo, you okay?
- Man, my eye's acting up.
Man, I'm renting new skates.
- I'm... I'm gonna go sit down.
- Y'all go on.
I'm about to get me some ofTootsie.
Here, Tootsie, Tootsie, Tootsie.
That thing that you're doing...
kind of like a twist, like you're jumping...
- and then kind of like...
- Tori, Tori, please, okay?
- I'm telling you...
- Please!
Gotcha!
Oh!
Oh, damn. Junior!
- He's got a woody!
- Shut up! Shut up!
My baby's big.
Damn.
Shut up! Shut up! First of all, they're
support briefs, and all the athletes wear 'em.
Wilt Chamberlain,
Kareem Abdul-Jabaar, O.J. Simpson.
They said they make you run faster.
All the ones that wear bras!
Shut up!
- I'll show you something big!
- Hey, man, this ain't funny!
This is not no joke. These dudes
don't even respect us.
They just chalk us up to be some poor
ghetto boys from the South Side...
that don't even have a pot to piss in.
And that's not even us.
We're them boys used to go down
to the Gardens to skate our asses off.
Now, I know I was the one
against going over there...
but now, fellas, we gotta go there.
Get back on top, no matter what.
We need to kick ass
at this skate-off come August.
- I see somebody got their balls off layaway.
- Yeah, whatever.
You just stop wearing purple panties...
and start putting lotion
on your ashy butt.
Hey, where we from, y'all?
South Side!
Hey, there's a homey right there!
What?
Bad dream?
All right. Come on.
- Xavier?
- Go to sleep.
What was Mom like?
Huh?
Tell me what she was like again.
Well...
she was a lot like you.
She was... She was always fantasizing
like she was somebody else.
Diana Ross, Tina Turner.
But she couldn't sing though.
- No?
- No, not a lick.
See, me and Dad didn't have
the heart to tell her...
so we would just
sit back on the couch...
and she'd just let it rip.
Yeah, Mom was so pretty.
Dad would always tell me...
"Son, God must really like us. "
Back then you couldn't
keep Dad from smiling.
But when he looks at you...
he gets that same grin on his face...
just like when he used to look at Mom.
Mom was like an angel.
A black angel?
Yeah, I guess so.
Have a good time, son. Make sure
you hold your sister's hand.
- And spend all his money, honey.
- Nice meeting you, Mr. Smith.
Uh-huh.
Oh, baby, I love you.
- Yes, you do.
- I love you.
And I love you back.
I gotcha.
Size 12!
What it is.
So?
You know, the ladies,
they can't get enough of Bernard.
I think it's the lips. You know,
not too pouty, not too brave.
You know, firm and tender like sirloin.
I used to do lip exercises on my pillow.
And a-one and two...
Can I get a size nine, please!
Now. Today. "Ahora. "
All right, 'fro magnum.
Dude, calm down.
Trying to bond with a brother, man.
That's all.
You ain't trying to bond with me.
You done gave me my skates a long
time ago, I wouldn't have to be waiting.
Dude, these are size 15's!
Man, why you keep doing me like this?
Check this out.
The ladies around here...
like a brother with a big... skate.
You got a size 17
back there, Bernard?
Size 17 back there, Bernard?
Talking my talk now.
Let me get you the...
Bye, X.
I told you I didn't want to bring her.
Oh, she don't wanna be with you.
She's going over there.
Look who it is.
'Sup, X? And how'd you get in, Jaws?
I see the metal detector
must be broken.
I don't know.
Ask your big-boned mama.
She the one working the door.
She got you again, Junior.
- You two need to quit, okay?
- Oh, don't talk to me.
Talk to him.
Stupid.
Oh, no, man. There go them dude
in them tights again. He look fruity.
- What is wrong with him?
- Whatever. Hey, yo, X, lace up.
I was watching "Kung Fu Theater. "
I know this move we could use.
- All right.
- All right. Yo. Hey.
Man, your friends are so stupid.
Hey, you're just now figuring that out?
I know. Right.
Session two is now beginning.
This next skate
will be for couples only.
This is a couples' skate.
- Oh, look, look, look.
- What? What?
There goes your other friend.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Hey, X.
- Hi.
- How are you doing?
So, how's everything going?
Everything's cool. Cool.
And real cool.
So?
Isn't this couples' skate?
You two should go skate.
I don't mind.
Thank you. I mean...
Hey, I remember those.
You've had those for a long time.
Your mom gave 'em to you
on your 13th birthday, right?
Right.
So, you wanna go
get out there together?
Uh, I can't.
I ate something today...
and my stomach is acting up,
and I don't think...
It's okay. It's okay.
Maybe another time.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
What a doof!
What's happening?
Hello?
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Hello.
I'm Vivian. Vivian Turner,
your new neighbor.
Oh. Hi. I'm Curtis.
Uh, yeah. I just got home from work,
and I got this note from my daughter...
saying she went skating with an... an X?
Yes. Um, X is my son, Xavier.
I dropped 'em off
a little while ago at the rink.
Okay. Well, is this
a once-in-a-while thing...
or do you make a practice of dropping off
people's kids that you don't even know?
- Hey, what...
- 'Cause if it is...
then maybe the authorities
should be notified about your activities.
- Look, Mrs. Turner...
- Miss Turner.
Oh, it's miss. Okay, Miss Lady
With A Bad Attitude, whatever...
Calm down, okay? The kids
were gonna ride the bus to the rink.
But, you know, being
the neglectful parent that I am...
I decided to give 'em a ride anyway.
Now, since you're so concerned
about your daughter's welfare...
I suggest you take a ride up to the rink.
It's about 30 minutes up Imperial.
They close at midnight.
However, my son will be here at 8:00.
So you can either wait...
but, you know, in your garage...
or you can go down there and be known
as the party-crashing mama on the block...
and give your daughter a serious complex
for the rest of her natural-born life.
Your choice.
- Your carburetor's flooded.
- So is yours.
Big old Fat Albert look-alike.
Must be crazy talking to me like...
How do you know
the carburetor's flooded?
You need to put
some lotion on them feet.
Man, this is Bruce Lee's "Fists of Fury. "
Ain't nobody doing this in the competition.
I wonder why, Junior.
Ah, now what?
And here he is,
center floor, Sweetwater's finest.
Give it up for Sweetness.
Go Sweetness! Go Sweetness!
Go Sweetness!
I- I don't know, y'all. I mean, he's good.
- Told you.
- He's okay.
But I've seen X do all those moves.
Oh, oh, oh, hell, no.
- Ohhh.
- Except that one.
Now, that was good.
I'll give that a 10.
Hey, Poindexter, get off me.
Get off of me, man!
You okay?
Somebody fan her for me.
Yeah.
Hey, I didn't know you were here.
Didn't see the Mustang out front.
Oh, um, yeah.
It's been, uh, giving me a little trouble,
so I put it in the shop.
Hmm.
Hey, Dad, where you going?
Oh, just over to Miss Jenkins's house.
She having a little get-together.
She kinda cornered me
in the frozen food section today...
so, you know,
I have to show my face.
Are there gonna be women there?
It's just that I've never seen you
get all dressed up like this before.
Wearing cologne.
Son, it's just a party.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's cool. It's cool.
- Oh, it's cool?
- It's cool.
- Take your time. Your time.
- Thank you so much.
- So, how was Sweetwater?
- Oh, it was good.
See, Dad, we're going against this guy named
Sweetness and his crew at the skate-off.
- Think you'll make it?
- I don't know, son.
I may have to work.
Oh.
You know, to be honest, son...
you could be doing something more constructive
than wasting time at that skating rink.
Mom didn't think it was a waste of time.
- Daddy.
- Hey, pretty girl. Come on. Come on.
Oh, boy, you're getting
so big, baby. Oh, man.
- You smell good, Daddy.
- Oh, thank you, baby.
Can you read me a story?
Mmm, yeah, I can read you a story.
Man, you've got to be crazy.
You ain't got to be from Ohio
to be one in Ohio, player.
This Tino glamour, baby.
- Hey, Rhonda, what's going on?
- Hi, Tino.
- Nothing much.
- How you doing?
- Good.
- How'd you get these napkins to match that outfit, mama?
- You know, you do your thing right here.
- I gotta do my thing.
- Get off my phone.
- All right, my heart. Hold on.
It ain't long distance.
You know what I'm saying.
I thought I'd bring you a drink.
Oh, um, thanks, Rhonda,
but I don't drink.
You don't drink? What,
you a Jehovah Witness or something?
- No, I'm just not a drinker. That's all.
- Mm.
- But, hey, I do like all this, uh, cheetah thing you got going.
- Cheetah?
It's leopard.
Cheetah's too gaudy.
Huh.
Well, I'll get you a Pepsi.
- Okay.
- You keep that wall up for me.
Ooh, Curtis, my man!
Curtis, my man!
Big Curtis! I didn't know
you was on Rhonda.
What? No, man. I'm just...
I ain't on nothing but this wall.
- Okay? Just the wall.
- Man, if I wasn't miserably married, man...
I'd be trying to tame
that big wild kingdom.
Whole lot of rumbling engine.
And she make a damn good rib.
I'll handle that cat.
Beat that cat down.
Let me get a piece of that rib.
Hey, man, don't touch my rib.
Rhonda, you ain't slick.
We saw you over there working Curtis.
What? Okay. Girl, please. I wasn't doing
nothing but getting that man a Pepsi.
- That's all.
- Mm-hmm.
- But he is fine.
- Girl, yes, he is!
Oh, I just feel so sorry
about what happened to Kathy.
- Yeah, I know.
- Oh, yeah.
- That was a beautiful woman.
- Yes, she was.
- She was.
- Now, who's Kathy?
- Oh, that's right. You don't know, do you?
- Mm-mm.
- Kathy was his wife.
- Oh.
She died last year... What was that...
two weeks or so before Christmas?
- Oh.
- Turns out she had some sort of a heart condition.
- It was sad. I feel bad for those kids.
- Mm, baby. Really sad.
- Oh.
- Yeah, it is.
In the meantime,
I'm gonna get him that Pepsi.
Girl.
That's a cute outfit, girl.
You need to work on your aim.
- Ah, they'll find it.
- Ohhh!
Maybe they'll start
paying me on time.
Hey, what's up with you
and that Naomi girl?
You guys used to date?
No, we were just friends.
- You should like her.
- Huh?
You heard me.
She's a cute girl.
What's not to like?
I see you checking her out.
Drooling, mouth all open.
But you ain't gotta be ashamed.
You know, I was gonna
tell you, though...
when you're with a girl,
you gotta be cool, okay?
You can't be no nerd letting her see you dribble,
because that you should be ashamed of.
- Your daddy should've told you this, but anyway...
- Tori.
Throw a paper.
All right, we got a live one.
Are we ready?
We're ready.
Tori!
Hey, X! Hey!
Ah! Ah, ah! Oh!
Tori!
No!
Man, no! Get outta here,
you little punks!
Tori, you all right?
Shut up. Just shut up.
Got you.
We got three weeks till the skate-off.
We need to step it up.
Last week at Sweetwater...
I ain't gonna name no names, Naps...
- What?
- But last week at Sweetwater...
some of us looked like crap.
What?
I'm gonna be ready.
I'm clutch.
No, what you need to do
is clutch some skating skills, clown.
Yeah, stop renting skates. Why don't you
just wear the ones that you have on?
Dude, what do I look like
rolling in my sister's skates?
No different.
You still look goofy.
- Forget you, Mike, albino punk.
- Whatever, Ricky Ricardo.
Hurry up! "What's Happening"
comes on at 4:00.
Mind your business, chain saw lips.
Naps, take the box.
Get in formation.