Subtitulos y Modificaciones por Hosen
hosen@fibertel.com.ar
Alyssa.
This is ridiculous.
I want you
to go give your dad a hug.
Why?
Because he'll be gone
for his birthday.
Can we have a party
for him while he's gone?
I hope you're showered
and ready for school.
Sam broke his closet.
Beat it!
Get outta there! No, wait.
Stay there. Good boy.
Right there.
Come to daddy.
Come here, Guster!
Have a nice day.
-Stay.
-This has got to stop.
He escaped.
Now he's back in.
Does it give you some sort
of perverse pleasure...
to expose your penis in front
of my 16-year-old daughter?
My exposure does not
face your windows.
George, this is the third time.
The plumber's due out tomorrow.
You will just have
to explain that to the police.
You were the one neighbor
I could tolerate.
Coleen!
Just how far out
that window did you have...
to stick your head
to be able to see my dick?
I like your PJs!
I wish you'd talk to him.
He needs a man.
His father's a man.
-A man he respects.
-He respects nothing.
Thanks for talking
about me behind my back.
It's useful in court.
Are you wearing eye makeup?
Take it off.
If I just walk out
the door right now...
who's gonna be here tonight
for the follow-through?
Have a nice flight.
Queer.
What did you say?
Dad said it first.
I get chocolate cake
for your birthday.
Are your hands clean?
He's a fuckin' freak.
Dude, nice look.
I saw your dad this morning.
Josh, what do you say?
Is he in?
Been thinking
about the job, man?
Forget him.
Two hours a week
for three hundred cash.
The whole summer.
Do the math.
He's not gonna do it, Josh.
Guess he doesn't have it in him.
They consider this a hatchback
or a station wagon?
Let's get outta here, dude.
Think about it.
I'll be around.
Dude, I was in total REM.
Benson Kitter Architecture.
Can I help you?
Yes, sir.
Done? Close to done?
-I'm doing the grass.
-Fuck the grass.
Burke bid out the Berlin Plaza.
Did he tell you?
I was gonna start that
on Monday.
He likes the look of the
computer models better anyway.
You take too long.
When you're done
mowing the grass here...
do you mind bringing
the house up to my office?
Got a presentation to make.
I wouldn't make a habit of it.
I could be anyone.
Then why do you stay you?
You should lock your door.
Ring the bell before
you try the door.
Did Sam call to tell you
he won't be over this weekend?
Why did you let him
pierce his chin?
What kind of a mother
can't stand her own son?
I don't know.
Why aren't you coming
for the weekend?
What is he doing? George?
-George, what are you doing?
-He doesn't answer.
He never answers.
Why does he have
a lock on his door?
Because he put a lock on it.
Do you really think I told him
he could put a hole in his face?
Just climb up there and tell him
what he can and can't do.
Take him for the summer, OK?
Whip him into shape.
Make him smile!
Let him hate you for a while.
You need all the brain cells
you've got.
Go away!
I don't know what to do anymore.
You take him.
Just take him.
You're such a good father.
What are you doing in my room?
I didn't go in your room.
I locked the door! Get out!
What do you think I'm stupid?
I locked the door!
This is my room !
You have no right in here!
This is mine!
This is stupid.
Why can't you all just die
and leave me alone?
Benson, Kitter, Fein,
Silver and Associates.
Can I help you please?
George, good morning.
Mr. Burke would like
to see you in his office.
Come on in.
Have a seat.
-Orange juice? Croissant?
-No, I'm good.
What are you on, George?
Beg your pardon?
How much weight have you lost?
I don't know.
Five, ten pounds.
Haven't been very hungry.
How's your wife?
Well, when we divorced
a decade ago...
she was very angry.
Now she's just hostile.
Right.
I did tell you, didn't l,
that I would be ready...
to start the Berlin model today?
George, this is not me.
We can show clients
endless options.
We can change anything,
really...
in a matter of hours
on the computer...
but you won't change.
I've been here twenty years.
Maybe that's too long.
Maybe?
It's too long.
Listen.
They decided
on a week a year severance...
but I got 'em to twenty-six, OK?
You can learn all you need to on
the computer long before that.
You can maybe even find a job
closer to home.
I hate this job.
George,
what are you talking about?
You love your job.
Nope.
From the day I started to today.
Can't stand it.
Well, good.
Then it sounds like
I'm doing you a favor.
You know what?
I feel better about this.
Good. I was hoping you would.
-Can I ask you one favor?
-What can I do for you?
I built my first model here
when I was twenty-five.
There must be hundreds of 'em
around the office.
I was wondering if I might
pick a few to take home.
Just the ones that
really mean something to me.
Well, those--
I mean, George, we can't
really keep our work.
I could maybe ask them
if you could choose one...
but they're a part of the firm.
Look, why don't you go
out there and look them over.
Every single one of them, OK?
You pick the one
you like the best.
Take it with you.
Now, run it by me first.
Just in case, you know.
I'm sure it'll be OK.
Benson, Kitter, Fein,
Silver and Associates.
May I help you, please?
Yes, sir.
George, Mr. Burke
would like to see you.
-Fine.
-ln his office when you're able.
Sure.
I'll keep this one
if that's all right with you.
You're a great architect
and a miserable human being.
That's mine.
No, George, don't! Shit!
You're not even
a fucking architect...
and you're
a miserable human being.
You're right. You win.
Sir?
Sir, are you all right?
Can you hear me?
Is he breathing?
Come on.
Someone call 91 1.
That took care of the pain?
I could kiss you.
No food.
I'm painless.
What would you do if you had
three or four months to live?
I'd eat a lot of red meat.
Good for you.
What would you do?
Build a house.
Yeah? What kind of house?
You know what
mortise and tenon is?
I've got every part of it ready.
It's like a jigsaw puzzle.
Only pieces now waiting
to make sense.
Been through design review...
the planning commission,
city council.
No one's really said...
that four months
is all you have, have they?
Nobody's even pretended
to offer treatment.
So you tell me,
when would you start...
eating red meat?
Can you build a house
in four months?
I can die trying.
Good for you.
I've not been touched in years.
Really?
No, I mean, not a friend?
Your mother?
People have to be touched.
Everyone gets touched
by somebody they love.
I know.
It's weird, isn't it?
I know my son,
when he was younger...
ten or eleven even,
he used to run up...
and throw his arms around me.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
Where have you been?
I called everyone everywhere.
You just vanished.
-You could be dead.
-Not today.
You are inconsiderate and
absolutely devoid of emotion.
You're the most beautiful woman
that I have ever known.
-What?
-I don't mean just physically.
Even your anger is perfect.
And where have you been
for a week?
Four days.
I have to talk to you.
Why would they tow your truck?
I'm gonna tear down the shack
and build the house.
You've been saying that
for twenty years.
While we were dating
you said it.
-Now there's nothing to stop me.
-Oh, money?
Severance pay.
And I'm gonna cash in
my life insurance policy.
Where will you live?
In the garage.
Look, I wasn't serious
about you taking Sam...
so you don't have to get
into any actual construction...
to get out of it.
When does school let out?
Friday. Tomorrow.
Oh, God.
I hate the thought
of him home all day.
I'll be by Saturday
to pick him up.
He doesn't want to spend
the weekends with you anymore.
Not for the weekend.
For the summer.
One of you would end up dead.
But at least we'd have
a house to show for it.
Forget it, really.
I'll survive.
I want him with me.
No, you don't. Trust me.
I want Sam for the summer.
Jesus.
Well, I'm married.
The whole summer, Sam.
Party in Tahoe.
I don't know, Corey.
Let me think about it, OK?
All we gotta do is sand
and paint the cabin.
My dad's gonna let me
use his boat.
My charm's gonna
let me use my rod.
And you know that
lncan Village is the place...
to hook up with some hump.
OK, I'll ask.
All right,
I'm just saying it beats...
letting townfolk
go down on you for the summer.
I haven't done anything.
I know what the deal is.
Josh is a pimp. I'm not stupid.
Obviously you don't know
what the deal is...
because there is
no fucking deal.
Lighten up, dude.
-Good morning, Mr. George.
-Hiya.
Mrs. Kimble is in the backyard.
And...
Packing.
Good.
Almost ready?
Would you mind
turning this down?!
It won't be all work, you know.
It won't be all work!
I heard you already.
Your mom and the boys
can come by anytime.
What, to check up on me?
I'll be there
to check up on you.
Why would you be there?
Well, I live there.
You live in Corey's
parents' cabin in Tahoe?
What are you talking about?
-Who's Corey?
-Corey's my friend.
I'm going to spend
the summer, OK?
No, you're not going anywhere.
You're spending the summer
with me.
Shit! No fucking way!
Robin, did you tell Sam he was
spending the summer with me?
What was I supposed to do?
I tried to call.
Your phone isn't working.
I don't have a phone anymore.
Who are you, anyway?
I don't even know you.
You'll know me
by the time we're through.
I'm not going.
I'll get your bag.
Would you tell him
that I'm not going?
You already promised me!
-George, I did say he could go.
-ls this everything?
Mom, please. Tell him !
George, l...
He is not spending
the entire summer...
with some kid in Tahoe!
He can hate me.
You can hate me.
He can try to kill me
while I'm sleeping!
I don't care!
Sam is spending
the summer with me, OK?
He's my son. He's sixteen.
That's it!
Can I hate you, too?
You can do anything you want.
-Go get in the truck.
-You go fuck yourself!
Listen to me.
I want that thing
out of your chin, OK?
You got nipple rings,
naval rings...
those come out, too.
And there's no makeup
at my house.
No glue sniffing, huffing...
no pills, no grass.
You've worn out your welcome
at this house, Sam.
This may well be the worst
summer of your entire life...
but you've earned it.
Now go pick up the suitcase,
get in the truck, now.
I'll hate you
for the rest of my life.
Well, you can't even begin to
know how much I hate my father.
Think of it
as a family tradition.
You like garlic?
Do you like garlic bread?
Thinking of jumping?
Pushing.
Well, don't jump
till you hear...
the wave crash
against the cliff.
Water'll take you out.
Let it.
First time I did it,
younger than you...
I thought I'd break my neck...
and just sort of
float out to Catalina.
You don't always get
what you wish for, Sam.
Shit.
Hello!
Oh, my God.
I don't believe this!
Are you totally insane?
God!
I don't believe this.
I got a total wacko
for a father.
I almost saw Catalina!
What have you gotten
all over yourself?
What is this?
Is this pasta sauce?
You crazy dog, Guster.
Come here. Lick it.
You're crazy, you know this?
What are you doing here?
They're trying to make me
spend the summer here...
but I'm leaving in the morning.
Where to?
I'm supposed to be in Tahoe.
I guess if you stay,
I'll see you around.
You should stay.
Where's your dad?
He jumped into the ocean.
Well, tell him I say hello.
I'm not taking a dump
with you in here.
My brothers say that it's the
worst smell they've ever smelt.
Which side of the bed
do you want?
-I'm not--
-Just kidding.
The sofa's a pull-out.
Jesus.
You know, I think
you have to have a door...
between where you cook
and where you crap.
Even in the bush,
tribal people don't like that.
They have a place for both.
Probably it's, like, a law.
God !
Probably in the Bible.
It's at least
a building code violation.
Good night.
I have to take a dump.
You wearing sunscreen?
Are you wearing sunscreen?
I wonder where he's living?
About time.
They're finally tearing down
this pile of junk.
Barbara, Tom.
Guess how many
low-income apartments...
the city approved for this lot.
Ballpark figure.
No. Not today.
There was also some talk
about a drug-rehab center.
Jerk.
We can't do anything.
What are you doing?
Don't touch me.
I warned you yesterday.
You can't touch me.
You stayed.
Rub him down, will you, Alyssa?
He's insane.
You look better without makeup.
I can't even take a shower here.
Come over to my house
whenever you want.
I'll tell my mom.
I might not even stay anyway.
I'll get your back.
No, that's OK. Thanks.
Have you ever had anyone
besides your mom or dad...
put it on for you?
It's weird how different it is.
Turn around. Just lay down.
Do you remember me?
From when you lived here before?
So I've decided that
I'm not going to shave...
my legs or my pits this summer.
I mean, Paula Cole
isn't a vertical kisser.
Really?
So, your dad's really
going to build his house?
I don't know.
You know, your dad dated my mom
after her divorce.
Really?
Yeah. I wanted him to marry her.
Why?
Turn over.
Josh and I are actually
going to South Coast.
Do you want a ride?
Maybe see a movie?
No, thanks.
All right, well,
don't forget your front.
I'll see you around.
Pretty, isn't she?
For a girl.
Feel free to pitch in anytime.
Sam, do you ever...
get the slightest inkling that
you might want to help me...
instead of doing
absolutely nothing?
Here.
I hate turkey.
No, you don't.
If I say I do, I do.
Please, take that thumbtack
out of your face.
-Let me just get it out.
-Why?
Come on. It bugs me.
You snore at night.
That really bugs me.
Can I take you out?
You know, your brothers
are right about that smell.
That was the most
god-awful thing...
I've ever had my nose around.
-Told you.
-It's toxic.
Thought you guys
might be hungry.
We're fine.
Turkey sandwiches.
Oh, well. For later, then.
-Makes me sad.
-Why?
I used to live here.
Yeah, and you hated four out of
the five years that you did.
I was here six years,
and I only hated two.
Which two?
The first and the last.
I don't even like
turkey sandwiches.
What's this pizza?
Sam's favorite.
Sure you don't want any?
George, you're too thin--
from what you used to be anyway.
Why the first and the last?
The first because I wasn't sure
you really loved me...
and the last because I wasn't
sure I really loved you.
I was up on that roof
this morning tearing it down...
and it struck me,
strong as anything ever has--
I'm happy today.
What were you before today?
I don't know what it was--
the way the sun struck the ocean
or the sound of the waves.
It was simple, whatever it was.
Then I started thinking...
when the last time was
that I felt like this.
Do you remember?
Yeah, the one time
I remember for sure.
I was with Sam in the ocean...
saving him from the waves.
He had his head on my shoulder,
and we were laughing.
I could feel his heart
pounding against my chest.
I remember I kissed his hair.
This was before it was blue.
We have it on video.
It was when my parents were
down for his sixth birthday.
I remember that.
I got to go.
What is it?
Oh, nothing. I'm fine.
I'll drop off your lunch
tomorrow.
I'm going for a walk.
I need some money.
You'll have money when you work.
You're predictable.
You haven't been happy
in ten years?
I'm not doing it.
It's going to be good.
You know, nobody
would blame me if I left.
I'd blame you.
I want you here.
Why don't you just go and
beg some money off of my dad...
so you can move
into someplace decent...
with a real kitchen
and a real bathroom?
I'd rather sell my nuts
to a castrati.
I don't beg.
And I don't take a shower
in the middle of the yard!
I can promise you
complete privacy.
No, you can't!
You can't promise me anything...
because you don't
have anything to promise.
You live in a garage, OK?
You don't have cable.
You're not hooked up
for the internet...
because you don't even
own a computer.
And you don't have a job.
Just try it.
That's all I'm asking.
Come on, Sam.
I'm begging, OK?
Go fuck yourself.
Is Alyssa home?
She went out with a friend.
I didn't recognize you.
Alyssa said you two don't even
have plumbing over there.
Not a shower.
Come on.
I hope your ex-husband's
equipped for the havoc of Sam...
because it seems absolutely
blissful here tonight.
There you go.
Do you think it's odd
your kids don't hug you?
Should l?
It would worry me.
If I let everything that
should worry me worry me...
I'd be dead from worry.
What would you be
if you asked Ryan and Adam...
to run in here right now
and hug you?
I'd be you.
I'll do it,
if that's what you want.
Kurt, is that you?
There has to be
a logical explanation.
No hot water.
Your buddy Mr. Dokos
called to complain...
that you and a boy are squatting
illegally in your garage.
Check the permits.
It was built as a guest house.
It's a legally-rentable unit.
Now, that's got to be illegal.
Dokos?
I'll piss on his lawn.
Bro, I need you tonight.
I locked the door.
lt'll take you
twenty, thirty minutes.
Does Alyssa know?
No. Nothing.
She sent me up here
to see if you wanted...
to hang out with her
and her mom and watch a movie.
You got any more weed?
You got any money?
Three hundred cash, two hours.
You don't have to do a thing.
Just get in, get out
as quick as you can.
Close your eyes.
Think of whatever.
So, what's the deal
between you and Alyssa?
Don't even. I'm there.
I didn't know. I'm sorry.
She wouldn't even fucking go out
with me until she was sixteen.
That wasn't even a rule.
That was just her own thing.
She figures things out
on her own, and that's it.
If this rings, run.
He already knows about
everything you can't do.
And you can tell him
not to look at you if you want.
This feels too weird now.
I don't like it.
Beats working.
You want to roll down
the window, please?
Look at me.
What'd you just toss
into the brush?
Nothing.
Hey, you ! Kid !
Stop right there!
Hold it, kid !
Turn off your engine.
Lunch.
Lunch? It's not breakfast yet.
I dreamed about your house
last night.
Finished or unfinished?
It was perfect, George.
It was amazing.
It was so real.
Didn't you once dream that
you could lick people well?
That wasn't a dream.
That was Sam.
Right.
His ear infection.
My tongue around the edge
of his ear is what cured him.
Will you go in that garage
and lick his attitude?
The antibiotics
weren't working...
and that is what I believe,
George.
You're wrong
about that first year.
I've been wrong
a lot in my life.
Hindsight.
It's like foresight
without a future.
I have three hours
before I go get the kids.
Where will I be most useful?
With your hands or your tongue?
You're not well.
-I just hit it?
-Hit it as hard as you can.
That's it. Yes.
I should go.
-Good morning.
-Sam, Ryan has a game later.
He asked if you'd go watch.
George Monroe?
-Robin.
-Excuse me.
Mr. Monroe.
I've been dreading you.
Bob Larson, city inspector.
Hi, Bob.
Do you have
an unenclosed toilet...
in proximity to a kitchen?
-A violation?
-Yes.
And if I enclose it?
An exhaust system
or a window is code.
Where is it?
A friend of yours is here.
Did you go through my pants?
I want it back.
Where'd you put it?
I think I may have a solution.
Where'd you hide it?
You're unbelievable,
you know that?
Where is it?
Where'd you put it,
in these shirts?
Just tell me where it is.
I'll look for it myself.
You don't have to--
Would you stop that?
I want to know where it is now!
You got no right
going through my things...
you know that?
It's an invasion of privacy.
I need that back.
I had to work for that.
-Doors.
-I hate to ask about the window.
Where is it?
I flushed it down the toilet.
No! Oh, my God.
If I had a gun,
I swear to God I'd kill you.
What's in my pants is none
of your fucking business.
Look, I'd say
you're in compliance.
I hope this makes
the pain in the ass...
that called you happy.
-You and me both.
-Bye.
Everything about you
is my business--
what you smoke, what you sniff,
what you swallow.
It's all my business.
I've been using
since I was twelve!
You're also unbelievably stupid,
you know that?
You didn't give a shit about
anything I did up until now!
I'll apologize
for everything but today!
Today, I give a shit!
Yeah? You're too fucking late.
These gloves are for you.
You can't make me do a thing.
-Sit down.
-No!
I'll call the cops--
Get off!
That's child abuse!
You're in big shit now!
People go to prison
for what you just did to me!
My dad used to play this game.
I never really even
understood what it was...
until after he was gone.
I was holding for somebody else.
It wasn't even mine.
The game was to make me
smaller than he was--
smaller, always smaller.
No matter what.
He could be almost invisible
as a human being...
but I still had to be smaller.
So that if I got
good grades in school...
then I was a pussy
for not playing football.
Or if I cut my hair for him...
it was never short enough.
Or if I shaved my head,
then I looked like a psycho.
I never won the game--never.
And if he couldn't...
make me smaller with words...
I'll have to pay him back.
I won't ever hit you.
Ever.
I don't want you smaller.
I want you to be happy.
You're not.
Not here with me,
not home with your mother...
not alone, not anywhere.
You're what I was
most of my life, Sam.
I see it in your eyes,
in your sleep...
in your answer to everything.
You're barely alive.
I'm not even listening.
You know the great thing,
though?
Is that change
can be so constant...
that you don't even
feel the difference...
until there is one.
It can be so slow
that you don't know...
that your life is better
or worse till it is.
Or it can just blow you away...
make you something different
in an instant.
It happened to me.
Build this house with me.
Come on.
You fuck.
I have to pay back what you
flushed down the toilet.
I want ten dollars an hour,
then I'm done.
This all has to come down
before we can start again.
Knock it down.
I have hated this house
from the moment my father...
put it in my name.
Twenty-five years
of hating what you live in.
Hating what you are.
This is an end of it, Sam.
Finally gonna build
something of my own.
Something I can be proud
to give you.
Don't.
-I don't want it.
-Fine.
You can do whatever
you want with it.
All I want is for you
to remember...
that we built a house together.
We haven't built shit.
You're just tearing
your father down.
Try it. Feels good.
Go!
Come on!
After you.
It's going down.
That's it.