Hey, hey, you're digging
the master jock for solid rock...
...Sweet Al Monte blasting, babies.
Being bold and pouring coal on KRML
in quaint little Carmel-by-the-Sea.
We're next door to magnificent Monterey,
home of the annual jazz festival.
Although it's four months away,
you got to get your tickets...
...because they're going fast
and it can't last.
The time is 7:54
and there's a breeze of 50 degrees...
...around your loving hips,
and there's a taste of fog.
I say we got a bowl of soul,
and if you think your heart can take it...
...come fly higher with The Heavy!
Now we're gonna wrap it up
for the week, folks.
A brand-new release from the funk capital
of the world, Squeeze Me.
Here he comes, the big "D" himself,
Dave Garver.
And Dave is gonna bring you
five hours of mellow groove.
In the meantime,
this is Sweet Al Monte saying:
"Hang in there, babies, because everything
is going to be everything."
'Bye.
What's that letter you got there?
Is that that Frisco gig?
Yeah.
All right, so what's happening?
They want the usual thing:
A biography, pictures.
Really? Is that that Madge Brenner chick?
Yeah, she's the one putting it together.
In that case, David, you're in.
How do you figure that?
Now, David, come on, man.
Are you kidding?
She's a grandmother.
So when did that ever stop you?
You better get a move on.
I already played your theme.
Yeah, I heard it.
You're a real human being.
And you're on the air, baby.
All right.
"Men have destroyed the roads of wonder
"And their cities squat like black toads
"In the orchards of life
nothing is clean or real
"Or as a girl, naked to love
or be a man with"
This is Dave Garver with a little verse,
a little talk...
...and five hours of music
to be very, very nice to each other by.
- KRML, Dave Garver speaking.
- Hello?
- Hi, what'll it be?
- Play Misty for me.
Misty?
We have that right on the play rack.
Thanks for calling.
I see you got your little Misty chick
calling you again. All righty.
- Swing along.
- You take it easy now.
See you in the a.m.
KRML, Dave Garver.
- Hi, Murphy.
- Hi, Dave. No messages for you.
- No?
- Heard your show tonight.
It sure beats hell out
of working for a living.
- Thanks for the plug.
- What are friends for?
- Bartender.
- Coke? Coming right up.
She's waiting for someone.
You sure?
That's what she says.
Guys have been striking out all night.
One game?
- Cry Bastion?
- What else?
Okay, coach. You asked for it.
Don't take all night. Move.
Okay.
Move.
Palfrey's Gambit.
Dirty rat.
Are we playing Copenhagen rules?
Make it easy on yourself, Murph.
Cry Bastion.
Sorry, no Bastion.
Damn, I didn't see that.
It's too bad, Murphy. Too bad.
- Careful now.
- That ought to do it.
Be really careful now.
Careful.
Hi.
He doesn't see it.
Yeah?
Cry Bastion.
Fool's ploy, my man. Fool's ploy.
Care to play the winner?
I'll just watch.
- My name is Dave Garver.
- Evelyn Draper.
Sit down, Evelyn Draper?
Care for a drink?
Okay.
- What'll it be?
- Surprise me.
- Screwdriver.
- Nice game.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- What happened?
- I won.
How? When?
When you said, "Okay."
I ought to be mad.
But you're not.
Not really.
It certainly was nice of you
to bring me home, Mr. Garver?
That's right.
I don't think I've been stood up on a date
since the ninth grade back in Albany.
Is something wrong?
No, I keep getting the feeling
I know you from someplace.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Here. Why don't you let me do that?
Oh, no. That's all right. I've got it.
Why don't you see
if you can get the fire started?
All right.
There are some matches right next to it.
It's getting late.
You're sure I'm not keeping you up?
No. I rarely get to bed before 3:00 a.m.
I didn't have a date tonight.
I went there because you talk about it
on your program sometimes...
...and I wanted to meet you.
I listen to you all the time.
I knew somebody was out there.
- You're making fun of me.
- No, I'm not.
- Say something else.
- Such as?
Play Misty for me?
Very good.
- You sure I'm not keeping you up?
- Don't you like me?
You're a very nice girl.
But who needs nice girls?
No, I like them.
I'm kind of hung up on one.
And you don't want to complicate your life.
- That's exactly right.
- Neither do I.
But that's no reason we shouldn't
sleep together tonight if we feel like it.
Solid silicone.
Hi, David, my man! How you been, baby?
See you got the joint cleaned up for once.
The Heavy digs it.
- Care for a beer?
- Not really.
I could go for something more uplifting,
but not a brew, my man.
Beer is all we've got.
You're gonna have to ease on out.
I got a lot of work to do today.
You don't understand.
I've been sent here to get you.
By whom?
That old chick I go with. What's her name?
- Carol?
- That's the one.
Girl thinks you've been working too hard.
She said we should get together tonight.
Who's this "we"?
Me, you, her and one of them hens
that you can dig up.
There is a fantastic new Mexican place
in Carmel called Susinos.
The albóndigas soup is unbelievable.
It is a mind-bender...
I know the joint, but I don't have a date,
and I got a lot to do.
Big deal, man. Get one!
If you have any problems getting one,
I'll get one for you as nice as I look.
It's too late, and besides,
I've got a lot of work to do.
But you gotta eat, David.
I'm gonna whip up something
here in my own kitchen.
You know, David,
I'm really worried about your social life.
You'll make someone
a tremendous mother.
Too narrow in the pelvis.
I sure appreciate you dropping by, Al.
Come by again sometime, anytime.
Never let it be said
that Sweet Al Monte can't take a hint.
- Who's hinting?
- Hi.
Why, hi there, yourself.
Dave Garver live here?
That depends on your point of view.
Hi.
This stuff weighs a ton.
Where's the kitchen?
Right inside.
Just come on in and help yourself.
Swing right around the bend there.
I know, David, she's from Chicken Delight.
Look, don't work too hard, my man.
Don't strain yourself.
How come you don't have any beer?
And what is this? A shrunken head?
Does that guy live here?
- I wanted...
- I hope you like steak.
- You look like a steak-and-potatoes type.
- Hang on.
I said to myself,
a nice salad with Roquefort and tomatoes...
...and baked potato with...
- What's going on here?
- Don't send me away.
- No, I want to ask you a question.
I just wanted to surprise you.
Surprise?
What happens if he and I
had been talking business?
Or maybe I have female company
and you come traipsing in with groceries?
That would be some surprise.
I'm sorry.
Keep that stuff.
I think I've lost my appetite.
Hang on a minute.
I'm just trying to tell you something.
I don't understand.
Should I go or stay? What?
I'm telling you there's a telephone,
and I pick it up and I dial it.
You answer and I say,
"What are you doing?"
And I say, "I'll be right over."
Fine. Next time,
why don't we do it that way?
Okay. Any way you like. Next time.
How do you like your steak?
Extremely rare.
That's just how I like mine.
I'll get some wine here. A little vino.
Vino! All this and heaven, too!
Terrific!
This is gonna be some dinner.
What happened to that discussion
we had last time?
You know,
the deal about no strings and all that?
There are no strings,
but I never said anything...
...about not coming back for seconds, did I?
That's right. You didn't.
When will I see you?
I'll give you a call.
- Dave, you're funny.
- How's that?
If you want to keep playing these games,
okay, but...
...they're really not necessary anymore,
not for me.
People are trying to sleep here!
People are trying to talk here!
- How'd you like to tell that to the law?
- How'd you like to go screw yourself?
Take it easy!
Guy's just trying to sleep, that's all.
You're right.
It's a terrific morning.
Why be selfish with it?
Bye-bye.
Wait a minute!
Yeah?
Excuse me, I saw the sweater,
and I thought you were somebody else.
You must be David.
Where have you been?
Around.
I was trying to join the revolt
against the representational.
Didn't quite make that though.
So now I'm just trying to play it cool.
Not quite making that either.
Got time for a break?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
- When did you get in town?
- Yesterday.
- You weren't gonna call me?
- Of course I was. I had to get settled first.
You shouldn't lend your sweaters
to blabbermouths.
You've gotten thinner.
No!
Well, so much for Sausalito.
Sausalito?
That's where I was staying.
Jay Jay's place.
- Jay Jay's place?
- It's nothing much, really.
It's just a little pied-à-terre,
but it's handy to the fleet.
You told me
you didn't know where she was.
So I lied. Picket me.
- Thanks a lot.
- Listen, stud, it wasn't my idea.
You should have caught her act.
The whole Bette Davis,
through-finished-kaput scene.
- And at 3:00 a.m.
- Come on, Jay Jay. He's exaggerating.
I'll check with Malcolm.
Maybe I can get you the afternoon off.
What happened, pussycat?
He ran into Anjelica.
She told him I was back.
That bitch should be hung by the thumbs
or something equally appropriate.
It's all set up.
Let's go.
It's nothing personal, really.
I happen to think
she could be a first-rate artist...
...if her damned hormones
didn't get in the way.
- There's not much he can do about that.
- He could kill himself.
Jay Jay,
why don't you go cruise some sailors?
Please, don't mention seafood.
Come on.
I really missed this place.
I missed you.
You'd do me a big favor
if you didn't say things like that.
Why is that?
I don't know.
Somehow it brings out the worst in me.
It makes me want to say things like,
"How's that redhead?"
What?
The redhead,
the one who worked in the bookstore.
She went back to Berkeley or whatever.
That's too bad.
You always have that blonde
from Santa Barbara to fall back on.
If that's the phrase I'm looking for,
and I think it probably is.
What are we gonna do?
Go through a whole list? Is that it?
Who's got that kind of time?
I just don't know if I'm up to it anymore.
Up to what?
Those nights sitting and waiting for you
to finish your program and come by.
Nights when it would start to get late...
...and I'd start to think:
"I wonder if he's run himself off a cliff
or maybe he's run into a blonde."
There was a time
when I started rooting for the accident.
I mean, if it was a choice
between that and a blonde.
You don't know
how secure you make me feel.
I didn't wish you anything too serious.
Just a couple of months in traction.
You're all heart.
You know, the thing I hate the most
in the whole world is a jealous female...
...and that's what I was becoming.
That's why I had to split.
I was starting to be
one of my most unfavorite people.
I hated it. I know you did, too.
That still works anyway.
- Too well sometimes.
- What does that mean?
I mean, there's a little spot in the middle
of each day, just about your size.
There's lots of girls my size
if you're really looking.
I'm not. That's what I'm trying to tell you.
You mean you've given up girls?
I haven't exactly been the monk
of the month or anything like that...
...but I have been making an effort.
There must be a real consternation
among those "gropies."
That's "groupies," isn't it?
I don't know, "groupies, gropies..."
You know, you've got to be fair.
It hasn't just been my fault.
Listen, I know.
They kept overpowering you.
You get a little bit of the blame, too,
you know.
You and that parade of roommates
that keep moving in and out of your place.
I didn't realize
they were such a trial to you.
What trial? I enjoyed it.
You and I sitting in front of the fireplace...
...and then some chick sitting there
with a bathrobe on, eating Fig Newtons.
What about the one with the St. Bernard?
She was a real winner.
She took up enough space.
And then that other one
that took the flute lessons.
Yeah, maybe it was a little rough on you.
I can think of a thousand reasons
why we should try again.
I've got about seven billion things to do.
What do you think?
You want to try for a new start,
right from the letter "A"?
- What am I gonna do with you?
- A lot.
Hi. Excuse me.
Hi.
- You've met Anjelica, my...
- Roommate. Yes.
I think I'll drive into Carmel and see
if I can't find some cleaning solvent.
There's plenty under the sink.
Okay.
This house ought to have a revolving door.
You know when my father left me
this house, he left me payments.
I can't handle that expense by myself
and most girls don't like the isolation.
- It's a long way from town.
- I know.
I better get back to work.
- Thanks.
- That's it, "thanks"?
Four months in Sausalito is a long time.
I am not gonna get back
on that same old merry-go-round again.
What do I have to do,
give you a notarized statement?
I need a couple of more days to try and...
...figure out where I'm at.
Okay. You get your bearings,
and then you'll give me a call, all right?
- Hi, Murph.
- Hi, Dave.
Sardine Factory.
Dave Garver?
You said this is Evelyn?
No.
Sorry, you've just missed him.
- What do you mean?
- He's gone. He's not here.
I think you'd better look again.
Believe me, you just missed him.
Now if you're interested
in someone more sophisticated...
...l'll be happy to...
That's what I get for being a dirty old man.
There's a message for you,
a Madge somebody from San Francisco.
- Brenner?
- That's it. Al Monte gave her this number.
"Received pictures and biography.
"Please send a two-hour tape
of your show as soon as possible."
- Thanks, Murph.
- Don't mention it.
I can't tell you how thrilled I am
to be your social secretary.
You will put that on my tab?
Surprise!
What are you doing here?
I was calling you from that phone booth
and he told me you'd left...
...and I was staring right at your car.
Isn't that funny?
Yeah, kind of funny.
Why didn't you take my call?
Where does it say I gotta drop everything
and answer the phone every time it rings?
Do you know your nostrils flare out
into little wings when you're mad?
- It's kind of cute.
- Come on, Evelyn. I gotta go.
- I'd love a Coke.
- Not now, I gotta get to the station.
No, you don't.
You're talking to your No. 1 fan.
You don't work tonight.
I've got this show that I'm trying to set
and it's very important to me.
That means I gotta pick the music,
write the lead-ins and find some poetry.
- Come on, will you?
- Poetry?
- Let me help you. I'm terrific with poetry...
- Not tonight!
Does he want his keys?
- Come on, Evelyn.
- Speak.
- Come on!
- God!
Good boy! Let's hear it. Come on.
Come on. Give me my keys.
- Come on. Give me the keys.
- Come on.
Give me the keys, goddamn it!
- Having some trouble, lady?
- Get lost!
Yeah, get lost, assholes!
Let's split.
He's got enough trouble already.
Yeah. Excuse me.
'Bye. See you later.
Hi.
Get all your work done?
What do you want, Evelyn?
One Coke?
I'll tell you, tonight I'm really whipped.
What time is it?
Time for me to go home.
Go back to sleep.
- Hey, I've got an idea.
- What's that?
Some night this week, after the show...
...corned beef and potato salad,
dill pickles, the whole bit.
My place. Deal?
I'll call you.
Thursday's good for me.
And now from KRML,
the big-band sounds of Dee Barton.
Here's a fresh reel of tape
for your air check.
- You want me to thread it up?
- No, leave it here. Thanks.
I think I will go out and hit the streets,
but before doing that...
...I will blow me a little number.
Care to partake?
Take it in the other room.
I get zonked just breathing the air here.
All right, be that way.
- AI?
- Yeah?
Do you ever find yourself...
...being completely smothered
by somebody?
- Anybody I know?
- You met her at my house the other day.
Chicken Delight!
That's what I call
a pretty good smothering.
You start a relationship thinking
you're gonna be completely honest and...
...suddenly the whole thing
gets out of hand.
What's the problem?
The problem is I've been trying
to uncomplicate my life...
...and now I can't even answer the door.
Besides, Tobie's back.
Oh, really? Tobie? When?
- I ran into her Sunday.
- That was a goody.
I'll tell you the truth.
I've always thought Tobie was
one of the foxiest chicks on the peninsula.
And why you gotta have so much action,
I just don't understand it anyway.
It's just a hang-up I have, or had.
But now that I seem to have that
straightened out...
...I can't seem to solve this other problem.
Well, you know what they always say,
my man.
No, what?
"He who lives by the sword
shall die by the sword."
Don't let the door hit you in the ass
on the way out.
Later.
We'll have more smooth sounds
in just one minute...
...but first, at ten minutes to the hour,
we're broadcasting from KRML...
...in the Carmel Rancho Shopping Center...
...home of the buccaneer,
the man's boutique.
KRML, Dave Garver speaking.
The whole point
in having an answering service...
...is to call in once in a while
to check for messages.
Hi, Evelyn. What's happening?
What could be happening, darling?
You're not here yet.
"Yet"?
I hope you like pastrami,
because there was no corned beef.
Now, wait a minute. Just hold on.
Are you trying to tell me
you forgot that we have a date tonight?
I thought I was supposed
to call you on that.
I feel kind of silly sitting here
in my brand-new lounging pajamas.
I just assumed...
Apparently, I assumed wrong.
That's right. You assumed wrong.
You don't have to come over
if you've got something better to do.
I'll be over in a little while.
You and I are gonna have to have a talk.
Whatever you say.
In the meantime,
haven't you forgotten something else?
What's that?
Weren't you gonna play Misty for me?
Yeah. I have that one right here.
Thank you, darling.
And now we have a pretty one
for lonely lovers on a cool, cool night.
It's the great Erroll Garner classic, Misty.
And this one is especially for Evelyn.
Just a second.
Come in.
Hi.
- Cold night?
- Yeah.
But you got here anyway. Stout fella.
There's something
we're gonna have to get straight.
It's amazing what a man will go through
for a hot pastrami sandwich.
- Look...
- Wait a minute.
You haven't told me how nice I look.
- You look fine.
- The sales lady guaranteed you'd flip.
- Now, listen. Can we talk?
- Wait.
First...
Surprise.
- Don't you like them?
- Yeah, they're great, but...
Don't spoil my fun, darling.
I love to give you things.
It's Madame Butterfly time.
First, friendly neighborhood geisha
remove honorable shoes.
Stop it, Evelyn!
Now, we've gotta talk!
Have I done something wrong?
I'm just trying to be straight with you,
that's all.
Be nice to me instead.
Jesus Christ!
I don't understand.
Are you trying to say
you don't love me anymore?
I never told you that I loved you.
Not in words maybe, but...
...there are ways of saying things
that have nothing to do with words.
I'm sorry you read it that way.
It's that other bitch, isn't it?
What are you talking about?
The silver-framed picture in your dresser.
- That picture's got nothing to do with you.
- What does have to do with me?
- I never lied to you.
- Big deal. He never lied to me.
What do you want for that?
The Congressional Medal of Honor?
- So long.
- What am I supposed to do?
Sit here all dressed up
in my little whore suit...
...waiting for my lord and master to call?
- Nobody asked you to wait for anything.
- You're not dumping me!
- Get off my back, Evelyn!
- Get off your back?
That's where you've been keeping me,
isn't it?
You're nothing!
You're not even good in bed!
I just felt sorry for you, that's all!
Bastard! You poor, pathetic bastard!
Hello?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean those things I said.
Will I see you tomorrow?
You don't listen, do you?
Let me come over.
If I could just see you, just talk to you.
- No, Evelyn.
- But I love you, David. I love you.
David! If I could just...
What's the matter?
Nothing. Why?
No, come on.
You haven't heard a word I've been saying.
- I have. I've heard everything you said.
- You did?
All right, tell me.
- You don't believe me?
- Go ahead.
Okay, wise chick.
We're supposed to go to a party
at Big Sur tomorrow night.
I'm supposed to meet you there at 9:00.
And the address is...
I didn't tell you that.
See how you are?
I don't know myself yet.
I'll call you tomorrow about it.
Okay.
You call me tomorrow.
Honey, we better go.
- We're just getting to the best part.
- But I've got to pick Anjelica up at 6:00.
God! How the pain is setting in.
Come on. She's a very nice girl.
Anyway, she's moving out tonight.
Now, that's about the best news
I've heard in years.
And Madalyn's moving in.
Madalyn?
Shit.
- What's going on?
- Don't tell me he was asleep!
What else at this hour of the morning?
I'm surprised his conscience
was that clear!
- What do you want, Evelyn?
- "What do you want, Evelyn?"
Do I have to want something?
Can't I just come over?
Or is it inconvenient?
- Wait a...
- Did I make a boo-boo?
Has someone been sleeping
in Papa Bear's bed?
Wait a minute, goddamn it!
"Come out, come out, wherever you are!"
I thought...
God, don't look at me that way, Dave.
I just don't know what to say to you.
I'm sorry I mistrusted you.
I know you'd never spoil it.
To spoil what?
What we have between us.
We don't have a goddamn thing!
How many ways do I have to say this?
I don't care how many ways you say it,
it's not true!
- What do I have to do to convince you?
- It's not true!
It's not!
What are you doing?
I'm gonna get dressed and drive you home,
that's what.
Why are you playing these games?
Why are you pretending you don't love me?
I don't even believe I'm hearing this.
But I love you!
You haven't got the vaguest idea
what love is.
We don't even know each other.
Wait a minute.
You don't have to do that.
I'm okay. I can drive home.
Are you sure?
Positive. I'm fine.
Let me just wash my face.
You ready?
You okay?
Oh, no.
How's she gonna be?
I sutured the wounds.
It wasn't quite as bad as it looked.
It couldn't have been.
You know, Dave,
I'm supposed to turn a report in on this.
But you won't. You see, Tobie's back.
I'd rather tell her, and not have her read it
in the paper somewhere.
I didn't know that. I'll tell Marie.
We'll do the spaghetti number.
- Somebody gonna be around here today?
- Me. I'll be here.
I bombed her out pretty good.
Let her sleep it off
before you take her home.
- And how long will that be?
- It's hard to say. Why?
- I'd like to take Tobie out tonight.
- No problem.
She'll wake up sometime this afternoon,
5:00 or so.
Is she gonna be all right?
The cuts were really pretty superficial.
I mean, do you think she'll try it again?
Chances are against it.
But I'd watch her.
I wouldn't leave her alone if she seems
unusually depressed or insecure.
Better get some sleep yourself.
You look like hell.
Call me if you need me.
Thanks, Frank. I really appreciate it.
How are you feeling?
Okay. Fine.
Here.
Thank you.
Brought you a little soup.
It looks good.
I don't know what to say.
It frightens me thinking about it.
Don't think about it.
I don't mean me. I mean you.
"Girl commits suicide
in disc jockey's home."
It's not very good publicity
for a man in your position.
Get some rest. As soon as you feel better,
I'll take you home.
Thank you, David.
I got your clothes hung up
in the closet there.
Maybe you better answer the phone.
Yeah. I'll get it in the other room.
Hello.
Hi. I just wanted to check.
We still on for tonight?
Yeah, I'm ready to go.
What time is the party?
Madalyn's already left,
and she won't be back for a long time...
...and I was just thinking...
Would you be disappointed if we didn't go
to the party and just stayed here instead?
I think I can bear up under it.
Don't be too long.
- That's me at the door.
- David...
...the way I look at it,
the hell with Sausalito.
Bye-bye.
Evelyn?
- What's the matter? Take it easy.
- I had a dream.
I was drowning in the ocean and
I called to you, but you just stood there...
...watching. Watching.
It was just a dream.
Oh, God, I'm so alone.
Hold me.
Hold me, Dave. Please.
Yeah.
Tighter.
Don't let me go.
David!
I woke up and you were gone.
If you have something planned for tonight,
you could just take me home.
Maybe that'd be best.
No, no, there's nothing.
Good.
Isn't this nice?
Just us here, together.
Here we go again.
Stone-cold dead in the market.
Must have been quite a party.
Go away, Birdie.
Any other bodies,
any other juiceheads around here?
Come back tomorrow, will you?
Or next year sometime.
I better check the workbench.
All right, break it up in here.
Looks like old times around this place.
Evelyn?
Lose something, tiger?
You couldn't find it within your heart
to come back at a later time, could you?
This is a later time, pussycat.
I'm paying you back
for the day I blew last week.
Evelyn?
Very funny, Birdie. Very funny.
What I can't figure out is,
with all this action going on in here...
...what are you doing
out there couching it?
What is this, some kind of Kinsey Report?
Do I come over to your house
and ask a lot of dumb questions?
You just ought to, pussycat.
Might open up
a whole new way of life to you.
Hold it.
Let's try to show a little class, shall we?
Mr. Garver's residence.
I'll see.
Do you want to talk to a Madge Brenner?
Yeah. I want to talk to her.
Thanks. Hello.
Hello, Mr. Garver? Madge Brenner.
We like the tape on your show.
Like it very much.
There are one or two others in the running,
but, frankly...
Can we have lunch today?
- Windjammer still good?
- Yeah, still very good.
Reserve a table in your name.
- See you then, Mr. Garver.
- Great. Bye-bye.
Looks like we found Evelyn.
"Good morning, darling. Gone shopping.
"Back in a flash with the hash."
A little humor in there.
"Love and kisses, Evelyn."
And then it says:
"If you can't find your keys, don't worry.
"I borrowed your car."
Here's your key, and here's your copy.
That'll be $0.40, please.
Thank you. Have a nice day.
David? I stopped by my...
Hi.
Don't you look all gussied up?
Good. I was gonna cook brunch
but this calls for something more festive.
How about the Marquis? My treat.
- After all I put you through, it's the least...
- I have a lunch date. Business.
- Business?
- Yeah. Can I have my car keys?
Sure.
I think you ought to take it easy, anyway.
Get some rest.
Yeah, I do feel a little tired.
Very funny, Dave.
Now, let's talk show.
Tell me, what do you think of the concept?
The unstructured...
...the loosey-goosey, Monterey pop,
Woodstock kind of thing?
I like it very much,
and I think I can handle it.
So do I.
I'll keep this
to promote your new career with.
You'll be working with kids,
bright and marvelous.
But they take handling.
If this goes the way I think it will...
...there's no reason in the world why...
- Isn't this cozy?
So this is your business lunch?
How's business?
Friend of yours?
- Just another trick.
- That's enough.
Is that your idea of a dish?
She's a little old for you, isn't she?
What is this,
"Be Kind to Senior Citizens Week"?
Get outta here!
I don't mind you being a bastard,
but do you have to be a tasteless one?
Stop it, you son of a bitch!
She couldn't get laid in a lumber camp!
You're hurting me!
Stop it, you dirty bastard! No!
Stop it! Dave!
No! No!
Don't leave me! Don't leave me!
She's nothing! Nothing! Nothing!
- I love you!
- Get her outta here.
Where to?
I did it because I love you.
Don't you understand that?
- I love you!
- Where to?
- Move!
- It's because I love you! Dave, please.
This is a private beach.
- I want to talk to you.
- I don't want to talk to you.
Are you drunk?
No, but that's not a bad idea.
- Why, David?
- Why what? Drunk?
No. Why last night?
That's what I came to explain to you.
Okay, good.
I think we should understand each other.
I'm not very happy with you.
That's fair enough.
Whatever it was, you could have called me.
No, I couldn't.
Why not?
I couldn't tell you the truth last night.
I'm not gonna lie to you anymore.
Now, why do you have to say that?
I just didn't want to take a chance
she'd try it again.
What if she does?
I swear to you, if she ever tries it...
...l'd just let her go right on ahead.
God!
Oh, my God.
What in the...
Oh, God, help me!
Please, somebody, help me!
Help me, somebody!
Oh, God, help me!
- Stay back, buddy.
- I live here, man.
Is she your housecleaning lady, Garver?
Okay, boys, let's take her out.
Watch your step.
It's gonna cost you double
to clean up this mess.
Watch your step.
- Dave Garver?
- Yeah.
I'm Sgt. McCallum.
Any ideas?
About what?
About your girlfriend in there.
That's not my girlfriend.
Let me get that straight right in front.
More or less a casual acquaintance,
you'd say?
That's right.
You're saying she came by to hack up
your wardrobe and your cleaning lady?
I'm not trying to tell you anything,
Sergeant.
Maybe you ought to.
The lady almost got herself killed.
And I'm stumbling around
in my stupid way trying to find out why.
What'll you have?
This Evelyn Draper,
where does she come from?
I don't know.
- What about her family?
- I don't know that either.
She just listens to my radio show,
and we met one night. That's all.
- Practically a stranger.
- That's right.
Then how does she happen to have
a key to your front door?
I don't know that either.
It boils down to,
you don't know a hell of a lot, do you?
What it boils down to is,
I'm getting sick of your questions.
And so am I!
But they get upset with me
down at the store if I don't ask them.
- Just take her through. I'll be right along.
- Right.
- Take her through what?
- Booking.
What she really needs is psychiatric help.
Really?
Now, look, those cuts on her wrists...
Don't know anything about those.
There's one other thing.
I know, "Don't leave town."
I was gonna say, "Why don't you play
some Mantovani sometime?"
Didn't know you liked the show.
I don't. I like Mantovani.
Go ahead, play!
All right!
Those of you who may have played
brass instruments...
...you know that was triple-tonguin', baby.
Let's give his tongue a nice hand!
He might just be
the fastest tongue in the West!
- Come on.
- All right, I'm coming.
What do you say...
- Something to eat?
- I've got to pick up my roommate, Annabel.
- Madalyn's your roommate.
- I found my man, and I'm moving out.
- And Annabel's moving in.
- Right.
- 'Bye.
- Ciao.
See you later.
Thank you. Thank you very kindly.
That was the Cannonball Adderley Group.
They're playing
at the Monterey Jazz Festival with...
...Duke Ellington, Woody Herman,
Joe Williams and many others.
Still got tickets for Sunday.
So get on out there
because that's where it's happening.
Now we're gonna hear from the Gator
Creek Organization and Feelin' Fine.
KRML. Dave Garver.
Hello.
Play Misty for me.
David?
I didn't mean to shake you up. I'm sorry.
Pretty stupid of me.
I've been released.
Therapy. It was a bad dream, but it's over.
- Where are you?
- The airport. San Francisco.
I've only got a minute between planes.
- Got a job in Hawaii.
- You're all right then?
Fine, David. Fine.
I just want to say
how sorry I am about everything.
- Forget it. I have.
- I hope so.
"Because this maiden
she lived with no other thought
"Than to love and be loved by you."
Are you near a radio?
No.
But play it for me anyway.
Hello.
- Garver?
- Yeah.
Sgt. McCallum. Sorry to wake you
but something's come up.
I know. She just paid me a visit
with a butcher knife.
Why?
Because she was released on parole
pending further legal action.
When?
A week ago.
I sure like the way you broke your ass
to let me know!
- I just found out about it myself.
- Who's in charge down there anyway?
Now, look. Do you want to help find her...
...or would you rather just sit there
and bellyache?
- All right.
- Good.
Now exactly what did she say to you?
I told you. She said that she was well
and that she was going to Hawaii.
What else?
- I already told you.
- Tell me again.
You know,
you really make lousy conversation.
You make lousy coffee.
Come on, what else did she say?
Nothing, except...
- Except what?
- It was nothing. It was a line from a poem.
- What poem?
- Lf I knew that, I'd know the line.
- Try to remember.
- You know, McCallum, it's getting late.
You're sounding very monotonous.
You're not exactly my idea
of a swinging date either.
Good night, McCallum.
- What happened to the Mantovani?
- The what?
I heard the show,
but I never did hear you play Mantovani.
You really did listen to the show?
Friend, if we had a TV
down at the station...
...l'd break my arm
before I turned your show on.
Thanks a lot.
Just hope we're lucky enough
to grab her the next time she tries it.
Tries what?
To kill you.
Yeah. And if you're not lucky enough?
That'd be hell.
The guys down at the station
would have to chip in and buy a TV.
You're a great comfort, Sergeant.
You will change the locks?
Hi.
Nothing like a nice brisk walk in the woods
to put roses on a girl's cheeks.
How are you?
Not so good, honey.
- She's back.
- Who?
Evelyn Draper,
the girl who tried to kill Birdie.
How can she be back?
I thought they'd put her
in a state sanitarium.
- They did, but they let her out.
- Does that mean she's all right?
Theoretically.
What happens now?
I think you and I ought to stay away
from each other for a couple of days...
...just in case she's tagging after me.
She's already following you, isn't she?
I don't want you to worry about it.
I can handle myself.
Yeah. So could Birdie.
All right then, you stand by.
They're all set to trace the call.
When she phones, just mention her
by name right away, Evelyn...
...and they start to trace her.
All you gotta do after that
is just keep her talking.
Fifteen minutes
before the hour here at KRML...
...and here's It's Not Unusual.
I guess it hasn't come to you yet.
- What?
- What she said.
Over the phone last night?
Part of a poem or something.
You were gonna try to remember.
I thought I had that, but I've forgotten.
Is it that important?
Until we pick her up,
everything's important.
What's wrong?
I'm worried about my girlfriend
with all this going on.
They're so damn isolated down there.
I'm thinking the best thing to do
is just have Al Monte sub for me.
The only chance we've got
is when she phones in here tonight.
You've got to be here, right on that mike.
- Lf she phones.
- She will. Believe me.
But only if you're here.
I'll tell you what I'll do.
If it'll make you feel better, I'll go over
and check your girlfriend's house myself.
I'd sure appreciate that.
She lives on Spindrift Road.
I think it's the fourth or fifth house down.
- "Williams" is on the mailbox.
- Why don't you phone her?
- Okay.
- Tell her to be expecting me.
McCallum.
Thanks.
Public servant.
- Hello?
- Hi. I'm just checking in. You all right?
Marvelous.
I'm just getting ready to do my nails
and I got your program on.
And Annabel's in the kitchen
making a couple of coffee grogs.
What more could a girl ask for?
No, honey, everything's fine.
There's a Sgt. McCallum
that's gonna drop by for a second...
...to see if you've buttoned up all right.
Let him in, but nobody else.
Okay.
David, you want to play something
soft and dreamy for us?
You got it. Bye-bye.
'Bye, hon.
- Annabel, how's that stuff coming?
- Here's something soft and sentimental...
...for Tobie and Annabel.
Hope you like cinnamon in yours.
Whatever's right.
Annabel.
Good?
Too much.
- So is this.
- Thank you.
Just one thing. Do you mind?
No, be my guest.
The eyes are wrong.
David's are more...
How shall I say?
Colder.
I didn't know you knew David.
I didn't realize you and David...
...were friends.
Friends?
No, not friends.
Not friends.
God, you're dumb.
"Because this maiden
she lived with no other thought
"Than to love and be loved by you."
- Tobie?
- We're waiting for you, David.
This is Dave Garver with a little verse...
...a little talk and five hours of music...
...to be very, very nice to each other by.
Careful.
I might put your eye out.
I'll bet David loves your eyes.
And your hair.
Does he run his fingers through your hair?
Have to get you all nice for David.
For David.
I hope he likes what he sees
when he walks in here...
...because that's what
he's taking to hell with him.
Miss Williams?
McCallum?
And now we have a pretty one
for lonely lovers on a cool, cool night.
It's the great Erroll Garner classic, Misty.
And this one is especially for Evelyn.