My head.
- Hey, Nick.
- Gil. How you been?
Move. Move. I said move.
First of all, A, I'm a cop.
B, we're in New Orleans and it's July.
Doesn't it get itchy? Sweaty?
The paper.
Even though your face is covered,
I can tell, you need a hug.
- Back off.
- Come on.
- Come to papa.
- You crazy.
- Give it up.
- You're crazy, man.
No love? Really?
You coming?
- What did I do?
- How should I know?
You gonna pick that up?
Hurry, I gotta go to court.
I will not run in this heat, Gil.
Now you owe me a bullet. Let's go.
Thank you.
Come on, man. You can't lock me up
for walking down the street.
Guy with the persuader
pointed at my head?
I don't know that guy.
- What's in the paper?
- News. Newspaper.
Wallet.
And the gun.
Okay, easy tiger.
What's with the paper?
This is a really unsatisfying
conversation.
- Put him someplace uncomfortable.
- How you doing?
Better than you.
He took my money.
And when you tell me what
I'm arresting you for, you'll get it back.
Off to dance with Lady Justice.
Luckily, she hasn't known you very long.
Go.
I've always been lucky.
Hey. What the hell?
Firearm.
Thank you, sir.
You're Lena Valoise.
I was.
Tomorrow, Again
is one of my favorite movies.
Me too.
- Nick.
- How do you do?
Great. What are you doing here?
I've come to see my son,
the assistant DA.
Me too.
- You must be very proud.
- I must.
- They'll let you in dressed like that?
- I'm hoping.
- You look a little lost.
- I am. Courtroom 3?
Come. I'll show you.
We call it the thin blue line, the police.
The fragile barrier
between the bad guys and you.
We give policemen
like Detective Nick Blades guns.
We pay them well.
And all we ask in return
is that they do what they swear they'll do.
Protect and serve.
But what happens
if they break that promise?
What happens if one day you can't tell
the good guys from the bad guys?
Your Honor, would Mr. Gold
care to join us in this case?
- Counsel?
- Chaos, my friends.
Anarchy.
The very wardrobe he so disrespectfully
wears in this courtroom...
...is emblematic of the point.
- Objection.
- Sustained.
When I was a kid,
I believed in Batman and Superman.
- Mr. Gold....
- You know what? I still do.
I believe there is such a thing
as right and wrong.
I believe in an irrepressible commitment
to the truth.
An irreproachable moral and ethical code
that cannot be compromised.
Detective Blades thought
he could be the law, but not follow it.
That's not right, ladies and gentlemen.
That's wrong.
Thank you.
We will adjourn for the day.
First time he called the police on me
he was 9.
- What'd you do?
- I took away his LEGOs.
Mr. Gold.
Your reaction
to the DA's decision to retire?
Clark Gunn has had a brilliant career.
I'll miss him.
Do you have any comments
on a frontrunner for the interim slot?
I've been dealing with police corruption.
It doesn't leave a lot of time
to deal with office personnel matters.
Do you plan on attending
Willie Van Beber's execution?
I did my job...
...putting Willie Van Beber
right where he belongs.
I'll let the good Lord and his executioner
take it from there.
Excuse me.
You people don't mind if I borrow my son,
the assistant DA, do you?
- I won't keep him long.
- Mom.
You sure you don't have
an announcement to make?
Your father is having an affair.
Would you and the good Lord
care to comment on that?
- I do not have time for this.
- What do you mean?
Every time you say
Dad's having sex with someone else.
Go to the country house.
Where's the van?
It's dead.
You were gonna replace the battery.
I thought we'd agree
we only use the Hawk in an emergency.
This is an emergency. Hurry.
I have a facial and massage at 1 :30.
Honey, this car represents
the last fragile thread of dignity...
...holding my family together.
Take my car. Park in my spot.
Theo.
I thought on people's birthdays, other
people are supposed to do what they want.
And I thought turning 40
meant not acting 7.
I'm pretty sure that you are having lunch
with the next DA.
Great. And you'll still earn less
than our gardener...
...and I'll still be paying for lunch
with my parents' credit card.
Jeez, Kelly, come on. Don't do this.
Just give me today. You're the one who
wants to live in a house big enough for 12.
You're the one who has the spa thing.
Not me.
I'm leaving.
I'm not done yet.
Leaving you.
Actually, you're the one leaving
since my parents own the house.
I'll give you one week
to get your things and get out.
Today you do this? Today?
On my birthday?
- The biggest day of my career?
- What about the 15 years...
...I've wasted on someone
going precisely nowhere?
Kelly, come on.
Wait a minute. What about the kids?
I can't live without my kids.
Really? And how many hours do you
spend with them on any given week?
- Two?
- Everything I do is because of them.
Finkle, Harbin, and Klotz offered you
three times what the DA's job pays.
- And you turned it down.
- Money isn't everything.
I believe in what I do. Is that so wrong?
And I believe in private school.
Is that so wrong?
Yeah? Okay.
They want me back.
- Right away, sir.
- Good.
Because I don't.
I'm sorry.
Please remember
to put the cover back on the Hawk.
- Good nap, counsel?
- Sorry.
I've received the following note
from the jurors.
"We have voted several times.
We are split 6-6 as to all counts.
We want to go home."
- They've only been out a couple of hours.
- Mr. Gold, sit.
The jury is deadlocked.
I declare a mistrial.
Would you like to set the matter
for retrial?
Yes. Absolutely, yes.
Blades? I don't care what the jury did.
You're on leave until you deal
with Internal Affairs. Do you hear me?
Until I say so, you are not police.
Trust me, LT, when I'm through with IA,
they're gonna rush out...
...and get my name tattooed
across their butt cheeks.
- Give me five.
- Nice going.
- Hey, way to go.
- Good job.
- Congrats.
- Where's Gil Ott?
Was in Interview 4,
but Schaefer needed the room...
...so he took him over to the jail.
Want me to go get him?
No, I'll go.
Dinner to celebrate? I'm buying.
You're buying? Or is Gil buying?
Technically, yeah, Gil's buying.
He was carrying the paper the cash
when I popped him.
Then some ape in a wool ski mask
came at me with a piece.
- He wanted this.
- Gil's delivering newspapers now?
There's numbers and letters
circled all over it.
Can you get Forensics to look at it?
It's some kind of code.
I tried to decipher it
but Gold's closing was distracting.
Sure. Yeah, I'll check it out.
I'll go sit on Gil.
Blades strikes me
as a pretty unimpressive bad guy.
He's dirty.
So he skimmed a few bucks.
He got drunk and over did it in a bar.
Yes, exactly. We used to call that felony
larceny and assault with a deadly weapon.
I understand Internal Affairs
is going to water board him next week.
Trust cops to deal with cops?
- Just give it some thought.
- We're retrying it.
Wouldn't it be nice
if life was all blacks and whites?
Turns out, it's mostly grays.
- Is that supposed to mean something?
- I'm just trying to get you to see the forest.
Okay, I'm drowning in metaphors here.
Am I supposed to see the forest
or mostly grays?
Look, everything I know
comes from you.
A much younger and stupider me.
- Are you happy doing this?
- I'm extremely happy.
Good. Grant Stone's gonna get
the interim appointment as the DA.
You're kidding? Grant Stone?
- You're a great trial lawyer.
- I'm the senior deputy.
And everyone in the office thinks
you're an asshole. So do the judges.
Most of the defense bar.
I should start caring about
defense lawyers?
Everybody in the system
gets chewed up, Theo.
Including the poor bastards
we send to prison.
Grant Stone cares about the bad guys.
That makes him more qualified than me--
Theo. Take some time off.
Go home. Look in the mirror.
I need Gil Ott for an interview.
- Not here.
- Where is he?
Check again. Detective Schaefer
brought him earlier.
- Come see for yourself.
- I had a hold on the guy.
The computer says the man isn't here.
What do you want? I just came on.
- Who was here earlier?
- Chin.
- Where'd Chin go?
- Chin and me ain't that close.
What the crap? Come on.
What's up with the sneak attack?
License, registration,
proof of insurance.
I'm a DA.
License, registration,
proof of insurance.
License.
My registration.
Have you had anything to drink tonight,
Mr. Gould, is it?
It's Gold. Theo Gold.
I'm chief assistant district attorney.
I was in my office all night working.
I'd appreciate you telling me what I did.
- Have you had anything to drink tonight?
- No.
Mr. Gold, you're becoming upset.
Please calm down.
If you do not calm down,
I will have to place you under arrest.
Are you joking? What is all this about?
- Please step out of the car.
- No.
Mr. Gold, please step out
of the vehicle now.
I am placing you under arrest.
This is absolutely ridiculous.
Mr. Gold, you are resisting arrest.
- No, I'm not.
- You are definitely resisting arrest.
What are you talking about?
If you continue to resist arrest,
I will Tase you.
Are you out of your freaking mind?
- Should I go again?
- Said Tase him, not barbecue him.
Make the call. Let's go 10-99.
Detective Nick Blades...
...there's something shocking
you should see, State and Chestnut.
Get the hell away from me.
- Mr. Gold, stop.
- Get the hell off of me.
- Then stop swinging at me.
- Fine.
Just leave me alone.
I can't believe your mom's Lena Valoise.
I've seen Tomorrow, Again
like 50 times.
Please don't speak to me.
What happened?
Two policemen kidnapped
and Tased me.
Friends of yours, I presume.
I've never been Tased myself.
Imagine the worst dental appointment
of all time.
You got lucky, detective.
It won't happen again.
I've always been lucky.
Today's my birthday.
I hope it's the best one ever.
Kelly!
No, no. Don't do this to me.
Kelly.
- Where's the Hawk?
- I have no idea.
- You know what time it is?
- Hawk's not in the driveway.
Give me the keys to your car.
The keys!
- Why?
- Because that minivan is dead...
...apparently,
your precious Hawk is missing...
...and you may remember,
I'm going to my parents...
...until you get the hell out of my house.
That's why.
Come on, Kelly, I'm begging.
Just give me a little more time
to explain to the kids.
- Bye, Daddy.
- Bye, guys. Daddy loves you.
See you soon.
This asshole must be having
the worst day of his life.
He just called in to report that
someone stole his car out of his driveway.
Stop, now you're just trying to hurt me.
- Where's it at?
- How should I know?
Wait, you don't think we stole his car?
You know what happens
when you wake up in the morning...
...and you can't tell the difference between
good guys and bad?
- Where's the car?
- Chaos, detective.
Anarchy.
And the Cubs win the World Series.
I'm telling you, Blades, the report is legit.
We didn't do it.
Yeah?
- What are you gonna do about your father?
- Nothing.
We've done our share of fooling around
over the years, Theo, but this is ridiculous.
It's time for him to hang up his sword and
die with something approaching dignity.
Mom, I don't need to hear this.
The worst part is he's lost interest in me.
I thought it was the cancer,
so I didn't push. But now I know.
- I still have needs, Theo.
- Please, stop, enough already.
What time are you picking us up
for lunch?
Theo?
I'm sorry, I have to cancel.
Kelly has my car.
- So take the van.
- It's dead.
Again? All right, you have my permission
to use the Hawk, just be very careful.
- I can't.
- Why not? What's wrong with the Hawk?
I don't believe this.
I gotta go.
If something happens to that automobile,
it'll kill your father.
- I'm hanging up the phone now.
- And I don't mean that metaphorically.
Move out of the street.
I just had an accident.
I think I may have broken something.
Please move out of the street
or I'll have to cite you.
I'm bleeding here. I'm bleeding here.
Move now.
My car was stolen. I saw the guy driving it
around the corner two minutes ago.
- I tried to go after him on the bike.
- Stolen, huh? Shocking.
Drive around the block, you might find him.
It's a 1957 Studebaker Golden Hawk.
I don't see anything.
- You're gonna have to call in a report.
- I did.
You know, I'm about to go off shift
if you want a ride downtown.
Thank you.
Okay, Blades,
so now you're buying two dinners.
And not the Whole Foods deli again,
either.
Someplace where they bring food
to the table.
Let's see what you got,
then we'll decide.
Well, it was code. Forensics figures it
for driver's license numbers.
- Maybe.
- Maybe?
- Did you run the registrations?
- Yep. And it's four local Louisiana plates.
It's just that there are three extra letters.
WVB or BVW,
depending on how you read it.
But one of the cars is registered
to YouTube's latest sensation, Taser Boy.
Theo Gold?
He reported his car stolen this morning.
- So, what is this, a shopping list?
- Gold must have a pretty nice car.
If we have the list and Gil's in jail,
how does the car get stolen?
- Jail has no record of him being there.
- That's impossible.
- I saw Schaefer walk him out the door.
- I'm gonna go hunt down Gil.
- You want me to call Gold?
- Let me deal with that.
Check with Schaefer and Chin.
I'm gonna stop by a couple of addresses
on my way to Gil's.
Okay.
Hi, Nick.
Blades. Goddamn it.
If you're out there impersonating
a police officer, I will pinch you myself.
- You got IA in 48 hours.
- I'm looking forward to it.
In the meantime,
I'm having my teeth cleaned...
...and maybe a trim.
- I've been waiting over an hour.
- I understand you've had a jolt, Mr. Gold.
There's no need to get all charged up.
We're having a busy morning here.
So as soon as we can unplug an officer
from another matter, we'll be with you.
Sergeant Rand, call your supervisor
and tell him to come out here now.
Lieutenant, Mr. Gold currently needs
to see you.
Thank you, sir.
Yes?
I understand that my reputation
precedes me.
I'll live with the abuse, okay?
But I'm here over an hour...
...my car was stolen,
and I just want a little help. That's all.
Despite the fact you've been trying
to put one of my best cops in jail...
...I find this conversation scintillating.
You, in fact,
may describe it as electrifying.
- How you doing?
- Good.
I'm detective Nick Blades,
New Orleans police.
- You're the one on TV.
- That's me.
- Your parents home?
- No.
- They at work?
- I give up. Where are they?
- Dead.
My grandma says
that if she was on the jury...
...she'd vote to send you to jail.
I guess I'm glad
your grandma's not on the jury.
My grandma says
you should be ashamed of yourself.
I am. Your grandma take care of you?
- Yeah.
- Is she home?
No.
Is that your grandma's car
in the driveway?
- Yeah.
- Then who's Dean Nickerson?
- My brother.
- So he owns the car?
- Yeah.
- Is he home?
- No.
- Where's he?
- Jail.
Does he get out soon?
My grandma said it depends if his jury
is as dumb as yours.
Tell your grandma
to lock the car up tight.
All right.
- Hand over the money already.
- It's not like it's because you got nothing.
Yeah, well.
It's okay, guys.
- Who might you be?
- Detective Nick Blades.
- Police?
- What are you, an idiot? He just said that.
Never heard of you. Let's see it.
Settle down, guys.
I think he's had enough.
Enjoy.
- You looking for Gil?
- Yeah.
- What'd the creep do this time?
- I don't know. Ask him.
What you want with Gil?
Where is the little creep?
After he robbed 400 off me,
he didn't leave no forwarding address.
- You see him with this guy?
- No.
- What's the boy into these days?
- You think he tells me?
All I know is, last time I saw him,
he was okay.
- He even asked me to dinner.
- He took you to Olive Garden.
I chose Olive Garden.
Can you hand me my badge, please, sir?
Thank you.
- I ain't no charity case.
- I took it off Gil.
I also took that off Gil.
Call 911. Or shoot him.
Either way, I wasn't here.
- Hey, Rosalyn.
- I heard.
I'm sure they'll find it.
But with my luck,
somebody will probably have peed in it.
- I'm confused.
- What'd you hear?
- Grant Stone, the interim appointee.
- Yeah.
Well, also in the meantime...
...my wife is taking away my kids,
my car was stolen...
...and because of Blades,
I'm getting no help from the cops.
- That sucks.
- Yes, indeed, it does.
My dad wanted me to be a dentist.
I should have listened.
- My father wants me to be a DA.
- He's a wise man, your father.
That's much better than rotting teeth.
You mentioned the Van Beber case.
Here's the murder book.
The whole story.
Man, I had that guy cold.
And everyone was mad at me
for not dealing.
The judge was mad at me
for ruining his summer vacation.
The boss didn't want me tied up
for three months.
Even the jurors hated me.
Everyone kept saying the same thing.
Plead it. Settle it. Compromise.
Well, in one week, Willie Van Beber
gets his just punishment...
...because I refused to compromise.
Grab that, will you?
- Hello?
- Kelly...
...you get your husband
on the phone right now.
- His father's finally gone over the edge.
- This isn't Kelly.
- Who the hell is this?
- You need to grab this now.
- Yeah.
- Who was that?
I thought it was Kelly, for God's sake.
I'm the village idiot telling some stranger
about our problems like it's CNN.
- Mom, calm down.
- I will not calm down.
We were leaving the doctor and suddenly
he insisted we come to your house.
When you weren't here,
he got very upset and locked himself...
- ...in your room with a gun.
- Dad has a gun?
Apparently. He must've had it
in that ridiculous fanny pack he wears...
- ...like some geriatric Dirty Harry.
- Where the hell did he get a gun?
How should I know?
You know how paranoid he is.
You can buy guns
in vending machines now.
- Call the cops.
- No. I will not have some SWAT team...
...blasting through the door
scaring your father to death.
Just stay away from him.
I'll be there as soon as I can. I gotta go.
- Same guy.
- Here he comes.
Good afternoon, Mr. Meter-Maid, sir.
Where'd you get those tickets? Kinko's?
Nice pants.
Nick? Oh, my God.
What are you doing here?
- Did Theo call you?
- Is this a bad time?
He's been threatening to kill himself
for the last 20 minutes.
- I'm sorry, who are we talking about?
- My husband.
Herb, I want the truth.
After 42 years, not a hell of a lot to ask.
Along with everything else,
he's cheating.
Mr. Gold, this is the police.
Can you hear me?
Herb. What did you do?
- Wait.
- Marty. Holy moly.
Put down the gun.
- Oh, Lord. Enough already.
- Marty, you look like crap.
He's not well, Nick.
He thinks you're his dead brother, Martin.
You're lucky. He won't shoot Marty.
- I've always been lucky.
- Kid.
You need a haircut.
I said I'd stay with him in sickness
and in health.
Now he's sick and I'm staying.
But I can't abide the cheating.
These are hotel receipts.
That's where he takes her.
Just follow him. I'll pay.
I wanna know the truth.
That sounds like a bad idea.
Wait a minute.
Didn't Theodore call you?
I heard about your son's car being stolen,
thought I could help.
What car?
- Oh, my God. The Hawk?
- Where's Dad?
- Where's the car?
- Is he okay?
He's sleeping.
And I'm just fine, thanks for asking.
Detective Blades happened to stop by
and everything's under control.
- I heard about the car.
- You heard about the car.
He heard about the car.
That's why he's here, Theo.
He's agreed to help find the car.
And the other matter?
Forget the other matter for the moment.
You and Theo find the Hawk.
I'll do everything I can
to keep this from your father.
I'll expect regular reports.
- She wants reports.
- I heard.
- Sorry, Dad.
- That's okay.
This is a very comfortable mattress.
- It must have cost you a bundle.
- Probably did.
Kelly bought it.
- Where did you get a gun, Dad?
- I bought it.
- Five, maybe seven years ago.
- Why?
Same reason everybody buys one.
It's a crazy world out there, son.
And I got like 30 percent off.
Don't you tell your mother.
I think the cat's out of the bag, Dad.
Am I dreaming this
or is your Uncle Marty here?
Uncle Marty?
Of course, he had to leave.
Took my gun.
I think that's probably for the best.
Theo, your mother
has to try this mattress.
I mean, it is incredible. You should try it.
Come on. Try it. Come on.
Yeah. So?
It is. It's a great mattress.
It is sublime is what it is.
Yeah.
It's nice.
- Sorry about your dad.
- Thanks.
- What's the car worth?
- I have no idea.
- Five?
- Triple that, at least.
In Buenos Aires, it's worth 100.
Now it's in a garage.
Tomorrow, on a truck. Monday, on a ship.
- You got 48 hours.
- That's what the police are for.
Trust me, you're not getting any play
from the department.
- Why you doing this?
- Two hundred a day, courtesy your mother.
You get your way, I'm gonna need
all the money I can scrape together.
I'm not dropping the charges,
even if you do find the car.
It's not just about the money.
Technically, it's my fault.
- Why?
- Yesterday I busted a guy named Gil Ott.
- You know him?
- How would I know him?
Gil was carrying a newspaper with
plates numbers written in code on it.
Your plate number was on the list.
I'm not surprised somebody has his eye
on the Hawk. It's a very nice car.
- Your mother seems to like it.
- She better like it.
I wasted every weekend of my childhood
working on that damn car.
It's a bit hard to explain.
It's kind of like their second child.
I get it.
So, what do we do? We go see Ott,
you slap him around a little...
...he tells us where my car is?
When I arrested Gil, I had to be in court,
so I had to park him.
While you were blasting me
in front of the jury, he slipped.
- How did he slip?
- I have no idea.
But I'll assume that he delivered
a copy of the list once he got out.
So how do we find my car?
How should I know?
- Aren't you, like, some great detective?
- Yeah.
Although, technically,
I'm on administrative leave.
Grab a mirror out of the glove box.
I think I got a tail.
Don't do that.
What--?
A real Second Amendment man, huh?
You ever use one of those?
I'm a lawyer. My mind is my weapon.
I'm betting you're gonna shoot me
long before I find your car.
Come on.
- Is this Gil supposed to be dangerous?
- Gil's not here.
Why are we here?
Come on, let's go.
- I left the gun in the car.
- Good.
The martial way is more than a sport.
It is our discipline.
It is our philosophy.
It is our way of life.
Gentlemen, we honor the master
and the practice...
...by bowing when we enter the dojo.
We're police. You Edward Mackie?
Actually, I'm with the district attorney.
Are you insane?
Ever see that scene in Indiana jones
where he watches some guy...
...with a big sword do his thing
and then shoots him?
In this situation, I'm Indy.
Move. Now.
- Sir, you can't park here.
- Do me a favor, pal--
Move.
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
Theodore, put thing down
before you kill someone.
Hey. Hey, give me a break.
- Sorry.
- A little pass for a fellow law enforcer?
It's already in the book.
Thanks for everything.
That's why those people
are so widely despised.
There's no give and take.
No compromise.
What does any of this
have to do with my car?
This one's on the list too.
It's Ed Mackie's.
- That was Ed in there, the karate guy?
- Yeah.
- Where's Ed?
- I guess Ed fled.
- Yo.
- Ed Mackie has a sheet.
In prison,
he was with the 4-4 Syndicate.
Another one of the 4-4's, I suspect,
looking for Gil at his father's place.
Do me a favor, ping the rest of the names
before I do more good deeds.
Start with Dean Nickerson.
Tried him this morning. He's in jail.
Since when did Gil Ott get connected?
The boy's running
so he must have burned somebody.
- Run the rest, see what comes up.
- Okay.
I seem to recall something about
my mother paying you to find my car?
It's a 1956 Studebaker Golden Hawk?
Remember?
- What do you know about prison gangs?
- A prison gang has my car?
Possibly. There seems to be a connection
between gangs and the list.
Before I was chief assistant,
I did head up the gang prosecution unit.
- I put Willie Van Beber on death row.
- Really?
- Really.
- Isn't he about to be executed?
Couldn't happen to a nicer fellow.
Get in.
Get in. Come on, move, move.
- You, too.
- Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
Go, go, go.
You hungry?
The doughnuts here are excellent.
No, thanks. You're like a walking cliché.
- Prosecutors don't eat?
- We eat when we're not being kidnapped.
Brother Blades. So nice to see you.
Happy, this is my partner,
Roberto Clemente.
The sainted ballplayer. It's my honor.
So I send one of my guys to find Gil Ott
and he ends up locked up.
You know anything about that?
I heard some old guys
kicked the shit out him.
- What's fresh?
- The maple just came out.
Give me six maple, two glazed,
and four chocolate with rainbow sprinkles.
And I'll need the paper back
when you're done reading it.
It's like warm maple syrup
being poured over your tongue.
- Rover.
- Cost me 50 grand to bail him out.
- That's a lot of doughnuts.
- You still police?
- Technically, he's on administrative leave.
- Technically.
Why do they never see that coming?
What a waste of 50 grand.
Take the damn handcuffs off, idiots.
- You make any sense of this?
- License plate numbers.
That one on the list?
Yep.
It's mine.
Better watch it.
People are stealing the cars on this list.
Yeah. I'll make sure to use my Club.
That was my guy yesterday,
outside the bar.
- Guy in the ski mask?
- Yeah.
Why a wool mask in July?
I was hoping to grab Gil
before he delivered the paper.
So I did you a favor.
Figured the paper was for you.
No, the paper wasn't for me.
Prison gangs have an unnecessarily
bad reputation, Blades.
4-4 Syndicate started with four poor
convicts on the four yard at Angola.
I was one of them. It was a social club.
I understand you've since
diversified considerably.
And like all other complex organizations,
we have our internal differences.
The newspaper was a delivery
from Willie Van Beber...
...to a pro hitter, identity unknown.
You know who Van Beber is?
Big shot 4-4.
About to get the needle, right?
Me and Willie, we started out together.
Now he's angry at me for various reasons.
He's running out of time.
So, he's tidying up his affairs.
You get me?
I believe I do.
So you didn't do me a favor.
You screwed things up.
I don't need that list.
It's already been replaced.
I need Gil because he's the one
that can ID the person out on the street...
...taking orders from Van Beber.
- Still with me?
- Yeah.
If you hadn't popped Gil,
I'd have his contact and it would be over.
I'm genuinely sorry. I had no idea
my nose was in your business.
- Yeah. These things happen.
- So where's Ed?
Ed's dead. Or will be shortly.
And you better keep your eye
on your little pal Roberto the DA...
...because if he's not on the list,
he will be.
You know
he's the one that put Willie down.
He's on the list.
Like I said, find Gil.
Get his contact, take him off the street,
or feed him to me.
Then, hopefully,
Van Beber will go to his great reward...
...and I'll get back
to my goddamn doughnuts.
- Blades.
- It's not cars. It's bodies.
- That's illegal now.
- Hold on.
Do you mind?
I'm trying to have a conversation here.
I mind. You're putting my life at risk
and those of everyone around you.
Idiot!
Hey, I'm back.
Got four license plates.
Other than Gold, three white males...
...all have long sheets, all are 4-4's.
Are you ready for the best part?
How many non-Whole Foods dinners
am I up to? I'm going to prison soon.
Two of out of the three
have federal jackets.
Happy Conners is a snitch?
That's hard to believe.
Negative. It's Ed Mackie and
Dean Nickerson are the informants.
- Which agency?
- FBI.
Happy says it's a hit list from a guy
named Willie Van Beber. Know him?
Yeah, he's a 4-4 shot caller.
I thought they executed him.
Very soon. This is his last hurrah.
It has to be one of us who sold Van Beber
the names of the informants.
Who has access to the FBI
informant database?
Anyone senior in this department or
in any other in the region, state or federal.
Why is Gold on the list though?
I'm sure there's more than a few
who wanna smoke Gold.
I expect it's because
he put Van Beber on death row.
Our hero.
So do you want me to run it up the pole?
No, we put this out there,
our leaky cop evaporates.
True.
Glass finds out I'm working this,
he'll have a coronary. I don't need that.
- What are you doing?
- I'll see if Dee has a line on Gil.
- Let it ride for a few hours.
- You sure?
- Come on! What are you doing?
- No.
Come on! Dude!
You coming?
Five-0 in the house.
Was that really necessary?
I keep my love of food
and my professional life separate.
- Fatty.
- Blades.
Give me a slab to go with
the sauce on the side.
I heard you paid off that jury.
I had no choice.
Couldn't live without your ribs.
And you get off?
You know there ain't no justice.
Along with my order,
I'll need an address on Gil Ott.
I don't know no Gil.
I know a Phil, goes by Little Philly.
And I do know me a Bill.
Theodore, assume for a moment...
...most of the people in this place
are on parole, probation...
...or otherwise in the system.
How long would it take for me to find out
one of them is in possession of a gun...
...resulting in their immediate
and protracted incarceration?
You ain't even no police.
Technically, I'm on administrative leave.
Feel free to call me any time
within the next five minutes.
Yeah.
Planting evidence, a.k.a. framing.
Most importantly, what does any of it
have to do with finding my car?
- You didn't even get what you came for.
- I did.
Fat Dee didn't even tell you where Gil is.
Talk to me.
Thanks, Fatty. I owe you.
Hey. You can't just go and
do whatever you want in life, Blades.
There are systems and rules.
These systems and rules exist
for a reason.
- You've prosecuted hundreds of cases.
- Yes.
And not once have you just cut a corner,
just bent a little.
You know what the United States
Supreme Court says?
United States Supreme Court says
a prosecutor is a representative...
...not of an ordinary party
to a controversy. No, sir.
As a prosecutor,
I am the representative of our sovereignty...
...whose obligation
to govern impartially...
...is as compelling as its obligation
to govern at all.
- You lost me at Supreme-something.
- Which means, detective...
...my solemn obligation
is not to win cases, but to do justice.
I make one wrong move,
I'm worse than the guy I'm prosecuting.
- It must be very tiring to be you.
- It can be.
It's very tiring to be around you.
You just bought a slab of ribs.
You kidding me? The last time I ate
at Fat Dee's, I was on the toilet for a week.
This place rocks.
I'll have a number three.
What are you having?
I'm feeling really lost. Can you try
and explain to me what's happening?
Your car look anything like that?
That's it. I don't believe this.
That's it. That's my car.
- I'm waiting on my sandwich.
- Who cares about your sandwich?
I'm sorry, Theodore, I would, I swear.
I have to meet with someone.
It's important.
- More important than my car?
- Hard to imagine, but yes.
Give me the keys.
It's good news.
We know it's still on the street.
I'm done.
Maybe I haven't made myself clear...
...on how important that car is
to my father. To me.
- I realize this is all just one big joke to you.
- It's not.
I need to find that car, Blades.
My family is gone, my career is shit,
my mother's insane and my father's dying.
The one thing I got half a chance of doing
is finding that car.
And if you can't or won't help me,
then goddamn it, I will do it myself.
Get off. Get off.
- Get off me.
- Sorry about this, Theodore.
Hello? I'm kidnapped. Here, here.
This is why this country's
going in the toilet.
- I've been kidnapped.
- What's with your perp?
- Actually, that's the guy prosecuting me.
- Really?
- Really.
- Edward Mackie's dead.
I just saw him.
Called from the trunk of his car
after you told me about the list.
- Died before we got there.
- Trunk? What happened?
A pro, for sure.
You were right about Mackie,
he was working for us.
- Happy Conners said he'd get hit.
- Happy Conners is a lucky bastard.
Mackie would have put him down forever.
I was actually figuring Happy
for the body.
I don't think so. Happy's on the list.
He tried to get it stopped.
- You know Willie Van Beber?
- 4-4 number-one shot caller?
Happy said it's his thing.
They must have some kind of beef.
Van Beber's settling up
before he gets executed.
They wanna kill each other,
it's fine with me.
Start smoking my informants,
I get annoyed.
I mean, Mackie means
we lose two ongoing investigations.
He made the list
for putting Van Beber on the row.
- How nice. Buy him a drink on me.
- You should be helping.
After you get your delivery boy,
plug the damn leak.
We're not even looking for my car.
I doubt we ever were.
- You need to trust me.
- What do you think I've been doing?
These things take time. Have faith.
- Those hurt.
- They're supposed to hurt.
I don't understand. Why are we waiting?
If Fat Dee is right, why don't we
just go in and get Gil Ott now?
Fools rush in, my friend.
I hate golf.
Other than working on the Hawk, this was
the one thing my father and I did together.
I just always feel like wrapping the clubs
around people's necks.
You just have to relax.
How?
Before you swing, breathe.
Okay, time's up. I'll go get him.
If Gil Ott's in there,
you think my car is nearby?
- Nope.
- Well, that's wonderful.
- You sure you don't need me?
- You keep breathing. I'll be back.
- Hey, Blades.
- Gil. How you been?
Until about two seconds ago,
pretty good.
We were in the middle of a conversation.
How'd you get out?
- Out where?
- Jail.
- You know what was in that paper?
- Blades, I pick up, I drop off.
My job is not to say shit about shit.
If I don't do my job, I'm dead. Okay?
Paper had the name of 4-4's,
two of which were federal snitches.
- One's already smoked.
- Don't tell me. I don't wanna know.
It also had the name of a DA named Theo
Gold, who also happens to be a friend.
You get the needle for whacking a DA.
- That is not my thing.
- Technically, it is your thing.
You're the only one
who can ID the source...
...which is why I assume you're whacked
out in this caddy shack shit hole.
That's just rude. I live here.
- This must be Mrs. Gil.
- Toss it.
Everybody wants you, Gil. Cops, 4's, FBI.
But I'm the only one that can save you.
Tell them I said hello, and goodbye.
- Easy, tiger.
- Yeah, yeah.
Sit down.
I need your contact. One name.
Give me that name and maybe
I'll let you live so you can remodel.
You're a real sweetheart, Blades.
Back inside.
Now!
You want me to go after them
or get those off you?
- Because I can't be in two places at once.
- Forget it.
- I'm really trying here, Blades.
- I appreciate the effort.
Did you ask about the car?
I forgot.
It's okay.
I'm sorry I shot you.
Nothing nine Band-Aids
and a bottle of Cuervo won't fix.
I did predict you'd shoot me.
I remember.
I decided I wanted to live
more than I want my car.
My father will understand that.
I'll take you home.
Just drop me off at my parents'.
I'll break the news.
I can already see his face.
God, I'd do anything to avoid
that slightly disappointed...
...but not altogether surprised look.
You know the look?
Please.
I got two ex-wives and a 14-year-old
daughter I see one weekend a month.
I know the look.
Theo, go get him before
one of the neighbors calls the police.
Yeah.
- Yep.
- What are you doing?
Call you in a bit.
I can't tell whether
I'm being guarded or surveilled.
Your little redheaded
co-counsel Rosalyn Wohl?
- She's the one that bailed Gil out of jail.
- Really? Why?
- Thought maybe you'd know.
- I don't know.
I just know her from working on your case.
She's a good lawyer.
- Have access to the informant database?
- Sure.
She just works on misdemeanors.
Why would she want access to that?
- Those names are worth a lot to some.
- Come on. That's ridiculous.
She can go to any private firm in this city
and make five times what she's making.
She doesn't need to sell informant data
for money, okay?
- You want me to call her? Let me call her.
- Thanks, Theodore. Maybe later.
My mother wants you to come in
for my belated birthday dinner.
She also wants to see where I shot you.
And please stop calling me Theodore.
First aid courtesy of Lena Valoise.
I'm living the dream, my friend.
She knows nothing about first aid.
She just likes to see other people's pain.
- She thinks we're looking for the Hawk.
- We're not?
Can you do the entire Valoise family a
favor and just stay off the subject? Please?
Did you know that Robert Evans was
our neighbor for a while in California?
Of course,
that was before he became huge.
- Actually, he was always huge.
- That's incredible.
Apparently not so incredible
that he cast me in anything.
Herb did everyone's teeth back then.
Sonny and Cher. Bobby Redford.
Bobby had a terrible overbite.
Tell me again. Who are you?
Blades is the corrupt police officer.
I'm the prosecutor in the case.
That is very interesting.
Your son's a great lawyer.
We would have preferred
if he had gone into dentistry...
...but you give them wings,
they fly away.
You know how it is, Marty.
I put the moves on Larry Olivier once.
That was before anyone told me
about his, you know, style.
Can I have another piece of cake?
Can you just cut it? Thank you.
- You have a home?
- Not much of one, no.
I used to think I had one.
Now I realize I burned it down
without even knowing.
Homes get rebuilt.
All I wanted was to spend
whatever time my dad has left...
...driving around with him in the Hawk.
- Pulling plugs. You know?
- And sending me to prison.
I figured this is the time
to be a good son.
After, I'd try to be a better
husband and father.
Tell me about your daughter.
She lives with her mom.
All the money I skimmed from the
detective busts went toward her school.
Child care, alimony, braces, whatever.
Life.
I feel horrible about it.
You expect me to drop the case...
...because you have the same problems
that everybody else does.
- You regret committing multiple felonies?
- I do.
- Regret it or expect me to drop the case?
- Ideally, both.
People get divorced
and pay for braces all the time...
- ...without skimming drug money.
- That's because they're not cops.
They lack opportunity.
Maybe.
I mean, my wife's family has money.
Otherwise my kids would be screwed.
You still can't tell me
what we've been doing for the past day?
For the moment, no.
And the car is safely on its way
to Argentina.
Bon voyage, old friend.
Theo, Nick, let's go.
I'm starting the movie.
Tomorrow, Again,
again and again and again.
- It's a great movie.
- Yeah. She's not your mother.
What's that about your mother?
Theo was just telling me
that Lena's not my mother.
You didn't know that?
I told you, detective, my father dropped
me off at the hotel. I was alone.
- He signed for a nightcap.
- That's really distracting.
- I can't help it.
- Try.
You're lying, Ms. McPherson.
He was there with you. He used three
capital letters to sign for the drink.
WMP. William McPherson.
Why do you hate me?
Don't you know?
I'm Willa McPherson. People love me.
- You too?
- I can't help it, I love it.
That scene kills me every time.
You mind pausing it?
I gotta hit the restroom.
- WVB?
- Yeah.
The initials at the end of the list.
A signature.
Makes sense, but we figured
it came from him.
And I talked to Rosalyn Wohl...
...and she says Gil snitched for her
in a possession case last year.
So she felt like she owed him a favor.
Gil gave her some story
about the hold being trumped up.
- She seemed really embarrassed.
- Do something for me.
Check and see
if Van Beber has any kids.
Nick, what the heck
are you doing in there?
- I gotta go. Just check.
- Okay.
I'm sorry.
Okay, that's it.
Thanks everybody for a wonderful birthday.
I'm going home.
- I'll bring your car back in the morning.
- Who said you could take my car?
You say you'll bring it back
and I nod like a robot?
I'll take him. Just let me get this. Yo.
Detective Blades? It's Rosalyn Wohl.
- Yes?
- Who is that?
- Is that Rosalyn?
- I'm listening.
- Want me to talk to her?
- What do I get?
He says he'll give you the guy
who's killing the people on the list.
All right. Where?
- Where what?
- I'm scared, Blades.
Just do what he says.
- What does Gil want?
- The list.
- Why?
- If he gets the list back...
...his employer refrains
from putting a bullet in his ear.
- So he's trading Rosalyn for the list?
- That's the story.
You don't have the list. Happy took it.
- Affirmative.
- Why am I on a hit list, Blades?
You know all those bad people you sent
to prison? They ever call to say thanks?
No. Sometimes I send people
to prison for doing bad things.
Doesn't necessarily mean
they're bad people.
I appreciate that.
- The list came from Willie Van Beber.
- Really?
Apparently his last wish is for you
to precede him to the promised land.
- I should go with you.
- This one's on me, Theo. Too dangerous.
It hasn't been dangerous so far?
Did you forget the driving range already?
- You shot me.
- And I apologize for that.
- Out.
- I'll stay in the car. Don't give me a gun.
It's Willie Van Beber.
I'd feel safer with you.
- You trust me?
- I trust you.
I'll have the thin blue line park outside.
Lock the doors.
Stay away from firearms.
- Yeah.
- Happy. Blades.
If you're not too busy making doughnuts
I could use some backup.
You're a cop, Blades.
Why are you calling me?
Well, technically,
I'm on administrative leave.
- Where's Blades?
- Garcia, right?
- Gold, yes. Where is he?
- He went to meet Gil Ott.
I guess he's got Rosalyn Wohl.
- Did he say where?
- I heard Sixth and Concord.
Let's go. Now. Come on.
You're staying with me.
Hey, Blades.
- Gil. How you been?
- Wonderful.
Hands on your head.
Hands.
Come on.
Why the hell isn't Blades picking up?
I don't know. Am I supposed to know?
Oh, shit. Call 911 and stay with the car.
- 911, what is your emergency?
- Police emergency.
I ran into your father, Gil.
- He's worried about you.
- My father?
That's funny. That's really--
That's hilarious.
- Where's the paper, Blades?
- Happy Conners took it.
Bullshit. Give me the goddamn paper.
He doesn't have it, Gil.
Happy Conners has it.
And you don't really need it anyway.
Hands up on your head.
I'm really sorry about
the way this ends, detective.
I had such a good time
watching you in trial.
You were the happiest defendant
I've ever seen.
- I try to stay positive.
- Turn around.
You know you were right.
About the list?
It doesn't really make any difference.
But you're a liability now.
You're not the first to say so,
although you may be the last.
Thought that kidnapping thing
sounded fishy.
I knew you'd respond
to a lady in distress.
That's no way to treat an employee.
Independent contractor.
I thought I was doing you
a favor though, killing Gold.
He wants to put you away.
Once you know him,
his intentions are good.
That's very magnanimous.
So Van Beber's your dad, yes?
Technically, for about another week or so.
Then he's gonna be my dead dad.
So, yeah, sad story all around.
Your methods are unorthodox.
But I must admit, I admire your loyalty.
Police!
A few of my dad's friends.
I'm an only child.
He gets kind of overprotective.
Oh, shit.
Blades.
You could have
put my father away for life.
Instead you had to kill him?
- I'm sorry. I was just doing my job.
- No compromises. No deals.
Right? Well, guess what.
No deal for you either.
Don't move.
Yeah, well,
Wohl was her mother's maiden name.
Van Beber never married her.
I hate to admit it, Blades,
but you're not a half-bad detective.
Okay, enough.
Thank you for driving me home.
I'm gonna go soak in a hot bath
the next 85 years.
Are we still on for Whole Foods?
You bet. Want a ride to work
in the morning?
Sure.
How very gallant of you.
Thanks.
- It's tomorrow.
- Again.
- At least this didn't happen on my birthday.
- That's good.
That is good.
- That's bad.
- That is bad.
Still going after my dad for adultery?
If your mom's still hiring.
I need the work.
- You know my dad isn't cheating, right?
- I know no such thing.
It's a fantasy. He never cheated on her.
She cheated on him.
He's a dentist for God's sake.
- But to the stars.
- Oh, God. More fantasy.
Does my mother have any
actual evidence of this affair?
Her theory is that he takes
his girl or girls...
...to this hotel.
- And what do you think?
- I don't get paid to think.
- That's clear.
- What's that supposed to mean?
It means I found the car.
If the Hawk was supposed
to be on its way to Argentina...
...why did it keep popping up
over town?
Excellent question.
You wouldn't expect a thief
to steal it then tool around.
- No.
- My dad is a notorious cheapskate.
Except when driving the Hawk.
He would never take a mistress
to a swank hotel.
He would park the car in a hotel garage
if it meant keeping it off the street.
Yes!
What do you say? I get a turn
at the wheel of this beauty?
All right, you've earned it.
You just go very easy, okay?
She likes to be rewed a lot
before she downshifts.
- Taser boy?
- Yes?
Relax.
That video is gonna get me elected.
No bad publicity except if it's an obituary.
- You got my vote.
- Convicts can't vote.
You have to convince 12 jurors,
including at least a few females.
Yes. Yes.
- You must have a lot of tickets.
- Drive!
- The biggest mistake of my life.
- What?
Letting you drive!
Apologize to your father for me.
Dad, I am really, really sorry.
Is he dead?
He never stood a chance
against the Hawk.
Who is he?
On Van Beber's payroll, no doubt.
I guess killing his daughter
didn't endear us to him.
We got lucky.
I've never been lucky.
Thanks.
For what?
Keeping me alive.
Protect and serve, my man.
That's the job.
So speaking of you
sending me to prison....
We were?
Admittedly, I've had some lapses
of judgment.
But I'm really not one of the bad guys.
Yeah, well, I've had some lapses
here and there.
And I'm definitely one of the good guys.
Thanks for showing me
the forest and the grays.
- Am I supposed to know what that means?
- Not really.
Oh, what am I gonna tell my dad?
What am I gonna tell my dad?
Tell him how much you love him.
The rest is pretty much
paint by numbers.
- Have you seen a red Studebaker Hawk?
- Sorry, I haven't.
Son.
Hey. Dad.
What time is it?
I have some bad news.
What? Where's mom?
Oh, no, no, no. It's okay. Mom is fine.
She's fine.
Now, look, Theo. I don't want you
to overreact or anything...
...but it appears as if
the Hawk has been stolen.
- Are you sure?
- I'm sorry.
I know how much it meant to you.
Me?
That car meant everything
in the world to you.
Everything? No, no, no.
It's a fine automobile...
...but you know what I always say:
It's just a car.
Yeah.
I love you, Dad.
I love you too, kiddo.
We interviewed a few jurors
after the mistrial...
...they seemed pretty unimpressed,
so we walked away.
But the fact that you decided
to dismiss the case...
...doesn't mean
Detective Blades is innocent.
- I used to know what that word means.
- Counsel, do you mind?
We couldn't make a case.
We dumped it.
I understand you spent time
with Detective Blades...
...looking for your car,
which you reported stolen?
- That's true.
- And in fact your father had the car?
We don't choose our parents, sergeant.
Looks like you and Detective Blades
had quite an adventure.
Detective Blades was instrumental
in uncovering a damaging leak...
...that was in our office.
A leak which had already resulted
in the death of an FBI informant.
That's very impressive. Look...
...you knew at the time that Detective
Blades was on administrative leave...
...and he had specific orders
not to do any police work.
My mother hired him as a Pl
to look for the car.
Which your father had.
- Exactly.
I bet Detective Blades
went out of his way...
...not to mislead anyone
about his status.
He never flipped his badge, right?
Never brandished his gun?
Never once in your presence
identified himself as a police officer?
Technically, no.
But he did order a lot of doughnuts.