Three minutes.
The girl. Now!
Let's hurry a bit,
shall we?
Come on!
Faster, faster!
Read!
Or we're all
gonna die!
No! Come back
Well, well, well.
Are you two
sitting comfortably?
Good. Now. Gentlemen.
Do you see
these file folders?
The ones with your names
on them?
Can you guess
what's in these file folders?
I'll give you
a hint.
Discipline
reports.
Lots of them.
And some wonderful
artwork as well.
This is...?
Spider
with human head?
I'm sorry. Spider?
With human head.
Yeah. He eats dogs
and cats and rabbits.
Does he?
Sean thought him up.
You see, sir,
we kinda have
this monster club, okay?
And we draw those pictures to put
on our clubhouse walls.
Correction,
Mr. Crenshaw.
You draw pictures
during Mrs. Carlson's science class
when you're supposed
to be paying attention.
Wait. I just want
to say one thing.
I mean, Ms. Carlson's
a nice teacher and all,
but she's boring and
has an odd-shaped head.
That's why Sean and the guys
call her "Meow Mix,"
'cause her head's
shaped like a cat head.
But I don't, sir,
'cause... how rude.
Boys...
I hear you.
I was a kid once.
I thought monsters
were cool.
And maybe, well...
well, gosh...
maybe I'm
just a big kid,
because, Sean, Patrick...
...I think science
is cool.
I dig it, man.
Now, I'm sure
both of you know
a great deal
about monsters,
but that's not the issue here.
The issue is...
...science is real.
Monsters are not.
We don't
know that, sir.
God, can you believe
Mr. Metzger?
Tell me about it. He touched me
and patted my shoulders and stuff.
The guy was fully
homo-ing out.
I smell like the '40s.
I mean, when they send you to school,
why don't they
tell you about the homos and
people with cat heads...
Sorry,
Mrs. Carlson.
Meow. Meow.
She's married, Sean.
Oh, my God! Some guy
kisses her at night?
I mean, a priest said,
"I now pronounce you man and wife,"
and it was
okay with him?
Hey.
Where's Fat Kid?
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen,
and welcome to our show.
What makes Fat Kid fat?
Fat kid?
Get out of here,
E.J.
"Get out of here, E.J."
Nope.
Not a good answer.
Doesn't make any sense.
Let's go to our man on the street. Derek.
Hi. I'm Derek,
and I'm in the street
where Fat Kid is blocking traffic.
Fat Kid, can't you
stop eating?
Look, I have
a glandular problem, okay?
At least I don't have a...
stupidity problem.
What'd you say, faggot?
What'd you say?
My name's Horace!
Horace.
Whore-ass.
Oops.
I tore it.
I guess I must have
a stupidity problem.
What'd you say, faggot?
What'd you say?
I said,
"You're an asshole."
Hey, Rudy.
E.J.
See you met
my friend Horace.
You okay?
Rudy, I, uh...
You dropped
your candy bar, E.J.
It's his.
It's your now.
Rudy... Eat.
Rudy, I'm not gonna...
Eat up!
And we'll
call it a day.
Look, Patrick,
I told you before,
Wolfman cannot drive a car.
Yes, he can.
No, he can't!
All I'm saying is,
Sean, he could if he had to.
He could not. You're
being such a dork!
I know you are, but what am I?
A dork.
I know you are,
but what am I?
Oh, great. A feeb.
A dork.
I know you are,
but what am I?
A dork.
I know you are,
but what am I?
Infinity! Look,
Wolfman doesn't go to work.
He's not, like, a guy.
What are you
talkin' about?
He walks around.
He wears pants.
He had to wear pants
'cause those movies
were made in the '40s.
He had to wear 'em
so you wouldn't see his...
wolf dork.
Wolf dork?
You guys!
I saw him.
He was watching us.
Who?
Scary German Guy.
Sean, he give me
the creeps.
Oh, he's just
a dude on welfare.
Maybe he's
a German spy.
Oh, good one.
We're not at war
with Germany anymore.
We're at war
with Vietnam.
What?
It's in Rambo.
You guys missed it!
Oh! Fat Kid!
Rudy saved my life!
Do you think we could
talk him into joining
the Monster Club?
Can we?
Huddle.
Sean, he's
in junior high.
I hear he killed his dad.
Get out of here,
Phoebe the Feeb!
Okay, you guys.
We should let him in
on one condition.
Monster test.
You guys!
I saw Scary...
I saw him!
I saw Scary German Guy!
He was watching!
I'm depressed.
What for?
What do you mean,
what for?
I'm flyin'
a World War II bomber
with wooden crates in it
and dead bodies.
I should have a party?
Do they complain?
Do they get airsick?
Do they ask for more
of the little almond
things?
You're right.
This is a great job.
I'm really happy.
I thought they were dead.
They are.
I'm goin' to, uh...
I'm gonna
check it out.
Okay. Good.
You do that.
I'll stay here and
make spooky sounds.
Come on.
Where are you,
you son of a bitch?
Two ways to kill
a vampire.
Good one, Fat Kid.
Excellent question.
Uh, stake through the heart.
Right.
What else?
Oh, real good.
Eugene.
I wasn't talking.
Get him in a muzzle,
will ya?
It was Pete.
You guys meet up here
a lot, or, uh...
Every day.
Do we meet up here a lot?
Eugene!
Man!
Eugene, make
Pete shut up.
Do you really think
that was a good question?
Rudy!
Are you gonna listen or
look out the window?
I told you he didn't want
to be in the club.
Lighten up, Patrick.
No way!
Hey, we're tryin'
to do the test
here, you know.
You're gonna
piss him off.
I'm beginnin'
to like this club.
Rudy! Come on.
It's a monster test.
It's important. Okay?
Second way
to kill a vampire.
Mmm... I give up.
Daylight.
Sunlight.
Ha ha ha!
Fat Kid,
what other kind
of light is there
durin' the day?
Go away, Pete!
Okay, question two.
Is Frankenstein
the name of the monster
or the guy who made him?
The guy.
Right.
Can't you read?
Mom said you have to let me
in the club,
or else it's prescruption.
That's discrimination,
jerkoid.
"Prescription" is drugs,
which you're on if you
think you're gettin' up here.
Come on, Sean!
I know about monsters.
Come on! Let me in the club!
Two ways to kill a werewolf.
Silver bullet?
And?
That's it. Shoot him
with a sliver bullet.
Nope. Sorry, Rudy.
Ha ha!
Okay, so, what's
the other way?
What?
Second way
to kill a werewolf?
Um...
Car crash?
Accident
with power tools?
Old age?
Falling out a window.
Onto a bomb!
Sean! Phoebe! Dinner!
Oops. Gotta go.
Wait. Am I in or what?
I mean it, spaz.
You gotta
stop it.
Wash up
for dinner,
guys.
Boring guy, boring guy,
boring guy, boring guy.
What's this, Mom?
Huh? Oh, I got that
for you today
at Jane Burgess'
garage sale.
Says it's
from that old house
up on Shadowbrook Road.
Holy shit! Uh, sor... cow.
Um, I'm sorry.
Mom, do you know
who wrote this book?
Yeah. It's, what,
Van Helsing something.
Now, he's the one
that fights Godzilla.
Right?
Dracula, Mom.
Well, then which
is the really tall one?
That's Godzilla.
My God!
Abraham Van Helsing.
This is great!
This is German.
Let it begin.
Hey, slick.
Busy day?
Not really.
Shoot any crooks today?
Afraid not.
But I still may
if you don't
wash up for dinner.
What's
on your mind?
Well, Dad, uh, some
of the guys and me
were maybe gonna go see
Groundhog Day Part 12 tonight,
only if it's okay with you.
Is it? Please?
Oh, we got
a problem.
No way!
Yes, way.
I gotta go out
with your mother
tonight.
You got a certain
5-year-old sister
who needs baby-sitting.
Oh, come on, Dad!
I've waited all year
to see this movie!
Pal, it's only a movie.
Look, tomorrow night,
you and I'll go see
Groundhog Day.
I'll get home
early.
Tomorrow night?
That'll be too late!
The guys will blab
the entire plot!
What?
Did I hear "plot"?
Sean, it is a guy
with an ax.
Anyway, I thought
they killed him
in the last one.
They did.
And he returns
from his grave.
Returns
from the grave?
Sean, he always
returns from the grave.
If they blew him up,
put his head in a blender,
and mailed the rest
of the pieces to Norway,
he would still
return from the grave.
That was part seven.
You want to know
what the plot is?
The plot separates you
from my five bucks.
I want to see
a stupid movie.
Well, you can't.
You're baby-sitting.
Fine. Can I have
five bucks anyway?
Absolutely.
So, where you two
goin' tonight?
Marriage counselor.
Again?
I thought
you quit smoking.
Sean.
Son, I love you dearly,
but do me a favor.
Put your basic lid
on it.
Now, get
outta here.
Hello. Yeah?
Officer, please!
Lock me up!
Lock...
Yeah. I'm a werewolf!
I'm a werewolf!
Please. Please.
Hey, Del.
I know it sounds
crazy, but...
Bad news.
Listen, I gotta
go downtown.
Can you reschedule
that appointment?
Honey, I'm a cop,
okay?
You knew that
when you bought
the package.
Look.
It's important.
I'm important.
I love you.
Prove it.
I'll see you
in a few hours.
Just for a night!
You see,
it's a full moon!
And I'm a werewolf!
Take it easy.
You don't understand!
You gotta lock me up!
You gotta put me
in a cage!
Buddy,
I'd like nothin' better!
Hold onto your pants!
Oh, God! You
don't understand!
You've gotta...
Anything you say,
fella.
Put the cuffs on him.
I got it.
All right.
I got him now.
Jesus Christ!
We need some backup!
Bon voyage!
Lock me up!
So, let me
get this straight.
You tellin' me
there was
this 2,000-year-old
mummy here, right?
Yes, sir.
Well, now he's not
here. He's gone.
Vanished. History.
Yes, sir.
And you're sayin'
you didn't hear anybody
come in here or leave.
Is that right?
Can you hear me now?
Hello?
I can
hear you fine.
So, nobody
took the mummy.
I would've heard them.
Of course he would've.
What a stupid question.
Did you take him?
No, sir!
Just a shot.
That's it, Del.
This case is
too hard, man.
Let's be firemen
instead.
I'm glad you're gettin'
major laughs
out of this, Rich.
The problem is,
2,000-year-old dead guys
do not get up
and walk away
by themself.
Accident patrol,
uh, request confirmation.
You have the 915-H
officer-involved shooting
en route?
My God!
You scared me!
Where are Steve
and Judy?
I thought
they were with you.
Not funny.
Well, something
funny's...
What did I miss?
Judy? Steve?
Hey!
Oh, sheriff.
You scared us.
Never mind about that.
This is
the best part.
Judy!
No!
Lieutenant,
you wanna come over
and take a look at this?
Dispatch, Unit 7.
Unit 7,
come in, please.
Please copy.
Wonderful. Great!
Just what I need.
Come again? You're...
What?
Uh, request,
uh, cadaver...
I can't hear you!
No, no, no!
I said "missing"!
The body's missing!
It's the second one
tonight.
Confirmed. That
makes two tonight,
right, Lieutenant?
Ha, ha.
That's very funny.
And you want
to shut up about it?
It's been so long.
So very long.
Wake up,
old friend.
It is our time.
Long... time...
...Master.
And you put the candle
next to your bed
like this.
Your mom did this
when you were a little girl?
It means
"I love you."
And as long
as it's here, nothing
bad can happen.
Sean says
when it lightnings,
monsters come.
Oh, he's just trying
to scare you, honey.
Will lightning
hit the house?
No.
The candle
keeps it away?
That's right.
Say goodnight
to Scraps.
Goodnight, Scraps.
Good night, Emily.
Mwah.
Good night,
sweetheart.
Are you gonna
yell at him?
Honey...
I love your father.
What?
I mean Sean,
for scaring me.
Of course you did.
I'll talk to him
about it, sweetheart.
Sweet dreams.
You're thinkin'
about your job,
isn't that right?
I can see it
in your eyes, Del.
Yeah! I'm glad you can
see it in my eyes,
'cause for a minute there
I thought I had you fooled.
Come on, this isn't...
No, come on!
Look in my eyes.
Look in my eyes!
I'll think
about stuff,
and you can tell me
when I'm
thinking correctly!
Keep your
voice down.
I don't want
the children...
I had a lousy night,
all right?
Every night
I have a lousy night.
I'm sorry it's such
a pain in the ass for you
with my stupid little job!
I am trying to explain...
Some guy steals
a priceless Egyptian mummy...
That happens every day.
Skip that.
Then I get a call
from some nutcase
who's shouting
he's a werewolf!
Huh? You like that?
What do they do?
They blow him away
right there
in the police station!
Wait a minute!
There is more to this!
...marriage counseling!
For what?
Wha?
There's a monster
in my closet.
Damn, son, look!
All of these monsters!
Come on,
all of you monsters,
outta here!
Everyone,
out of this room!
Come...
You, on the bed.
Come on. Out. Out.
Take a hike.
There he goes.
You see
any more monsters?
In the closet?
Sure. We can go
into the closet.
We can do that.
Okay, monsters!
Look at that big,
scary monster!
Listen. You are
not gonna sleep
with your mother
and me tonight,
so you can
forget it.
And keep this up,
and you're not gonna look
at those monster magazines.
Understand?
Okay.
We're all here.
What's
the deal?
Yeah.
What the hell's
Monster Squad?
It's us.
We're
the Monster
Squad.
Since when?
Since now!
What's a "squad"?
It's like
Miami Vice, I think.
Look. I think
there's monsters.
Like, real ones.
I heard my dad talking
on the telephone
to a guy down
at the police station.
There was a guy screaming
he was a werewolf.
And they shot him.
And the body disappeared
from the coroner van.
And the coroner guy
was dead.
So what? He got shot,
and the werewolf
took his body?
No, you pinhead!
He was a werewolf!
Maybe.
But if they shot him...
They must've been
regular bullets,
not silver ones.
Look, I know
this will sound
pretty stupid,
but a mummy disappeared
from the museum tonight.
Mummy came
in my house.
And, guys...
Dracula might
be here, too.
Aw, man,
Fat Kid farted!
Oh, God.
Did not.
Can't you
hold it? God!
God damn it,
would you shut up?
Did you hear
a word I said?
The guys are dead!
Get a clue!
Something's out there,
and it's killin' people!
And if it's monsters,
nobody's gonna do a thing
about it but us.
So, what do we do?
Think this book
might be important.
Look. It's
Van Helsing's diary.
Mom said they found it
in an old house
on Shadowbrook Road.
But I can't read it.
It's all in German.
My sister takes German
in high school.
Your sister
doesn't speak German.
All she does
is hang around,
and the guys
touch her tits.
Your sister wouldn't
happen to live next-door,
would she?
So what?
That girl's
your sister?
So, what do you say?
Are we Monster Squad...
...or what?
Cool.
All right.
How does that dog
get up here, anyways?
Old friend.
How do you like
your new home?
Home.
I must
sleep soon,
so listen
very carefully.
Van Helsing's diary...
...is missing.
I want you
to retrieve it
for me.
You understand?
Yes...
Master.
Children... possess it.
I want you
to find them
and take the diary.
If they do not
cooperate...
...you will kill them.
Gentlemen, I'd just like
to say three words:
Scary German Guy.
Who else are we
gonna get to translate
this thing?
Come on. Somebody
go up and knock.
You knock.
You're our leader.
Firstly, he's scary, okay?
And "B,"
he's German.
Maybe he doesn't
even speak English.
Okay, so what's
German for...
"Please don't
murder us"?
Bitte, moerden-zie
uns nicht.
Boys...
time is almost up.
It's your
last chance for pie.
Thanks, Mister, uh, guy.
Now, here we go.
I mean...
No, thanks.
So? Ja?
Now, where
were we?
Ah... ja.
"The amulet itself
is fairly small
and carved with
intricate symbols."
Rather an odd-looking
thing,
don't you think?
Scary German
Guy's bitchin'.
Sir, the thing
I don't understand is
the part about
the equilibrium.
Well, according
to this rather
curious book
you have
brought me,
"The forces
of good and evil..."
Uh, that is a B-17,
in case you are
wondering.
It's rad!
"Good and evil
"are
in constant flux,
"back and forth.
"Only once,
every hundred years,
are these forces
balanced."
And what about
the amulet?
The amulet,
so nearly as I
can translate,
is "concentrated good.
"It is a talisman
which wards off evil
and is..."
how you say, uh...
"indestructible"?
That means
it can't be
destroyed.
Or, in any case,
normally destroyed.
However,
and this part
is underlined...
"Once
every hundred years,
"at the stoke
of midnight,
"the amulet
becomes vulnerable,
"and at that moment,
it can be
shattered."
And if it is?
Then the balance
between
good and evil
will shift,
and evil will rule.
However, our friend
Mr. Van Helsing
claims there is a way
to stop the forces
of darkness.
How?
"If one
could gain possession
of the amulet
before those forces..."
"...then
every hundred years,
"at midnight,
"there is
another option:
"a ceremony which,
when followed
to the letter,
"will open a hole
"into Limbo itself
"where dwell
the damned;
"a vortex,
"which like
a great whirlwind,
"can swallow
the forces of evil
forever."
Well... does it describe
the procedure at all?
In detail.
This was the last entry.
On this date,
he was to battle
those forces himself.
Interesting.
It is
tomorrow's date,
one hundred years ago!
A hundred years ago?
Tomorrow night.
Thank you very much.
Thanks.
Bye. Thank you
very much
for all your time.
Thank you.
I expect
you boys thought
I was some kind
of monster myself?
A vampire, perhaps?
That's quite
all right.
But I am not,
you know.
If I were
a vampire,
then I wouldn't have
a reflection.
Now, would I?
Man, you sure know
a lot about monsters.
Now that
you mention it...
I suppose I do.
Guys, wait up!
Tomorrow night?
What do we have to
do again?
Blow a hole
in Dumbo?
Limbo, stupid.
So, how do
we know
the amulet's
there, anyway?
Because, you dweeb,
Dracula's obviously
here looking for it.
If we don't find it
before he does,
we're beast bait.
Okay, so,
say we get
the amulet.
Then what?
Wait till
midnight... and?
We get
a virgin.
A virgin?
Yeah.
Okay, right.
Then what?
Well, our virgin
takes the amulet,
reads the magic spell
from the book,
and, blamo, we blow
a hole in Limbo.
That's so easy.
Oh, a cinch.
Piece of cake.
Yeah.
Rudy. Question.
Shoot.
Know any virgins?
Okay. Rudy, find
some silver bullets.
And where the hell
am I supposed to find
silver bullets?
K-Mart?
I don't know.
Gimme a break.
Fat Kid, get a map.
Find Shadowbrook
Road.
What, do I look
in the index for
"big, scary mansion"?
Oh, you're a riot.
You guys!
How can we trust
Scary German Guy?
Why would he lie
about a thing
like this?
Sean!
Phoebe,
have a life.
Okay?
You're being
a spaz!
Ow! God!
You bit me,
you brat!
I'm tellin'
Mom on you!
Would ya look?
It's okay,
you guys!
He's friends
with us.
Come on!
Don't be chickenshit!
Come on.
I want to show you
my friends.
Sean, no.
Oh, go for it.
Sean, are you crazy?
That's a walkin'
dead guy.
Sean, please don't die.
Are... are you dead?
D-Dead?
Does Mom know
about him?
No. Only us.
Hey, guys,
get over here!
He's great!
Now can I be
in the Monster Club?
I can't believe it.
Frankenstein's monster
in our clubhouse.
Let's ask him
to leave, okay?
You're not still
scared, are you?
Well, he is
a little bit
gross, Sean.
Scr...
Scra-aps.
I taught him
to talk.
Bo-gus.
Give me...
a... break.
Huddle up, you guys.
Sean, we gotta
get an adult.
And your dad's a cop,
so if we get your dad...
Absolutely no
grown-ups. Okay?
They'll lock him up
in a cage or something.
Dissect him.
Or put him
on TV!
Fat Kid.
Ha ha ha!
Why are you
such a lame-oid?
You're the lame one.
Bogus!
Bogus.
Dudes,
check it out.
Sc...
Scary?
The amulet is in here.
Very near, yes.
Oh... Van Helsing,
your disciples
were very clumsy,
trying to hide from me
the very thing
that is mine.
No hiding,
never, from me.
Ah! It's here!
My prize.
Soon, Van Helsing...
soon, the creatures
of the night
shall rule the world.
And there is
no one to stop us!
# I don't wanna go home?
# I don't wanna leave
the floor?
# Someone turn
the lights down?
# Close the cage
and lock the door?
# We ain't gonna let
this feelin' under?
? We gotta cut loose
and turn it up all the way?
# Rock until you drop?
# Dance until
your heart stops?
# Rock until you drop?
# Dance until
your feet fall off?
# I don't want to sit down?
# I don't need
no easy chair?
# Someone turn
the clock back?
# We ain't gonna
go nowhere?
# Hey?
# Now we're gonna go in
big like thunder?
# No one can stop us now?
# We're goin' all the way?
# Rock until you drop?
# Yeah, dance
until your heart stops?
# Oh, rock until you drop?
# Dance until
your feet fall off?
# No, no, no?
# Hey?
# We ain't gonna let this
feelin' under?
# Cut it loose
and rock some more?
# Now we're gonna comb
this big night under?
# It's totally rad,
it's cool cool?
? It's cool cool,
it's cool?
# Rock until you drop?
# Hey, hey?
# Dance until
your heart stops?
# Hey?
# Rock until you drop?
# Yeah,
hey, hey, hey?
# Dance until
your feet fall off?
# You better rock me?
# Yeah, rock me?
# Dance until
your heart stops?
# Everybody, sing it?
# Rock until you drop?
# Rockin' dude?
# Party till
your brains fall out?
# Rock until you drop?
# Dance until
your heart stops?
# Party till you die?
# Rock until you drop?
# Baby, baby, baby?
# Dance until
your feet fall off?
# Ooh, yeah, rock?
I do regret
the dosage,
my friend.
Most, um... lethal...
by human standards.
But then, um,
human standards
do not apply, do they?
Well, uh, I'll,
uh, go have a bite
while you change
into something
more, um...
comfortable.
Last night,
near the ambulance
crash,
get this...
eyewitness report:
long black hearse.
No plates.
You wanna ask me
about the hood
ornament?
What about
the hood ornament?
I thought
you'd never ask.
A silver skull.
I consider this
an exciting lead.
I am excited.
Are you excited?
I'm thrilled.
Put out an APB.
I already did.
I'm a very good
policeman.
You know?
Crenshaw.
Hurry!
Get all your men
and send them
down to 666
Shadowbrook road!
It's an old mansion!
He's found the amulet!
There's... There's no time!
Who the hell is this?
I'm the one
they shot last night!
I'm a werewolf
now, but...
Have a nice night.
No! No! No! No!
Don't hang up!
Uhh! He's gonna kill
your son!
Patrick!
Come in. Patrick.
Patrick,
come in.
Yeah, we're here.
Where are you?
We're almost there.
Everything set with you?
Know in a minute.
Rudy?
Rudy!
This babe is major.
Rudy's in love.
Well, good for Rudy.
Thanks a lot, Pete.
Okay, remember...
rendezvous position "A",
2200 hours.
Say what?
10:00, doofus.
How do we know
the amulet's there,
anyway?
We don't, but it's
all we have to go on.
Sean.
Okay. Well.
Good luck,
butt love.
Sean.
I know you are,
but what am I?
Sean.
Out.
What, Eugene?
Creature
stole my Twinkie.
So?
What did you want
to ask me?
What do we want
to ask you.
Okay. Um, Sis...
me and Ru...
Rudy?
Your show, Ace.
Okay.
We just wanted
to know...
if you're a virgin.
What?
Okay. What we want
to know is...
are you a...
Ahem. Look.
What your brother
is so delicately
attempting to inquire,
and let me, out of my own
personal curiosity,
is the degree to which
you may have or...
have not,
at some point in time...
...been dorked?
You guys are sick!
Guess what.
Fox Photo's got
a two-for-one deal
this week,
and wouldn't you know it,
there's a space
on the bulletin board
right between
the prom committee notes...
and the football roster.
Sean.
About this
Monster Squad thing.
Maybe we could go
back to the clubhouse
and rethink it
with the other guys.
Fat Kid... you're
bein' a wuss.
Wuss?
Can it, Frank.
Time's runnin' out.
Sean, no!
Scary house...
real monsters...
us... 12 years old?
Remember?
Midnight...
end of world.
Remember?
Master... is near.
Master wants
children dead.
Um, Sean?
Maybe we could be
like Math Squad
instead, you know...
do math problems.
Stay home.
Or Nature Squad.
We could look at rocks,
collect birds.
Not be dead. See,
it's this whole death thing
I'm not crazy about.
Well... no amulet.
Let's go.
Look. We got
two consolations.
Number one,
Frankenstein's
on our side.
And number two,
my dad's a cop.
Anybody fools around with us,
he kicks their ass.
Hey, Frankie.
Come on.
Frank!
Wake up!
Eugene, get
away from there!
He won't wake up!
Fat Kid, use your eyes.
Does it look like
you can help him?
But... But what
do I do, Sean?
A monster!
Don't call him
a monster.
Well... what
if he's dead?
Then he died
to help us.
Now, look.
I'm the leader
of this squad,
so listen up.
He said Dracula
knows we're here.
So let's just try
to find the amulet...
...and get the hell
outta here.
Sean!
Kick him
in the nards!
What?
Kick him in the nards!
He doesn't have nards!
Do it! Do it!
Wolfman's got nards!
Come on! Come on!
What are you doin'?
Haven't you read
The Hardy Boys?
You pull some lever down
and a secret door opens!
You gotta
be kidding!
You have
a better idea?
Come on, Sean.
Damn!
Where is he?
Where are you?
Come in!
Sean!
Where are you,
Sean?
10:00.
They're late.
Maybe the monsters
got them.
"Maybe the monsters
got them."
Can we go home, Sean?
Oh, great.
Please? Can't we go home?
Just great.
Frankenstein's dead,
Eugene's whining,
and we're sitting here
with Pirate Bill.
Come on, Sean.
Man, we're dead.
Eugene, stop it.
Bingo.
You guys, I got it!
Give it to me.
Give it to me!
Get out of here!
Help!
Give it to me!
Garlic! Come on!
Get outta here!
You guys,
we got Scary German Guy
to help us!
The cavalry!
Thank Christ.
Yeah, we figured
you guys were in trouble.
It was boss!
I saw Dracula!
And I kicked Wolfman in the nards...
Fat Kid, bag it. Okay?
Is she a virgin?
Why don't you put it
on the 6:00 news,
you little shit?
Yeah, she is.
Perhaps we should all
go back to my place
for some pie.
The book was right.
Don't you see?
It's all true!
We found the amulet,
but now there's monsters after us.
We gotta go to a place
where there's a lot of people.
Church.
What?
Church!
He's right.
There's an old church
in the town plaza.
Perfect.
Monsters hate religious stuff.
Del.
Del. Del!
Look, I'm sorry.
What, you
tryin' to tell me
that we're gonna go
all the way out to Shadowbrook Road
because you get
a call from some guy
who tells you
he's a werewolf?
Ha ha ha!
Ho ho!
Look, I'm sorry.
I guess it's feasible, Del.
Listen to me.
Come on, man.
I apologize. All right?
Ha ha ha!
Look! It's 20 minutes
till midnight!
We pull this off,
I'm gonna shit!
Holy shit!
Jesus Christ!
Give me some slack!
What are you doing?
Patrick, just give me some slack!
No!
You're closer! Just give me some slack!
No way!
Don't be a wuss!
Okay!
Come on! Hurry!
Yes!
Come on! Let go! Let go!
Let go of her! Let go!
Go! Go!
Go! Look at that!
It's dust!
Come on! Yes! Come on!
Go!
See you later...
Band-Aid breath.
Del, I don't know
if you're aware of this,
but we're going
a hundred miles an hour!
I notice little things
like that.
I'm a very good policeman.
You know that?
I'm not sayin'
anything.
Not a single word.
I appreciate that.
Meeting adjourned.
Dispatch to Unit 28. Please respond.
Freeze!
You move, and
I'll kill you!
Dispatch, we got a 10-35.
Send backup! Hurry it up!
Del!
Get outta there!
That's enough.
I will have your son.
Del?
D-Del, what's happening?
What?
The kids.
Sean?
Phoebe.
Phoebe?
Sean!
Phoebe!
Sean, can you hear me?
Where are you?
Sean! Can you hear me?
Dad! I'm here!
We're almost to Town Square.
Hurry up!
Don't kick the church!
It's religious!
It's locked
is what it is.
Fine.
Okay.
We'll just have to
do it right here.
Like, really
religious, Sean.
Why don't we just
go over and do it in Burger King?
You guys!
Oh, shit!
Patrick,
come on!
Okay, come on, read the book.
Go!
Okay!
Read! Go!
Wait!
Read!
I'm flunking German!
Read it in German.
Try.
Damn! Really,
you should read it!
He's not a virgin,
you stupid!
Did you ask him?
Where you goin',
Rudy?
I'm in the god damn club,
aren't I?
I don't believe this!
Will you speak English?
I can't understand you!
Come on!
Drunken munchkin warehouse!
Yeah, yeah,
what he said!
Okay, skanks,
come and get it.
I don't believe this.
Please read!
Oh, shit!
Sean, look out!
Dad!
You stay there!
My God.
Suck on this,
you son of a bitch.
Hey, asshole.
You looked.
It's okay.
All right, let's try it again,
now, shall we?
Look, you've
got me upset!
Read it?
Come on, read!
Oh, my God!
I said it!
Ho ho!
All right!
You did!
I have absolutely no idea how!
l...
Where's Limbo?
We just went through
some major shit,
and where's
the big Limbo thing?
Jesus... Christ!
Holy shit!
Kid, watch it!
Let's get him!
Let's go!
Go! Go!
Are you
absolutely sure
that she is...
You're not a virgin,
are you?
No? No, what do you
mean, no?
Well... Steve, but
he doesn't count!
Doesn't count?
Bang.
God.
Thank you.
Told ya.
Only one way
to kill a werewolf.
What?
Is she a vershion?
She? A virgin?
Yes! A virgin!
We'll use the girl!
She can't read!
She's five years old!
I'll help her!
Yah!
E.J.!
Let me in, E.J.!
Let me in!
Hey! Fat Kid!
Good job.
My name...
is Horace.
Don't look up.
Hey! Hey, hold
it right there a minute.
Hey! I said to stop right there.
Aah! No!
Phoebe!
Dad, no!
Phoebe! Oh, no!
Phoebe!
Give me the amulet,
you bitch!
Phoebe! That's
my daughter!
Bogus.
Phoebe.
Die!
No!
Dad!
Sean!
Sean! Please!
No!
Don't go!
Don't go away!
Phoebe!
Phoebe.
Don't go!
Bye...
Don't go away,
Frankenstein!
Please don't go!
Please!
Please don't go away,
Frankenstein!
Bye.
Mommy!
Del.
She's fine.
Hey, sweetheart.
Who's Eugene?
All right, son...
where are they?
Where are
the monsters?
The mummy
came in my house.
Can somebody tell me what the
Sam Hell is goin' on around here?
Well, we can, sir.
Well, who are you?
We're the Monster Squad.
All right, pal!
Yeah!
# Gotta get up,
gotta get out?
Who the hell is she?
Yeah!
# In a hundred years,
in the darkest night?
# The forces of evil
come out to fight?
# The amulet
they must destroy?
# Or spend forever
in the darkest void?
# Who can stop
their deadly might?
# Who will stand up
for the right?
# From the mouth of babes
comes dynamite?
# The Monster Squad
gonna groove tonight?
# First came Dracula,
now the Wolfman, too?
# Mummy and the creature
from the Black Lagoon?
# We need silver bullets,
we need wooden stakes?
# Normal stuff won't stop 'em
'cause they live on hate?
# Speak some magic words
from a virgin's lips?
# Maybe that'll shake 'em,
make 'em slip and trip?
# There's no turnin' back,
gotta fight the fight?
# Yeah, the Monster Squad
gonna get 'em tonight?
# Monster Squad?
# We're the Monster Squad,
and the forces of evil?
# Better run and hide?
# Monster Squad?
# We're the Monster Squad,
and the forces of evil?
# Best beware of
the Monster Squad?
# Gotta get up,
gotta get out?
# We got work to do?
# Work to do?
# Gotta get up,
gotta get out?
# We got work to do,
work to do?
# Mama can't help us,
Dad don't understand?
# No one will believe it?
# Put it in our hands?
# Gotta stop those creatures,
send them back to hell?
# Or there's no tomorrow,
no saved by the bell?
# There's no place to run,
nowhere to hide?
# Now it's time to see
what you got inside?
# No evil will
escape my sight?
# Yeah, the Monster Squad
gonna jam tonight?
# This ain't Halloween
or some phony deal?
# They be playin' for keeps,
they be playin' for real?
# They want darkness spread
all across the land?
# We're the only ones left
to make a stand?
# We don't wanna hang
with the walkin' dead?
# So we gotta kick
some monster butt instead?
# And you'll never see
such a ghastly sight?
# When the Monster Squad
saves the world tonight?
# Monster Squad?
# We're the Monster Squad,
and the forces of evil...?