(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
BECCA: What would you do
to save someone you love?
For Edward,
I would stop at nothing.
(GASPS)
What is he doing?
Hey, party in the fountain!
(ALL WHOOPING)
Edward!
Yoo-hoo!
Edward! Edward!
(ALL CLAMORING)
(GRUNTS IN FRUSTRATION)
(GROANING)
(EXCLAIMS)
Edward!
Edward? Where?
Oh, my God! There he is!
Edward, we love you,
you're the best!
No, Jacob's the best!
(GROANS)
(ALL YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
He's exposing himself!
(BOTTLE SHATTERING)
No! No.
Edward!
(HISSING)
(GASPS)
(SNARLS)
(SCREAMING)
BECCA: Let me start
from the beginning.
I used to live
with my mom in Nevada.
But now she's always
on the road,
because she started
doing some pro golfer.
So, I came here
to the foggy town
of Sporks, Washington.
Population: 3,120.
(GASPING)
(SNARLS)
Holy shit!
Make that 3,119.
Anyway, I came here
to live with my dad, Frank.
He's the town sheriff.
I haven't seen you
in a while.
Your hair's longer.
I grew it out.
I guess it's hard
for me to accept
my little girl's growing up.
I mean,
look at the size
of those tits.
Dad!
What?
(SCOFFS)
(MY PANTIES PLAYING)
I feel so lonely
Nobody gets me
I am so unhappy
Why can't I find
a cool alternative boyfriend?
BECCA: There is something
strange about this town.
I couldn't put
my finger on it.
(SNARLS)
I used to live here
when I was younger.
But I haven't been
back in a long time.
I kept your room
just as you left it.
(LULLABY CHIMING)
Great.
Remember your hamster,
Herman?
Might have missed
a couple of feedings.
You could play
with your dollies.
I don't think so.
What's that?
Oh, that's
a special edition
feel-real dolly.
I warm it up
in the tub first
so it's not creepy.
It's been lonely
since your mom left.
(CAR HONKING)
Oh, hey.
You wanna come downstairs?
Some people are excited
to see you.
Who wants their pacie?
Good girl.
Dad, I'm a teenager.
Right.
I guess I'd better get you
some new stuff then.
BECCA: Frank didn't get me.
I wasn't his little girl
anymore.
(EXCLAIMS)
(THUDDING)
Becca, you remember
Bobby White.
BECCA: Yeah.
You're looking good.
Good? I'm in a wheelchair.
I can't feel anything
below my waist.
You know what's
below my waist?
My penis!
Sorry.
We're all glad you're here,
especially your dad.
He wouldn't
shut up about you.
Careful there, Bob,
I'm gonna roll you
down the hill.
Oh, boy,
I'm real scared.
Bring it on.
(CHUCKLING)
Boy, here we go!
You're in trouble
there, mister!
Hi. I'm Jacob.
Hi.
(BOBBY GRUNTING)
We used to make
mud pies together.
(CHUCKLES)
Play doctor?
Oh, right, right.
(GROANS)
I remember now.
I gave you
a prostate exam.
So, are we going to be
at the same school?
I go to school
on the reservation.
It must be fun to drink
and gamble all day.
Too bad we're not
gonna be at school
together.
It'd be nice to know
at least one person.
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
(CHUCKLING)
Got you a welcome
home present.
What do you think?
I think that you're trying
to buy my affection with
that piece-of-shit truck
to make up for the years
that you neglected me
as a father.
Told you she'd like it.
(CHUCKLING) That's great.
I fixed up
the engine myself.
Thanks, Jacob.
Go ahead, hop in.
(GROANS)
Okay. So you gotta pump
the gas to start her up.
(SNIFFING) Damn fleas.
(SIGHING CONTENTEDLY)
Jacob, your foot.
Ever since puberty,
I've been feeling
a little different.
Excuse me.
I gotta take a leak.
I guess my body is just
going through some changes.
(CAT MEWING)
Cat!
(JACOB BARKING)
Come here, cat!
Come here!
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
BECCA: Transferring
to a school that's
already in session.
Being the new kid
is never easy.
Nice clothes.
Still shopping in
the boys' section?
Give her a break.
That's what I used to wear
when I was a virgin.
Where'd you get that haircut,
"Fantastic Lesbians"?
(BECCA GRUNTING)
Hey, new kid!
(GROANS)
Hi, I'm Derric.
I'm Becca.
I'm the eyes and ears
of this place.
I can hook you up
with anything you need.
Cheat sheets,
human growth hormone,
harvested organs.
(BEATING)
No, thanks.
Oh, I get it.
You're one of
those antisocial,
long-suffering
loner types.
Actually, I'm more
of the humorless type.
Kind of a sourpuss, really.
Full of insecurities,
with no great personality,
yet every hot guy
finds me irresistible.
You must be Becca.
I'm Rick.
Damn, girl, you seem
really boring and frigid.
You want to go to
the prom with me?
See?
I'm Jennifer,
future prom queen.
I'm gonna pretend
to be your BFF,
but if you touch Rick's wang,
I'll cut you.
(SIGHS)
Who are they?
Oh! Those are the Sullens.
They're, like,
all adopted by Dr. Carlton,
so they're not
biologically-related,
but they're really,
really close.
They moved here
a few years ago,
and they're, like,
super-weird.
It's a total mystery.
Their skin is ice-cold,
they feed on human flesh,
and they all
sleep in coffins.
Maybe they're Canadian.
Oh!
And who's that?
Snooki, JWOWW, DJ Pauly D...
No.
Not the douchebags
from the Jersey Shore.
Him.
The really pale dude
with big hair
and constipated look.
(CLEARING THROAT)
Edward Sullen.
(GIGGLING)
He's a complete hottie.
But, evidently,
no one here is worthy.
He wouldn't even accept me
as his Facebook friend.
BECCA: "Favorite activity.
"Searching for a soul
which has been cast
into eternal damnation"?
But I don't care
about Edward.
I've got another guy
on the side. Yeah.
Sadly, he went off
to fight in Iraq
for a year.
But we write to each
other all the time.
His name is John.
JENNIFER: "Dear John,
two weeks together.
"That's all it took
to fall in love with you.
"And in those two weeks,
you did things to me
no guy had ever done before.
"I just hope I'm able
to poop again soon."
Are you, like,
even listening?
(SCOFFS)
Oh! You guys are having,
like, an instant connection.
How can you tell?
Duh. Hardwicke 101?
You're both staring
at each other
in slow motion,
which although
cheesy and obvious,
it underscores your
respective yearnings.
Oh!
Right.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(RETCHING)
Ah! Becca.
Why don't you take
the empty seat next to
that mysterious boy
you're destined
to have a fatalistic
relationship with
that will spawn four books
and a movie franchise?
(SNIFFING)
(EXHALING)
Do I smell?
Yeah. Like tuna.
Lunch.
(AIR HISSING)
I'm Becca.
I'm Edward.
So you're new to Sporks.
How do you like
the weather?
I don't like cold,
wet things.
So you must
hate Slurpees.
(SLURPING)
I'm just trying
to figure you out.
All right, class.
Turn to page 63
in your books.
(STUTTERS)
This is biology.
Why are we reading
The Vampire Diaries?
In the '80s,
coke was all the rage.
The '90s, grunge.
Now it's the era
of vampires.
It's just super-trendy.
That's amazing.
(GURGLING)
(GURGLING CONTINUES)
(BABY CRYING)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(CLANGING)
Oh!
Hi. (GASPS)
Why aren't you
wearing a shirt?
I work part-time at
Abercrombie & Fitch.
It's always the same
inane questions.
"Who are you?"
"Why are you doing this?"
"Does the carpet
match the drapes?"
Yeah.
Oh, that's hot.
I got a serious
case of the munchies.
And I think you know
what I need to eat.
Cheetos?
Oh, hell, yeah.
Thanks, dawg.
You a'ight with me.
(ANTOINE LAUGHING) Whoo!
Antoine?
What?
The killing.
(GASPING)
Oh!
Right. My fault.
You know who we are,
don't you?
(SNARLING)
Yes.
You're the
Black Eyed Peas!
Come on. Not again.
Why does everyone
always think we're
the Black Eyed Peas?
I mean, her, I get. I get it.
She looks just like Fergie.
And he looks
like Will.i.am,
but, Jesus Christ,
they don't even have
a white guy in their band!
(SNARLING)
Ow!
He hit me!
SCULLEY: That's right!
Mixed martial arts,
Tae Bo,
and Yogalates
created this!
Huh?
(GROANS)
How you like that,
pretty boy? Huh?
(SCREAMING)
(DISTORTED LAUGHTER)
Get him off me!
Now the elbow!
Son of a bitch!
I am not afraid of you!
You should be.
(SCULLEY YELLING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(GASPING)
(NECK CRACKING)
(GROANS)
(YELLING)
Damn that overwrought
unrequited teenage love.
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
BECCA: I couldn't stop
thinking about Edward Sullen.
Amazing dexterity.
He can't be human.
(EXHALING)
GOSSIP GIRL:
Meanwhile, uptown, Blair
was getting cozy with Nate,
who was secretly
crushing on Serena.
BECCA: Excuse me, but you're
interrupting my narration.
GOSSIP GIRL:
Oh, shit!
Wrong show!
X-O-X-O, Gossip Girl.
Becca!
(GASPING) Jacob.
I heard about
the accident.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I got you these.
(CHUCKLES)
Thanks, Jacob.
You're so sweet
and thoughtful.
Any girl would be
lucky to have you.
Just not me, of course.
You're like my little
gay brother.
I heard you were
hanging out with
Edward Sullen.
Stay away from him.
There's just something
really odd about that guy.
FRANK: Becca!
I'd better go.
Hey, sweetheart.
There you are.
There was
a killing today.
Fisherman Sculley,
by the docks.
The blood was drained
from his body
and he had
multiple bite wounds
all over his neck.
You know what
that means?
The Kardashians
are in town.
(GASPING)
Here.
I want you
to have this.
Mace?
You're my little girl,
and there's a killer
on the loose.
I'm not gonna leave
until I know you can
protect yourself.
Now,
I'm going to come at you,
and I want you to mace me.
Dad...
Honey, I've been
trained for this, okay?
Here I come.
(YELLING)
Good God!
God damn it!
(YELLING CONTINUES)
It's so painful! It burns!
Sorry, Dad.
No! I'm proud of you.
Are you okay?
Mace will only temporarily
stop your attacker.
You have to hit a man
where he breathes, Becca.
(GRUNTING)
(SHUDDERING)
(IN HIGH PITCHED TONE) You got
the franks and beans there.
Good for you.
But I'm still
coming at you.
Rip off the moustache,
sweetheart.
But you love
your moustache.
If anything happened to you,
I could not live with myself.
Do it! Do it! Do it!
(YELLING)
You're good to go.
(YELLING CONTINUES)
(GASPING)
Edward?
Uh...
Am I dreaming?
Right.
You're dreaming.
So you're not
really here?
Exactly.
Go back to sleep.
Yeah.
(GRUNTS)
Got to...
Got to TiVo
Wizards of Waverly Place.
(MOANING)
Patrón! Mario López!
(SIGHS IN DISGUST)
(MUTTERING)
Becca, you're
sleepwalking.
(YELLING)
(SIGHING)
Hey, you're sleepwalking.
(SIGHS)
(BECCA GRUNTING)
(CONTINUES MUTTERING)
Just you breathing
is the greatest gift
you could give me.
(FARTING)
(EXCLAIMING IN DISGUST)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(DOG BARKING)
BECCA: I started to wonder,
maybe I wasn't
dreaming after all.
I had to figure out
the riddle.
Who was Edward Sullen?
Was he human,
or something
different entirely?
Oh, snap!
He dropped his business card!
(ENGINE FIRES)
PRINCIPAL ON PA: Good morning,
Sporks High students!
Tickets are now
on sale for prom.
And after school today,
don't forget to visit
the quad for the blood drive
generously sponsored
by the Sullen family.
Prom! Come to prom!
Prom's almost here! Prom!
Here! Get your
flyer for prom.
Check it out.
We finally got a theme.
It's gonna be awesome.
The theme is vampires?
We just came up
with it randomly!
Cool, huh?
(SNARLING)
It's gonna be like
the festival of
St. Salvatore,
like the one they have
in Italy every year
that celebrates
the killing of vampires.
And we're renting out
a huge stone courtyard.
It's gonna feel just like
we're in the 15th century.
It should be super fun.
Lots of red capes,
blood and binge drinking!
You in?
I don't know.
Prom's really not my thing.
Well, it's my thing.
I mean, really, Becca,
what is with you?
Prom is, like,
the pivotal moment
in any girl's life.
I've only been
dreaming about being
crowned prom queen
since I was a sperm
in my dad's balls. (SCOFFS)
We need to talk.
Your skin is pale white.
You dress fashionably.
And you abstain from sex.
I know what you are.
Say it.
Out loud. Say it.
Jonas brother.
That's right.
Wait, what?
No, I'm a vampire. Duh.
That was my next guess.
Then ask yourself
the most obvious question.
What do we like to eat?
Vampire cereal?
You need to see what
I really look like.
This is why we don't
show ourselves
in the sunlight.
People would know
we're different.
You're shining.
No, that's just my bling.
You don't get it.
I am a killer!
(EXCLAIMS)
(SCREAMING)
Are you texting?
Yeah, Jennifer.
(SCREAMING)
I am the world's most
dangerous predator.
(CHIRRUPING)
I want to eat you!
That's cool.
Most guys
aren't into that.
My family, we're not
like other vampires.
We can control our thirst
to only hunt animals
and the Real Housewives
of Atlanta.
But I don't know
if I can control
myself around you.
Look, Ed.
I don't like to
play games, so
I'm just gonna lay
my cards on the table.
I really like you.
I dig the Eurotrash
heroin-chic look.
You're totally happening,
and I wanna be with you.
I can read
everybody's minds
but yours.
You have to tell me
exactly what
you're thinking.
You're pretty,
so you don't
have to be smart.
Would you like to go
to the prom with me?
(CHUCKLES)
Yes.
That's awesome.
(SNARLING)
(SCREECHING)
BECCA: There were three things
I was absolutely
positive about.
First, Edward was a vampire.
Second, American Idol
is gonna blow without Simon.
And third,
the next time
I saw Edward,
I was gonna hump
the shit out of him and...
Boo.
(GASPS)
Oh, gosh, you scared me.
There is something
that I wanted to try.
Me, too.
I love role-playing.
(CLEARING THROAT)
That's not what I meant.
(CHUCKLES)
Don't move.
Kiss me already.
I know it'll be okay.
(SIGHING)
That was amazing.
I've never gone
to first base before.
Now let's go
all the way.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTING)
Purity ring.
Yeah.
Oh!
I won't be able
to resist my urges
to kill you!
I don't mind.
What?
Oh, God!
Becca, no!
(SIGHS)
Oh, yeah?
I like it rough.
Stay away from me.
No, please, please, please,
don't come any closer!
This is for your own safety.
I'm trying to protect you.
Becca?
(GRUNTING)
If this is going to work,
we're gonna have to take
things slow.
I guess that's okay.
Even though my teen
hormones are raging
and I want to
have sex with you,
I feel conflicted
about losing my virginity.
I know you'll never
have sex with me,
because you're a vampire,
so, really,
it's the ultimate
pubescent girl fantasy.
That was
incredibly insightful.
(SIGHS)
I read it on
Stephenie Meyer's
Twitter page.
Becca, I promise,
as long as you're with me,
you'll never get hurt.
(GRUNTING)
(CLANGING)
Starting now.
(SNIFFING)
(ALL SNARL)
Shit!
Well, I think we all know
whatever killed Fisherman
Sculley was no animal.
Look at those tracks.
It could only mean
one thing.
Canadians.
Damn border-jumpers.
They come here
and take all the shitty jobs
us lazy Americans don't want,
and now they're killing
our fishermen, too.
Yeah, Frank,
I think you're missing
the big picture.
That is a big picture.
BECCA: It was
my 18th birthday,
and the Sullens were
throwing me a party.
Well, this is home.
Hey.
There is no reason
to be nervous.
Well, I'm different
than you.
They might not accept me.
It's like the time
when my ex-boyfriend,
DeShawn,
invited me to his
grandmama's house
to celebrate Kwanzaa.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Dandelion, come where
the sunshine shines
When you clock that second
And your heart starts ticking
May it land on mine
If we make it to space
I'll meet you
Oh, my dandelion
I want you
to meet my family.
You must be Becca.
I'm Edward's mom, Eden.
We've heard so much
about you.
Finger food?
That's Alex and Rosalyn.
I just know we're going
to be great, great friends.
And this is Iris.
I hope we will be.
No, she already knows
it will happen.
Some of us have
special powers.
Iris has visions
of the future.
Oh!
But I'm not on my period.
You will be.
It's coming early
this month.
Relax, Becca.
We're just like any other
normal American family.
Except, of course,
we have no souls,
and we walk the earth
trying to satisfy
an unquenchable
thirst for blood.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(SNIFFING)
I'm Jeremiah.
He's new
to the family.
He's still trying
to control his hunger
for humans.
Look, I don't want
to cause any problems.
Maybe I should go.
But you have to
open your presents.
Ow!
Paper cut.
(JEREMIAH SNARLING)
(YELLING)
You're bleeding.
BECCA: Really bad, actually.
I must have hit an artery.
(BOTH SNARLING)
(BOTH GROWLING)
(BOTH YELPING)
Becca, your nose!
I knew I shouldn't
have partied last night
with Lindsay Lohan.
(ALL SNARLING)
Every time
I bring a girl home,
you guys try to eat her!
It's not fair!
Come on!
(DOOR BELL RINGING)
Someone here
order Chinese food?
(YELLING)
Quick,
they'll be hungry again
in half an hour.
What happened back there
can never happen again.
I now know,
as long as I'm around you
you'll never be safe.
That's why I want you
to bite me, and turn me
into a vampire.
No.
I keep aging and
you stay the same.
I'm 18 now.
I'm practically a cougar.
I just...
I couldn't live with myself
if I turned you
into a vampire.
You're always
sexy and healthy,
and super good-looking,
with tons of free time
and money to travel the world.
It's a lot like being
George Clooney.
Strangely,
the only thing that does
keep aging is your ass.
(CLEARING THROAT)
It gets pretty
wrinkly over time.
You'll never
see me again.
Just promise me
that you won't do
anything reckless.
Okay. I promise
I won't date Chris Brown.
Farewell.
Edward?
Edward! Edward!
Edward!
You're just gonna leave me
here alone in woods
in an area
filled with vampires
who want to eat me?
(WAILING)
(SCREAMING)
Looks like Edward
left us a treat.
Great. This is exactly
what I was talking about.
Take that!
(SCREAMING)
I came here to
help you, bitch!
Sorry.
There's nowhere
else to run.
Your beloved Edward
isn't here to save you.
(SCREAMING)
(SNARLS)
Hmm?
Come on, Jack.
Where's the bro code, huh?
You know you don't try
to eat someone's girlfriend
right after they
break up with them.
(EXCLAIMING)
(TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYING)
Kardashians.
Jack, no!
(BOTH SNARLING)
(SNARLING)
Let's go!
(CHOKING)
Becca.
I'm going to have to suck
the venom out of you.
This is going to
be tough for me
because the taste
of your blood could
send me into a frenzy.
But on the other hand...
(IN DEMONIC VOICE)
Just do it already!
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
Okay, Edward,
I think you got
all the venom out.
You can stop now.
(SLURPING)
(GASPING)
BECCA: And just like that,
Edward was gone.
I just couldn't get over him.
Why did he have to leave me?
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
And the rain is pouring down
And the tears are falling
But they never make...
BECCA: Time passed,
but my yearning for Edward
never subsided.
Everyone reminded me of him.
I couldn't get
Edward out of my mind.
No matter where I looked.
No matter what I saw.
Without Edward,
my life was over.
I felt like dying.
And every night,
I had nightmares
that would make me scream
really, really loud.
(BECCA SCREAMING)
Becca. Becca. Becca.
Becca! Becca! Becca!
You're so upset.
Let me check
your levels.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
Oh. That's not good.
You've got more angst
than The Secret Life of
the American Teenager.
You know, honey,
I'm not real good at the
whole parenting thing.
But I do know that
breakups are hard.
Especially when
you're dumped by someone
as handsome
and hunky as Edward.
That boy can really
fill out a pair of pants.
I'm like,
"Mmm! Look at that!
Look at that!"
Yeah.
And let's face it, honey.
You're no looker.
And you twitch a lot.
It's kind of irritating.
That's for sure
the best piece of ass
you'll ever get.
My advice,
get yourself some of
those big, juicy
onion-butt implants.
Fix your hair up
pretty like Beyoncé
and,
who knows, honey, maybe
a black guy will do you.
That's my girl.
Oh!
Your friend Jennifer
keeps calling.
You should hang out with her.
Probably cheer you up.
I want you to say good night
to your new mommy.
(IN FEMININE VOICE)
Good night, Becca.
I love you. I love you.
She really does.
Well, we're gonna get busy.
Good night, sweetheart.
I don't get it.
Why would anyone want
to date a vampire? Lame.
Yeah. So lame.
That movie's
totally going to flop.
I can't believe
they get married
and have a vampire baby.
(ALL GROANING)
Thanks for
the spoiler alert,
dumbshit!
(CLICKING TONGUE)
It's too bad Edward
dumped you
and now you don't have
a date for the prom.
'Cause that dress
would have looked
great on you.
But you don't
need a dress,
because Edward
left you behind
in the woods like bear shit.
(GASPING) So I'm going
to wear it instead!
(LAUGHING)
And check this out.
Everyone's going to be,
like, super jealous.
Couldn't you just die?
No.
But you can.
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Well, this is me.
Where are you parked?
Uh...
Over there.
(GASPING) Ooh!
Right next to those mean
and scary biker dudes?
See you at school tomorrow!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Hey, baby! Come over here!
You can sit on my bike.
(BIKERS HOOTING)
Becca. Those guys
are dangerous. Walk away.
Edward?
Ow!
Shit. Those guys
are dangerous.
Told you.
This is your brake.
And this is your throttle.
Jacob, there's...
There's something
different about you.
I don't know what it is.
I've been
meaning to tell you.
I'm a man now, Becca.
Are you telling me that...
That's right.
I've had my bar mitzvah.
Mazel tov!
So will you date me now?
(ENGINE REVVING)
Say again?
I couldn't hear you.
(CHUCKLES) Right.
Will you go on a date
with... No, no.
What?
Maybe if you'd stop
revving the bike
whenever I'm about to ask
you something really
important, you'd hear me.
Right. Sorry.
Thank you.
Becca, I wanted to ask
if you would just...
(TRUCK HORN BLARING)
Oh, come on!
(YELLING)
Becca, will you go
on a date with me?
Sorry, but I don't like
to be yelled at, Jacob.
I think I'll just
take her for a spin.
Just one thing first.
Becca, you just
cut the brake line!
(ENGINE REVVING)
Becca, stop.
You're going
to hurt yourself.
(BECCA VOCALIZING)
(SINGING) Hey, Eddy
Well, I know
it might seem petty
But I can't stop
obsessing over you
Put down that guitar
and stop singing
like Taylor Swift.
(GRUNTING)
If this is what
it takes to be with you,
Edward, so be it.
Becca! Don't drink that milk.
You know
you're lactose
intolerant.
This is for you, Edward.
Oh, God.
(STOMACH RUMBLING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Sorry. But I did
try to warn you.
Becca!
Are you trying to get
yourself killed?
Uh-huh.
You're bleeding. Here.
(GRUNTING)
Your body is so...
...furry.
Are those teats?
Yeah, 10 of them, actually.
Oh!
I'd better go
get you some help.
That was fast.
You are so scrumptious.
No!
Be happy it was me
that found you
and not Rachel.
Why? What happened
to Rachel?
She was...
...recast.
(GASPS)
Shh!
She wants to torture you
for what you did to Jack.
At least I will
eat you fast.
(GROWLING)
Becca!
Jacob, run!
That's it?
A Chihuahua?
Yeah, I guess so.
This whole transformation
thing is new to me.
You can't stop me.
You're no werewolf.
That's why I always
travel in a pack.
(SNARLING)
(ALL SNARLING)
(IT'S RAINING MEN PLAYING)
It's raining men
Hallelujah
Amen
I'm gonna go out
I'm gonna let myself get
Absolutely soaking wet
It's raining men
Hallelujah
Amen
It's raining men, yeah
Please.
Get him, girls!
(SQUEALING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Hey.
Sign this?
Now, let's get you home.
You'll be all right now.
I know it's worked!
(SCREAMING)
(SNIFFLING)
Why can't they
just be together?
(SNORTING)
There you are!
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
You look like shit.
What do you want?
Look, we're all sorry
we tried to drink Becca's
blood, even Jeremiah.
But something terrible
has happened to her.
(BURPING)
Becca who?
I am totally over her.
I've moved on. I am done
with normal chicks.
I've finally found
someone as freaky as me.
(MY FIRST WISH PLAYING)
My first wish
Turn the music up
as loud as it gets
My second wish
Me and the girls are
in the hottest outfits
My third wish
(SIGHING)
Too freaky?
Edward, I had a vision!
Becca was riding a motorcycle.
She tried to kill herself.
I fear Becca may be dead.
No.
I've got to find out.
How do you feel?
It's Edward, isn't it?
Here.
Why did you just
take off your shirt?
My contract says
I have to every
1 0 minutes of screen time.
Hmm.
Look, Edward left you.
But I would never do that.
I want to take it
out of the friend zone.
I really like you, Becca.
I like you, too.
When I'm with you,
I just feel
so safe and secure.
Thanks.
As opposed to how
I feel about Edward,
which is all passion,
lust, complete
forbidden fruit stuff.
I mean, with him,
it's all about my pussy.
Okay!
(PHONE RINGING)
Do you mind getting that?
Sure.
Hello.
EDWARD ON PHONE:
Officer Crane?
No, he's not
here right now.
Where is he?
It is very important
that I speak with him.
(FRANK SPEAKING)
He's at the funeral.
Oh, God, no.
Yeah.
And supposedly,
the body was so mangled
that the undertaker
had to use Krazy Glue
to stick the head
back on and put marbles
where the eyes once were.
Hello? Hello?
(SIGHS)
It's true.
Becca's dead.
Edward, I'm so sorry.
I can't live without her.
(GASPING)
Goodbye, Iris.
I'm going to kill myself.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I just had another
vision about Becca!
(SIGHING) Becca's fine.
You don't have to
kill yourself anymore.
Edward!
Shit.
(RICK HOOTING)
Prom rocks!
(BOTH WHOOPING)
I love drinking!
Oh!
What's the matter, Becca?
Still no date for the prom?
Loser!
Here, have a drink, bitch!
RICK: She promised me
sex tonight!
High point of my life!
Becca! Get in the car, now!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
What's wrong?
Edward thinks
you're dead.
Why would he think that?
Um...
Beats me.
He won't live without you
and he wants to die.
He's such a romantic.
(GASPING)
Becca!
Jacob?
Becca, don't go.
You belong with me.
Oh!
I need to know,
who's it going to be?
Is it going to be me or him?
Jacob, I...
I'm not gonna take
no for an answer.
I'm not going to let go
until you tell me,
once and for all.
All right!
Jacob, I'll tell you.
I choose...
Cat!
(GROWLING)
Come back here, pussy!
(CAT YOWLING)
Edward is going
to the Zolturi
to have them kill him.
I saw it. I had a vision.
What are you talking about?
Who are the Zolturi?
They are the evil
bloodsuckers who only
care about themselves
and their own narrow
vision of the world.
They're kind of
like Fox News.
Oh, my God.
Edward's going
to expose himself
in the sunlight,
and the Zolturi
are going to kill him.
They can't allow humans
to know vampires
live among them.
It could destroy us.
Okay, where is this
going to happen?
At the prom.
The Zolturi never miss
a good St. Salvatore Day
festival.
They flew all the way
in from Italy.
Say what you want
about them, but they
do know how to party.
ALL: Suck! Suck! Suck!
Suck! Suck! Suck!
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCREAMS)
(DARO GRUNTING)
(ALL CHEERING)
Oh! I got skills, bitch.
Welcome,
Sporks High students,
to the 201 0 prom.
(HONKING)
And don't forget,
the main event is
coming up shortly.
The crowning of your
prom king and queen.
And if you haven't had
a chance to vote yet,
don't worry,
there's still time.
Just to be sure.
Becca, you're the only one
that can stop Edward.
You have to show him
you're still alive.
I'll do whatever it takes.
BECCA: So, what would you do
to save someone you love?
For Edward,
I would stop at nothing.
Whoa.
You already saw
this part, so let's get
to what happens next.
No!
Edward!
(HISSING)
(SNARLS)
(SCREAMING)
Shit!
(EXCLAIMING)
(GROANING)
(BECCA SCREAMING)
BOTH: Uh-oh.
Edward!
Edward, it's not sunny
anymore. It's twilight.
Hey, new moon.
Ah! Eclipse?
Look at me, everyone!
This is me
in all my glory.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Lucky penny.
(CROWD EXCLAIMING IN DISGUST)
Oh!
Huh?
(ALL LAUGHING)
Edward!
Becca? You're alive?
We have to go now.
Becca, I am so sorry.
I promise you
that I will never
leave you again.
The Zolturi are standing
right behind me, aren't they?
Yep.
Don't worry, Becca.
(SNARLS)
Not talking
smack now, are we?
Stop it!
"Stop it!"
You're killing him!
"You're killing him!"
And we haven't
even had sex yet.
"And we haven't
even had sex..."
Really?
Even... (EXCLAIMING)
Oh!
(GRUNTING)
(RAP SONG PLAYING)
(THE HUSTLE PLAYING)
(SINGING)
(EXCLAIMING)
Becca. Becca.
Oh! Dad.
There you are.
I was worried
about my little girl.
You know, there's still
a killer on the loose.
But I can see you're dancing
with your friends,
so everything's all right.
Dad, no...
No, Frank, wait.
You have to know
the truth.
All of the killing
was done by vampires.
Edward's one, also.
(DARO GRUNTING)
And Bobby White's
a werewolf.
Oh, oh...
Ow!
Sorry.
I understand.
Thank God.
The theme of the prom!
(LAUGHING)
No, Dad.
Enjoy, okay?
Becca, by the way,
thanks for everything.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(ALL THRU THE NITE PLAYING)
All through the night
Too close. Separate,
arms length apart.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Too close. Separate!
Arms length apart!
(GRUNTS)
Hmm.
(HUMMING)
(YELLING)
Say cheese.
(GASPING)
Whoo!
What...
...the hell?
(EDWARD READING)
Oh!
(YELLING)
Where's Becca?
(WHIMPERING)
(GRUNTING)
Surrender now,
or Salvatore will snap
her neck like a Slim Jim.
You must pay for
exposing yourself.
Tell you what
I'm going to do,
Ed-to-the-ward.
I won't kill you.
But Becca has to
become a vampire.
Cool?
No, not cool.
No way! Never!
All right.
Pull Edward's head off,
then rip his body apart
and set him on fire.
No, no, no.
I mean, yes!
I meant yes!
(CHUCKLING) Of course,
she would love to
become a vampire.
She practically brings it up
all the time. Right, hon?
Uh, I guess so.
Then bite her now!
Bite!
(GNARLING)
Listen up, people!
May I have your attention?
And now the moment
you've all been waiting for.
And this year's
Sporks High prom king
and prom queen is...
...Jennifer and Rick!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(ALL CHEERING)
RICK: Triumph for the Rick!
Congratulations.
Thank you!
Yeah!
Oh!
Hold on!
It seems you two received
over 69,000 votes
in a class of only 300.
(ALL BOOING)
I'm afraid
you're disqualified.
What?
Oh!
God! You asswipe!
(GROANS)
My life is over!
As your principal,
I will nominate a new
prom king and queen.
(ALL CHATTERING)
And I will pick...
I will... Let me see.
I will choose...
I pick you two!
Us?
Yes!
Because you two exemplify
what's best about
this whole prom.
I mean, you really look
like a couple of mean,
evil bloodsucking vampires.
(GROWLING)
Oh, my God!
We won! We won!
(ALL CHEERING)
Yes, yes, yes!
Move. Out of the way.
(HOOTING)
(CRYING) Oh!
(CLEARING THROAT)
Edward!
Bite. Bite.
Do it.
Bite me now.
I don't want to wait
a second longer.
I will only turn you
into a vampire
on one condition.
Marry me.
Yes.
Are you ready?
(LAUGHING)
(MOANING)
How do you feel?
Perfect.
It's how I always imagined.
I love you, Becca...
(YELPS)
Team Jacob, bitch!
(GROANING)
Fuck me.
(SCREAMING)
(IF I WAS YOUR VAMPIRE
PLAYING)
If I was your vampire
Slim as the moon
Instead of killing time
We'll have each other
till the sun
If I was your vampire
Death waits for no one
Put my hands across your face
Because I think
our time has come
Digging your smile apart
with my spade tongue
And the hole
is where the heart is
We built this tomb together
I will fill it alone
Beyond the pale
Everything's black
No turning back
If I was your vampire
Slim as the moon
Instead of killing time
We'll have each other
till the sun
If I was your vampire
Death waits for no one
Put my hands across your face
Because I think
our time has come
Beyond the pale
Everything's black
No turning back, no
Beyond the pale
Everything's black
No turning back, no
(MY PANTIES PLAYING)
I feel so lonely
Nobody gets me
I am so unhappy
Why can't I find a cool
alternative boyfriend
who understands me?
We can watch the classics
Shop at Hot Topic
We're sexting dirty pics
of me in my panties
We can watch the classics
Shop at Hot Topic
Sexting dirty pics
of me in my panties
My panties, my panties
Sexting dirty pics
of me in my panties
My panties, my panties
We can watch the classics
Shop at Hot Topic
We're sexting dirty pics
of me in my panties
We can watch the classics
Shop at Hot Topic
Sexting dirty pics
of me in my panties
My panties, my panties
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
I'm the one
who's always thinking about
All the ways
to get to the end of it
You came around
And I think that I found
A good reason
to try and sit with it
You're taking me down
But I like the sound
And I want to get
with you anyway
Is this solid ground
Or am I getting drowned?
I'm just as happy
taking it day by day
And in the end
We all end up the same
Love and desire
Will be you once again
Life, listen and sing
We all end up the same
And in the end
It all goes up in flames
Scars on the skin
You're bringing me in
And I'm closer, closer
Every minute
We'll start to spin
And I'm in it to win
And I'm taking
every last bit of it
Looking at your face
Making my heart race
And I can't seem
Can't seem to make it stop
Sitting by your side
Want to go for a ride
And I'm waiting
Waiting for you to drive
And in the end
We all end up the same
Love and desire
Will be almost plain
Life, listen and sing
We all end up the same
And in the end
It all goes up in flames
ENGLISH - US - PSDH