Quoi de neuf Bob ?
I feel good, I feel great I feel wonderful
Good Morning Gil.
I said ... Good Morning Gil.
I gotta go to work
See Ya.
Wish Me Luck Gil !
Doctor, It's your wife on the phone
Thank you Claire.
Fay, Are you sitting down ?
My Publisher thinks it's gonna happen
Ya, he thinks Good Morning America is coming to lake
Pinasetoki next week to interview me.
It's a tremendous shock in the arm for my book.
Ye.. No! It's very unsual..
Well I think they did visit doctor Rooth once but, other than that ...
Hold on a second honey.
Yes.
Excuse me doctor, but there is doctor Godswell on the phone.
Thank You.
Fay, I have to go, just another collegue on the phone.
Wow, it's rude to come out to the real work when you're famous
Good bye there.
Godswell !
Leo ! Long time no see huh !
You've got a big book out !
Things are really clikin' huh ?
That's the way I planned it !
Listen Leo, I'm quitting my practice for a while, I'm leaving town.
And I have one patient I'd like to refer to you.
Exactly what kind of case is it Godswell ? He's not psycothic is he ?
No ! No ...nothing like that !
Listen, his name is Bob Willey
He pays early, he comes on time.
He just  needs someone brilliant.
I know you don't like flatery but,
If there's anyone I know who could win a Nobel Prize, it's you.
Well...I suppose I could find an hour for him sometime after labour day
Okay ! I'll work him in for an interview
Hey Godswell , huh , how come you're leaving town ?
We're a dying breed Leo, Good Luck !
Free !
Claire, If a Bob Willey calls, schedule him for a short interview
right after I get back from my vacation
He's already called Dr Marvin, twice, he's your next apointment.
Hmm , That's persistence.
I feel good, I feel great I feel wonderful
I feel good.
Can I Help you Sir ?
Yes, Dr Marvin, Dr Leo Marvin
Second Elevator, 44th Floor.
Thank You.
Elevator ?
Bob..Willey...
Hum, Why don't you sit down, it will be a few minutes.
Dr Marvin, Bob Willey.
Thank You.
Thank you for working me Doctor.
Should I call you Dr Marvin or Leo ?
Which ever you like.
Call me Bob.
Is that your family ?
Yes.
Oh wait, let me guess, I'm very good at this!
Err, That's Harriet...
And then Ronny
Gretchen
And Rita.
Eh wait, wait a second,
Cecilia,
Dorothy
And this is Kennet
And Bamby.
This is my son Sigmund
And my wife Fay
And my daughter Anna
And that's my sister Lily
Lily ? I was close.
It's a beautiful family.
Thank You.
Have a seat.
Why don't I start ?
The simplest way to put it,
I have problems.
I worry about diseases,so,
I have trouble touching things,
In public places it's almost impossible.
I have a real big problem moving.
Talk about moving.
As long as I'm in my apartment, I'm ok.
But when I go out, I get WEIRED !
Talk about weired.
Well, I get desease spams, ellosia,
Cold sweats,
Hot Sweats,
fiber blestures,
difficulty breathing, difficulty swallowing,
Bird Vision,involntary tremble
Dead ends, nom lips,
Finger nails sensitivity,
Pelvis discomfort,
So the real question is, what is the crisis ?
What is that you're trully affraid of ..
What if my heart stops beating ?
What if ... I'm looking for a bathroom , I can't find it...
and my bladder exploses...
Do you ever heard of thread syndrom ?
Involontary shouting profanity..
It's exceptionnaly rare ...
SHUT IT SON OF A BITCH !
BASTARD !
Why exactly are you doing this ?
If I fake it, then I don't have it !
You know it's the same with the cardiac arrest.
Are you married ?
I'm divorced.
Would you like to talk about that ?
There are two types of people in this world.
Those who like Neil Daemon
and those who don't.
My ex-wife loves him.
I see,
So, what you're saying is
that even you are an almost paralyzed,
multi-phobic personality that he's in a constant state of panic,
your wife did not leave you, you left her,
because she liked Neil Daemon
No, you're saying that maybe,
maybe I didn't leave her because she likes Neil Daemon,
but maybe, she left me ?
Yes.
Oh Oh Oh Oh ....
Dr Marvin,
You can help me, for the first time in my life,
I feel like there's hope !
I feel like I can be somebody.
Bob, there's an old saying,
that's the best psychiatric in the world,
is the one right inside of you.
Yeah...
I can help you, yes.
Thank you.
Bob, there is a ground-breaking new book, that has just come out,
Now, I have writed this book, of course it applies to you, but,
I'm sure that you can see
when you see the title,
exactly how it could help.
Baby Steps ?
It means setting small reasonnable goals for yourself
one day at a time.
On tiny step at a time
Baby steps
For Instance, hum...
When you leave this office,
don't think about everything you have to do
in order to get out of the building,
just think to what you must do to
get out of this room,
and when you get to the hall,
deal with that hall,
and so ...
You see ?
Baby steps !
Baby steps.
Oh boy !
Baby steps, baby steps,
baby steps through the office,
baby steps out the door,
it works !
All I have to do ..
just take one little step at a time,
and I can do anything !
Baby step throughout the office, Baby step throughout the office.
That should give you a lot to digest while I'm on vacation..
v..vacation ?
Oh, certainly my secretary told you,
as this afternoon I'm taking my family on vacation
until labour day.
That's a month !
What if I need you ? What if I need to talk ?
Well my associate, Dr Armand, will be happy to talk...
and Bob, I'll be back !
Just read baby steps.
Baby steps, out of the office.
Very good.
Baby steps to the hall.
Very good Bob, keep going.
That's it !
Bye.
I'll see you in a month !
Baby steps to the elevator,
Baby steps to the elevator.
July 31st, Bob Willey,
Introductory interview,
Multiphobic personality,
characterized by huge separation with reality,
and extremely for family connections,
bid the usual rates for the interview and $29.95 for the book
It's your publisher,
he's says Good Morning America is definitely coming
Yes !
Thank You.
Baby steps onto the elevator,
Baby steps into the elevator,
I'm in the elevator,
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Manhattan exchange,
Yes this is Bob Willey, I'm a patient of Dr Marvin,
I have to speak with him right away, it's urgent...
I'm sorry Mr Willey, But Dr Marvin's out...
It's Bob and you are ?
Betty
Betty, Hi !
Bob, Dr Marvin's out of town, and Dr Armand is taking his cause,
I know that Betty,
It's just the expense of confusion,
I was supposed to call Dr Marvin,
but I've lost his phone number.
Bob, I can't give out that number.
I know that Betty,
But you could call him on the other line,
and tell him that I'm on hold on the other line, could you please ?
Thanks Betty please ...
Phone Daddy..
Thank you Anna.
Thank you sweet heart.
Yes.
Dr Marvin, this is Betty at your exchange,
I'm sorry to disturb you but,
I have a Bob Willey on the line
who says you wants to talk to him
Betty you know better than that ...
Dr Armand is covering for me
I told him that Doctor,
but he lost your number and then it was urgent.
All right, put him through
Go ahead bob.
This is Dr Marvin, what's the problem Bob ?
Dr Marvin, how's the wheater up there ?
What ?
How's your brewd ?
You're gonna get the chance to relax ?
Bob ...
I thought I made it clearly,
I'm on vacation,
Well I know,
but I'm just worst as usual this time, really bad.
Bob, if this is really an emergency,
go to the ER.
And if it isn't call Dr Armand,
I'm sure he can help you.
Well I'd just feel so much so much better
if I knew where you were !
It's my disvenue right ?
Bob,
But, can't we just talk ?
Yes we can,
In my office after labour day !
After your bathroom fire all huh ?
Good Bye Bob.
You want to keep me not to yourself ?
Good Bye Bob !
Is this a fake hang up ?
It's a fake hang up !
I'll get the phone, I'll get the phone
Allo ?
Doctor, It's Betty again,
I have an urgent call from your sister
My sister ?
Put her through
Go ahead.
It's not you, it's me.
Lily ? What's wrong ?
Dr Marvin, please don't be hangry, this is Bob.
I know that I shouldn't be calling..
Bob, the doctor patient relationship is based
on trust, and when you call me pretenting to be my sister,
I can't trust you anymore.
Go to the ER, please, do not call me here again!
No no no no...
That was not smart !
Who is it ?
Detective Robertson, from homicide, I have some questions about a Bob Willey.
What ?
That was the Bob who kept calling Dr Marvin.
That was that Bob who kept calling.
Unfortunately, Bob comitted suicide about 15 minutes ago.
Oh my God!
That's terrible !
Very sad, It should never happend
A very sweet guy,
but he did leave a note however
mentionning a Betty
She's Betty.
I'm Betty.
Oh.
So you're Betty.
Oh, Bob called here trying to reach his psychiatric
Oh, well where is he ?
I may ask him some questions too.
Dr Marvin is on vacation in New Hampshire.
New Hampshire!
I can get it on the phone for you.
Good.
No! don't !
If I really need to, I'll send some NHPD to drop by.
Err, but,
what if I wanted to write him a letter... would you have a mailing adress or some kind up there ?
Oh, sure !
That's PO BOX 14
Lake Winnipeusaukee
Which is spelled ?
W.I.N.N.I.P.E.S.A.U.K.E.E.
Thank you very much ladies!
I'm crazy about you!
Especially you Betty.
Allo ?
What ?
All right.
Thank you for calling Betty.
It was the service.
That patient who called before,
he comitted suicide.
Oh Leo, how horrible.
Oh well , that's not gonna spoil our vacation.
Baby Steps get on the bus..
Baby Steps ...
This is the last bus to winnipesaukee Bob.
Yes I know Wing, Thank you !
Baby Steps get on the bus..
Baby Steps ..
You think you can do it today Bob ?
What a busy schedule ...
Baby Steps in the bus ...
Baby Steps in the halley...
Baby Steps...
And seat.
Hello !
I'm Bob,
Would you knock me out please ? Just a hit in the face...
Do we have enough to feed the entire film creature ?
Honey, we have enough to feed the entire network !
Oh Great! Another vacation that is not a vacation...
Why do I have to dress up for this stupid show ?
You mean, you already tryied on everything you own !
I have not !
All right ! All right ! Oh My Gosh !
It will probably be a short interview anyway,
just me and the family
my book.
Easy fellows, we're almost there !
False alarm.
Dr Marvin !
Dr Leo Marvin !
Doctor
Marvin !
Thank You !
- Bye Doctor !
- Thanks Again
Isn't someone calling you ?
Right over there !
Oh My God !
Doctor
Leo
Leo, do you know that man ?
Get in the car !
Come on ! Hurry !
Hurry , Hurry !
Doctor Marvin !
Ohhhhh I really appreciate this !
Everyone in the car ! Come on !
Doctor Marvin...
This is a bad time ?
The fam' !
- Who's that ?
- I don't know ...
What are you doing here ?
I thought you were dead !
Oh well,
I felt a little bit,
but don't be mad at me...
Bob, your behaviour is completely inapropriate,
You're hangry...
No, No, I don't get hangry...
So you're upset...
I don't get upset!
Well let's have a little talk...
Bob, I do not see patients on vacation, ever !
How many ways can I make that clear ?
Now, what I would like you to do
is to get on this bus,
and go back to New York.
I can't ! I'm totally paralized !
I'm all locked up !
You got yourself here !
Barrely...
Well getting back to the therapeutic !
Could we just have a little talk ?
Bob ! You are testing my patience !
Come on ! I come so far !
- Bob !
- Baby Steps...
- I'm doing the work !
Baby Steps! And I'm not a slacker !
Check it out ! I'm in a really bad shape !
Come on please !
Gimme,Gimme,Gimme, I need, I need, I need !
Ok ok ok ! All right ! All right !
All right, it's 2 o'clock
go to the bus station, buy yourself a ticket home
and then wait for me at that coffee shop.
You'll meet me ?
I'll call you !
In 2 hours...
Oh my God! You're the greatest !
No no no... just you have to promess me that
you will buy your ticket and go home !
Absolutely !
I'll do it right now!
All right, I'll call you at 4 o'clock..
You could possibly make it 3:30 could you ?
Bob !
4 ! 4 okay !
Exactly 4 o'clock ! It's better. Okay
Thank you Dr M. !
Baby Steps to 4 o'clock...
Oh my Gosh !
I need a bowl !
- What ?
- I need a bow, he's been locked in for abour 8 hours !
he's about to scream.
he's furious.
Sorry Gil. Little Negligence on my part,
here you go, come on tight fellow
Ohhh, it was a long ride wasn't it ? I know, I need a scratch...
Hey No ! No ! No !
I'm expecting a phone call !
Thank You.
Thanks a lot! Thanks everybody, I really appreciate it!
Also,
If I ...
loose consciousness or black out or
something explodes,
whould you tell Dr Marvin when he calls
Doctor Leo Marvin ?
Do you know him ?
Yeah !
He bought our dream house !
It's a lifetime to save for downpaiment
He sew down with a bag full of money,
and grab the tab for unders.
Son of a bitch !
She never says that.
Stay as far away from him as possible!
Well that will be easy !
He don't see me, that's why I'm expecting a phone call.
He won't see you...
Well,
We'll show you where he lives !
You will ?
The son of a bitch !
She never says that !
Siggy, I have the whole house to fix,
all the art to hang,
I have no idea whenever I will be on the TV show,
but I've stopped everything in order to teach you how to dive.
This is as important for me to see you dive
as it is for me to appear on Good Morning America.
Oh man ! This is really pressure.
Come on take off your rode
Why are you always wearing black ?
What is it with you and the death mecanization ?
Maybe I'm morring from my lost childhood
All right, come on turn around !
Close to the edge, that's it!
Remember what we did last year.
One, Two Three Spread.
Now bend up the knees, bend your waist, hands out, step on the board.
One, Two , Three..
Spread !
One
Two
Three
Spread
Summerfall, time to go dad!
I don't understand...
why won't you dive ?
From all the horror in this world, what difference does it make ?
Hi Lily !
I'm just calling to remind you about Leo surprise party.
Thursday night 7 o'clock.
ok ?
Well, it will be after his interview so he should be relaxed,
oh, wait a minute.
Oh Yes! Of course I'm thrilled Lily,
the last person interviwed on vacation
was Dcotor Rooth.
Here he comes, Thursday night 7 o'clock, don't forget ok ? Bye bye
He didn't dive ?
No ...
Oh come on sweetie, he's just a little bit affraid of it!
The patience...
No, it's not like I wanted him to jump from an airplane...
When i was growing up, I thought diving was fun !
I thought you were born grown up daddy !
Yes, I'd like the number to the godlam's coffee...
What are you doing here ?
I'm sorry, don't be mad,
the goldams brought me
Thank you Mr and Mrs G. !
You're welcome Bobby !
Hello Doctor Marvin !
The house looks good !
Burn in hell Dr Marvin !
Bob, we agreed I would call you !
Coming here is unbelievably inapropriate !
Dad, can I ...
Oh, I'm sorry
Hi ! You're Anna aren't you ?
I saw your picture, I'm Bob!
Hi bob !
Nice to meet you Bob !
Hi ! I'm Bob !
I'm Fay.
Oh Mrs M. you are even
prettier than your picture !
and younger !
Thank you !
Fay, Anna, Would you please excuse us ?
I think Bob and I have something to talk about.
Really ?
You think so too ?
Let's take a walk !
-Oh Bob, could I get your fish ?
- Oh yes, thank you!
he's already been in a bowl otherwise.
This is a great place !
No wonder why the goldam want it !
I'm sorry about bargging you like this !
That's all right !
I understand.
The problems don't go away just because I go.
Bob, I'd like you to ... take a long look around you
what is everything you see here have in common ?
Vacation Bob !
Vacation.
Now,
I can't Bob, at this time, give you the kind of therapy
to contension you need to solve all your problems
and you know why...
you're on vacation !
Exactly !
What I can do,
is, this.
Don't give me pills ! I already have plenty !
This is not pills !
Read It !
It says,
Take a vacation
from my problems.
Give you a persmission to take a vacation
from your problems !
Not a vacation from your work,
not a vacation from daily life,
but a vacation
from my problems.
Exactly !
And now I want you to get on that bus
and go back to New York.
But !
Every single time a problem arises,
I want you to take that prescription out
and follow it to the letter, Doctor's orders.
I see you in New York, in my office
in one month !
This is incredible !
This is a step on me !
For the first time since ever, I feel free !
You gave me a great gift Doctor !
The gift of life !
You're a great man !
I knew coming right here was the right thing to do...
It feels right because you are here
and it feels right because you're leaving.
- Have a great vacation !
- You too Bob !
The vacation from my problems !
You bet I will !
Here you go !
Baby Steps.
Is everything all right honey ?
- Yes, everything is perfectly fine.
- he seemed pleasant enough
When he's controlled
I got so excited I forgot to bring you with me !
Gil...
Oh! The Fish !
Wow, that's a very nice likes of you.
Thank you very much.
of everyone actually.
Bye Bob!
Bye bye Bob!
Bye bye !
You've got to be Sigmund ?
Yes, this is Sigmund and
and this is Bob
and Bob was just leaving.
Hi !
Oh, this is Gil my fish Sigmund.
Did you get him on the lake ?
No, he's a sitty fish.
Cool.
Be he love uppon here!
You father is the most incredible psychiatrist,
I sincerely hope you appreciate him.
Have a great vacation family !
Me too.
Good Bye Bob !
Bye Bob!
Bye!
Well, he's different.
Or ...
This.
I told you, I like the riffle, I think it's a symbol
of virility.
Now can I eat breakfast, I'm supposed to go sailing
on George's boat.
Wait , Wait !
Fay, I need your opinion, riffle or us ?
I think both are wonderful sweetie !
hmm Fay !
You know I can't live with that kind of answers !
I need feedback !
Good morning Doctor Marvin !
No ! These aren't for you !
They're for Fay !
For yesterday,
for your hospitality
to Gil and me.
I didn't say thank you.
I thought about what you said !
Take a vacation from my problems,
and I did !
But you're back !
No I'm not !
You're not ?
I'm on vacation !
This isn't an apointment, I'm dropping by !
This is my first time over the lake !
This is my first time...
anywhere !
Well I'm anxious cause I'm not able to get food yet,
but I'm staying at the goldman's and I told them what you said,
They insisted.
No no no no no!
I know it can't work.
But let's get the friendship going.
See you later !
It seems thats he's staying, doesn't it ?
Hey, Paper Boy, this was on the couch.
Thank you.
Family conference!
All right, now, I don't want any of you
letting Bob into this house.
Why ?
- Why ??
- Sweet heart, aren't you over-reacting just a little bit ?
Good we found an agreeement,
Family conference is over.
The vacation from my problems
There is nobody here.
There's nothing to fear.
I will be alone
I'm all by myself.
There is nobody here.
Hi Bob !
- Hi!
- Where are you going ?
Just going to town.
- Buy some kleenex.
- Well you want a ride ?
I'd love one.
Do a lot of people use this car ?
Just us.
So, how's it like to be the daughter of a brilliant analyst ?
When he's in the next bedroom at night when you need him, is it great ?
Hmm No ... It's not great.
I have problems, the same as anyone else.
The same as you.
You're affraid your bladder explode ?
What other ones are the same ?
Like what ? Like what ?
Well like analyzing everything !
to death, to see what I'm feeling is normal.
Yes, I have it !
Do you freeze up and, turn into wood when you're around a good looking guy
you don't even know if he likes you or not!
Well, not a guy, but yes I freeze.
You know, I treat people,
as if they were telephones,
If I meet somebody I think doesn't likes me I say I'm Bob,
this one is temporarely out of order.
you know, don't break the connection,
just hang up and try again!
Does it work ?
It seems to be !
I'm on vacation at lake winnipesaukee !
All right ?
Do you want to come sailing on
my friend George's boat ?
ohhh no...
That's ok, you don't have to.
No, I'd love to !
It sounds great !
I've never been on a boat, and I don't know how to handle it!
It just make my lips hard to think about it.
But if you find a good sailor, and the craft to see
Yes, I would go sailing !
Yeah Let's go sailing !
I know the plans !
I'm sailing !
This is child abuse !
If you drop me I'll prosecute !
I'm not gonna let go until you're ready ok ?
Trust me!
Put your hans up like I showed you.
I'm not ready.
You hear me ? I'm not ready ! Don't drop me !
I'm not ready !
Dr Marvin ! I'm sailing !
Oh, Siggy....
Murderer !
Killer !
- Hi dad !
- I sail !
Anna !
Anna ! Come here please !
- Dad !
- Anna, I'd like to speak to you please.
Dr Marvin, Dr Marvin, guess what !
I sail !
I'm a sailor ! I sail !
- I'd like to talk to my daughter alone !
- What is this ? a break through ?
Do you think that I'm a sailor ?
I sail ?
I sail now ?
Keep sailing Bob !
On a boat on the lake.
Very far away from the dock.
Into the wind, with the sky and everything.
I thought I told you to stay away from Bob Willey !
Dady, I was with my friends !
- Where are we going ?
- Home !
- What about the car ?
- Leave it, it's been a long time since I've got a talk with my daughter !
Oh daddy ! Not here !
Anna, Anna, Anna !
Anna ...
- I know you won't listen to your father,
but you will always listen to me.
- So I'm asking not to see Bob Willey.
- Daddy, I am just...
- I can't hear you !
- Where are you Anna ?
- I'm just having fun with my friends !
- And Bob Willey.
- Yes and Bob Willey !
- Bob Willey is your father's patient
- Bob Willey is a very sensitive person !
- Your father's sensitive ?
- Bob listens to people !
- You father listens to people !
- Except when he's up here on lake Winnipesaukee.
He is FUN !
You father is ... kinda fun.
I'm Fay Marvin.
Doctor Marvin's wife.
And I'm very happy to be on your program.
And these are our childrens, Anna and Siggy.
I'm a failure.
What ?
Going on national television tomorrow as an expert on human behaviour,
and in the space of the last hour, both of my childrens
told me that they hate me.
Come on, you know they don't mean it.
Anna accused me of being insensitive.
No, what she actually said was,
I was insensitive,
and I didn't listen,
and I wasn't any fun,
and that Bob Willey was...
Give me...
Some time...
To blow the man down...
You see something different about me ?
- No.
- Do you sail ?
Well I just picked that up
What am I going to pick up next ?
- Try diving !
- All right ! Diving !
I know a great teacher.
My dad, he just dropped me into the water, without warning me first.
I mean, I nearly drunked.
My whole life flashed before my eyes.
Well you're lucky you're only 12!
That still grim.
I mean what is it with him and diving ?
What's the big deal ?
Well .. he ...
Wow...
He probably just want you to beat it, that's all.
You know he probably just want you to dive, because you're affraid of diving.
Didn't I tell you I sailed on my first try ?
I just let the boat do the work,  that was my secret.
But, with diving, what's the thing ?
- What's the trick ?
- I don't know
It's supposed to be easy.
Can you give me a handle on it ?
Thanks.
- Careful, oh careful !
- Let's go to the edge.
Go to the Edge!
Come on toes off, close to the edge.
Don't worry.
- Come on!
- Let's call this the edge, right here, this is the edge.
Ok, step out this edge.
Now walk up to our edge.
Okay
Got you.
Bend your knees.
Very good.
- Stick to the board.
- I am sticked to the board.
Just a second, no rush.
Just a second, it's my first dive.
Well I can't see what you're doing,
why don't you get first ?
Hey careful, hold it hold it!
- Come up, come up
- Hold it , hold it!
- Hold my shirt, I'll show you.
- I got it.
- Okay, bend my knees.
Bend your knees.
Hands forward.
Stick to the board.
Honey,
Come here, look.
Come here, come here.
I don't want to see this !
No please !
- One
- Please No !
- Two
- Don't do it ! Please !
- Three
Yes !
Yeah !
Bravo !
Hey Bob ! Thank you !
I'll take him from here !
Look what you did Bob !
Wonderful !
Did you see me dive dad ?
I go !
Thank you, Excellent !
watch this ! I can do it again !
I'll take ou from here !
See it dad !
I'm gonna do it again !
Oh my God ! Bob !
WHAT ARE YOU STARRING AT ??
I HAD THE RIGHT TO BUY THIS HOUSE !!
Am I gonna die ?
- Am I gonna die ?
- No !
Fay ...
Look everybody, I'm not wrong often
but when I am, I admit it.
I mean it.
I would like you all to accept my apology.
- But what about Bob ?
- What about Bob ?
Yeah, dad, don't you think you should apologies to Bob ?
I will not apologies to Bob.
Why not?
All right.
I'll apologies to Bob.
And now I'd like him to go.
Leo, why are you so hostile to him ?
Because he's a patient !
Fay, don't you get it, he's a patient !
A patient ! A patient !
- Mum, can we have Bob over for dinner ?
- Dinner ?
Yeah !
I don't want Bob for dinner Fay.
Leo, it's for the kids.
I want to think about my interview tomorrow !
I'm sorry Leo.
Right is right.
Fay, this is so crunchious.
- Is this hand chocked ?
Would you like some more chicken Bob ?
- Leo do you want the breast ?
- No no no, that's fine, eat up !
Hmm nice bicuits huh ?
Yeah, great biscuits, great corn, great potatoes.
You want some more salad Bob ?
Ya, I think I do.
Can you get that tomatoe off there please ?
Sure.
Thank you.
This is delicious !
Will you stop that please !
Leo, I see salt and pepper, is there a salt substitute ?
I'll get it!
And dont call me Leo.
But you said in your office that I could call you Leo.
That was in my office.
In my home, I'd like you to call me Dr Marvin.
He's just a little bit nervous about his interview tomorrow.
Oh yeah ! I heard about your upcoming date view !
Congratulations Le... Dr Marvin!
Your book is gonna do a lot of good to a lot of people !
I'm a walking proof of that !
- Is this butter or margarine ?
- Butter.
Dad ?
Dad, are you okay ?
- Dad ?
- Honey ?
Don't panic, I know what to do !
Don't worry, hang on !
He's dying !
I'm doing the right thing !
Honey , I love you ! Breath !!
Maybe with your knee more !
Hit him harder !
Spit it up !
He doesn't blew !
Spit again !
- Leo are you ok ?
- Get him off me !
Bob you saved him !
That was incredible !
I just never gave up hope !
We're singing in the rain ...
just singing in the rain ...
what a glorious day,
I'm happy again ...
I walk through the kitchen...
With the bowl for the chicken...
And I put in Leo, I mean Dr Marvin's refrigerator...
Thank you.
I'm singing in the rain ...
Well being a party cool, but tomorrow is really important
better calling  the night.
I don't want to be rude, but maybe it's time for Bob to sing his way home !
Honey he can't walk under this !
Did I say that ?
I'll drive him !
- Oh dad ! The car is still at the marina !
- What ?
You said to leave her, remember ?
Well that gonna led up soon.
He's gonna go home then.
But what if it starts up again ?
He can borrow my slicker !
- Leo ..
- Shhht
- Leo ...
- Shhht... I think it's ledding up !
Leo, honey, it's 1 o'clock in the morning...
we can't make Bob sit here all night !
Let just him stay over...
STAY !!
Good Morning America will be here at 7 o'clock !
You don't want them to discover a sevirely disturbed patient sleeping on one of my coaches !
There's an extra bed in Siggy's room.
- Fay !!
- Leo, you were very upset over Anna and Siggy...
It's your chance to show what kind of guy
Leo Marvin really is...
Come on sweetie.
Come on.
Bob, We would love for you to spend the night.
That's a great idea !
Do you have a pillow ?
Sure, sure ! Anna would you get a pillow and some sheets for Bob ?
Sure !
Siggy, would you get one of you father's ropes for Bob ?
Yeah !
Are you sure I'm not imposing ?
Oh no ! Not at all !
okay ...
Do you care which bed ?
Well I prefer facing south-east.
This one.
Did you find a tooth brush ?
Yes.
Fay, you know where my new tooth brush is ?
In the bathroom.
I know it should be in the bathroom but it is not in the bathroom !
Leo, honey, juste because you're going on television tomorrow
this isn't giving you any right being so snippy !
It is not that that is making me snippy!
- It's him !
- Him who ?
Bob ?
Yes Bob !
Who else am I talking about ?
- Quiet, he would hear you !
- So what if he hears me ! It's my house ins't it ?
Don't you get it ? He faked suicide !
Wasn't that a cry for help ?
What is the matter with all of you ?
Don't you understand ?
This man is crazy !
I mean, for all we know, he could be a...
Mass Murderer !
Oh Come on Leo !
He's a sweet guy !
He's perfectly harmless !
Maybe a little nevrotic, but
not crazy.
Don't you realize, that everything he's done,
violates the doctor/patient relationship ?
And now he's in there,
with our son !
Bob ?
Yeah ?
Are you affraid of death ?
Yeah ...
Me too...
Ther's no way out of it ...
You're going in to die..
I'm going to die...
It's going to happend
What difference does it make if it's tomorrow
or in 80 years ...
Much sooner you get it...
Do you know how fast does time goes ?
I was 6 like yesterday ...
Me too...
I'm going to die !
You ... are going to die.
There's nothing to be affraid of !
Well not diving anymore ...
But ...
Treat syndrom.
What's treat syndrom ?
Oh, I'm very proud of it Mr Obson,
very encourage by its success
I think the greatest challenge to me is not for writing.
Butt head !
Snup Face !
Don't you ram it !
Turkey tits !
Open this door !
Sigmund !
Sigmund Open this door immediately !
I'm sorry dad.
Sorry.
What is going on around here ?
Treats.
I'm sorry Da... Leo... Dr Marvin.
I don't want to ear another pipe out of this room !
People are trying to sleep around here !
I think it's just kids being kids !
Well tomorrow is just the most important day of my carreer !
We're sorry, we'll stop.
We just got carried away.
It will never happend again.
I want you to be out of here by 6:30, do you understand me ?
The camera crew is coming at 7, I want you out by 6:30 !
Sure, Would you like something for sleep ?
What ?
I have valium if you need it.
No ! I don't need any valium !
I want some peace and quiet !
I'll be quiet.
I'll be peace.
Come on Bob.
Come on, here we go.
Now, we've got to keep your father calm for Good Morning America tomorrow
Bob gave you great things to be affraid of instead of death.
That's nice sweetie.
That's very nice Bob.
- Good night fellows.
- Good Night
- Mrs M., could you leave the door open just a creak ?
- Oki Doki.
6 o'clock Bob, time to wake up, come on !
Come on Bob ! Get Up ! Bob !
Come on Bob !
Bob, rising shine ! Come on !
BOB ! COME ON BOB ! GET UP !
BOB !
BOB ! GET UP !
COME ON !
IT'S 6 O'CLOCK ! RISING SHINE RISING SHINE !
Anna go get the car right away !
Now come on Bob !
Come on !
BOB !
CUTCUDADEDOE !
DOH !
Honey, relax !
Baby stepping down the stairs.
Success, this is a beautiful morning or what ?
Get Out !
- I had the most incredible dream last night !
- Leave !
- Good Bye Mrs M. See you later !
- Bye bye Bob !
Bye Anna !
Bye Bob !
Good Bye rat dick suck nut !
Good bye pissing
See you later testicule head beaver !
Good Morning America's here !
Hi ! I'm Mary Grady.
That's an honor to get you in Good Morning America.
I watch your stuff all the time !
- Aren't we jumping out too early ?
- No ! Not at All !
- I'm Derek Catrell the director.
And this is our producer Larry Binds.
- Nice to meet you.
- Well, may we come in ?
- Ya ! Oh sure !
This is our home,
I was thinking of something by the fire ?
It's frieplace shot fellows !
This is even nicer than the pictures.
Thank You.
Is this your family ?
Yes, yes it is.
Oh ! Excuse me, I'm sorry,
this is my wife Fay,
Oh, sorry,
And this is my daughter Anna,
And my son ... hmm
- Siggy ?
- Siggy !
Oh ! Hi ! I'm Mary.
Hello Mary, I'm Bob.
Yes, that was Bob,
He's a patient he lives down the road.
Dr Marvin, what a great idea !
A Baby Step real action !
- What ?
- Oh, Dr Marvin's gonna get a patient with him.
Fine, Lenny listen up how we should shot this fire place.
Let's set up over here and shoot.
Oh ! Wait a minute !
No problem Dr Marvin ! We can still use the fire place.
You on one side and bob on the other.
I don't think it's such a good idea to have a patient on with me.
- It is !
- It is ?
Yeah ! It's a great idea !
The the better way to show the effectiveness of your book,
is to have a patient on with you!
I think it's a fireplace shot.
Can I speak to you outside for just one second ?
Thank you so much.
I worked very hard to be where I am, you understand me ?
- Screwing alone, yes.
- I don't want you on the show with me, do you understand ?
- I think I do.
- I'll make up some excuse.
Dr Marvin, Bob can we have you for a minute in please ?
- I can't Dr Marvin doesn't want ...
- Eh eh eh ! No ! Get in there !
They're waiting for us !
Right this way.
In ...
Three
Two
One
We're back and we're now going to our live style reporter
Mary Grady and the Lake Winnipesaukee New Hampshire
And Mary what is so special about Lake Winnipesaukee ?
Well Jone, among other things,
it's the summer home of Dr Leo Marvin.
Author of the newest sensational therapy in Baby Steps.
And with Dr Marvin is Bob Willey
who is a patient and obviously a
big fan of Baby Steps Therapy.
Good Morning Dr Marvin, Bob.
- Good Morning
Now clearly, to come on national television live
with a patient, shows a remarquable amount of confidence
in your methods.
False Alarm.
Sorry.
Okay ?
Good.
Now, Dr Marvin.
Exactly how does Baby Steps work on someone like Bob ?
Well Jone, I'm very proud of Baby Steps, enormously gratified by its success,
I think the greatest challenge aside for the writing,
is finding ways to make the ideas accessible to everyone.
Hum, Bob, Tell us your impressions of Baby Steps.
I couldn't be happier about Baby Steps
I was a total disaster
and now, because of this man
this morning I'm on TV in front of
millions and millions of people
I don't even think Dr Marvin know what is going on,
he can't believe what's going on.
I'm very excited !
You know it sounds like a very intriguing process.
How long have you been a patient of Dr Marvin ?
3 or 4 days.
3/4 days ??
Book is not really ment to work that quickly !
It only worked that quickly with Boub.
Boub ?
Bob.
You can call me Boub.
No, I don't want to call you Boub.
Even if you did as an accident.
No ! I really don't want to call him Boub,
the book isn't make to work that quick.
But it did work that way !
That's the miracle !
The Miracle of Baby Steps.
It's not just this book.
It's this man.
It's the compation.
It's the dignity, the wisdom.
It's the horse sense,
of the guy.
That gets you !
He actually had me stay here last night in his jammies.
Using his tooth brush.
In his house.
And, I spent the day swmming,
sailing with his family.
Fay, Anna and Siggy, come here !
Here is the fam' !
The Marvins.
This is Fay, Anna and Siggy.
I want diving with testerday.
Doctor Marvin pushed me in,
You have a very nice family,
- Thank you.
- Thank you for coming.
Mary, you are wise,
what do I say to someone who has turned my whole life
forever and who is giving some much of time and vacation
to make me better.
What I'd really like to do is put the greatness of this man in perspective.
I think there's really only 3 names
Dr Albert Schweitzer,
Mother Trice of Calcuta probably,
and Leo Marvin.
The book is Baby Steps, the author is Dr Leo Marvin,
and we've been talking with Bob Willey
Pretty impressive stuff Bob !
Dr Marvin.
Back to you June.
Way to go Bobby !
That was wonderful Bob !
Thank you very much Mary.
We can come out after a few month and talk about your problems ?
Hum, as long as it is ok with my doctor ?
What ?
Oh !
Absolutely !
That's a very good idea !
Ok Great !
Come on dad ! We're taking a picture !
- Come on !
- Come on Dr Marvin !
- No...
You got that ...
All right.
- How long do you stay ?
- Just till labour day and then we go back to New York City.
Ok.. Big smiles everybody !
Cheeeeeeeeeeese !
Ok, bye bye.
Good Bye Mary.
Bye bye.
That was nice talking to you !
They're so nice !
You wer great Bob !
You really were !
You were incredible !
I mean dad shocked, you saved him !
Here is the one who made me happy !
- Oh Sweetie !
- Dr Leo Marvin !
Get Out...
No we won't get out ! You deserve it !
I mean , GET OUT !
GET OUT !!
Is it something I said ?
You ruined my life !
You ruined my career !
You ruined my book !
You put a perfectly peaceful house into an insame asylum !
Get out !!
- Daddy !
- What's got into you ?
It was a disaster Fay !
No it wasn't you were wonderful sweetie !
You were fine dad !
Why do you need to keep Bob out of the house ?
You think he's gone ?
He's not gone !
That's the all point !
He's never gone !!
Is this some radical new therapy ?
YOU SEE ??
We can't be expected to understant,
he's so far above us !
We're like ropes on a goodyear blim.
Are you all right ?
I want to apologies to you for that terrible outverse,
I'm trully sorry.
call it the show-business nerves.
Oh, we can all certainly understand that !
A lot of people freeze on TV dad !
Thank you.
Bob...
how do you feel about you and me having a little talk ?
Just me and you ?
I think I'dle like to spend a little time with you,
pay you back, for all the time you spent with me.
What do you say ?
Do you feel like for a little ride ?
Do I ??
- This is so sweet !
- It's really nice dad !
Look how happy he is !
Try to be home by 7.
Where we're going ?
Intensive psychotherapy.
Waow !
Okay !
Some free association from my infancy...
A beach ball
A dog
A frog
A lock
A puddle
A nuddle
A duddle
Dr Marvin to see Dr Tobski.
Dr Leo Marvin.
Err Main building Doctor, they're expecting you.
Hey, you're Bob Willey aren't you ?
- Yeah !
- I saw you on TV, you were great !
Ah !
Hello Leo ! Long time no see !
Sorry, I missed your show this morning.
Well this is the friend you called about !
Bob Willey ! I would like you to meet your new pal, Dr Tobski.
Hello Bob.
New Pal ?
What's wrong with my old pal ?
Would you show Mr Willey to his room please ?
Oh no, wait a second doctor, doctor !
You come with me don't you ?
I have compulsions, my bladder is feeling funny !
Really appreciating you're helping me on this Catherine.
I can only hold him for 24 hours Leo, without staff corraboration.
Not to worry about that !
I'm sure your entire staff will corroborate !
Thank you, Thank you very much Catherine.
- You're welcome !
- Thank you.
Ahh, you see Bob,
I will not be defeated !
I won't negociate and I won't compromise the defeat !
Cigarret Bob ?
Oh ! Sorry !
I didn't realize you wear administrate jacket !
Honey,
Catherine Tobski's on the phone.
Allo ?
What ?
No !
No !!
- Son of a bitch !
- Where's Bob ?
- Son of a bitch !!
- Where's Bob ??
Honey ! Where's Bob ?
What about Bob ?
WHAT ABOUT BOB ?
It's a female !
Do you think I'm wearing something ?
But, it reminds me my favorite poem,
which is ..
Well this is a red,
fouled as a blue,
I'm a skit as franck
and so am I.
So the psychiatrist says...
It's not the joke yet !
Wait a second ...
He draws a picture of a tree, what do you think of that one ?
He answered sex, ok, he draws the picture of a car, sex, sex
Then the doctor says, you're obssesed with sex !
And the patient says, oh ! you're the one drawing dirty pictures !
I'm giving you back your admitting form Leo,
to save you an embarassment.
- EMBARASSMENT ?
- Yeah !
Catherine ! You have been dubted, by a brilliant sociopath !
Brilliant enough to dubt my entire staff ?
I doubt that !
Look, it's perfectly natural for a patient to bind with his analyst !
If you want to be rid of him, just tell him you won't treat him anymore !
Catherine, that's easy for you to say !
The man is human crazy-glue !
You should have never let him sleep in your pijamas Leo !
I can't believe I'm hearing this !
Relax Leo !
I'm relaxed !!
Take a vacation !
I'm on vacation !!
Maybe you should check in here for a few days...
We can handle on things.
It was an interesting morning, fruitful,
but it lacks the intensity that you and I generate together.
the sparks that we get one on one
we should discut out a way to work around your schedule,
do we work afternoons ?
2 to 4 ?
3 to 5 ?
Monday, Wednesday, Friday, Saturday and Sunday ?
You think we'd rather work on mornings ?
Get Out !!
It's a combustible relationship isn't it ?
Is it just you and me ?
or it it you and everybody ?
Hoy !
Excuse me Officer ?
Can you please make sure he's home by 7 ?
Hey ! Didn't I see that guy on TV ?
Oh Damn !
Son of a Bitch !
I'm Home !
Fay !
We're all here sweetie !
SURPRISE !
HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU !
HAPPY BIRTHDAY DEAR MARVIN !
Dad, what happend ?
Dad ?
Honey, you're a mess !
Are you all right ?
Oh yeah yeah !
Just a little car trouble !
Ohhh on your birthday ...
Happy birthday Leo !
HAPPY BIRTHDAY LEO !
Sweetie, we have a great big surprise for you !
You sister Lily is here from Chicago !
Happy birthday Leo !
Lily !!
We are all here for you Dr M. !
This is your night !
DON'T TOUCH MY SISTER !
I've never seen him like this Phil...
He's been under a lot of stress Fay,
Bob, his interview which didn't go so well...
- And his birthday...
- Exactly...
Phil, do you think Leo was surprised ?
Oh I think so !
- How is he ?
- I'm leaving a prescription for PROZAC.
Excuse me Phil, but with these particular symptoms, is PROZAC the right choice ?
You think PROZAC is a mistake ?
For this kind of episode, I would says LIBERRINE is a more effective management tool.
You could be right, I'll rewrite the prescription.
Bob, why do you think Leo act to you like that ?
I don't know ! He's been tensed today,
But don't worry, no matter how long it takes, I'm gonna stay on and help the family to be the daddy !
You are such a good friend !
Leo is lucky to have you !
Thank you sweetie !
Oh, no problem !
It's been a real pleasure !
Keep me posted !
Okay !
- Bye Lily !
- Good Bye
Bye Lily !
This is so hard Bob, but...
We're not defending Leo's behaviour in anyway so...
please don't take this personnaly !
Oh no...
That how irrational the reasons, Leo is so upset at you,
We just think it would be best if you're not here when he wakes up.
Please, that's not the way I want it !
Me either.
Or me.
You want me to go ?
I'm sorry.
Really ?
Good Bye.
Later !
- Good bye Bob !
- Bye Anna !
- Take care of yourself !
- Okay , and you take care of Leo !
Just temporarly disconnected, that's all !
You know, I've got to tell you !
I've got the greatest vacation with you all !
No ! Too messy !
No ! Not painfull enough !
Yes !
He's not at the dock !
He's not downstairs !
Let's get the car ! Come on !
Maybe he went for a walk !
Allo !!!
Oh God !
Doctor Marvin !
Doctor !
Doctor Leo Marvin !
Dr Marvin !
Dr Marvin !!
Hello Bob !
What are you doing with a riffle ?
Get back ! Get back !
- What are you doing ?
- Quick ! quick !
Stand there !
Dad !
Where are you ?
Where goes the fam' ?
You'll be very quiet !
And do exactly as I say !
Turn around !
and move
- Where to ?
- Death therapy Bob !
- It's a gurantee cure.
- Wow !
You should I put my hands up ?
Yes that's good ! do that !
- Err, which way ?
- To the left !
To the left, yes !
It is so right that we have come together, isn't it right Dr Marvin ?
I know it was ment to be !
- You think so Bob ?
- Yes !
Because It's time !
And I'm ready !
But Dr Godswell didn't think I was ready...
And Dr Rosingay and Tcheski.
I was certainly not ready for Malestine or Miller.
But with you ! Finnally , I'm ready !
What do you think is the difference between the others guys and me Bob ?
Is that now I'm gonna kill you !
But if you shoot me, our therapy will be over !
I'm not gonna shoot you Bob !
I don't think I can shoot anybody !
I'm gonna blow you up !
This is called black powder Bob !
Here you go !
How much is this ?
20 pounds worth !
You understand don't you ?
That there is no other solution !
You won't go away !
- I will !
- No you won't !
You're just saying you will,
But after, if I don't kill you, you show up again.
And you make everyone in my life think you are wonderful
and I'm a schmock
I'm not a schmock Bob !
And I won't let you take my family away, just beacause you're crazy engouh to be fun !
You'll take care of Gil for me ?
Yeah don't worry ! I'll feed him until is big jelly is fat !
And then I'll eat him Bob !
You sure aren't convincing Dr M. !
This is tricky !
What ?? Oh ! It's terrible news Fay !
Well he tryied to commit suicide once before
and we should have seen this coming.
More fish anyone ?
I'm all tied up...
And tied up...
Yes ! you said it ! I'm all tied up inside !
okay !
I'm all tied up inside...
and those dirty bombs means that ...
If I don't...
Untie myself inside the emotional knots ...
I'm gonna explode !
Yeah !
Oh it's so simple !
And so brilliant !
Ok Doctor M. !
I Get it !
Baby Step.
Untie your knots !
Free !
Doctor M. !
Doctor Marvin ! Doctor Marvin !
You did It ! Leo !
On tuesday we'll eat Gil.
On Wednesday we'll eat Bob !
No no no that's going too far !
Dad ! Daddy !
Daddy you're all right ?
I'm fine ! I'm fine !
I'm fine ! thank you really for asking ! I'm fine !
Now Bob's gone.
- Yes we know...
- You do ?
How ?
I didn't ear it go off !
It's Bob !
Bob, just please ...
Dr Leo is a genius !
Your death therapy cured me, you're a genius !
What are you doing here ?
You killed me doctor !
The bags I put around your neck Bob,
Where are they ?
In the House.
Why ?
Sweetie ... our house ?
Oups...
Burn Burn Burn !
You think he can hear us talk to him ?
Can we talk to him ?
I don't know if it will help you. Try.
Come on sweetie.
Leo !
Sweetie !
Can you hear me ?
Daddy it's me Anna !
Leo, it's me Lily, your sister !
We don't care about the house !
Come back to us !
The worst is over !
Yeah dad ! How much worst can it get ?
Do you Bob Willey take Lily Marvin, to be your loveful wife, loves honor and cherrish her
until death do you part ?
I do.
Do you Lily Marvin take Bob Willy o be your loveful husband, loves honor and cherrish her
until death do you part ?
I do !
If anyone here, knows any reason why these two
should not be joined together in the holly matrimony
Speak now or forever hold your peace.
Then by the power invested in me...
by the state of New York, I pronounce you Husband and Wife.
No!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
Dad's Back !
Daddy !
Honey !