'More rain tomorrow
with the chance of thunderstorms... '
Mikey, quit playing,
get ready for school.
Come on, start eating.
Your mom's coming in ten minutes.
- Hey, were you messing with this?
- No.
No! Bet you were.
I bet you were fooling around.
- I'll get it.
- All right.
Hello.
Hi, Jane.
- Mikey, you want more juice?
- Sure.
- Here you go.
- Yeah, no problem.
OK. See ya.
- Jane can't make it.
- Why not?
- She didn't say.
- Didn't say what?
- Your mom can't pick you up.
- Does that mean I miss school?
No! It means I take you instead.
Nice try, tiger.
It was a nice try, though.
- Where you going, baby?
- My publishers.
They're gonna show me the cover.
Wow. You look great.
You look really great.
You look really, really great.
No, John, we're late already.
And you have toothpaste on your mouth.
Right there.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
- Well, I might be...
more than OK.
Oh, my God in heaven.
Yes! Yes, yes!
This could be wrong. I'll do another one.
- Let's tell Mike he's getting a brother.
- Wait.
I'll do another test and then see the doctor.
Congratulations, honey.
Lunch bag.
Suit bag.
Kiss.
All right. See you in a couple of days.
Say hi to your mom.
And you, take it easy.
I know.
Hey!
Bye. I love you.
See you later. Don't worry.
- Hi, Kelvin.
- How you doing?
- Mr. Rivers.
- Hey.
Frank asked if you'd call
as soon as you're in.
Oh. Sure.
Wow.
- Wow what?
- You. You're smiling.
Is that a big deal that I'm smiling?
- It is on a Monday morning, yeah.
- Really?
- Really.
- OK.
- Yeah.
- Hey, Karen,
order me a bouquet of flowers
for the end of the day, lilies.
And champa... No, not champagne,
get me chocolates.
Those Belgian kind.
You know? What are you looking at?
Something's up.
- Something's really up.
- Would you just...?
- I'm going.
- Thank you.
- But I know something's up.
- Frank.
Hey, babe, are you home?
'You have one message.
'Message received Monday 16th, 6:07 pm. '
'Hey, honey, it's me.
So Julie's having trouble with Ben, again. '
- What's new?
- 'So I said I'd have a drink with her.
'Don't worry, I'll stick to water,
and I'll call when I'm on my way home.
'Did you see the demo cover?
What do you think?
'I was kind of thinking... '
'No messages. '
'Hi, it's Anna. Leave a message
after the beep and I will call you back. '
Hi, it's me, it's a little before midnight.
I guess you're still with Julie.
Give me a call, let me know.
All right? Love you, bye.
'Hi, it's Julie. Leave a message. '
Julie, hi, it's John. Do me a favor.
When you get this message,
have Anna give me a call.
I guess you guys are having a good time.
Thank you.
'... victim of a tragic accident.
'Police have discovered
the heel of a woman's shoe
'close to her abandoned car
on Argyle Avenue.
'She may have slipped into the river
while attending to a flat tire.
'Although divers are still searching the area,
'reported sightings of the best-selling author
'continue to reach police
from towns up to 20 miles away.
'Police are keeping an open mind
as to her whereabouts.
'Anna Rivers' latest novel The Eternal Wait
is scheduled for release this fall
'and her husband,
architect Jonathan Rivers,
'is said to be taking time out
to accompany her on her promotional tour. '
- We're gonna get going.
- OK.
Come on, Michael.
- Mark'll be home in a minute, so...
- OK. OK.
- Come on, pal, say goodbye to your dad.
- Come here.
Be a good boy.
Take care of your mom. Go get your stuff.
Hey, there's a bed at our place if you want it.
Oh, thanks. Jane,
you don't have to put yourself out for me.
I know I wasn't a very good...
OK.
'It's ten days now since international
author Anna Rivers' car was found... '
'Although police still suspect
she could have drowned,
'they are not ruling out
the possibility of abduction.
'Architect husband Jonathan Rivers
spoke of his anguish today... '
'Three weeks since
the disappearance of author Anna Rivers... '
'Police say they are constructing
a profile of a likely abductor. '
'Distraught husband, Jonathan Rivers... '
'... had this message for anyone
who may know of her whereabouts. '
'It's, er, difficult.
'But you never give up hope, ever.
'Lt's the only way to get by. '
I got 50 guys and thousands of dollars'
worth of equipment waiting,
so if you want to tell them
to wait a month, call me.
- My goodness.
- You were outside my house.
- I'm sorry.
- You were outside my house
and now you're outside my office.
Don't insult my intelligence
by telling me that's a coincidence.
No, it's no coincidence.
Do I know you?
My name is Raymond Price.
- Are you following me?
- It's about Anna, Mr. Rivers.
I've been receiving messages from her,
from the other side.
From what other side?
Jonathan...
your wife is dead.
I have proof. She's been trying to communicate
ever since the moment of her death.
Look, Mr. Rivers,
my son died when he was 12.
- For years I've been suicidal.
- Look. Just stay away from me.
But then someone told me
what I have told you.
That my son, my dead son,
had made contact.
And he had, Mr. Rivers, it was true.
From the other side.
And he was happy. Happy.
Please. Yes. And also at ease.
And it changed my life, Mr. Rivers,
because then, then I knew.
So please, please, Mr. Rivers,
put this in a drawer, hide it, forget about it,
but please don't throw it away.
Because, one day...
you will want to know.
My thoughts are with you both.
'It's Anna Rivers.
'The fabulous Anna Rivers
carrying groceries. '
- 'Stop it. '
- 'How was shopping? '
- 'Turn it off. '
- 'OK. Just...
- 'There's one of her best features. '
- 'Shut up. '
'That's a beautiful thing,
ladies and gentlemen. '
'The body of internationally renowned
author Anna Rivers
'was discovered last night
by a security guard making a routine visit... '
'... to the disused pier 16,
three miles upriver
'from where her car was found abandoned
'five weeks ago on Argyle Avenue.
'The discovery brings to an end... '
'Before she drowned,
'your wife sustained injuries consistent
with a fall onto the rocks by the river.
'The damage to the head,
the break to the arm.
'When the tide came in, she would have been
unable to help herself.
'She would have been swept upstream
several miles.
'I'm so sorry for your loss. '
'Divers recovered
her personal effects.
'Her cell phone was in her car,
and we're returning it to you. '
...giving her to us, her family and friends,
to know and to love as a companion
on our earthly pilgrimage.
Give us faith to see in death
the gate of eternal life,
so that in quiet confidence
we may continue our course on earth
until, by Your call, we are reunited
with those who have gone before.
- Amen.
- So, what do you think?
- I love it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. It's nice here.
- All right.
- It's a fresh start.
I guess.
Could you...
Could you take Mikey for the weekend?
Yeah, of course.
Maybe... maybe a little longer.
As long as you want, John.
We're gonna go lay the floor now.
- When are you gonna bring them?
- They'd like to see you this week.
Sure. Fine, it shouldn't be any problem.
Whoops.
You brought me here
just to do that, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
Let me see what I can do here.
This is where you tell me
you're running over budget, right?
Shit. Keep doing that!
I'm sorry, I didn't...
Ask them if they have a light.
- You guys OK?
- We are now.
Yeah.
I trust you'll fix this
before Mr. Cunningham arrives.
Anna?
'Jonathan. '
'You have one message.
'Message received Wednesday 23rd,
'2:30am. '
'Jonathan. '
'End of message. You have no messages. '
'You have no messages.
'You have no messages. '
Oh! Please, come. How nice.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Look, er...
- I was just about to finish with someone.
- I can come back.
- No, it won't take long.
I'm really glad to see you.
I was hoping that you'd come.
- Thank you.
- This is Sarah Tate.
Let me introduce you to Mr. Rivers.
Sorry, I'm a little...
We've had a breakthrough today.
It's incredible.
It truly is.
- This is ridiculous.
- Stay awhile.
I should get these boxes back to the store.
Sarah, there's no need to hurry.
Make yourself a cup of tea.
I suppose. Thank you.
Would you like one?
Yeah, that'd be great. Thank you.
Thank you.
Mr. Rivers, please.
Oh, er... Excuse me. Please, sit here. Sit.
So, have you heard of E.V.P., Mr. Rivers?
No.
I'm not surprised.
Those that have call us cranks.
E.V.P. Stands for
electronic voice phenomenon.
- I'm listening.
- Well.
I'm not a clairvoyant, I'm not a medium,
I don't contact the dead,
the dead contact me.
And, with E.V.P.,
I can hear them,
I can see them, and...
I can record them.
'... I understand... '
'... you shouldn't be... '
- And they are...
- That's right.
People that have passed over.
Is this your job, or a hobby, or what?
I think obsession
would be more appropriate, to be honest.
Now, I wonder where... Ah!
Here we are. They don't always appear visually
the first few times.
We tend only to pick up their voices
and people can find that frustrating.
But when it works,
and you see the faces of the people
that you're able to help, like Sarah,
nothing, believe me, nothing comes close.
Mr. Rivers, do you want to hear your wife?
Yes.
'Jonathan.
'Find him.
'Jonathan Rivers.
'Jonathan... Jonathan...
'Rivers...
'Find him, please. '
The frustrating thing about E.V.P.
Is it's not live.
You need to make the recording
and you'll only know
if you've got results when you play it back.
Here. It has milk.
- Perfect. Thank you.
- Excuse me for a moment.
It's an amazing feeling, isn't it?
Er...
It's indescribable.
It took me a few visits to get used to it
but it's addictive.
I'm here all the time. He's really helped me.
I try to help him when I can,
so I keep some of this stuff at the store.
- What store?
- I have a bookstore.
Your wife was a wonderful writer, Mr. Rivers.
Yeah.
- So what made you come here?
- My fiancé.
He died eight months ago. We've had trouble
deciphering what he's been saying
but this afternoon we cracked it.
Only two words - "Sarah, yes. "
Because, before he died, he promised me
that if it was like they say it is
that he would find a way of getting to me
and letting me know that he's happy.
So, "Sarah, yes. "
Oh.
Raymond thinks we probably won't
see him again now but that's OK.
And I've heard what I wanted to hear.
Anna...
this is John.
If there's any way you can hear me...
will you please let me know?
Please.
Just any kind of... Just any kind of sign.
'Susie. '
'Susie, I... '
I recorded this a few hours ago.
It's quite faint, so I had to save it as a sound
file on the computer to enhance the sound.
So, um...
- she knows that I visited?
- I believe so.
- So will I get to see her this time?
- No.
This will just be sound. I'm sorry, John,
we have to be a little patient.
Trust me, John,
this is just the beginning. Sit, here.
Now...
If you want to hear it again,
just press that key.
I'll be back in a moment.
'Tell him... because I love him. '
'Bastard. Bastard. '
'Bastard. '
What was that?
It's OK, it's OK.
We do have some very bad people out there.
You just have to press that...
and they're all gone.
We've had a step towards visual contact
with Anna. Let's celebrate that.
Here.
They can't all be nice,
they can't all be Anna.
'Susie Tomlinson... smile. '
'Susie Tomlinson... sm... '
Hello.
- 'Lt's Raymond. Something's happening. '
- Really?
- 'Get over here. '
- I'm on my way.
Hello?
Raymond?
So you'll tell me whatever you find out?
I can't tell you any more
than you'll read in the papers.
Yeah, thanks.
Thank you for coming to the service.
It would've meant a lot to him.
Oh. Thank you for doing this for me.
I'm not sure where to start.
He was working off a disk, so...
Maybe Anna's original tapes
might be in one of these boxes.
You all right?
I still can't believe he's gone.
Well...
- Maybe he'll be in touch.
- I don't know.
Said he'd made enough of a nuisance
of himself when he was alive.
Just doesn't make any sense.
He was helping people.
Wow.
- These go back years.
- 23, to be precise.
"Carol should know. "
"Tell Thomas he should. "
"Men in the room. "
Oh, here's one - "500 dollars still there. "
- That's the kind of message I like.
- Yeah.
There we go.
Why do we got so many?
So you can watch your favorite show
and I can watch my favorite show.
Yeah.
OK... Um...
They're showing me something.
It's...
It's, uh...
Willow Avenue.
They're showing me Willow Avenue. Yes?
No. No. No.
Oh. OK.
It's no problem. Sometimes it happens.
Your wife, she passed over recently.
Yeah.
Her passing was difficult.
She was, um...
She's a writer. She was a writer.
Yeah, her words are important.
Oh...
I'm sorry, the light is way too bright.
It's... it's like these tiny, noisy, little pinpoints.
It's making it hard to see anything at all.
Can you...
- It's electronic voice...
- I know what this is.
- I've been making tapes...
- You shouldn't.
You shouldn't try this by yourself,
it's not safe.
It's like homemade Ouija boards
and teenage séances at Halloween.
E.V.P. Is not good.
We spend years developing
our relationships with our guides
so that we can protect you.
- From what?
- From the ones who like damage.
Cos they are out there and they will find you.
If you're gonna
keep insisting on meddling, then...
Anna, my wife, she sent me a sign.
No. No. Not Anna.
You are misreading everything.
Listen, it is one thing to contact the dead,
it is another to meddle,
and you are meddling.
- I just came cos I wanted some help.
- I know, I can help you.
It's just that they are urging me
to tell you to stop.
Right. Thank you.
Mr. Rivers...
Willow Avenue. Are you sure?
They keep showing me Willow Avenue.
No.
No Willow Avenue,
no Willow Street, no Willow Terrace.
Mr. Rivers. She was pregnant. Yes?
'We play every day. '
'He says you are happier now. '
'Did I die? '
'Susie.
'Susie Tomlinson...
'smile.
'Susie Tomlinson.
'Smile'