A case in point in anger's
ability to change us
is my mother.
My mother was always
the nicest person I ever knew.
She was the nicest, sweetest woman
than anyone who knew her ever knew.
Then things changed...
then she changed.
She got angry.
Good and angry.
Anger has turned my mother
into a very sad and bitter woman.
If she wasn't my mother,
I'd slap her.
I would.
I'd look her straight in the face and
tell her what I really think of her...
and then I'd run really fast
in the opposite direction.
- Are you eating?
- Yes.
I want you eating.
I mean it.
Okay.
You ladies
are old enough now,
I'm not gonna pull
any punches here.
He took his wallet...
and he left.
When he didn't come home
the other night,
you know,
I thought we got lucky
and he was just
in a car crash,
dead by the side of the road,
but the fact is,
he's run off with his little Swedish
secretary, who, oh, what a coincidence,
mysteriously left work three days ago
and moved back to Sweden!
But where did he go?
Have you spoken to him?
No, I haven't
spoken to him.
There is
very little to say.
He knows that. But I did cut off
all his goddamn credit cards.
Closed his checking
account, yeah.
See how long she sticks
around when he's broke.
Your father is a...
small man.
Very small.
I hope that's not an allusion
to the man's genitals
- 'cause that'd just be gross.
- Aw, dude,
- I was about to eat a string bean.
- Oh, my god...
Excuse me, excuse me.
Everything is not a joke.
I am talking.
And as
a jittery nation worries
about a counterstrike, we'll go to the
scene of the anthrax scare in Florida.
Sheesh.
Hey. Hey, Terry.
What do you want?
Well, I-I...
I wanted to talk
to you and Grey
about them building that
subdivision back there?
- Yeah?
- He's so, um...
He's so damned set
against it,
he hasn't even heard
the proposal.
Grey doesn't
live here anymore, Denny.
He doesn't exist.
Go away.
Officials tell us
that they are worried
about how to manage the fragile US-led
coalition in the days ahead,
but the facts
are already evident
from south Asia, to Africa,
to the Middle East.
Worldwide, thousands
of angry demonstrators
are taking to the streets
to protest US military...
The least he could have done
was taken this stupid jock with him.
There have been plenty
of protests in the world.
And I suspect...
Ugh.
What... what...
what do you mean,
"He doesn't exist"?
Oh.
Are you stoned?
- Yeah.
- Oh... Jesus.
What do you...
what do you mean,
"He... he doesn't exist"?
He's been messing around
with his assistant.
Go talk about it
on the radio.
No, I'm... I'm...
no, I'm-I'm... I'm-I'm be...
I'm being serious.
I need... I need to talk to him.
Um...
He left me.
- He left you?
- Mm. For Danken Shane
or whatever his
secretary's name is,
so Denny you can go ahead
and build your...
damn subdivision
back there...
I don't know,
whatever it is you want.
It was him who had
the problem with it, not me, okay?
- He left you?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hey, I'm sorry,
Terry.
You know, go ahead and build
your houses back there, Denny.
- He's gone. He won't stop...
- They're not my houses.
They're not.
I'm just, um...
I'm just the front man,
you know,
wave the
World Series ring.
They get the sales,
I'm getting a free lot out of it.
Ooh, a free lot.
- Hmm.
- It's something Shep set up.
He really left?
Really?
This is... true?
Yeah.
Hey, come on.
Just go away.
Hey. Well... ah... look,
let me come in.
Come on, if yo...
if you don't want,
I won't talk. I'll just sit there
and I'll drink with you.
There was a large mob...
of angry demonstrators
here today,
proving that a number
of people are willing to go and fight.
- The feeling is that...
- I got her to school.
Thank you.
You know I'm going back
to school in the morning,
you're gonna get her
yourself tomorrow.
Billy Edwards on my bus says
that when you get really drunk,
you get friendly and you sign baseballs
without bitching about it.
- He does?
- Yeah.
So, you got any
baseballs around?
No.
Why don't you run
down the street to my house.
I got a...
stack of boxes in my garage.
There's a key under my mat.
You grab one of those boxes.
You bring it back here.
One box.
Anything she makes...
I'm gonna split with her.
Buddy, Goddamn you!
Out!
What's the big deal? He wasn't licking
it more than three seconds.
The three second thing is for floors,
not dogs' mouths.
He spends all day
licking other dogs' asses.
Oh, let's just call
for take-out.
It's fine. You guys, it's good chicken.
It's fine.
Like you'd eat it?
You know the Zilwaukees'
Great Dane, "Mo'fo?"
You're licking
his asshole right now.
You know what,
that's really sick.
How's dinner coming?
Good.
We made your favorite.
- Chicken.
- Thank you.
Um, can you make an extra plate?
Denny's staying for dinner.
That was quick.
What was quick?
Denny?!
Please...
Give me more credit than that, Hadley.
He's a drunk.
You make a nice couple.
My life is falling apart
at this moment.
I expect some compassion
from you.
Now you go back up
to school tomorrow,
come back home
at Christmas break
and bust my hump
if you want to,
but right this minute, I want
the benefit of the doubt at every turn!
Are we clear?
Yes.
Thank you.
Mm, this looks good.
What kind of a dick-head
runs away
with his secretary?
That is lame.
Take a right,
make a left
at pathetic.
I think he's coming
back home.
Maybe not soon,
but... I do.
I think we should
call him.
And say what?
"Hey Dad, how's your
new life going so far?
I got an A
in interpretive dance."
He doesn't care about you, Emily.
Get real.
He lost his job, Hadley.
- What?
- Your father was about to be laid off.
He was told
a few months ago.
He was devastated.
He didn't want you girls to know it.
Okay? I think he
flipped out or something.
I read this article
on the internet.
Apparently, it's common.
They lose their jobs,
and they go nuts.
What do you want
from me?
It's the best
that I can come up with.
I don't want
anything from you.
Well, don't take it out on me, Hadley.
You aren't gonna have to be here.
You aren't gonna know
how empty this house is gonna be.
Well, if it makes you feel
any better, I hate him too.
Oh, does that mean
you hate me?
You are such a mental.
I have to go, okay?
All right.
I'll see you later,
okay?
Terry.
Hey.
Listen to my show
today, okay?
I'll mention you.
I'm gonna bring you up
as a drinking buddy
- I watched the invasion with.
- I don't want you to do that, Denny.
I know, but...
you don't have a choice.
Yeah, I do. I don't want to be
mentioned on the radio.
You don't want
to be mentioned?
- # She cried more, more, more! #
- No.
#With a rebel yell #
- # She cried more, more, more! #
- Okay.
Oh God.
Hey, come on!
Slow down!
- There's children playing here!
- Sorry, sorry, sorry!
- Sorry!
And now, once again,
Detroit's own legendary
Denny Davies.
Okay, it's the Denny Davies show.
And if you're
a regular listener,
and you've just tuned in, you know
that you haven't missed much.
And you know that's the beauty
of the show, right, Shep?
You can always just
jump right in here with us
- because...
- Because nothing ever happens.
Nothing ever
happens, exactly
Now what were we talking about
just before the commercial?
Oh yeah.
The invasion, right?
- See?
- Right?
- You still do have your memory.
- Yeah.
I know what people are saying.
Were you watching TV?
As a matter of fact,
I was watching it
with my drinking buddy
the very sweet,
the very tall
and absolutely sexy
Terry Ann Wolfmeyer.
But you...
but you know what?
- What?
- She doesn't want me to talk about her,
so I'm not gonna do it.
I'm not gonna talk about her.
Not gonna talk
about who?
- Terry Ann Wolfmeyer.
I get it. We're not even mentioning
Terry Ann Wolfmeyer's name.
- Nope.
- Is that the game that you're playing?
- Not even gonna bring her up.
- Terry Ann Wolfmeyer.
- You're getting no play.
- On 101 WRIF Detroit.
You're listening
to the Denny Davies show.
What I don't get, is how come
you won't talk about baseball?
With all they pay you every year,
what's with you not talking about base...
Hey, guess what,
guess what, pinhead?
They don't pay me
that much.
He just got flushed.
Okay, that's...
that's it for me folks,
the Poobah's up next,
Big Daddy Arthur P.
But I'll be with you tomorrow,
and you can all call in
give me hell, the radio equivalent
of dunking the clown...
into the water.
WRIF Detroit at 5:00...
That wasn't too bad,
was it, Shep?
Wasn't too... vicious?
No, you were mild today. You probably
only lost about 6 or 7,000 listeners.
You should feel really good
about yourself.
- WRIF or email the Poobah
at Arthur P...
Hey, but what was
all that about?
- All what?
- That whole thing about the woman
you watched the invasion
with? Who's she?
Just a girl.
Yeah, she's one
of the 20-year-olds, isn't she?
From the college thing.
The one I got you.
No.
No, she's not 20.
She's nowhere near 20.
In fact, look,
don't superimpose
your warped thinking
onto my life, okay?
I got enough problems.
Okay, well,
then while we're at it,
don't knock
my dating habits, okay?
'Cause they keep me young.
I happen to be a walking encyclopedia
of every boy-band that ever existed.
Trust me, you don't get that from dating
Arianna Huffington.
Did you, uh, find out about that, uh,
mall opening in Toledo?
- What it's price was?
- Yeah, $10,000.
$10,000 for you
to show up
for one-half an hour.
- You know, it must suck for you...
- You're going.
...not, uh, being me.
- Yeah, almost as much as it must suck
- actually being you.
- And now, your Rock 'n' Roll
- radio chaperone of Detroit...
- Go home.
Seriously. I've got a real
disc jockey to produce.
A die-hard drinking fan
with a serious football problem.
My impression of you
in about 15 minutes.
...WRIF Detroit.
That was said with love.
Where's Mom?
She's upstairs
taking a shower.
What are you working on?
What are you looking
in the want-ads for?
A job.
I need to work.
I'm not going to college.
Okay.
It's okay with me,
I guess.
Thank you.
- What are you gonna do?
- I want to be a reporter.
- A newscaster.
- Well, you have the face for it.
Oh. Are you staying
for dinner?
Depends.
If you're making any more
of that chicken, I am.
Here you go.
A little something
to get you into second gear.
What are you doing?
I wasn't looking,
relax.
Get out!
Jesus!
I get out, I'm taking
this drink with me.
Have you ever heard
of boundaries?
Okay, that's it.
I'm drinking them both.
Give me the drink.
I-I wasn't looking.
All right?
I, uh...
I didn't see much.
All right, well...
what are you doing here?
- What do you want?
- Well, little Emily invited me...
for dinner.
- She did?
- Yes, she did,
and I think you know
my position on free food.
Which one of you
recites Brownie?
Come on, your mother
told me once that one of you
recites Brownie,
beautifully.
Oh. Browning,
Elizabeth Barrett Browning
and I was telling you that...
um... Popeye,
a few years back
when you were like,
I don't know, nine or 10 or so.
I had her read Browning
and she used to
commit some
of the poems to memory
and recite them here
at the dinner table.
That's right.
That's what it was.
That sounds...
that sounds good.
I've never heard anything
like it before
but it...
it sounds fun.
To who?
To all of us,
if she can remember.
Popeye?
Can we do this tomorrow night
when I've had notice
and can make plans
to eat somewhere else?
I don't remember any
of them anyway.
I do.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Really?
Wow.
I'm impressed.
Good.
You should be.
What's so funny?
Nothing. Just...
You're just all...
I don't know...
very female.
I got her number in Sweden...
from Helen Trailer.
It forwards and I...
called last night.
It must've been the middle
of the night there.
It was Grey that answered.
I'm sure of it.
Yeah. I hung up
like a six-year-old.
Ah, he'll marry her.
I'd bet any money in the world.
What do you think
you'll do?
Eh, what can I do?
Well, you're set up,
right?
Right?
I mean Grey's got to be
pretty chunky
in the money department,
- plus, you have...
- I have, what?
Bills?
Responsibilities?
Four girls?
One that hates me,
two or three that are
leaning that way.
You can have your damn lots
back there, Denny.
I'm not here
for the lots.
Then leave.
Any other reason than that
for you to be here, frankly,
is just pitiful.
- Are you okay?
- No.
I'm a wreck.
She's gonna take us
to school.
You see women...
on TV, in the movies,
and they get left
or whatever.
You just wanna kick 'em,
they're so whiny.
Look at me.
I hate his guts.
I hate his guts for what he's done.
Oh.
He's a pig,
your dad.
Just a vile, selfish,
horrible pig,
but you know what?
I'm not gonna trash him
to you girls.
I'm not.
I hate him too.
I hate him so much.
I know you do, baby.
You're human.
How could you not?
#When your eyes
were open wide #
- All right. See you.
- # For the the last... #
Hey, hey, wait.
Who is that?
He's cute.
That's Gorden Reiner.
He's new.
He's from Chicago.
- Go meet him.
- Yeah.
I met him. He's not
interested in me.
All he likes to talk about
is bungee jumping.
Tell him you're
from a broken home.
- I'm serious.
- Should I?
Guys think things
like that are great.
Trust me.
I'm gonna use it.
Hi, Gorden.
Hey.
Did you know I'm
from a broken home?
Okay, bye.
Turn it down.
- Wolfmeyer residence
- Hey, beautiful.
It's Denny.
- Which one is this?
- It's Andy.
Bingo. You still
lookin' for work?
- I am.
- Well, I want you to come in tomorrow.
And see Shep Goodman
from my show.
He needs
a production assistant.
Denny, you're kidding me.
- You're amazing.
- Yeah...
well, you tell that
to your mom, we're even.
So you come in tomorrow, okay?
I'll set you two up.
Okay!
Thank you so much!
Oh my God.
I might get a job
working on Denny's show.
- Are you kidding me?
- No!
- That would be amazing!
- That would be so cool.
- Oh my God.
- What's up?
Denny just called.
She might get a job on his show.
Oh, really?
Denny just called here?
Yeah, I have an
interview tomorrow
for a job.
Wait, wait.
What about school?
I want a job.
I'm not going to college.
Wha... you're not going
to college?
No, I told Daddy and he wanted me
to wait to tell you, but now...
Oh, but now that he's off
screwing his assistant,
you think you can safely drop
the bomb on me, is that it?
No.
"No" is right.
You are going to college!
You know damn well
how I feel about this.
All four of you.
You're all goddamn going to college!
I don't have a job open.
It's that simple, Denny.
It's cut and dry.
This girl has something.
She does, Sheppy,
she's sharp.
She has class.
You could be hiring the next, um...
Diane Sawyer.
I don't have a job open.
I know you don't,
but you could do this
for me, right?
You could do this for me.
No, I can't.
Wanna know why?
- Yes, why?
- Okay, I'm gonna come in there.
I'm gonna tell you.
Hold on.
Jesus.
I'm going on
in a second here.
Because, my lord,
I'm too busy doing
other things
for you.
"My lord"?
#I'm looking for #
#A simple kind of life.
Slow and easy #
- # A life that won't #
- Hi.
- # Bring me down #
- Um, I'm Andy Wolfmeyer,
I'm here to see
Shep Goodman about a job.
Um... Denny Davies
asked me to come in.
Oh, okay. Well, if you'd like
to take a seat over there.
- I'll let him know you're here.
- Okay, thank you.
No, you're not
understanding me,
- You're making this really...
- I found one!
I've got an opening.
Something's come up.
I found an opening.
- I'm on the phone.
- Okay.
If you want her to have
the job, I'll make it happen.
You'll just owe me, as usual.
I got the job.
What job?
With Denny, as a
production assistant.
Yes, what?
Are you looking
to get laid?
Is... is this
what's going on?
I mean, are-are you
looking for
another notch in your belt,
or... I don't know...
whatever it is you super
sports heroes call it.
I mean are you
looking to get lucky with me...
- to get me into bed?
- Uh, who's calling?
Be straight with me, Denny.
Be straight. Now, Grey always thought
you had an eye for me,
and I need you to be
really straight with me now.
Uh, okay. Um...
I do like you.
I always have.
Um...
You wanna have sex with me.
Is that it?
No! Uh, no, I mean...
um... well, uh...
yeah, if you're offering,
I guess.
Okay then.
I'll be right there.
Give me 10 minutes.
- Uh, ex... excuse me?
- Give me 10 minutes.
I'm not gonna do much with my face,
though, so don't expect much.
In fact,
keep the drapes shut.
I don't like a lot of light.
It's not very light in there, is it?
No, there, uh...
there's not a lot
of light here.
Okay, well,
have a drink.
Have a couple.
I don't want you to have
a real clear memory of this
when it's over, okay?
I'll see you soon.
Slow down!
- Slow down!
- Oh, please. Come on.
- There's children playing here!
- Ah, get over yourself!
There's children
playing here!
Hello?
I'm here!
Uh, Denny?
Denny?
I'm coming up!
Hello?
It's me.
Listen, um,
something came up.
I had a, uh...
I had a call.
They needed me right away
over at the station.
- Shep's in some kind of trouble.
- Oh, yeah.
- You are so full of shit.
- I'm not.
- No, I'm not.
- Yes, you are.
I'm not and...
in fact, I'd like
a rain check.
It's not gonna happen.
This was like...
Halley's Comet.
It's not coming around
again for 57 years.
What the fuck
is Halley's Comet?
But this is the main
production booth
This is where you and I will be
doing a lot of working.
- Okay.
- Here, come on, I'll show you this.
This is the live
on-air studio. Arthur?
Say hello to my new
assistant Andy Wolfmeyer.
- Hello, Andy.
- This is Arthur Pennhallow.
- He's a big deal here in town.
- Yeah.
We're friends.
He idolizes me, actually.
The fuck I do.
- He does.
- Okay.
That was a joke. We're tight,
and we're good friends.
Okay.
So what is "Andy" short for?
"Andrea?"
- Yeah, "Andrea."
- Cool. See? I'm good with names.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll show you
up at the office now,
- where we work a lot up there, too.
- Okay.
Have you seen
an Emmy in person?
- You've won an Emmy?
- Couple.
Local, but who's counting?
Actually, I have three.
There's only two up there, 'cause one
I keep for the hotel room when I travel.
Wow.
Kids, hurry up!
You're gonna be late!
- How's your lunch, Gordon?
- It's good.
Did you ever see that documentary
on the Chicago Seven?
What about the one...
the one about
the Kent State killings?
- No.
- Something like...
six people were killed
by the cops,
there was
all this turmoil
and it got really ugly and just opened
up a lot of old wounds
between the police
and the people
of the area.
I'm from
a broken home also.
You are?
Hey, do you bungee jump?
- No.
- Well, I do.
I go up with my dad.
We drive up north
to Fenton Valley...
- and bungee jump off this huge crane.
- That sounds exciting.
Well, I read your letter.
Was it too mean?
I don't want it
to be mean.
Well, I mean I do,
but I don't.
Well, he's your father
and he's...
left you
at a very tough time.
I know and I want him to know
that it pisses me off he hasn't called.
Oh, he knows.
He's not talking to his brother
or his friends at work.
He knows what he's done.
Are you gonna call him?
Please?
This is stupid.
It's just a stupid game.
You said you have
his number.
This letter is good.
I mean, it's good for you
to get your feelings out.
Um...
I want you eating,
though.
You are dancing so much.
Do you think maybe
it's too much?
I know you have this out here.
Daddy built it for you,
- but you spend so much time out here.
- You're such a head case.
- What?
- Be happy for me.
Be proud! Shit!
You know? I'm focused!
What is your problem?
The only thing you're focused
on is drinking and Denny!
Be glad that I have
a dream!
I was just going to tell
you how proud I am of you.
That's the sad thing.
What?
Well,
I'm not going to now.
Not after that outburst.
Fine, I don't care.
I'm in the kitchen
making dinner,
and it wouldn't kill you
to come up and help.
Who knows? You may
get there just in time
to pull my head out
of the oven.
- Hello?
- What... what are you doing?
- Oh, making the girls' lunches.
- Good for you.
Yeah, what the hell. I'm going after
the Mother-of-the-year award.
See, um...
- You know what I was thinking?
- No.
Maybe it's been...
57 years.
- What are you talking about?
- Halley's Comet, you know?
By the way, it's, uh...
76 years, but I'll give you
that one, smarty pants.
Can I come over?
When?
Now.
- Now?
- Yeah, now.
- Did you hang up?
- Uh, not yet.
Good, then, um...
I'm coming over.
I am, so...
don't go hide
in the yard,
don't pull any
reciprocal crap.
Is that what you did that day?
You hid in the yard?
No, um...
You know what?
Delete that last line.
Look, um...
I'm coming over.
I am.
I'm coming now.
Hold it.
#Hold it! #
Wait, wait, wait.
- What is this?
- Your lunches.
- Our lunches?
- Mm-hmm.
- Are you kidding?
- I make my own lunch.
You haven't done
it in years.
I'm back to basics.
What do you want?
- Bye.
- Have a good day!
No!
Oh, shit. Great.
Were you...
you taking off?
Hey. You're taking off,
just like that?
Yeah, I'm going to hide
in your yard.
Oh, come on, that's bullshit.
I was kidding.
- What are you doing?
- Step out.
Just step out.
- Are you stoned?
- Not at all.
- Not a bit.
- Well, you should be.
Listen, I, uh...
I know that you're fresh.
I know you're good and hurt
and I know that on some level,
this is way too soon...
- and not right.
- Yeah.
What's the other level?
I dial your number
10 times a day and hang up.
Come on!
Just a minute.
Goddamn, Terry, it's not like, you know,
it's not like I'm asking a lot.
It's just...
it's just...
I get it, okay?
I know who I am
for you.
I'm this guy that you sit
and you drink...
and you talk with.
- And now you want to fuck me.
- Well, you offered it.
That was before you hid
in your yard.
Well, I'm not hiding
in my yard, now am I?!
- Hey come on, lady!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Can that horn, now!
Jeez!
Not bad.
Thank you.
You wanna...
go back to my house?
I've seen your house.
I'll make the bed!
Let's go to my house.
Fine, let's go
to your house.
Oh, God.
Now that was
a real misstep.
Aw...
that was
a sweet thing to say.
God, what am I doing?
Why am I here?
You're here because
you're sad and lonely.
Desperate.
You need someone,
something,
anything to fill you.
Any...
- port in a storm.
- Mmm.
I asked why I
was here, not you.
What's my story?
Oh, your story is...
you're good
and bent out of shape.
Pissed off like
I've never seen a woman.
What?
Francis Wellard.
Timothy Westerburg.
Matthew Wintergarden.
Hadley Wolfmeyer!
Stephanie Winnington!
Nancy Woodside.
It's a special day
for her. So, just be nice.
- She's excited for you to meet him.
- Oh, really,
how excited can she be?
She's been seeing him for three years.
And she's in love?
She's in love?
- I'm just hearing about this today?
- Be nice!
It's not in my nature.
Why does she hate me so damn much?
She doesn't hate you,
she just thinks that he's stupid.
She thinks he's stupid?!
I thought she loved him.
No, she thinks
you'll think he's stupid.
Well, I won't think that.
That's my point.
She judges me so harshly.
I am her mother.
- Okay.
- I love her. I want her to be happy.
I mean, if she loves
this guy I'm gonna love...
- Okie dokie.
- Hi! Hi! Oh, baby!
Baby!
Oh God, I'm so proud
of you! I am!
I am so proud of you.
- Let me see your face.
- Mother.
A college graduate.
I'm so proud of you.
Your father doesn't know
what he's missing today.
I think he might.
Mm-mmm!
This is it.
This is life.
Mom?
- David. Hi, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you too.
My parents are having lunch
at the Wheeler hotel.
- You're all invited.
- The Wheeler, really?
We'd... well, girls,
would you like that?
- We... we had lunch.
- Have it again.
Come on, I want us to go.
I want you to meet David's parents.
David you tell your folks
we'd absolutely love to join them, okay?
- Cool. Okay, see you later.
- See you later.
Bye.
Wow.
He is so handsome.
Nice and...
- intelligent.
- Mother.
Oh! He is, baby.
I can tell by looking at him.
He's incredibly
intelligent.
All right...
um...
there's something
you all should know.
You're pregnant
and you're getting married.
How did you know that?
Who told you that?
I guessed?
Really?
I guessed that?
I was right?
No, you've got
to be kidding me.
No, I'm... I'm not.
I'm getting married.
This is how I find out?
Through Popeye?
A 15-year-old?
- Don't be condescending...
- Close it!
You are a child.
What do you know?
Oh, that old chestnut.
You close it
as well, please.
Do his parents know?
Yes, they're ecstatic.
Oh, how long
have they been ecstatic?
You know what, can we just
go to the lunch please?
How long have they been
ecstatic, damn you, Hadley?!
I need a Bloody Mary as soon
as is humanly possible.
Hi. I'm Terry.
Oh. Gina.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- And this is David, my husband.
Oh, David Senior.
That's nice.
You're not Jews, obviously.
Oh, well I mean
not that that's a good or a bad thing.
That they don't
just name their children
after... okay,
that was horrible.
Um... these are
Hadley's sisters,
Emily, Andrea
and Popeye.
- Hi, girls.
- Hi.
Could we order you
a drink before lunch?
Oh, I'm set for now.
Thank you.
Um, I'll have the same.
Mmn. Mmn!
So, I understand we have something
to celebrate? Some good news, huh?
Oh, we're
very excited, Terry.
We are crazy about Hadley.
We really are.
I knew from the minute
I met her. I did.
- You did not.
- I did.
No, Mother, you didn't.
If she said she did,
she probably did!
Well, I was taken
for a surprise,
- but... but a happy one.
- Yeah, well, you and me both.
- Should we toast?
- Oh, yes. Let's do.
Well... to David
and Hadley.
- David and Hadley...
- Oh wait, wait, wait.
My glass is...
this is bad luck. Uh, waiter?
Mother, it's okay.
Here.
Oh.
Oh, just...
a little more.
Just...
Thank you.
So, shall we toast?
- May I?
- Please, do.
To David and Hadley.
A long and beautiful
partnership.
- Aww.
- Thanks.
The... mostly right now...
I'm sorry, David,
this is very emotional for me.
To my baby.
My first born,
my little Hadley-wadley.
Aww.
That's what we called her.
Hadley-wadley.
She was so loved
from the minute she was born.
Just an adorable
little thing.
She was... well,
she grew up too fast didn't she?
She grew up so fast
and had a mouth on her.
Mother!
When she was in her teens
she was her own little boss.
Mother!
And she would sometimes
just not come home...
All right, could we just toast, please?
Thank you.
Okay, baby.
We'll toast.
You have to
forgive me. Um...
you all had a chance
to process this,
and I'm just coming
on board, so to speak.
To Hadley-wadley.
Hadley-wadley.
Mmn.
Oh.
Oh!
Oh, no, no.
I'm done toasting.
I'm just ordering
another drink.
- It was horrible.
- Maybe it wasn't.
Maybe it wasn't
as bad as you thought.
No, it was horrible.
It was. I made an ass
of myself. I was like...
a public service film
against drinking.
Just...
yeah, I was an old lush.
Poor Hadley.
I feel so bad
for her, Denny.
Why are we going
out here?
I hate the way
I come off to my girls.
I just hate that I can't
control my emotions.
Oh God.
This is creepy.
This was all a farm
owned by the...
Firestone family
until the 50's.
This and the whole
subdivision.
It goes on a bit
about another eight acres.
Why are we out
here today?
I wanna do it.
- Out here?
- No.
Don't be an asshole.
I wanna sell
my part of it.
Just let your friends develop
the lots and tell them "Yes."
Tell them I don't need
the money, though.
If they think I need the money,
they'll play games with me.
- Do you?
- No.
Yes. No.
I don't know.
I'm in some trouble...
unless I officially
divorce the shitbox
which I refuse to do,
until at least he has
the balls to show his face.
I wanna give
the girls the money.
Just tell your friend Shep
I want to make the deal.
What?
Nothin'.
Good.
I'm going in.
This place is a clearinghouse
for Lime disease.
- Hey, this is cute.
- Shep...
- How are you, pal?
- I'm doing great.
I'm hanging with Andy,
how could I not be?
Hello, Terry.
Hadley...
Hadley's boyfriend.
Okay, okay.
- We're gonna go watch a movie.
- Isn't that sweet?
"The Bicycle Thief."
She's never seen "The Bicycle Thief."
He's a nut
for foreign cinema.
Anyone wanna join us?
Snuggle up on the couch?
Watch a classic?
I think we'll, uh,
probably pass.
Is it the subtitles?
You know me too well.
I do and it's a burden.
- I know him too well...
- Okay.
So it's a burden.
That's it.
Okay.
I cannot tell you how much
this thing disgusts me.
Oh, come on.
She's doing great at work.
Shep's got her producing
morning drive-time,
plus... I think
he really likes her.
Oh, the whole thing
just infuriates me.
That's probably half
the attraction.
What?
You know what.
Not another word.
The deep hatred that men
have felt for one another
through the ages has blossomed
into one chapter after another
of repression,
violence, hate, rape,
religious slang
and genocide.
I'm still working on it.
I need to fix the music.
It's my final
in television production.
You're really handsome,
Gorden.
Thanks.
I should go.
I really do have to go.
The power of stress
and naked anger
is seen over and over again
in the relationships
that exist between the male
and the female of our species.
Here, in rural Botswana,
an unfaithful tribeswoman
is brought to a field
by a group of locals
for a ritualized punishment
of beating and harassment.
Events quickly spiral out of control
for the tribesmen, though
as the woman's fury
becomes too great to contain
and the men are quickly forced
to flee for their safety.
Why am I not excited by it?
Um, because I don't think
any of these new age arts colleges
are really colleges.
Of course, it's a college.
What are you talking about?
Honey, I've been there.
I have.
I wanted to be a poet,
remember?
Just take arts courses
at Ann Arbor.
I don't want to go
to school in Ann Arbor.
No, of course you don't. It's what
I want you to do. Why would you?
Okay, four years learning
dance theory?
I have a theory about that.
It's not going to happen.
How's the show?
You enjoying it?
I wish you would
take me seriously.
Honey, I take you seriously.
I just don't think you have much
capacity for self-evaluation.
You know, you'd think
you'd be happy for me...
considering the way
your life turned out.
- The way your parents pushed you...
- To marry your father?