- Is everything in place?
- You weren't supposed to relieve me.
I know, but I felt like taking a shift.
You like him, don't you?
You like watching him.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- We're gonna kill him. You understand?
Morpheus believes he is the One.
- Do you?
- It doesn't matter what I believe.
You don't, do you?
- Did you hear that?
- Hear what?
Are you sure this line is clean?
Yeah, of course I'm sure.
I better go.
- Freeze! Police!
- Hands on your head!
Do it! Do it now!
- Lieutenant.
- Oh, shit.
Lieutenant, you were given
specific orders.
Hey, I'm just doing my job.
You give me that "juris-my-dick-tion"
crap, you can cram it up your ass.
The orders were for your protection.
I think we can handle one little girl.
I sent two units!
They're bringing her down now!
No, Lieutenant, your men are
already dead.
Shit.
Morpheus, the line was traced.
I don't know how.
I know. They cut the hard line.
There's no time.
Get to another exit.
- Are there any agents?
- Yes.
Goddamn it.
You have to focus, Trinity.
There's a phone at Wells and Lake.
You can make it.
- All right.
- Go.
That's impossible.
Get up, Trinity.
Just get up.
Get up.
She got out.
It doesn't matter.
The informant is real.
- We have the name of their next target.
- The name is Neo.
We'll need a search running.
It has already begun.
What?
What the hell?
"Follow the white rabbit."
Who is it?
It's Choi.
You're two hours late.
- I know. It's her fault.
- You got the money?
Two grand.
Hold on.
Hallelujah.
You're my savior, man.
My own personal Jesus Christ.
You get caught using that...
I know. This never happened.
You don't exist.
- Right.
- Something wrong, man?
You look a little whiter than usual.
My computer, it...
You ever have that feeling where you're
not sure if you're awake or still dreaming?
All the time.
It's called mescaline.
It's the only way to fly.
Hey, look, it just sounds like
you might need to unplug, man.
You know? Get some R and R?
What do you think, Dujour?
Should we take him with us?
Definitely.
No, I can't. I have work tomorrow.
Come on.
It'll be fun. I promise.
Yeah.
Sure. I'll go.
Hello, Neo.
How do you know that name?
I know a lot about you.
- Who are you?
- My name is Trinity.
Trinity.
The Trinity?
That cracked the IRS D-base?
That was a long time ago.
- Jesus.
- What?
I just thought...
...you were a guy.
- Most guys do.
That was you on my computer.
- How did you do that?
- Right now, all I can tell you...
...is that you're in danger.
- I brought you here to warn you.
- Of what?
They're watching you, Neo.
- Who is?
- Please, just listen.
I know why you're here, Neo.
I know what you've been doing.
I know why you hardly sleep...
...why you live alone, and why,
night after night...
...you sit at your computer.
You're looking for him.
I know, because I was once
looking for the same thing.
And when he found me...
...he told me I wasn't really
looking for him...
...I was looking for an answer.
It's the question that drives us, Neo.
It's the question
that brought you here.
You know the question...
...just as I did.
What is the Matrix?
The answer is out there, Neo.
It's looking for you.
And it will find you...
...if you want it to.
Shit.
Shit, shit.
You have a problem with authority,
Mr. Anderson.
You believe that you are special,
that somehow the rules do not apply to you.
Obviously, you are mistaken.
This is one of the top
software companies in the world...
...because every employee understands
they are part of a whole.
Thus, if an employee has a problem,
the company has a problem.
The time has come to make
a choice, Mr. Anderson.
Either you choose to be at your desk
on time from this day forth...
...or you choose to find yourself
another job.
Do I make myself clear?
Yes, Mr. Rhineheart.
Perfectly clear.
Thomas Anderson?
Yeah, that's me.
Great.
Have a nice day.
- Hello?
- Hello, Neo.
Do you know who this is?
- Morpheus.
- Yes.
I've been looking for you, Neo.
I don't know if you're ready to see
what I want to show you...
...but, unfortunately, you and I
have run out of time.
They're coming for you, Neo,
and I don't know what they're going to do.
Who's coming for me?
Stand up and see for yourself.
What? Right now?
Yes. Now.
Do it slowly.
The elevator.
- Oh, shit!
- Yes.
- What do they want?
- I don't know.
But if you don't want to find out,
get out of there.
- How?
- I can guide you...
...but you must do exactly
as I say.
- Okay.
- The cubicle across from you is empty.
- But what if they...?
- Go. Now.
Stay here for just a moment.
When I tell you,
go to the end of the row...
...to the office
at the end of the hall.
Stay as low as you can.
Go. Now.
Good. Now, outside
there is a scaffold.
- How do you know all this?
- We don't have time.
To your left there's a window.
Go to it.
Open it.
Use the scaffold to get
to the roof.
No way! No way!
This is crazy!
There are two ways
out of this building.
One is that scaffold.
The other is in their custody.
You take a chance either way.
I leave it to you.
This is insane!
Why is this happening to me?
What'd I do?
I'm nobody.
I didn't do anything.
I'm gonna die.
Shit!
Oh, shit!
I can't do this.
Shit.
As you can see, we've had our eye
on you for some time now, Mr. Anderson.
It seems that you've been living...
...two lives.
In one life,
you're Thomas A. Anderson...
...program writer for a respectable
software company.
You have a social security number.
You pay your taxes.
And you...
...help your landlady
carry out her garbage.
The other life is lived in computers...
...where you go by
the hacker alias "Neo"...
...and are guilty of virtually every
computer crime we have a law for.
One of these lives...
...has a future.
And one of them does not.
I'm going to be as forthcoming
as I can be, Mr. Anderson.
You're here...
...because we need your help.
We know that you've been contacted
by a certain...
...individual.
A man who calls himself "Morpheus."
Whatever you think you know
about this man is irrelevant.
He is considered by many authorities...
...to be the most dangerous man alive.
My colleagues...
...believe that I am wasting
my time with you.
But I believe you wish
to do the right thing.
We're willing to wipe the slate clean...
...give you a fresh start.
All that we're asking in return
is your cooperation...
...in bringing
a known terrorist to justice.
Yeah.
Well, that sounds like a really good deal.
But I think I got a better one.
How about...
...I give you the finger...
...and you give me my phone call.
Mr. Anderson...
...you disappoint me.
You can't scare me
with this gestapo crap.
I know my rights.
I want my phone call.
Tell me, Mr. Anderson...
...what good is a phone call
if you're unable to speak?
You're going to help us,
Mr. Anderson...
...whether you want to or not.
This line is tapped,
so I must be brief.
They got to you first, but they've
underestimated how important you are.
If they knew what I know...
...you would probably be dead.
What are you talking about?
What is happening to me?
You are the One, Neo. You see,
you may have spent the last few years...
...looking for me, but I've spent
my entire life...
...looking for you.
Now, do you still want to meet?
- Yes.
- Then go to the Adams Street bridge.
Get in.
- What the hell is this?
- It's necessary, Neo.
- For our protection.
- From what?
From you.
- Take off your shirt.
- What?
Stop the car.
Listen to me, coppertop.
We don't have time for 20 Questions.
Right now, there's only one rule:
Our way...
...or the highway.
Fine.
Please, Neo, you have to trust me.
- Why?
- Because you have been down there, Neo.
You know that road.
You know exactly where it ends.
And I know that's
not where you want to be.
Apoc, lights.
Lie back.
Lift up your shirt.
- What is that thing?
- We think you're bugged.
Try and relax.
Come on.
It's on the move.
Come on, you shit.
- You're gonna lose it.
- No, I'm not.
Clear!
Jesus Christ! That thing is real?!
This is it.
Let me give you one piece of advice.
Be honest.
He knows more than you can imagine.
At last.
Welcome, Neo.
As you no doubt have guessed...
...I am Morpheus.
It's an honor to meet you.
No...
...the honor is mine.
Please, come. Sit.
I imagine...
...that right now you're feeling
a bit like Alice.
Tumbling down the rabbit hole?
You could say that.
I can see it in your eyes.
You have the look of a man
who accepts what he sees...
...because he's expecting to wake up.
Ironically, this is not
far from the truth.
Do you believe in fate, Neo?
- No.
- Why not?
Because I don't like the idea that
I'm not in control of my life.
I know exactly what you mean.
Let me tell you why you're here.
You're here because you know something.
What you know, you can't explain.
But you feel it.
You felt it your entire life:
There's something wrong with the world.
You don't know what, but it's there.
Like a splinter in your mind...
...driving you mad.
It is this feeling
that has brought you to me.
Do you know what
I'm talking about?
The Matrix?
Do you want to know...
...what it is?
The Matrix is everywhere.
It is all around us.
Even now, in this very room.
You can see it when you
look out your window...
...or when you turn on your television.
You can feel it when you go to work...
...when you go to church...
...when you pay your taxes.
It is the world that has been
pulled over your eyes...
...to blind you from the truth.
What truth?
That you are a slave, Neo.
Like everyone else,
you were born into bondage...
...born into a prison that you cannot
smell or taste or touch.
A prison for your mind.
Unfortunately, no one can be...
...told what the Matrix is.
You have to see it for yourself.
This is your last chance.
After this, there is no turning back.
You take the blue pill...
...the story ends, you wake up
in your bed and believe...
...whatever you want to believe.
You take the red pill...
...you stay in Wonderland...
...and I show you how deep
the rabbit hole goes.
Remember...
...all I'm offering is the truth.
Nothing more.
Follow me.
Apoc, are we online?
Almost.
Time is always against us.
Please, take a seat there.
You did all this?
The pill you took is
part of a trace program.
It disrupts your input/output carrier signals
so we can pinpoint your location.
What does that mean?
It means buckle
your seat belt, Dorothy...
...because Kansas is going bye-bye.
Did you...?
Have you ever had a dream, Neo,
that you were so sure was real?
What if you were unable
to wake from that dream?
How would you know the difference
between the dream world...
...and the real world?
- This can't be.
- Be what?
Be real?
It's going into replication.
Still nothing.
It's cold. It's cold!
Tank, we're going to need a signal soon.
I got a fibrillation.
Apoc, location.
Targeting almost there.
He's going into arrest.
- Lock. I got him!
- Now, Tank, now!
Welcome...
...to the real world.
We've done it, Trinity.
We found him.
- I hope you're right.
- I don't have to hope.
I know it.
Am I dead?
Far from it.
He still needs a lot of work.
What are you doing?
Your muscles have atrophied.
We're rebuilding them.
Why do my eyes hurt?
You've never used them before.
Rest, Neo. The answers are coming.
Morpheus, what's happened to me?
- What is this place?
- More important than "what" is "when."
- "When"?
- You believe it's the year 1999...
...when, in fact, it's closer to 2199.
I can't tell you exactly what year it is
because we honestly don't know.
There's nothing I can say
that will explain it for you.
Come with me. See for yourself.
This is my ship.
The Nebuchadnezzar.
It's a hovercraft.
This is the main deck.
This is the core...
...where we broadcast our pirate signal
and hack into the Matrix.
Most of my crew you already know.
This is Apoc...
...Switch...
...and Cypher.
- Hi.
The ones you don't know,
Tank and his big brother, Dozer.
The little one behind you is Mouse.
You wanted to know
what the Matrix is, Neo?
Trinity.
Try to relax.
This will feel a little weird.
This...
...is the Construct.
It's our loading program.
We can load anything, from clothing...
...to equipment...
...weapons...
...training simulations...
...anything we need.
Right now we're inside
a computer program?
Is it really so hard to believe?
Your clothes are different.
The plugs in your body are gone.
Your hair has changed.
Your appearance now is what we call
"residual self-image."
It is the mental projection
of your digital self.
- This isn't real?
- What is "real"?
How do you define "real"?
If you're talking about what you can feel,
what you can smell, taste and see...
...then "real" is simply electrical
signals interpreted by your brain.
This is the world that you know.
The world as it was at the end
of the 20th century.
It exists now only as part of
a neural-interactive simulation...
...that we call the Matrix.
You've been living
in a dream world, Neo.
This is the world as it exists today.
Welcome to the desert...
...of the real.
We have only bits and pieces
of information.
But what we know for certain is that
in the early 21 st century...
...all of mankind was united
in celebration.
We marveled at our own magnificence
as we gave birth to Al.
Al.
You mean artificial intelligence.
A singular consciousness that spawned
an entire race of machines.
We don't know who struck first,
us or them.
But we know that it was us
that scorched the sky.
They were dependent on solar power...
...and it was believed that
they would be unable to survive...
...without an energy source
as abundant as the sun.
Throughout human history, we have been
dependent on machines to survive.
Fate, it seems, is not
without a sense of irony.
The human body generates more
bioelectricity than a 120-volt battery.
And over 25,000 BTUs of body heat.
Combined with a form of fusion...
...the machines had found all the energy
they would ever need.
There are fields, Neo, endless fields...
...where human beings
are no longer born.
We are grown.
For the longest time,
I wouldn't believe it.
And then I saw the fields
with my own eyes...
...watched them liquefy the dead...
...so they could be fed intravenously
to the living.
And standing there,
facing the pure, horrifying precision...
...I came to realize
the obviousness of the truth.
What is the Matrix?
Control.
The Matrix is a computer-generated
dream world...
...built to keep us under control...
...in order to change a human being...
...into this.
No.
I don't believe it.
It's not possible.
I didn't say it would be easy, Neo.
- I just said it would be the truth.
- Stop!
Let me out!
Let me out! I want out!
- Easy, Neo. Easy.
- Get this thing out of me.
Get this thing out of me!
Don't touch me! Get away from me!
Stay away from me!
I don't believe it.
- I don't believe it.
- He's gonna pop.
Breathe, Neo. Just breathe.
I can't go back, can I?
No.
But if you could...
...would you really want to?
I feel I owe you an apology.
We have a rule:
We never free a mind
once it's reached a certain age.
It's dangerous.
The mind has trouble letting go.
I've seen it before, and I'm sorry.
I did what I did because...
...I had to.
When the Matrix was first built,
there was a man born inside...
...who had the ability
to change whatever he wanted...
...to remake the Matrix as he saw fit.
It was he who freed the first of us...
...taught us the truth.
As long as the Matrix exists...
...the human race will never be free.
After he died...
...the Oracle prophesied his return...
...and that his coming would hail
the destruction of the Matrix...
...end the war...
...bring freedom to our people.
That is why there are those of us who have
spent our entire lives searching the Matrix...
...looking for him.
I did what I did because...
...I believe that search is over.