Subtitulos y Modificaciones por Hosen
hosen@fibertel. com. ar
Excuse me, sir.
Yes?
I'm afraid you've come in
the wrong way.
I'm sorry...
This is the old entrance.
The visitor's centre's out
and around to the left.
Right, well...
I'll wander over then.
Well worth it.
Been through some amazing times.
(Murmurs) Yeah.
I believe that this nation
should commit itself
to achieving the goal,
before this decade is out,
of landing a man on the moon
and returning him safely
to the Earth.
SONG: # Come and see
the real thing
# Come and see the real thing
Come and see
Come and see the real thing
# Come and see
# There's a meaning there
# But the meaning there
doesn't really mean a thing
# Come and see
the real thing... #
MAN: Godspeed, John Glenn.
# Come and see
# I am the real... #
KENNEDY: We choose to
go to the moon.
We choose to go to the moon
in this decade
and do the other things,
not because they are easy,
but because they are hard.
# Trying hard to understand
but really not just seeing me
# There's a meaning there
# But the meaning there
doesn't really mean a thing... #
MAN: lgnition sequence starts.
# Come and see the real thing
Come and see
# I am the real thing... #
MAN: Tower, clear.
RADIO: 'Apollo 9', you are go...
RADIO: 'Apollo 10',
your trajectory and guidance are go.
MAN: Man is about to launch himself
on a trip to the moon.
MAN: Neil Armstrong.
Edwin 'Buzz' Aldrin.
Michael Collins.
Next stop for them - the moon.
The lunar age is about to begin.
# I am not seeing you
# Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah. #
When the guy
counts down to zero,
the three astronauts will take off
in 'Apollo 11 ' from America.
And the rocket will fly up to
the moon like this and, er...
Landing module.
Landing module comes off
and lands on the moon.
The astronauts will come out
in their spacesuits,
and get shot by martians!
(All scream)
Damien...
And their heads will explode!
They'll fly back to Earth
and kill everyone.
That's not going to happen.
It might.
Who's next? Graeme?
Um, just a minute, Graeme.
Melanie?
I haven't done the moon landing.
(Mutters) Thank God.
I've made a model of
the telescope and receiving dish
in the town of Parkes.
When astronaut Neil Armstrong
lands on the moon,
people all over the world
will be watching television pictures
provided by the radio telescope
in Parkes.
WOMAN: Mr Callem,
the Prime Minister wants to see you.
Can it wait?
I don't think so.
What's it about?
He's just got off the phone
to the White House.
Do you know
who was on the phone then?
No, sir.
The US President.
Nixon...
Sorry, sir...
.. thanking me for allowing NASA
to use our facility.
Yes, sir.
And something about an upgrade?
Right.
What's he talking about?
There's a briefing docu...
I don't read those!
( BELL RINGS )
Are we raising this?
I think we should.
So what's this all about?
The President was referring to
our radio telescope.
Some months ago, NASA requested -
and you approved -
its use in the Apollo program,
originally as a backup receiver.
Originally?
They upgraded its role.
When 'Apollo 11 '
gets to the moon,
Parkes will now be
the prime receiving station.
Meaning?
We've got the moon walk.
Shit. The people at this place -
do they know what they're doing?
I believe so.
I bloody well hope so.
Why'd they pick us?
It's the largest radio telescope
in the Southern Hemisphere.
What's it doing in the middle
of a sheep paddock?
MAN: The Parkes radio telescope,
or, as we call it, the dish,
will track 'Apollo 11 '
throughout its journey
gathering voice signals
from the astronauts,
telemetry from the spaceship
and then, most importantly,
the TV signals from the moon itself.
It's 210 feet in diameter,
it weighs 1,000 tons
and it can be moved to point
in virtually every direction.
It's the most powerful
receiving dish in the world.
.. in the world.
Can I have their full names
and specific roles?
This is Ross Mitchell.
He's responsible
for manoeuvring the dish.
This is Mr Glenn Latham.
Glenn's in charge of
all the electronics.
Glenn's a Sagittarius. He enjoys
knitting, flower-arranging...
Mitch, I do not!
Don't write that.
From NASA, Al Burnett.
Al makes sure the signals
get back safely to Mission Control.
Enjoying your stay in Australia?
Very much, sir.
The people are warm...
And friendly. That's great.
And you, Cliff.
What's your official title?
Cliff Buxton, director.
Or the 'dishmaster'.
OK. Now I just need
a few personal details.
You married?
Yeah.
Glenn?
Fiancee, Janine Kellerman.
Mitch! She's not my fiancee.
Local girl.
I don't have a fiancee.
Married.
Two boys, in Houston.
And you, Cliff?
Married.
And just finally,
I mean, no offence,
but when you think about it,
the Americans spent 10 years,
billions of dollars,
to let us watch man
walk on the moon,
and in the end it falls
to you blokes. (Laughs)
I mean,
how do you feel about that?
A lot better
before you opened your trap.
We feel confident we have
the expertise to complete our role.
But, Cliff. I mean,
it's pretty amazing, isn't it?
Yes, it is amazing.
And so Australia finds itself
a vital cog
in this grand endeavour.
ALL: Hear, hear.
Only this morning,
I conveyed to President Nixon
my long-term interest
and commitment to this project.
It will be
one of the proudest moments
in Australia's
scientific history.
ALL: Hear, hear.
And I thought it fitting
to accept the invitation
of the mayor of Parkes
to be there on Monday
and witness first-hand
our vital contribution.
ALL: Hear, hear.
Now THAT is an RSVP.
The Prime Minister
coming to Parkes.
I'll frame that.
The icing on the cake.
You know why this means so much?
Helps your political career.
No, Len.
It does.
The PM standing with
the candidate.
It's all about brownnosing.
Licking arse!
No! It's a vindication.
Oh!
Oh, vindication.
Vindication of my campaign
to get that dish here
in the first place.
That was an episode!
You know what people said
when I proposed Parkes?
That you were grandstanding.
It's a self-serving stunt
to big-note yourself.
Who said that?
Oh...
They said I was a dreamer.
A visionary.
Yeah, that's right.
"Bob Mclntyre," they said,
"you'll never pull it off. "
And now, which town is part of
the 'Apollo 11 ' mission?
RADIO: Honeysuckle network,
Net 2.
HONEYSUCKLE: Honeysuckle.
NET 2: Roger, would you confirm
that Parkes is all up...
NEWSREADER: As 'Apollo 11 '
is being readied for launch,
NASA is completing final checks
on its deep space network.
The vast array of radio telescopes
and cable links
all over the world,
including a number in Australia,
that will allow communications
with 'Apollo 11 '
on its historic journey.
AL:.. and it deposits signals
straight to Sydney.
Strip the TV,
send that to Moree...
Both receivers.
Sorry, go on.
The rest will be sent
to the demodulator
at Honeysuckle Creek first.
The biomed telemetry feeds -
can we send those
on separate lines?
Mitch?
Yeah, no problem.
AL: OK. Biomed, TM split feeds.
It's a big book
you've got there, Al.
Hold on.
What is it?
These coordinates don't match.
They've been changed.
Are you sure?
This is unacceptable.
Glenn, come here.
What?
Every coordinate in this book
has been changed.
Yeah?
I changed them.
You what?
Why?
Because they were wrong.
Why were they wrong?
I don't know.
No, what about them was wrong?
The figures NASA sent us
were for the Northern Hemisphere.
And we're in
the Southern Hemisphere.
I can change them back,
but you'd point in the wrong...
It might be a good idea
to tell us.
Oh, sure.
I just didn't want to worry you.
Cup of tea, Al?
No, thank you.
MITCH: I'll have one.
Thank you, Glenn.
This is why we have to check
and double-check.
All of NASA's work.
Everyone's work, unless you have
a problem with that.
I don't have a problem
with that.
I got a problem...
OK, Mitch. Let's get on with it.
I'll go and start the dish.
MAN: Hi, Bob!
Phil.
Keith.
Major Mclntyre.
I'm a long time out of uniform.
You fought, sir. In a war, sir.
You'll get your chance.
I hope so, sir.
Kid's a cadet.
He's keen.
Hello, Bob.
How's it going, Pearl?
Bob, busy as a bee.
The whole town's abuzz.
They'll have something else
to talk about soon.
I can't say too much,
but we might be
getting a visitor.
The Prime Minister. May phoned.
And the American ambassador.
That woman...
Can you keep it under your hat?
I don't think so.
Don't worry.
How are the boys at the dish?
They're raring to go.
The American chap settling in?
I think so. Quiet fella.
Came in here yesterday...
wanting pretzels!
Pretzels?
Yep. It's a world event.
The Prime Minister.
Better get a jig-along.
See you later.
MAN ON RADIO: Last report,
all systems were go at the cape
and the countdown
proceeding to schedule.
MAN 2: Let's go back
to Cape Kennedy
and correspondent Fred Turner.
( RADIO BABBLE CONTINUES )
(Yells) The launch is definitely
going ahead tonight.
And the ball is definitely
going ahead Friday night.
So can we get back to fixing...
Oh, yeah. Got another surge.
(Plays 'Cuando, Cuando, Cuando')
(Band stops)
Oh! I could rumba right now.
I hope we've got
some slow numbers.
Yes, Mrs Spears.
Um, we've got a new song too.
Who's it by?
J- James Hendrix.
Let's hear a couple of bars.
(Band plays 'Foxy Lady')
There's a slower version.
That is not to go above three.
Yes, Mrs Spears.
You're right
with the American anthem?
The what?
Are you telling me
you haven't prepared
the American national anthem?
How does it go?
You've got 48 hours.
MITCH: I knew it
the day he arrived!
NASA sent him - fine,
they're renting the dish.
But how about some respect?
Two-way street.
Honestly,
I wouldn't worry about it.
We're a professional unit...
GLENN: Mitch.
You right?
Sorry, mate.
Still not flat enough, Glenn.
I'll give it a tweak.
Drop it down a couple of clicks.
Probably on NASA settings.
MITCH: We're senior members
of the department of radio physics.
We're not mugs at this game.
Know what he asked me?
Do we have a dress standard?
I mean, can you believe that?
That is hard to believe.
Wish he'd gone home
with the rest.
What's his problem?
Well, perhaps he's just
feeling the pressure.
(Scoffs) Feeling the pressure.
He's got to learn to relax.
I'll tell you a little secret, Mitch.
He's not the only one.
(Hatch opens)
We just got word from Houston.
It's go for launch.
( 'SPANISH FLEA' BY HERB ALPERT
AND THE TIJUANA BRASS PLAYS )
BOB: Ha-ha! Kelsos!
Now the party can start. Come in.
Melna!
All the way from Grenfell.
Wouldn't miss it!
How's Clem? Chesty.
Happy to have you home
from university.
It's for the weekend.
I go back Monday.
Phone's been ringing all day.
You'll miss the moon landing.
Good.
This whole mission's typical
of America's imperialistic greed.
CSIRO, reporters, Reg Baxter.
They're just walking on it.
And then what?
Come home, I suppose.
That's enough, Marie.
Mr Purvis doesn't want to hear
all that nonsense.
Pick up the phone
and I yell, "Yeah, what?"
And do you know who it was?
The science minister.
Who's for another
devil-on-horseback?
They've all got families.
I know. It's extraordinary.
I wouldn't let Don go.
I know exactly what you mean.
How do you reckon they go to...
(Whistles).. up there?
I suppose they just hold on.
For four days.
Looking forward to the dance.
It's a ball.
They're not eating big meals,
just pills and stuff.
You can't hold on
for four days, Len.
They should try these -
block them up for a week.
TELEVISION: And all is still go
as we monitor our status...
How's it looking, Billy?
It's full of liquid hydrogen.
Can they fix that?
No, it means it's go for launch.
Oh, hydrogen!
And the Prime Minister?
He'll be here on Monday.
For the lunch!
Luncheon, Melna.
Men on the moon, eh?
Yep, and we're part of it, Dad.
Part of it - we're slap-bang
in the middle of it.
MAY: And there could be
a small announcement.
Really?
It's not official yet.
But Bob's got the nomination
for Parkes.
(Squeals)
But we're not telling anybody!
What's that?
Bob's got the nomination
for Parkes.
Bob, congratulations
on the nomination.
Bob, the nomination. Well done.
May...
BILLY: Dad, they're talking
about Parkes!
Crikey!
TELEVISION: Well, the signals from
the radio telescope antenna at Parkes
will come in here
over the postmaster general's
video system.
We're building a new antenna
in Australia...
LEN: Who's that?
BOB: Wilson Hunter.
Bigwig from NASA. Good fella.
Dad looked after him.
He's NASA's
senior scientific representative.
That's what it's all about.
Sucking up to the bigwigs.
No, that's not it.
TELEVISION: All indications
coming in to the control centre
indicate we are go.
Our status board indicates
the third stage
completely pressurised.
T- minus 60 seconds and counting.
We've passed T-minus 60.
55 seconds and counting.
All still go at this time.
Neil Armstrong reported back
when he received good wishes,
"Thank you very much.
We know it will be a good flight. "
Good luck and Godspeed.
40 seconds away from
the 'Apollo 11 ' lift-off.
All the second-stage tanks
now pressurised.
35 seconds and counting.
We are still go with 'Apollo 11 '.
30 seconds and counting.
Astronauts report,
"It feels good. "
T- minus 25 seconds.
20 seconds and counting.
Guidance is internal.
TELEVISION: 15 seconds.
TELEVISION: 12, 11, 10...
Ignition sequence starts.
TELEVISION:
lgnition sequence starts.
Six, five, four,
three, two, one, zero.
All engines running.
Lift-off. We have a lift-off.
32 minutes past the hour.
Lift-off on 'Apollo 11 '.
( ROCKET RUMBLES )
TELEVISION: Tower cleared.
ARMSTRONG: We've got to
roll program.
TELEVISION:
Neil Armstrong reporting
the roll and pitch program
which puts 'Apollo 11 '
on proper heading.
ARMSTRONG: Roll is complete
and the pitch is programming.
TELEVISION: Plus 30 seconds.
Down range - 1 mile.
Altitude - 3, 4 miles an hour.
Godspeed.
Amen.
TELEVISION: Velocity -
2,195 feet per second...
TELEVISION: 'Apollo 11 ' is now
out over the lndian Ocean
approaching the western shore
of Australia.
And as you perhaps know,
the crew will make
1.5 revolutions of the Earth...
RADIO:.. from the ABC,
read by Tom Kelly.
The 'Apollo 11 ' has had
a perfect launching
on its journey to the moon.
The Saturn rocket rose
on a blur of orange-red flame
from Cape Kennedy,
right on time at 11:32 tonight,
Eastern Australian Time.
The spaceship
and the rocket's final stage
are now orbiting the Earth,
before setting out in 4 hours...
KEITH: Ten-hut!
Morning, Marie.
SONG: # Good morning, starshine
# You lead us along
# My love and me as we sing... #
( GEARS CRUNCH )
# Baby, la-be-loo-be la-la
# La-la-la lo-lo... #
(Sighs)
# Do-be-do-be wah-la
# Do-be-aba-naba
# Early morning
singing this song. #
Visitor entering compound.
Await identification.
You're being stupid, Rudi.
Visitor offering resistance.
You've got a gun!
Yeah.
Official NASA requirement -
armed security.
Does Mum know?
No, and don't tell her, Janine.
She'll come and take it off me.
This is getting cold.
I've got to sign you in. Janine!
Entry authorised.
A bickie too.
JANINE: Hello, everyone.
Morning, Mr Buxton.
Well, if it isn't
the most beautiful girl in Parkes.
Good morning, Mr Burnett.
Thank you, Janine.
Good morning, Mitch.
Janine.
Good morning, Glenn.
Hi, Janine.
I put extra cheese on yours.
Thanks, Janine.
You tiger.
Mitch.
How's Mum?
She's good, Mr Buxton.
Getting ready for the ball.
The whole town is over the moon.
(Janine and Cliff laugh)
JANINE: It is so exciting.
The ambassador arrives tomorrow.
Oh! Over the moon.
(Giggles) The Prime Minister's
here on Monday.
On the news they showed Parkes.
They show the dish?
Mm-hm. Everyone's so proud.
RADIO: PKS,
Houston Flight Control.
Awaiting downlink frequencies.
PKS. Roger that, Houston.
Was that Neil Armstrong?
No, we're not online
at the moment, Janine.
Sorry?
There's two
major tracking stations.
There's us and Goldstone.
Goldstone?
California.
When the moon's on our side
of the world, Parkes is online.
When it's on the other,
then it's Goldstone.
Right, but...
Why don't you explain it, Glenn?
Go on.
Um... OK.
Imagine the Earth
is a basketball.
This'll be good.
On top of the basketball is...
What's that thing
you put the pump into?
The hole.
Yeah, but it's got a name.
Oh, the valve.
The valve is Goldstone,
on the other side is another valve...
Basketballs only have one valve.
What's something
with two valves?
A tuba.
No, round.
Tambourine.
Doesn't have valves.
Coconut...
Mitch.
Let's just say it's a basketball
with two valves.
When the Goldstone valve
can't see 'Apollo 11 ',
the Parkes valve can.
That's it.
Good work, Glenn.
But how do you know
where 'Apollo 11 ' is?
Computer.
Wow.
20 seconds it does
what took me five hours with a slide rule.
And a basketball.
Does the computer move the dish?
Mitch does that...
Janine, we'll have to
return to work.
Thank you for the refreshments.
Oh, it was my pleasure.
Thanks very much, Janine.
See you, love.
She's a lovely girl.
Yeah. Not much of a driver but.
You should ask her out
when all this is over.
Oh, boy. Ask Janine out -
I don't know, Cliff.
You should see her
come to the cricket club
and everyone wants to talk to her.
And Garry Kenny - wouldn't be
surprised if they're going out.
Do you reckon?
Yeah, I reckon.
What if she said no?
Well, sometimes
you've just got to take a risk.
( NEWS THEME MUSIC )
Armstrong, Aldrin and Collins
started their epic mission
a little more than 19 hours ago.
Where are they now, Kevin?
At the moment, the astronauts
are 93,250 miles from Earth
and the moon is
146,750 miles ahead.
If we look at it on this scale,
which we should stress
is not drawn to scale...
Pity they don't mention
who got the dish here.
Come on, love.
You've never got due credit,
Robert Mclntyre.
I've done alright, Maysie.
Please don't call me Maysie
in front of the ambassador.
What do I care if some bigwig Yank
sees I love my wife?
Now, Bob, the blue or the lemon?
The yellow.
Lemon.
Come on, Maysie. Give us a kiss!
What did I just say?!
No idea!
If you get into Parliament,
will you abolish the national draft?
Anything for you, sweetheart.
Dad, it's a political issue.
Oh. Leave it with me.
Cliff, about before.
I don't want you and Mitch to think
I'm holding on too tight.
Well, you've got a lot
on your plate, Al.
It's just that now that the teams
have gone back,
I'm responsible.
Am I holding on too tight?
Well, there's a lot at stake, Al.
There's no guarantees.
A lot of variables.
We'll be right.
( 'CLASSICAL GAS' PLAYS )
MITCH: Zenith - 59, 56,
57, 58, 59, 60.
6001.
CLIFF: Hold it there.
( SHEEP BLEAT )
Glenn?
Nothing.
HGA?
Prelimit.
CLIFF: Run APP prime.
Antenna porting processor
running.
We've got a signal.
Glenn?
It's weak.
Pick it up, Mitch.
Azimuth - 8522, 24, 26, 28...
AL: It's up.
GLENN: 90DBM. Solid.
( BEEP )
RADIO: 'Apollo 11 ', Houston...
CLIFF: OK, switching to M.E.
Equatorial control locked on.
Reading?
2.5.
Set...
.. and holding.
Acquisition of signal.
We are go for command.
PKS, Houston NC.
RADIO: Houston Network Control.
Go ahead, Parkes.
Standing by for handover.
HOUSTON: Copy that, Parkes.
All stations Net 2,
we are switching to PKS.
ASTRONAUT: Roger, understand...
Who's for a cup of tea?
HOUSTON: '11 ',
it was a good readback,
and we'd like
a crew status report, over.
ASTRONAUT: Houston, 'Apollo 11 ',
the battery charging is complete
and the crew status report
is as follows.
CDR, VMV, LMD,
negative medication.
Fit as a fiddle, over.
HOUSTON: Roger, copy, '11 '.
Thank you so much.
We'd like you to verify
a reading...
(English accent) Houston,
the moon city of the US.
Dr Charles Berry
is the astronauts' doctor.
(Speaks ltalian)
We've had concerns about whether
they're able to rest adequately.
We're pretty sure
we know how to do it.
(Speaks Japanese)
.. is following
the 'Apollo 11 ' mission
with intense personal interest.
RADIO: PKS, Houston. Contact.
MITCH: Go ahead, Houston.
HOUSTON: Can we have
a CSM switch reading, please?
1-3-0.
Roger, signal strength
is negative 1-3-0.
Solid lock on prime.
HOUSTON: Standby for UDB.
Uplink data buffer standing by.
What was that?
Just a CSM switch.
Nothing to worry about.
Won't be long.
Take your time.
Can you run a verification
of the projected plot points
for the next handover?
I've done it.
Now with the adjusted bearings.
Oh, well, I stand corrected.
No, you're wrong.
Got a problem?
Yeah.
CLIFF: Mitch...
No.
You treat us like
a pack of galahs.
That's a kind of parrot.
Just because I don't wear a tie
or spend all day
buried in a manual
doesn't mean I'm a drongo.
That's a hopeless...
Yeah, I get the idea, Glenn.
I've got nothing but complete respect
for your capabilities.
I'd appreciate the same
in return.
Al, it's probably time
to get along now.
Let me know if...
Don't worry.
RUDl: 'Bye, Mr Burnett.
Guys, I've been calling you...
Oh, right.
It's been switched off again.
Testing, 1, 2, testing...
( FEEDBACK )
Right.
MITCH:
What were you calling about?
What's that?
You've been calling -
what were you calling about?
Oh, it was just the, um...
.. the...
Routine call?
Yep, that's right, Mr Buxton.
It was the routine call.
Anyway, I'd better get back
to my post.
Can we set up over here?
That's it - there's
a camera crew downstairs.
Entry's been authorised.
Ambassador's taking his time.
Must still be at the motel.
You organise that fruit platter?
Yep, nice big one.
Major Mclntyre.
Keith.
Is Marie here, sir?
No, apparently the ambassador
is a "cultural imperialist".
Sorry, sir?
She's gone in.
Be careful, son.
Yes, sir.
That boy's about to
get a taste of war.
In a few days time,
we'll be watching
television pictures from the moon.
Could you explain how these pictures
will be received?
Got a basketball?
When Armstrong emerges
from the lunar landing module,
he'll activate
a small camera here,
which will capture pictures
of him descending the ladder
and walking
on the surface of the moon.
REPORTER: These pictures -
how will they make it back to Earth?
Carrier pigeon.
There's a small S-band
transmitter on top
which sends the images
back down to us.
It's certainly
amazing technology...
(Glenn laughs) Carrier pigeon.
REPORTER:
We'll have to go again.
LEN: Ambassador of
the United States.
Can't get the lump
out of my throat.
Should stop eating
those party pies.
You're right, Len.
It is a big day for Parkes.
It's a vindication.
They're here, Bob.
MAY: What do we call him?
Your Excellency?
Turn it up.
He's not bloody royalty.
It's important, Bob.
We're his first impression
of Parkes.
Mr Ambassador, on behalf of
the people of Parkes,
we welcome you to Parkes.
Why, thank you, Bob.
I can call you Bob?
Absolutely, Mr Ambassador.
Howard. And this is...?
Len.
G'day.
I mean May. My wife, May.
She's the lemon.
RADIO: 'Apollo 11 ', Houston.
We recommend you accept 1 '49.
Continue through
your sequence of sighting
and then we'll analyse the data
afterwards, over.
ASTRONAUT: OK.
Cliff?
Time for a cup of tea?
I haven't been treated like this
since I stripped harvesters.
He reckons the only people
who can do a job properly
are Americans.
Aren't you being
a little unfair?
Cliff,
what's happened to you lately?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, that came out wrong.
But this was always your dish.
You'd never let anyone else
come in and run the place.
We're part of a worldwide team
on this.
Part of NASA.
And what's NASA?
It's money and equipment
on a plate.
No, Mitch. NASA's just
a bigger bunch of us.
Have you thought about
what's being attempted here?
Of course I have.
We're in the middle
of the greatest feat ever attempted.
This is science's chance
to be daring.
What are you doing?
Standing around, bitching.
( FOOTSTEPS )
Rudi.
Fellas.
Janine dropped some food over
from the dance.
Lovely.
Her and Glenn are down there
by themselves?
Yeah.
I don't know if you guys have noticed,
but Janine likes Glenn.
Is that right?
Rudi, what's with the gun?
It's an official
NASA installation, Mr Buxton.
We may need this.
Don't worry about that - I've tasted it.
What?
The food.
It could have been
tampered with.
We can't take chances, guys.
Do you want a couple more?
Thanks, I'm still starving.
(Clicks radio) Leaving Sector A.
Um, I thought the foyer
was Sector A.
Yeah. It was.
But now I've decided to go
alphabetically
from the top down.
That's not locked in yet.
Cliff.
This whole thing -
I can't believe I'm a part of it.
Certainly can't believe
Rudi's a part of it.
(Laughs)
Me too.
Helen would've been proud.
(Band plays
'God Save the Queen' badly)
Ladies and gentlemen,
distinguished guests,
please remain upstanding
for the national anthem
of the United States of America.
(Plays 'Hawaii Five-0' theme)
(Mouths)
CLIFF: PKS, Houston.
Confirm handover at 1700 hours.
HOUSTON: Roger, PKS. Copy, 1700.
PKS, out.
Where'd you get the chocolate?
Janine.
So, um...
I will, Cliff. I will. I promise.
( BAND PLAYS,
GENERAL CHATTER )
The Prime Minister's people
want to meet and greet,
and I can't find the car keys!
About to call a cab
and what do I see...
The keys in the car door.
Why don't we dance?
(All laugh)
Keys were hanging out the door.
(Laughs)
( 'A TASTE OF HONEY' PLAYS )
Not too racey?
Oh, no.
Marie.
What?
I was wondering
if you'd like to dance.
Are you stupid?
No.
Would you?
You're sure I wouldn't be
in the way?
We'd be honoured
to have you visit.
Sorry about that mix-up
earlier, Howard.
No harm done, Bob.
Sometimes I wish it was
our national anthem.
(Laughs) Oh, beauty.
You'll love this bloke.
(Sings) # Fly me to the moon
# Let me swing
among the stars... #
He's from Brisbane.
Is he? He's a little like Frank Sinatra.
Mmm, if not better.
# ln other words,
hold my hand... #
( ELECTRICITY FUSES )
Oh, who's playing funny buggers?
Shit!
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
We're sorting it out.
Copped another surge.
It's not that pie-warmer again?
MITCH: What's happened?
CLIFF: Blackout.
GLENN: Control panel's dead.
Sorry, folks.
Have it fixed in a jiffy.
Receivers.
Negative.
Demodulators.
Nuh.
Whole rack's dead.
Everything's dead.
Bloody hell.
What happened to
the backup generator?
Shit.
(All gasp)
( APPLAUSE )
Sorry about that, Howard.
No trouble for me, Bob.
As long as everything is fine
out at the installation.
What, the dish? Oh, they'd have
all that under control.
Backup generators, the works.
I'll check with Al.
Where's Al?
( 'THE LOVED ONE'
BY THE LOVED ONES PLAYS )
Anything?
Nothing.
We've lost lock.
What happened to the generator?
Er, the fuel pump.
What about it?
Well, when I drained it,
I must have...
I forgot to
prime the lines again.
You forgot?!
It was...
How could you let that happen?!
This is what happens...
Don't you dare!
Alright.
We've got to find that ship.
Switch to manual drive,
see if we can get a lock.
What's its position?
Um...
CLIFF: Come on!
I think the computer's wiped.
Oh, shit.
Are we stuffed?
Kinda.
Glenn?
Yep, we're stuffed.
What's that noise?
It's moving.
CLIFF: How?
M.E. must be chasing
its own tail.
Shut it down.
We'll have to override...
( GEARS STOP )
How far did it move?
Far enough.
Are we sending anything?
RADIO: Sydney OTC,
this is Flight Control Houston.
Are you receiving a signal
from Parkes?
SYDNEY: Negative, Houston.
HOUSTON: PKS, Flight Control
Houston here. Do you copy?
Flight Control, this is Parkes.
We copy.
HOUSTON: Parkes, we've lost
your signal. Confirm status.
Er, Houston, this is Parkes.
We still have a strong signal.
Must be a relay problem.
HOUSTON: Copy that, Parkes.
We'll look into it. Stand by.
Parkes, standing by.
Cliff, that's bullshit.
You just bullshitted NASA.
That's not good.
Oh...
I bought us some time.
AL: Let me get this straight.
You've lost 'Apollo 11 '.
Yep.
Southern Hemisphere's
prime receiving station
has no idea
where 'Apollo 11 ' is.
It's on its way
to the moon.
Computer can't lock us back on?
Once it loses power,
it loses data.
I thought there's
an uninterruptable power source.
It was designed as a UPS,
but, um,
the generator
didn't kick back in.
How come?
It just didn't, Al.
Look, the power's back on.
Everything's under control.
Except we've lost 'Apollo 11 '.
Except for that.
We have the data, it just has to
be programmed back in.
How long will that take?
Glenn?
Hours. A day. Month.
How long, Glenn?
Take a shot.
12, 24 hours.
It's a lot of calculations.
If we're not relaying data,
Houston would've noticed.
Well, as a matter of fact,
they did call.
What did you tell them?
I told them that the problem
wasn't at our end.
You lied?
GLENN: Bullshitted them.
We have to tell them, Cliff.
That we stuffed up?
Yes, that we stuffed it.
Like they stuffed
the Southern Hemisphere coordinates.
They'll give us
the current position.
And say we're not required.
Excuse me?
We're dickheads who can't maintain
a practice signal.
I'm telling you...
Listen, Al.
We can reprogram the system.
We need you to keep NASA
off our backs.
Cliff, I am NASA. And I'm saying
we tell them what happened.
RADIO: PKS, Houston NC.
Go ahead, Houston.
HOUSTON: Spoken to IMCO.
No closer to finding
this breakdown.
Are you sure it's downstream?
PKS...
.. is still online, Houston,
confirming loss of signal
downstream.
HOUSTON: Roger that, Parkes.
We'll maintain alternative feed.
(Murmurs) What have I done?
You bullshitted NASA.
Good man, Al.
Right, let's get cracking.
SONG: # I chose you
for the one... #
I've never been more proud of
being mayor than I was tonight.
Plus I got to go home
with the prettiest girl at the dance.
You look great in yellow.
Lemon.
( PHONE RINGS )
Who's that?
Crikey! There'll be
10 or 15 press coming with it.
They're not going to be mugs.
Alright.
Alright, what if you
come clean, just tell NASA?
Tell them what?
Th-that, um...
That we lost 'Apollo 11 '?
I wouldn't say that first.
What would you say?
Well, you know, "Hey, you'll
never guess what happened... "
Bob, it's 'Apollo 11 '.
What would they do?
I'm not exactly sure.
Pull the pin?
Well, not officially,
but they might downgrade our role.
We'd lose the moon walk.
Try keeping a lid on that.
We'll be the punchline
to a joke.
RUDl: Who goes there?
It's just us, Rudi.
Oh, OK.
Who?
Cliff and Bob.
Hi, Bob.
Rudi.
How are you?
Good. Fine.
OK. Nighty-night.
We know roughly when they reappear,
but not where.
The same place as yesterday.
Yesterday, they were orbiting.
Now they're translunar.
We'll have to re-do every angle.
That'll take forever.
Make it a two-body calculation.
Get an approximate fix
then scan.
Yeah, that should do it.
I'll give you a hand
with the figures.
Al, I found out what happened
to the generator.
What?
I forgot to prime
the fuel lines.
Well, these things happen.
Better get to work.
If we come on-stream tomorrow,
it never happened.
You think you can do it?
I made a commitment to NASA
and I intend to fulfil it.
Haven't heard that tone
for a while.
You remember that night
at my place,
trying to sort out the contract
with that fella from NASA?
"What about this?
What about that?"
Two hours,
and you finally speak.
"Gentlemen,
this should be the contract.
"We agree to support
the 'Apollo 11 ' mission. "
That was it - one sentence.
They couldn't believe it.
It was a wonderful moment.
But this isn't.
No, this is a shithouse moment.
RUDl: Halt. Who goes there?
( SHEEP BLEATS )
( WONDROUS MUSIC )
MITCH: Glenn?
No, I'm not sure.
I thought you said
you were confident.
I am. I was.
Look, it's got to be within
this range.
But if we sweep here,
it may be outside and we miss it.
And if we sweep wider,
well, we still might miss it.
You're confident about that?
They're in the commanding
service module
until they reach the moon,
and the rockets aren't on.
Really?
They just sit and wait.
Is that right?
This is the fastest
man's ever travelled.
Go on.
If you ask me,
it's the biggest
chauvinistic exercise in history.
That's why nobody asks you,
darling.
There you go, Bob.
I'll go get
my 'Saturn V' rocket.
Yeah, go get it. Thanks, love.
Is everything alright
at the dish?
Maysie, can you keep a secret?
(Laughs) No.
What's happened, Bob?
What if we split the difference?
Ship's moving too fast.
OK, let's just call Houston
and ask for the current coordinates.
Which tells them
we've been bullshitting.
Just tell them what happened.
We lied - that'll go down well.
I don't think it will.
Morning, everyone.
How's it going?
Good.
You were on the news again
last night.
Is everything alright?
Glenn?
Um, yeah. It's fine.
Glenn was just checking...
some stuff.
Oh, really?
Oh, well, I'd better let you
get to it.
I'm sorry for interrupting.
Not at all, Janine, really.
Thanks for bringing the food.
No problem, Mr Buxton.
Cliff, what do you want to do?
Just give this
a little more thought.
RUDI ON RADIO:
Sector G, come in.
GLENN: Let me
just try something.
Not now, Rudi.
You've got a visitor.
It's the ambassador.
Of the United States of America.
Oh, God.
RUDl: ls this thing working?
Just a minute, Rudi.
Roger that, Sector G.
Confirm Sector A, hold on.
He asked to visit.
I didn't think he'd come so soon.
He's here.
Space nut. Knows everything
about 'Apollo 11 '.
Does he know where it is?
OK, let's make this brief.
Send him up, Rudi.
Roger that.
This is the main control panel.
That moves the dish up and down
and that's
your sideways movement.
It's incredible.
You can actually pinpoint
a tiny spaceship
thousands of miles away
and lock onto it.
Pretty much.
The ambassador didn't sign in,
but I've let it go.
Didn't want to pull rank
or anything.
Now, correct me,
but the other facilities down this way -
North West Cape
and Honeysuckle Creek -
they also have voice
and telemetry, yes?
That's right, sir.
But when it comes to TV,
yours is the only dish large enough?
Yeah.
How does that make you feel?
Where do you get them glasses?
Sir, I'm afraid that
we're entering overlap now.
Oh. So you'll be getting
transmissions?
Yeah.
You'll be able to hear Armstrong
talking to Houston?
Just by hitting
a couple of buttons there.
Oh, let's do that.
Sure. OK.
I don't think that, er...
No, you're right.
I don't think...
Just a brief listen
and then I'll go.
MITCH: Not a problem.
Er... l'll just have to...
reorient... the, er...
Al.
Cliff, if you could patch
the audio in from Mezzanine 3.
MAN ON RADIO: Columbia, Houston.
Guidance systems OK.
You're still go for auto.
MAN 2: Copy that.
MAN 1: Telemetry reports that
O2 and CO2 are OK and steady,
and biomed telemetry
is now reading your vital statistics
as being adequate
within the limits.
(American accent) Copy that.
Neil, we have you currently
at 124,000 nautical miles from Earth
and at an approach velocity
of 32,000 feet per second.
MITCH: Copy that.
AL: We might just let you
get back to work.
MITCH: Copy that.
RUDl: ls that you, Neil?
I repeat, this is Sector A.
Is that you, Mr Armstrong?
(Pulls plug) That's funny.
Must be a crossed line
from Honeysuckle Creek.
Sir, we must get back
to work now.
Oh. Oh!
I'll see you out.
I'll just move the dish.
Oh, it's incredible.
That was a true highlight.
I was going to say good luck,
but after what I've seen here
this morning,
you gentlemen don't need it.
Thank you very much, sir.
Mr Buxton, you'll never guess
what happened.
Later, Rudi.
Should I get him to sign out?
Just wait.
That's got to be a felony.
Right, let's find this ship.
Glenn.
Moving target.
Everything's moving.
If we had a point of reference,
maybe we could do it.
We take a punt.
Choose a sector, arc that.
GLENN: It's still a long shot.
I thought you were confident.
I know where 'Apollo 11 ' is.
It's on its way to the moon.
That's your point of reference.
They've gone 150,000 miles.
They've got to be
within 3 or 4 degrees.
Yeah. That might be OK.
I think it might be OK.
Yeah.
So, we can rub this out?
MITCH: 5707... 5708...
( GEARS STOP )
There's your moon.
Have a fish around, Mitch.
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC )
6730.
MITCH: 6731.
( BEEP! )
We've got a signal!
It's 'Apollo 11 '.
Definite?
GLENN: 2.28.
AL: It's the tin can.
Glenn?
Yep! Signal lock!
( RADIO BABBLE )
PKS, Houston Net 2.
HOUSTON: Houston, PKS.
Parkes is online.
HOUSTON: Copy that, Parkes.
And, copy, we're receiving
your signal.
Switching to master equatorial.
And with 15 minutes to spare.
Just enough time
to go and check the generator.
(Chuckles)
It's great news, Cliff.
( KNOCK AT DOOR )
Ah, look, I've got to dash.
Um, look, I appreciate the call.
What? (Laughs)
Yeah! 'Bye.
Major Mclntyre.
Keith.
What?
Oh, I just wanted
to ask Marie something.
Fire when ready.
Marie, it's Keith.
Would you like to watch
the moon landing with me on Monday?
MARIE: Don't you get it?!
Get what, sir?
I think that's a no.
Oh.
You're a brave lad.
RADIO: 'Apollo 11 ',
this is Houston, over.
ASTRONAUT: Roger, go ahead,
Houston. 'Apollo 11 '.
HOUSTON: '11 ', Houston.
You are go for LOl, over.
ASTRONAUT: Roger, go for LOl.
Houston, 'Apollo 11 '. You want
to give me a time check, please?
HOUSTON: Give you a mark of
13 minutes and 30 seconds to ignition.
ASTRONAUT: Roger.
HOUSTON: Roger, out.
HOUSTON: 'Apollo 11 ',
all your systems are looking good.
Going around the corner,
we'll see you on the other side, over.
TELEVISION:
.. will orbit the moon
in preparation for its historic descent
to the lunar surface
on Monday afternoon...
That's all we need to know.
Vol-au-vent?
Ah, thank you.
The boys give you a tour?
Oh, yes.
Very impressive facility.
And you actually heard
Neil Armstrong.
I had the privilege.
How did he sound?
Like he was next door.
(Gasps)
SONG: # We have got to
get it together
# We have got to
get it together now... #
That was a day and a half.
I'll be 52 on Monday.
Oh, happy birthday.
52 years,
and half of them in radio telescopes,
mapping the stars.
And then this came along.
Your pipe.
No, the moon mission.
Do you know what I thought
when it first came up?
You beauty.
I thought,
"Imagine stuffing that up. "
Isn't that odd?
What?
Well, that I was more scared
than excited.
I don't think that's odd.
I feel like that all the time.
How come you changed?
My wife said something.
She said, "Failure is never
quite so frightening as regret. "
Oh, that's good advice.
Yeah, pretty good.
I wish someone
would tell me that.
God bless you, Glenn.
( 'LET'S GET TOGETHER'
BY THE YOUNGBLOODS PLAYS )
# Love is but a song to sing
# And fear's the way we die
# You can make
the mountains ring
# Or make the angels cry
# Though the bird is on the wing
# And you may not know why
# Come on, people, now
Smile on your brother
# Everybody get together
# Try to love one another
right now... #
Al.
Yeah.
When I said
I was sorry about...
.. l meant I was sorry
for everything.
Mitch, that's not necessary.
No.
When you first arrived,
I felt a little...
.. you're this hot shot from NASA
and I'm some country kid
with the arse falling out of me daks.
Your...?
Pants.
The point is I was wrong.
I never thought of you
as a guy with
the ass falling out of his...
Daks.
.. daks.
Everyone at NASA
is a college genius.
The guy I most admire is from
a one-horse town in Ohio.
And what's he do?
Tomorrow he's going to
walk on the moon.
Who's the guy?
AL: Armstrong.
You know, it would've been OK
to tell Houston.
Things go wrong there
all the time.
Oh, yeah.
Mission Control turns blue
every launch
from 50 people
holding their breath.
Guess how many rockets blew up
before we put men inside them.
That's a while ago.
Six weeks ago.
Testing the lunar landing module.
10 simulations without a hitch.
On the 11th, the controls jammed.
It crashed and burned.
Strewth. Any idea why?
No, they still have no idea why.
Let's hope 11
isn't an unlucky number.
We pray also for those three
brave souls who, as we speak,
are taking the first steps
and exploring God's great universe.
And for the many technicians
and scientists
whose efforts contribute to
this brave endeavour.
BOB: lf you think
this 'Apollo 11 ' thing's big here,
you should hear what's going on
in the States.
Really?
What were you saying
last night, Howard?
You shouldn't drink so much.
(All laugh)
If you'll excuse me.
He was round for dinner
last night.
Imagine two basketballs.
One's there and one's there
and there's a valve on top.
They won't be televising
the whole time?
Wouldn't have thought so, no.
Bounces off the basketball,
and then it bounces off
the Goldstone one...
They could sneak around the back
and have a... (Whistles).
Reckon it depends.
On whether they're doing
a number... (Whistles)
.. or a number...
(Whistles twice)
What was that, Ray?
We're just having a chat
about the television coverage.
Oh, yes.
Listen, whereabouts around here
can I take a... (Whistles)
Ah, thanks.
# Smile on your brother
# Everybody get together
# Try to love one another
right now... #
Thanks for bringing
the sandwiches.
Thanks for fixing my bumper bar.
Oh, that's OK.
Have you...
Janine, I was wonder...
(Both giggle)
You go first.
No, you.
What were you going to say?
N- nothing.
What about you?
Nothing.
CLIFF: Has he asked her out yet?
(Sighs) No.
Oh, this is painful.
JANINE: No,
I really like weekends too.
Yeah, I like Fridays
'cause you're always
looking forward to the weekend.
BOTH: Yeah.
What were you gonna say before?
Nothing.
What were you going to say?
Alright.
See you.
Do you want to go out
Friday night?
What did you say?
Um, nothing.
Did you just say, "Do you want
to go out Friday night?"
Um, maybe.
I'd love to go out Friday night.
Oh... with me?
(Giggles) Yes.
Righto, then.
(Starts engine)
He ask her out?
Um, I'm not sure.
Cliff, I had a chat to Al
this morning.
Really?
Yeah.
He's not such a bad bloke.
You should give him a chance.
You'll be right
for a couple of hours?
Yeah, we'll be right.
If you've got problems...
I'll call Rudi.
BOB: Have more.
That's prime Parkes lamb.
I've got enough.
More where that came from.
I'll just have the vegetables.
Yes, dear.
Cliff?
This is wonderful, May.
Glad you could get away.
The boys have it under control.
When are you up?
Not till four.
Tomorrow's the big day.
All being well.
Man on the bloody moon, eh?
Gravy?
It's extraordinary, sending men
off into the galaxies
as the whole world watches.
Certainly takes your mind off
our trivial concerns.
Elbows.
Our school's watching it.
I think every school
will watch it.
What are they estimating?
I believe it's 600 million.
600 million?
600 million.
Peas?
Do the people in lndia
get to watch it?
Yeah, but all on the one telly.
(All laugh)
I'm serious.
Far too serious, darling.
How are they filming it?
Cliff.
No, go ahead.
There's a boom outside
with a camera.
Once Armstrong's outside,
he'll pull a ring and it'll swing out.
Is there an antenna on the roof?
Transmitter, Dad.
Right, Billy. It's about
the size of that bowl there.
Pumpkin?
Yes, please.
All this effort for television.
When NASA first came,
they hardly mentioned television.
Interesting change, isn't it?
Still not sure what's more important
to get back safely -
the astronauts or the pictures.
MAY: How lovely. Elbows.
MARIE: Can I ask a question?
Sure.
Is this mission being funded
by the CIA?
Not entirely.
Really?
No.
(All snicker)
How do they know they won't sink
when they land?
Crikey!
MAY: Oh, good Lord!
Well, we actually know
a great deal about the moon -
soil composition, density,
the gravitational force.
There aren't too many mysteries.
If we know so much, why go?
There's one thing
that we don't know.
BOB: What's that, Cliff?
Whether we can get there.
(Whispers) Elbows.
Well, let's start.
Man on the moon or not,
we've still got to eat.
You'll really like that.
MAY: Oh, dear.
BOB: Oh, strewth.
Back to work, eh?
Well, it's all go.
May, that roast lamb
was magnificent.
I'll bet you don't get that
in Houston.
No.
We can't have you wasting away.
Thank you.
Thanks very much, May.
It's been quite a while
since I've had a good roast.
Oh, Cliff.
Billy.
Good luck for tomorrow.
Thank you.
Marie, it was an absolute pleasure
to meet you.
Really?
Really.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
Heard the Prime Minister
on the news this morning.
Could he just shut up about it?
Do you ever have those moments
and you wonder,
"What are we doing in the middle
of the 'Apollo 11 ' mission?"
Never mind, Bob.
They'll probably knight you for this.
Or behead me.
Dad!
Keith!
About face!
Quick march!
Boy's not a soldier,
he's a Kamikaze.
SONG: # I like to dream
# Yes, yes
# Right between
the sound machine
# On a cloud of sound
I drift in the night
# Any place it goes is right
# Goes far, flies near
# To the stars
away from here... #
What are you grinning about?
What? Nothing. What?
You've had a smile
on your face all day.
(Laughs) No, I haven't.
Yes, you have!
Hello. How was lunch?
Actually, it was wonderful.
I think we ate an entire sheep.
Glenn. Rudi's on the way.
All in order?
Yeah, I'll just check
the receivers.
I'll do it.
I'll stow the dish.
I'll take a hayride.
Yep.
Hayride? What's a hayride?
CLIFF: When it's down
we can't get up through the core,
so it's just as quick
to go for a ride.
AL: OK. Interesting.
OK, Mitch.
And, strangely,
this is not in the manual.
Mm-hm. Curious oversight,
wouldn't you say?
(Al chuckles)
( GEARS WHIRR )
It wasn't good,
what you said at lunch.
What's that?
One thing we don't know
is whether we can get there.
Yes, it's easy to forget.
Before I left Houston,
the scientists had planned
all these experiments
for Armstrong to do -
rock samples,
measuring radiation.
Flight director put his foot down,
so they say to him,
"You tell us - if Armstrong
gets to the moon,
"what's the most important thing
he should do?"
FD says, "Get off it. "
(Both chuckle)
CLIFF: Well, I guess
that would be number one.
I kind of felt for him,
you know?
To be honest, there's really
only one thing I want to see.
Something about putting
a footprint on the moon.
Makes our spirits soar.
Exactly.
Did you come up with that?
Actually, I'm ashamed to say
I didn't.
It was my wife.
She died last year.
I'm sorry to hear that, Cliff.
She was so excited by all this.
Made me realise
that I should be excited too.
And I am.
The only thing is
she's not here to share it.
So, there it is.
( MELANCHOLY MUSIC )
MITCH: 34, 36..
CLIFF: Hold it there.
Glenn?
Yep.
Strength?
Negative 140.
Intermittent lock on prime.
Do you want me to...
No.
Glenn, run AGC.
Auto gate control running.
Yep, negative 90.
Solid lock. We're on, Cliff.
( RADIO BABBLE )
Switching to M.E.
Got it.
All yours, Al.
AL: Houston Net 2, PKS.
RADIO: Houston Net 2.
AL: Parkes is online.
ASTRONAUT: Control, Houston,
the RCS has supervised
that we're all go.
HOUSTON: Roger.
Mike, would you confirm
thruster B3 and C4 are off? Over.
COLLINS: C4 is off. B3 is off.
I've got my roll jets
back on now.
ARMSTRONG: And you're
manoeuvring, right?
COLLINS:
I will be shortly, Neil.
HOUSTON: 'Apollo 11 ', Houston.
We are go for undocking, over.
ARMSTRONG: Roger, understand.
HOUSTON: 'Eagle', Houston,
we see you on the screen, over.
( SOPRANO ARIA UNDERSCORES )
ARMSTRONG: Roger.
'Eagle's undocked.
HOUSTON: Roger.
How does it look?
ARMSTRONG:
The 'Eagle' has wings.
HOUSTON: Roger.
ARMSTRONG: Looking good.
HOUSTON: Roger, Neil.
If you give us data,
we've got some notes for you.
HOUSTON: We reckon now
you're go for PDl, over.
ARMSTRONG: Roger, understand.
RADIO: Bob McNeil with
another 'Apollo 11 ' update.
The descent
of the 'Eagle' landing module
has entered its fifth
and final hour.
And according to
the Flight Control Centre at Houston,
the status is still go
for a landing.
We believe the 'Eagle' module
is in the final critical stages
before touchdown.
So, just repeating,
in a matter of minutes,
astronauts Neil Armstrong
and Buzz Aldrin
will attempt to land
on the surface of the moon.
MITCH ON RADIO: Rudi.
Rudi!
Rudi, Sector 5... A... D... E.
Um, Rudi, over.
They're about to land, mate.
RADIO: 'Eagle', Houston.
After yaw around,
angle S-band pitch
minus 9 yaw plus 1-8.
'EAGLE': Roger.
HOUSTON: You are go... you are go
to continue powered descent.
You are go to continue
powered descent.
RUDl: Have they landed?
Almost.
'EAGLE':.. go for landing.
3,000 feet.
HOUSTON: We are looking great.
'EAGLE': 2,000 feet. 2,000 feet.
47 degrees.
HOUSTON: Roger.
'EAGLE': 37 degrees.
HOUSTON: You're go.
'EAGLE': Program alarm.
AL: Did he say alarm?
'EAGLE': 1201 alarm.
HOUSTON: Roger, 1201 alarm.
"1201- executive overflow. "
Computer's overloaded.
They're gonna abort.
'EAGLE': OK, we're go.
HOUSTON: We're go.
MITCH: Jesus, they're going it.
'EAGLE': 743.
'EAGLE': 540 feet, down at 15.
'EAGLE': 350 feet, down at 4.
'EAGLE':
Altitude-velocity light.
And down. 220 feet.
11 forward. Coming down nicely.
200 feet. 4.5 down.
5.5 down.
100 feet. 3.5 down. 9 forward.
75 feet and looking good.
Down a half.
6 forward.
HOUSTON: 60 seconds.
'EAGLE': Lights on. Forward.
Fuel?
I think so.
'EAGLE': 30 feet down. 2.5.
Kicking up some dust.
Faint shadow.
4 forward. Drifting
to the right a little.
HOUSTON: 30 seconds.
It's definitely a fuel call.
30 seconds of fuel left.
'EAGLE': Contact light.
'EAGLE': OK, engines stopped.
HOUSTON: We copy you down,
'Eagle'.
'EAGLE': Houston, er...
.. Tranquillity Base, here.
The 'Eagle' has landed.
HOUSTON: Roger, Tranquillity.
We copy you on the ground.
They're on the moon.
(Laughs)
(All laugh)
Whoo!
MITCH: Bloody hell.
(Sighs) Oh! 30 seconds of fuel.
RUDl: So what happens now?
AL: Sleep break.
RUDl: It's a good idea.
TELEVISION: Just confirming,
Armstrong and Aldrin
are on the moon,
both men preparing now
for EVA...
What's that?
Extra-vehicular activities.
Hey?
The moon walk!
Oh.
Hey, did they get rid of
that hydrogen?
Dad, they needed that for fuel.
Oh...
TELEVISION: I must stress
these are not to scale.
Marie, the Prime Minister's
on his way!
He's a fascist!
I beg your pardon!
Bob, speak to Marie.
(Calls) Marie!
(Sighs)
TELEVISION:.. to collect
some rock samples.
Here at the CBS news
space centre...
I might just shut that.
What?
Wind.
Glenn's onto the bureau.
What's it blowing?
15 knots.
And we're rated to...
30.
So we're fine.
For now.
Come on, Glenn.
And if it goes above 30?
If it goes above 10
we stow the dish.
That's pointing up.
We've got to be pointing east.
We understand that, Al.
Duty forecaster says
it doesn't make sense.
Great.
Did he say anything else?
Just "hello" and "goodbye".
He was very polite.
30 knots can't be
the absolute maximum.
It's the theoretical maximum.
So it's never been tested?
No.
So...
Al, we don't know.
And quite frankly,
I don't want to know.
There's 1,000 tons
above that azimuth track.
GLENN: That's not good.
Alright, let's just...
We've got nine hours
until they walk.
Could this thing
blow itself out by then?
Yeah, I reckon it could.
Yeah...
Yeah.
Good.
Cliff, Bob.
Just ringing to say good luck.
( CAR HORN TOOTS )
Hang on.
There in a minute.
It's a bit breezy this morning.
That wouldn't affect...?
Right.
What happens then?
Oh, I see. So...
You reckon?
Yeah.
Crikey.
It's a special day, Bob.
Yep.
It's thanks to you.
I wouldn't take all the credit.
You got the dish here.
Thanks.
When people think of
the moon walk,
when they think of
the role Parkes played,
they'll think of Bob Mclntyre.
Your name...
Len! Shut up!
RADIO: The Prime Minister
arrived in Parkes
where he was greeted by
US ambassador Mr Howard Cotfield,
along with local dignitaries
and townspeople eager to watch
the historic lunar landing.
BOB: This is Cliff Buxton,
the director of the facility.
Oh, yeah.
That was the official opening.
Why did they decide
to build the thing here?
If I may, Bob?
Weather, Prime Minister.
Parkes has the sort of stable
climatic conditions
conducive to the operation
of large-scale radio telescopes.
( ALARM RINGS )
(Turns off alarm)
Fire?
We've hit 30 knots.
Glenn, get back to the bureau.
Sure.
RUDl: What's up?
Relax, Rudi.
What's the bell for?
Lets us know it's windy.
I could've told you that.
It's blowing a bloody gale.
Well done with all this.
The ladies helped hang these.
No, 'Apollo 11 '.
Your dish.
Thank you, Prime Minister.
And congratulations
on getting the nod.
The party needs performers.
How are they going out there?
Oh, good, good. Perfectly.
We sit here on our arses
for five bloody days.
Not a breath of bloody wind.
Then, on cue, out of nowhere,
just when it's our turn,
a bloody cyclone
decides to park its arse on us!
Um... I'm sorry, lads.
(Clears throat) I just...
.. might just go check
some bloody thing.
Yeah, it's all going well.
Obviously nothing's foolproof.
There's always limitations.
Well, there are no guarantees,
all things considered.
Life, I guess.
You're joking, aren't you,
Mclntyre?
Yeah. (Chuckles)
Yeah, everything's fine.
You know, Mclntyre,
we have a saying in the party.
You don't fuck up.
Eh?
That's it.
Cliff!
What?
They're walking early.
Armstrong overruled the sleep break.
Armstrong's overruled it?
Said, "We don't want to sleep.
We want to walk. "
Armstrong - he goes for it.
Rudi!
When do they walk?
Soon. Now.
So we're off the hook.
No.
Goldstone are having
relay problems.
They want us up from the start.
How? We don't see the moon
till 1:00.
GLENN: 12:56.
AL: Come 12:56,
if Armstrong hasn't walked,
this dish has got to be
pointed at the moon.
From now this place
is locked down.
No-one gets in. Understand?
Yes, sir.
We'll have to move this dish.
There is a safety issue, Al.
I understand that.
We're under no obligations
in these conditions.
Mitch, what will happen?
Dunno.
What do you think will happen?
It's a big sail area.
The wind grabs hold of it...
( WIND RUSHES )
We wait.
Come on. They're going early.
It could happen any moment.
Come on, quickly.
You'll miss it.
I'd do the same.
If I just landed on the moon,
I wouldn't want to sleep.
Like telling your kid
to sleep in Christmas morning, eh?
(Laughs)
More tea, Prime Minister?
Oh, yes. Lovely.
Bob, they're going early.
Yeah, I know.
Are you alright?
I am now.
Sorry?
Goldstone can take the pictures.
Goldstone?
Cliff can't move the dish
in this wind.
Good Lord!
Hopefully it'll die down
and they'll be able to use us later.
Still, it would've been nice
to have been there from the start.
Bob, it doesn't matter
what pictures are caught by who.
We're part of the team.
That's the most important thing
right now.
Yeah, you're right, Maysie.
Shirt, Bob.
At least the boys at the dish
can relax for a while.
( BANGING )
Mitch?
Getting worse.
It's gusting to 50.
Can't move this dish.
RADIO: PKS,
Radio Houston TV Net 2.
AL: PKS Video. Go ahead.
HOUSTON: We've still got
relay problems with Goldstone
and we'll need you
as a prime receiver.
Prime?
HOUSTON: The signal
between Goldstone and Houston's dead.
It's gone to ground somewhere,
and it's still go for walk.
Roger, Houston.
We'll advise when in position.
HOUSTON: Roger, PKS.
As soon as possible, please.
AL: Cliff?
Glenn, come here.
Mitch, talk to me.
It gets shaken like this
in the upright position.
What are you saying?
It's not designed
to take these forces.
It was a question...
Wait. Finish.
It could collapse.
Man's about to walk on the moon.
And he still will.
No-one's going to see it!
Al, let's be clear about this.
There are five lives at risk.
I'm responsible for those lives.
Most people would say
that's sufficient reason
not to move the dish.
And everyone'll accept that.
But will you?
You were right, Cliff.
This is science's chance to be daring.
If we don't move this dish now,
it may as well be rubble.
Al?
I still think
11 's a lucky number.
Glenn?
What?
Sometimes you've got to
take a risk.
Alright.
Let's do it.
I like that Cliff -
he goes for it.
From north to south
They came from near and far
To witness man take to the sky
In search of moon and star.
But ponder this
as rockets fly...
( GEARS WHIRR )
( TENSE MUSIC )
( BANGING )
Oh, Jesus!
65 miles an hour.
Keep going, Mitch.
Neil Armstrong and Buzz Aldrin,
the lunar surface near.
TELEVISION: Geoffrey,
what's happening now?
GEOFFREY:
From the voice transmissions,
we can tell Armstrong has commenced
his evacuation.
We expect television pictures
any moment.
( TENSE MUSIC )
Christ! What the hell was that?
Drive cog must have slipped a few teeth.
Either that,
or Janine's trying to park.
CLIFF: Stick with it, Mitch.
I'm staying, mate.
Whatever happens.
ARMSTRONG: Houston,
I'm on the porch.
He's out of the LM.
HOUSTON: Roger, Neil.
He's outside!
HOUSTON: Columbia, Columbia,
this is Houston.
One minute, 30 seconds to LOS.
All systems go. Over.
( MUSIC INTENSIFIES )
HOUSTON: Houston, roger.
We copy.
'EAGLE': Standing by...
And we're in position now.
Good boy.
CLIFF: Glenn?
Nothing.
ARMSTRONG: Houston.
This is Neil. Radio check.
HOUSTON: Neil, this is Houston.
Loud and clear. Break, break.
Buzz, this is Houston.
Radio check and verify
TV circuit breaker in.
ALDRIN: Roger,
TV circuit breaker's in...
.. and read you loud and clear.
HOUSTON:
Parkes, please advise status.
PKS in position, signal...
.. negative.
MITCH: Glenn?
The moon's
still not high enough.
If he could just wait
a couple of minutes.
CLIFF: Go lower, Mitch.
I'm at 6003.
Next stop's concrete.
Offset feed.
Offset. Offset.
ARMSTRONG: OK, that's good.
ARMSTRONG:
OK, you want this bag?
Come on.
ARMSTRONG: Better.
HOUSTON: And we're getting
a picture on the TV.
BETTY: Man will then
have travelled...
It's Armstrong!
.. so far from home...
Thanks.
I've got another two verses.
Man's walking on the moon.
Oh.
ARMSTRONG: You have
a good picture, huh?
HOUSTON: There's a great deal
of contrast in it.
We can make out
a fair amount of detail.
GLENN: That's Armstrong.
On the moon.
HOUSTON: OK, would you verify
the position...
Well.
(Mitch chuckles)
HOUSTON: OK, Neil, we can see you
coming down the ladder now.
( WONDROUS MUSIC )
ARMSTRONG: I checked
getting back up to that first step.
The strut isn't collapsed
too far,
but it's adequate
to get back up.
HOUSTON: Roger, we copy.
ARMSTRONG: It's a pretty good
little jump.
CLIFF: Glenn.
Glenn!
Switch back to main axis.
How's that?
GIRL: Fine.
ARMSTRONG: The LM's footpads
are only depressed in the surface
about one or two inches,
although the surface appears to be...
very, very fine-grained
as you get close to it.
It's almost like a powder.
ARMSTRONG: OK, I'm going to
step off the LM now.
That's one small step for man...
.. one giant leap for mankind.
ALDRIN: That looks beautiful
from here, Neil.
ARMSTRONG: It has a stark beauty
all of its own.
It's like much of a high desert
of the United States...
Dad! He's on the moon!
I know, mate.
ARMSTRONG:
It's very pretty out here.
Thank God for that hydrogen, eh?
ARMSTRONG: Are you getting
the TV picture now, Houston?
You betcha.
HOUSTON: Neil, yes,
we are getting a TV picture.
You're in our field of view now.
ALDRIN: OK, I'm on the top step.
It's a very simple matter to hop down
from one step to the next.
ARMSTRONG: You've got three more
steps and then a long one.
ARMSTRONG: There you go.
ALDRIN: Beautiful view.
ARMSTRONG: lsn't that something?
ARMSTRONG:
Magnificent sight out here.
ALDRIN: Magnificent desolation.
(Whispers) Alright,
you can stay this once.
Get it off!
ARMSTRONG: For those who haven't
read the plaque,
we'll read the plaque
that's on the landing gear of this LM.
It says,
"Here men from the planet Earth
"first stepped foot
upon the moon.
"July, 1969 AD.
"We came in peace
for all mankind. "
It has the crew members'
signatures
and the signature of
the President of the United States.
( MUSIC CRESCENDOS )
HOUSTON: Columbia,
this is Houston.
Reading you loud and clear,
over.
COLLINS: How's it going?
HOUSTON: Roger, the EVA
is progressing beautifully.
COLLINS: Great.
HOUSTON: I guess you're about
the only person around
that doesn't have TV coverage
of the scene.
COLLINS: That's alright.
I don't mind a bit.
How is the quality of the TV?
HOUSTON: Oh, it's beautiful, Mike.
It really is.
COLLINS: Beautiful,
just beautiful.
Bob, it's a wonderful day
for Parkes.
Pearl, they're good pictures.
HOUSTON: The President
of the United States
is in his office now
and would like to say
a few words to you, over.
ARMSTRONG:
That would be an honour.
HOUSTON: Go ahead, Mr President.
This is Houston, out.
NIXON: Hello, Neil and Buzz.
Excuse me.
NIXON:.. from the Oval Room
at the White House...
(Whispers)
That was Cliff on the phone.
The pictures -
they came from us!
You bloody beauty!
Bloody fantastic!
Here's to Parkes.
MAN: The lunar age has begun.
MAN 2: 500 million people
gathered at TV sets
around the world...
MAN 1: The date's now indelible.
It'll be remembered as long as
man survives - July 20, 1969.
NIXON: And for people
all over the world.
I am sure that they too
join with Americans
in recognising
what an immense feat this is.
Because of what you have done...
Well done, guys.
What sector is Rudi again?
(Chuckles) A?
Copy that, Sector A.
Well done, Mr Armstrong.
HOUSTON: Roger, Columbia,
this is Houston.
Reading you loud and clear.
The crew of Tranquillity Base
is back inside their base.
Everything went beautifully,
over.
COLLINS: Hallelujah.
HOUSTON: Tranquillity Base,
this is Houston, over.
TRANQUILLITY BASE:
Roger, go ahead.
HOUSTON: We'd like to say
from all of us down here in Houston,
and, really, from all of us
in all the countries
in the entire world,
we think that you've done
a magnificent job up there today.
Over.
TRANQUILLITY BASE: Thank you
very much. It's been a long day.
Thanks, Bernie.
Well, the official telegram
will go to your prime minister, but,
"To congratulate personnel
of Parkes radio telescope facility
"for their outstanding support
"in man's first
lunar surface expedition. "
Signed C. Charlesworth,
'Apollo 11 ' Flight Director.
Well, we did it, eh, guys?
Yeah, we did, Al.
Good work, Mitch, and well done.
Thanks, Cliff.
Congratulations, Al.
Cliff.
Good on you, Glenn.
Thanks.
I'm proud of you.
And happy birthday, Cliff.
Thanks, Glenn.
BOB: "This should be
the contract -
"We agree to support
the 'Apollo 11 ' mission. "
MAY: It's extraordinary,
sending men off into the galaxies...
BOB:.. when you wonder,
"What are we doing
"in the middle of
the 'Apollo 11 ' mission?"
NIXON: It inspires us
to redouble our efforts
to bring peace
and tranquillity to Earth.
For one priceless moment,
in the whole history of man,
all the people on this Earth
are truly one.
Sir, I have to ask you to go back
and in the public entrance.
I'm very sorry.
Tours leave on the hour.
Well, maybe not today.
But you never know,
I might come back another time.
I'd do it. People get a buzz
from being up there.
I'll bet they do.
Do I know you, sir?
No, I don't believe so.
You look familiar.
Well, I'd better be off.
Right, sir. Back out
and around to the left.
SONG: # Wa-hoo
# Wa-hoo-hoo-hoo!
# Wa-hoo!
# On the wings of an eagle!
# I find myself
lifted through the skies!
# Lifted up above the world
to sing!
# On the wings of an eagle!
# I find myself
lifted through the skies!
# Lifted up above the world
to sing
# Can you see me?
# As the days roll on
When the nights get long
# The changing of the seasons
# And the falling autumn leaves
They bring me down
# They bring me down
( INSTRUMENTAL BREAK )
# Do you lose your way
in the middle of the day?
# Do you see
your brother crawling?
# And all the while
was calling out for help from you
# Wa-hoo
# Wa-hoo-hoo-hoo
# On the wings of an eagle
# I find myself
lifted through the skies
# Lifted up above the world
to sing
# On the wings of an eagle
# I find myself
lifted through the skies
# Lifted up above the world
to sing
# Can you see me?
Subtitulado por _Hosen_
hosen@fibertel. com. ar
( 'THE DISH' THEME MUSIC PLAYS )