Sailing love would make you
rich, is what my mother told me.
Just not involving the heart.
INSPIRED BY A TRUE STORY...
Eight, seven, six, five,
four three, two, one.
Damn happy new year.
We know that this is
the best country in the world...
And I'm the luckiest man
in the world, sit and listen.
What's with this fucking country?
Yes, the great temple of happiness,
Jews in preference.
Give him a round of applause.
Let's make some money.
This here is the machine more
revolutionary world.
Who wants some of this?
It's the best.
Digging fingernails are dirty...
And the good machine is still working.
There's no business without a machine.
Oh, well, and taught enough.
Ok, guys.
Some fun,
forward with the music.
Wait, wait,
"Nobody is going to make a toast?
Charlie, go back a moment.
Sorry, do not get mad,
but everyone knows that you do not lose
nothing... and that's the best you have.
Now try to ignore, is a bit
shy but if you ask nicely.
I'll stay here.
Grace is the new year, see here.
Sorry, I am giving guidance,
someone has to work here.
Hold this.
Ok.
My third leg.
Do not think I'm crazy
Eh, darling? - Happy New Year.
The first kiss in the new year.
Samantha.
Ok, baby, I have to go.
Warren. Happy New Year to all.
Hello, happy new year, we are on
that music, all for fun.
Are you having fun?
You...
Ok, soldier. - This bitch
have to give me what I want.
You're a damn fool.
Just like you.
Come on, baby, put on clothes
I invite you a drink.
I'm not going to get for what I paid.
Do not pay for garbage.
I'll have it anyway.
Warren. - Please
let go, leave me alone.
Care, Warren, has a knife.
Has a knife, get out of here.
Go away and not come back,
Get out of here.
Return.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Recedes.
Care.
Quiet.
Easy.
Recedes.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, Charlie. Sorry.
This fucking cut you eh? And
now ruined my damn guitar.
Charlie, you okay?
I'm fine, I am.
How are you? Are you okay?
I can not wait to start the new year.
Come on, do not let
it affects us, please.
Come on, we have
encourage us, to continue the party.
We, free drinks for everyone.
Did you hear that?
Free drinks for everyone.
Happy New Year.
That great way to
damn start the new year.
Oh, Charlie, I'm exhausted.
I'm too damn tired.
But I have to fix that problem
with the fucking shit man.
Maybe I can... no, I have to go.
Sorry. - Ok.
Please pay the bill.
Are you having fun? Because
we can do together.
I'm cracking as this damn town.
"Another test? A second opinion.
I could be wrong."
No, you know everything.
Happen everyday problems
all are things each day.
No, I'm tangled up.
No Love Bad
news, not before dinner.
Speak of the devil and he appears to be.
And then how would you spend,
good or bad? - Well, I guess.
Where do we go, Charlie? I
go home. I have headache.
Oh, no, no. We have to see
that's what I said.
What do you mean?
To which I said, do not listen,
I told you about nine times.
Remember what I told you Bruza?
Who?
Armando Bruza, boxer Argentina
I saw betting.
I was losing like crazy.
Oh, no, again.
What is this place?
It sure where the fire burns.
I stay in the car. - No, this
our place belongs to us.
Lower your truck back, Grace.
I will not go anywhere if you wear that hat.
This hat cost me $ 300, baby.
Who do you think you are?
"Claein Viscutt?
Does the damn queen of England?
It smells, it's good, honey.
Sure, like if we keep
bodies in a pool.
I love this, baby.
Charlie, I need here.
Grace, you're my wife, is not
well? This Bruza not anyone.
If he wins fights, I win.
Is fifth in the world
in the first division...
And I have two fights on the way
then I will give one with Muhammad Ali.
Oh, Charlie, not again.
Hey, do not do that again.
Do not you realize, honey?
This will leave around the country...
And you know, dear, that if I
my hands on these guys,
no one will achieve
what I can do.
The Ranch of Love, come,
Sweetheart, we celebrities.
Come on, baby, you can
do so. Hey, Prado.
Can you call me Dan?
That's my name, not Prado.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
How is everything?
This boy is not so good, no
much paste, it may be easier to defeat.
For mejorémoslo. I talked to
Liz and people are interested.
Bruza, hey, my man.
Charlie, man.
You look very well. Brought to a
of these tiny you, eh?
One of those damned whores.
I brought my wife.
What?
That I brought my wife.
Oh, your wife.
Do all your head get in there?
Like the Beatles,
but you know, I am country
any damn famous Beatle.
I am more beloved than Perón
and his whore wife, eh?
Come here, Grace,
will not hurt you, come here.
Hi, Bruza,
the wild bull of the Pampas.
I know it's great, ma'am.
The pleasure is all mine.
Ok, all here, girls.
Samantha already.
IRINN.
Alana.
Cristina.
You.
You, girl.
Yes, lady.
That there.
Ok. Thank you very much, that
have a good time.
Come here, do not stop,
do not stop, go slower.
Then last night I had this guy...
Just in time and says
who wants it from behind...
And you know I am accessible but
I said we needed to negotiate.
They always want something for free.
They think they can forget
all in fun.
You came into my room.
I covers the TV.
Can you move?
Went to my room and stole.
I know it was you.
"I went to your room?"
Oh, my god, you're crazy
maybe you lost and do not remember.
Give it back or I will tell Charlie.
Oh, no.
He will say to Charlie, I have fear.
"You're kidding?"
Yesterday was new year, do you think
Charlie has time for you?
A small space, for sure.
Have you made you do that pose a dog?
Something and bark.
Hey, when I did, was very good
me, let me stay with the collar.
Calla.
Even I use it on my appointments, it's nice.
Ok, damn dogs. Charlie and I
we are together, he said he loved me.
Do you love? That's very sweet.
You're fuckin 'crazy, out
of my way. - Bitch.
Damn bitch, you broke my dress.
Do not mess with me.
Enough, girls.
She started.
Do not touch me again.
Enough.
Yes, come on.
Damn old hag.
We will discount $ 500.
500?
What does she do?
I will tell Charlie.
Go tell Charlie, but I'm
the boss here, do not forget, okay?
I make the rules. If you want to stay
here you'll do as I say, okay?
That bitch broke my dress.
Really? Who?
You know what? I will make the
Next, I bought one at Kmart.
Come on, go to your room.
Ok, the show is over.
Okay, Grace.
Hey good?
I have everything ready to
boys. - Listen
the next time I steal something
and gave it to one of your bitches,
I'll break your hands as you have no idea,
to see if you ever steal something from my closet.
Oh, come on, baby.
Do not treat me like a tramp.
Charlie hurts, it hurts me and bothers me
you do it in front of my nose.
You know how it work, come on.
Do you have to do with the ranch?
It has nothing to do with the ranch.
If you have nothing to do with
the ranch what the hell is?
The ranch is not the only
shit in the world, ok?
Grace, I know.
Tell me what it is.
Remember that boy
works with the election commission?
He says there are complaints people
of the church, we need to talk.
Hi, Grace.
Hello.
Honey, talk after that, sorry.
Are you Charlie? Is it good time?
I, Bruza.
Do you remember me? Is the fighter?
Oh, I remember, the wild bull.
Yes, that, could you please
to help me with my stuff?
Do your stuff? What things?
Charlie did not tell him?
No.
No, Charlie did not tell me.
I'll move with you.
Bruza, my champion.
Hey, Charlie, good to see you.
What is this Charlie
shit is dumb here?
That's right,
will move here to farm.
What?
It's good for business.
What the hell, telling me
what is good for business?
Oh, come on.
Look, if there is a problem.
No problem, right, Grace?
Looks a little angry.
No, not angry, are
women's things, you know.
Come here, I want to show something.
Come on, bring those bags for me.
What is it?
Stay there.
Girls, come on.
These are Samantha and Angel.
He is the champion, will teach the
quarter of a leopard, you know what I mean?
Leopard Room "?
The fourth of leopard.
Come on Tiger, all yours.
Ok, let's go.
Hey, Grace, what's going to talk
well, compared to that damn stupid?
That boy.
What? You mean the contract?
Paid for their bets, how much?
Virtually nothing. Maybe $ 15,000.
Oh, well, fifteen for you.
You gave that idiot 25 large,
then we'll go 50 and 50, Charlie,
Gave him 25 grand in my pocket.
No, it is not.
Oh, I misunderstood.
Yes.
Oh, let's see then.
Oh, come to the ranch, eat,
have sex with all girls,
do not pay a dime is not it?
No.
Now, listen,
you can act like you want out there
who want to fuck
and smoking all your shit
but here is different.
Do not take what is mine
if you touch mine, fuck you
to where you have no idea.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Really? Do you think?
You really believe that.
Oh, Charlie.
Who the hell do you think? - Oh, no,
the phone, I need it. Sorry.
I'm sorry, okay?
Why the hell did you say that?
Sorry.
Maybe you're right with the boxer, I
I'm just here with bills and all...
And I have no idea that a whore, ok?
Grace, Grace.
Do not I always right in these
things? - Yes, yes, all the time.
Ok, look, you want a new
toy? You have a new
but do not have to stay at the ranch.
Can not stay somewhere else?
I told you, there will be many papers,
be stupid, do you want?
No, I do not want.
Grace, I do not know if you know what that means
for me, for us, going to Vegas...
And all those idiots...
Say, "Charlie, you can
get me tickets for the fight?
Charlie, come to my restaurant and
bring your beautiful wife, and then...
Please welcome...
heavyweight champion of the world.
Promoted by Charlie...
And his beautiful wife, Grace.
You have all my life in your hands.
You're a damn fool, Charlie.
I try to be more
every day, hear one more thing.
That boy, Prado.
Prado? Who's Prado?
Prado or whatever,
the coach or manager,
which met in
the gym the other day
do not trust him so I stayed
that you would be their new manager.
What?
Yes.
Are you out of it?
Honey, I told you, is business,
we must protect.
Why do not you do it?
I can not, need
a license, I'm a convict.
What I have to assume that
do? "Fasten gloves?
You do not have to do that
simply sign
go to the fights, sitting
in his corner and all.
No need to charge the gloves.
Oh, you're amazing.
We are incredible
Sweetheart, I have to go to the city.
Not much.
Charlie is the owner of this?
Yes, it is enriched, while
these people live.
Smart.
We see that democracy works.
Charlie held this and next
the ranch is stable.
Charlie wants to give you this.
Use it to pay for a hotel in Reno or
Stay here and you can save.
I'm staying here.
Love Ranch, where all
fantasies become reality.
How I can help?
Pink bag.
Fifteen.
One time, baby, Grace.
Take this left him in the morning.
These are good times.
It's crazy to work here outside in the snow.
What do you mean? Are you or
not a rematch against Ali?
Charlie wants you here.
Go to Reno, there is a gym.
Charge and silver.
Sorry but I do not move here.
It sucks.
I need to get something to his wife.
We need to eat, right?
I think it's a good use of the ranch.
Are you sure that tree
may be subjected to all this bag?
Hey, I thought I wanted to talk.
Sorry about yesterday, did not know
you did not know I would.
Charlie explained everything to me,
No need to worry.
I sleep well anywhere.
Exercising not have that here,
You can go inside if you want.
I'd rather be here, I
like to be in, no offense.
Here I feel free.
Yes, do not feel very free.
I do not care what he says
Charlie, he works with the girls.
So you ignore me, ok?
Will you help me?
Help you what?
It is my manager, must
have me ready for the fight.
Oh, no, I said to Charlie,
this is crazy.
It is my manager, is supposed to help.
Listen, I have too
things to do.
As accounts and troubleshooting.
I do not like working alone.
I feel lonely.
A big boy like you.
Yes, a big boy like me.
I need people to talk to.
C'mon, it's easy, teach, observe.
Hit so
and you say well ok?
Come on, say, say it.
Well.
Right now hitting well.
You say it works well.
Oh, this is stupid.
No, not stupid, we say so.
Say: it works well.
Works well.
There you go. Now you train me,
is all he did the other man,
so I gave the other 30%.
One last thing to do...
And you say, do not get tired.
Do not tire, we will say so.
Come on, say so.
Do not get tired.
There you go. He saw that easy. I look
and I exercise for ten minutes.
One last thing, hold the bag.
What?
Go to the other side and hold the bag.
Are you kidding? Hit me.
No, quiet, come on.
Please.
Give me the stick, come on.
Ok.
Do you feel that?
You're crazy.
Do you really think so?
Hey, his staff.
I have to work, follow
hitting the bag, okay?
Bruza.
In Argentina you are a king, a champion.
You do not belong here.
Black, is exactly what I do.
Dress, surviving...
We're going to be up again.
These people are not going to get
champion, the old is pimp.
Come home, Bruza.
If God forgives you
forgive yourself.
What God?
I talked to the sister of Carmela.
Nobody blames you. Nobody.
Listen to one thing
What the hell's wrong with your head?
What Carmela Carmela or what?
I will not go, Do you hear?
Do you understand?, You laburo is...
My laburo is take care of you.
I worry about my own life.
Fuck.
I do not talk like that.
Do you think that this ranch will surrender?
It's a damn shit. Huh?
It's disgusting, the client
read it, remove all, come on.
Not just the posters, Charlie.
Oh, yeah?
What do you mean, little man?
Do not forget for whom you work.
Help him.
Quick, I have to do
more things with that Tom Macy.
Ok, folks, only two,
are lucky to buy
at this low price.
It is one of the best, good luck.
I like it.
Is it 375, right?
No, the kitchen is 475 and
double garage, pretty architecture.
I think there's someone inside.
No, dear, let us talk with Mr. Macy.
Let me tell you something, folks, if you
made today, it might be good with the price.
There's someone inside.
It's a nice room.
Perhaps the ghost guard.
I was still here.
Feel at home, give him a
look, feel comfortable, okay?
I love this.
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, you gotta get outta here.
Leave it with me
little friend, listen,
Do you think you can mock
me and fuck me in business?
Think you can do
that? Is it what you thought?
Bastard, "believed to
make fun of me and do what you like, eh?
And tease me from falling,
but that will never happen.
You hear me? And now you take all
against me or fuck you without mercy.
Do you understand? Do you understand?
Do you understand?, Ok,
it's all good, man.
It's all good,
all right, all right.
You have 45 days or I'll firewood.
Will be best for the business,
better to stop, you know?
Yes, Charlie, I understand.
Yes.
Look good,
now go to those poor people and now
you know you should do is for your benefit.
Great folks.
In five, four three, two...
And for a referendum on the legalization
of prostitution, then...
We have the following
invited to discuss this.
Miss Mary Fynch of
Nevada Family Association...
And Charles Bontempo's' Rancho
Love ', the legal brothel.
You should feel very proud of his
person, a great place for fun.
Someone is enjoying a good
time now, do not you think?
It is the moral pollution of our
company operated by people like you.
Mr. Bontempo, the way it happens.
Always have to bring God,
I hate when they do,
is so bad that they put in the church.
Is all this crap they have there.
If I go to hell
go to hell, baby,
I do not care what you say that witch.
Oh, I have to mention that it was
cute in a way, all that.
I even think I could put him
hand and enjoy your beautiful bottom.
Now you changed your mind,
course.
You think so? - Listen
we have another letter from the AROS.
Want to review the books.
"Good or bad? Was
easier when we were illegal."
Only used to enjoy all
money in our pockets.
Yes, but do not count those secrets
or we get into trouble.
Hey, do me a favor, do not act like
if you had not ever stolen anything, ok?
If this keeps happening I will not be
the need to hold the bag.
Do not worry too much or
will give you a heart attack.
I have to leave the ring, I need
to fight for food.
Hey, Charlie.
What the hell are you doing here?
This is private.
Oh, I did, sorry.
I did not know, sorry.
It's great this view.
Yes, this is where I come to relax.
Yes, I can see why.
I had the idea when I was in Folsom.
Folsom?
Yes, in prison, you can see everything.
Yes, it looks all
from here.
The main center.
Yes What?
I told you I'm sorry.
Yes, well, happens.
Let me show you something, you see
this?, it's great, now I see.
Stay here and see if
may have good luck.
That.
Go.
I came as a dream
a star, so suddenly.
You see this?, With some lights will be great...
And no matter how far you are,
you will see the Ranch of Love.
Do not touch it, this is genuine,
great job, it can collapse.
That is, will the new 'Ranch
Love 'anything.
It's great, Charlie.
Thanks.
You know? I never had anything like
this, no place to go.
You're a champion who makes money.
Oh, money.
The beams and you lose, you
a great life, Charlie, you have.
Yes, depending on how you see it, you know?
I mean, I've also left things behind.
You mean to children?
Nothing is equal, all life
change in an instant.
I'll never have my own team
football and say get out to destroy them.
My son...
Do you have a baby doctor?
A great doctor, Grace raised him well.
What about you? Have children?
Yes, in Argentina.
Oh, look.
But I do not see a long time ago.
Why?
Because it is complicated.
Hey, bunny, the champion and I
we have a little talk here.
Back in twenties.
Did you see Charlie?
No, I saw all day.
There are a liar do you?
Not really.
I'm a big liar.
"That bitch has my busy man?"
Nor tell, I'm used
this shit. - Mrs.
You and Charlie are a great team.
Yes, of course, are the best.
I see that you two are great, I know.
Someday I'll have a place like this.
Is that your ambition? Great.
I travel around the world
sometimes they do not know where I am,
but here I feel great.
You and Charlie are like
Dad and Mom and...
Girls do not like sisters...
but they are great.
How did they do with Charlie,
all this?
You mean I'm doing
in a place like this? Leave me alone.
Oh, no, please, it's serious.
It's easy, my mother was a bitch.
Your mother?
Do you mind?
Maybe.
They are so predictable. - How much
Charlie takes time with that girl?
A week.
That's not your problem or did it?
Well I care a bit.
You are a fucking sick.
Maybe.
Are not you supposed to
should be training?
Then go do it.
This is a great fight, here we all
to witness something spectacular
and is with us
Bruza to prove it.
And we see Muhammad Ali
see that is no match for Bruza.
Ali and I hope to come and see me
I must be who fight,
and not that clown white.
Bruza, what answer that?
All bring flowers to the next.
What do you mean?
It will be a funeral,
Colter small funeral.
I'm not white, I am Argentine.
For white light for me.
Billy Little white. - I will teach the
next month differences in the ring.
Not even know what it is
a ring, small white idiot.
Mr. Colter, in my business
those who say that have large,
is because the are small.
She is the manager, guys.
Very good, huh?
Who is that old? Your mother?
This ugly and dirty prostitute.
You no longer stand it, whitey.
Then jumped to Bruza
defend your honor? That's sexy.
Nobody had done for me.
You're wrong.
Once my ex put a coat on the floor
not to get dirty, but it was my coat.
Who is it? Go ahead.
And managed all the roles.
Honey, that's fantastic.
The system is best with 35,
but only for medical benefits.
How I'll take care of the twins?
Did you go to school for three years
to provide the best for your children...
And you sit back
accepting what they give you?
I like it here, Grace,
I feel safe,
outside is different
I do not trust anyone.
I will easy for you.
What is this?
Your payment, you're fired.
What?
Take it, go to your truck.
Give the best for your children,
you can come back in six months
and be happy
but now packed and get out of here.
Come on.
Thanks, Grace.
No problem.
What?
I had a flash.
I see you and
Bruza floating on stage
and then behaving Charlie
like an idiot with his rope magic.
You look crazy. - Yes, but
let me ask you something, Grace.
Did you you were unfaithful to Charlie?
I do not know if you noticed but that
piece out there is very sexy.
That's just like someone else.
Charlie negotiated with him by the thousands.
Good for him.
Sorry, it's my money too.
Money is money. Have fun
a little, you will not live forever.
We saved by the bell.
A little love
your dog is coming.
You have to admit, since
he's here have more energy
a little more of that pump
a little love to the youth.
I tell you.
Think about it.
Do not get tired.
I should not teach you that word.
Here's what to do,
this in a fashion icon,
this is a corset Japanese
all original design.
Girls, this is great
money in the bank.
Glad you like.
This is my magical piece and form
a spectacular body for you.
Are you tired?
Looks like something.
Not so much a mile and a half.
Ok, but I need a break.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Need more practice if you want to win.
What's there? "On the other side?
I do not know more of the same,
maybe a couple of coyotes.
Maybe you did not see the right person.
Really? And who is that?
"Mr. Wild diapers?
"Diapers?"
You are very funny.
Love you, Grace.
Well, it's my job.
Yes, it's part of your job.
Yes, but do not relax much, get up
my car. More respect, please.
I wonder if the drivers are...
Mind dying as
left for the animals.
Maybe not as good.
Tell me something about yourself and your mother.
Finally the big question
about whether I am a bitch as my mother.
The answer is no.
My mother said that in his work
there was more money than any other,
so I had my first house at 20.
I started my business without being legal...
And one day I met three girls.
He saw me and dropped it.
Do not know what to do and waved.
Charlie?
Yes, him. He told me he was not interested
girls, he was interested in seeing me.
Then we rented a house
he had this plan to make it illegal.
He said that would be illegal, we would not have
the police with his hands around.
Visitors leave enough money.
He was right.
Yes, he was right.
I was thinking about the ranch and
need to change many things now.
Oh is it serious?
If, for example...
I do not know why you let your
girls not care, it is not sexy.
Remain dirty after
sex, I heard that and got my thing.
So remind me of washing
the mouth at all when you return.
I have many ideas for
make the farm better.
May be called El Rancho de Bruza.
No, it should not be called that, should
Grace called the Ranch and Bruza.
Oh, well, Charlie is not going to like it.
Charlie?
Yes, of course, who needs to Charlie?
You see, Grace? We think alike.
We are a good team.
You know, you still do not know why
even with that little man.
It goes whenever she wants
with that girl.
It sickens me how you question.
You do not love, Grace, a woman
you can not love someone like him.
We can be just you and me.
Go.
What?
Get out the fucking car, go, go.
You think I'm so stupid?
Ok, I'm going out, quiet.
Come on, Grace,
come on, Grace, come on.
Not what I meant.
I'm sorry. Grace!
Shit.