This will be the final
boarding call for flight 2...
to London, Heathrow.
Okay.
I'm not even
gonna say it, Kate.
Then it'll be
like I never left.
Okay?
Wait.
I have a really bad feeling
about this.
About the plane?
You think it's gonna crash?
Don't say that.
No. Look, I know that we've
talked about this a thousand times,
and we agreed that going to
London was the right thing to do.
But in my heart...
this feels wrong.
Don't go, Jack.
You mean don't go at all?
Well, what...
what about my internship?
Believe me, I know... I know what an
incredible opportunity this is for you.
For us, Kate.
Right, for us.
But I'm afraid that if you
get on that plane... Look.
We're at the airport. Nobody ever
thinks clearly at the airport.
So we should just trust
the decision we already made.
You've been accepted to one of the
best law schools in the country.
I've got this internship at Barclay's
Bank. We have a great plan, honey.
You wanna do something
great, Jack?
Let's flush the plan. Let's
start our lives right now, today.
I mean, I have no idea what
this life is gonna look like,
but I know that it has the both
of us in it, and I choose us.
The plan doesn't
make us great, Jack.
What we have together,
that's what makes us great.
- I love you, Kate.
- I love you too. I do.
And one year in London
is not gonna change that.
A hundred years
couldn't change that.
Experts are predicting
a mild rally in the bond market.
Last night was incredible.
Huh?
I said, last night was great.
You are
an amazing lover.
Thanks.
You're not bad yourself.
- I wanna see you again.
- I'd like that too.
Tonight.
It's Christmas eve, Jack.
So? I'll pour
eggnog over you.
- I have to go visit
my parents out in Jersey.
Jersey? Do you have any idea
what the traffic's gonna be like?
That's why I'm taking
the train.
It was nice
meeting you, Jack.
Mrs. Peterson.
Hello, Jack.
You don't have to stop singing on my
account. Oh, it's because I'm shy, Betty.
So, when are you gonna leave that old
corpse, Mr. Peterson, and run away with me?
You know you could never
satisfy me the way he does.
Ah.
Merry Christmas,
Mr. Campbell.
How'd you make out
this year, Tony?
About four grand, and a bottle
of 25-year-old Scotch from 9D.
I'm putting it all in
commercial paper like you said.
Good, but just until
the deutsche mark turns.
- Thank you, Mr. Campbell.
- All right.
Good morning, Joe.
Merry Christmas, sir.
Campbell wants these
available. Thanks, Adelle.
Better you than me.
If MedTech shares fall
any lower than 43,
we're in trouble
with the stock valuations.
So for God's sake, please watch what
you say to your institutional customers.
We still have almost a full day of trading
before zero hour, and I don't want any trouble.
A penny for
your thoughts, Alan.
Hmm? Oh, God, I'm sorry.
Jack, I was thinking about,
you know, Dee and the kids.
I promised I'd be home for
dinner. It's Christmas eve, Jack.
Oh, is that tonight?
You think I like being
here on Christmas eve, Alan?
No. Well, maybe.
Okay.
Okay, maybe I do have a touch of
tunnel vision this holiday season.
But in two days
we're going to announce...
one of the largest mergers
in U.S. Corporate history.
When a deal like this turns up, you get
on it and you ride it till it's over.
You don't ask it
for a vacation.
December 26. After that there'll be
so much money floating around here,
it'll be like Christmas
every day.
December 26, people. If you'd like to
celebrate that day, you all have my blessing.
- You're right. I'm sorry.
- I don't want you to be sorry. I want you to be excited.
I want my gift to you to be the first
gift you open this year. You know why?
- Because my gift comes
with ten zeroes.
You're right.
I'm focused. I'm there.
Good man. Everybody, turn to
page 12 in your prospectus.
You have six messages. Two of them
are imperative. Whoa. I'm going home.
I'm not even here now. Good night.
Merry Christmas. Merry Christmas.
It's only 8:30. I'm disappointed.
Got some last-minute shopping to do?
You too? This holiday's about giving. I'm
giving everything I've got to this deal.
So in a way, I'm more Christmassy than
anybody. You're my role model, Jack.
Oh, and Oxford called.
Ooh, my suits are ready.
- Mm-hmm.
- Care for a Lifesaver?
No, thank you.
Help yourself.
Kate Reynolds. Her assistant said you
could reach her at home after 8:00.
Kate Reynolds was
my girlfriend in college.
I almost married her.
You?
Married?
Almost married.
And almost a broker at
E.F. Hutton. Excuse me?
She didn't want me
to go to London.
We're standing at the airport saying
good-bye, and she asked me to stay.
So you left her.
- Wasn't easy.
- Oh, stop it. I'm getting all weepy.
I took the road
less traveled, Adelle.
And look where it took ya. I'm
gonna get this gal on the phone.
Nope. You almost married this woman.
You're not even curious
why she called?
She's probably just having
a fit of nostalgia.
Lonely Christmas eve. Called the one that
got away. Why call her back and mislead her?
This happened
a very, very long time ago.
8:35 on Christmas eve.
Jack Campbell still
at his desk.
Now there's
a Hallmark moment for you.
Peter, I don't see you
rushing home to trim the tree.
That's because I'm a heartless
bastard who only cares about money.
Well, you know what?
God love you for that.
Got a call
from Terry Haight.
Bob Thomas is nervous.
That'll happen when you're about to
spend $130 billion on some aspirin.
Somebody's gotta
nurse him through this.
Why are you staring
at my breasts, Peter?
I need you, tiger.
Where is he?
- Aspen.
- Call Aunt Irma and tell her I won't be able to make it.
You're a credit
to capitalism, Jack.
Hey, Peter, let me
ask you a question.
An old girlfriend calls you out
of the blue on Christmas eve.
- What do you do?
- You suddenly having trouble getting dates?
- Yeah.
- Leave it in the past.
Old flames are like
old tax returns...
put 'em in the file cabinet for three
years, and then you cut 'em loose.
I'll leave from my office
tomorrow in the afternoon.
Call the group. Schedule an
emergency strategy session for noon.
That'll be a nice
little holiday treat.
Good night, Frank.
Hey, Mr. Campbell.
Why didn't you call down? I
would have had Joe get your ride.
I'm thinking I'll walk tonight.
It's a nice night for it.
I'll send your car home
for you. That'll be fine.
- And Merry Christmas to you, sir.
- To you too.
Eggnog? Yeah, dairy case. Five dollar.
Okay.
Hey, yo. Y'all do the lotto here,
right? Y'all do the lotto here?
Yeah. Cool. 'Cause I got a
winner, baby. I got a winner.
Certified, good as gold. I know lotto keep
a lot of brothers down, but not Cash Money.
Don't do me none, son,
'cause I'd be like...
Bang on the lottery! You know
what I mean? It's all good.
Relax, son. Relax. I got you
four numbers. Check it. Bust it.
6, 14, 16, 49.
That's a winner, son.
$238, B.
Cheddar coming.
Give me my money. I'm sorry. Your
ticket bad. You draw in the lines.
What are you talking about, B? You draw in
the lines with a pencil. I know about this.
Yo, buster, check the
ticket, son. No, you get out.
Yo, you ain't even looked at the ticket.
You lookin' at me, son. Check the ticket.
You get out now! You take
the ticket somewhere else!
Next customer in line!
You get out or I call 9-1-1.
Oh, my God!
Check the ticket, stupid.
Look at the ticket. Shit, now
I'm gonna make you call God.
That's my word. You best check that
ticket, fool! Let me see the ticket.
Was I talkin' to you?
Maybe I'll buy it from you. You
know, make a little business deal.
Stupid-ass white boy in $2,000 suit gets
capped trying to be a hero. News at 11:00.
That's what you wanna see? You wanna see
Cash up in here? You want me to set it, son?
Do you wanna die?
Do you want to die?
No.
Look, I'm talking about
a business deal.
Okay? I buy the ticket
from you for $200.
I take it to a store where the guy behind
the counter doesn't have a death wish.
I just made myself
a quick $38.
Like I said, it's...
it's just a business deal.
All right. Yeah.
All right.
You blew it, B.
You blew it.
The ticket was real.
Damn, you had your chance too.
Come on, Jack.
Let's get out of here.
How'd you know my name
was Jack?
I call
all you guys Jack.
Here. Nice doing
business with ya.
Hey. Hey, um...
What do you want to carry
that gun around for anyway?
You're just gonna wind up
doing something you regret.
You're talking to the wrong
person about regrets, Jack.
I mean, there must be programs
out there and, um, opportunities.
Wait a minute. Are you
actually trying to save me?
This is bananas.
This man thinks
I need to be saved, yo!
Well, everybody
needs something.
Yeah? Well, what
do you need, Jack?
Me? You just said,
everybody needs something.
I got everything I need.
Wow. It must be great
being you.
I'm not saying that you'd be able to do it
without some hard work, some honest hard work,
and possibly some medicine.
You know, I'm gonna
really enjoy this.
You just remember that
you did this, Jack, okay?
You brought this
on yourself.
Merry Christmas.
Mmm, ten more minutes, Jack.
It's Christmas.
Never mind.
- Who's here?
- Rise and shine.
Don't you think
we should open some presents?
- I think you should give Mama five more minutes in bed.
- Come on, Dad. Get up.
Can we do that? Yea! It's Christmas!
- It's Christmas!
- Look, your sister's jumping on the bed.
What is this dog doing on the
bed? He needs to get off the bed.
Did Santa come? I don't
know. We'll have to go see.
- Let's go see the presents.
- You wanna get some presents?
Mommy just needs
to wake up.
Jack. Strong coffee.
Oh, Jack.
Merry Christmas, dear.
Lorraine. Ed.
Hey, Jack, you old bird dog.
Merry Christmas to ya.
Talk to him. One day a year
away from the Ponderosa.
- I don't think that's asking too much.
- This is who I am.
Tell her, Jack, for God's sake. You're
the only one around here that gets me.
- I need some eggnog.
- 'Course you do, sweet thing. Almost 8:00 in the morning.
Excuse me. Where you going, Jack?
Josh, Annie, giddyup! Where's
my car? Where's my Ferrari?
What?
Where's my Ferrari?
What the hell are you talking... What's
he talking about? You got a Ferrari?
Let me borrow your car and then
I promise I'll have it returned.
My Caddy?
Drive your own damn car.
Oh, just let him borrow your
precious Cadillac, for God sakes.
There's a perfectly good minivan
sitting out there in the driveway. Here.
What the hell's wrong
with him anyway?
- Tony, thank God!
- Sorry, pal. Entrance is for residents and guests only.
What? What are
you talking about?
Jack Campbell, penthouse "C."
What's the matter with you? Uh-huh.
Mrs. Peterson, I think there's
something wrong with our man Tony here.
Who is this man?
Oh, come on. What is going
on with you two this morning?
Is this like a, uh...
a Christmas joke?
"Who is this man?" Well, we're on
the co-op board together, Betty.
And we fought side by side
for garbage disposals.
And every morning we exchange
quasi-sexual witty banter.
Okay? Shall I call the cops?
I'm gonna call the cops.
No, I'm gonna call the cops!
You're scaring me.
- No, no, no, no.
- Thank you for not calling the cops.
Now, I'm going upstairs, I'm gonna
get some sleep. Then I'll be fine.
Sleep you shall. Noblesse oblige
isn't dead. Not yet anyway.
Let's, um... Let's get you some help. Surely
there's a shelter somewhere in this city.
A shelter?
Hey, hey, are you
smacked out of your head?
I'm the richest man in this building!
I've got twice the square footage you have!
And I'm going upstairs.
Take a walk, pal.
Oh, not cool.
Not cool!
You wanna get cute?
Get cute.
I'm gonna go to my office. I'm gonna file
a complaint to the manager of the building.
I'm gonna have you fired, Tony. And, Mrs.
Peterson, you're on notice with the co-op board!
So you better just stop whatever
this is that you're doing!
Oh, yeah.
Oh. Oh, yeah.
Oh, come on!
Frank, you won't believe what's been
happening to me. Is Adelle here yet?
Hold it right there.
Where's Mintz?
The building is closed, pal.
You have to come back tomorrow.
Frank, why do I feel the need to remind
you that I'm Jack Campbell, President?
I don't care who you are. It's Christmas,
and like I told you, the building is closed.
I don't think
you heard me correctly.
I'm Jack Campbell.
Jack Campbell!
President!
Have a nice holiday, man.
- That's my car!
- Hi, Jack.
- You stole my car.
- I know this whole thing is really bizarre to you...
and you're feeling
quite shocked, but just hop in.
I'll explain everything
to you, okay?
Come on.
You're probably gonna wanna
buckle up, Jack. This thing moves.
- What's happening to me?
- Breathe into the bag, Jack.
This kind of thing makes a lot of guys
have to throw up. I seen it happen before.
So if you feel the urge, you roll
down the window and do it out there.
Try not to get
so worked up, Jack.
After all, you brought
this on yourself.
Brought what on myself?
I didn't do anything!
"I got everything I need. "
That sound familiar?
You mean 'cause you thought I was
cocky, I'm now on a permanent acid trip?
Bag yourself, Jack.
Oh, my God! Ah!
The way you intervened in that store last
night, you did a good thing there, Jack.
I mean, it was incredibly impressive
all the way across the board...
Oh, God! To the upper
echelons of the organization.
Please just tell me what's
happening to me in plain English...
without the mumbo-jumbo.
This is a glimpse, Jack.
A glimpse?
I... A glimpse of what?
You're gonna have to figure that out
for yourself and you got plenty of time.
- How much time?
- As much time as it takes,
which in your case is probably
gonna be considerable.
Okay, look, look. I-I-I
just want my life back, okay?
Now, what's it gonna take?
You wanna talk turkey?
Let's talk turkey.
How much money?
- It doesn't work like that, and I can't tell you why.
- Why not?
Because you have to figure
this thing out for yourself.
Are you listening to me? Figure it
out, figure it out. Figure out what?
- Let it come to you, man.
- I don't have time for this right now.
- I'm in the middle of a deal.
- Well, you're working on a new deal now, baby.
What's this?
Open it.
What is it,
some kind of a signal?
Will you come
whenever I ring it?
Now you gotta
get out of the car, Jack.
But what do I do? I'm sorry. I
can't spend any more time with you.
I got some other business I gotta take
care of. No, y-y-you did this to me.
You can't just
leave me like this.
Okay. Look, you wanna get some air?
Let's get outside, get some air.
We'll walk and I'll explain
everything to you, okay?
- Thanks, man.
- Sure.
Excuse me. Do you know
where Merrison Street is?
Jeannie.
I found Jack.
Oh, there you are, stranger.
Where you been?
You look terrible.
Truth is, I expected you.
Kate called and asked
if I knew where you were, so...
Oh, I put the Barcalounger in the center
of the room. It's throwing everybody off.
What do you think?
It's a great room.
Great room.
You and me, buddy,
we know how to live, huh?
Come on.
Come on, Jack.
Come on...
Whoo!
Come on, buddy.
Take your seat.
Are you okay?
I mean, you take off Christmas morning and
you don't tell anyone where you're going.
- We're friends?
- Talk to me.
I'm having kind of
a bad day.
You know, I read somewhere that the
suicide rate doubles during the holiday.
What am I saying that for? You
don't wanna hear that. Come on.
Is it...
Is it trouble at work?
I... I don't think so.
Well, it's not Kate,
is it?
You see, huh? It's like we're
inside each other's heads.
Kate's my wife.
Just keep saying it over and over again,
Jack, like a mantra. Keep saying it.
Look, you know,
you fit the profile exactly...
in your 30s, house, kids,
financial responsibilities.
You start thinking this
isn't the life I dreamt about.
Where's the romance,
you know?
Where's the joie de vivre?
Suddenly every lingerie ad
in the Newark Star-Ledger...
represents a life
that you can't have.
It's just two kids,
right?
Come on. Come on.
All right, sometimes it feels like you
gave up the whole world. I know that.
But look what you got.
Look at that: Four bedrooms,
two-and-a-half baths,
a partially finished basement.
And good kids.
Look. You know what?
You probably don't wanna
hear this right now.
But remember last summer when I almost had
that thing with Arnie, Jr. 's speech therapist?
You remember what
you said to me?
You said, " Don't screw up
the best thing in your life...
just because you're a little
unsure about who you are. "
Okay?
Go get 'em, tiger.
Could you hold on
a second?
Um, never mind because...
because he just walked in.
Thank you. Thank you.
Do you... have any idea
what you put us through today?
You walk out of here
at 7:30 in the morning.
You don't tell me where you're
going, or even that you're going.
And I don't see you
till hours later?
I called all of our friends. I had
the state troopers looking for you.
I was on the phone with the
hospital, for God's sakes.
What kind of man leaves his family Christmas
morning without a word about where he's going?
What kind of a man does
that, Jack? I don't know.
Could you... Could you please
stop yelling at me?
Where were you?
I was in the city.
The city?
New York City?
Yeah.
Why?
Because that's where I live.
Don't start, Jack. Don't.
Look, you don't understand.
I... I... I woke up
this morning here.
And this is very strange
because...
this isn't my house.
And those aren't my kids.
I'm not Dad.
I- I-I'm not a dad.
You're not my wife.
You know what, Jack.
It's not funny this time...
because I am really mad.
I mean, really mad.
I mean it.
I don't even...
What...
What's that?
I like it.
Thanks, Dad.
That's mine. Hey,
I need that back.
She took my bell.
You missed the whole thing...
the pancakes
and the presents.
You spent six hours putting
that bike together for Annie,
and then you didn't even get to see
the look on her face when she opened it.
You missed Christmas, Jack.
I'm sorry.
You know, we don't even
have enough time for this.
And at least you're okay.
I'm okay, we're okay.
But you've gotta get dressed for the
Thompson party. And you are not wearing that.
I don't care how hilarious
you think it is.
Party? No, I'm not
going to a party.
You look forward to this party all
year. What is it with you today?
Believe me, Kate. I really don't
think that going to a party...
is the right move for me
at the present time.
Okay, fine. You know what? Then
you just do whatever you wanna do.
What are you doing? Telling my mother
she doesn't have to stay with the kids.
Why not?
Because you'll be here.
I'll be ready in ten minutes.
This is... This is
just subpar.
Lance, here you go.
Excuse me.
Kate. Jack.
Evelyn.
Come in. Hey, everybody,
Kate and Jack are here.
Hey!
Jeannie.
Merry Christmas.
Jack,
Whoops.
Here.
So, like the dress?
Oh, it's lovely.
I thought I saw you notice
it at the kids' recital.
It's lovely.
There he is.
Hey, Jack. Happy holidays, man. Yeah.
Jack, come on over.
Hey, Jack.
Cheers, baby.
You guys see Van Horn last
night? Thirty-two points.
That kid's gonna take the Nets to the
championship. The Nets? Are you kidding?
They suck.
But they're due.
They're certainly due.
So, tomorrow's
the big day, Jackie.
Okay. Why?
My triple bypass.
I'm going under the knife
tomorrow. I told you that, right?
Triple bypass.
Yeah.
You really think you should
be eating all that? Eh.
Figure I'm going in
for a cleaning tomorrow.
Might as well load up on the
fried stuff tonight, right?
That's good thinking, Bill.
Have another drink.
Some fried pork, mashed potatoes.
He'll be dead by morning.
- How 'bout a cigar, Jack?
- Oh, no, thank you. I'm cutting down.
- Come on. They're American made, not Cuban.
- Oh, really?
Come on.
Very nice.
I thought you'd like 'em.
Mm. Mmm!
Superb.
How 'bout you, Arnie?
I'm all right. Thanks.
Finger food? No, thank you. I'm fine.
Come on. Soon as I put 'em
down, you're gonna grab a couple.
You always do.
No, I'm okay.
Let me. They will melt
in your mouth.
Yeah.
Good?
Fabulous.
At the end of this whole thing, she
made me this hand-embroidered sweater.
It was really lovely.
How nice.
So I'm slipping it on and I notice that
she's misspelled the word "lawyers. "
Uh-oh. I spent the entire
day walking around...
with a sweater that said,
"Nonprofit layers do it for free. "
So you're a lawyer?
A nonprofit lawyer?
Probono.
- You don't get paid at all? Nobody makes a dime?
- Jack?
"Anyhoo... "
I better go wake my mom.
There you go.
Uh, I don't think so.
- She's your dog, Jack.
- No, she's not.
You're right.
She's the kids' dog.
Maybe we should go wake Josh
and make him walk her.
If you take a dump sometime in this century,
then we could go home where it's warm.
If I can even remember
how to get home.
You remember,
don't you, girl?
Hello?
- Hey!
- What?
Oh. That baby's crying.
And?
Don't give me that look, Jack.
Tuesday's your day and you know it.
And listen, try and get Josh
to day care on time, okay?
Yeah.
All right.
Holy Mother of God!
Ohh!
You're not really
my dad, are you?
No, I'm not.
I work on Wall Street, you
know, with the big buildings.
I live in an apartment
with a doorman.
And I can buy
almost anything I want.
This isn't my life.
It's just a glimpse.
Where's my real dad?
I don't know.
But don't worry.
He loves you, and I'm sure
he'll be back very soon.
What are you doing?
They did a pretty good job.
Who did?
The aliens
in the mother ship.
You look just like him.
Oh, thanks.
Slightly better looking
though, right?
Oh, no, you're not gonna
start crying, are you?
I don't think I could
really deal with that right now.
Do you like kids?
On a case by case basis.
Do you know how
to make chocolate milk?
I... I think I could
figure it out.
Promise you won't kidnap
me and my brother...
and plant stuff
in our brains?
Sure.
Welcome to Earth.
This is where babies go when
their parents are at work.
Check.
Just push the red button.
Okay.
Do I get a receipt
or something?
I have winter camping till 4:00
and ballet class until 5:30.
5:30. Okay.
And try not to be late...
'cause kids don't like to be the
last one picked up. Got it. Good tip.
Bye.
- Hey, Annie. Where do I go now?
- Big Ed's.
Big Ed's Tires?
Why?
- 'Cause you work there.
- You mean I sell tires.
That's what I do.
I'm a tire salesman.
Good Lord!
- Morning, Jack.
- Hi.
- Good morning, Jack.
Hey, Jack.
Jack, my boy.
Hey, guess who I played
bridge with two nights ago.
Hell, you'll never guess.
One Sydney Potter. That's Sydney
Potter, C.E.O., BuyRite Transport.
Only the third biggest
trucking outfit in the state.
"Anyhoo," he's lookin'
for a new parts supplier.
We can handle volume
like that, now can't we, Jack?
I'm gonna have to
get back to you on that, Ed.
Right on.
Excuse me. Uh, do I... do I have a
private office somewhere in the building?
Sure, Jack.
Where is it?
Oh, uh, it's...
it's right back...
right back there.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
You must've needed this
every day.
What are you smiling about?
Eighty-eight?
I was in London in 1988.
You never went to London.
Jack, you're needed in mag
wheels. Customer waiting.
I was the number one junior sales
associate for E.F. Hutton in 1988.
Did you know that? Uh, no. No, I didn't.
That's great.
That's the kind of thing you
could really build on, you know?
Uh-huh. Yeah. I mean, sales has
always been a feeder for M&A. Always.
Uh-huh.
Well, look, here we are.
The mag wheels. Mag wheels.
Oh.
So.
Hey, Jack, um,
are you sure you're okay?
Well, I'm just a little confused
right now about why I work here.
Uh...
I just started here
last Tuesday, so...
The closing tip was
a mildly bullish plus-76.
Much of the market's action today was
fueled by the latest round of merger mania...
to hit Wall Street...
when Global Health Systems and MedTech
Pharmaceutical announced their intentions...
to join forces in a massive
$122 billion stock swap deal,
the largest ever
in the health care industry.
When asked about the possible
anti-competitive implications,
Global chairman Bob Thomas
referred reporters...
to P.K. Lassiter & Company president
Alan Mintz, the architect behind the deal.
- That's my deal!
- Ironically, Mintz first met Thomas at a Lamaze class.
While coaching their pregnant
wives, Mintz and Thomas... What?
Struck up a dialogue, and two months
later, the deal with MedTech was born.
He wasn't the architect!
I'm the architect!
Labor department officials announced today
that 275,000 new jobs have been created.
The kids are asleep.
The kids, hon.
Honey.
Sweetheart, I said
the kids are asleep.
That's just great. Those little
monkeys can be a real handful.
Hey, I was watching that.
Not tonight.
Please leave
my socks alone.
Wait.
- You want me.
- That is the general idea, yeah.
Oh, well, maybe we should
grab a bottle of wine first.
Kind of break the ice.
Yeah, that's very funny.
Look, it's 10:30.
By 11:00 you're gonna be
snoring like a monster,
but that's very sweet.
I'll remember that
for next time.
Whatever you say...
honey.
Yeah.
Oh, God, you're beautiful.
Thanks, Jack.
No, I'm serious.
You're really stunning.
This is good stuff.
I want you to keep this up.
You were always a very pretty girl in
college. There's no question about that.
But this...
You've really grown
into a beautiful woman.
How can you do that?
What?
Look at me like you haven't seen
me every day for the last 13 years.
Okay, wait. Don't move.
Don't look.
Stay right there.
I got something.
Good night, sweetheart.
Okay, we're almost
out of here.
Mary Janes, Mommy.
You promised.
That's right. I did
promise. Okay. All right.
We're gonna stop at the
kids' shoe department first,
and then I gotta pick up my
watch from the battery store.
Then I'm gonna go
to the linen store.
Why don't we go
to all the stores?
Every single store in this
godforsaken shopping mall.
Wouldn't that
be exciting?
You know what?
Why don't I take the kids,
and you just stay here and hang
out in the men's department?
Come on, hon.
It's perfect
for your frame.
Why don't you try it on?
I might want to take an
inch out of the back. Okay.
Lengthen the sleeve.
You look amazing
in that suit.
I mean, really...
wow!
Off the charts, great.
It's an unbelievable thing.
Wearing this suit actually makes
me feel like a better person.
I'm gonna buy it.
It's $2,400.
Are you out of your mind?
Come on, let's go.
She got those shoes.
Those shoes were $25.
Come on.
Take it off, all right?
We'll go to the food court and get
one of those funnel cakes you like.
Daddy's a crazy guy.
No.
Do you have any idea
what my life is like?
- Excuse me?
- I wake up in the morning covered in dog saliva.
I drop the kids off,
spend eight hours
selling tires retail.
Retail, Kate.
I pick the kids up,
walk the dog,
which, by the way,
carries the added bonus...
of carting away
her monstrous crap.
I play with the kids,
take out the garbage,
get six hours of sleep
if I'm lucky.
Then everything starts
all over again.
So what's in it for me?
Wh-Where are my Mary Janes?
You know, it's sad to hear that your
life is such a disappointment to you.
I can't believe it isn't
a disappointment to you!
Jesus, Kate, I could have been a
thousand times the man I became.
I could have been one of
the richest... Forbes...
How could you do this to me? How could
you let me give up on my dreams like this?
Really, I want to know.
Who are you?
All right, look.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I was such
a saint before...
and I'm such a prick now!
But maybe I'm just not...
the same guy that I was
when we got married.
You know what?
Maybe you're not.
Because the Jack Campbell I married
would not need a $2,400 suit...
to feel better
about his life.
But I'm telling you, if that's
what it's gonna take, then buy it.
Jesus! We'll take the money
out of the kids college fund.
Forget it.
We'll get a funnel cake.
It'll be the highlight
of my week.
Listen, I'm really sorry
about that back in the store.
I don't want to fight
with you.
I just sometimes wonder how
we ended up here, you know.
I mean, back in college,
d- did you see us here?
Life has thrown us a few
surprises. I'll give you that.
It really has, hasn't it?
Yeah. So, if you had to, what would
you say was the biggest surprise?
Just out of curiosity.
I'm just asking.
- Well, Annie, for one.
- Surprise, we're pregnant.
Yeah, that must have been.
I mean, that... that was. That
was a very unexpected moment.
- What are you gonna do?
- I think it turned out all right, don't you?
Yeah.
I really like Annie.
Well, good, Jack.
Maybe we'll keep her.
No, I love her.
I love Annie.
I'm just...
We had a lot of good times,
didn't we?
Do you remember the place on
Charles Street where we used to go?
Charles Street?
In the village?
When we were living
in Greenwich Village.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Great times. Great place.
Why did we ever leave?
You can't really raise a kid
in an apartment in the village.
Then there was the whole trek out to
the hospital. That didn't help either.
You were great. I mean, surviving
the heart attack was one thing.
- You had a heart attack?
- Hey, Jack, stop that.
'Cause I am...
I'm still mad at you.
Who knows what would have happened
if you hadn't stepped in at the store?
That's why I work
for Big Ed.
for Big Ed. Yeah.
So we had a baby,
Big Ed had a heart attack.
Bought that house, and I've
been workin' for him ever since.
Sayonara, Wall Street.
Our life in a nutshell.
If you want to
look at it that way.
How would you look at it?
A great success story.
What do you say, Jack? Show 'em how
to do it, baby. Jack, we need a strike.
- Damn!
- Jesus, Jack. What are you doin'?
It's a league match. Where's your
follow through? Where's your stance?
You know what?
I'm doin' the best I can.
It's okay, Jack.
Why am I so competitive
all the time?
You can still pick up that
spare. Crack 'em, Jack!
Here we go.
Hurt 'em.
Youre Jack Campbell.
You're better than the sport.
You shot the rapids in Kanai. You
ran with the bulls in Pamplona.
You've jumped out of an airplane over
the Mojave Desert, for Christ's sake.
You can do this.