- It's him, it's Dad. He's here.
- That'll be him now, Nelly.
- Here.
- About time, I've been worried.
Good lad.
Dad! I've been waiting for you.
Have you got my things?
- Have you got my whip?
- Easy, Cathy, hold on.
Did you get my Whip?
- Slow down.
- Where have you been?
- There you are, sir.
- Joseph.
Mr Earnshaw, sir.
We were worried, what with t'weather.
You're soaked through.
Come and sit by t'fire.
Get yourself warmed up, sir.
Hold on.
I've got a surprise for you.
Leave him.
I found him in the street.
Well, he had no one.
- So I thought...
- What'?
It was the Christian thing to do.
Say hello.
- Fairydog!
Shame on you, Catherine Earnshaw!
Go on!
Nelly, can you clean him up?
Let go! No.
Give me the jacket.
Just fuck off, Fairydog.
You ungrateful little...
Sleep well?
Move.
Are you hurt?
Can you understand me?
Come.
Come on!
That's a hen harrier.
That's a moorcock.
That's a lapwing, my favourite.
You say it. Lapwing.
Lapkwing.
Lapwing.
"For I will take you
from among the heathen"
"and gather you out of all countries"
"and will bring you into your own land."
"Then will I sprinkle clean water upon you
and ye shall be clean."
"From all your filthiness
and from all your idols,
will I cleanse you."
And what will be his name?
Heathcliff.
Heathcliff, do you reject Satan?
Come on.
No, lad.
Don't struggle, now.
Be still.
Hey, Heathcliff. Heathcliff!
Cathy?!
Cathy!
He's gone.
Close your eyes.
Come on, it's nice.
Open your mouth.
Heathens.
- God forgive you both. Eh?
- But we didn't...
Get to your room and shut up!
I don't want to see you again tonight!
Steady!
Come on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey!
- Steady.
Which one would you like, Heathcliff?
Eh? You need your own.
- The grey.
- Excellent.
Hindley, you can have the other.
Come on.
- Come on.
There's something wrong.
I think he's lame.
Where you going?
Give me your horse.
Fuck off, you dog.
Want me to show him what you do?
I'll tell him.
Take my horse, then, you damn gypsy.
I hope it breaks your neck
and kicks your fucking brains out.
Let me see.
I'm sorry.
You know, I've tried to teach you.
Tried to show you
how to be a good Christian.
I'd hoped you'd have treated him
like he was your brother.
He's not my
brother, he's a nigger.
You leave me no option, lad.
Hold your hand out.
Hand out!
Out!
Now get out of me sight.
I hope you don't feel pleasure at this.
Hey, look at me.
Joseph!
Come here!
- Here we are, lad.
- Give it here.
- Grab that.
- Look after yourself, Hindley.
An education'll be the making of you, lad.
- Go on.
- Take care, sir.
Safe journey, lad.
- In you get.
- Bye, Hindley.
- Mind how you go.
Ow!
- Dad!
- Cathy!
Bad child.
How can I love you?
I regret the day that you were born.
Go on, both of you.
Go and get out of those wet clothes.
- Hey!
And ask God to forgive you both.
Sing for us, Cathy.
Why can't you always be
such a good lass, Cathy?
such a good man, Father?
What the devil were that?
Go see to it, Heathcliff.
Just go! Go and fetch the doctor!
Will you just go now, woman?!
Right, Cathy. Come on, out!
Come on!
No, I'm not leaving my dad!
- Cathy!
- Cathy, get upstairs, will you?
- No! No! No!
Heathcliff! Take Cathy upstairs!
Now!
Let me see my dad!
It's Hindley.
He's got someone wi' 'im.
Hello, Hindley.
- Hey, good girl.
- You're home. Who's her?
Here we are, love.
Well... welcome home, sir.
Joseph, meet my wife, Frances.
- Pleasure to meet you, madam.
- Hello, Joseph.
You must both be cold and hungry
after all that, so let's get you inside.
- This is my sister, Cathy.
- Nice to meet you.
Who's this, Hindley?
Heathcliff.
- Come and help with the bags. Take 'em in.
- Hindley!
Don't start, Cathy. I'm in charge now.
Come on, let's go in.
- Did you hear me?
- Don't be so hateful, Hindley.
Your choice, nigger.
Work or leave.
Cathy.
Come on, choose. I'm waiting.
Come on, Cathy. Let's go inside.
Get the trunk.
When you've done that,
get your stuff and move in
with the animals where you belong.
You're a fucking idiot, Hindley.
Things are gonna change round here.
"He shall cover thee with his feathers
and under his wings shalt thou trust."
"Thou shalt not be afraid
of the terror by night,"
"not by the arrow that ﬂieth by day,"
"nor for the pestilence
that walketh in darkness,"
"nor for the destruction..."
I think they're the new people.
How do? Afternoon.
Is that the young black
Earnshaw found in Liverpool?
Might make some improvements.
- Still got trees to pull up then?
- Outside.
Bring this place up to date.
Aye, it needs it.
That'll do, Heathcliff.
Heathcliff.
Heathcliff!
I'm done here.
- Come on!
- The two of you will go to hell!
See you there, Joseph.
Useless, he is.
- Quick.
- Good for nothing!
You eat like a pig.
Ow!
No, it's not his fault,
I made him stop working!
Hindley, he's our brother!
Don't be stupid, look at him.
Stop it!
Cathy, go away!
You get off me!
Get off me!
You... No! No!
You know if our dad were still here,
he'd see what a hateful bastard you are
and he'd be ashamed of you!
- Leave him alone!
- Even the animals work round here.
You're here to work!
You'll work!
You OK, my love?
Let me see your back.
Isn't that where the new
people live, there?
That big house?
Race you there.
Come on.
It's my dog It's ours.
It's my dog. Get off him!
What idiots.
Father!
Somebody's got me! Run!
- Cathy!
Get off!
Skulker, get away!
Go on, get away! Get away!
Get out! Go on! Get out!
- Come on, lass.
- Cathy?
Robert?
Skulker's had a lass, sir.
There's a lad here too,
a right out-and-outer.
Just a boy.
We should hang you now,
before you get any older.
Do the county a favour.
Fuck you all, cunts.
It's Cathy Earnshaw.
I heard her brother lets her run wild.
And you're the boy
Earnshaw got from Liverpool.
The little lascar. The stowaway.
That makes sense.
Did you hear his language?
- You set the dog on us. Stupid whore.
- Robert, throw him out.
And send someone to fetch Dr Kenneth.
- Girls, fetch some water...
- Cathy!
And brandy.
Get out!
Would you like one?
How do, Kenneth?
Go on.
Hindley's looking for you.
Heathcliff!
I should beat you.
When Cathy comes home,
you are not to speak to her.
Is that clear'?
If I see you talking to her
without my permission,
you will be told to leave.
Hindley, I need you.
You know, I think it's good that
Cathy's going to go stay with the Lintons.
It'll do her good.
I prefer the Moorcock.
I've got a big collection of it at
home and I've got lots of lapwing feathers.
You'd like it at the Heights.
It's different to here though.
Joseph!
Look at you! How smart!
Joseph, grab the reins.
What a wonderful dress.
We hardly recognised you.
I've got him, I've got him.
- Hold him while I get down.
- I've got him.
Been quiet round here without you.
Come on, then, let's get you in.
Cathy!
Look at you! You're a beauty.
- Hindley!
- Don't she look well?
Cathy, I love this dress.
- Isabella gave it to me.
- Aren't you lucky?
I said a stay at the Lintons'
would do her good.
Where's Heathcliff? Where is he?
He's somewhere. I saw him earlier.
- Tea, anyone?
- Yes, please.
Heathcliff!
God's sake.
Aren't you pleased to see me?
Are you laughing at me?
Didn't mean to laugh.
All you have to do is wash and clean up
and you won't look so bad.
You do look dirty.
You didn't have to touch me.
Heathcliff?
I like being dirty.
I can help make you look smart,
if you like.
If you come now,
I can sort you out before dinner.
I want to be good.
Can you clean me up?
That's more like it.
The Linton's are coming today.
We'll have to get you clean like that Edgar.
Let me see.
Look at you. You're a prince.
I bet your mother was an African queen...
and your father a Chinese emperor.
I think somebody must have kidnapped you
and brought you to England.
- Hello, Edgar. Hello, Isabella.
- Hello.
- So you got here all right, then?
- Yes.
Just need a hand.
We've got some barrels.
- There we go.
- Nelly's been cooking all morning.
You do like goose, don't you?
Goose, my favourite.
Right, it's this way.
Come on.
That looks nice, Nelly.
You sit there.
Look at this. This looks nice.
Well, look at you, Heathcliff.
Get out!
Look at him, he's all dressed up
like a little circus monkey.
- Get out!
- Heathcliff!
You idiot-
You should have just spoken to him.
He'll be beaten now.
I hate it when he's beaten.
Get off him!
Hindley! No!
Stop it, Hindley!
Off him, Hindley.
Heathcliff.
Oi! What's going on?
What's he done now?
Take him in.
I don't want to see him. Lock him up.
Get up, lad. Get up!
Come on.
Here we are.
Heathcliff?
Can you hear?
The band's here.
Are you hurt?
He should be back now.
Nelly! Nelly, come quick!
- The baby's coming!
- Tell Hindley.
And get Dr Kenneth. Quick!
Oh, it's coming, it's coming!
I can't...
That's it. Just breathe.
Push.
It's coming, it's coming.
I can see its head.
"Blessed be the name of the Lord."
"I will keep my mouth,
as it were a bridle."
"While the ungodly was in my sight,."
"I held my tongue and spake nothing."
"I kept silence, even from good words,
but it was pain and grief to me."
"My heart was hot within me,
and while I was musing the fire kindled."
"At last I spoke with my tongue."
"Lord, let me know mine end"
"and the number of my days."
Breathe in. Stand still.
That's a good girl.
Do I look nice, Nelly?
Lovely.
Hold still.
Are you going anywhere?
- It's raining.
- Why you wearing that, then?
Aren't you supposed to be working?
No.
Joseph will tell.
He will never know. He's not here.
Nelly, you're brushing
all t'curls out my hair.
- Up you come.
Oh!
What were you saying?
You spend more time with them than me.
- As if I'd notice.
- I notice.
You never have anything to say.
May as well play with the baby.
You never complained before.
I've not come too soon, have I?
No.