- Intrusive?
- Intrusive.
Finally, a large emplacement
of intrusive rocks such as that found...
Ever since I can remember,
I've wanted to be clever.
Some people
are born clever
the same way some people
are born beautiful.
I'm not one
of those people.
I've had to work at it.
If there's a question,
I have to know
the right answer.
Crystalline or glassy
in appearance,
which of the three
principal classes of rock
is formed by the cooling
of molten earth material?
- What do you reckon, Bri?
- Volcanic.
- Is it igneous?
- Igneous is correct.
- That was nearly right.
... starter question for 10 points.
Derived from the Greek words
for "wing" and "finger,"
what name is given
to a flying lizard
- of the Jurassic and Cretaceous period?
- Pterodactyl.
Cronin, Oxford.
- Is it a pterodactyl?
- Pterodactyl is correct.
- Yes.
- Clever little thing, aren't you, eh?
Exeter College, Oxford,
magnificent score 235 points.
As Francis Bacon once said,
"Knowledge is power,"
which is why I want
to know everything.
I want to know about Plato
and Newton,
Tolstoy and Bob Dylan,
what the words "dialectic"
and "peripatetic" mean.
I want to know why
people actually like jazz.
If I'm going
to find the answers,
I need to be in a place where people
have a passion for knowledge,
think it's important...
sacred, even.
That's why I hope
you'll accept my application
to this university.
So was that
the correct answer?
Well, it's not
really a question
of correct
or incorrect,
but it's certainly been...
entertaining.
I think that's
everything, Brian.
Thank you.
- We should let him in, do you think?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
- I think so, yes.
We'll see you
in October, Mr. Jackson.
Yes!
So this is it.
I've made it.
Of course there are going to be
some pretty big changes...
leaving home,
moving to a new city
away from people
I've known all my life
and friends who have
always supported me.
You're not gonna
turn into a wanker, are you?
What?
I mean, you're not going
to get all poncy,
start saying, "One does"
and wearing a cloak and talking Latin.
Yes, Tone, that's exactly
what's gonna happen.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Right.
Oi, slow down.
Why do we always
have to listen to this?
Because.
- Because what?
- Because it's Motorhead.
- And?
- And the Head rule.
Because you say so?
- Because it's my ghetto blaster.
- Which ghetto is that, Tone?
It's Westcliff-on-sea.
Yeah, good one, Bri.
Tell you what,
why don't you stick on
a bit of Kate Bush?
We'll have a really good dance
listening to Kate Bush.
Have a good time. We'll listen to Kate
Bush. Have a great dance, yeah...
Bloody hell, Spencer!
I did this for you.
Trick your new mates
into thinking you got some taste.
Cheers, Spence.
This is amazing.
It's only a tape, Bri.
There's no need to get all gay about it.
So...
you think you will
retake your exams or...
- Oh, don't start.
- Don't start what?
- The careers guidance.
- I just think it's a waste, that's all.
Of course it's a waste.
Sitting on your ass for three years
reading poems, that's a waste.
It's not just about that.
It's about life experience,
expanding your mind,
grappling with
the big questions,
- making exciting new friends...
- As opposed to boring old ones?
- I didn't say that, did I?
- Look, I'm fine as I am, thanks, Bri.
Assholes.
Besides, there's always Tone
to debate the weighty issues of the day.
I'll never get that again.
Thanks, mate.
- Best tape I ever made...
- Let's get him.
...in the sea.
What?
No, hang on.
It weren't right!
It had to come out of your...
Right! That's it!
Spencer...
Oh, is that
what you're wearing?
- You don't mind, do you?
- No.
No no,
of course not.
No, it's very smart.
Now... bread,
do you need bread?
- Mom, I'll get bread there.
- Chip pan?
I'll miss the train, Mom.
- Don't drink too much.
- I won't if you won't.
And don't be cheeky.
Now are you sure you don't want me
to walk you to the station?
Mom, I'm all right,
honestly.
Now take this.
No no, you can't
afford it, Mom.
- Just take it.
- Mom...
Try to eat a piece
of fresh fruit every now and then.
He'd have been
so proud of you.
Bye.
Oh no!
Yeah!
Take that!
Hi there,
I'm your housemate.
Brian...
Brian Jackson.
Hello, Brian Jackson.
- I'm Josh. This is Marcus.
- Hello.
Hello.
Want me to show you
to your quarters?
Yeah.
Hope you don't mind,
but we allocated the rooms.
It's a bit small,
isn't it?
Yes...
yes, it is.
Well, we'll leave you to get
ready for the party then.
Party?
Tarts and vicars.
You are coming?
Actually, um...
I think I'm gonna stay here...
unpack and do
some reading.
Right. I'll purchase
the alcoholic beverages.
You got any money,
Barry?
Any cash?
It's just I don't have
any pockets.
Um, okay.
- Cheers, squire.
- Ta ta.
I just got back
from India.
- Oh right?
- Amazing experience.
It transformed me in ways
I never could have imagined.
- Such as?
- Do you use toilet paper?
Well...
now and then.
Not cool, you know.
Terrible for
the environment.
So, uh...
how do you...
you know?
I use my hand
and a bucket of water.
You should try it
sometime.
- Sorry, I've just seen somebody I know.
- All right.
Hi, do you mind
if I pretend to know you?
Has he been asking you
about toilet paper?
- Yeah, it's uncool apparently.
- Yeah.
Well, so is
gastroenteritis.
The ironic thing is
I actually am a vicar.
- So what did you come as?
- A normal person.
You could at least
have come as a vicar.
- Except I'm Jewish.
- Really?
Wow, I've never met
a Jew before...
not properly,
anyway.
Which is strange, really,
because loads of my heroes are Jewish...
Woody Allen, Marx,
Einstein, Dustin Hoffman...
- Jesus.
... Jesus, Freud, Kubrick.
Yeah, God, there certainly
have been some amazing Jews.
My people thank you.
Here you go, squire.
You don't waste any time,
do you, Barry?
Nice work, Barry.
- Was there any change?
- Sorry.
Well, uh...
nice talking
to you, Barry.
Actually, it's Brian.
But he just
called you Barry.
- Yeah, he did.
- What, and you didn't correct him?
No... I'm sorry,
I didn't get your name.
Rebecca.
Rebecca Epstein.
Rebecca Epstein?
That's a Jewish name, isn't it?
Shalom, Brian.
Right.
Absolutely.
Oh, bring it on!
Shit!
I'm sorry!
Sorry!
Oh, excuse me.
What's the hurry?
- Rebecca.
- Right.
- Come to our demonstration.
- I can't stop.
- I've got an important meeting.
- Right,
more important than the struggle
against the apartheid?
I'm really interested in this,
it's just that I'm late.
Yeah, I know.
Contemporary
Jewish Studies.
Oh, sorry.
- Halt!
- Hi, I'm here for...
Fingers on buzzers,
first question...
- what's that in your hand?
- It's a poster.
Why is it in your hand rather than on
the wall where everyone can see it?
- Um...
- Never mind. Fill this in, will you?
Anyone else
waiting out there?
- Don't think so, no.
- Really? Bugger.
- Subject?
- English literature.
But I'm pretty good
on sciences.
Newton's Third Law
of Motion.
Reaction is equal
and opposite to action.
Take a seat, please.
Anywhere?
Right, let's get started
then, shall we?
I'm sorry there
aren't more of us.
It seems that vandals
have been tearing down the posters.
I'm Patrick Watts
from Ashton-under-Lyne.
I am reading
Mechanical Engineering.
Some of you may recognize
me from last year's TV tournament.
Once again, I'll be captaining
this year's team...
- Why?
- Sorry?
If we lost last year,
why are you still captain?
Well, because
I'm a post-grad,
and I've been captain
for the last three years.
- We've lost for the last three years.
- Let's just crack on.
Shall we?
In order to qualify, you'll need to
answer 30 questions in 30 minutes,
and the top three scores
join me... the captain...
in this year's team.
Now there's some lively
little questions in there,
so I think you're in
for a pretty good time.
But it is against the clock,
so people, if you're ready...
let's quiz!
Hi.
Sorry sorry.
It's fine.
Beautiful.
You've got 30 minutes
to answer 30 questions. Just sit down.
- Can I borrow this?
- Of course you can.
Thank you.
Okay, concentrate.
Question six.
Question six is...
Why is she smiling at me?
That's not question six.
Concentrate.
Must concentrate.
Look at the paper.
Don't look at her.
Don't look...
d- don't look at her legs.
Or the curve
of her neck.
Just concentrate.
Right.
Question sex...
six, six.
"Hey, handsome,
would you mind giving me the answers
to three and five?
Thanks. "
Cheating...
she wants me to cheat.
I can't do that.
"With pleasure.
Three is potassium
permanganate,
and five is Papua,
New Guinea. "
...overworked and underpaid.
Cheers.
Support our nurses.
Support our nurses?
Brian, can I help you?
- I'm here for the team meeting.
- Alice!
- Hi!
- Hello, come in.
Brian, you're not on the team.
Alice here beat you.
- Only by one point.
- But Brian's still the loser.
"Loser" is a strong word.
He is first reserve.
Shoes off, please.
Follow me.
- Brian, I'm so sorry.
- Well...
If you hadn't given me those answers,
you'd have been on the team.
Alice, it's no big deal.
- Really?
- Yeah.
All right,
but I owe you.
Watts, Bristol.
Sorry, I'm going
to have to hurry you.
Is it...
Schubert, "Death and the Maiden. "
Schubert.
- Schubert.
- Is it Tchaikovsky?
No, I'm afraid that's not
the correct answer. Anyone?
- Simon, Queens.
- Schubert, "Death and the Maiden. "
Is correct.
At the sound of the gong,
the winners of this year's grand final
are Queens' College, Cambridge.
Obviously, I take no pleasure
in showing that to you.
But as someone once wrote,
"To err is human. " Anyone?
Alexander Pope's
"Essay on Man. "
And you know,
I really feel
that with dedication
and good old-fashioned teamwork
that this could be our year.
Which is why we're
assembled here today...
the fantastic four,
if you will,
each with his or her
own special powers.
Colin...
history, politics.
Lucy...
science, medicine.
Alice...
arts and literature.
And myself as a sort of floating
Renaissance man.
Brian!
Coaster, please.
Now qualifying heats
are in two weeks' time.
It's untelevised,
but we'll still need...
to be in good form
if we're to show them what we're...
can do... Brian?
- Should I come along?
- That won't be necessary.
- He is first reserve.
- I would be more than happy.
Team members only, Brian.
I'm sure we can manage
without you.
- I'm so sorry.
- Now quantum mechanics, anyone?
"Dear Spencer,
just a quick note to let you know how
things are going here.
My housemates are really interesting.
It's great to meet people
from different backgrounds,
and we're all having
a really good laugh. "
I'm so sorry.
"I've also become increasingly
politically active,
and have so far protested
against apartheid, nuclear weapons,
nuclear power, gay bashing,
and the sexual
exploitation of women. "
...the mere objects for
the sexual entertainment of men...
"Did you know that under
the bastard Tories,
7% of the country currently own 84%
of the wealth?"
...own 84% of the wealth.
It's the same old story.
"It's the same old story.
The rich get richer,
and the most vulnerable
in our country suffer. "
"Anyway, how are you?
How's the job hunt going?
Got anything more permanent?
Are you still 'signing on'?
I know there's not much out there at the
moment, thanks to bloody Thatcher,
but I'm sure something
will come up soon. "
Hey, piss off out of it.
"Must sign off now,
as I've got a lecture.
I'm currently wrestling
with the Romantic poets,
not literally of course, as they have
been dead for some time now. "
What do the so-called
Romantic poets mean
by the term "romance"?
It's certainly not hearts and flowers
though an appreciation
of extreme beauty
was a vital source
of inspiration.
But the notion of the Romantic poets
as swooning
lovelorn fops
is a fallacy.
Byron, Wordsworth,
Shelley in particular,
were all passionately
politically engaged.
- Come on!
- Shh!
- Shouldn't you be at the qualifiers?
- That's the thing.
Colin's been
knocked over by a bus.
He's okay, but it means
you're on the team.
Yes!
I'm so glad
that he's okay.
50 questions,
30 minutes.
Conferring is allowed,
and to make the grade,
um, we need a score
of 70% or higher.
Excuse me, but we're trying
to do a quiz here,
- and it's against the clock.
- It's got to be done sometime.
This man has been sent from the offices
of "University Challenge"!
So if we're ready.
Sergeant Troy, Fanny Robin,
and Bathsheba Everdene
all appear in which novel
by Thomas Hardy?
- "Return of the Native"!
- "Return of the Native. "
I think it might be
"Far from the Madding Crowd. "
Oh, of course it is.
Go with Brian.
- "Far from the Madding Crowd. "
- Correct.
Passer Domesticus is the scientific name
for which commonly known bird?
- The common house sparrow.
- Correct.
- Inflammation of the pancreas.
- The Sistine Chapel.
- Is the correct answer.
- The rings of Saturn.
- Correct.
- The 38th parallel?
- They carry their young in pouches.
- Correct.
"My love is like
a red red rose. " 1664!
- Prime numbers. Diaghilev. The spleen.
- Correct.
The Berlin Airlift. Trick question...
none of them. Gamma rays.
- Longshore drift. The "Venus de Milo. "
- Correct.
And your final question:
Which decade saw the invention
of the replaceable razor,
the formation of the Ford Motor Company,
and the death of Oscar Wilde?
- The 1890s.
- 1900s.
- 1890s.
- I'm pretty sure it's the 1900s.
- I am going to have to hurry you.
- Lucy, what do you think?
Actually,
I think Brian's right.
- Is the answer the 1900s?
- Correct.
Right, well then.
Congratulations, team.
Brian...
glad to have you onboard.
- Great.
- Thanks.
Bye.
Brian...
I've never seen
anything like it.
You're a general-knowledge god.
So what made you wanna
take the Challenge anyway?
"The Challenge. "
Well, I want
to be an actress,
or a TV presenter
or something,
and it's all experience,
isn't it?
- Yeah.
- How about you?
- How come you know all that stuff?
- Misspent youth.
I suppose I've always
just liked that feeling
of knowing things.
Look, for some reason
it all goes in and stays there,
and it's just
useless knowledge.
Do you think there's such a thing
as useless knowledge?
Well, sometimes
I wish I hadn't learned to crochet.
You are joking,
aren't you?
Oi, watch it.
Hey hey!
Ooh, better not.
There might
be dog poo in there.
Right.
Oh God, I just remembered...
mask workshop.
I got to run. I'll see you at
the next rehearsal.
Alice, what are you
doing on Friday?
L... it's just...
it's my birthday.
You're having a party?
Well, of course I'll come.
Not a party exactly.
I was thinking more dinner.
Or something?
Just me and you?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, Brian,
I'd love to.
Is the correct answer.
Okay, Friday.
Yes!
Oh.
Is something wrong?
No.
No, I just think
you could have put in
a bit more effort, that's all.
So where are you
taking me?
It's a good job
I reserved a table.
- This is great.
- Are you sure?
It looked posher from outside,
with all the candles and everything.
But I love pizza,
and they do one
with chips on.
The King Edward.
Um, right.
Hello?
Hey, excuse me?
The Lambrusco
bianco...
- could you tell me what year it is?
- 1985.
No, I know what year it is.
I just meant
what year is the wine?
1985.
Very well.
We'll have the white
Lambrusco bianco '85 please.
Look, breadsticks.
Hooray!
Do you know,
I think I'm going to have
these garlic mushrooms.
Well, you won't be
snogging anyone tonight.
So have you had
many boyfriends or?
Whoa.
- Where did that come from?
- Don't know, I'm just curious.
- What, you really want to know?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
When I was 15,
there was Charlie,
who was the lead singer
in this...
this band.
He was incredibly handsome...
gorgeous.
I left him for Rufus.
We then had a nine-month affair.
I then went out
with his best friend...
Then I had a fling with a lovely
Italian guy called Alessandro.
He was all sporty and stuff.
He was skinny because he was younger,
but he had muscles
and definition...
Gregor was lovely,
but incredibly possessive.
In the end,
we had to call the police,
and I think he was
deported.
And I think that
that's about it.
Funny, isn't it?
How many of them
end up being mad or suicidal...
- or in prison?
- I know.
Rufus, you know, the performance artist,
the one who set fire to himself?
Mmm.
He used to say
I had the kiss of death.
That's why
I'm giving it all up
to concentrate
on my work.
Then get me
to a nunnery.
"Hamlet," Act III,
Scene I.
You never stop, do you?
What do your parents
do again?
Mom works in a shoe shop
and Dad's dead.
- Oh.
- It's all right.
No need to get all serious.
It was a long time ago.
What happened?
Well, he was a salesman,
double glazing...
you know,
working on commission.
Long long hours.
He hated it.
Anyway, it must have been
eating away at him,
because one day
he just fell over apparently,
in this old couple's
living room
selling them
polyurethane windows.
41 years old.
Let's...
let's get another drink.
Excuse me?
Do you think about him?
Of course.
Every day.
But we never really
got to know one other.
Not as adults anyway.
I really only remember sitting in front
of the telly with him.
Quizzes.
He loved quizzes,
nature programs,
anything educational.
Knowledge...
that was the key,
he said, to being happy.
Not ending up doing
some job that you hate.
Where's that waiter?
He'd have loved you.
- You think so?
- Of course.
Don't you?
Don't know.
I think he might've thought I was a bit
weird, to be honest.
- He would have been very proud of you.
- Why?
You're going to university,
the star
of the quiz team,
doing all the things
he never got to do.
Yeah, maybe, maybe.
Anyway, Alice,
excuse me.
Do you mind
if I just pop off to the loo?
You are such
a lovely man.
Listen,
I'm sorry about tonight.
I don't usually cry
until much later in the evening.
Oh, you mustn't
apologize.
It was very...
illuminating.
Brian, what are you doing
at Christmas?
Oh, just the usual...
watching telly with Mom,
eating cheap chocolate.
Just that kind
of thing, really. Why?
Well, it's just we've got
this cottage in Suffolk.
And it's so dull when it's just Michael
and Rose and me...
- Who are Michael and Rose?
- My parents.
I thought maybe
you could come and stay?
- I can't really leave Mom.
- Yeah, but after Christmas.
For New Year.
My parents keep themselves
to themselves most of the time,
so it'd just be me and you...
walking, reading,
hanging out.
If the idea fills you
with dread,
- then, you know...
- Yes.
No... yes.
That would
be really good.
It's decided then.
Thank you.
Good night.
I take it
it went okay then, Romeo?
Well, you know,
it went all right.
So is love in the air?
Not love.
Um... like.
Like is in the air.
Mom, I'm home.
Mom?
Brian! Get out!
Get out now!
Our obligation to make our own
individual contributions,
however small...
His name's Des...
a widower from down the road.
An ice-cream man.
You know when he's coming around
because you can hear the chimes.
They've been keeping
each other company
ever since I left,
twice a day sometimes.
These are nice, Julie.
Little sausages
wrapped in bacon, Des.
Eat your sprouts.
You'll get rickets.
Rickets is calcium deficiency, Mom.
You're thinking about scurvy.
Oh, Brian, I don't care.
Just eat them, will you?
And I hope that we shall
all try to make
some good news
in the coming year.
By the way, I've got
an announcement to make.
What's that then?
Well, it's just something
that happened last term.
Oh, God, Brian.
- Mom, don't worry. It's a good thing.
- Tell me then.
I'm going to be
on "University Challenge. "
What, that thing
on the telly?
Yeah.
Congratulations, Bri.
- That's brilliant news!
- Cheers.
- Oh God, what a relief.
- Why?
Well, to be honest, Bri,
I thought you were going
to say you were gay.
What are you doing, Mom?
Just telling him
what you're up to...
how you're going
to be on the telly and everything.
What does Dad say?
He doesn't
say anything, Bri.
How long are you
down for then?
Actually, I'm leaving
the day after tomorrow.
You're not
coming out New Year?
No, I'm going to go and stay
with my mate Alice in her cottage.
Cottage?
What is she, a milkmaid?
- So you shagging her then?
- Tone, it's platonic.
- What does that mean?
- Means she won't let him shag her.
Yeah!
- I'll get you next time.
- What?
All right, where now?
Lucy's, Mannan's?
Not Mannan's.
Actually, I think I'm going
to go home.
Come on, Jackson,
you wuss.
No no, I'm all right.
I've got reading and stuff,
- but I'll see you soon, yeah?
- Yeah yeah, piss off.
What's up with you?
Why are we always telling
each other to piss off, Spence?
What's wrong
with "Good night"?
You know, "Sleep well,
Happy Christmas. "
I just don't get
all this hostility.
Listen, Bri...
you're my oldest mate.
You're my best mate,
and I love you.
I think it's great
that you're going out there,
meeting all these new people,
staying in cottages,
all that stuff.
Promise me one thing,
yeah?
Promise me you haven't
turned into a wanker.
Oi, Spence!
Spence, wait for me!
- Here, take a towel.
- I'll use their towels.
- You can't use their towels!
- Bye, Mom.
Well, here,
at least take this.
- What is it?
- Cold meat...
turkey, ham, a couple of those
little sausages.
Mom, I really don't think
they're gonna need...
Oh, take it.
It'll only go off.
Please.
Stick it in.
Are you sure you don't wanna stay
for New Year?
Not this year. Besides, you've got
Mr. Whippy now, ain't you?
Brian, that's enough.
- What?
- You know what.
Go on, then.
Have fun.
Happy Christmas, Brian.
It's so good
to see you.
In actual fact,
bees hum by blowing air
through their spiracles.
Spiracles...
that's fascinating.
- I know.
- Isn't that fascinating, Michael?
Sorry,
I was somewhere else.
So, Brian, is this
your first time in Suffolk?
No, I was here once before
on a climbing holiday.
- Really?
- Mmm.
Isn't it very flat
for climbing?
I was misinformed.
- Brian's joking, Rose.
- Oh.
Oh my God,
I love this song.
I lost my virginity
to this on a mime course at Tuscany.
Yeah?
Let's set the mood.
Michael and Rose
have gone to bed.
Um, no thanks.
What's up?
I just can't smoke.
You can't smoke?
No, I never learned.
Oh my God, Brian,
how can you not smoke?
Smoking is what I do best.
Second best, anyway.
All right, we'll try
a different approach.
On your knees,
facing me.
Hands behind
your back.
Now...
I'm going to blow
the smoke into your mouth,
and you're going
to inhale very deeply.
- Understood?
- Mm-hmm.
Nice?
Very nice.
- Again?
- Please.
- Are you sure? It's very strong.
- I can take it.
Okay, here it goes.
You should exhale now.
This is a terrible idea.
Kiss of death,
remember?
Actually...
I feel a little bit...
Oh, for Christ's sake.
Good night, Brian.
Oh, shit!
Yes!
Oh my God!
Well, hello,
Mrs. Harbinson.
Brian,
you scared me.
Still, I expect you've seen hundreds
of naked women before.
You'd be surprised,
Mrs. Harbinson.
I've told you before, please don't call
me that. It makes me feel so old.
Call me Rose.
Are you trying to seduce me,
Mrs. Harbinson?
What?
I said,
"Are you trying to seduce me,
Mrs. Harbinson?"
No Brian,
I most certainly am not.
No, I know.
It's just like a quote.
You know,
like Mrs. Robinson...
I haven't the least intention
of trying to seduce you.
Oh no, and I don't want
to seduce you either.
That's not to say
that you're unattractive,
because obviously you've got a beautiful
body for someone of your age.
- I beg your pardon?
- What's going on down here?
Nothing's going on.
Hello, Mr. Harbinson.
Then what the hell
are you talking about?
Nothing. I just came down
for a glass of milk
and I bumped
into Brian that's all.
Right, I think I'll
just head back upstairs.
Brian, where
are your trousers?
Well, you can talk,
big guy.
Brian, are you...
are you stoned?
No way, man.
I'm so sorry
about all this.
We only found out
this morning.
Granny fell down the stairs
and fractured her hip apparently.
We just thought we'd better
go see her in hospital down in Dorset.
My mom and dad set off
early this morning.
They send their love,
by the way.
They're so sorry you can't be here
for New Year's Eve.
Actually, I bumped into them
in the kitchen last night.
Really?
Did they say anything?
No, not at all.
Right.
Listen, Brian, the train's not for six,
seven minutes yet.
Oh...
Do you mind
if I don't hang around?
Of course not.
Hello?
Anyone home?
No, thought not.
Excuse me,
come to our demonstration.
Not a bad turnout
for New Year's Eve.
- Come to our demonstration?
- Sorry, no thank you.
Protesting
on New Year's Eve?
Injustice never rests.
Well, methinks the lady
doth protest too much.
It's from "Hamlet. "
It's a joke.
I think I'll be
the judge of that.
Good Christmas?
Not really.
You?
We're secular Jewish
non-Zionist socialists.
We don't really
do Christmas.
- Right, sounds a riot.
- Mm-hmm.
Why do you think
I'm back here?
- What's in the bag?
- Just New Year's Eve dinner.
Individual chicken pie
and a tin of sweet corn.
Fasten your seatbelts.
Yeah, except for
a souvenir tea towel.
Well, I hope you
had some clothes on.
Socks, shoes,
no trousers.
What, and then she
chucked you out?
- She didn't chuck me out, Rebecca.
- No?
Alice's elderly grandmother
accidentally had a fall down the stairs,
and fractured her hip.
She could have been
telling the truth.
Yeah, of course
she was telling the truth.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
I'm sorry.
So what are we
going to do tonight?
Haven't you got
a party to go to?
I think I can skip that.
I've got an individual
chicken pie.
Oh, well then how
could I possibly refuse?
I'm only flesh
and blood.
I've never been very good
at those parties anyway...
200 drunk students hurling
themselves at each other
in a tiny room.
Then at 3:00
in the morning,
some lager-breathed stranger
trying to rub his face on me.
I think I'm safer here.
So you don't have a...
I don't know,
what's the word...
boyfriend
- or partner?
- Or comrade.
Not as such.
I never seem to have much luck
in that department.
I don't know why.
I don't know why either.
- Brian, are you trying to flirt?
- No.
Then why are you
putting on that voice?
Look, I just mean...
I'm sure you could have a...
you know,
boyfriend
if you wanted one.
I have my amorous moments,
I suppose,
once in a while.
What's this?
It's my notebook.
That's just for
jotting down ideas.
- It's poetry.
- Oh, right.
Brian...
- you have to promise me something.
- Yes?
Promise me that
you will never...
never show me
your poetry.
I wouldn't dare,
Rebecca.
- Hey, what's the time?
- It's...
it's 11:56.
Well, we can't start 1986
listening to this moaning.
- We?
- Right.
Well, I hope you're not too...
- disappointed.
- What?
You're stuck here with me,
instead of Blondie.
Rebecca!
Of course not!
Look, I'd much
rather be here.
Is that right?
- Hey, what's the time?
- It is 11:58.
Two minutes to go.
What should we do
to pass the time?