Subtitle Rip; TheHeLL
You're listening
to Springbok Radio
and this is
the news at six.
The entire population will be
entered on a central register
with separate classification for
whites, natives, and coloreds.
Colored people are
also to be subdivided
into ethnic groups including
I ndian and Chinese.
Do you really like it?
It's beautiful.
I think it's going to
better than last year.
I want to finish it today
so that I can practice in it.
Good idea.
...1957 and make all central...
You know I don't
stand for second best.
Me neither.
Rain is expected...
Hally, are you up yet?
Hey Sam, you ready to
bring home the title?
He's a dancer,
not a fighter.
Did you hear about
Verwoerd's new policy?
Policy?
It's on the wireless.
Hendrik Verwoerd wants to give
our children Bantu education
so they'll never be more than
kitchen boys and street sweepers.
Hey wena, full upl No more.
Hey, Williel
What about you, Willie?
You ready for the big day?
Hey Willie, I know one
of the ballroom judges.
He's from
Motherwell Township.
Does he drink whiskey?
Maybe you can take him a case, Willie.
Haaikona, gents.
New Brighton must win
this one fair and square.
Then we can't
rely on Willie.
Don't worry
about that one.
Willie, just remember
what I told you,
the secret is to make it look easy.
Ballroom must look happy.
Like, like romance.
I've got no romance left
for Hilda anymore, Boet Sam.
Then pretend. I magine
Hilda is Ginger Rogers.
With no teeth?
You try.
Use one dab of Brylcreem
just a little dab
makes your hair
look excitingly...
Hally, you're
going to be late again I
Brylcreem...
Brylcreem,
a little dab'll do yah
Brylcreem, you'll
look so debonair.
Brylcreem, the gals'll
all pursue yah
they love to get
their fingers in your...
I'm going, mum.
Okay. Where's
my kiss?
Ah, you're not
even dressed.
Bye, Hally. Have
you got your lunch?
Kom, kom, julle passe!
Let me see your passes.
Waar's jou pas?
Here, baas.
Baie dankie baas.
Hurry up.
Yes, Boss, I think
I have it.
Hey, Sam I You
dropped it on the busl
May I, Boss?
Ja.
Sorry, Boss.
Semela?
Yes, Boss.
That's a Basutu name.
So what are you doing here
on the Eastern Oape?
Working, Boss.
I've got Section 10.
The paper's in
the back, Boss.
Okay.
Hey,
Ballard I That's my boy I
Must be hard to stand on three
legs when you're pissed, hey.
Whoa!
That's my boy I
For his speech titled
"The greatest
adventure show on earth...
a drop of pond water under
the microscope" Harold Ballard
That's my boy!
Aren't you having
another drink, Harry?
He wasn't pissed.
Oh, yeah, I'm sure he wasn't.
How do you spell gimp?
Lost his legs in the
Great War, huh, Hally?
Yeah.
Stupid cripple.
It's true, Boet Sam.
Hilda Samuels
is a bitch!
Three nights now she
doesn't come practice.
I wind up gramophone, I get
record ready, and I sit and wait.
Ten o'clock I start
dancing with my pillow.
How's your pillow
with the quickstep?
Good! And why?
Because she's got no legs.
That's her trouble.
She can't move
them quick enough.
Struesgod, she doesn't
come tonight
I take back my dress,
my ballroom shoes
I find me
a new partner.
Size 26.
Shoe size 7.
Hey, Willie.
Ja, and now she's making trouble
for me with the baby again.
Reports me to child welfare,
that I'm not giving her money.
Haai boet Sam man.
She lies, Boet Sam.
Every week I am giving
her money for milk.
And how do I know
its my baby?
Only his hair
look like me.
Ach.
Good morning, Madam.
Good morning.
Morning. Did you
oversleep again, Willie?
Or are you going to
blame the bus this time?
The bus was late, Madam, and the
police were checking for passes.
Ja, every day
a new excuse.
It's true, Mrs. Ballard.
It was easier when we were
allowed to live here in town.
Ja, okay. Hurry up now.
The water's not even boiling.
And Willie.
Yes, Madam.
I want clean
tablecloths out.
Yes, Madam.
Come, come.
The Population
Registration Act
and the Bantu
Education Act.
Music, Boet Sam.
Hendrik Verwoerd,
Minister of Native Affairs
was compiling
a curriculum...
Okay, Willie.
Hey, hey, hey. This is
a tea room, not a sheen.
Sorry, Madam.
Come now, you've got work to do.
I hope you've
sharpened those pencils.
I want to see the three
projections of the clutch plate.
Ballard, Ballard, Ballard.
Tell your parents you
want be a librarian.
Yeah.
Try and keep
it down, chum.
Can't we ask the nurse
for more painkillers?
Sorry, pal. I'd be much
better off if I was back home.
It was a bad fall, chum.
It's for the best.
Dr. Oolley's still got
tests to do and things.
Sam, I have to go
to the hospital.
Tell Hally
I'll phone him.
Yes, Madam.
Tell Willie to
clean this floor.
Yes.
Bloody rain.
Make sure Hally eats some lunch.
Yes, Madam.
And tell Willie
no buggering around.
Yes, Madam.
So much for business.
I mean it.
Of course, Madam.
# She
was scandalizing my name #
# She took my money
She called me honey #
# She called this love
She was playin' a game ##
Alright.
Oh.
Hey, Boet Sam,
I'm getting it.
The quickstep!
Look now
and tell me.
Show me again.
Oount for me.
Ready?
Ready.
And five, six,
seven, eight
And one, two,
three, four
five, six,
seven, eight...
Your shoulders!
Two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight
Don't look down, Willie!
Two, three, four, five, six...
look happy I
No, Willie, relax.
I'm relaxed.
No, you're not.
Willie, relax!
- I am relaxed!
- Relax.
Breathe, and relax.
Boet Sam!
You make me
make mistakes.
No, you are too stiff. You
must try to glide through it.
Glide?
Ja, give it more style.
You must look like you
are enjoying yourself.
I wasn't.
Exactly.
Willie... tell
me something.
When did you last
give Hilda a hiding?
Sunday night.
Aah, hiding
on Sunday night
then Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday
she doesn't come to practice.
And you are
asking me why.
One day she's going
to leave you for good.
So, she makes
me the hell in.
You had the same
trouble with Eunice.
Because she also made
me the hell in, Boet Sam.
Willie...
She never got the steps
right, even the waltz.
Beating her up every time she
makes a mistake in the waltz
no, Willie, that takes the
pleasure out of ballroom dancing.
Look and learn
don't worry about making
mistakes or the judges
or the other competitors.
It's just you, Hilda,
and the music.
And you are going to have a good time.
Okay, Sam.
What Oount Basie
do you play?
U m, "You the cream
on my cupcake
you're the salt
in my soup. "
M m-hm, right, right. Give
it to me in strict tempo.
Okay.
Ready?
Ready.
# And you're
the cream on my cupcake #
# You're the salt
in my soup #
# You will always
be right here for me #
# I'm a mess without
you, bam-bam I ##
Great, Boet Sam.
Bravo. No question
about it.
First place,
Mr. Sam Semela.
Ohhh!
Howzit, chaps?
Okay, Hally.
At your service,
Master Harold.
Not long to the
big event, hey?
Two weeks' time.
You think you
stand a chance?
Let's just say I'm ready to
go out there and dance. Ahhh.
Ahhh.
You look like it.
What about you, Willie?
He's got leg trouble.
Boet Sam!
Ah, sorry to hear
that, Willie.
Oh, God, what a
lousy bloody day.
Bad day for business,
chaps, but...
it leaves room for
a nice quiet afternoon.
Ah. Where's my
mom? Shopping?
The hospital.
But it's Thursday.
There's no visiting on Thursday
afternoons. Is Dad okay?
I'm not sure, Halley,
the hospital phoned.
Maybe he's coming home.
What makes you say that?
Oh, I don't know, I just
heard your mom talking.
She said
she'd phone you.
You want to eat?
Halley, do you want lunch?
Ja, just soup.
Kempston?
Mental pollution.
Take them away.
They can't be
discharging him.
They said he'd need at least
another three weeks of treatment!
No, Willie, Sam's
definitely made a mistake!
H uh.
So, Willie!
So, Willie, which
leg is sore?
Boet Sam is only
making jokes.
So you'll be
in the competition?
Only if I find
myself a partner.
What about Hilda?
She's the one
with leg trouble.
I think the lady's
gone a bit lame.
Boet Sam I
Have you taken her
to see a doctor, Willie?
I think a vet
would be better.
What the hell do you
think you're doing, Willie!
Act your bloody age!
Get on with your work.
You, too, Sam.
Stop fooling around.
No. Hang on. Tell me
exactly what my mom said.
I have.
"When Hally comes, tell him
I've gone to the hospital
and I'll phone him. "
So she didn't say anything
about taking my dad home?
- No, it's just when she was...
- No, Sam, it's just...
We saw him last night
and he wasn't in
good shape at all.
And now suddenly
today he's better?
You've definitely
got it wrong.
Okay, Hally.
Who is this supposed to be?
Old fart-face Prentice.
Teacher?
He thinks
he is.
- Has he seen it?
- Ja.
Said I was no
Leonardo da Vinci
and that bad art
had to be punished.
Six of the best?
And his are bloody good.
With your trousers down!
No. He's not
quite that barbaric.
Ja. That's the way
they do it in jail.
Really?
Ja. When the magistrate sentences
you to "strokes with a light cane. "
Go on.
Come, Willie!
First you have
to lie on a bench
one policeman pulls your trousers
down and holds your ankles.
It's not
fair, is it, Hally?
A kaffir's black ass.
The other policeman pulls
your shirt over your head
and holds your arms.
Thank you,
that's enough.
Then the one who's about
to give you the strokes...
I've heard enough, Sam!
Jesus!
It's a bloody awful world
when you come to think of it.
That's the way
it is, Hally.
Well, it doesn't
have to be.
You'll see, somebody's going to
get up one of these days and...
They're called
social reformers.
My history book's
full of them.
So where is ours?
I don't know, Sam.
Napoleon and the
Principle of Equality.
"Napoleon regarded
all people as equal under the law
"and wanted them to have equal
opportunities for advancement.
All ves-ti-ges"...
All that's
remaining.
"All vestiges of
the feudal system
with its oppression of
the poor were abolished. "
Aha! There's the social reformer
that we've been waiting for.
No, sure, Hally. He sounds
like somebody who is big.
Big and important.
What would you call it?
A man of... magnitude.
Magnitude. Aha.
I don't know, Sam.
Well, who would
you say was?
Abraham Lincoln.
No, Sam, now
you're confusing
historical significances
with greatness.
Try turning it
the other way.
I know what
I'm doing.
How did it happen?
Stop interfering
with my work, Sam.
Wait a minute... I got it!
Darwin! Oharles Darwin.
The Origin of the Species.
Remember?
He's your man
of magnitude?
Ja, precisely. For his
theory of evolution.
Who's yours?
Jesus.
Oh, come on, Sam.
Jesus Ohrist.
The Messiah.
Sam.
The Saviorl
Ja, but still...
No, Sam.
Don't let's get
started on religion.
I'm not going to waste my
time again arguing with you
about the
existence of God!
You know perfectly well
I'm an atheist
and I've got
homework to do!
Okay, Hally,
okay, I take him back.
You have time
for one more name.
Willie, what
are you doing?
Singing with God,
Master Harold.
Ohh.
Hally! I've got one.
I doubt it.
Think moldy
apricot jam.
Penicillin and
Sir Alexander Fleming!
Splendid, Sam! Splendid!
It's deeply gratifying
to know that I haven't
been wasting my time
in talking to you.
Tolstoy may have
educated his peasants
but I've educated you.
My first lesson
was geography.
Geography? God, ja, the
J ubilee Boarding House.
That's how it all started.
Nothing but bloody
misery wherever you went.
Somebody was always
complaining about the food
or my mother was having
a fight with M icky Nash
because she'd caught her with
a petty officer in her room.
Maude Meiring
was another one.
Do you remember
those two?
There were prostitutes,
you know. Ja.
Soldiers and sailors
from the troopships.
Bottom fell out of the
business when the war ended.
God, the flotsam and
jetsam that life
washed up on
our shores, eh?
The memories
are coming back now.
Walking home from
school and thinking:
"What can I do
this afternoon?"
And tried a few ideas,
but sooner or later
I'd end up back in
there with you fellows.
Like that time
I barged in
and caught you and
Myriam... at it. Remember?
Hell, Sam, couldn't you have
waited until it was dark?
No...
And if you
don't believe me
wait until
your time comes.
No, thanks.
Now, where was I?
Oh, ja, a gray little room
with a cold cement floor.
Your bed was
against that wall.
And I now know why the
mattress sagged so much!
Sam, your things neat and tidy
in a trunk right next to your bed
and on it is a picture
of you and Myriam
in your ballroom clothes
your first silver cup
for third place
in a competition
and an old radio.
Sam, do you want me to
teach you about South Africa?
Sure, I'd like to learn
about South Africa.
Right, repeat
after me, Sam.
Gold in the Transvaal.
Mealies in the Free State.
Sugar in Natal.
Grapes in the Cape.
Good. Okay, now once
more from the beginning.
Haai man, haai, it's
too late for school.
What are you
doing in bed, Willie?
Hey, wena.
Williel
Hally, are you in there?
Sam, Willie... Is he
in here with you boys?
Hally, will you come
out of there at once!
So much for
friendship, huh.
Hally, we couldn't lie
to her, she already knew.
Ha, it's more likely your
brain was getting fried
and you wanted me
out of there
before I got on to the
rivers and mountains.
No, Hally, I was happy
for the lesson.
But, come now, Hally,
it wasn't all so bad.
Ja, it was.
No, Hally.
Okay, maybe there
was one good day.
Only one?
Ja.
And?
Come on, Sam...
Tell us, Hally.
Please, Master
Harold, we want to hear.
It started off
looking like another
of those useless
nothing to do afternoons.
I'd already been down to Main
Street looking for adventure.
But nothing happened.
I didn't feel like
climbing trees
or pretending I was a private
eye and following a stranger
so, as usual:
See what's cooking
in Sam's room.
This time it was
you on the floor.
You had two
thin pieces of wood
and you were smoothing
them down with a knife.
It didn't look
particularly interesting
but when I asked you
what you were doing
you just said
"Wait and see, Hally.
Wait and see... "
in that secret way of yours
so I knew there was
a surprise coming.
You teased me, you bugger,
by being deliberately slow
not answering
my questionsl
And whistling
while you worked away I
God, it was infuriating I
I could have brained you I
It was only when you tied the two
pieces of wood together into a cross
and put that down
on the brown paper
that I realized
what you were doing.
Sam's making a kite.
I mean, the sheer audacity
of it took my breath away.
Seriously, what the hell does a
black man know about flying a kite?
I'll be honest with you, Sam, I
had no hope for it, none at all.
No, if you think I was
excited and happy
you got another
guess coming.
I n fact, I was shit-scared we were
going to make fools of ourselves.
Ja, I could see that.
I made it
obvious, did I?
You refused
to carry it.
Do you blame me?
Can you remember what the
poor thing looked like?
Tomato-box wood,
brown paper
Flour and water
for gluel
And then two of my mother's
old stockings for a tail
and all those bits and
pieces of string
you had me tie together
so that we could fly it I
Hell, no, that was only
asking for a miracle to happen.
No, Sam, that kite
will never fly.
Not without a
tail it won't.
Harold!
Hally!
So what happened?
Come on, Sam, you remember
it as well as I do.
I want to hear
it from you.
When I let the
kite go, you run.
No, do you want me to
be a laughingstock?
Of who?
Come on now,
let's try it.
This is it, I thought
like everything else
in my life
here comes another fiasco.
Then you shouted,
"Go, Hally, gol"
Ready... and go.
And I started to run.
Faster, Hally I Fasterl
I don't know how
to describe it, Sam.
Jal Ja, the miracle happened.
I was running, waiting for it
to crash to the ground behind me
but instead I felt something
alive at the end of the string
tugging at it as if
it wanted to be free.
You shouted to me to
let it have more string
and I did, until there
was none left
and I was just holding that one
piece of wood we'd tied to it.
And I looked back and I
still can't believe my eyes.
It was flying!
Looping around and trying to climb up
even higher
into the sky.
It works, Sam,
it worksl We've done it I
And we had. I was
so proud of us.
It was the most splendid
thing I'd ever seen.
And you came up and joined me.
You were laughing.
She's beautiful, Sam.
That she is.
The part that
scared me, though
was when you showed me how
to make it dive to the ground
then just on
the point of crashing
swoop it up again.
You didn't
want to try it.
Of course not.
God, I'd have been suicidal
if anything had happened to it
watching you do it
made me nervous enough.
I was quite happy
just to see it up there
with its tail
fluttering behind it.
Who's laughing
at you now?
You left me after
that, didn't you?
You explained how
to get it down
we tied it to the bench so
that I could sit and watch it
but then you went away.
I wanted you
to stay, you know.
I was a little scared about
having to look after it by myself.
I had work to do.
Why'd you make
that kite, Sam?
I can't remember.
Truly?
Too long ago, Hally.
It's time for
another one, you know
wouldn't be a good
day to fly it, though.
No, you can't fly
kites on rainy days.
Strange, isn't it?
What?
You and me
a little white boy and a
black man flying a kite.
Not every day
you see that.
But why strange?
I don't know.
Would have been just
as strange, I suppose
had it been
me and my dad.
A crippled man
and a white boy.
Nope!
No, there's no chance
of me flying a kite
without it being strange.
There's a nice little
story in that, you know.
"The Kite-Flyers. "
But we'd have to find
a twist in the ending.
Twist...?
Yes, something unexpected.
I mean, the way it ended with
us was far too straightforward...
me on the bench and
you going back to work.
There's no drama in that.
St. George's Park Tea Room.
Yes, Madam.
He's here.
Hally?
It's your mother.
Hello Mom?
Hally, I'm bringing
Daddy home.
Oh, God!
But how can he get better so suddenly?
He's not really better
it's just... he wants
to come home.
Well, well, then very
obviously you must say no!
Be firm with him, Mom.
Say Dr. Oolley wants
more X-rays of his stump.
Or bribe him. We'll sneak
double tots of brandy in future.
But Daddy's already up
and ready to go, Hally.
Well, order him to get
back into bed at once!
If he's going to behave like
a child, treat him like one.
No, Hally I Nol
Okay, Mom I I was just trying to...
You know how
much he loves you.
I'm sorry.
That's not good, Hally.
I said I'm sorry.
Wait, my tickey-box
is running out.
Tell the boys when they're
finished with the floors
they must clean
the windows.
Okay, Mom, just
listen to me carefully.
All it needs is for you
to put your foot down.
Do you hear me?
I'll see what
I can do.
My mom says that when you're
finished with the floors
you must do the windows.
Don't misunderstand
me, chaps
all I want is for
him to get better.
And if he was, I'd be the first
person to say, "Bring him home"
but he's just not.
So don't just stand there!
Get on with it!
What about when he's home?
Do you want me to pass my exams at
the end of the year or don't you?
Agh, Hally, don't
start with that talk.
I'm supposed to be
fresh for school
and I spend half the night
massaging his gammy leg.
Hally, respect!
I'm not being
disrespectful
I'm just sick and tired of
changing his stinking chamber pots
full of phlegm and piss.
No, you don't.
I do. When you're not
there he asks me to do it.
Why do you think I've got
no appetite for my food?
You're not eating?
There's a lot of
things you don't know.
For your information, I still haven't
got that science textbook I need.
Well, I gave
you the money.
Yes, and he
borrowed it.
For what?
Why do you think, Mom? Booze.
All I can say
is fick-it-all.
I'm sure he'll
listen to your mom.
Please, Sam. He'll
tie her up in knots.
I suppose he
gets lonely there.
With all the nurses
and patients around?
Regular visits from
the Salvation Army. Balls!
It's ten times worse
for him at home.
I'm at school and my
mother's here all day.
At least he's
got you at night.
And we've got him!
Lts just a plain
bloody mess, this is.
And people are fools. They
bloody well deserve what they get.
All right, Hally, all right.
What homework
do you have?
Bullshit as usual.
Write 500 words
describing an annual event
of cultural or
historical significance.
Well, that should be
easy enough for you.
Please, Sam I
Just leave me.
I'm not in
the mood for games.
And remember, you're to
help Willie with the windows.
Come on, now. I don't
want any nonsense.
All right,
all right.
Scary enough?
It could've been
scarier, chum.
Yes, the music
was creepy.
Really creepy.
How about when the woman
went into the church?
We saw the dark
shadow following her?
That's when you first
grabbed my arm, right?
Right.
If you didn't lose
your leg in the last war
you would be there,
wouldn't you, Dad?
Fighting H itler?
I didn't lose my leg
in the war, chum.
I fell down the
ship's gangway
on the trip over
from South Hampton.
I never got
to the war, Hally.
One, two, three, one...
One, two, three.
Much better.
Just a little
quick on the turn.
See what happens when you
relax and enjoy yourself.
But I don't have
a partner, Boet Sam.
Maybe Hilda will
turn up tonight?
No, I gave her
a good hiding.
You mean a bad one.
Good bad one.
They'll refund you
if you withdraw now.
No! I wait too long
and I practice too hard.
Then find Hilda.
Tell her that
you are sorry
and that you promise
not to beat her again.
No.
Then withdraw.
No!
Then I give up.
Haaikona, Boet Sam,
you can't.
What do you mean, I can't?
I'm telling you, I give up.
No! It was you who start
me ballroom dancing.
So?
Before that, I
used to be happy.
Are you blaming me?
Yes.
Hey Willie... Willie?
And now all you
do is make jokes?
You wait. When Myriam leave
you, it will be my turn to laugh.
Ha! Ha! Ha!
If Myriam leaves me tonight
I know what to do.
U h-huh?
May I have
the pleasure?
# I'm just a fellow
with a pillow #
Sam!
# Dancin' like a willow
I n the autumn breeze #
Boet Sam I Boet Sam I
I swear, I don't know...
For Ohrist's sake,
you two! Sam, Willie!
How the hell am I
supposed to concentrate?
He start doing...
Shut up, Willie. Get on with your work.
You too, Sam.
Do you want
another one, Willie?
Willie.
Suppose a customer
had walked in then?
Or the park superintendent?
That would have been the
end of my mother's license
and your jobs!
Well, from now on
there will be no more
of your ballroom
nonsense in here.
It's a harmless
pleasure, Hally.
It's also a rather
simple one, you know.
You reckon so?
Have you ever tried?
You're not asking me to take
ballroom dancing serious, are you?
Yes.
Oh, well, so much for trying
to give you a decent education.
What's wrong with admiring
something that is beautiful
and then trying
to do it yourself?
I'm sure the word you mean
to use is entertaining.
No. Beautiful.
And if you want proof
come to the Centenary Hall in
New Brighton in two weeks' time.
Please, Sam, I've seen the two of you
prancing around in here often enough.
Look, this is not the real
thing, Hally... We're just...
So? I can use
my imagination.
And?
I see lot of people dancing around
and having a so-called good time.
We're getting ready
for the championships, Hally
not just another dance.
Yes, there will
be a lot of people
and yes, they will be
having a good time
but those are
only spectators.
It's just the competitors
out there on the dance floor.
Party decorations and fancy
lights all around the walls.
And the ladies in beautiful
evening dresses!
My mother's got
one of those, Sam
and quite frankly it's an
embarrassment every time she wears it.
And your imagination
left out the excitement.
One of those couples will be
the 1950
Eastern Province Champions.
And your imagination
left out the music.
Mr. Elijah Gladman Guzanna
and his
Orchestral Jazzonians!
And finally,
your imagination
left out the climax
of the evening.
The dancing is finished
and the judges have stopped
whispering among themselves.
The Master of Ceremonies
collects the scorecards
and goes up to the stage
to announce the finalists.
Okay. And you say it
takes place every year?
Every year, Master Harold.
But only every third
year in New Brighton.
Which, I guess, makes it an
even more significant event.
Our "occasion" is now
a "significant event. "
I wonder.
"Write 500 words describing an annual event
of cultural or historical significance. "
You going to write
about it, Master Hally?
Shall we give it a go?
I'm ready.
Me also.
Right. To build the tension
and suspense, I need facts, Sam.
Give him facts, Boet Sam. Facts!
What you called the
climax... how many finalists?
Six couples.
Go on. Give
me the picture.
The six finalists
go onto the dance floor
and take up
their positions.
The Master of Ceremonies
goes to the microphone.
Ja... sh... we know
how to make a noise, hey?
But that's okay, it means we
know how to enjoy ourselves.
And isn't that
what we're here for!
Ladies and gentlemen.
My, my, my.
Aren't they looking
absolutely beautiful?
Yesl Yesl
No, I'm not talking
about our judges
I'm talking
about our finalists.
That's a good
touch... a joke.
Oreating a relaxed atmosphere
which will soon change
to one of tension and drama
as the climax is approached.
Ladies and gentlemen
we've now come
to the great moment
that we've been
waiting for this evening.
The finals of the 1950
Eastern Province Open
Ballroom Dancing Ohampionships.
Let me introduce
the finalists!
Mr. And Mrs. Welcome
Tchabalala from Kingwilliamstown!
Mr. M ulligan N kikelane
and Miss Nomhle N konyeni
of Grahamstown.
Mr. Fats Bokolane
and Miss Dina Plaatjies
from East London.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Down, boys. Down, boys.
Mr. Willie Malopo
and Miss Hilda Samuels!
Me?
Hilda!
Relaxed and
ready to romance.
Okay, here we go.
Take it away, boys.
One, two, three.
Good, that's good.
Keep it up, Willie!
Okay, now how are
the points scored?
A maximum of 10 points each
for individual style,
deportment, rhythm
and general appearance.
And penalties?
Penalties?
Ja. For doing
something wrong.
Say you stumble
or bump into somebody.
Hally...
What?
Willie.
He wants to know
what happens
if me and Myriam bump
into you and Hilda.
Why? What did I say?
Hally, there are no
collisions out there.
That's what that
moment is all about.
To be one of the finalists out
there on that dance floor is like...
like being in a dream about a world
in which accidents don't happen.
Jesus, Sam!
That's beautiful.
Ja, it is, Master Hally.
It's beautiful because that's
what we want life to be.
But instead,
like you, Hally
we're bumping into
each other all the time.
None of us
know the steps
and there's no
music playing.
And it doesn't
just stop with us.
America is bumping
into Russia
England is bumping
into I ndia
rich man
into poor man.
Those are
big collisions.
People get hurt and we're
sick and tired of it now.
Are we never going
to get it right, Hally?
Learn to dance
life like champions
instead of always being just
a bunch of beginners at it.
You've got a vision, Sam.
Not just me.
Everybody's got it.
That's why there's only standing
room left at the Oentenary Hall.
For as long
as the music lasts
we are going to see
six couples get it right
the way we want
life to be.
Is this the best
we can do, Sam?
Dream about the way
it should be?
Without the dream we won't
know what we're going for.
Oh, when you come
to think of it
that's what the U nited Nations
boils down to...
a dancing school
for politicians!
H mmm. Let's hope
they learn, Hally.
All right. This is a lot
bigger than I thought.
So what have we got?
Our title. "A World
Without Oollisions. "
"A World Without
Oollisions. " Beautiful.
Subtitle, "Global Politics
on the Dance Floor. "
Eh.
Nah, a bit heavy, hey?
How about " Ballroom
Dancing as a Political Vision"?
Saint George's
Park Tea Room.
Yes, Madam.
Hally, it's your mom.
Hally, she's waiting.
Hello, Mom.
I've brought
Daddy home, Hally.
Hally.
Hally, are you there?
Well, I just hope you know
what you've let us in for.
Give him a chance. Please?
Okay, Mom I
But just remember to start
hiding your bag away again
because he'll be at your purse
before long, for money, for booze.
I don't want to hear
you talking like this.
Then don't complain to me
when he starts his old tricks.
When do I ever
complain to you?
Yes, I get it from you one side
and him on the other
and it makes
life hell for me.
I'm warning you now when the
two of you start fighting again
I'm leaving home.
Oh, Hally,
how can you...
Mom, if you start crying, I'm
going to put down the receiver.
That's enough now.
We're all going to try
to do our very best.
Okay, Mom.
Aren't we, Hally?
I heard you.
Do you want
to say hello?
No! I'll see him
when I get home!
He wants to
talk to you.
Mom! I don't
want to!
No, Mom. No, Mom,
I don't want tol
Nol Mom I
Hello?
Welcome home, chum!
Sorry to spring
this on you, chum.
I bet the last thing
you need right now
is your old man back home
fouling everything up.
Don't be silly, Dad.
You being home is just about
the best news in the world.
Hell, man, I'm happy
to be out of that place.
I bet you are.
Bloody depressing there with everybody
going on about their aliments, hey.
Like a bunch
of old women.
So how you feeling?
Fighting fit, chum.
Good.
How're things
with you, pal?
Everything's just
hunky-dory on my side, Dad.
Good. So... what's up?
Oh, well... well,
to start with
there's a nice pile of
comics for you on the counter.
Batman and Robin, Submariner...
just your cup of tea.
Ahhh I
I'll bring them home.
Good. I've got some great
new jokes to tell you, chum.
Ja, sure, we'll spin
a few yarns tonight.
Ja.
That's for sure.
All right then, chum, I'll
see you in a little while.
You won't be late?
No, I promise. I'll
come straight home.
Okay, I'm handing you back
to the commanding officer.
Hally, now don't forget to
bring home Daddy's brandy.
Yes, I'll put it in my bag
now, for God's sake. Bye.
That sounded like
quite a bump, Hally.
M ind your
own business, Sam.
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to interfere.
Shall we
carry on? Hally?
Boet Sam, tell him about when
they're giving out the cups.
Jal That's
another big moment.
The presentation of the cups after
the winner has been announced.
The presentation
of the cups.
You've got to put that
in there, Master Hally.
So much for a bloody
world without collisions.
We did say it
was only a dream.
Life's a fick-up and it's
never going to change.
Maybe that's true.
There's no maybe about it.
All we've done this
afternoon is waste our time.
Not if we get
your homework done.
I don't give a shit
about my homework!
Hurry up now and
finish your work.
I want to lock up and get out of here.
And go where?
Home-sweet-freaking-home.
Jesus, I hate that word.
Do you want to know
what's really wrong
with your lovely
little dream, Sam?
It's not just that
we're all bad dancers
there's more
to it than that.
'Oause you left
out the cripples.
Hally.
Jal Ja, they're also
out there dancing...
like a bunch of broken spiders
trying to do the quickstep.
I mean it's bad
enough on two legs
but one and a
pair of crutchesl
That's guaranteed to turn that
dance floor into a shambles.
For once this afternoon let's use
our imaginations sensibly, right?
There's no music, nobody knows the steps
and the cripples are always out
there tripping everyone else up
and it's called
the All-Comers-
How-To-Make-a-Fickup-
of-Life Ohampionship.
And guess who I think is
going to be this year's winner?
Now, Hally, stopl
That's your father
you're talking about.
So?
Take back those words
and ask for forgivenessl
It's a terrible sin
for a son
to mock his father
with jokes like that.
Hally, I understand how you
are feeling, but even so...
No, you don't!
I think I do.
And I'm telling
you you don't!
Nobody does!
It's your turn to be
careful, Sam. Very careful!
Just leave me and
my father alone!
I'm not the one saying
terrible things about him.
What goes on between me and my
dad is none of your businessl
Okay, then don't
tell me about it.
All that concerns
you in here, Sam
is to try and do what
you get paid for.
Keep the place clean
and serve the customers.
My mother's
always warned me
about allowing you to
get too familiar.
You're only
a servant in here
and don't forget it.
And as far as my
father's concerned
all you need to remember
is that he is your boss.
No, he isn't. I get
paid by your mother.
He's a white man and
that's good enough for you.
I'll try to forget
you said that.
Don't.
Look, Hally...
You're right.
If we're not careful,
somebody is going to get hurt.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Yes, you do.
Jesus!
I wish you'd stop
trying to tell me
what I do and
what I don't know.
Come, Willie,
let's finish up.
Don't turn your
back on me!
Don't do that!
All right.
I'm listening. What do
you want to say to me?
Well, to start with
why don't you start
calling me Master Harold
like Willie.
Do you mean that?
Why the hell do you
think I said it?
If I don't?
You might just
lose your job.
If you make me
say it once
I'll never call you
anything else again.
So? Is that meant
to be a threat?
Just telling you
what will happen.
You must decide
what it means to you.
Well, I have.
It's good news.
Because that's exactly what
Master Harold wants from now on.
Think of it as a little
lesson in respect, Sam
that's long overdue.
My dad agrees with my
mom, you know.
"You must teach the boys to
show you more respect, my son. "
So now you can stop
complaining about going home.
Everybody is going
to be happy tonight.
That's perfectly correct.
You see
You mustn't get the wrong
idea about me and my dad, Sam.
We also have our
good times together.
Some bloody
good laughs.
Want to know what
our favorite joke is?
He gives out this big
groan, you see, and says
"Oh, it's not fair,
is it, Hally?"
Then I have to ask,
"What chum?"
And then he says,
"A kaffir's ass. "
We both have
a good laugh.
Oh, what's... what's
the matter, Willie?
Don't you catch
the joke?
It's what's
called a pun.
You see, fair means
both light in color
and to be just
and decent.
I thought you
would catch it, Sam.
I catch it all right.
But it doesn't appeal
to your sense of humor?
Do you really laugh?
Of course.
To please him? To
make him feel good?
No, for heaven's sake!
I laugh because I think
it's a bloody good joke.
You're really trying hard
to be ugly, aren't you?
And why drag poor Willie into it?
He's done nothing but
show you the respect
that you want so badly.
And that also is not "fair"
and this time I mean
just or decent.
Sam, It's all right.
Leave it now.
Why didn't you just
say "Sam's ass"?
That's the ass you're
trying to kick.
Anyway, how do you
know it's not fair?
You've never seen it.
Do you want to?
There. Have
a good look.
A real Basuto ass.
Look at my assl
Satisfied?
Now you can make
your dad even happier.
Tell him I showed you my
ass and yes, he is right.
It's not fair.
Come, Willie,
let's finish up.
Sam...
Leave it, Boet Sam.
It's all right, Willie.
Well, you've done it...
Master... Harold.
I'll start calling
you that from now on.
It won't be
difficult anymore.
You just hurt yourself.
I saw it coming
I tried to warn you,
but you wouldn't listen.
So now you just
hurt yourself bad.
And you're a coward,
Master Harold.
The face you should be
spitting in is your father's
but you used mine, because
you think you are safe
inside your fair skin I
No, Boet Sam.
You don't know all of
what you've just done...
Master Harold.
Not only have you made
me feel dirtier
than ever I've ever
been in my life.
But how do I wash off yours
and your father's filth?
A long time ago I made
a promise to myself
but you've just shown
me, Master Harold...
I've failed.
I've also got
a memory...
of a little white boy in
short trousers and a black man
but they were
not flying a kite.
It was the old
J ubilee days
after dinner one night.
You came into my room
and stood against the wall
looking down
at the ground.
Ahh.
What is it, Hally?
And only after
I'd asked you
I don't know how many
times, "What do you want?"...
Hally, what's wrong?
...did you finally speak
and so soft I could
barely hear you.
Come now.
"Sam, please help
me fetch my Dad. "
Do you remember?
He was dead drunk on the
floor of the Oentral Hotel Bar.
They phoned your mother, but
you were the only one home.
You went in first
and asked permission for me to go in.
Wat soek jy hier?
You better take
him home, he's pissed himself.
You mean, pissed again.
Come, Mr. Ballard.
I loaded your dad on my back
and I carried
him like a baby.
Poor thing.
What a disgrace.
Get me some water
from the basement.
We have to
clean him up.
Don't let them take
my other leg, Hally.
Promise, you won't let
them take my other leg?
I won't.
I felt for that little boy...
Master Harold.
I felt for him.
I love him, Sam.
I know you do.
That's why I tried to stop
you from saying those things.
You love him... but you
are ashamed of him.
You are ashamed
of so much!
And now that's going
to include yourself.
That's the promise
that I made to myself
to try to stop that
from happening.
You didn't do anything wrong,
but for days you went around,
as if you owed the world an apology,
for being alive.
I didn't like seeing that.
That's not the way a
boy grows up to be a man!
But the one who should
have been teaching you
what it means was the
cause of your shame.
And if you really
want to know
that's why I made
you that kite.
I wanted you to look up
to be proud
of something
of yourself...
and you certainly were that
when I left you up there
on the hill
with the kite.
Something elsel
If you ever do write
a short story about it
there was a
twist in the ending.
I couldn't sit and
stay there with you.
It was a
"White's Only" bench.
You were too young,
too excited to notice.
But not anymore.
And if you're not careful,
"Master Harold... "
you will be sitting up there by yourself,
for a long time to come,
and there won't be a kite in the sky.
Willie...
Will you lock up for me
and look after the keys?
Okay.
You forgot the comics.
Hally...
I've got no right to tell
you what it is to be a man
if I don't behave
like one myself.
Should we try again?
Try what?
Fly another kite,
I suppose.
You can't fly kites
on rainy days, remember?
So what do we do?
Hope for better
weather tomorrow?
I don't know.
I don't know
anything anymore.
You sure of that, Hally?
Because it would be pretty
hopeless if that were true.
Anyway, I don't believe you.
I reckon there's
one thing you know.
You don't have to sit
up there by yourself.
You know what
that bench means now.
And all you have
to do is stand up...
and walk away from it.
Come inside, Boet Sam.
It's going to be
okay tomorrow.
Boet Sam, you're right.
I think about it
and you're right.
Tonight I find Hilda
and say I'm sorry.
And promise not to
beat her no more.
You hear me, Boet Sam?
I hear you, Willie.
Then we practice.
Then I relax and romance with
her from beginning to end.
Non-stop!
You watch, Boet Sam!
Two weeks' time, "First
prize for promising newcomers
Mr. Willie Malopo
and Miss Hilda Samuels. "
How did you
say it, Boet Sam?
Let's dream.
You lead, I follow.