We are also going to be talking...
with Kim Alexander on following
the money trail.
Getting broken in by Senor
Rape-ez here, huh?
Yeah? You having a good day?
- Yeah.
- I'll break it down
for you, alright?
All you really need to know is...
among this whole sea
of brown skin...
a Mexican man hates a Honduran,
just like a Guatemalan
hates a Salvadoran.
They're really not all the same.
Everybody's dealin' dope,
twenty-four/seven.
It's an open-air supermarket.
Everybody's got a woodstick
for the LAPD.
Typical, onionhead gangbanger.
It'll be a Mexican. You know.
A Patuso or a Fuego.
And all this shit,
it all derives from something
real important,
like what little berg in the Culiacán
Uncle Juanito comes from.
How many fuckin' coyotes
the dirty little hamster
bred with on his journey up
here to the promised land.
What about the scandal?
The scandal's bullshit.
Two dickhead cops got embroiled
in some fuck up.
Ratted out an entire
sweet division...
to save their own wretched asses.
The D.A.'s office is running
scared, afraid to file,
afraid not to exonerate
en-fucking-masse.
Now you got a lot of hopped-up
Rodney King wannabe beaners
making whoop-de-doo of their own,
with get-out- of-jail-free cards
and a pile of county cash.
This used to be a glorious soldier's
department. Now it's... you.
What's funny?
Private Hatchet woman over
here is inquiring
about the scandal of the century.
You didn't touch your fries.
What? Oh.
I had a couple of them, but
I got a cholesterol thing.
Why, you want them?
No, you want them. Finish it.
I can't... I don't
eat French fries.
Well, then you shouldn't
have ordered them.
Finish those fries.
Dave hates wasting food.
You never see him eat, but...
he hates wasting food.
If you keep going like this,
you're gonna look like a crackhead.
Munch, munch, cowgirl. C'mon.
A very attractive crackhead,
mind you.
You makin' eyes at me?
You want one?
No, no, no. You're doin' good.
I stay healthy.
Finish those fries if you
wanna make probation.
- Okay?
- Yes, sir.
Your dad ever discipline you?
Huh?
No, sir.
I never met my father.
You never met him. Why?
He wasn't around.
General!
You guys make a great couple.
I was just bull-shitting you.
Thanks, boss.
There you go. Eat up. Eat up.
You aim for the shortest wetback,
you watch him skedaddle...
plow the dice and the Schlitz
Malt Liquor cans...
and hit your siren in farewell.
Let's see what we've got.
Wooo!
Green cards!
Yeah, you'll get the hang of it.
- Aren't you worried?
- About?
You'll get a 128?
Okay, listen. This is the most
important thing I've told you so far.
Everything you learned at
the Academy is bullshit.
An Illegal is just a sick bird.
This is some military occupation,
kid. Emergency law.
Alright, let's have some fun.
What went on here?
Caught him boosting ephedrine
and propyl alcohol.
What happened?
Ow.
He hit you?
Yeah.
You hit him? Tough guy?
Step outside, will you?
- Outside?
- Yeah, outside.
Hey, will you step out, too?
- I don't know, sir
- Now!
And shut that door behind you.
Nice tat.
Now, you're cooking crank
out of somebody's garage.
I don't know where that
garage is, but you do.
Now where oh where could
that damn garage be?
I don't see it, but you do.
- No, I don't.
- Yes, you do.
Okay, so now you have petty
theft, assault...
I'm sure you have at
least four priors.
That's a violation and mandatory
bullet, compadre.
Now, you give me that address,
and it all goes away.
What's the address?
I don't want to hurt you.
I don't. I like you.
- You don't know anything?
- Don't know, nothin'.
Tell me where it is. C'mon.
I don't know where it fuckin'
is. I don't fuckin' know!
That's your man.
- What?
- Meth lab. 41 East Cesar Chavez.
That's it? No explanation, Dave?
- Hey, Dave, question?
- Yeah?
Circuit Court appeals for illegal
search and seizure.
Give me a precedent.
Cuthbert versus Ingleside County,
Virginia, 1966. Look it up.
You have all those cases memorized?
Sure, and if I don't, I make it up.
...takes place in this great,
great country of ours. C'mon.
But let's imagine if you will
what might be happening
out there beyond America,
beyond our word, because I'm
sure this will leave you
simply breathless.
It's my opinion that when we hear
of some bizarre or repugnant
or deviant story
like the one you are
about to hear, well,
it's not that the world suddenly...
- Hey, ladies.
- Dave.
- Hey, babe.
- Any wine for me?
- Dinner's at 6:30.
- I'll be there.
Daddy!
Hey.
- How are my girls?
- Great.
Yeah? No hello, Helen?
- Hey, Date Rape.
- Don't call me that.
Something about it that's...
What's up, monkey?
Helen has a question.
Maybe you have a question.
We both have a question.
Helen's studying genetics
in school,
and since our moms are sisters...
and you're our dad, we
were just wondering...
if we were inbred.
It's not funny!
No, sorry. Sorry.
No, I married your moms consecutively,
not concurrently...
which makes you and Helen first
cousins and sisters, half.
It's all perfectly legal
and genetically up to insurance
industry standards.
You're not gonna turn into
mongoloids any time soon,
if that's what you're asking.
You're not inbred. You
know what you are?
You're native.
- It's sad.
- They're dead. They can't
commit suicide.
Is this a new TV show?
No. I'm trying to make it up.
It sounds like it. The
ghosts are depressed?
No. I was thinking about
maybe making it
a graphic novel or something.
You could do that.
- Suicidal ghosts.
- I would like to see that.
They want out. So these people,
who I think are actually...
Barbara, where's the olives?
There's no olives.
I'm sorry. I don't know.
I think we're out, I'll look,
but I think we're out.
They're complete barbarians.
And they have just as many
problems as we do.
Why do you let her put
that on the wall?
Helen's poster?
Yeah, that little collage.
It's amazing. She's been
working hard on it.
She's worked on that thing
for three weeks.
- It's amazing, is
it? It is amazing.
- It's quite something.
I think it should be in a museum.
That's what I think.
Don't you tell your mother
you learned that from me.
Here, give me your plate, Marg.
And that's not okay
if that's a bowl.
May I sleep with you tonight?
I have sketching to do. Please.
So that's not a no, is it?
That would be a very
nice way to say no.
What about a nice way to say yes?
What about after your sketching?
No, no...
I'm gonna be up all night.
Aunt Bee, is there
any more broccoli?
Are you asking for more vegetables?
Only broccoli because I
like eating the stems.
Helen, I'm curious about
that artwork you have...
on the wall there.
- What is it?
- What kind of a mother are you?
- She's a broccoli hoarder.
- What does it mean?
What does it mean...
Yeah, what does that
mean? That collage?
It's these little bits of paper,
and you cut them out
and you glue them together
and make another picture.
Okay, so you have a
man's head and...
a woman's heel digging
into his head and
stepping on his mouth and...
- It's art, Dave. It's art.
- We can be grateful
that he noticed.
...a naked woman with the blood
flowing from her vagina.
Alright. Okay.
- You have the C word prominently
displayed.
- Alright.
You have eyes. That's great.
What's the problem?
What is the problem?
- Oh, let it be, would you?
- Margaret?
Do you like her collage?
I'll ask it. What is it?
It just needs more color.
More color.
Like rainbows.
Honey, how's your spaghetti?
- Pretty good.
- Yeah?
That's good.
How is yours?
It's very good, thank you.
You should try some.
Oh, I'm fine, thank you.
Do you want to cuddle later?
I have a boyfriend.
Cheat on him.
Like you cheat on your taxes?
I don't cheat on my taxes.
Okay? You can't cheat on something
you never committed to.
How do you know how much you
pay for taxes anyway?
I think I'm gonna go take a
walk, look for some olives.
Come on. Would you sit and
have something to eat?
He wouldn't be like
this if you guys
weren't so hard on him.
It's the truth.
No, it's not the truth.
He is too hard on you, but still...
♫ Listen to the rhythm of
the gentle Bossa Nova ♫
♫ You'll be dancing with 'em too ♫
♫ before the night is over ♫
♫ How can you lose? ♫
♫ The lights are much
brighter there ♫
♫ You can forget all
your troubles ♫
♫ forget all your cares ♫
And where you go? That's right.
♫ Things'll be great
when you're... ♫
♫ Downtown... ♫
♫ Don't wait a minute more ♫
Dave Brown's just too plain
a name for someone like me.
What, you don't have a moniker?
You don't have a moniker? Like
something your cop buddies call you?
You know the lingo.
Yeah, my brother was on the
San Berdoo Sheriff's.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I got a little thing for cops.
You don't have it for your brother?
What, no! No!
Nice!
That was a very, very impressive...
No, thank you. I don't smoke.
- You don't smoke?
- No. I don't need it.
Then that wasn't as impressive
as it would have been.
No, it was still a very
impressive trick.
No smoking in here, sir.
Jesus Christ.
You used to let me smoke in here.
Poor little rose.
That's for you.
Wow. I didn't get you anything.
That's okay. You'll
think of something.
So come on, tell me.
What's your moniker?
What does it matter?
Could tell me all I need
to know about you.
You know, maybe a little bit more.
Come on. Don't be shy. What
is it? Let me guess.
Is it...
"Roughhouse" Dave?
Yeah? Or...
I like that.
Or "Bang Bang" Brown?
"Date Rape" Dave.
Why is that?
Rumor from when I worked
Hollywood Sex...
and I can't confirm it
and I won't deny it.
So tell me.
Maybe I killed a bad
guy, maybe I didn't.
Either way, he got what he paid for
and he'll never hurt another
woman ever again.
Is that your foot?
Yeah.
Oh, stop, stop, stop.
Okay, Do it again, do it
again, do it again.
Woo!
Oh, well.
Hey, what's your fucking problem?
Ow!
[Newscaster [ Brown was videotaped
severely beating a motorist
named Shondell Parmallee in
what civil rights groups
are calling "old school
L.A.P.D. Brutality
"revisited, revived,
and regurgitated."
Local activists have launched
new attacks on the L.A.P.D.
For its "culture of
racial misconduct"
while Officer Brown remains
on limited duty
awaiting possible disciplinary
action
and pending civil lawsuits.
The Shondell-gate matter is in the
early stages of investigation,
as opposed to the Rampart Scandal,
which as you know is a longstanding
highly complex and
multifaceted issue
- of great social import.
- Son of a bitch.
That's Bill B. For you. He got "highly
complex", "multifaceted"
and "great social import"
into one sentence,
and he didn't say a damn thing.
I'll say this though.
Our citizens are sick and tired
Yeah?
...of the old way of
doing business.
How was your day?
- Good. You?
- Pretty good.
Is Helen still mad at me?
I don't know. What are we watching?
Just...
yeah.
Hey, did you do your homework?
No.
Great idea.
How about we make this
a homework-free day?
Not that you'll tell your mom.
And we'll just watch television.
Okay.
What do you want to watch?
Is this good?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Jab it in and turn it.
Suction. Suction!
Now. Now!
Where the hell is the blood?
Grab that clamp and
push it back hard.
- I can't
- Come on!
No justice, no peace!
Hey, Dave. Man of the hour.
Date Rape?
Thanks for making us
look good, Dave.
You're the man! Good job!
Thank you.
Thighs apart, heads up.
Have a nice day.
What's the word, Chief?
Close the door.
What should I say?
I'll say whatever I need to.
Have you thought about retirement?
No.
In fact...
if you force me to retire
and file on me,
I'll plead not guilty, take it to
trial, and represent myself.
I'll be playing to a mentally
deficient jury, so I'll lose
though I'll work Vietnam
for all it's worth.
I'll have PTSD, DDT,
TNT, Agent Orange
and the Creeping Chinese
Crud before it's over,
not to mention 24 years on the job.
I'll draw a fine and a
suspended sentence.
Court TV will broadcast
the whole thing.
I'll have my own show on Fox
News inside one week.
You'll be my first guest.
So you have thought about it?
I don't intend to retire,
Miss Confrey.
All right.
You know, Rampart has
become a shitstorm
of such epic proportions,
legally and financially.
We have bullshit police
brutality complaints
bullshit felony evidence plants,
wrong door fuck-ups,
we have them all.
I have a ton of testimony,
solicited and unsolicited,
that is ambiguous, if not
downright indecipherable.
The county's going bankrupt
paying out lawsuit money.
The D.A.'s office and L.A.P.D.
Are hemorrhaging prestige,
and many hardened criminals
are out on the street way
before they should be.
And now, Dave, we have
you to deal with.
And we can't afford you.
So how do we solve a problem like
Dave Brown? You tell me.
I was under attack.
I went after the suspect.
End of story.
The tape doesn't show everything.
They never do.
- I had to neutralize him.
- The tape shows you,
brutally beating a man
almost to death.
I think on his part it was assault
with a deadly weapon
You think he drove into
you on purpose?
It was an assault with
a deadly weapon.
- I got out of the car,
- It was an accident.
- It was a collision.
- I intended to help
that gentleman.
He opened the door into me and ran.
A lot of cops would have shot
him and got a medal.
I took it easy on him, and
now I'm here before you.
I don't think what we saw was
taking it easy on anyone.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but nine out of ten cops
would have shot him right there.
Do you admit that you overreacted?
You seem to have everything
under control here,
and I do appreciate
the opportunity.
Just remember which side you're on.
♫ If I could go back
to our mistakes ♫
♫ we both know how this
act is gonna end ♫
♫ After Boston and seattle ♫
♫ we thought maybe California
was the place ♫
♫ Thought I might hold out awhile ♫
♫ and we could start to move
from grass to grace. ♫
You're wearing a courtroom suit
and you have litigator eyes.
You here for me?
No.
Dave.
Linda.
Gordy!
Isn't there a game on?
I can't find the clicker.
Yeah.
Tell me you're not a lawyer.
Okay, I'm not a lawyer.
Are you selling something? Art?
Insurance? Pharmaceuticals?
- What about real estate?
- Great.
That's good.
Yep. I'm in from Phoenix.
My 87-year-old husband
He's taking a six-hour nap,
I'm taking a five-hour walk.
How's that work for you?
- Perfect.
- Good.
- I am looking to refinance.
- That's good.
Gordy.
Anyway, thank you for
talking to me.
Yeah, well, I figure I'll be safe.
Everybody's watching
your every move.
Now they're watching you.
Maybe I like being watched.
Well, I'm watching you.
You are the most beautiful
woman I've ever seen...
in this bar.
What are you doing?
I gotta go.
Sneaking out on me?
- You don't have to go.
- I gotta go.
Come here. Give me that purse.
I gotta go.
- You don't have to go anywhere.
- I gotta go. I do.
Okay, I gotta go. I have to go.
You have to stay.
- What's the matter?
- Jesus! Hartshorn.
You too famous for me
all of a sudden?
It's all deliberate provocation.
They predicted your response,
and you fell for it.
And who are "they?"
"They?" They who don't like you.
And why me?
Because they don't like you.
Look, what do I know?
Maybe it's a coincidence
the camera was there.
Look, if this is the gang
fucks, I don't mind.
Or generic criminal scum, bogus
lawsuit settlement scum.
Press scum.
I can deal with scum.
But if this is Rampart, L.A.P.D.,
some fucking girly politician
setting me up as a shit magnet
to take the heat off
the fucking scandal,
I gotta go deep into this.
Look, what can I do?
I am just a law-abiding retiree
enjoying his golden years.
Fuck you with the Mickey
Cohen routine, old man.
You've got your fingers
in more Department twat
han any active cop I know.
Now, milk your contacts.
I've got cash left from
the Harris job.
Thanks for that, by the way.
You could just stop
beating people up.
This isn't your father's
L.A.P.D., you know.
I know.
It's more fun than a
barrel of monkeys.
It is a barrel of monkeys.
I'll get through it. I always do.
You know, when you first
came in the Department,
I wasn't certain whether you
were the dumbest rookie ever
or the most bull-headed.
I'm still debating it.
That's what my old man
said about you,
you were the most bullheaded
man he ever met.
I should have filed
Murder One on you
for that date-rape shooting.
I would've booked him on
eleven counts of rape,
Sodomy One, penetration with
a foreign weapon, etc.
Gentlemen, can we talk about
the present circumstances?
Fourteen years, tops.
I'd say your punishment
breached legal status
as well as moral code.
"The law must acknowledge and
occasionally accommodate..."
"the extraordinary vicissitudes of
justice." Judge D.T. Eagleton, 1946.
I don't know that quote.
You went to Cal State.
At least I passed the bar.
Knock it off.
Barely, I'm told. Hence, politics.
Should I break out the
milk and cookies here?
Can we actually talk about
the possibility
of your holding a press
conference together,
addressing what's happened
with Mr. Parmallee,
issuing an apology, and moving on?
It would help if I'd done
something wrong.
You've done nothing wrong.
Someone planted a camera in my way.
Maybe it's you, maybe
it's someone smart...
definitely smarter than me,
because I don't stop to see
if there's a photographer nearby
when I do the people's dirty work.
So you can't see yourself taking
any responsibility that
moves us beyond this?
No, because the only thing
that's wrong here
is that a camera caught him
doing "police work."
Is this a fucking joke to you?
You think it's funny?
What is funny and peculiar
to me is how this office
spends all its time going
after decent cops.
Did you do it?
Do what?
Without admitting guilt or
complicity, did you actually
kill that rapist?
Alleged rapist?
Did you do it?
I don't live in the past.
Is that a yes?
Let me rephrase. If you were to have
done it, could you tell me why?
So women would love me.
I don't think that could
be the reason.
I'm curious why you're so curious.
We can talk about it this weekend.
Give me a call.
Brown, I have your number.
I bet you do.
The stupidest trade in the
history of sports...
What did you do to the Captain?
Come on, let's get back
to homework, hon.
You have anything you
want to say to me?
As in what?
Why am I still collecting
a paycheck?
Shondell skipped town.
His nerves are shot. And that civil
lawsuit is still going forward.
Someone upstairs is pulling
strings for you.
Close the door.
Shoot.
Close the door with
you on the outside.
I'm L.A.P.D. And I want
to stay L.A.P.D.
That's the most important
thing for me.
Why?
Why what?
I'm just asking. What if we
negotiated a settlement?
Why is staying a cop the
most important thing?
Because I'm a hard-charging
dutiful motherfucker,
and I want to explicate the L.A.P.D.'s
somewhat hyperbolized misdeeds
with true panache, regardless
of my alleged transgressions.
Capiche?
In other words, I have nowhere
else to go, so...
if I get canned by the Department,
I swear to God,
I'll study for the bar this
time, and come back here
and work as your token fascist.
Well...
we'll need a retainer.
That's standard.
- You're so cute.
- No, you're cute.
- Have you seen my pick?
- No.
- Are you still mad at me?
- Yeah.
Why? What did I do?
Whatever.
You didn't even finish it.
I just quit.
Right.
Hey. You remember when we used
to make up songs together?
You know, like that one...
"I am you and you are me"
- "we were always meant to be"
- No.
"You are me and I am you"
- "And we were meant
to see it through."
- No.
You have to remember that.
I have no idea what you're
talking about.
Let's take a walk.
No, I'm busy.
How long you been standing there?
"You are me, I am you..."
Get out.
Get out, Dave.
Yeah?
Hey. Back in town?
Yeah, it was fun.
What do you mean, "the truth?"
So you were lying about everything?
Dave, we were playing with
each other. C'mon.
I liked the way you moved,
okay? That was it.
It's like a John wayne thing
or something. I don't know.
And I like to suck cock. So sue me.
It seemed like a fine idea
at the time, didn't it?
And you were asking for it, Dave.
"Tell me you're not
a lawyer." I did.
There's something you're
not telling me.
What, that I hate the scum that
I represent? Okay, I told you.
And when I was at the
D.A.'s office,
at least I got to see
these guys go down.
That's not it.
Dave, I help criminals go free
with County cash in their fuckin'
pockets because L.A.P.D. Fucks up.
And 8 times out of 10, they're
right back at Rampart again.
You're giving me a
closing statement.
- You came looking for me.
- No, I didn't.
What is it you're not telling me?
You're either lying to me
or you're withholding.
This is what I do.
The guy that you killed,
the date-rape guy...
I'm a defense attorney. And
I'm not supposed to, but
I respect what you did.
I'm sorry.
No proof I killed anyone.
I have daughters.
I'm sorry.
Can I sleep with you tonight?
Yes.
Nice surprise.
- Hello.
Was she any good?
She was.
I've got to talk to you.
Can't it wait?
No.
I'm kind of busy right now.
We've got to put the houses
on the market.
You've got to start thinking about
finding another place to live. Okay?
No. That's not okay.
You've got to do it.
This isn't working.
You can't do that.
Everybody living on
top of each other?
You know it isn't working
as well as I do.
- We've got to...
- You can't do that.
We gotta go our own ways.
You can't make the decisions
for us anymore.
You've got to let us go.
That's not acceptable. We've got
to keep everybody together.
This is gonna blow over,
I promise you.
We've been trying to keep us
together for a long time.
But we've got to know
when we're licked.
You've got to let us go.
- Don't say that.
- You've got to let us go.
I'll never let you go.
- That's what I mean.
- I'll never let you go.
"You won't see me no more"
"'Cause I'm gonna stay
down here in L.A."
They all know someone like
me is more dangerous
on the witness stand
than on the streets.
Right?
You gave them only one option.
Top brass is gonna try to bury
the beating and the scandal
and keep you as the sideshow.
Keep the press guessing while they
investigate it into oblivion.
Just stick to the "assault with
a deadly weapon" routine,
and they won't touch you.
I hope you're right.
Meanwhile, I'm hemorrhaging cash.
I know that twitch.
Okay.
There's gonna be a high-stakes
card game
at the Crystal Market tonight.
You didn't hear it from me, buddy.
Thanks, Hart. You don't know
how much this means to me.
I was gonna mention
it before, but...
You know, man, the shape
you're in, jeez...
I hate to see you bled
dry like that.
How you doing?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're hanging in there.
- Hanging in there.
- You're hanging in there.
- You keeping it going.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm in on this one, too.
What have you got?
I'm in on this one.
Twenty on that one.
Shut the fuck up!
Don't even look up!
Look the fuck down!
Stop moving, motherfuckers!
No, fuck! I got kids, man, please!
Don't fucking kill me!
Take off your mask.
Take off your mask!
Alright, man!
Please don't fucking shoot
me, man! Please!
Get some money out of there.
Put it in your fucking pocket!
Hurry up, goddamnit!
Go! Go!
Brown is embroiled in a high-stakes
card game robbery
that he apparently...
Is this a two box or a three box.
I can't remember what you said.
That's the part that gets
me the most upset, Mom,
is when you keep saying sorry.
I know, I just feel bad.
Why do you feel bad? You didn't
do anything. What did you do?
That's the point. I
didn't do anything.
I'm sorry about the reporters.
Do you have cancer?
Because if you don't, I'm done.
We're done.
He fired at me three times.
I returned fire in self-defense.
It was self-defense.
I swear to God.
You need rest. You need to eat.
I didn't know about the
card game. I swear.
You need to set up shop
someplace else.
Right now.
I talked to Barb.
Big Jim.
The hookers that work the
bar weekends, your call.
I notify Central Nightwatch
or I don't.
You can't keep doing this, Dave.
A fifth of scotch, a room
and a wake-up call.
I could lose my job.
At least you'll be on the outside.
Your bun boy honked a Vice cop
at the Pink Parrot last night.
He's got a parole hold, so no bail.
Lorazapam and Phenobarb,
and it all goes away.
We've taken a look at
your team's report.
It's a pretty extensive package.
Not germane to the issue, sir.
I'd like the event to
be judged ad hoc.
Empirical knowledge often
distorts the content
of the act under scrutiny, sir.
You're not making this easy.
And you're not making friends here.
I have all the friends I need at
this stage in my life, sir.
Describe the events that
led up to your use
of deadly force, Officer Brown.
You're alive. And an
individual named...
Jose Lancha Macias is dead.
Now how did that occur?
At approximately 2350
hours, I was parked
near the southeast corner of Ewing
Street and Echo Park Avenue.
A man approached my patrol
car and stated
that he thought he had seen suspicious
men in the adjacent alley.
The alley in question was just
to the west of my location.
At this time, I observed an
unknown suspect with a gun
chasing another man who
appeared to be unarmed.
I identified myself verbally and began
chasing the man with the gun.
Get on past me.
Who tipped you to the game?
You know I can't give
you that, Dave.
You got a tip. I improvised.
There's a man dead.
How do you feel about that?
The streets smell cleaner already.
L.A.P.D. Is back in town, and
it's called Dave Brown.
Where's your gratitude?
Glad I could help.
I need to know.
Forget it, I can't. I don't play
games, I don't name names.
Shh yourself, goddammit!
That's the way I handle
it. You understand?
Yeah. It's a good motto.
What are the odds they go and I go
the same night to take
that game down?
What are the odds?
You handled it, Dave. Hurray.
I could have got killed myself.
You didn't.
I don't know how much more
of this shit I can take.
Jesus Christ!
Where were you? I left
you six messages.
I'm not your fucking girlfriend.
My battery died.
I nearly got killed the other night
while you were out looking
for a bone to chew on.
Where the hell were you?
Fuck you.
You're insane, Dave. You're insane.
Well, guess what, Linda? It
takes one to know one.
I want the truth.
You came after me that night.
Of course I fucking did. You're
the man of my dreams, right?
Who the hell are you working for?
You watch too much television.
I told you I'm on your side!
I'm not working for
anyone or anybody.
- You're paranoid.
- You're breaking my heart.
Yeah? You broke into
my fucking house.
I located your security flaw.
- Fuck you.
- Your pool gate was open.
Should I leave?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm a mess.
Will you sleep with me?
Just tonight?
No. You drink too much.
Really?
You're great in the sack, Linda,
but you lie to be liked.
Is that right?
That's right.
Yeah, well, guess what?
It takes one to know one.
You're a bitch. You know that?
Yeah.
General?
General!
Get over here, now!
How are you doing?
Doing okay. How're you?
I'm good.
How are you?
- Didn't we just go through this?
- Yeah.
Hey... look at me.
Look me right in the eye.
Did you see anything
unusual lately?
No.
Anything around the Crystal Market?
I said no. I didn't see shit.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- You positive?
- Not a damn thing.
Fancy.
Go ahead, take two.
What the hell happened
to your head?
Watch that beard.
Don't want to see you
go up in smoke.
Two dickhead cops
broke flashlights on me.
Ow!
Fuck! Don't do that!
Just keeping the streets safe.
I'm not hurting anybody.
If I sell a little, smoke a little,
it's no big deal to nobody.
I'm nobody. I'm nothing.
I'm nobody. Nobody.
They got fucking niggers
slinging golf balls
up and down these streets.
All talk, cavi, cavi, cavi, cavi.
Want to crack my head open.
Asshole cops.
Give me a sip.
Here.
Call this lawyer, sue the L.A.P.D.
Linda.
Is she hot? Linda... Fentress?
And blonde all over.
Fuck, yeah.
Why, your thing still working?
No. Not really.
But a starving man eats
the best pussy.
Are we brothers?
You're my brother.
Keep it...
brother.
- Hey, man.
- Can I help you?
Let me get a number six.
A number six.
Okay. It'll be five minutes.
You fucking with me?
What?
I'm listening. What are you, I. A?
Man, I'm just sitting here
trying to get my shrimp.
Is that what you're gonna
say next time I spot you?
Here we go. Here we go.
Kyle Timkins, D.A. Investigator.
You say both robbers escaped?
That's kind of hard to believe.
Also, there's a big gap between
the time the neighbors
say they heard the shots and
you reported the incident.
Also, it's kind of strange
that you would be in that location
without your radio.
Why isn't the Robbery Unit on this when
both robbers did indeed escape?
- Your recent misconduct...
- Perceived misconduct.
Perceived misconduct brings into
question your mental state
on the night of the incident.
That's why I'm here.
Listen, uh, Jack...
No, I'm Kyle.
Listen, Jack...
you got this assignment because
I'm controversial
and your ancestors were
stolen from Africa.
You got this assignment to
cover the Department on
perceived racial bias
pertaining to Shondell J. Parmallee
and other shit-faced scum.
You're mad as hell, and
you want me to know it.
But while you're playing gumshoe,
bear in mind that I
am not a racist.
Fact is, I hate all people equally.
And if it helps, I've slept
with some of your people.
You want to be mad at someone,
try J. Edgar Hoover.
He was a racist.
Or the Founding Fathers,
all slave-owners.
Me, I'm just doing my job.
All that may be true, but we're
not here talking about me.
We're here talking about you. Okay?
Officer Hoover?
I've got another question.
Why are you still with
the Department?
After all the shit that's going on,
the scandal, the Mayor, the
D.A., the Chief of Police,
why do they still have you around?
Must be because I'm innocent.
Nice to meet you, Kyle.
You all have seen how every
wannabe gangbanger
walking down the street being
pulled down by their dogs
Hey, Boss! Boss! Get him!
Get him, Boss! Boss, what did
I say? Sit tight. Hey, Boss!
Dave.
Stay up late last night?
Of course.
How you feeling?
Good, good, good.
Just waiting for the pits
to eat a protestor.
You know you're being watched?
What do you mean?
Good boy! There he goes.
There he goes.
I'm glad you found me.
It wasn't hard. I just wanted
to see for myself.
Mom says you're deeper in the shit.
Those are my words, not hers.
Well...
people keep telling me that.
Well, maybe it's true, then.
Yeah, I am.
You took a cab, right?
Tell me you didn't take a bus
out here to the goddamn jungle.
It's the Barrio, Dad. It's
not the fucking jungle.
- And yes, I took a bus.
- I told you, babe,
I don't want you...
Don't call me "babe."
I don't want you straying
east of La Brea...
It's disgusting.
How is... How's school?
It sucks.
It's full of...
"candy-assed future fags
and dykes, like me."
Those are your words, not mine.
I never said that.
How's it going at home?
Margaret's onto you. She's angry.
Guess that's something every Dave
Brown daughter has to go through.
You're a dinosaur, Date-rape.
You're a classic racist,
a bigot, a sexist.
A womanizer, a chauvinist,
a misanthrope,
homophobic clearly, or maybe
you don't like yourself.
How long did it take you
to rehearse that?
Well, say something.
Don't touch me, say something!
Why don't I drive you home?
No, I don't want to go home.
They're having an open house.
I don't want to be there.
I want to be at Jo's.
Joe/Joseph or Jo/Josephine?
I'll just take the bus!
Helen... I'm kidding!
Yeah.
Your phone is tapped.
Don't say a word.
Jesus, the shit I have to take
care of because of you.
You're just like your father, Dave.
You think you're smarter
than you are.
Every shooting testimony contains
inconsistencies.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have a job.
No man who ever shoots
and kills another man
is entirely cogent in the moment.
No plan survives contact
with the enemy.
Did you learn that with the
first man you killed?
I learned that serving my country
as a non-electric pop-up target
in an often misunderstood crusade
for liberty and justice
turned puppet show for politicians
Called Vietnam.
Known as the Vietnam war.
Can we not go to Vietnam today?
Let's fast-forward to the present.
Why are you looking
to hang me? Why me?
I know you're setting me up.
Blago's got it in for me.
Answer my question. Of all the
truly rotten cops out there
why are you after the
one guy who gets it?
"The one cop who gets it"?
- Are you in on this?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
Let me remind you that
several years ago
you killed an alleged serial
date-rapist premeditatively.
Did you know that he had a wife
and three small children?
She had a nervous breakdown
after his death,
and ended up in an insane asylum,
where she spent nine years
until she cut her wrists with
a disposable razor blade.
The kids were raised, by the
way, in foster homes.
Two of them alleged that they
were sexually abused by
their foster fathers.
So please don't come
in here whining.
You've got a lot of nerve.
Up this time. And something
to make it hard.
Watch it, man.
I mean, I feel like...
Dave, what are you doing here?
Listen, my lawyers are burning
through my money
and we're gonna have to
tighten our belts.
We're gonna have a trial
date soon, so...
what are you even doing here, Dave?
I came to talk to you about this.
You don't live here any more.
You can't walk in like
you still live here.
Oh, for God's sakes.
You know what I think?
I think you were a dirty
cop from day one.
Okay.
You were a dirty cop
with a dirty mind
and you dirtied all of
us up by default.
I think you think you can
just ride this out,
thinking you can go back
to your fucking
- You've got to go.
- Tough guy, law and
order bullshit.
It's over, Dave. It's over.
You know what happened to you?
- Just let him go.
- First the bar. And then
- the women and the booze
- Cathy.
- You're a selfish man, Dave!
- Come on.
It's not worth it. Just let him go.
You were a bad husband.
You're a bad father.
- You're a bad lay.
- Why are you doing this?
Just let him go.
This "man keeping family
together" bullshit?
It's fucked the girls
up forever. Forever.
Helen is out here. Can you stop?
You don't know one thing
about your girls.
You are a fraud, Dave.
That's enough.
- You're a fraud.
- You've got to go.
Okay.
It's okay.
Bye.
Come on. Everything's okay.
Let's go inside.
I'm sorry, honey.
Damn it.
I'm thirsty.
I'll bet you are.
Come on, just give me a pull.
Just give me a pull.
Get your fucking hand
out of the car.
Come on. You're my brother.
Just a sip. A sip.
Give me a smoke.
Give me a smoke. I want a cigarette.
Give me a cigarette.
No.
Yeah. Come on, give me a drink.
Sober up.
Linda's a good woman. She's taken
really good care of me.
We're gonna take all your
asshole friends down.
Can you spot me a fiver?
I don't feel so hot.
Sell your wheelchair.
Fuck you, white skin. I got robbed.
I need a blanket.
Five bucks, please.
Just five bucks.
Do I look like Santa Claus to you?
No, you don't look like Santa
Claus. You're my brother.
Us vets got to stick
together, don't we?
I'm not your brother.
- I don't have a family.
- Yes you are. Yes you do.
I'll pay you back.
I'll pay you back when Linda
and I make a killing.
- Stop saying her name.
- Linda.
You stop saying her name, okay?
You say her name one more time,
I'll hurt you.
You don't get it. We're
gonna be rich as shit.
I'm gonna go around the world,
around the world.
Around the world. Around the world.
I'm gonna tell my story and they're
gonna fucking pay me.
I'm gonna be on talk shows.
I'm gonna have a suit.
- What did you tell her?
- I told her everything.
- Tell me exactly what
you told her.
- I told her my plan...
about we're gonna get a
big house together...
somewhere in Northern California
on a lot of property where
anybody can come
who needs a place, has a place
where you can shower,
you can hang out,
or you can get your head right.
All my friends are gonna be there,
so you should definitely come.
And Linda will make us eggs.
What about the Crystal Market?
- I told her everything.
- Everything?
Everything.
Come on, give me a drink.
Get the fuck out of here!
What the hell are you doing?
Why, are you afraid of something?
Will you come inside? Come
on. It's raining.
Yeah, I can see that. I'm already
in. What does it matter?
What are you doing?
General told you.
Who?
He saw me shoot that man in the Crystal
Market and drop a piece on him.
Baby, I don't want to hear this.
It's raining. Come inside.
He got roughed up by the
L.A.P.D. That's all.
You gonna believe him over me?
- What?
- Get in the pool.
I'm not getting in the
fucking pool. No.
If you're on my side, get
in the fucking pool.
No. You're crazy. I'm going in.
Get in the fucking pool.
I'm going in. You make
the next move.
- Get in the pool.
- Don't fucking touch me. Get off.
Don't go inside. Get in this pool.
No.
- Come here.
- No.
- Don't.
- Get in this pool.
No.
You bitch.
Come in.
You think you can take me down?
I don't need you! I
don't need anyone!
I'm just a fucking cop!
I'm a fucking soldier!
I'm dispensable!
There're a lot of other
cocks to suck!
You're heartless, Linda!
You played me!
I hate you! I fucking hate you!!
Are you even listening, you bitch?!
Get in this fucking pool!
Discrepancies and inconsistencies.
Ah, Jesus.
Dave, I've got six card players,
all of them claiming that
it was a no weapons game.
Four of them heard the shots.
All of them claim it was
two sets of three pops,
all at the same clip,
which indicates you fired
your weapon first.
Right? Now, I traced
the gun right back
to this station right here.
Ballistics show that
the gun was involved
in another officer shooting.
Alright?
So I'm sweating the cop
that sold you the gun,
because not only can I prove
that his shooting was dirty,
I can prove that your
shooting was dirty,
just like I can prove you're dirty.
I got two eyewitnesses
that saw your ass
outside of that Crystal Market
right before it jumped off.
So go home and pack a bag.
Make sure there's a
wetsuit in there
because I'm sending your
ass up the river.
Come on, baby.
I've been up river, motherfucker,
when you were still sucking
on your mama's tit.
My mother died when I was born,
you racist son-of-a-bitch.
You save that Grand wizard
shit for the jury.
I need you to help me put
a leash on Kyle Timkins.
Help you?
That's all I do is help.
I am not the help.
Crystal Market.
Again with the market.
No, still with the market.
You're covering for someone
who's trying to bury me.
I'm not sure I understand
the rules, okay?
The rules change.
The laws change. The people change.
They accommodate. They adapt.
But not you.
Why is that?
Explain to me exactly what happened
at the Crystal Market.
I've got to get away from you.
I've got a business to
protect, contacts.
I don't know you. I don't know...
Put that away.
Why me, Hart? Why me?
Stop whining. Why you?
Why me? Why anybody?
You set me up.
You set yourself up, Dave.
Give me the gun.
Call an ambulance.
Hey.
Come in.
What was that noise?
Oh, the lock.
Come on. Come in. Get out
of the hallway. Please.
Come on.
Hey, what a surprise.
Do you want to give it to him?
- I thought you wanted to.
- No, I'm fine.
These are for you.
Thank you.
- How are you?
- Good.
Yeah?
So tell me... what have
you been up to?
Nothing. We just came by
to drop off the clothes.
Oh. Okay.
You found me.
How did you do that?
There was a caller I.D.
What?
Caller I.D. You called
the house from here.
That's good police work.
Yeah, it was really hard.
So...
here you are.
Come on in. Don't be afraid.
You want to sit?
No.
Can I get you a soda?
- No, I'm good.
- Yeah?
Okay.
You don't want anything?
No, I'm good.
You look beautiful, both of you.
Your face looks red.
Too much sun.
It means he's been drinking.
Haven't you?
What?
You've been drinking.
I was just... Yeah, a little bit.
A little bit.
Okay. Wow.
- Do you wanna go?
- Yeah.
I don't know.
We're gonna go.
You want to talk a little bit?
No, that's fine.
Hey. Hey.
I know why you came.
To drop off the clothes.
Let's go. Come on.
You want to know if it's true.
Every bad thing you've
heard about me?
You want me to give you some
way out so it doesn't
hurt so much.
There's no way out.
Every single thing you heard
and more, it's all true.
I can never... change.
But I want you to know
I never hurt any good people.
What about us?
No, that's not what I mean, Helen.
I don't understand
what you do mean.
Have I hurt you?
I didn't mean to.
We have to go, okay?
Hey.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- Hey. Come on.
Hey! Hey, come here!
- Come back to the room.
- What are you doing?
I love you, monkey. You
know that, right?
I'm not letting you do this.
I'm gonna get you a soda, okay?
- I'll get you a soda.
- No.
Will you come back? Monkey,
come back to the room.
What's on your mind, Hoover?
This is Officer David D. Brown
of the Los Angeles
Police Department.
This statement is made
of my own free will.
During my twenty-four
year police career
I employed brutal and coercive
methods at whim.
And... created racial animus
with reckless disregard for the law
that I was sworn to uphold
as a police officer.
On April 15th, 1987,
I murdered a business acquaintance
of mine, Karl Joseph Huneck
and rationalized the act
as a morally sound expression
of street justice
against a man who I knew to
be a serial date-rapist.
I was legally sane at the
time I committed the act.
Over the years, I've killed many
men. Bad guys, all of them.
And if there are one
or two exceptions
I can only assume they ended up
on the wrong end of my gun
to satisfy some karmic breech.
This statement is proffered
lucidly.
I am not in a state of duress.
Okay.
I'll give you this tape
if you cut me a deal.
I don't want your tape.
What?
That's not the confession I want.
You want that fucking Crystal Market
case. You're a fucking idiot.
Next time I see you, I'm
putting cuffs on you.
Are you out of your mind?
Timkins! Take what you've got,
which is a good case.
It's the wrong confession.
Take the fucking tape.
You fucking idiot.
Take this fucking tape!
You're a fucking idiot, Timkins!
Fucking idiot.
But this one has something
in her ear.
Oh!
Watch.
- Where did it go?
- You get to keep it.
Where will it say? Oh, 1882.
1882? That's pretty valuable.
Really? That's so sweet of
you. Oh, my goodness.
Where you going?
Smoke.
- What?
- Smoke.
What did she say?