Andy, have you seen my new blue tie?
Yeah, second cabinet, uh, top left drawer.
Great.
Uh, briefcase? Anywhere?
Front door!
Okay, I know I had a
few drinks last night,
but I could've sworn when I came
home, this place was full of boxes.
I know. I unpacked this
morning.Want a tour?
No, that's okay.
It'll just be like a scavenger
hunt every morning.It'll be great.
What's wrong?
I'm just scattered.I
got court this morning.
What, you got butterflies, detective?
Yeah, a little, before I
testify.It's no big deal.
Well, you look great.
Yeah, so do you.
- You know what?
- What?
- I'm happy.
- I know. Me, too.
Ooh, I'm really hoping
those aren't Dov's hands.
You know what I'm hoping?
Yeah, I keep telling you, your
voice will drop once puberty hits.
Thanks, hon.
Actually, I was hoping to use
my bathroom, in my apartment,
because, you know, I pay rent here.
Sorry.Sorry, bro.
Six weeks off the job.
It feels great to be back in action.
So how long is Gail gonna be here, man?
'Cause I didn't sign
up for another roommate.
What are you talking
about? She's not a roommate.
Sweetie, don't put your
brush in my drawer.
Your hair gets in my
moisturizer, and it's nasty.
Sorry, babe. What?
Nothing.Nothing.I'm just gonna
go take a pee... in your room.
What's that?
A little housewarming
card for your new place.
Apparently, that's you and Luke.
Leo is in his purple phase.
Very cute. Thank you.
So how's the move going? You settled?
Uh, yeah. It's great.I actually
have everything unpacked.
What?
You, the girl who took six months
to hang pictures in her last place?
I know. It's-it's different now.
It's like... it's like I
know where everything belongs.
It's very good.
Is that... Boyd?
- Yeah.
- What is he doing here?
Trying to get Swarek back into guns
and gangs, some kinda task force.
McNally, Nash.
Sir.
Uh, I need you over at supernova.
There's a concert going on there.
1,000 wristbands went out, and
they only got room for 800.
You're in charge, McNally.Take
the other rookies.
Great.Who's playin'?
Just another day at the office.
I said, get down!
Oh, I was looking for my friends.
Yeah, you were standing
on top of my cruiser.
I wasn't standing. I was dancing.
What are you on, genius?
Um, natural high.
Natural high, my ass.
Let's go. Let's go!
- Thank you.Thank you.
- Okay, okay. That's enough.
Hey, Andy, what do you want me to
do with the rest of the stragglers?
Uh, if they have
wristbands, get 'em in line.
If not, uh, put 'em on the sidewalk.
Okay.
Hey, so, uh, I was just wondering- and
it's totally cool with me either way...
But, uh, how long do you think you'll
be staying, you know, at the place?
Oh, you were wondering?
Come on, people.
If you're hiding any alcohol or
drugs, now's your chance to dump it.
Have your pockets and
purses ready to be searched.
Better be water in that bottle.
Officer Epstein.
Come on, people. Patience is a virtue.
- Dov? Dov Epstein?
- Mark? Mark Johnson.
- How are you?
- Great, man.
- Wow.Not in a million years.
- Dov.
- I haven't seen you since, uh...
- Your brother's birthday.
The big 2-5.
Where the-where
barbecue caught on fire.
Yeah, man.So how's he doing?
- How is Adam?
- Great.He's great.
Uh... actually, I-I don't
know why I just said that.
He died about four years ago, so
yeah... uh, anyway, great to see you, mark.
Let's go, people. Wait now, tweet later.
All right, they're letting
them in ten at a time.
We just need to keep
the rest of 'em calm.
This is what happens when you put the
word "free" in front of the word "concert."
See, I love it. That's free
music.That's culture to the masses.
Don't get any of your
culture on my car, buddy.
That's right.Take it over there.
What, are you practicing your "bad
cop" routine for guns and gangs?
I haven't decided yet.
What's holding you back?
You.
I love working with you, McNally.I
can't imagine my life without you in it.
Hey, you get to wear
all that hair gel again.
We got a problem at the door.
I'm on it.
See you later.
What's up?
50 more-that's it. Then the
doors are shutting for good.
Great.The crowd's gonna go nuts.
Let's hope. Maybe the riot squad will
let me shoot someone with a water Cannon.
What's wrong with you?
I haven't driven over 60 on this job.
I need a little action.
Fine. Then go take the back of the
line. They're definitely not getting in.
All right, you guys, cool it.
Any pushing or shoving, and
you're going home.
Sorry to bother you, officer, but security
told me that the line was over here,
and I was waiting over there, and I didn't
want to leave, just in case-I feel ridiculous.
My only job was to stand in
line and watch my friend's place,
and now I'm not even in that line.
Look, I'm watching my roommate's
spot. We have wristbands.
Where's your friend?
She's just around the corner.
There's nothing I can do. I
mean, we're closing it off.
Look, she went to go get hot
chocolate for me at Artie's.
I got confused. The guy said
that it was to the right, and...
You always do what
people tell you to do?
- Pretty much.
- Yeah, me, too.
Well, used to, anyway.
Artie's is really good, by
the way.It takes forever, but...
- You can't hurry love.
- That's true.
All right, I'll make
sure I get you guys in.
Thank you.Seriously, my roommate
has been dying to see this show.
Yeah, no problem.
Hey, boss.
I'm gonna keep things
moving, if, uh, that's okay with you.
Okay.
- Boyfriend?
- No.
He's my tr
well, was my training officer.
He's cute. I had a lab partner
like that. Acts all tough, but...
Oh, yeah?
Lie back!
1509.Shots fired.
Supernova, queens quay and Richardson.
Two people shot. Officer down.
Rush an ambulance right
away. Repeat-officer down.
It's okay. It's all
right.Just let the air out.
McNally, you're gonna be fine, okay?
You gotta stay down. Don't
try to get up. All right?
Looks like the bullet just
got stuck in your vest.
Just stay put.Just try to breathe, okay?
Andy. Andy, you're
fine. You just got winded.
The bullet's stuck in your vest. Okay?
I'll be back. I gotta
be the boss right now.
Nash, Diaz, get that thing.Move it
over there.Get it out of the way.
Right here.
Gunshot wound, the back of
the head-the red jacket.
Back of the head. That's all that
I can see.I got pressure on it.
I'm right here.
No, no, no, no, no, McNally.Mcnally, sit
back. Sit back, relax.It's okay, okay?
I need you to stay put for a
second. We gotta get you checked out.
I'm good. I'm fine.
I know you are.But that blood, that bullet
you're evidence, okay?
Just breathe.
Hey, Epstein, you're
gonna stay with the girl.
Diaz, round up those people. Get 'em over
there.Don't let anybody go, all right?
Get 'em all over there.
Okay, everybody, I need
all of you to step back.
What happened?!
Uh, j-you can't go. Just
calm down. Just calm down.
Kate!
Calm down. Just
just calm down.
Oh, my God!
All right, Epstein, you're gonna
stay with her until further notice.
Okay? Write everything down
time of arrival, time that she goes into surgery,
all of her doctors' names, time that she's declared
if she's declared.
Okay? Stay on your phone.I'm
gonna go find her family.
Wait. What's her name?
Kate.
I think her name is Kate.
I need you to bag her for me.
C.T.A.S.One.
I have a 22-year-old female
with a g.S.W.To the head.
G.C.S.Is a 3.E.T.A.5 minutes.
What's happening?
Anyone notifying her next of kin?
- Oliver's working on it.
- Good.
Shots came from over there.
We got 3 casings from
a.380.1 of them got trampled.
No sign of the weapon.
Peck and Diaz are rounding up witnesses.
The victim's roommate is
heading to the station.
Who's helping from homicide?
Oh, we're trying to reach
Callaghan, but he's in court all day.
He's got his phone off.Not
that this is a homicide.
Looks like it's gonna be.
Oh, and we are going to treat it as
such. Detective, thanks for coming.
Heard most of it on the
radio on my way over.
I'm glad to help. Got me out of a sewer.
Detective jo rosati. She was trained
at homicide. She works out at 27.
Sam Swarek.
Oliver Shaw. How are you?
Where's the rookie
the one who got hit?
Andy McNally.She's right over there.
Okay, then. Uh, I'm gonna start with her.
You guys look like you have
the rest of this under control.
- You did good, McNally.
- Frank.
Jo, good to see you.
McNally, this is, uh, detective rosati.
She's gonna ask you a few questions.
That hurt? You okay?
Yeah, I'm good. I'm fine.
Yeah, I bet.
First of all, we're gonna
need your vest, okay?
Okay.
Walter, right?
It's okay. Relax.Relax.
- Okay. Let's have a look.
- Sorry?
I'm serious.You're gonna
have to go to the hospital.
Let's see how soon.
I'm fine, really.
How many times have you said that today?
A hundred.
Well, you're probably gonna have to say
it about a hundred more, but good on ya.
McNally, right?
Yeah.
You wanna tell me what happened?
- Yeah, I, uh...
- It's no rush, okay?
No big deal.
I got shot once. Vest, right up here.
Puked for three days.
Didn't go to work for a month.
I was
I was the painkiller queen.
I could tell you every
soap opera plot for 33 days.
She was really nice.
That girl was... very sweet.
Anyway, I-I let her
in, and, uh, I shouldn't have.
I- I could've made her go
home, but I-I let her in.
Sure. She was nice. Of
course you let her in.
So-so I did, and, um, we
were just talking.
She was behind me.
We were talking about, um, hot-hot chocolate, and...
And then there was the sh- she-she got shot.
Oh, my God.
You're doing great.Okay?
Hey, how you feeling?
I'm fine.
Sam, that was really
scary, and that hurt so bad.
I'm all right.
It's just that I've already got
this bruise that's forming, and-what?
Sam.
You gotta be kidding me.
You gotta get behind that truck.
Police. Get your hands up. Hands up.
- All right.
- You got any weapons on you?
- No.
- Turn around. Get down on the ground.
Down on the ground.
You got a gun on you, so help me God.
Give me that.
This is Swarek. I got a male
party in possession of a.380.
I'm in a lot behind the
communications truck.
Please. I'm telling you
the truth.It's not mine.
Someone must've left it there.
You should be looking
for them right now.
I was just minding my own business, going
for a walk, and I found it, okay?
Look, how many times
do I have to tell you?
It was there on the sidewalk.
I- I-I
picked it up!
That's probably enough
times.So you can shut up now.
- I was gonna turn it in to you guys. I swear.
- Is that him?
Oscar Benson-17,resides at 422 Beckett.
Good. Let's get started.
Ident's on the way over to check for
g.S.R., so don't let him wash his hands.
What the hell is g.S.R.?
'Cause whatever it is, I don't have it.
Oscar, it's okay. It's okay. This
is just standard procedure.
We're gonna have you
out in no time, all right?
But, uh, let's get you a place
to sit and, um, I'll find you, uh,
something to drink once we get in there.
Right this way.
She just bought you guys about 20
minutes...Before that kid starts thinking lawyer.
She's good.
Yeah, she is.
The hospital is five minutes from here.
Yeah, it's a very
it's a very quick trip.
You know that talk
you were gonna give me?
W
what talk?
My first day.
You said that we were gonna go and get a
coffee, and you were gonna give me the talk.
That's, uh, that's a long time ago.
Not really.
Okay.
Um... I'm Oliver.
Oliver Shaw. I'll be your training
officer, uh, until further notice.
You don't touch anything in
the car until, uh, I tell you to.
You don't write anything down in
your memo book until I tell you to.
You don't talk to oth-other
people. You look at me first.
You do as I say, not as, um, I do.
I know you probably think right now
I'm-I'm being a bit of a hard-ass,
but if it gets stressed out there, I will be, because my
my job is to keep you safe.
This crest, uh, on my shoulder
this represents, you, McNally, and we're...
We're both going home today.
That's a really good talk.
Andy? Andy.
- It's okay. It's not mine. It's fine.
- Where'd it get you?
It's just my ribs. It's
fine. I'm fine. I'm fine.
- Sorry.
- No, it's okay. It's okay. Relax, okay? It's just sore.
McNally.S
sorry.
Uh, the roommate wants
detective Callaghan.
Jo, what are you doing here?
I'm just in to help.
The roommate wants to talk to you.She's
in the d's office. If you're up for it.
I hear we got the shooter.
Yeah, looks like. We found a kid with
a gun.We're just about to talk to him.
You don't have to do this. Just give
'em your statement.I'll drive you home.
Yeah, you know what? I
understand that. I'm fine, okay?
I want to be here. I need to be here.
We'd been in line for, like, an hour.
I mean, she was cold. She's always freezing. So
I went to get us some hot chocolate.
And I shouldn't have gone. I
shouldn't have waited for it.
I should've just come right back.
Miranda, I get what you're saying, but
it wouldn't have changed anything.
She didn't even want to come today.
Kate barely even listens to music.I
mean, she listens to classical.
But she says it helps her study.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, we're just talking about Kate.
Okay.
Oscar Benson-no priors, but
his brother's in a gang.
- Doesn't mean he is.
- Doesn't mean he isn't.
Think it's an initiation?
Yeah, targeting a cop
in certain circles, that might buy you some credibility.
Okay, Luke, we got it.
- What, are you serious?
- Yeah, I called her.
You were in court.I needed backup.
Yeah, but I'm here now, and
this guy shot a cop.
A cop who happens to be your girlfriend.
I mean, unless she's not, and
you just like to make out
with every cute officer
who takes a bullet.
Uh, I-it's a conflict.
Okay, you do live with her.
Congratulations.
Jerry, this is what I do, all right?
So I'm doing something.
All right, your name goes on nothing, and
you have to stay away from this guy.
- Fine.
- I'm gonna take first crack.
Uh, all right with you? I'm not
really up for playing good cop.
You guys used to partner together, right?
Yeah.
She ever play good cop?
- No.
- Right.
So the girl you shot's
in critical condition.
And guess what else.
You also shot a police officer, Oscar.
I didn't shoot anyone.
Can you just tell me who you were
aiming for, or should I ask your brother?
My brother has nothing to do with it.
So you did it all by yourself?
That's not what I meant.
I seriously doubt that you
were aiming for Kate novatski,
but I guess that's the problem
with shooting into a crowd.
I saw a gun on the
sidewalk. I picked it up.
Why didn't you come forward?
I wanted to sell it. I could
get 500 bucks for that thing.
You found it?
Yeah, that's right.
They took her into surgery at 14:43.
Doesn't look good.
What else can I do?
I'll call you back.
- Ms. novatski.
- Where's Katie? Is she okay?
She's in surgery right
now.I'll take you there.
- You were with her?
- I was in the ambulance.
Was she awake? Responsive? How
much blood did she lose?
Ma'am, a doctor will give you all that...
Okay, look, please. I'm a
nurse at oakville general.
I know how these things work.
They're gonna shove
me into a waiting room,
and they're not gonna tell me
anything until she's out of surgery,
so I need to know something.
She was outside at a concert
hall. There were shots fired.She got hit.
Where? Where was she hit?
It's a head injury.
Was there any brain activity?
Ms. novatski, you need
to talk to a doctor.
Katie-she wanted to
be a... an organ donor.
It was really important to her.
And she's young, and she's, uh...
She's healthy, so with a head wound,
she's a very good
candidate to be a donor.
So you need to help me.
Okay.
Somebody must've seen something.We
just gotta jog their brains a bit.
Charming.
- Don't judge me.
- Too late.
All right, everyone
take a seat, over there.
All right, since none of you
ran when the shots were fired,
and we didn't find any weapons on
you, right now you're not suspects.
But nobody is going home until
we know everything you know.
Yeah, every little detail, and we really
don't care if it takes all night.
I'll stay up all night with you.
You'll stay up all night washing
the pepper spray out of your eyes
if don't let go of me right now.
All right, who wants to go first?
How about who's had less
than six drinks today?
Lightweight, you're up.
I got something, but I don't
think you're gonna like it.
Try me.
2:33 P.M.- the exact time the gunshots
were fired- Oscar Benson was on his phone.
With his gangbanging brother?
No, with his God-fearing mother.
They were on from 2:26 to 2:37 P.M.
11 minutes on the phone with his mother.
That'd be a record for me. I'd
definitely shoot somebody.
I told you you weren't gonna like it.
I like anything that gets us answers.
So maybe he did find the gun.At
least we still got the weapon.
That was ballistics.
The gun was jammed, but the bullet we got
out of Andy's vest is a match to Oscar's gun.
The gun jammed?
Yeah, that means shot number four
never made it out of the barrel.
It's over. I just got back from the
hospital. Kate novatski's not gonna make it.
I need a minute of your time.
Kate novatski was pre-med.
She wrote her college admissions
essay on organ donation.
Donor card's complete. It's the
only thing her mother wants.
We gotta find a way.
Dov, as soon as they take her off
the respirator, it becomes a homicide.
Chain of evidence, forensics, autopsy
we need the body intact.
She got shot in the head. We know what
happened. What do her lungs have to do with it?
What the hell does her
heart have to do with it?
D
Dov.I get it.
You were there with the
mother. It's terrible.
Yeah, it's terrible, but it
doesn't have to be meaningless,
'cause right now that's
all it's ever gonna be.
But for this woman, for this family, we
have a chance to do something
that'll actually help 'em get
through this, so come on, please.
Fine. So we get a signed confession
today, before they take her off the respirator,
before they do the autopsy.
I'll make a case to the
coroner, and we take it from there.
No, seriously, let's work it out.
Signed confession today, huh?
Yeah. It's always good to have a goal.
Roommate literally laughed when I asked
if Kate was involved in anything illicit.
Uh, she's an "a"
student, full scholarship.
No-no boyfriend, no enemies.
McNally, you gotta go home, okay?
No, I don't need to go home, okay? I don't
want to go home. What am I gonna do?
You want me to watch some tv?
You want me
you want me to take a nap?
Listen, if I'm gonna
figure this thing out,
then I need to understand why...
Understand? What are
you gonna understand?
Shots were fired.You were hit.She
was hit.She's on a respirator.
Kate. Kate's not a "she."
It's Kate, and she was
standing right next to me,
and-and I-I need
to know who she is.
Okay.
Take the roommate back to residence
and talk to her on the way.
Okay.
I don't understand.
If Kate's on a respirator, then
she's still alive.
Not exactly.
The machine's keeping her
breathing, but... I'm so sorry.
You know what? I can take you to the
hospital right now if you want to see her.
No, I don't want to go
there.Her mom is there.
I'm the reason her daughter's dead
or-or almost dead or, like, about to die.
I made her come with me.
I left her there, in line.
I let her in.
I thought I was being nice.
Listen, I-if Kate... is
really who you say she is,
then-then... this shot
wasn't meant for her.
It was an accident.
It wasn't your fault.
- Yes, it was.
- Right?
You sound like my philosophy t.A.Always
trying to make sense of everything
by saying,"nothing makes sense."
It doesn't change the fact that she
got shot and she's almost dead or...
All right, what about
him looked suspicious?
I didn't say he looked suspicious.
I said he was acting suspicious.
A person isn't
suspicious. Their behavior is.
I'm doing my master's in criminology.
Well, good for you.
So what about his behavior
made him suspicious?
He was sober.
She was standing right in front of
me, and I saw the gun in her hand.
Or maybe it was a cell phone.
It was one of those
flip phones, you know,
so it kinda looked like
it could've been a gun.
Anyone cough up anything yet?
Uh, one guy threw up a corn dog.
We got the day to solve this.
- Okay.
- So let's solve it.
Okay.
If any of you tweeted, texted, blogged,
or uploaded any cell phone photos from
outside supernova, step forward now.
Larry, you're up.
Give me your phone.
It's a total violation
of the privacy act.
Listen, you grad school poser.
A 22-year-old girl was murdered today, so
if you have any photos of the crime scene,
you better show us, or I'll arrest
your ass for obstruction of justice.
That was so hot.
Let's see what you got.
You're still thinking gang, huh?
I guess you're not.
A gun like that is too valuable.
Gangbanger's not gonna get rid
of it just 'cause it jammed.
Well, it's not revenge.It's not
like the girl had any enemies.
Well, if it ain't revenge
and it ain't money...
It's love.
I don't know where it is.
I mean, I've seen her writing in a
journal, but I don't know where she keeps it.
Okay.
Is this her computer?
Yeah.
You know her password?
No, I would never
I wouldn't ask.
She was wearing that coat today.
It's mine. I gave it to her
when I left. She was freezing.
You wear that a lot? Every day.I mean...
Not now, I guess.
- We haven't talked about you.
- What about me?
Well, we talked about Kate.
We know that she doesn't have
any ex-boyfriends, enemies.
Well... unlike my perfect
roommate, there are probably
about a million people who hate my
guts- a few ex-boyfriends, a couple t.A.S,
but it's not them that I care about.
It's my friend.
Who was wearing your coat.
Are they printing?
Yeah, they're printing.
They're printing it right now.
Did you send me that one from
that, uh, the one kid's camera?
- You got it?
- I'm sending things over right now.
We worked from tweets, tweet pics, tweetdeck
hootsuite, Facebook, and cell phone photos.
Not a clue what you're talking about.
All these pictures were taken
moments before the shots were fired.
Now it's possible someone accidentally
took a picture of the shooter.
All right, bring 'em in.
All right, everybody, I want you to grab a
marker and take a look at these photographs.
If you've seen any of
these people with this girl...
The girl who got shot today
I want you to circle their face.
Now be sure. If you're
not sure, take a pass.
You got something, poindexter?
I know this guy from the student union.
So?
So I saw him today and I tried to
say hi, but he just kept walking.
You ever seen him with this girl?
No, I don't think so.
But I've seen him with-with her.
That's Kate's roommate.
- We should call Andy.
- I'm gonna grab detective rosati.
And the student becomes the master.
I wouldn't go that far.
Guy's name is Adrian sparks, 27,a
grad student philosophy t.A.,
lives at 1493 spadina, apartment 12.
Just hold on. It's
Andy. She's on the line.
McNally, can you ask Miranda
about a guy named Adrian sparks?
I'm not with Miranda right now.
Where are you?
I came to the student affairs office.
Miranda mentioned
filing some grievances.
I thought I'd check it out.
Hey,"Adrian sparks" ring a bell?
Yeah.
Miranda made a complaint against him..
Two complaints, actually.
It's not unusual.
Favoritism, harassment, stalking, ignoring, "he
loves me, he hates me."
Thank you.
Okay, Adrian sparks
was her philosophy t.A.
They had a relationship.
And she was the one to break it off.
Harassment, a couple of threats, and
she even had to get her locks changed.
We're working on that.
Adrian was up for assistant Professor.
We passed him over, pending
the investigation.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.Good luck.
Thanks.
Okay, Kate was wearing Miranda's coat.
It's bright red, very distinctive.
Miranda says she wears it every day.
From a distance, the two
of them look very similar.
Okay, McNally, go and get Miranda.
We're gonna head over there, all right?
Sounds good.
All right, let's go.
Miranda?
Miranda, please open the door.
I just need to talk to you for a minute.
Miranda?
Hey!
Hey, get off of her!
You're Adrian.
It's okay. It's all right.
I'm a friend of Miranda's.
This is your ex-boyfriend, the
one you were telling me about.
- You told her about me?!
- I didn't say anything!
What did you tell her?!
Miranda, shut up!
Were you at the show today?
No.
No, you know what?
I don't have to do this.
Yes, you do.
So put your hands up and turn around.
Please help me!
He wants to kill me!
He's gonna kill me!
Please help me!
Stay here!
Adrian, stop!
Stop!
Don't move!
I said...Don't move.
Look around
you, Adrian, 'cause this is it.
Turn around.
Why?
I wanna talk.
What, you gonna talk
me down off the ledge?
I love it.
No.
I thought that was your job.
Not really, so if you
wanna jump, then do it.
So then why are you
pointing a gun at me?
I don't know.
Doesn't really make much sense, does it?
So now we can talk...Really talk.
Okay, fine. You go first.
Why are you doing this?
Why not?
It's what I wanted in the first place.
She'd be over.
I'd be over.
The whole thing would be over.
That didn't work out so well.
Miranda's still here.
So are you.
It's pathetic!
And now Kate novatski is...
Is dead because she was cold.
Yeah.
You're so naive.
You're just like... aah!
Uhh!
Aah!
Let go!
No! Don't!
I just wanted it to be done!
I just wanted to jump!
Yeah, I don't care.
Let go of me!
I just wanted it to be over!
He's up there.
Andy?
Suspect's secure on the
roof of the student dorm.
Pretty sure it's empty.
Uh, we got the guy...
Kate novatski's killer.
Luke's in with him right now,
so we probably have a
confession any minute.
I was in charge today.
I was in charge, and she got shot.
A girl got... shot.
So did you.
I thought if we caught the
guy, and maybe I could understand
why this happened, that
I would feel better.
I don't.
Well, that's 'cause there's
nothing left for you to do.
Everybody else
they're gonna live their lives,
eventually forget about
this, but... you can't.
Dov, that's the most
depressing pep talk ever.
Sorry.
Epstein.
Frank's waiting for you in his office.
I'm okay, really.
You will be.
I'm dealing with it now.
Nothing is the same now?
Thank you.
Peter mckee, 42 years old, 3 kids.
He's been waiting for a heart
transplant almost two years.
Ambulance needs police
escorts at St. pat's.
Epstein, don't, um...
Don't have an accident.
I didn't even know Dov had a brother.
Yeah. Adam.
He was a few years older.
Was he sick?
Uh...
Dov doesn't like to talk about it, so...
He killed himself.
You know, he... he hung himself.
After that, Dov's parents split for good.
Wow.
I... um...
Well, Chris, you
know, you're, um... you know,
you're back at work now,
and-and you don't need me
to take care of you anymore,
so I should probably
just move out, right?
No.
I like having you around.
Luke?
Hey, I think we did good.
From nothing to a signed
confession in six hours?
We've never done that before.
We did it on that
cardello chain saw thing.
I don't think that counts.
The chain saw was practically smoking.
Remember the, uh, Ivan Wallace fiasco?
Rebuilt the entire crime
scene in our apartment...
Felt like we'd shacked up
with two chalk outlines.
Well, we got the guy in the end.
No, I got the guy in the end.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
Wait, do you remember it differently?
Yeah.
Is there something gross in there?
Oh. No.
I was just thinking about Andy.
You know, like, what if the
bullet hadn't hit her vest?
I mean, if it had
hit, like, 6 inches higher
but it didn't.
We can't think like that.
Anybody want a drink?
Apparently, I'm buying, so...
You were amazing today.
Thanks.
Doesn't mean I want you as a roommate.
Doesn't mean I care.
I'm not taking time off.
Come on. It's all signed,
sealed confession. That never happens.
Uh-huh. What about the cardello case?
I heard you guys talking.
That was a long time ago.
I know.
Jo and I were partners for three years.
How long did you live together?
Two and a half.
Any regrets?
Not one.
Good.
That's really funny.
- Hey.
How's the...
- Ooh!
- Nice.
- Wow.
Anything broken?
That looks worse than...
You had us worried, McNally.
Nice working with you, detective.
Oh, thanks, you, too.
Looks like, uh, we might get
a chance to do it again.
Oh, yeah?
Always tricky switching teams
midseason, but, uh, duty calls.
You're gonna stay at 15,huh?
Well, you guys had an opening.I
put in for a transfer.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
What about you?
I heard you were headed
over to guns and gangs.
Uh, yeah.
I haven't decided yet.
Cheers.