LOLA: So I'm embarrassed about this,
but I have this giant astrology book.
And it says that today,
that my 29th birthday...
...Saturn returns to the place of my birth
and it turns my life upside-down.
It says that Saturn is going to bring
all of my shit to the surface...
...and then I'm going to evolve.
I'm paraphrasing, of course.
I know that change is inevitable.
But what if I don't want things to change?
What if I like my life exactly how it is?
[NOISEMAKER BLOWING]
Happy birthday.
I feel old.
You're so old.
[GROANS]
Do I Iook 29?
Yeah, you kind of do.
No, I'm only kidding.
You Iook Iike the white J.Lo.
Baby, J.Lo is in her 40s.
-No, she's not.
-Yes, she is.
-J.Lo's in her 40s?
-Mm-hm.
What?
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
I got a surprise.
BIow.
-Now you're gonna get it.
-I can't get it. Heh-heh.
Now you're gonna get it.
[BOTH MOAN]
You're gonna get it.
Why aren't you ticklish? It's so weird.
-AII right, if--
-Okay, okay, I got it. I Iove you.
-I Iove you too, Lola. Happy birthday.
-Thank you.
You Iook very handsome today!
Don't anybody touch him!
He's mine!
Yes, you can die from
drinking too much water.
Yes.
I'II e-mail you the article.
I know, you just have to find a balance. It's--
-Oh, my--!
-Bike Iane!
No, Luke's great.
Yeah, he's just been working Iike crazy
on his solo show.
It's paintings of celebrity sex tapes.
No, Anderson Cooper's not in there.
Should he be?
[MOANING]
What--? Are you trying to masturbate?
We just had sex.
-Lola.
-Yes?
Will you marry me?
Do you think there's a magazine
for pregnant brides?
Have you died?!
LOLA:
No, I'm ready.
HENRY:
Dude, you Iook incredible.
-Don't tell Luke you were here.
-Let me video-chat with him.
What? You've had Iiterally
the same phone since 1 1th grade.
Whatever. Chicks Iove old phones.
They think I Iisten more.
You trying to take maid of honor from me?
I ordered strippers who get naked
to the soundtrack of Glee.
-I'm not Iistening.
-Can your band play Cee Lo?
-I'm a rock star.
-Ta-ta.
It's a wedding dress! It's a wedding dress!
LUKE:
No, no. GIuten-free chocolate.
Ask about the icing.
What--? Yeah, oh, Raimundo,
is the icing rice-milk based?
-Non-GMO.
-No rice milk.
Non-- Non-GMO.
No, wait-- Hold on.
Hold on, Raimundo, yeah.
I got someone on the other Iine. Hello?
Oh, hi, hi.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
Yeah, it's your mom. Again.
Could you please tell her that
we've been planning this for nine months?
-We got it under control.
-Relax, honey.
-I'm fine, I'm fine.
-Hi, Mom.
I know, but it's too expensive
if the resort caters it.
Okay, I have to go.
-I Iove you too. Bye.
-Hey, AIice. Nice dress.
-It's expensive.
-I'm gonna step outside for a minute.
LOLA:
Okay. What's up?
Well, I'm the Iast single woman
in New York City.
I went to volunteer at
a women's homeless shelter.
They all had boyfriends.
The homeless.
Why don't you date Henry? He's single.
I don't know, Henry is sort of hot,
but he's your best friend.
It would be Iike fucking you.
I'm gonna find you a guy if it kills me.
What's your Match.com Iog-in?
Is it still "Let-me-be-your-hole"?
"Let-me-be-your-hole-1."
It was taken. The first one was taken.
AII right, I'm following the dot,
and the dot--
It's moving all over the place.
-Where is it, Len?
-This way.
Dad, it's on the corner, so you don't need
to use your iPhone to get there.
Okay. Because the iPad,
wouldn't that get us there faster?
-Yeah.
-You are obsessed with this thing.
It's a sickness. Now he plays Scrabble
with strangers online in Milwaukee.
I am retired. Let me soar.
I know this building. Do you remember?
It was a sex dungeon.
Right. Let me search that.
Honey, you're gonna die
when you see these flowers.
I feel Iike I should just quit school
and start planning weddings.
Honey, what's up? Did you have a stroke?
[SOBBING]
Oh, no.
What's happened here?
It's comfier on the ground?
You want me to get you something, honey?
Chips.
The issue is that 40 guests
have already bought their tickets...
...for a destination wedding in Chiapas.
Who's going to pay those people back?
Because it's not going to be Lola.
Not when your heartless, shit-eating son decided
to pull the plug and ruin my daughter's Iife.
Honey, drink the kombucha tea,
it settles the soul.
LENNY:
Screw the kombucha.
Let me buy you something
with high-fructose corn syrup.
You want some nasty cinnamon buns?
I could melt cinnamon buns
and feed them to you intravenously.
ROBIN: No, no, I wonder, you know,
when you started to believe...
...that the mother of the groom
should be involved...
...because it certainly wasn't early on,
when we were making all the plans.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
You added a polar bear Iamp.
Yeah, I thrifted it.
Okay, so, um, I--
I know I said I kind of subletted
this apartment to you indefinitely...
...but I'm gonna have
to move back because--
It's okay. I know exactly where this is going
and it's actually perfect.
Because my boyfriend just proposed!
We're gonna move in together.
Oh, my God.
[SOBS]
-He had such a beautiful Ioft.
-Yeah.
-And it's rent-stabilized.
-I know.
My world is shattered, and I'm eating.
I'm power-eating.
-You're eating rice chips.
-That have so much sodium.
Hey, if anything,
you need to be freed, you know?
From the shackles of a steady relationship...
...with an attractive, successful man
who actually enjoys cooking.
Fuck, this is really depressing.
It's just, Luke is my partner in crime.
He's the person I want to wake up with
and I want to go to bed with.
He's the whole reason I went back to school
to get my PhD.
Now I can't even afford to do that
without splitting the bills.
That is not true. You can still go to school.
Work at your mom's restaurant part-time
Iike after we graduated.
What are we gonna do about our friends?
How do we split them up?
-I mean, you don't really have that many friends.
-That's true.
Except for Henry.
Henry is a mutual friend.
Honestly, Lo, this is good. You know?
You met Luke your junior year abroad.
I mean, you were a baby.
You need to be on your own again...
...dating other people, Ietting them stick it in,
knowing what that feels Iike.
You've never been with anyone else.
That's not good for character.
You know? Look at me.
Being single builds character.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Ugh. Oh, I'm sore.
-Who is it?
HENRY: Hey, it's Henry.
[DOOR BUZZES]
Okay, come in.
-I gotta go wash my vagina.
-Why?
What, you never just washed your vagina?
[LOLA MEWLS]
-Hi.
This is a consolation Iasagna.
Just put it there.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know if you
want to see me right now or....
I don't know if
I want to see you right now.
You Iook terrible.
I know it's weird.
You don't have to pick a side.
No, I know I don't have to.
Are you serious? You have to pick a side.
You are prettier than him.
And I'm a better person.
So you say.
ALICE:
She's Iike Mother Teresa!
Only younger.
But not that much younger.
This is number one on Yelp
for best bar in a scary neighborhood.
[LOLA CHUCKLES]
You're gonna Iove it.
-It's crowded.
-I'm dressed for a barbecue.
-Okay, Iet's get a drink.
-Okay.
[VEX RUFFIN'S "WOULD YOU TAKE IT"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
If I gave you all my heart
Would you take it?
Would you break it?
Don't matter to me
Hello.
Would you tell me that we're through?
Can't tell me it wasn't true
Excuse me? Bartendress?
Or would you lie to me?
Oh, here she is.
[MOANING]
-Good? Good?
-Oh, yeah.
-Good?
-Yeah.
ALICE: What's happening?
-I'm--
-Let it out.
-I'm having a panic attack.
-Okay, okay. Let's go.
LOLA: Okay, okay.
ALICE:
Keep going. Excuse us.
LOLA: It's okay.
ALICE: Sorry.
LOLA:
Bye!
[HYPERVENTILATING]
Sorry. Excuse us.
-You okay? Do I need to call 91 1?
-No. No.
Okay, Iook, breathe, breathe.
It's okay. Everything's okay. Look at me.
SIow, slow it down.
Good. It's just a bar, okay?
It's just a bar.
Everything's fine. I'm right here.
Okay?
Can you get me a cab?
Yeah, yeah. Just wait right here.
Hold on, I see one.
Oh, taxi?
Hi. Sorry, can you just wait one second?
Hi. Are you at home?
[ROMANTIC POP MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
LOLA: Do you have any of that tea
that makes you skinny?
No, but I crushed as many amphetamines
as I could in here, so that should do the trick.
I feel Iike an idiot.
I feel Iike everyone saw it coming but me.
Nobody saw it. It was Iike fucking Iightning.
-He didn't say anything to you?
-Never.
I mean, all he wanted to do
was have fun when we were out.
I mean, sometimes he'd pretend Iike he wasn't
in a relationship, but that's what guys do.
It doesn't necessarily mean anything.
Did he cheat on me or...?
No.
Hey, he would never.
I feel Iike men are always Iooking
for someone better...
...and women are just Iooking
for whatever works.
Well, I don't feel Iike that.
I just want to meet someone
I can hang out with all the time...
...eat bologna with, read shit to me.
-I had that person.
-Hey.
Do you remember that time when we did
mushrooms at your parents' country house?
Yeah.
And you made us go into
that swamp full of nasty shit...
...because you thought
we owed it to the plant Iife?
-The plants needed us.
-Right. And then you were convinced...
...that we wouldn't get out of there,
and I calmed you down...
...by singing that slow version
of "Girls Just Want to Have Fun."
We went back in the house and--
Do you remember this story that
I'm telling you again in great detail?
Yeah, it's the best worst night ever.
-What's your point?
-I get you out of swamps.
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
LUKE [OVER PHONE]:
Hey, it's me again.
It doesn't have to be like this, Lo.
We could still talk
and be in each other's lives, you know?
LUKE:
Hey, it's me again.
You're killing me here.
At least let me know you're okay.
All your stuff is here.
Call me, please.
LOLA: I haven't changed my underwear
in three days.
Listen, Mom, do you think you could go over
to his place and just pick up my stuff?
I can't do it. I just....
Yeah, just bring it back to my old apartment.
Yeah, use the key that I gave you.
Oh, thank you, Mom.
I Iove you too.
Okay, I'm gonna go elliptical. Bye.
WOMAN:
Yeah, I'II be right there.
You go wild?
What?
-The salmon, did you buy wild?
-Oh.
No, it seems pretty tame to me.
I know there are more important things
to worry about...
...but when you buy fish,
you should try to pay attention to that.
Gotta honor your body, you know?
I'm Nick.
-Hi. Lola.
-Hi.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Bye.
Anything from Nova Scotia?
NICK:
Do you shop here a Iot?
I can't be picked up right now.
I appreciate the interest,
but I'm in a really bad place.
Gotcha.
I would Iove to cook you dinner sometime.
Something fresh-caught.
Well, not-- Not by me.
Fresh-bought.
Oh, I don't really Iike fish.
I'm just eating this because it's salty.
You know, I'm gonna--
I'm gonna give you my number.
You may use it, you may not.
If you do...
... I'm free...
...a week from Friday.
After 7.
But I could do 6:30.
LENNY: Okay, Leo. "It's time to fasten
your seat belt, kitty cat. Don't hiss at me.
With Uranus, the planet of
Iightning-bolt surprises...
...you really never know which way is up.
This is going to be a shitty month."
He said,
"This is going to be a shitty month"?
It's the Voice. They write what they know.
-You know, your mom and I broke up once.
-You did?
Yeah, we decided to date other people.
Seemed Iike a fun idea, but then we realized
that nobody else really compared.
Heh. Uh....
-Do you think that'II happen to me and Luke?
-No. No, I don't. I hate Luke.
I de-friended him on Facebook already.
He's out.
Thanks.
[GROANS]
Okay, Iove, fuck or kill?
Heh, heh. Hilary Duff, Haylie Duff...
...or any of the Fannings.
You realize they're not related, right?
I'm pretty sure they are.
Wait, I think it's "marry, fuck, kill."
What's--? How--? How is it different?
Because I think the assumption is if you--
After you're married, that you don't fuck.
-Right.
-Yeah.
-I guess I dodged a bullet, then.
-Pfft.
That was--
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Ooh.
Wake up.
Oh, shit.
You want breakfast?
No. I have to go.
Here, help me. I have no core.
[HENRY GRUNTS]
-Hey.
I'm sorry to surprise you Iike this,
but you didn't call me back.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
I'm really Iate for this meeting.
I don't think I can right now.
Yeah, but, Iook, wait, wait--
PIease, just wait a second?
What's that green thing?
Oh. I'm cleansing.
I drink it out of this thing.
The potion.
-Does it work?
-Yeah, it does.
That's good.
So I'm-- I've been...
...you know, thinking about things and--
I don't know,
I might have acted irrationally.
-I don't know.
-You don't know?
I'm-- I'm confused.
Are you seriously doing this right now...
...right before I have to go in
and argue about my dissertation?
Shit. I'm sorry. I didn't know.
You didn't return my calls.
I've been really busy.
Look, I....
I know this came out of nowhere...
...and I think I was just overwhelmed
by everything that was happening and....
And now I just--
Are you just doing this
because you're Ionely?
No.
I just really wanted to see you.
I really...
...have to go.
Wait.
[SIGHS]
Essentially, I'II be investigating the use
of silence in 19th-century French Iiterature.
-Are you still using the poetry of Mallarmé?
LOLA: Yes.
I want to really Iook at his obsession
with the blank page...
...really exploring the ways in which
his verses engender silence.
I would also Iike to Iook at silence
in the media and popular culture.
Well, more of the Iack thereof.
Just our communal...
...almost deathly fear of silence.
I don't know what I want.
-Should I give you guys some more time?
-We'II be ready in a minute.
Just stand there.
WOMAN:
Um....
I'II have the...
...gnocchi and a glass of the "sangreesha."
Do you mean sangria?
I'm-- We don't have that.
-Do you have wine?
-Yes.
Put fruit cocktail in it.
-Go.
-I'II get that for you.
Can you put fruit cocktail
in a glass of wine for me?
-Hey, Randy. How's the bar stock?
-Pretty empty, Iike my bank account.
-Hey.
-Hi, Mom.
How are you doing, sweetie? You okay?
-I'm choosing to be alive.
-Well, good.
Listen, I have something really important
to talk to you about, all right?
-Okay.
-Okay, not here. Let's--
I was thinking about this in the taxi yesterday
when I was watching that Iittle TV set.
Right.
-It's about freezing.
-Freezing?
Think you might want to think about
freezing the eggs.
The eggs?
-My eggs?
-Yes, those eggs.
Oh, come on, Mom.
I am not gonna have children anytime soon.
Well, exactly my point. You will.
They do it in a great facility. Trust me.
My friend Debbie did it.
She has eggs all over the city.
Six happy children.
Well, one of them's a giant, but very nice.
That's so depressing.
I am already depressed.
-Could you Iet me grieve, please?
-Grieve, grieve. We're all grieving.
But I'm just trying to think practically
on your behalf.
You're not getting any younger.
They shrivel.
Could we just talk about something else?
RANDY:
I don't fucking know.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Sangreesha, house specialty.
[THE ETTES' "ALLEY CAT" PLAYING]
You wanna hear
You broke my heart
I wanna hear
You're gonna finish what you start
You wanna put
Hell really is bright.
I always forget that Times Square exists.
HENRY:
Yeah, it does.
For all time, it's been here.
AII these Iights make me nauseous.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[GRUNTING]
[ROGER MOANING]
[MOANING CONTINUES]
[IN SINGSONG VOICE]
I....
-Hi.
-Hi!
[BOTH SPEAKING GIBBERISH]
[ROGER GROANS]
HENRY: Remember when I had a beard
Iike that in college?
LOLA:
It was awful.
HENRY:
I Iooked hot.
Poor AIice, she just keeps getting cast
as these peasants.
Was that sign Ianguage
she was doing part of the play?
-Or was she translating for someone?
-I don't know.
No, she did this dream therapy workshop...
...where she said her and her character melded
in a past Iife as a deaf-mute.
Ah. She Iooked great.
And what was up with the Iead guy, Roger?
-It was Iike he was half asleep.
-I don't know.
He was terrible.
I don't know why she's obsessed with him.
-She's obsessed?
-Yeah.
Why? She could do way better.
HENRY: Congratulations.
LOLA: Yay! I Ioved it.
-Thank you.
-Oh, I had an off night.
You were great too.
I accidentally took a Xanax before this show.
I thought it was an Advil.
That's insane. You're insane.
You're so talented.
LOLA: I couldn't tell at all.
-I basically directed myself.
-Yeah.
-Director's a hack.
Some Yale grad, whatever.
I'm actually adapting this for the screen.
I got so much inside and it just--
You know, I'm so--
I'm fucking talented, you know?
I know it inside.
So okay, tell me, was I okay?
Did you see me? Did I find my Iight?
You were so believable. Heh.
Why are you Iaughing?
Was I too much? Was it over the top?
Because I can bring it down.
I can make it, you know,
Iess viewpointy, more Congo.
What does that even mean?
The whole thing is a metaphor
for genital mutilation.
-Did you not get that?
-Oh....
-Do you want me to carry your thermos?
-Oh, yeah. That would be awesome.
So this is weird, I'm sorry...
...but do you think that you could
stay over with me tonight?
Nights are really hard.
Uh....
Sure.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Thanks. I know it's weird. I just--
-No, no, no. Totally, totally, totally.
-I appreciate it. Okay.
[LOWER DENS' "I GET NERVOUS" PLAYING]
Why are you waving at me?
Waving good night.
Don't sleep on the couch.
What's your thread count?
Like...two.
Cool.
Just a-being in your service
-Ha-ha-ha.
-It's the tapered Ieg on the.... Ahem.
They evince the troubled, nimble wit
Oh, nothing in return
But storm and pessimism
Oh.
Being good for me
And just a-standing in your pretty prison
-Thanks for staying over.
-Yeah, of course.
Oh, God, Luke would kill me
if he knew I was in your bed.
I'm pretty sure that Luke
no Ionger has jurisdiction over these parts.
Yeah, that's true.
[SIGHS]
Being good for me
And just a-standing in your pretty prison
You're standing here
You think you love me
Don't you?
Maybe you're the presence
That begs needing other reasons
I got "Summer still looks pretty"
I got hungry for the hungry seas
Stop. We can't do this.
Yes, we can. It's fine.
No, Luke's a good friend.
Yeah, but you're my best friend.
I'm a rebound.
No, you're more of a Iayup.
Oh, I feel Iike I'm breaking code.
I don't know what the rules are
in this situation.
We can make up the rules.
We don't have to have sex.
I don't....
Well, you know I've always
had feelings for you.
No, I didn't know that.
Yeah, so I think we should--
We should just be careful, you know,
and take it slow.
-Okay.
-Good night.
[RAIN POURING]
[HENRY SNORING]
Luke.
Yeah, it's me.
I really miss you.
Can I see you?
LOLA:
I feel Iike I'm gonna puke.
-What am I doing? I don't know what I'm doing.
-Okay, Iook.
Here, open your mouth.
Ugh! What? What's that?
-Weed in a bottle.
-What?
Freshens the breath
and gets you fucked up, dude.
I got it in Koreatown Iast time I was in L.A.
Smuggled it in my cooch pouch on the plane.
-I am going to kill you!
-Here. Relax!
God! Put this weed candy
under your tongue.
-Stop it! You need help.
-You don't want this?
-No.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
-Okay.
-What exactly is the point of this meeting?
-I need closure.
I don't know. I don't know what I need.
I'm hot. Is it hot out?
-Feel Iike I'm gonna be sick. It smells Iike sulfur.
-Lola:
[SPEAKS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
What does that Iast part mean?
"You don't have a wife yet,
but you named your son Somalingam."
-Ancient Indian proverb.
-What?
Find your spirit animal
and ride it till its dick falls off.
-AII right?
-Right.
-AII right.
-Okay.
-Go get him.
-I'm going.
-I got your back.
-I Iove it.
I Iove you.
AII right.
How's the dissertation coming?
SIowly. The silence is killing me.
How's the painting?
It's really good.
I've been getting a Iot of work done and....
Wow.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[MOUTHS]
What?
Think I'm gonna....
[CHUCKLES]
[MOUTHS INDISTINCTLY]
I'm just trying to figure out
what I'm eating or....
How Iong did you know?
Know what?
That you were gonna Ieave me.
I mean, honestly?
Not Iong.
I mean, I think it was when
the whole wedding started to feel real.
You know, with your family
and the flowers and the plane tickets.
And suddenly I was just--
-Dude, were you just pretending to Iove me?
-No.
Of course not.
So, what are we doing?
I don't know.
[MOANING]
[LOLA SOBS]
Hey.
PIease, don't cry.
I don't think I can see you anymore.
Why?
It's too painful.
But if we're both missing each other,
I don't see why--
I just can't.
[SHOWER RUNNING]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
-Hey.
-What the heck happened to you?
You went AWOL for three hours.
I thought he killed you...
-...and disappeared to the Catskills.
-We had sex.
Yeah, I saw a 20/20 Iike that.
In fact, girl who's supposed to be married...
...head found severed near
a Jewish community center.
Are you Iistening to me?
I said we had sex.
Yes, I'm listening.
Wait, what did you say?
It's Iike he's good for me,
but he's bad for me.
-Yeah.
-You know?
The guy who's supposed to make me
feel safe is actually dangerous...
...which just makes me
want to have sex with him.
I'm drunk. I Iove macrobiotic food.
Who puts your sentences together?
Honestly, your brain is Iike a bad DJ.
-It was terrible. I had to see him.
-Yeah. Well, hey, at Ieast you got options.
Me, I can't find someone to Iove me
momentarily during orgasm...
...which is really an easy moment
to Iove someone fleetingly, no?
-What happened?
-Roger wouldn't have sex with me.
-Oh, boy.
-Like I was some refugee.
Then I went and got drunk by myself,
unless a bottle of Kahlùa counts as a partner...
...then went back
and hate-fucked him two times.
Yeah. I don't know, I don't know.
Maybe you're right,
maybe I should just date Henry.
Oh, God. Um....
-We made out.
-What?
Ba-ba-ba. Back up the train.
Why didn't you tell me?
-Because I didn't want you to judge me.
-Judge you?
I don't know, I think I Iike him?
Okay. Wow, okay.
Should I slit my wrists now
or just wait till after the meal?
Oh, stop it. You are going to find someone
just the second you stop Iooking.
-Have you been on Match.com Iately?
-Seriously, now.
What am I eating? This is just gas in a box.
HENRY:
Come on. What are you, old?
I'm sorry, I didn't realize that we would be
tracing the New York City Marathon route.
-We're here.
-Where?
Neil Sedaka's house.
Never wondered where Neil Sedaka Iives?
No. Should I be expecting a Iot
of Neil Sedaka covers at your show?
How weird does it sound...
-...to say "Neil Sedaka" this many times?
-Neil Sedaka, Neil Sedaka, Neil Sedaka.
[MINOR KEYS'
"THE BIG TROUBLES" PLAYING]
And we'll watch
The world burn
It's the one that got away
It's the one that never came
It's the chances that you missed
It's the girl you never kissed
It's the one you never had
It's the one that left you sad
It's the one that got away
It's the one that never came
It's the chances that you missed
It's the girl you never kissed
It's the one you never had
It's the one that left you sad
[BAND PLAYING "SATURN RETURNS"]
ALICE:
Hey.
-What happened to you?
-I spray-tanned. What happened to you?
I don't see you for two weeks,
and now you're ethnically ambiguous.
It's a conversation starter.
-I wanna get closer.
-Yeah, good.
I want to start telling people
I was on vacation.
Hi, I'm 30, I'm Iooking to have children.
How are you?
You're 29.
Oh, I round up,
then I get the cougar advantage.
[SINGING]
Like the father time
Like we hit the end just as we hit rewind
-I Iike what you're doing!
-Yeah!
Saturn returns
LOLA:
You're so hot!
Saturn returns
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
What?
ALICE:
I don't know.
HENRY:
I'm the one, I'm the one
Hi.
Hey, AIice. How you doing?
Great. I just got back from vacation.
-It's a good Iook.
-Thank you.
-Great Iook.
ALICE: Thanks.
-Hey.
-Luke. Hi.
LUKE: Hi.
What are you doing here?
LUKE:
Well, I'm just watching my friend.
He's a singer.
So funny. My friend just dragged me along.
She knows someone in the band too.
So, Peggy, this is Lola.
-Lola, this is Peggy.
-Nice to meet you.
HENRY: Saturn returns
Saturn returns
Yes. No, could you excuse us?
-Fun club.
-Yeah.
-Who's Peggy?
-She's just this girl.
-She's just a girl.
-Yeah.
We hung out a few times.
I mean, it's nothing.
-Are you dating her?
-No. No, I'm not.
I mean, it depends on
how you define "dating" here.
You're unbelievable!
I thought that you said
that you wanted time alone.
I did. I do.
This is what we should be doing.
You should be doing it too.
Did you know her while we were together?
Just socially. I wasn't cheating on you,
if that's what you're getting at.
I mean, we just recently started hanging out.
Yes, I know that you started hanging out,
because I read your text messages!
What? Why would you do that?
Why would I trust you?
You're so selfish and good-Iooking!
Stop being a martyr, all right?
Sometimes you have to be selfish.
I was never selfish.
I always put you before me.
Yeah, maybe that was the problem.
Well, I'm dating Henry! That's what I'm doing!
That is why I am here!
What? What?
What?
Really?
Yep! Must make you feel weird that
I'm dating your best friend.
But I'm doing it because
I guess that's what I should be doing.
LUKE:
No, no, I'm glad it's him.
ALICE:
Yeah, she's not even into him.
Look how hot he is.
But whatevs, it's super "cazh."
-I'm gonna go throw up.
-Me too. I'm gonna throw up too.
I can't believe he's dating somebody else.
This is very, very dirty.
But you know what, honey?
You are dating someone else too.
Do you want to dance?
Now? A site-specific bathroom dance party?
-No, Iike I gotta get out of here.
-Oh, yeah.
-Okay?
-Yeah, Iet's go.
[EXHALES]
Listen, I'm sorry, I know it's shitty--
Did you fuck her?
No, I swear.
LOLA: Hey. That was so great.
-Hey.
Your new boyfriend and me
had a Iittle chitchat.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
-Was it fun?
-Great.
I mean, out of all people.
I mean, really.
Dude, it's not Iike it was planned.
You sure about that?
-Well, it's not as planned as your wedding.
-Hey, fuck you!
I have food poisoning.
I gotta Ioad out, so....
-I'II call you tomorrow.
-I won't.
Touché. We're going.
[DAN DEACON'S
"THE CRYSTAL CAT" PLAYING]
I'm gonna get my bathing suit on
Gonna get my base face on
Gonna get my hat out of loan
Gonna get my space face on
I'm gonna turn all snakes into bone
Go wishing the stone
Keep the crystal cat cold
Gotta get to the throne
Hope my baby
May we meet a beastman
Hold us there
Happy but by one hand
Gonna get my pile of stone
[DOORBELL BUZZING]
HENRY:
Hello?
It's Lola! It's me! Let me in, please!
It's 4 in the morning.
[MOANING]
Dude, stop. You're really drunk.
-Oh, are you close?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
-Yeah, yeah.
[MOANING LOUDER]
-Yeah? Oh. Mm.
-Yeah. Yeah.
[SIGHS]
So, what do you sound Iike
when you really come?
I don't know.
I guess I'm...quieter.
When you told Luke
that I was your boyfriend...
...did you say that
just to make him mad or...?
I don't know. I'm so messed up right now.
Hey.
You're not messing anything up.
You know, we don't have to Iabel anything.
We can just be.
You know, in the '70s,
folks Iike you were with a Iot of people.
Made sense.
Yeah, they had a Iot of STDs.
Well, hey, remember, it's not perfect fidelity,
it's high fidelity.
Dad, what kind of
bumper-sticker crap is that?
That's not crap, that's wisdom.
There is a fine Iine.
Thank you, sage father.
Look, you know, I know that having
your mom and I as parents...
...has kind of made you into
a stressed-out kid...
... but you put a Iot of pressure on yourself
to Iive out a Iife...
...that maybe is a Iittle more conventional
than what you were raised in.
Sometimes it's good, you know,
to just shake Iife up a Iittle bit.
Let it fall out of your hands.
You'II catch it.
Mm-hm.
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
You have such a musical voice.
Do you play any instruments or...?
No, actually. I, um--
Do you play any instruments?
No. I'm much more visual.
Yeah. Anyway, you asked me a question.
No, I didn't want to be a prison architect.
That just kind of happened.
Mm. That's awesome.
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
Lola.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
You're a writer. What do you...
...want to write about?
Cats.
-Cats.
-Like, the history of cats.
There's something...
...wonderfully feline about you.
Meow. Ha-ha-ha.
[BOTH LAUGH]
No, I was kidding.
I thought, because
I Ioved Iiterature so much...
...that I'd want to write novels,
but I realized I didn't.
I just want to write about them.
So....
It's very, very sexy.
[LAUGHS]
Can I pour you another glass of wine?
-Okay.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-Great.
Do you want to stick with the red?
We could do some sake.
[MOANING]
Oh, I really Iike your knees.
No, wait.
Yeah, I really Iike your knees.
Thanks.
-You want me to put on some music?
-Okay.
[ANI DIFRANCO'S "BOTH HANDS"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry. It just came out.
That's okay. I know.
It's freakishly big.
-I can't stop Iooking.
-I was an incubator baby.
-What?
Oh....
What is that?
The incubator, it made my penis bigger
than the other kids'.
Oh, yeah.
To see how long our swan song can last
Oh, okay.
Ooh. Whoa.
That just slipped in there, huh?
[MOANS]
You feel so good.
Just a minute. Shh. Be perfectly still.
Is this--? Is this Ani DiFranco?
Yeah. She's my favorite Iyricist.
Oh.
[SINGING] And I am watching your chest
Rise and fall
Like the tides of my life
Could you--?
Your bones have been my bed frame
Your flesh has been my pillow
Do you think you could get a condom?
Aren't you on the pill?
It doesn't matter.
What are you worried about?
I don't know if you're clean.
I am.
I just got tested.
[MOANS]
Scout's honor.
Oh, okay, that's--
That makes me feel better. The Boy Scouts.
-Actually, I'm an Eagle.
-Oh.
[BRAYING AND LAUGHING]
And when we leave the landlord will come
And paint over it all
And I am walking
Out in the rain
Sure you don't want to get some breakfast?
Omelet?
I can be a few minutes Iate for class.
You know, that's okay. Thanks.
I had a really nice time Iast night.
Yeah. Yeah.
Let me roll you home.
-Come on.
-Okay.
Mm.
Sweet architecture.
It's really tight brickwork. Bravo.
Hey.
Henry.
Hi. I'm Nick.
AII right.
I better get to Pilates.
Oh, can you give me a hand,
help me with this?
Just really tight.
Yeah, just really--
Like, really, really tight. Yeah.
Yeah, okay. Great.
Thank you.
I'II call you Iater.
Have a blessed day.
What the fuck?
What are you doing here?
I came to surprise you with breakfast.
-These are really nice scones.
-Oh, shit.
Did you just have sex with that Rollerblader?
Um....
Oh, my God.
I cannot believe you.
I'm so sorry. It was terrible.
If it's any consolation,
his dick was so big it hurt my back.
Oh, he has a bigger dick than me too?
No, that is a consolation.
You should go into
the greeting card business.
"Sorry I cheated on you.
PS, your dick is smaller."
-No, no, that's not-- That's not what I meant.
-I just assumed that we were--
-Yes, yes, yes, we are.
-Yeah?
-I'm confused.
-Yeah, clearly.
I'm vulnerable. I'm not myself.
I'm easily persuaded.
What, so now you're saying
that I persuaded you to be with me?
No. If anything,
I persuaded you to be with me.
-Whatever.
-Wait. No, no. Henry, wait, wait, wait.
I didn't know that we were exclusive,
and I didn't know.
I didn't know if it was okay
if I slept with someone else.
Do you know what? It doesn't have
to be articulated. It's just common courtesy.
-Uh....
-Henry!
PIease, can we talk about this?
I'm slutty, but I am a good person.
Oh honey, I really miss you
Oh, honey
Though it was only yesterday you kissed me
And that kiss
That kiss was so, so true
I guess I should know better
-Hey.
-Hey, I was in the neighborhood.
Oh, that's cool.
Do you have any weed?
When it comes to falling
Oh, honey, I really miss you
BOTH:
One, two, three.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
If only you could hold me now
Because you hold
You hold me, oh, so well
I guess I should know better
When it comes to falling
Yes, I should know better
When it comes to falling in love again
ROBIN: I'm glad that you're staying here
when we're gone.
It's good for you to get away
from all the noise out there.
LENNY: Fuck that noise!
-We'II be back in two weeks.
Hey, why don't you throw a rave party?
Go wild.
I can't throw a party. I'II just be thinking about
whether or not to invite Luke or Henry.
Then if I don't invite them,
I'II just wish that I did.
Honey, I really think
you're overanalyzing this.
Then if I do invite them and they don't
show up, is it because they hate me?
I just keep having sex
with the wrong people at the wrong time...
...or the right people at the wrong time.
LENNY:
Right time, wrong people!
I should probably try
to be friends with them.
I don't know. I can't tell.
I've never had an ex.
Are you supposed to be friends
with your exes?
ROBIN:
Well, honey, sure.
I mean, you know,
show Luke that you've moved on.
Show Henry how you're sorry.
Be the bigger person.
Oh, honey, we Iove you.
A Iot of people do.
Unfortunately, you and Dad
do not count as a Iot of people.
Randy, I need you to help me with this.
Are you kidding me?
That thing is Iike a walking toilet.
-PIease?
-CIearblue?
-More Iike clear yellow.
-Tell me whether it's negative.
I Iet a man I met at a fish store
do me without a condom.
Okay, show me.
Show me! Don't touch me.
It's negative.
I don't know why I do this to myself. It's Iike
I'm constantly attracted to men who punish me.
Maybe because you need to be punished.
Okay, Iisten, there's at Ieast
four baby daddies here for you...
...and I just texted three more.
One is a serious krumper.
Yeah, Iet's just set up a gang bang
and see who sticks.
And Ted, the one from
my cervical cancer commercial...
...on his way, just turned 40, totally mature.
-I don't want old sperm.
-Sperm's too old. Got it.
Oh, God. This guy, Nick,
won't stop texting me.
-Monster Dick Nick?
-Yeah.
We slept together, Iike, weeks ago,
and now he thinks we're dating.
Yucko.
You want any wine?
I have a sweet Zinfandel.
Yeah, yes, Zinfandel.
-What are you doing?
-Baby-wiping my whole body.
Hey, remember you told me
how there's that brain chemical...
...that releases when a woman orgasms?
Oxytocin.
I found it. In a pill.
-What?
-Yeah, my friend was telling me...
...he's been taking it recreationally or whatever,
which I thought was weird...
...because generally dudes can just get off
by Iooking at their own reflection.
Who's resentful?
But, anyway, I took it tonight.
No. AIice, there is no pill form of oxytocin.
-What you took was OxyContin.
-Yeah, same thing.
No, different thing. Drug-addict thing.
It's Iike heroin.
It's a really powerful narcotic.
I have been feeling nauseous...
...but often that's the precursor to my orgasms,
so I was just sort of going with it.
Luke and Henry just walked in.
Quick, get me a hot guy to talk to.
ALICE:
What? You invited them?
Oh, damn, Henry. You Iook tasty.
Yeah, this was my party to normalize things.
Are my boobs even?
You think I'm the drug addict. Eh.
See you on the other side.
Oh.
AIice?
Whoo!
[MELLOW POP MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
LOLA:
Hey. I'm so glad you came.
It's cool.
-Are you still mad at me?
-No.
I'm really sorry.
It's all good.
I hope things aren't weird
with you and Luke.
No. I called him.
We sorted it all out. Yeah.
Awesome.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
-Oh, I got-- I'm gonna be back.
-Yeah.
Just one sec.
[ALICE SCREAMS AND MOANS]
You see, I Iearned everything
I know about being a woman...
...from 90210.
That explains a Iot.
In every woman-- Henry.
In every woman...
-...there's a Brenda...
-Mm-hm.
... Kelly, my personal favorite...
...a Donna, hopefully minus
the gaping boob-hole...
...and an Andrea.
See, every woman is all of those women.
See?
Well, what about Emily Valentine?
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[CHUCKLES]
Well, he really sounds Iike a nice guy.
We've only been out twice,
but he is definitely courting me.
He designs prisons.
-I don't Iike him.
-Neither do I.
-Well, get rid of him.
-I gotta take what I can get.
Come on. You're Lola.
You can get whoever you want.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
-So you and Henry are talking again.
-Yeah.
I mean....
I mean, that was stupid.
I get it.
-Cool.
-Yeah.
I mean, he's been really cool
these Iast few weeks.
We've been hanging out.
It's been Iike old times.
But, you know, his place, it sucks.
-And my place, it's huge.
-So?
I was thinking, you know,
he might move in with me.
Or he is. He's moving in with me.
[ALL LAUGHING]
What?
I'm sorry. Is that--? Is that totally weird?
-No.
-Good.
Sounds Iike a super-fun party house.
Like Real World: Miami.
I'm gonna have some people over.
We're having some people over...
...and, I mean, I'd Iove for you to come.
I'II be there.
Great.
[PIANO KEYS CHIME]
LOLA:
I never wanted this for you.
I work my whole Iife, I don't apologize,
to take care of my family.
And I refused to be a fool...
...dancing on the string
held by all those big shots.
But I thought that, when it was your turn,
that you would be the one to hold the strings.
Well, it wasn't enough time.
But, that being said,
I pledge on the souls of my grandchildren...
...that I will not be the one to break the peace
we have made here today.
Did you just break up with me
as the Godfather?
You know what we should do sometime?
We should get a nice bottle of red
and just do the trilogy.
Lola! It's not even the best Godfather.
That's-- Pfft!
Ahh.
What is it you'd Iike to accomplish today
in your hypnotic trance?
I'd just Iike to find quiet.
My mind is, Iike, on crazy overdrive.
I'm constantly obsessing about everything.
Food, boys.
I need to concentrate,
I need to be writing, I can't do it.
Yeah, I just--
I'm unable to be in the moment.
Then that's exactly what we'II work on.
CIose your eyes.
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
Oh, my God. I'm s--
I'm just turning it off. It's just....
Right now. One second.
Okay. It's off. Okay.
LOLA:
Hey, AIice, it's me.
Listen, I'm really nervous
about going to Luke's party.
I feel Iike we're gonna be
the only single people there.
Do you think I should get a perm?
AIso not sure if I should
wear something see-through.
Call me.
LOLA:
I feel Iike I haven't seen you in ages.
I don't know. I've been around.
Well, I called you twice Iast week
and you didn't call me back.
Really?
You know what? Um....
One of those nights, I think
I was at a concert, maybe, with Hen.
And then the other one....
I can't remember. My back is so sweaty.
This party's gonna suck. Let's just not go.
No, I can do this. I just saw both of them.
The only difference now is I'm seeing them...
...in the apartment that I thought
I'd raise my children in.
Yeah, you're right.
When you put it that way, it does sound fun.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
I don't know if I can be here right now.
Does it make me Iook poor if I don't
eat the white outside part on the Brie?
What's up, AIice?
Oh, hey, what's up?
Where's Henry?
-He's over there.
-Oh, okay.
I'm gonna go say hi.
-You Iike the cheese?
-Yep.
So does your shirt.
Mm. Yeah, I'm eating for two.
What?
Oh, no. No, me and my shirt.
I'm eating for my shirt and me.
Sorry, that was such a dumb joke.
-I think I just peed a Iittle, yeah.
-I'm totally not pregnant at all.
LOLA:
How are you and...?
-Who?
-Leggy.
Her name is Peggy.
I know what her name is.
You seem really happy.
Hey, hey, Iet's go.
I think my TiVo's broken...
...and I have a very important episode
on the History Channel.
History of Witches. Do you--?
Oh, and Peggy says
she needs help with the ice, so....
Oh, right. You know,
she Ioves you, by the way.
-Oh, really?
-Yeah.
She Ioves you? How can she Iove you
after meeting you one time in a club?
So have you guys been talking?
Yeah, we're talking. That's what people do.
Um, anyway--
Oh, I was watching Chelsea Lately--
-Talking about what?
ALICE: Oh.
It's nothing. It's nothing important,
Honestly, don't worry about it.
We're not doing this here.
-Yes, we are.
-No, we're not.
-What is going on?
Uh....
Okay. Lo, we need to talk.
-No.
ALICE: It's nothing.
I mean, it's something,
but it hasn't become anything.
I mean, without me telling you first.
-Fuck, I'm an asshole. Shit, Iet me start over.
-No!
No, no, no, Lola.
-Listen to me. Not here, okay?
LOLA: No!
You could have just talked to me about it!
Then I wouldn't have been ambushed Iike this!
-I didn't go after this. It was an accident.
-No!
AII you had to do was tell me you had feelings.
We could've talked!
-Whoa, guys.
-Shut up!
When do I ever have time to tell you things?
-You're wrapped up in your own shit.
LOLA: Like I don't Iisten to your shit.
-AII that shit with that actor Roger?
-At Ieast I'm aware I'm not alone in this world.
I am alone in this world.
You've all Ieft me alone.
I never Ieft you, okay?
I've been beside you
every step of this process.
-The one time I step in front of you--
-I Ieft you.
They didn't Ieave you. I Ieft you.
And AIice and I, we make each other calm.
Calm, calm. If you were any more calm,
you would be dead.
Just work on you, okay, Lola?
Hey. Hey, Iady.
Lady, there's only $2 here.
Hello. You want to go to jail, Iady?
There's only $2 here! I'm talking to you!
[HISSES]
Are you insane? You better get back here.
Mmm.
[LOLA CHEERING]
Mm.
Yeah, Iadies! Mm. Mm.
Work the pole.
You know, Jessie Spano
was such a good girl, you know?
It's Iike why did she do it?
Like, the caffeine pills....
Get off the stage, bitch!
I don't want to go with you.
I Iike these people. They're my friends.
No.
Okay.
I'm down. I'm all the way down.
MAN: Get her out of here.
-I want to go back.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, God.
[SOBS]
LOLA: I wish I could say that
this was someone else's fault.
That it was Luke's fault.
Or Henry's fault, or Alice's.
But it's not.
It's me.
Release your emotions.
Feel the healing power of the platza.
Relax.
You feel good.
Ah!
Huh? That's good.
-A Iittle more. Good.
-Ah!
LOLA: In his final poem,
Mallarmé writes of shipwreck:
The man without a vessel
A solitary plume
Overwhelmed
Untouched
With very few words on the page...
...the writing itself creates space
for silence and pause.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
For in this world of shipwreck...
...there is hope in uncertainty.
Hi, AIice.
It's Lola.
I know that you probably don't
want to see me...
...but I would Iove to see you.
I'm around, if you want.
Okay.
Bye.
Hey, remember how much
I Ioved Cinderella as a kid?
-What a sick fucking kid.
-It's a classic.
It's what messes Iittle girls up,
because we all get obsessed with shoes...
...and then we think that some guy
is gonna come put them on our feet.
-That is a man's job.
-I actually thought I was Iiving in a fairy tale...
...and that Luke's shoe fit me perfectly.
I guess no shoe is a perfect fit,
especially when you have slightly irregular feet.
Right. Well, you gotta find
your own style, baby.
Are you telling me to go shoe shopping?
I have a friend, Diane--
No, she has an eight-and-a-half
and a nine-and-a-half.
That's not even close. That's a whole size.
-That's depressing, Mom.
-No, I know.
It's scary to think that one side could grow
and the other side doesn't.
-It's disgusting.
-Imagine her bras.
LOLA:
I got you something.
Oh, my God, you shouldn't have.
It's a douche.
I know you've been wanting a new one.
-I'm douchey.
-Eh.
-I'm so sorry about how I acted.
I'm sorry too.
I should have told you sooner.
-I was so stupid.
-Don't-- Don't be sorry.
I am so happy for you and Henry.
Really.
I Iove you.
Oh. Ahem.
So I want to have a party for my birthday
and I need your help.
-Is this a trick?
-No.
I know I have never had a birthday party before,
but I think I'm ready.
Okay. Yeah, I'm Ioving it.
Let's-- What are we doing?
Going to Six FIags?
No, I just think I need a clean start...
...because I've really fucked up
all my friendships over the past year.
-So....
-No.
It's Iike everyone always says:
To Iove someone else,
you have to Iearn how to Iove yourself.
But I don't know, after this year,
I don't think that's true.
I think to Iove yourself,
you have to Iearn how to Iove other people.
LOLA: IIIuminati.
ALICE: The IIIuminati.
And they say that Hillary CIinton is a Iizard.
The thing is, if you Iook at the sky enough,
you will see Iasers shooting out of the moon.
If you really, really Iook,
because I have seen it.
It was on YouTube, but I did see it
with my eyes through a computer.
-It's because the apocalypse is coming.
-I know.
-I'm moving to Canada.
-I'm just gonna try to keep to my routine.
ALICE:
AII right, I'm getting pizza.
LOLA:
Oh, my God.
-Hey!
LOLA: You came!
I'm so happy you came!
You never have a birthday party.
I'm having a bit of a rebirth,
so I thought it was cause for celebration.
-About the whole AIice thing--
-No.
-It's so fine.
-Really?
We don't hold grudges.
Well, I am actually still upset
that you Iost my Boyz II Men cassette.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
Oh, I don't speak Spanish.
-Ugh.
-Ugh. Come on.
LOLA:
Mm.
Missed you.
-Did you know he was coming?
-No.
I'm gonna get some nibblers.
Hey.
-What are you doing here?
-I couldn't miss this.
It's just kind of a picnic.
Yeah, well, I didn't want to miss this...
...because I miss this.
-Are you speaking in rhyming verse now?
-Yes.
Because I'm nervous. Uh....
Look, I just gotta say this. Um....
I mean, I got my space.
-I just ended up in another relationship.
-Right.
But it's fleeting.
And it's not real.
And I just think I needed some distance
to realize that.
-Was that all you needed?
-Yeah.
I mean, now we can go at this
from a totally new way.
I don't know what to say.
You didn't want me or us or any of it.
And then you got this distance.
But the thing is, I haven't, really.
What do you mean?
I mean, you've had time.
It's been months.
But I spent all that time obsessing over you.
And other people.
And I think I finally have some
perspective on what I need.
-Which is?
-Which is....
I'm so touched that you want to start
all of this back up again...
...but I'm taken. Heh.
By myself. I....
I've just got to do me for a while.
ALICE:
Lola!
I'm coming!
[BOTH LAUGH]
HENRY: Okay, yeah. Come on.
Let's go, folks. Fire up this pastry.
Here we go, here we go.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
LOLA: Okay, okay.
AII right.
Birthday rap!
-Get ready.
-Okay.
[RAPPING]
You're 6, you're Lola
You live in Angola
You're African, except you're not
But you're just as hot
You're a writer, you're a fighter
Like a Mark Wahlberg fighter
-Except you're Donnie
-I'm your mommy
And I'm your friend who's black
This is not what we rehearsed.
Happy birthday!
ALL:
[GROUP CHEERING]
LOLA:
AII right, Iet's eat cake.
Thank you.
Ooh!
LOLA:
I have 29 years before the next upheaval.
Before that crazy planet comes back
to wreak havoc on my life.
And when it's over...
...I hope I feel exactly the way I do right now.
[English - US - SDH]