You once said, talking
about your childhood,
"I grew up with seriousness
all around me. "
Yeah. My parents
were very, very strict.
He thinks
I put up 100,000
to watch it
go down the toilet?
He doesn't care
about your money.
I want him to know
it's every cent I've got.
It represents
pocket change.
I can't get hit harder.
Does he know what this
can do to me and Karen?
I know you're out there.
Does he know it?
Michael...
Listen, Roger, that does it.
Sounds good.
Fax it to me.
I'll look at it,
talk to you tomorrow.
I tried to keep it quiet.
I heard a noise
from downstairs.
Didn't you hear it?
No. I was on
the phone with Roger.
It's probably the wind,
Fuzzface here.
Why does he hate me?
If you paid more
attention to him,
he'd like you better.
If I fed him goodies
like you do.
I think you're jealous
ofTiny.
Of course. He sleeps
with you more often.
Is that...
Um, I'll go down.
Maybe we should
call the police.
No, that's O.K.
I'll just check it out.
Don't worry.
If it's anything serious,
I'll come back
for my driver.
Michael,
is everything all right?
There's somebody
in the house.
Call the police.
Michael!
No!
Stop it.
Stop!
Stop, motherfucker!
Back off.
Back off!.
O.K.
Drop it! Drop-drop it!
Drop it.
Drop it!
Just take anything
you want, all right?
You can have my watch.
I don't want
that goddamn watch.
Please don't hurt her.
I'll give you
anything you want.
Aah!
Karen!
Police, sir.
Hi. Come on in, guys.
Hi. I'm Officer Cole.
This is my partner
Officer Davis.
Mike, how are you?
What happened
to your foot?
I knocked a beer bottle
down in the kitchen.
I stepped in it.
It's nothing, really.
So, Mr. Carr, can you
tell us what happened?
Yeah. We were, uh,
we were upstairs in my office,
my wife and I,
and we, uh, heard a noise.
This is my wife Karen.
Thanks for coming
so quickly.
What happened after
you heard the noise?
Michael went down,
and I-I, uh...
I- I heard another noise.
I went down, and, uh...
It's O.K., Mrs. Carr.
Just take your time.
Well, this man jumped
out of the closet,
and he and Michael fought.
It wasn't much
of a fight, really.
I just grabbed his leg.
He was trying
to get away.
Got out in the kitchen.
He got ahold of Karen
and went out back.
He put a knife
to her throat.
You O.K.?
Yes.
You need a doctor?
No.
You sure?
Yeah, thanks.
Tiny.
Tiny?
Come here, Tiny.
Not a very good
watch cat, are you, Tiny?
He's useless.
Well, I guess
he likes policemen.
We'll have someone over in
the morning to dust for prints.
Try and not disturb
too much.
We've had several break-ins
in this area lately.
We're pretty sure
it's the same guy.
On this street?
In this general area,
but we'll get him.
Wouldn't mind
being there for that.
Does anybody want coffee?
Yes. I never
turn down coffee.
Whoa! Watch-
Watch the glass.
Oh.
Excuse me.
Thanks.
If this guy's been
doing this around here,
is there any chance
he's going to come back?
We were told this
was a safe neighborhood.
All things considered,
Mrs. Carr,
this is a safe neighborhood.
Mr. Carr probably scared
the hell out of the guy,
so he won't come back.
I'm getting a gun.
What?
No guns in this house.
Maybe she'll listen
to you guys.
Don't get a gun.
You can say that.
You've got one.
And I'm trained to use it.
I've done some shooting.
At targets.
Not people.
Look, take our advice.
Get an alarm.
Get a dog.
Forget about guns.
The wrong people
always get hurt.
Nice people.
Hey, I know what
you're thinking.
What-what am I
thinking, Roy?
I'm never going
to be able to sleep.
Me, either.
I thought he-
When he grabbed me,
I thought...
It's all right.
I don't think
I can stay here, Michael.
It's just so weird.
We'll get
some things together
and go to a hotel.
No. I mean I don't think
I can live here anymore.
I think we should
sell the house.
Wait. You love this house.
I know, but we
really don't need this.
Slow down.
Michael,
we're in way
over our heads.
We can barely
afford this place.
Don't get carried away.
Know what
we're going to do?
We're going to take
that cop's advice.
Tomorrow morning
I'll make a few phone calls.
We'll get the best security system
known to man, all right?
If that doesn't do it,
we'll just-we'll-
We'll get
a killer watchdog.
I mean, a vicious...
pit bull...
with fangs...
with a studded collar.
Come on, honey.
We'll be all right.
Come on.
You chased him around
with a fucking putter?
You're a hero.
Dirty Harry
and Arnold Palmer
all wrapped into one,
that's me.
Sounds pretty intense.
With me, boom.
Heart attack. Done.
You did O.K.
You guys all right?
Yeah. Well, Karen's upset.
Shit. Here he comes.
We have to kiss him?
Gentlemen.
I read your prospectus.
Demographics look good.
Well, I'll tell you,Jerry.
I'm not a big believer
in demographics.
It's a lawyer's tool.
No offense, Roger.
None taken.
Quite an amazing place.
The potential here's
fantastic, huh?
I've learned to go
with my instincts.
The one time
I used demographics,
I went belly up.
That wasn't Denver, was it?
He's done his homework.
You weren't the only one.
I put a lot of my
clients' money there.
All those buildings
are still empty.
That won't happen here.
This downtown area
has undergone
some amazing revitalization.
Those new buildings
over the last 10 years?
All filled with people,
all within shouting distance
of this place here.
O.K. Here's what
I want to do,
what worked
the other three times.
Put on a backers' party-
It's mine.
Hello.
Hi. It's me.
Hey.
Bad timing?
We're in the middle of it,
but we're getting close.
What's going on?
Those security people
haven't shown up yet,
neither have the police
to dust for prints.
Did you call?
Yeah. All I get
is the runaround.
Great.
I'll tell you what.
Here's what you do.
Call the police.
Ask to talk to those cops
from last night.
Those guys can help, O.K.?
O.K. I'll try.
I'll be home soon.
You all right?
Uh-huh.
You sure?
I love you. Bye.
Michael, this guy's good.
I'm being grilled here.
Michael, this area's high-crime.
So you get people in.
How do you keep
the bad element out?
I'm into that as we speak.
I'm working
on security right now.
Ha ha ha!
Michael, you remember
Officer Davis?
Oh, yeah.
How you doing?
I didn't recognize you
out of uniform.
You did all this?
It's no big deal.
It is.
We appreciate it.
It's the least I could do.
Mrs. Carr called my captain
and said nice things
about me and my partner.
Usually people call to bitch.
It was nice.
I'm grateful.
Can I get you something?
Sure. That would be great.
- Great.
- Thanks.
There's going
to be contact switches
on every point of entry.
A breeze won't
get into this house
without you knowing it.
Here you'll have
an infrared motion detector.
This right here
will be tripped
if anybody
breaks the glass.
Hey, w-what's he doing
in the bathroom here?
Oh.
Um...
It's-it's just
an extra precaution.
It's a safe room.
These old houses are great
because the doors
are like solid rock!
We put a heavy dead bolt
on each entrance here.
In case there's an intruder,
you lock yourself in
and wait for the cavalry,
which is us.
You just have to pick out
a code word now.
It's got to be seven letters.
Pyramid.
Pyramid?
Uh, this is
the Michael Carr residence,
and the code word's
going to be "pyramid. "
Right.
O.K. Thank you.
That's it.
Oh, yeah.
440 cubes, 500 horses.
Jesus.
You do the work yourself?
Uh-huh.
Every nut and bolt.
Installed the alarm.
Relaxes me.
That is nice, really nice.
Thanks.
You got a knack for
this security stuff.
Did you ever think about
consulting as a sideline?
Consulting?
Yeah.
Homes, businesses.
I got a club
I'm putting together downtown.
It's what you're doing today,
but you get paid
for your time.
I never thought about it.
Staying for dinner?
Yeah.
- You doing anything?
- Not tonight.
I'd be crossing the line-
Cops on one side,
everybody else on the other.
Come on in.
This has really been nice.
Usually, dinner for me
is a bunch of us
sitting around
boring each other
with war stories.
That's why cops
stick together.
Nobody else
could stand us.
You've never been married?
No. Nope.
She'll try to line you up
with one of her friends.
I'll get her,Jack!
Sorry, Michael.
She smells that meat
and goes crazy.
Meet me around the front.
I'm sorry.
I'm still a little freaked.
That's O.K.
That's understandable.
I can't believe you've never
been serious about anyone.
No.
Cops and marriage
are a tough combination.
I can't believe
how much I'm talking.
When I was a kid,
I hardly ever talked.
When I was in school,
I never talked.
I was famous for it.
Oh, well,
take it from a teacher.
We love those
quiet little boys
in the back of the class.
Don't you believe her, Pete.
She loves all kids.
Oh, that's what's missing.
I'm surprised you two
don't have a few
running around.
Michael, I'm-I'm sorry
about bringing up kids.
That's really none
of my business.
I just wanted
to thank you.
You really went out
of your way.
I can't tell you
what you did for Karen.
She'll bounce back.
She'll bounce back quicker
because of you.
What about you?
Have you bounced back?
I don't know.
Guy gets his hands
on your wife like that,
you feel pretty helpless.
You did what you could.
You showed
a lot of balls
going up
against that guy.
There was one moment
there where, uh,
he had ahold of her,
and I had that
stupid golf club,
but I thought
I could just-
I didn't-didn't
take the shot.
A fucking nightmare
when you think
about what could've
happened to her.
I wouldn't mind
one more shot
at that son of a bitch.
Really?
Hell, yeah.
I'd like to kick
the shit out of him.
I'm sure you would.
Wouldn't you?
I already know
what I would do.
I was just wondering
about a nice
civilized guy like you.
After what he did to Karen,
I think all the rules
are out the window.
I'd rip his fuckin' heart out.
Michael.
You're a scary guy.
Hey...
You know,
I bet you'd enjoy
coming on a ride-along.
What's that?
Ride along with us
on patrol one night.
You can do that?
We do it all the time
for writers,journalists.
Yeah. That sounds-
Yeah. I could do that.
I'm going to set it up.
Come watch us
kick some butt.
When?
Tomorrow.
Ugh.
Come on.
It'll be fun.
Yeah.
Why not?
Great. I'll see you then.
Sign this so your old lady
can't come after the city
if you get killed,
maimed, or dismembered.
Nothing will
happen to him.
He's with me.
Hey, Pete.
O.K., Mike,
a dope dealer, a public
defender, and my ex-wife
all get thrown off
the Empire State Building.
Which one hits
the cement first?
I don't know.
Who lands first?
- Who cares?
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, my gosh.
Look at this.
Think she's
a real blonde, Roy?
Officer...
was I going too fast?
Mm-hmm.
Do you have a license
and a registration, ma'am?
Yes.
Certain types of women
just have a thing for cops.
They think
we're like movie stars.
We ever search any one
of these assholes here,
we'd be up to our butts
in drugs and guns.
This place is one giant
supermarket of shit.
Isn't that right, Leon?
Whatever you say, Officer.
I ain't into nothing.
This is Mr. Clean.
That's right.
That's me.
Yes, sir. Mr. Clean.
Maria, como esta?
Bien.
Everything O.K.?
It's O.K.
No problemos?
No. No problemas.
If there is, you
let me know, O.K.?
All right.
I don't think you'll
be finding any clientele
for your club
around here, Michael.
Try it.
Best in L.A.
You know,
I ate before I came out.
I'm really full.
So...
you enjoying yourself?
Yeah. Yeah.
It's an eye-opener.
Something occurred to me
when you were
over at the house
for the barbecue, Pete.
I don't know how it works
in Los Angeles,
but when I was in Phoenix
and Kansas City,
I hired off-duty
police officers
to work the club.
Hear that? Mike's offering us
moonlighting money.
I'd like to talk about it.
Hi.
So how are you?
Are you, like,
the captain or something?
Lieutenant.
Rosa...
Come on. Vamonos.
Can't you see the lieutenant's
a married man?
Oh, yeah?
Oh.
Oh, well.
Te amo, roy.
Bye, Pete.
See you later, Rosa.
These bitches can't
get enough of us.
Michael, stay here.
Keep away.
Police. Everything
all right in there?
No! Everything
isn't all right!
Fucking asshole
hitJim in the face!
Fuck you!
In the fucking face!
Shut up!
There you go.
You all right?
Attaboy.
Just stay here with me
and hang on
for a second.
Roy, I'll take him now.
Take that piece of shit
back to the jailhouse
where he belongs!
Aah!
Mom!
Mommy!
See? They got him.
Why don't you go up and
get yourself cleaned up?
Me and Mike
will put the car to bed.
Works for me.
Later, gentlemen.
Take care.
It's a hell of a life,
huh, Mike?
Is it always like this?
Oh, yeah.
Day in and day out.
Hop up in front.
Uh, yeah.
And your wife
wants to know
why I can't meet
a nice woman.
You guys handled it all
pretty well.
Listen, where are we headed?
Just got one more
errand to run.
Come on!
Move!
Michael!
Aah!
Stay there.
Michael, meet Ernie Pike.
Come out and I.D.
This piece of shit.
Come on,
motherfucker!
Hey, that's him!
You got him.
Goddamn it!
That's him!
Did you hear that?
You just been made.
You just been made,
scumbag!
Picked up
a crackhead pal of his.
Turned in Pike here.
You broke into
my friend's house?
Huh?
Did you scare him
and his pretty wife?
Did you do that?
O.K. I'm sorry, man.
O.K.?
Shut the fuck up!
He doesn't want to hear
about you being sorry.
He wants to kick your ass,
and guess what, scumbag?
I'm going to let him.
Ready?
What?
What are you waiting for?
Let's go.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I'm serious.
You said you wanted
to rip his
fucking heart out.
Well, yeah, but I mean,
that was, you know-
I was just talking.
Tell him.
Say it. Say how you wanted
that uptown pussy.
Say it!
Is that what
you wanted? Say it!
Say it!
O.K. I...
Tell him!
Whatever you say, man.
Whatever you say.
Come here.
Don't you
fucking resist me.
Don't you resist me!
Now walk.
I said walk.
He just gave you the O.K.
Here. You don't even
have to touch him.
I wasn't going to
hurt nobody, man.
Shut up.
Come on.
Come on, Michael.
It's O.K. Listen.
He resisted.
He gets hit.
Shit happens.
Come on, Pete.
Y- you got him.
Nice going.
Let's take him in.
Michael, he put a knife
to Karen's throat.
You're going to let him
get away with that?
Hit the motherfucker!
Pete.
Hit him! Hit him!
No. I'm not doing this.
Hey!
Aah!
Motherfucker!
Aah! Aah!
Hey, Pete!
Pete!
Jesus, that's enough!
Honey?
Michael?
Yeah. It's me.
How'd it go?
Boy, what a screwed-up night.
What happened?
Ah, it was just-
It was weird.
I went with the guys
on a few calls,
got to watch them be cops.
Then we dropped Roy off,
and Pete had
a little surprise for me.
The guy who broke in here.
He caught him?
He did more than that.
The guy's in jail.
Hospital's more likely.
He really beat the living shit
out of this guy,
which is what I
was supposed to do.
What?
Pete was showing off for me.
Had the whole thing set up
so I could nail the guy.
I'm just glad it's over.
Yeah.
Are you sure
you're O.K.?
Yeah.
What's the matter?
I just...
I think our cop friend
is a little too tightly
wound, that's all.
Well, do you think you might be
overreacting a little bit?
Not really.
You know, I feel like
a big weight's been lifted.
Yeah. Well, I'm glad
you feel better, honey,
but I don't want him
around here anymore.
Honey, you're upset.
I understand.
But shouldn't
we give him
the benefit
of the doubt?
You're acting like Pete's
the criminal.
Oh, am I?
I was there, Karen.
I saw it, O.K.?
I don't care
what you think.
You don't care
what I think.
Fine. I won't
bother thinking.
Knock it off.
No, you knock it off!.
I'm sorry, but I don't
share your sympathy
for the man who broke in
and put a knife to my throat!
Hi. Uh, sorry.
I didn't mean
to scare you.
That's O.K.
Can I talk to you
for a minute, please?
Just let me
get my robe, all right?
You know, you really should
put a lock on that gate.
I don't think you came here
to discuss my gate.
No.
Did you hear
I arrested the burglar?
What happened?
What happened was,
the burglar
knocked me down
and took off running,
and when I caught him,
he resisted,
and it-it got ugly.
I don't think Michael
took it too well.
He didn't quite
put it that way.
It's not a TV show
out there, Mrs. Carr.
The reality gets to people
who've never seen it
up close like that.
You mean the violence.
Look...
When I first started out,
uh, I went
on a routine call.
All right?
It was a young kid.
He was high on drugs.
He was beating
on his girlfriend.
She couldn't have been
more than 15, 16.
Sweet girl-
blond hair, blue eyes,
so I didn't pay her
much attention.
I was reading the kid
his rights
when she took out a gun
and she shot me
right here in the chest.
So now I restrain
felons first
with whatever it takes-
Whatever it takes,
and that's how it was last night.
I don't need
another bullet in the chest,
and you don't need
a dead husband.
I'm very sorry
if Michael's upset.
I was just doing my job.
Pete. Pete, wait.
I- I'm...
I'm glad you got him.
That guy's
not going to forget
the night he made the mistake
of breaking in here.
That's for sure.
O.K. Enjoy your swim.
This is the chromalite,
and it serves
as the backdrop
for the dance floor area here.
With this chromalite,
we can create any environment.
We've got cityscape here,
but this could be a desert
or mountain. Anything.
Yeow!
I didn't know Michael had
so many good-looking friends.
Are you kidding?
We don't know
any of these people.
They're all
potential investors
or friends
of Michael's lawyer.
That's too bad.
Oh, now, there's one
I'd like to meet.
That's the guy I was
telling you about.
Your cop?
Mmm.
Really?
Candace said
the music's too loud.
Who?
Candace. My wife.
Roger, I got a question
only you can answer.
I got an I RS auditor
and a lawyer-
Another lawyer joke.
Divorce lawyer-jump off
a building at the same time.
Who lands first?
- Who cares?
Hi. How you doing, Mike?
Pete.
This place is great.
Thanks.
Pete Davis.
Los Angeles Police.
Hello, Pete.
Jerry Lurie.
Excuse me.
Jerry.
- My wife Candace.
- Hi, Pete.
Roger Graham.
Mike's been talking to me
about security
for the club.
Are you working
the area tonight?
No. I did the precheck
of the exterior.
I know it's normal to have
your entrance under the marquee,
but it's too open.
It's hard to control.
Be better to put
the entrance in the alley.
Make people line up
and file in.
If things get crazy
and we have to get heavy,
only a few people
will see it.
Something to think about.
Why don't you get
yourself a drink?
I'll be with you
in a minute.
Yeah. Good idea.
I know you have business to discuss.
I'll fill you in later.
Take care.
He makes a lot of sense.
Yeah.
You guys aren't bullshitting.
No. I take security
very seriously.
Yeah. We're really on top of it.
Hi, there.
Oh, Penny.
This is Pete.
Pete, Penny.
Hi, Penny.
Nice meeting you.
Hi. Nice meeting you.
We teach together.
Oh. Oh.
The kids at school
would be so impressed
I'm talking to
a real policeman.
They love cops.
They're young.
Give them time.
Maybe you'd like to come and
give them a talk sometime.
Um...
Yeah. Sure.
Public relations
loves stuff like that.
Well, speaking of public relations,
do you dance?
Honey, can you rescue Roger-
Help me out?
Hey, Penny.
Come on, Pete,
let's get that drink.
Here's to your club, Mike.
Pete, uh, I want to get
something straight here.
I'd like you to leave.
Michael,
what's with you tonight?
Why did you even
invite me here?
Oh, no. Telling you
and inviting you
are two completely
different things.
You seem so uptight.
Relax. Is it because
you were up late last night?
How do you know?
I was driving
by your house on patrol.
I saw your lights on
till well after 3:00.
You don't have to protect us
anymore. You caught him.
You think that's it?
You're not
a virgin anymore.
You saw how much
evil shit's out there.
What kind of friend wouldn't try
to protect you and Karen?
You listen to me
'cause I'm telling you-
You leave us alone.
You know, I think
I understand
where this is coming from.
Oh, do you?
Yeah. Just cut the shit, O.K.?
Nobody expects you to be me.
I make my living going up
against guys like Pike.
You don't. You've got nothing
to be ashamed of.
Is that what you think
this is about?
Yeah, I do.
I bet you had one hell of a night
when you got home.
A friend would be
thanking me.
I'm not your friend.
I'm nothing to you.
You're a sick guy.
I don't want you
around me or my wife.
Michael, your guests-
I'll be right there.
Michael needs to get
some things off his chest.
- Michael, Roger-
- Honey, please.
Kicking me out, Michael?
Honey, please don't
keep them waiting.
If I have to.
Tell Roger I'll be there
in a second, O.K.?
Everybody's free
To feel good
What are you going to do?
You going to call the cops?
Get the fuck out!
Lower your voice.
Fuck you!
- Lower your voice.
- Fuck you!
Your pigeon's watching.
Hope he doesn't
fly away on you.
Hey, need your car, man?
Ticket.
Don't you think
you were rough on Pete?
I told you I don't
want him around.
I wanted to make that clear.
Well, you succeeded.
Come on, guys,
it's time for our toast.
Come on.
Uh, good health,
good fortune,
and the time
to enjoy it.
That's an old
Castilian toast.
Translated.
Honey, looks like
you've just made
these two people very happy.
Candace, I know three people
your husband's
made happy tonight.
We'll all be happy when
everything falls into place, Roger.
What's not to fall into place?
That is a nice ride, dude.
I thought you were about to propose
another one of those wonderful
continental toasts.
To the two most
charming women here-
Your beautiful wife
and mine.
Ohh...
Mmm...
I'm glad you called.
I been thinking
about you a lot lately.
Leave it.
Sorry.
Still sensitive, huh?
You get shot
or something?
It was a fishing accident.
Yeah.
Who fishes with guns?
Are you all right?
'Cause we can go
to a motel
on a nice, cozy bed.
I mean, if you're having
a problem...
A problem?
The only problem
that I have...
is sleazy,
lowlife whores like you.
That's my problem.
What the hell's
wrong with you?
Get out.
I'm not getting out here!
Just get the fuck out!
Are you crazy?
I don't know where the fuck I am.
That's exactly
your fucking problem, isn't it?
Isn't it?
So, being a policeman
is really
all about helping people.
It's about
being a friend.
It's not about shooting
it out with bad guys.
That's what
you see on TV.
That's not why
I wanted to become a cop.
I became a cop
to protect people-
To make them
feel happy and safe.
Everybody understand that?
Yes.
Does anybody have
any questions?
What?
Do you wear
bulletproof vests?
Uh-huh. Have to
to protect myself.
Who else?
In the police car,
are you always
with somebody?
Mm-hmm. I have a partner
named Officer Roy Cole.
We've worked together
for the past 7, 8 years.
He's a very good friend.
O.K. You.
Can you show me how
to use your handcuffs?
Ha ha ha.
Sure. Come here.
What's your name?
Matthew.
Matthew?
All right, Matthew,
put your hands out.
Think I could get him
to use those on me?
There you go.
You're under arrest,
Matthew.
Hi. I couldn't take off
without saying thanks
for letting me
impress the kids.
That was really
a lot of fun.
Penny really set it up.
Yeah. I talked
to Penny before.
I'd like to apologize
for the other night.
Michael's behavior,
that kind of took me
by surprise.
I would've
never shown up.
Pete, it's not you.
It's him.
He's just not
been himself lately.
Would you like to go
get a cup of coffee?
I- I don't go on
for a while.
That's not a good idea.
You're safe with me.
I'm a cop.
Just for a little while?
Yeah. Just...
Is everybody in here a cop?
Yeah, pretty much.
About a year ago,
some jerk came in here
and tried to rip
this place off.
He didn't do too well.
When he come crashing
through the skylight,
I say, " How's your dick?"
I'm sorry. We should go
somewhere else.
No. This is great.
Really?
Yeah.
I think it's really nice
you got a place to go.
I'd like one.
Just-this is...
this is my least favorite
time of the day.
Why?
Uh... well, 'cause
it's getting dark out
and Michael's
not home yet.
How'd you and Michael
get together?
I was a waitress
at his first club.
Really? You were a waitress?
It was the first job
I ever had-
The first one I needed.
We were
kind of well-off.
My father,
as it turned out,
had sort of a gambling
problem, so...
You know, then people
started coming over
and taking our cars
in the middle of the night.
It-it was
kind of a scary time.
And Michael took you
away from all that?
Things always came
really easily to Michael.
Is that why
you married him?
I married him because
I fell in love with him.
Hmmph.
This is, uh...
I hardly know you,
and I'm talking like this.
Karen, all the things that come
so easily to Michael-
Were you one of them?
'Cause there's no man that deserves
that much good fortune.
I mean that.
A woman like you a man
should never take for granted,
and you should
never feel unsafe.
And I want you to know
that if you ever
need anything-
You're feeling bad
in any way
or you just need to talk-
That I'm there for you, O.K.?
As a friend...
as a real friend,
I'm there for you.
O.K.?
Come on. Let me
get you out of here.
How was your afternoon?
Hey. Good.
It was fine.
You and Mrs. Carr
getting along O.K.?
We seem to be.
When I was a kid
at Erasmus,
I didn't have a single teacher
that looked like Karen.
I mean,
they all had blue hair
with names like Mushbutt
or Silvercrone.
Silvercrone's my maiden name.
She had me.
Thank you.
The good news is
Frank Taft
was so taken with you,
he's considering kicking in
half the capital himself.
Frank Taft?
Booyoo Records?
Yeah.
We handle him.
There's a company
that's on a roll.
Major roll.
The kids love it.
Excuse me, sir,
I'm sorry.
Do you have
another card?
What's the problem?
It's canceled.
That's impossible.
Computer glitch.
Happens to me all the time.
This is unbelievable.
Relax.
You'll get the next one.
If you insist.
Don't worry about it.
All right. Now, we're on
for Tuesday night.
Bye.
Take care, Roger.
Michael, what's that?
Looks like you're having
a bad night, Michael.
Look, all I know
is what's on the
computer print-out,
and the computer says
you got parking tickets.
And the computer is wrong,
so I'm not paying 600 bucks
for tickets I didn't get.
I've worked here five years.
The computer's never wrong.
Do you want the boot off
your car or not?
Ha ha.
This is unbelievable.
Here.
Wait a minute.
Not that one.
Honey, you sure about this?
Remember the night we went
to the Minzers' house?
What?
They had the party
on Caon Avenue.
I got one ticket.
600 bucks?
Come on. Jesus.
Sorry, pal. You're over
the limit on this card.
It's a computer thing,
like Roger said.
Yeah. Right.
600 bucks.
Oh, Michael, drop it, O.K.?
Things went pretty well,
didn't they?
Yeah.
I thought
it went pretty good.
You know what?
It went great.
You really charmed
the pants off the Luries.
Oh, please.
Thanks.
Stay here
and lock the door.
Michael, what are you doing?
Karen, it's all right.
Hello.
Yes.
It's Michael Carr.
Uh, code word is pyramid.
Well, we just had our cat
knock over a screen is all.
Thank you. Bye.
You know, I never thought
I'd be so happy to see him.
Look, I thought it was
the right thing to do.
Thanks for making that decision
for both of us
without my having a say.
Goddamn it, you know
how I feel about those things.
You know how I feel
watching a man
attack my wife
and I can't do
anything about it?
I'm not going to be
in that position again.
I don't care
what the police say.
I'm keeping that gun.
I'm sorry.
I should've told you.
You all right?
Yeah.
Are you?
Aah!
Jesus Christ!
Just a goddamn minute! Hey!
What the fuck
are you doing?
I was responding
to your alarm, Michael.
Bullshit!
You tripped it yourself!.
What?
The credit cards,
the boot on my car-
You did that, too,
didn't you?
Everything all right
in here?
False alarm.
False alarm, my ass.
I'm as embarrassed
as you are.
Get the fuck
out of my house!
I'm very sorry,
Mrs. Carr.
Oh, man.
That son of a bitch is crazy.
Hello.
Yeah. Roger.
Michael?
I know it's late.
I'm sorry.
Listen, how do I get
a psycho cop off my back?
And you're
the same Michael Carr
that I O.K.'d
to do a ride-along
with Officer Davis
and Officer Cole?
Yes, sir. That's right.
The same Michael Carr whose wife
called to commend officer Davis?
Yeah.
The same two people
that are now
being terrorized
by this out-of-control sicko.
Out-of-control sicko.
Sure there's nothing personal
in this, Mr. Carr?
There's no question
that it's personal.
What do you call it when an officer
busts into your bedroom
while you're having sex
with your wife?
Yes, well...
Officer Cole's report says
he and Officer Davis were
responding to an alarm.
That was verified
by your security company.
Sure. How about the boot,
my credit cards?
What about them?
Got any proof that this guy
did those things?
You know, you're accusing
a highly decorated officer.
I don't care
how many medals he has.
I want this
taken care of.
Or else?
You're not
giving me anything.
You didn't
bring any evidence.
You don't have
any witnesses,
not even a home video.
These days, everybody's got
a goddamn home video.
O.K. Fine. You're just going
to bury this thing.
Mr. Carr,
this is a professional
organization here,
and we're going to do
a professional investigation, O.K.?
Mac, bring me
the complaint forms, will you?
If there's any truth to your
allegations, we'll take care of it.
Thank you.