Come with me
To the sea
Of
Love
Do you remember
When we met
That's the day
I knew you were my pet
I want to tell you
How much I love you
Come with me
To the sea
Of
Love
Do you remember
Oh, baby.
Okay?
I can't...
Is this okay?
Is this okay...
I.D. S, fellows.
Invites, guys, invites.
Invites and I.D. S, guys,
invites and I.D.s.
I.D. S, fellas.
Invites and I.D. S, fellas.
Welcome to the Yankees.
All right,
go on in, young man.
Welcome to the Third Annual
Meet the Yankees Breakfast.
Have a seat, fellas.
The Yankees will be here soon.
Hey, yo, Frank.
Yo, David.
- How you guys doing?
- Yo, bro. Where the Yankees at?
- Oh, they're coming.
- You a Yankee?
- You don't recognize me?
- Shortstop?
- Used to be.
- What?
Sure. Holy cow!
- I thought so.
- You're the Scooter!
Yo, Efram, this dude
is Phil Rizzuto.
Do that again.
Holy cow!
Phil, how come
you pouring us juice?
How we get to the game?
We got you covered.
Yanks up in here?
- Oh, yeah.
- All right. Bust it out.
Yo, Scooter.
Scooter!
Scooter.
Hey, hey, I'm good.
Get some food.
Go ahead.
Okay, fellas.
I got good news,
and I got bad news.
Which you want first?
Good news, good news!
Fuck that. Give up
the bad news, homeboy.
- Yeah!
Bad news wins.
Uh, the Yanks
can't make it here, guys.
You can't go
to the stadium.
We got 45
outstanding warrants...
eating our pancakes here.
On behalf of
the New York Yankees...
and the New York City
Career Criminals Investigation Unit...
you are all under arrest.
Sorry, guys.
We got you.
What's the good news?
Good news is coming around.
Yo! Yo!
Excuse me.
I'd like to
propose a toast.
Hold it.
To Detective Frank Keller...
on today, his 20th anniversary
on the job.
- Sit down!
- Boo!
I can't believe
you're not retiring.
I get 20 years,
I'm history.
Take half my pay...
Open a motel, a bar,
a polygraph school.
I'm going
to be 46 years old...
sticking my pencil in some dead skull
looking for a bullet?
Nothing wrong with motels.
I'll come visit you.
Yeah, sure.
Anyway, congratulations.
Hey, am I too late?
Got an invitation?
Yeah.
Who's this?
That's my son.
Ernest Lee, the invitation's
for you only.
I can hardly meet
Dave Winfield...
without taking my boy.
You got I.D., Ernest?
Yeah.
Grand theft auto...
two counts.
We're all booked up, Ernest.
Hey, I got an invite.
I said we're all booked up.
Thanks, man.
Catch you later.
Gruber.
Frank Keller.
How you doing?
I wake you?
Could I... Could I speak
with my wife, please?
Yeah, my ex-wife.
Denise. How you doing?
I wake you?
Oh, I'm sorry. Listen...
I got to talk to you.
I think...
I got appendicitis.
Hello?
Do you remember
When we met
That's the day
I knew you were my pet
I want to tell you
How much I love you
Come with me
My love
Mr. Mackey!
To the sea
The sea oflove
I want to tell you
How much I love you
Do you remember
Mr. Mackey?
Thank you, Chief.
- Where's it at?
- 18F.
- Anybody talk to you?
- No one of weight.
No one of weight?
You ever on the job?
Me?
I'm just a square badge.
I was in Korea.
Yeah? I thought
you were on the job.
Listen, we'll talk later, okay?
I'm of weight.
"You ever on the job?"
Oh, shit.
It's called making
people feel good...
so they'll cooperate with you.
You should try it sometime.
I'm sorry about
that phone thing last night.
I'm having a mid-life crisis.
I don't want you
calling at 3 A.M.
Call Denise at decent hours.
Decent hours?
What's that?
9 A.M. To what...
Dinnertime? 8 P.M.?
I can't believe those guys.
You never saw Joe Louis.
In the bedroom.
Louis? Where did you see him?
Way before you were born.
Joe Louis.
They called him
the Brown Bomber.
He was gorgeous.
You want to take
the lady outside?
Getting a little
crowded in here.
Your prints, too, Chief.
So, what's
this guy's name?
James...
Mackey.
Mack the Knife.
You know...
when she was
married to me...
I was never going to die.
We fight, we split...
she goes to you.
So it goes.
Life is forever, right?
What do I care?
I passed my 20 yesterday.
Everybody says retire...
so...
I feel mortal
all of a sudden.
Know what I mean?
I say he's dead 48 hours.
No.
Look at the lividity.
It's more like 36.
Smells like 48.
Smells like 36.
I was just trying to
get some attention.
You know?
I apologize.
It was just...
we're in the same squad...
six years.
Huh?
We don't so much as have
a beer together.
How the hell do you
take my wife away?
Hey...
I didn't take
nobody nowhere.
You understand?
You didn't treat her right.
She walked.
I didn't treat her right?
You want to kick
somebody's ass about it...
you kick your own.
Fuckface.
I'll check everybody out,
but truthfully...
it boils down to grabbing
the strange trim...
he got hooked up with.
This guy's a swordsman
extraordinaire.
Could be a lady
gets pissed off...
because they're in bed, he's...
Starts moaning Mary
instead of Gladys.
Hell hath no fury
and all that.
How do you know
the trim is strange?
Maybe it's a steady.
Strange. Know how I know?
Records... 45s.
Nobody whips out old 45s...
except on
first or second dates.
Getting to know you,
so what do you do?
Take out old records...
show the broad
you kept them...
meaning you're
a sentimental individual.
Who does that
with somebody they know?
Once you know them,
who gives a shit?
How you doing, Chief?
Hey, working hard
or hardly working?
Little of both.
How you doing?
- Okay.
- You think of anybody else?
Maybe the mailman
in the afternoon.
I don't remember.
There's a cable TV repairman.
What's that, Cabletime?
But he was down
in the basement.
Pretty much what
I told you yesterday.
What about ladies?
See any young ladies?
See any of them?
You told me
there was a sex parade.
If I'm looking to see somebody
in particular, I'll see them.
But if I'm hailing a cab
or in the package room...
Okay. We'll talk again.
So the emcee says
to the first husband...
"Where did your wife say...
was the most exotic place
you ever made love?"
So this guy's thinking, right?
He's got a brain
like a frigging pea...
but he's thinking.
Finally he says,
"In the butt".
You get it?
Hey, anybody do any work...
over at 365
West End Avenue Monday?
I did.
See anybody there
not looking right?
You know...
freaked out, scared?
Running like lost?
I saw some ladies
in the laundry room.
Why? What happened?
There was a shooting.
If you remember,
want to give me a call?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thank you.
Mmm
Come with me
My love
To the sea
It's so good.
It feels so good.
Please. Please...
- Excuse me.
- Hey! A toast.
Excuse me.
For our host.
10 promotions, overdue.
Meet your detectives.
Tommy Squibb,
detective third grade.
Felix King,
Joe Pines,
detective third grade.
Hey, fellas!
Come on,
I'm giving a toast here.
Tommy Squibb,
detective third grade.
All right, George.
Where do you learn that?
That's like
watching a movie.
Yeah, well,
it keeps me fit.
I get in a beef
with a guy...
I hit him fast,
I'm out of there.
I don't like getting hurt.
God gave fat guys guns
to handle that. You Frank Keller?
- Sherman Touhey from the 112.
- Forest Hills?
I heard you caught
a good one...
face-down taxpayer,
back of the head?
- Me, too, on Yellowstone Boulevard.
- No shit?
The bullet's no use.
Pancaked on the bed frame.
We got cigarette butts
with lipstick on them.
We didn't get any butts.
Any prints?
Yeah, nothing showed up
on the files, though.
Let's compare tomorrow.
Uh, Dewars, double Dewars
on the rocks.
Budweiser.
You know something?
You talk lipstick...
I think my guy
got done by a broad.
Oh, yeah?
How's that?
We're talking
four-star ladies man here.
Hey, you play, you pay.
Am I right?
My wedding night,
I wake up...
my wife's got the tattoo needle,
the eyeshades.
I got "property of"
on my balls.
Only kidding,
but catch my drift?
This guy, I found letters
from singles magazines...
he placed an ad in.
He didn't open
any envelopes.
You find any records there?
What do you mean,
like files?
Records, like old records, 45s.
One was playing
on the turntable.
Sea of Love.
Remember that one?
Jesus.
Come with me, my love
To the sea
The sea of love
I
Wanna tell you
How much
I love you
Yeah.
Do you remember
When we met
That's the day
I knew you were my pet
I wanna tell you
How much
I love you
Do do do do
- Something's got to come off.
- That's it?
- You got to take something off.
- I...
- Yeah!
- All right!
Come on, take it off!
I just met this guy.
Actually,
I admire this woman...
whoever she is,
for her directness.
I mean, the guy
fucks around on her...
falls asleep... whatever... Bingo!
Pop him in the head,
it's over.
Other women, like my ex-wife
Denise, for example...
you step out of line
a little...
she'd like to stick it here,
stick it there...
let you
walk around bleeding.
This one, bingo!
No muss, no fuss.
Evelyn Woods School
of Speed Revenge.
No walking wounded.
Oh... fuckin' women!
Hey, Grube,
let me ask you something.
Your wife, does she
stick it to you?
So what are you
trying to say to me?
You're a happily
married man.
Maybe Gruber's too busy
sticking it into her...
to notice when she's
sticking it into him.
Guys, break it up!
Break it up!
Are you okay?
He's crazy. Let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
Fuck it.
"Silver moons...
a lifetime of Junes,
old rock tunes."
Who the hell are you?
Oh, wait a minute.
Uh... what's my name?
This isn't funny.
What's my name?
Jim Mackey.
So you answered his ad
in New York Weekly, huh?
Uh-huh.
I don't know
why I'm crying.
I never even
got to meet him.
It's just so sad,
somebody dying.
So you wrote him,
or you called him?
I wrote him...
and then he called me.
Fate sucks, I swear.
Hey, Gina, maybe
you'd feel better...
if you took
those balloons off.
They're the only things
keeping me up.
Frank.
The lieutenant said I could
read the jacket on your case.
Guess what?
The prints match.
The same doer.
Ain't that grand?
Well, I got one for you,
my man.
Your guy put an ad
in a singles magazine?
New York Weekly.
Bingo to that.
My guy's in there, too.
"Silver balloons,
endless Junes...
"old rock tunes...
"let me put it
in your moon.
Wire palladin."
Something like that.
Want to hear my guy?
"City streets
beneath my feet...
"4 A.M., the longest hour...
"the hunt goes on
till the break of dawn...
for love,
the rarest flower."
This lady,
she's in the crosshairs.
Poetry lover.
More like she hates it.
Listen, I had my lieu
talk to your lieu...
and we're
a two-man task force.
What do you think?
Queens or here?
You fucking kidding me?
I'd kill to work in Manhattan.
You want to work in Queens?
Let me introduce you around.
I'll catch them tomorrow.
I got a tuxedo fitting
in an hour.
Got a lounge act?
My daughter's getting
married Sunday.
Hey, you like weddings?
Steve walks warily
down the street
With the brim
pulled way down low
Ain't no sound
but the sound of his feet
Machine guns ready to go
Are you ready
Are you ready for this
Are you hangin' on
the edge of your seat
Out of the doorway
the bullets rip
To the sound of the beat
Another one bites the dust
And another one gone
and another one gone
And another one
bites the dust
Hey, I'm gonna get you, too
Another one bites the dust
Yeah
Whoo!
Want to dance with
a couple bridesmaids?
Okay. Want to know
how we catch her?
We put in our own ad.
Say what?
New York Weekly magazine.
We put our own ad in.
100 guys place ads
in there a month.
They get 30-50
responses each.
That's 4,000-5,000 women.
Do we go out with 5,000 women?
Hell, no.
She's into rhyming ads,
so we put one in...
moon, June, spoon,
sand dune.
We set up dates
with 40-50 of them.
We take them out...
some restaurant,
some bar...
get prints on a wineglass...
Bingo! She's dropped.
That's horseshit,
but I love it.
How many guys placed ads
last month that rhymed?
Three.
She went out
with two of them.
Oh, shit!
We haven't chased down
that third guy.
Raymond Brown.
8130 Austin Avenue.
I tracked him
through his postbox.
You a fucking cop?
Sometimes.
Gruber.
I'll catch up with you.
How you doing?
This 20-year thing,
it's kicking my ass.
I'm sorry.
"Raymond Brown,
Downtown Brown."
Here we go.
"Loneliness and silence...
"envelop a heart
that pounds like thunder.
"All the love I have inside...
- is ripping me asunder."
- Ha ha!
"The city is a jungle of pain...
but my love
is from the soul."
So be so kind
as to answer this ad...
and you can ride on my pole.
Give the guy a break.
This is a major
lonleyhearts here.
Major.
Good afternoon.
I'm Detective Frank Keller.
This is Detective
Sherman Touhey.
Does Raymond Brown
live here?
Daddy!
They're cops.
What's up, fellas?
What's the matter?
Daddy, are you okay?
I want to tell
you something.
I love my family.
Raymond, no kidding,
we don't give a shit.
We need names
of your dates...
and their letters.
No letters.
Raymond, there's some
psycho woman killing guys.
I swear I didn't
go out with them.
I threw the letters away.
Raymond, you take the time...
to make up
this beautiful poem...
about loneliness
and silence.
You spring $300...
to put the ad
in the magazine.
You spring another,
say, 5 yards a month...
for some love nest
in the village...
50 bucks for
the post office box.
You're telling us...
you never
went out with them?
Raymond, please.
The worst part
of being a cop...
is all you hear
from people are lies.
"I didn't do it.
I wasn't there.
It's somebody else."
Blah this. Blah that.
I swear on the eyes
of my children.
30 sit-downs,
30 sets of prints...
Miss Wrong, we got her.
Upstairs gives us 300
for the magazine ad...
we spring for a few vinos,
a chef salad or two...
bag the wine glasses,
it's over.
What? Come on.
"What? Come on"?
Suppose I get my own money,
buy the ad myself...
we drop her, you pay me back
like it's a bet?
Suppose I set you up
with my sister-in-law?
She got great tits.
Divorced, no kids, no cats.
The lieu's sister-in-law...
she sounds great.
I swear on the eyes
of my children.
We should've tailed him.
We fucked up.
He fucked up.
Don't leave the restaurant.
Don't lay a hand on them.
Don't have
intercourse with them.
It's over.
I'm not doing it.
You converse, you get prints,
and you split.
You wear a wire.
We'll have a sound van outside.
Two-man backup
at another table.
Keep the restaurant receipts.
I don't want to read about this
in The Village Voice.
What's with the backup
and wire?
What's she going to do... confess,
shoot me? We're in a restaurant.
To make me happy.
Now, who's writing the ad?
Who's the poet?
Roses are red...
violets are blue...
I got one yea-long...
and it's all for you.
I got one yea-long!
Check it out.
I got one, I got one,
I got one!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Check this one out.
Windswept hallways
in my heart...
echo the blackness
of eternity.
Get out!
Edgar Allan Poe, this guy.
I'll be sitting across
from Morticia Addams.
- Thing.
- Gomez!
No, she's a shooter, right?
So, how about
something like, um...
Uh... many a girl
has shot me down.
I've been shot before...
Shot me down...
Hot to trot,
give Frank a shot.
I live alone...
within myself...
like a hut
within the woods.
I keep my heart high
upon a shelf...
barren of other goods.
I need another's arms
to reach for it...
and place it
where it belongs.
I need another's touch
and smile...
to fill my hut with songs.
Not bad, huh?
It's a little corny,
but it's good.
Better than what we got.
Just make that up, Mr. K?
Frank's mother wrote that.
In high school. 1934.
She was a goddamn
beautiful person.
Go ahead. Use it.
She'd have liked that.
- Good poem.
- Say it again.
You guys are fucking slobs.
- And you're GQ.
- Later, Frank.
Oh, God.
Pop. Come on.
You stay here
with me tonight.
Come on, come on.
Come on. Come.
Come on.
Come on, come on. Come on.
That's it, that's it.
Where are you taking me?
Am I walking?
I'm walking, right?
Pass for it, yeah.
You got the wrong guy.
- Shut up.
- I'm the wrong guy.
Sorry, Frank.
Okay, kid, smell
a shooter in there?
Ahh.
I don't know, Gloria.
I just got this...
this hopeful feeling...
when I read your letter.
It was just...
I can't explain it.
I'm a printer. Yeah.
My own business.
Amanda. My mother's name
was Amanda.
- Okay.
- Miranda.
You're a what?
That's what?
You like guys and girls
or girls?
Oh, that's cool.
That's cool. Me?
Yeah, well, sometimes,
you know...
but, uh, mainly girls.
Women, you know.
Uh-huh. Well...
how's around, uh...
you a night owl?
Solid. Let's get crazy then.
Not that I haven't
done this before.
Shove this in here.
I like doing this.
- Is he on, Bill?
- Yup.
Okay, man.
- I look natural.
- You look good.
Can I help you?
- Good evening, sir.
- Good evening.
Chair this evening?
Yes, thank you.
- Cocktail this evening?
- Yeah.
What kind, sir?
Bourbon and water.
Bourbon and water
it is, sir.
Come back, now.
Do you remember
When we met
That's the day
I knew you were my pet
Can I get a little
hi-de-hi here?
If I look half as good as you
at your age...
you got nothing
to worry about.
You look great.
You're very sweet.
It's just that I should've said
on the phone the age I am.
You look better than
3/4 of the girls I know...
that are half your age.
Did that come out right?
Yes, yes, thank you.
I'll buy that.
I'll quit while I'm ahead.
So, uh, the lady would like
another white wine?
- Yes, please.
- And I'm fine here.
Well...
what do we do now?
Well, I tell you...
I got to pick up
my son in half an hour...
and the timing's terrible.
Should we
have dinner sometime?
Oh, sure. We'll call.
We?
- We? I said we?
- Yes.
That's me. All day on the phone,
it's "We this, we that,"
meaning my company,
you know. I'll call you.
Check, please.
I'll call you.
Me.
No, you won't.
Oh, well.
I don't know.
I get this
very weird feeling...
you're not
who you say are you.
There's something
not right about this.
Oh?
What do you mean?
Like what?
You got cop's eyes.
Cop's eyes.
You look at me, I feel like
I did something.
Like what?
My ex-husband was a cop.
You're a printer?
If you're a printer,
I got a dick.
Well.
I didn't doubt it
for a minute, baby.
Think you could go
for a babe with a dick?
Depends on
her personality, really.
So, you're divorced, right?
I said that.
You got kids?
Kid... one kid.
A boy?
No. A girl.
You got a girl, right?
You know, it's interesting...
your coming
from York, Pennsylvania...
because in a way...
you went from York
to New York.
You like the park,
and I like the beach.
You're a printer,
I manage a shoe store.
And I don't believe in
wasting time on this stuff.
You know what you know
and you go with it.
- You go with what?
- You're just not my type.
Oh, well.
I mean, you just sat down.
Give it a little bit of time.
I believe
in animal attraction.
I believe in love at first sight.
I believe in this.
I don't feel it with you.
I'm hell on wheels
once you know me.
How are you folks doing here?
Is that wine okay, miss?
You haven't even
touched your glass.
Have a little sip.
You know, warm up.
Let's raise a glass here.
Come on, here.
- Let's have a happy hunting toast.
- It's nothing personal.
Oh, come on.
Where are you going?
Come on.
Kiss my tiara, bitch.
Look at that.
I didn't get prints.
How many more
of these we got?
Okay. That's two more.
Two more.
Ah, no.
Oh, mercy, mercy, mercy.
How are you doing, Frank?
Okay.
Anything on the prints?
Nothing yet.
How's your head?
It couldn't be worse.
Hey, how are you doing?
Terry. Cabletone.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's up?
I told your partner...
there was a kid there
that day.
A black kid.
I think he was
from the supermarket...
'cause I saw him
with groceries earlier on.
Anyhow, I'm working
down in the basement.
About 20 minutes later...
he tears through there
like a bat out of hell.
No groceries.
I mean, why is he going out
through the basement?
There's a lobby, right?
Anyhow...
the kid has those, um...
those black militant
corn holes...
I mean, corn rows
in his hair.
He looks like a real shitbag,
if you ask me.
How are you doing, Chief?
One of your kids got corn rows?
You know, Afro hairdo?
Stevie Wonder hair.
- Wonder hair?
- Reggie, he means Quawi.
Where's he?
- I fired his ass Monday.
- How come?
On a delivery,
he doesn't like the tip...
he screams at the customer.
- You got his address?
- Maybe.
What did he do,
kill somebody?
Quawi...
Quawi Benjamin.
"Spooney." Call him that,
he goes crazy.
I got nothing here.
He only worked
like a week or so.
If he comes in
or you see him, call us.
Sure.
Hell on wheels, huh?
How quickly we forget.
No.
I don't forget you.
You're the "animal attraction,"
right?
"Love at first sight."
- What, do you live around here?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah?
88th Street.
I live on 85th.
You know that poem you wrote,
you didn't write it.
I read that poem...
and figured this is either
a very sensitive guy...
or he ripped off
some lady's poem...
or some girl's poem.
- You didn't write it, right?
- Nope.
Some lady did, right?
My mother wrote it
some 50-odd years ago.
That's why my father fell
in love with her.
Something like that.
Is that true?
So he says.
Hmm. I like that.
I like that, uh,
that you did that.
You want to hear
my idea of poetry?
Precision in life.
Knowing when and how
to make your move.
Say your piece...
like you the other night
with me.
Oh, that was...
poetry in motion.
Beautiful.
Look at me.
What?
You still want to go have
that happy hunting toast?
What happened to, uh,
the animal attraction?
What are you,
fucking nuts?
What if she's the doer?
We won't get the prints
back till tomorrow.
Wait till then.
Hey, come on,
the doer's down south.
Spooney, Quawi,
what's his name.
Listen, listen.
This... This one walked.
You remember her?
You with that bitch...
who wouldn't even
drink with you?
Yeah. It's good in a way.
I'll get her prints.
By sending your dick
to the lab?
That'll be
some great testimony...
"You see, Your Honor...
"first, I whipped it out,
then she whipped it out."
You catch my drift?
How do you know
it's this Quawi kid?
It's probably a broad.
You know that.
She's a friggin' suspect.
Walk away.
Frankie? Just walk away.
Nothing to it, Chief.
That's it.
I'm walking. Okay?
See you tomorrow.
No. Just a girlfriend.
Yeah. All right.
Okay. Thanks a lot.
I'll talk to you later.
Something came up,
you know.
Isn't that crazy?
Boy.
What's your name again?
Helen.
You know why
I got married?
I was 37.
I wasn't married.
- So I got married.
- I can top that.
You know why
I got married?
Some guy says, "I love you".
I knew him a week.
- Playing hard to get?
- Yeah, right.
We didn't last very long.
Me, neither.
The wedding lasted longer
than the marriage.
But we still...
We're still friends.
Sort of. You?
Friends? No.
I found out I was pregnant,
I walked.
You walked?
What do you mean?
- The guy didn't know about the kid?
- No. He's out of the picture.
You know, sometimes when
I think about...
the people I got involved with,
the choices I made...
it's pretty amazing.
But I found something out.
There are very few mistakes
that can't be corrected...
if you got the guts.
If you got the guts.
Last call.
What are they, bombing us?
Oh, hell.
You know,
when it gets late...
sometimes...
I feel like a... big cat...
in a small cage.
Oh, yeah?
You know...
I have done some desperate,
foolish things...
come 3:00 in the morning.
You mean
like being here with me?
Where's your bathroom?
Huh?
Over there.
Where's my bag?
Get in bed.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, good Christ.
Holy fuck.
What the fuck?
Oh, shit.
Holy fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I can't believe it.
I can't believe it.
Oh, fuck.
Jesus Christ.
Oh! Oh, my God!
Where did you put it?
Oh, no! No! No!
What are you doing?
Open the door!
Open this fucking door!
Open this door!
What is it?
This ain't real.
Open this fucking door!
It's a starter's pistol.
I saw...
You goddamn son of a bitch!
Easy, easy.
Don't you ever fucking
put your hands on me!
- I got scared.
- Tell me about scared.
What are you doing
with a starter's pistol?
None of your business!
Get off of me.
Listen. Listen to me!
I saw the gun
sticking out of the purse.
I freaked, okay?
It was a reflex.
Feel my heart.
Go ahead.
It's like a drum.
Feel it?
I'll tell you some stories
about scared sometime.
You don't know.
This city...
what it does to people.
I can't apologize enough for...
I don't know.
I got this survival rush.
You start to...
You start to think
with your hands...
not your...
Like an animal.
I just...
Did I hurt you?
No.
What?
What are you looking for?
What are you doing?
Huh? Huh?
What are you looking for, huh?
What are you looking for?
Oh.
Huh?
Ah, Jesus.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, Jesus.
What are you looking for?
It was too late
to call you back.
Yeah, just a friend.
Okay, I'll be home...
I'll be home
when I get home. Bye.
Damn.
You're killing me.
Is that the sun?
Are we still alive?
I thought you were
an insomniac.
I am.
I must have fainted.
What are you doing there?
I can't make you out.
Helen, right?
Uh-huh.
Come here.
What?
I got to talk to you.
There's something
I got to say.
You're kidding.
Are you kidding?
I'll have to be airlifted
to a standing position.
But you, you're something.
You go in the kitchen.
You made coffee.
What are you, Superman?
Wonder Woman.
What do you wonder about?
How we made it through
last night in one piece.
Last night?
Let me tell you
about last night.
Let me tell you.
Uh-uh.
No. Yes.
Cut it out.
I have to get home
to my daughter.
Your daughter?
She's with
your mother, right?
Mm-hmm.
Your mother live with you?
She's helping us out
for a couple of weeks.
I don't know about this.
What's it like working
in a print shop?
A print shop?
Yeah.
Inky.
What's it like
running a shoe store?
It's okay.
But we don't live
for our work, do we?
No.
I like to think
I live for love.
I mean, what else is there... food?
You're something else.
No, you're something else.
You've no idea how many creeps
are out there.
You're wired like
no one I ever met...
but you're a good man.
You never know.
I always know.
Or at least I find out.
What do you mean, creeps?
Manipulators. Liars.
Guys who wait
till you're in deep...
before you find out
who they really are.
Then you're fighting
for your life.
Creeps.
You asked.
You got any cigarettes?
You smoke?
Sometimes.
Does that bother you?
What brand?
I mooch.
I think I'm out.
Let's see here.
See any jump out at me?
I got to go.
- Huh?
- I got to go.
I like to be home when
my daughter wakes up.
Hello.
Keller here.
She's still out there.
No prints match up.
So, uh...
So should we dust your dick?
You know, cover all bases?
Would you finish that sale?
Help you
with something, sir?
Yeah, you got this
in a sneaker?
I was in the neighborhood,
so, you know...
I thought I'd come in.
Why are you whispering?
I'm whispering?
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
I just want to talk to you.
Okay. Have a seat.
I'll be with you
in a minute.
What did you want
to talk to me about?
Well...
I was going to ask you
about something.
About some of the people
you've been seeing...
over the past month or so.
You know... guys.
It's none of your business.
It is, in a way,
my business.
Yeah, and how's that?
Well...
forget it.
It's stupid.
Forget it.
Look, I don't sleep around,
if that's what you're talking about.
No, that's not it.
Why don't you
come over to my house...
tonight for dinner,
and we'll talk.
Yo. Lady.
I was in here... what...
six months ago...
and, uh...
you had this beautiful boot.
It was Rivoli, Ravioli...
something like that.
Rivoli. We're out.
Try back in two weeks.
Look, can I help you
or what, huh?
What's your problem?
Tommy, let's blow.
The guy's a cop.
Hey, hey...
Let's blow.
If I beat the shit out of you...
I get nailed for assaulting
an officer, right?
You piece of shit.
Okay, what?
You're a cop?
Yeah.
So? What?
Pretty bad, huh?
It's just too much for you.
You let that scum in...
but my being a cop
is just too much.
Let me tell you something
about this.
All these people in here
with their rocks and furs...
they get robbed or raped,
I'm all of a sudden their daddy.
Come the wet-ass hour...
I'm everybody's daddy!
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
What do you mean?
Don't try to turn
this around on me.
You lied to me.
You looked like the plague.
Why did you say
you were a printer?
I always wanted
to be a printer.
Talk to me.
For 20 years,
I go out with people, right?
I tell them I'm a cop.
You know what happens?
I'm a nonperson.
What do you think
I put the ad in the paper for?
Look, you ever keep something
inside yourself?
But you know you'll let it out.
I just wanted to get
on solid ground with you.
I wanted us to know each other
before I told you.
That's all I wanted.
I wanted to bring it along slowly.
So you're a cop, huh?
I'm Frank. Okay?
I'm just Frank.
Don't lie to me again.
I don't like it.
Look at these.
They're so soft.
They feel like feet.
They're very subtle.
Wild, right?
This girl, you know...
My girl give them to me.
Got to wear them, right?
Pretty jazzy.
You know,
look at these things.
She works in a shoe store.
You never did get her prints.
She's not the shooter.
This we know... How?
I asked her.
Golden Cadillac.
Screaming golden Cadillac.
What makes it scream?
Getting attacked
by a white Russian.
That's very clever.
Make that two.
Want yours screaming, too?
You have very tight skin.
You know that?
That's 'cause I'm fat.
It pushes it out
like balloon rubber.
Did you get that order?
See you.
I've seen
eight women tonight.
I bet every one made
more money than me.
That blonde...
she was a school principal.
How come none of
these women are married?
How come I'm not married?
Gentlemen, anyone up for
the Island of Lost Souls?
No, not me tonight, kids.
What's the matter, Frank?
I don't know. I'm tired.
You tired?
I'm going to walk home.
Talk to you tomorrow, kids.
All right, Frank.
Hey, how you doing?
Did I wake you? Oh.
Listen, uh...
is your daughter asleep?
You think you can
get somebody to watch her?
Good.
Uh...
what do you got on?
Yeah.
No, no, take them off.
Oh!
I was just, uh...
Sea of Love.
What?
You have Sea of Love.
I haven't looked
in those boxes in years.
Why, do you
like that record?
Yeah, I like it.
I'm saving them
for my daughter.
Probably worth
a fortune by now.
They'd fall apart
on the turntable.
You never play them, huh?
I don't even know
what's in there anymore.
You want
something to drink?
Yeah. Yeah.
A lot of people
keep records, huh?
I should have kept mine.
I had thousands
and thousands of them.
They'd be
worth something now.
You better go home...
before it gets light out.
Okay. All right.
I want you to see something.
Oh, beautiful.
How would you know?
You didn't even
look at her.
What do you mean?
I didn't want to wake her.
I wonder what kind of father
you would make.
Me?
I don't know.
You know, who the hell
wants a policeman for a father?
She's got a father,
doesn't she?
She does have a father.
You know what I mean?
Go home.
He's not dead.
You're divorced, right?
Oh, yeah.
You mad at me?
No.
Okay.
Oh, shit! Fuck.
Is your mother back?
Could you stay
with me tonight?
Good. I've got something
important to discuss.
Okay? I'm taking you somewhere,
so dress nice.
Waiter!
Can I call you back?
All right.
Okay. Take care.
How are you doing?
Something from the bar?
I know you.
You're that cop.
You're a police officer?
Did you get fired?
This is Gina.
What do you want?
Shh! Shh! Shh!
Just sit down. It's okay.
This is Gina Gallagher.
- Hi, Gina.
- This is Detective Sherman Touhey.
She's good people.
Hi.
I'm gone.
I feel like Betty Fucking
Crocker in this.
Jesus, it's only 8:00,
and I'm hammered.
I'm staying here tonight.
If I leave,
I'll die like a dog.
It would make
a nice headline.
I'll call the wife...
tell her I'll crash
around here.
Go to the squad room.
There's this nice cozy
army cot there.
I got extra keys.
I'm two blocks away.
We're sleeping together?
I'm going to see
this Helen later.
I got this hotel suite.
An ex-partner is head of security,
so he owes me.
It'll be a nice surprise.
You see this guy
This guy's in love with you
I'm asking her
to move in with me.
You just met her.
I feel like
a fucking teenager.
The guy says to me,
"Frank, retire".
I said, "To what?"
There's nothing
out there after this.
Could you get
the waiter, please?
Is there a waiter
in this place?
So, what's this
important thing...
you wanted to ask me?
What? Oh.
Maybe you should
slow it down, huh?
Maybe the menu should come
sometime this century.
What's the big question
you wanted to ask?
I don't know.
Waiter. Waiter.
I feel like I got
the London Philharmonic up my ass.
Let's go. Come on.
We just got here.
I know. Let's get out of here.
Bad choice.
Okay.
Not my favorite place.
I love this neighborhood.
I figure the worst
that could happen...
is I'd trip over
a Perrier bottle.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Could get worse, you know.
Nicely nice,
this neighborhood, huh?
Hold it.
Last year alone...
we had three murders
right in this block.
See that garage?
One in there.
That building? Second floor.
Two months later, third floor.
One in there.
This town's one big
city of the dead for you, huh?
City of the dead?
What do you say that for?
I love life.
I'm just trying to...
share with them.
When you live
with a cop...
tell you this.
There are certain things,
you know, a cop's eyes.
What we see.
There's you, what you see...
which is like nothing, and...
our eyes, our life,
what we see.
"If you live with a cop."
What?
You said if you live
with a cop.
You mean if I live
with a cop. Me.
Have you thought about this?
I have a kid.
It's a whole family.
You get that, right?
I want to ask you something.
The singles magazine.
I don't know, you know?
I mean the dates.
How can you do that shit?
I mean, you know...
go out with guys like that.
How can you do that?
You do it. Did you forget
how we met, Frank?
What's that mean?
I was on a job.
I was wearing a wire.
We were going
to drop somebody.
I'd never do that for real.
The part about the wire.
You want to
run that by me again?
Let me just tell you...
Fuck you!
Wait a minute, now.
I was just... Listen.
I was just saying that...
Here's the pitch.
The ball's hit
to center field!
What're you having, Frank?
Double Dewars, Pete.
You got it.
Oh, I...
Is...
It's 1:00 in the morning.
I'm Frank.
I know who you are.
My mouth ain't working
so good tonight, so, uh...
all I can say...
right now is that...
the circumstances...
were the circumstances, and...
No, that's not good enough.
Okay.
Okay. The whole thing
is horseshit.
Know what I mean?
The wire, the job.
There was no wire, no job,
no nothing.
I was just... saying that...
to push you away from me.
Because I was going to ask you
to live with me.
And I got...
scared, you know?
I'm sorry.
You know...
you never even told me...
what your kid's name is.
Sarah.
I would like...
for the three of us...
you know...
to go somewhere...
movie or something.
Just... take it slow,
you know?
Helen...
I can't even sleep
in my own bed anymore...
unless you're in it.
I mean...
I need you
to lie down with me.
Otherwise, I'm just going to
walk the streets all night.
Oh, I'm so tired.
You got to come
lay down with me.
Helen...
I got these shoes here.
See?
Come back with me, please.
Let me go tell my mother.
Frank.
I didn't want
to wake her up.
I need some time
to think all this through.
I think I should
be alone tonight.
Okay.
Catch you later.
Sherman.
- Frankie?
- Yeah.
- Frank?
- I forgot you were here.
You scared the shit out of me.
I'll stay on the couch.
Weren't you going
to a hotel?
It didn't work out.
What's he doing here?
Is this his place?
L... Look, I'll go to
the station house.
No. I got to talk to you.
Frank, I never did
nothing like this before.
That's okay.
No, listen. I got
to talk to you about this.
None of this was my idea.
Gina starts rubbing
my leg under the table.
You threw the keys.
I told you not to.
Want to go get her?
Want me to get her?
I'm sorry, Sherman. L...
I'm sorry.
- Thanks, Frank.
- Take care.
"Catch you later"? Huh?
What's that supposed to mean?
Is that some kind
of brush-off, Frank?
No, not at all.
No.
I got something for you.
Oh, yeah?
What?
Mmm mmm
You were looking at this
like it rang some bells.
Mmm mmm
Bum bum bum bum
Bum-bum bum-bum
Bum-bum
- Please?
- Come with me
Want to dance?
- Okay.
- To the sea
The sea oflove
Got something for me?
I want to tell you
You got something special
for me tonight, huh?
Uh-huh. Real special.
What do you got, Mommy?
Got something special
for me, Mommy?
Yeah, special.
What are you
going to give me?
Find it.
Where's it at?
Here? Hmm?
Cut it out!
I want to tell you
Let's see what's here.
What?
Let's see.
Oh, what's this?
What... You bring
the fake one, huh?
You forgot the real one?
Want to try mine?
Y-You're crazy.
Come on.
Let's get it over with.
I don't want to wait.
Do it now. Bingo.
Put it away, please.
Want to fuck first?
Get me face down?
Put the gun away, okay?
What kind of creep am I?
The guy who fucks you once...
and wants
to own you, right?
What aboutJames Mackey?
What kind of creep was he?
That poor bastard in Queens?
What's his name?
Raymond Brown.
You fucked him good.
You've been
following me around?
Last chance.
How long you
been following me?
I haven't been following you.
How do you know
about them?
It's my job.
It's what I'm paid for.
I didn't sleep with those guys.
They were just dates.
Shut up!
I slept with Mackey!
Big deal! He didn't...
I don't care!
Why'd you do it, Helen?
Tell me why you did it.
Tell me you did it.
I want to know everything,
all right?
Come on. Talk to me.
Look. I'm wearing your shoes.
Talk to me. Come on.
Talk to me.
Look.
The arresting officer
was fucking the doer!
See? It's a joke.
It won't go to trial even.
You understand?
Talk to me. Come on.
Come on!
Helen. Please.
Talk to me.
Get out.
Come on.
Go ahead. Okay?
- Helen?
- Aah!
I know you!
You fucking swinging dick!
You got in deep, man!
She throws a fucking
court order at me!
It's not your family!
It's not your daughter!
Oh! God!
Don't! Don't!
Don't!
Go!
On the bed!
Get down on the bed, man.
Get down.
Did you have a good time
with her last night?
Who do you mean?
Who? Who?
You a fucking owl?
I don't know who
you're talking about.
I'm talking about my wife.
My wife Helen.
You remember her,
don't you, huh?
I don't know. Look...
- I'm a New York City...
- I know who you are.
Show me how you
did it to her!
- I didn't.
- Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
You show me,
and I'll let you go.
I didn't do anything.
Show me what you did to her!
- Show me!
- We didn't do anything.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
This? You mean this?
- Okay?
- Fucking bastard!
Get... Get your clothes off!
Get your clothes off!
Take your fucking... Aah!
- Aah!
- Don't fucking move!
Put it down!
On the floor!
Hands behind the head! Move!
Get them on there!
Don't ever fucking move!
- Okay. Okay.
- What are you going to do...
Lock me up and
throw away the key?
Shut the fuck up!
It ain't going to work!
It's not your wife!
It... It's not your family!
What are you doing?
Aah!
No!
I hadn't seen him
in about a year.
I thought
he was gone for good.
Oh, yeah. That's it.
That's the stuff.
This is on the house.
You don't want to get up.
Come here.
How you doing, sport?
Good to see you.
I'm doing better than you.
What are you drinking, scotch?
No. A club soda and lime.
Club soda and lime.
Club soda and lime?
What a cheap date.
Oh, it's the new me.
Here's to the new you
and the old me.
Mmm.
Rub it in, rub it in.
How you doing, Frank?
Hanging in, hanging out.
- I'm with the 1-9 now.
- Yeah?
You?
Same old. That was
a hard job to top.
I hear that.
Wildest ride I was ever on.
You know, I, uh,
followed up that nutbag.
The husband Terry?
Turns out he'd been
shadowing her for eight months.
Can you believe it?
Jesus.
Man.
She always had
that edge, you know?
Like she smelled him,
sensed him, or something.
I must have sensed him, too.
Wonder what she saw in him.
I don't know.
What does anybody
see in anybody?
People are work, brother.
A lot of work.
Too much work.
Ever see her again?
Well, I tried, but...
she didn't want to.
Can you blame her?
I'm in bed with her,
making love...
I'm out of bed,
I'm stalking her, like...
She had that nutcase over one
shoulder, me over the other.
Come on.
Can you blame her?
Yeah, right.
I'm going to let her go.
I ran her through
a wringer, man.
You know?
Hey, what am I
supposed to do?
She'd tear my head off.
What are you looking at?
- How you doing?
- Just great.
Good. How's, uh...
How's your daughter?
She's fine.
Oh, good, good.
I'm working out
of the 1-9 now.
That's this area here.
We had a series of break-ins
around here.
You've been okay? Your shop's
wired to the precinct?
Yep.
Yeah. Well, uh, listen,
the reason I come by is I, uh...
I wanted you
to meet somebody.
Oh? Who, Frank?
Well, actually, I'd very much like
to introduce myself to you.
Yeah? Who are you this week,
a fighter pilot?
Fighter pilot? No.
No more surprises.
No more... lies.
I'm... I'm all here.
Right. The circumstances are
no longer the circumstances, huh?
I hung fire to be with you
through that.
There's a lot I don't know.
You got to give me
a chance.
You never really got
to know me. Not 100%.
The person you
got involved with...
that was half of me.
You owe it to yourself.
Check out the complete person.
Cut the crap, okay?
I had a rough day.
What'll I do, follow you
all over the city?
How do I get
over with you now?
Get over with me?
After what you did...
you're looking
to get over with me?
It couldn't be helped.
I couldn't help that.
It's killing me
not seeing you.
It's killing me.
How do you think
it makes me feel?
I don't know.
How do you...
How's it make you feel?
It doesn't make any difference.
I'm moving back home anyway.
Back to York?
That's fantastic.
Because just this morning...
I got offered a job in York,
Pennsylvania. Police department.
They want me to head
this huge, uh...
Break up this huge
counterfeit produce ring.
Hey, listen!
This is fantastic, you know?
- Look. Look, tell you what.
- What?
I'll take the job now.
All right?
You could help me out there.
Do you know
any nice apartments...
houses, stuff
that I could, uh...
Okay, enough, Frank.
Enough.
No, really!
When are you going?
You're not going?
You're staying here, right?
I've been on the wagon...
for seven weeks now.
You still drink coffee?
Oh! Like it's going out of style.
I'll buy you a cup,
if you like.
Come with me
To the sea
Oh, yeah
Oh, do you remember
the night we met
Ooh, that's the night
I just knew you were my pet
I wanna tell you
how much I love you
Oh, I'm down here
on the sea of love
Oh, come with me
To the sea
Oh, yeah
Oh, do you remember
the night we met
Ooh, that was when
I just knew
you were my pet
I wanna tell you
how much I love you
Down on the sea of love
Come with me
To the sea
Oh, yeah
Do you remember
the night we met
That's the night
I just knew you were my pet
I wanna tell you
how much I love you
Down there in
the sea of love
Oh, come with me
To the sea
Oh, yeah
Come with me
My love
To the sea
The sea of love
I wanna tell you
how much I love you
I'm down here
in the sea of love
Oh, come with me
To the sea
Oh, yeah
Do you remember
the night we met
That's the night
I just knew
you were my pet
I wanna tell you
how much I love you
Oh, I'm down in
the sea of love
Oh, come with me
To the sea
Oh, yeah
Do you remember
the night we met
That's the night
I just knew you were my pet
I wanna tell you
how much I love you