MOTHER  Strip
PISTOLS WITH LARGE
Forgive me.
Well.
Which of you nuns
violated my first commandment?
Do not steal from Chavo.
No.
Chavo stole from you?
Tell me, mother.
I will not hurt.
Yes or no?
No.
Now, you!
Chavo stole from you?
No? I lie?
- I lie Chavo?
- No.
Where are you going?
Come here.
Take it.
It's your problem.
Thank you.
Let's go.
TATE gleamy
From Father Bernardo.
Nice.
Come on. Choose the one you want.
It's on the house.
Want something special?
Very good.
I go and prepare it for you.
Faster. I have one
triple that paid for her ass.
- No need to tell you the second time.
- I tell you one last time.
Not anymore.
- Use another girl.
- No, no, no.
They need to know it's a real nun.
There are no dirty whore. Do not like it.
- I can not help.
- Damn quacks.
You pay a fortune to do so.
So do it.
It can do many things
but were not criminal.
Well.
One could do it.
Get older.
Father Bernardo Damn.
God bless him.
You think that's funny?
Come, laugh with me.
Damn!
Another one.
You paid for a nun.
There ...
spoil ...
merchandise.
Vraciu!
Get your ass here.
Get rid of them. Now.
I was told that God came to me.
He said: you have a greater purpose in life.
God spoke to you.
It's just a side effect
the crap you've put them in the flesh.
- What did God say.
- He told me to kill.
- Who to kill?
- To all those who sin against him.
God told you to walk
and kill people?
Shit.
I think you bad dreams.
Because ... I gave you good stuff.
He wants to go.
To purify my mind
only with his words.
Only then will be ready
to revenge him.
Forget it.
For you.
If you do God's work,
you'll need these tools.
Take care, are loaded.
What you said God?
He said he will tell me.
To see if the merit
Let us continue the mission.
- What kind of test?
- You should not show mercy.
No one who is merciful to me.
sister Sarah.
A year later .
Fr.
Each?
Church of Carlitos.
Take care of my drugs.
- Thank you, Father.
- Bon voyage, my son.
Goodbye, Carlitos.
Lord with you.
Sister Angelina .
Carlitos!
Carlitos  Fr.
Do you have a customer here.
Carlitos?
May God, who has turned on every heart
to teach you your sins
and trust in his mercy.
Bless me, Father, I have sinned.
It's been a day since the last confession.
Too bad it bothers you so much
the need to come back after a day?
We work as usual at our monastery.
Valambrosa massacre.
A day earlier.
The sisters cooked the drug.
Motorcyclists and the priest talked of money.
I did not know that death will be felt
presence in the house of God.
Foreign killed the priest?
Be patient, parent,
arrive at the best.
Stranger entered and whispered
priest's ear.
You should have put the fear of God in him,
because all he could say was,
Carlitos.
And that was what he wanted to hear foreign.
Foreign priest pushed him into his seat
came back and left.
But he had a say.
He made one of his guns.
- The priest has killed foreign?
- No.
Foreign killed the priest?
What happened with the priest?
Four gunshots.
The leading ...
chest ...
shoulder ...
shoulder.
Sign of the Cross.
What happened to foreign?
It came as a demon
and disappeared like an angel.
Nonsense. You have no proof.
How do I know it's true?
Who the hell are you?
Who sent you? Talk to me!
Who the hell ...
A fucking liar yelper.
Can be shot in the chapel
to let in some strange, yes?
Why do I pay you protection
every month if you can not see anything?
Do not worry.
Are you still alive, right?
Do not tell me that. Got bitch
to me, for God's sake.
- How do I know I'm not next on the list?
- I said that we handle.
Hello? Hello?
Shit! It's a bloody vigilante
which brings down the priests
and all I can say is that will happen?
How will he do?
How were held by Father Bernardo?
What happened to the world if a man
frock can not do God's work?
Great pity.
Bernardo makes good money.
Lord to have mercy on his soul.
Workshop  Chavez.
Located on the outskirts .
- Hello. How are you?
- There's something wrong. You can check, please?
- What cave!
- Penny, be careful how you speak.
- But it is.
- Come here.
What?
- This is for attitude, young lady.
- Dad!
Can I put your fingers through the radiator.
It's rusty.
Dude, let's take this tea bag.
I will miss him.
Just get people to be killed.
Just kidding, anyway.
I'm going to see what guys do.
You do that.
I miss friends.
I could be on the beach, the ocean ...
- Look at all you ...
- Dude!
What?
Come to see something.
- Do not look at them.
- Where's Dad?
- Ladies!
- Get your hands off her!
Stanley!
- What happened?
- I was joking with my buddy.
Your buddy?
Why are you crying?
It's okay. Come.
Come, come.
- We do not want problems.
- Problems? We show the problem?
- Surely you are a good bunch of guys.
- Yes, yes. We are very good boys.
But ... we have a problem
when people come to us
are not respectful.
I am respectful.
I look a slut?
- No!
- I did bitch, right?
Trying to pay me money
for hookers?
Want to see a slut?
Here it is.
Show and bitch.
Kick Stand
Los Muerte band.
You tool ... with courage.
Be a man.
Go ahead and save it for the bad guys.
I'll stop. I promise.
Come on, you do it. Go!
Be a man.
Go! Save it!
Hello.
Sorry about your father.
I think it will have to be your daddy.
You're cute.
- Chavo on the phone.
- Who?
- It's him.
- Damn! What does he want?
He wants to talk to you.
- How it sounds?
- Quite seriously.
I'll be back for you, Mom.
Chavez's workshop.
You're welcome, we do not care.
Father Bernardo is dead.
As Lobo and Chinaco.
It was a fucking massacre.
Have not taken anything. No money, no drugs.
It was something strictly personal.
Fucking.
Collect and manage your people.
Boss, we have a surprise for you.
It's not cute? I checked it.
Is not Kick Stand?
Sure.
- Do you want to thicken the icing?
- Yes.
But I can not.
We work.
Boys ... We are in the middle
a holy war.
In fact, my mother always said:
"If you want a sweet peach,
will have to wait to fall from the tree. "
So sweet and juicy.
Look.
Dad said:
"Acre or sweet, we need to chew."
Just saying.
Chavo? What are you doing?
Speak of the mother and you live
fucking with your father?
I said nothing.
If we talk of mother
gonna fly eggs.
- Chavo!
- Let's not talk about my mother.
If more than one mother says,
be prepared
to lose a few inches.
- Rigo!
- Yes.
- You like that?
You want me to give you?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Give it to him.
Not now. Leave me alone.
Shit!
Hello, Chavo.
You do a great job
taking care of my place.
That's a lot of money I make.
Listen.
It's a vigilante on the streets.
It kills bad guys.
In case you forgot, we are the bad guys.
Well.
I want to know when anyone enters the door.
It has been understood?
Go! Go!
Okay, okay. I deal with it.
My hat.
We witnessed how you satisfaceati
each other into the house.
Such blasphemy will not be tolerated
in my church.
- Fr Carlitos there. It's scary.
- Okay.
Why not call the police
and let's leave them to handle?
Jews have called for help.
When Moses came down from the mountain,
did not ask who is on their side.
They responded by taking weapons
the name of the Lord
killing those hostile to God.
Not spared anyone.
Are you ready for this?
Ready to go
bloody hands
to shoot and kill more priests?
I was not prepared for it.
You know what we have done?
Will continue to do so all that new.
Should be punished, Angelina.
be punished on behalf of believers.
Look at me.
How can the Lord,
when I can not master their own hands?
I think not only to go back
the monastery, in my dirty cell,
Where can I put needles in your arm
so I can forget.
Mother Magda told me to die.
Be patient.
I went through this.
When I was in his hands
Lord spoke to me.
He gave me this assignment.
At first, I was not prepared for it.
I had to prepare.
- What did God say?
- They were words.
It was intense excitement of being alive
one that spoke to me.
How do you get rid of them?
God sent an angel to me
guide and defend me.
- As you protect me me now?
- Yes.
Now that we found each other,
We will be back a whole.
It's not easy to become a nun.
It's a life you flee
the outside world,
life is sacrifice.
When times become unbearable,
trust, knowing that
sacrifice that we make
is the name of our Lord
Jesus Christ.
When you pass through those doors,
you will be born again.
You come with nothing and you will be absolved
sins without question.
Do not ask and do not talk
about our past life.
To make a closer union
the crucifixion,
You will be ...
subject to the exercises and tasks
and humility.
If you doubt this process,
if you're not part of us.
Mother Magda .
To be covered in all to death
the love of God.
You'll be perfect nun.
I want to dwell?
No.
I am willing to listen to the story.
- I'm on it.
- Could be the killer of priests.
The Bible is the only protection
I need.
God has shone all souls
taught you not to sin
and trust in his mercy.
Forgive me, Lord,
for they're about to sin.
No God
are the only tool that works through to me.
Tell me what's so hard on my heart
The confession must come to you
at this time?
I'm not here to confess my sins.
I'm here to do.
You must have courage to live in my house.
You know who you chicken?
How much money passes through this church?
To kill some priests
will not change anything.
- No idea who you fuck.
- Tell me who work
and you will not suffer
brethren who have suffered.
I work for God.
He is my pastor.
Motel "No way"
Butch's.
Located in the famed city.
Make yourself comfortable.
Damn.
Is always the same.
Damn. Passing.
There is nothing sacred?
No dressing. It's okay
It only takes a minute.
- We need a room.
- The hour or all night?
- All night.
- $ 30, cash.
Camera lucky seven.
Halfbreed.
These guys, they're yours.
- Okay?
- Yes.
How to count money all,
including yours?
What's your problem?
You want to count my money?
- I'd like to see them.
- Count them.
- No, that's fine. It's good.
Rigo.
Go to work, man.
- Chavo's workshop. Are Rigo.
- Give it to Chavo. Now!
Well.
- Carlitos, who?
- Bastards killed him in his church.
- I should have prayed harder.
- You need to put an end to this, right now.
Well.
If you want to finish the bastard,
will usually cost you double that.
- I have so much money.
- Father, do not play with me.
We've already lost two people
in your holy war.
In fact, I know that Jesus has deep pockets
for such nonsense.
If you pay double, I do everything
in half the usual time.
Meet with Mother Magda
Carlitos his church. You wait.
Carlitos ...
It sounds good.
On here.
You guys stay here and make sure
that we are unwelcome guests.
- What do you think?
- I'm dead.
Can you stop?
Let's make them pay.
There are too forgiving, Magda.
Returns cheek, love your enemy ...
All the crap they teach.
Listen, I was summoned to the monastery
to fix this.
And I expect to resolve
as soon as possible.
I heard the first, right?
I know you want to solve quickly.
You want a miracle.
That's your job.
But as shown,
Your job does not work very well.
Now. There are witnesses?
Sister Mary was first told us
this situation.
- Then get it here.
- Do not use anything.
Sister Mary is here for 20 years.
I kept it here just because he knew
to keep his big mouth closed.
We'll see. Bring it.
Who did this?
Who killed him?
Well.
I ask you once beautiful.
If you do not want to talk, one to bring him
the Kick Stand, to take over the interrogation.
Who killed him?
Well.
Your choice.
I'll be back.
Mary, tell me now what you saw.
Mary what you saw?
It's okay. Well, I can say
I will not tell anyone.
Between us.
Mary will be back for you
and I can not stop.
What did you see?
Kick Stand, move over.
Now!
Who killed him, Mary?
You know who it was, eh?
I've seen, is not it?
Looks?
Kick Stand, get to work.
I'll crucify
as Jesus was crucified on the cross.
Kick Stand, enough.
It was a nun.
- It was God's hands.
- A nun?
It seems to be one of your penguins, Magda.
- What kind of weapon to have?
- One high.
I looked into her eyes
and saw the devil in them.
- What to do now, boss?
- First, gather the troops and then ...
we go hunting for nuns.
Halfbreed not fooling around and come here.
We seek a nun.
A nun with a big weapon.
I mean, big boobs big as a weapon?
I said weapons.
I'm surrounded by idiots.
Pull yourself together, or you'll end up here
in a pine coffin.
Spread the rumor on the streets.
Fix that. Go and check it out.
What about her?
E nun.
Yes it is.
Are you a murderer?
No, no, no. Not that.
I think he can not even take
a weapon, but to fire her.
Let's go.
We'll be back later after you.
S back errant daughter.
When you've found the body in Valambrosa
I thought it would not do us any trouble.
And now that you sit in front of me
I know I was right.
Your only power is in your hands.
I know you did not last a week out.
Looking for someone?
Take a good look at him.
God punishes those
Why I serve Satan.
Let me go.
- A delivery from Magda.
- What should I do with it?
I hate the religious crap.
Magda told her to give Chavo's
and when it ends with a throw away.
- Put it there.
- Okay.
Beautiful view.
- Hi, Chavo.
- Hello, love.
Tell him to bring me Beverly
some beer, please.
Come with me.
Exactly how I remember you.
- Dance for me, MAMAC?
- Of course.
Come on, come here.
Thanks, Beverly.
Listen, if you see a crazy chick like this
shoot first and then ask her who she is
These are his orders and Chavo.
- Halfbreed, want a beer?
- What the hell do you think? Yes.
I think God is trying to tell me something.
Wherever I go, I see the nuns.
What the hell you said earlier?
The girl in the picture. I saw the cazându
at the Palms Hotel, last evening.
It looked dirty.
I do not know, I think he has a drinking problem.
You saw this nun
cazându himself in a hotel 2 money last night?
I was with Butch.
Ask her, will tell you the same thing.
If you're wrong Beverly,
then God help you.
- What? I'm busy.
- I want to wake up and be careful.
Yes, now you have my attention.
What the hell is so important
The morning I wake up in the middle?
It's four in the afternoon, you stupid cow.
- He stayed a nun, last night?
- No.
Beverly, I'll rip your ass
when you close the phone.
Leave it the hell alone, Jesus.
It was checked last night.
We stayed at 3 o'clock one morning.
Butch, it's time to play with me.
Room number seven.
Even I checked it.
That mutt not let go.
We are on the road.
We have some irresponsible heterosexual .
We  lesbianism, homosexuality
trans sexual
much sexuality. All sexuality.
All are sins.
We lesbians ...
She's dead?
No, but Beverly has seen the nun
cazându to the motel last night.
I want to see this heroine.
Kick Stand, go there.
Add it to me ... alive.
Go.
If not let me go now
will have to kill you.
If you have not noticed,
I'm the one with the gun.
You do not have to go through this.
I know that God forgives sins.
- You just have to ask forgiveness.
- What do you know about sin?
You really are a true nun
or any Swindler dressed like that?
I took communion
at my church, in God's name.
You think you're so strong.
Who are you to preach?
What do you know half of sins
they condemn?
- I am a sinner.
- What are your sins, sister?
- Sin with the body.
- Big deal.
Half of you are ridden
priests.
It may be true.
My sins are not of the flesh.
But the same kind of sex.
Get back on the bed, cur.
We sin today.
And tomorrow we ask forgiveness.
That's the beauty of faith.
- Who the hell are you?
- You thought, you thought, you thought wrong.
- You said you can be forgiven.
- Want to be forgiven? Ask for forgiveness.
Please ... please.
Please ...
You graduate.
You ... graduate.
of all sins.
But there is forgiveness
for the limits of hell.
Where the hell have you been all day?
At Tate fâlfâitoare?
There is no girl there.
I say it e.
It is dressed in nun
and makes you give your pants off.
Have you seen a nun
the Tate fâlfâitoare?
- How did you stay there, you idiot?
- Pope told to stay there.
Get out of my face fucking.
- What now?
- Butch is dead.
A nun who has worked very well.
Chavo will be angry.
Sorry, boss. But I have bad news.
Butch is dead.
- It was all messed up there, man.
- Mutt that's crazy.
Prospect says she's a nun
the Tate fâlfâitoare "right now.
Come on.
- Dance Fâlfâitoare.
- Hey, man, are Halfbreed.
- I bet that you're looking for the nun.
- Tell the Pope that Chavo is on its way.
Yes, I have to wash my mutt that.
- What is it?
- Chavo is on its way.
Get a mutt that and clean
before it can get it here.
What happens Halfbreed?
Not now, cur.
Wake up!
And get dressed.
heart will not let me wait.
I pray God to save me
and meet us.
If not in this world
in heaven above.
Get your stinking hands off me.
Where's Angelina?
E Tate fâlfâitoare "
with some old friends of yours.
I had to put things right.
Kick Stand, tell him Pope
bring to a nun.
Hi again, ucigaso.
I know that you are not mantis
they seek.
You should do something.
- Pope leaves us less alone.
- I'll be down.
I'll also give.
Nun.
Put the gun down, softly.
Who the hell are you?
Fucking mutt!
No, no, no, calm down.
Yes, yes.
Do not touch anything. It's okay.
Come, go.
Are you okay?
- I will.
- No, no, no ...
No, no.
No! No, no, no.
Everybody?
No. I'll handle it myself.
Father ...
are prepared to do this task
in God's name?