"How Lionel gave me sex"
by Henry McCanthy read by David.
"I must say thanks to all
at West Rockville High School. "
"Without the experience I would not
being a writer. "
"Few are paid to write about it,
they wish had happened. "
"Yes. Cheerleader Girls,
sports guys, the nerds "-
- "Gays who would soon come
out of the closet, and teachers "-
- "Has been
to shape me. "
"One day I will return
to thank everyone personally. "
"And of course, Lionel,
which showed me how to do. "
We come too late. So late
you need to count your toes with.
After 20 years
Henry should be retrieved at the gate.
Listen, wino. When Henry asks us
about his book, we're at it.
"A fictional story about a teenager
way through the difficult time at school. "
Sounds like facts.
"Chapter one. " Say You, Say Me '
Pine, your name is high school. "
"The first day of school
I felt alone. "
"I was a nerd,
the invisible "-
- "Until I met
Bryan and Wayne. "
"We figured out that scum
was safer in a group. "
"Crowd gave reassurance. "
Good to see you.
How do I sign? You look great.
- What a hairdo...
Your luggage?
- Are gone. Let's just run.
Imagine...
- Is this your car?
There's the wino!
- Yes!
Hello.
"Hours of bored me.
Nobody knew who I was "-
- "Other than my two friends
and football guy who threatened me. "
I told you.
It is dangerous in traffic.
Now here we are almost there.
Gay, dear gay.
Thanks, guys.
- Remember balloons.
One for Henry, me and wino.
What time tomorrow?
Six o'clock.
- Av it!
Zombie Early. See you.
- Welcome home Henry. See you!
My little treasure has come home.
- Hi, Mom.
"Hi, mom... "
How are you?
- Fine.
Do not have laundry?
- Yes, but the baggage smoke to Tokyo.
I'm sorry.
Then we shop!
How's the father?
"I was a stranger
in a foreign country. "
"Mom treated me like a child
and dad was obsessed with his hobby. "
Hi, Dad. Nice to see you.
- Hello.
What do you want to eat?
I'm not hungry. I must
up early to write the speech.
Pancakes or waffles in the morning?
- Waffles.
"After graduation I took the toothbrush
and a pair of shoes and fled. "
"But I left
a big question. "
"I knew
that one day I might find the answer. "
JAVIER
Hello.
- How are you?
I'm in the room.
Wait until the connection is poor.
I have read about your broken heart
and know the place brings back memories.
I'm your agent.
Call, I'll come.
Yes, I understand, Javier.
Vitale know. Hello.
In listening to John John,
KRAC 88.1, station...
"Girls were mysteries. How
I had to smell and talk to them? "
"And the clothes? Varde to boxer shorts
or tight underpants? "
"I spent too tight. My Testicles
was not as developed as others. "
"Then I discovered Lionel. He was
chewy and knew things about women. "
"Lionel said, 'You mean more
than words can express? "
"And:"... you are the rain,
makes me foolhardy '"
"He was my crash course
from having sex. "
Good morning.
Sexy is fashionable again.
KRAC 88.1.
We have had visits -
- Of our local success writer
Henry McCanthy.
Let's talk about the book
"How Lionel gave me sex. "
It is a serious insight
in miserable teenage love.
Cheerleader Girl...
She was a real heartbreaker?
I mention no names.
- Has she read the book?
It would surprise me.
Thanks, Henry.
We're back after jingle.
As you know, I called John John.
I will have T-bones teak and eggs.
Through Fried.
It was all... And pancakes
with strawberries without cream.
Only a little whipped cream.
Anything else?
- No, that was all.
I do not eat it all.
Is Mike Miller?
He recognized us.
He recognized you.
He has worked in this two years.
Stephanie works in the bank
and Josh in the dry cleaner.
On Main Street?
The entire class of 1988 are scattered
all over Rockville.
If you see someone in a store
avoiding the one -
as if one divides
a dark secret with them.
Looking not each other, need
not ashamed of her life.
It is embarrassing and self-destructive.
Big Girl would not help it.
How about Scarlet Smith?
What? Come on.
Oh no. No, no, no.
I'm just asking.
- Your pathetic wretch.
You must not.
Forget it.
- Yes, and you should too.
Forget it. Henry?
- Forget that I asked.
Our school. What happened?
- It's gone!
They tore it down to avoid being
reminded of all the destroyed lives.
Let's go inside.
- I do not go there. Nope.
Teenagers are being tortured there.
I never go there.
Wish me luck.
See you in 45 minutes.
45?
- Yes.
Pull your pants up
Now is the min.
What is it?
- Guess.
Come on.
It is a pen.
Silence!
and keep the queue moving.
Henry!
- Rector. Thanks for your invitation.
When I heard that an old student
had been successful author-
examination was elected speaker,
but I have not read the books.
You show
what a girl or a boy can achieve...
...When they have taken their exams.
- Thanks.
You are a true winner.
Students will hear a winning speech.
Yes, they have to.
- Using final premises...
...Such as library
canteen or sports premises.
What makes you feel
exam mood.
Okay.
Should I follow some guidelines?
No profanity. We will not offend
someone, so avoid "hell", "penis"...
We will, as said
not offend anyone.
No, we will not.
I forgot something.
Here are some examples of speeches
some of my favorite speeches.
Look at them. Think of the Gettysburg speech,
Martin Luther, "let us agree" -
or Bette Midler
"Wind Beneath My Wings".
What you believe will strengthen
and spicing up the students.
Give them confidence
and willingness to read on.
Naturally.
Departure Students arrange it all.
Talk to them when you have spoken
with me, which is now... Local 502nd
I know
that I have much to do -
- But this is important
for school leavers.
Oh no... Mrs. Looch...
- What do you want?
Rector has sent me.
- Sit down. We'll talk after class.
Everyone must be involved
and spend some more time.
Your family knows that it is important
For example, to lead the group
dealing imprint tion
of the yearbook, and...
Shasta!
Listen.
I will review your case
before translocation.
Why?
- So we know that it is good enough.
And if it does not it?
- That we do not think so now.
Well not...
We have experienced much, sweetheart.
Who's your daddy?
Exactly.
Why is it called a bra? It looks like
a g-string. How did it go?
Do not ask. Many memories came back
although they have torn the building down.
I told you. You got away last.
It makes you maybe not this time.
I'm just trying
to process my memories.
The place spoil people's lives!
I know.
- Big Girl believes what she says!
Can you see the kimono?
It is right. Listen to the kimono.
You need to manipulate...
What does it really mean?
Give me your feelings on toast,
I'll work on them.
I told you. Memories...
Want something to drink?
- No thanks.
How was school?
- Well, you know...
I do not know
what might encourage the young.
Let me see...
I flip through my yearbook.
Well, the yearbook. Who helped?
- Yes...
Scarlet. "Thanks... "
"... Because you're so sweet. "
What?
"Ring in the summer.
Scarlet Smith. "
Scarlet Smith?
"I'm so in love that I do not know
what to do. "The Scarlet?
Are you ready?
Call her.
No. It is 19 summers ago.
Say that time ran from you.
Think.
Okay.
- Yes! Good boy. Really.
What is her phone number?
- She is gorgeous. It's here.
Are you ready? 869th..
Should I take it, mother?
I will not talk to Brad.
Is this all?
- Hello?
Yes...
Hello?
- But...
Why did you do it?
- I should not call her.
No, you must not call her.
- I'm calling you.
I'll call themselves.
- How should it be.
You were just a little tense.
- What's the number?
I'll take it.
It's over, its fun!
That's your problem!
Was I too hard?
Is... Scarlet on?
Who is it?
It is Henry McCanthy.
Who are you?
I've been
her best friend for 30 years. Darcy.
Henry McCanthy?
From school...
I was sifting
through the school yearbook -
and she had written: "You're cute.
Ring in the summer. "
She wrote it with an exclamation point,
screaming.
She can not remember you.
She... She can not remember it.
Just a moment.
If you look on page twelve and...
We must look for.
Find yearbook.
On page 132 is
a pretty good picture of me.
Great... Look here,
she has not right now.
She can not find it.
- She's not on the nightstand...
...Beside tandbøjlen
and enjørning-poster.
Would you say
Henry McCanthy called?
I hang up now.
Thank you for calling.
Okay. Hello.
Who is it?
- He is in love with you.
I am weak.
- Yes.
How bummer.
What did you do?
- We called Scarlet Smith.
That's right.
- I can not eat... Jo.
Yes.
Will not you forget it?
And you will not help him.
He has nothing to lose.
- Or win.
I just wanted to hear what she is doing.
- I guess it was mutual?
Forget it, forget it.
Forget it.
I'm proud.
- Self-destructive...
She saw me as a nerd.
What a force!
- It's the first thing I agree with:
"So," you as a nerd?
You're still a geek.
Forget it. Forget it.
You do not need that kind.
Are you with me? Your heart would
have increased by smoking crack.
She did not look at the picture to remember
why she can not remember me.
Great!
Now you are thinking positively.
I found your yearbook!
And those here, thanks.
Here it is.
Have you found him?
Was he nice?
We had chemistry.
Yes, we had chemistry hours together.
He was so sweet. Always helpful.
- He used that you were stupid.
Now I get a bad conscience.
- Why would you remember him?
He looks old-fashioned.
Like my father.
Would you call him?
- He seems enough, I am part.
So are you. What happens
if I take this one?
Anal Leakage.
Truant you already?
Shasta O'Neill
one of school leavers.
Shasta.
You came not to hours.
- I had not done her homework.
It is not good.
I thought that I could get
more about the students here.
As far as I can see -
the library is still a sanctuary
for the socially handicapped.
- Exercise...
- Down on the floor.
Ned.
- The outlets are closed.
Should we not go out by fire alarm?
- This is an emergency alarm.
There is perhaps one of Firearms
on school property.
Relax. Nobody has guns.
It's just an exercise.
Jaså?
How often do I practice on this?
A couple times a week.
- Well. Great.
Hello?
- Ringer I too late? This is Scarlet.
Yes, Scarlet.
- You called me.
Hello?
It's me, Dad.
- It's pretty late...
The one girl's father.
Hello. How are you?
- My life is a little turbulent right now.
I'm moving
and stuff.
It's nice to hear from you.
- I live temporarily with my mother.
So I must also tackle.
Henry McCanthy. How are you?
- Fine.
How are you?
"I saw her, Lauren Landers
and there was something weird. "
"We had attended the same school,
but now she was a woman. "
"From the moment
She was constantly in my thoughts. "
"One day Lauren bumped into me at
time. I felt the ten elbow. "
"Like a lightning strike. "
Tomorrow night
at half past eight?
Yes. That sounds good.
Perfect.
"She left and I stood back
like an idiot and muttered: "Laurer"
"'Is this how
love feels? "'
Hello?
- Wake up. It is Javier.
Just a moment.
The connection is bad. Wait.
I have some news.
Is everything okay, Henry?
A big film company will have
a little right for your book.
- It is certainly not small...
- They'll change the title of "Lionel".
- What do they want instead?
- Something modern as Linkin Park.
- Linkin Park? There is no sex.
- Women, 15-25 years, liked them.
Men of 15-35 years
warmest positive.
Hello? Henry?
Remember when I said that the title
"Late developed" was not good.
- Linkin Park do not give a sex.
- Oh yes. Well, we agree.
If you're sweet on Desirée -
she's sweet on you.
She likes...
...A firm hand sometimes.
- I drive only when you think.
- She should be out among people.
Damn...
I can just rent a car?
No, no. You must not do.
Oh no.
She gives me already a rash.
Let us see.
God.
Is this your parasitic twin?
- Ladies!
- I'm not a tourist attraction.
See.
Okay, ladies...
A cold compress, herbal tea,
light foundation and a donut.
- Doughnut?
- Yes, it is to me.
- What will you do about it?
- Not much.
We can attack, but the syvdageskrig
all to notice.
It's Scarlet-stress.
- What can I do?
- Relax. Do you like whale song?
Come with
cold compress!
"The last year I was luckily
next to Lauren in chemistry lessons. "
"But I asked only whether she would
need help to dissect the frog. "
- Henry?
- Hello, Scarlet.
- This seems odd, no?
- Oh no.
I just think all the time
Henry from school.
In a teenager.
I just need to get used to it.
- Is that so bad?
- No, no.
But the Henryvar...
But now you're a grown man
with a beard and a beer.
Yes, it's just happened...
But you have not changed you.
- Is it positive or negative?
- You are incredible sex.
It was embarrassing, no?
I'm pharmacies. It is depressing
supplying antidepressants.
You can also call me
a drug dealer in a small town.
- I'm not in my niche.
- It's none of us.
You must have accomplish something
when you need to keep talking.
- Well, I've written some books.
- Are you a writer?
Yes, if someone else read them.
You probably have many fans
who read them. I also want.
- Where can I find a book?
- I'll get to you.
No, I will buy it
for my own money.
- It is available in bookstores.
- Okay.
- It was nice to see you.
- It was also nice to see you.
- Bye.
What is the book?
"How Lionel gave me sex. "
Just a moment.
- Who is Lionel?
- Richie.
With "Dancing On The Ceiling"?
Lionel Richie gave him sex?
Maybe.
I have read about it.
The book is on shelf E. The books are
alphabetically by author.
Okay, what happened?
You smile as if he were delicious...
- ... Or you are embarrassed Daten.
- It was not a date.
I promise not to tease you.
He was fat and bald?
- No...
- Jeans?
Was he a divorced dad
with lots of children?
It must have been pretty good
when you bet on the relationship.
You buy his book. I would never
read unite husband's sake.
Here it is.
Bingo! Photo by the author...
- Let's see how he looks.
- Is it important?
Yes, that's it.
Will you destroy your genes?
I gambled on the appearance,
and now I live with my mom.
- Wait. Is it him?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
- He is actually quite delicious.
- I know.
What other geeks
was delicious after school hours?
You are so pretty with your blonde hair.
Oh, you're so pretty.
Why is not bold Scarlet
and five obese children?
Then the case would be settled.
Why is it not?
- Because the world peace depends on it.
- I pretend that I understand it.
Beautiful. It lasted good choice.
- Henry. Hello!
- Hi, Shasta. How are you?
Good morning, Mr. McCanthy.
May I see the speech?
I am still working on it.
- Is this a problem?
- Yes, I guess.
As I've said, we must
have enough time to read the speech.
If we have not read the speech,
you probably do not hold it.
- When we see something?
- As soon as I see something.
- Hello.
- Hello, Scarlet. What are you doing?
I just want to see
what you do.
I try
To get started with the speech.
Jaså. How are you?
It is not at all.
- How about a little distraction?
- I could well use.
- Meet me in front of the house.
- Okay.
I want to know who Lionel is.
Hello!
- You have school tomorrow...
- I come home late!
Cheers to Mrs. Looch,
still picks on me.
Why does Mrs. Leuchtenberg
called Mrs. Looch?
- Say the name.
- Lutchenberger.
Leuchtenberg.
As in Leuch-tenberger.
Luh... Leuchen...
- Do you understand now?
- Yes. Why you got me for that?
That's why
she called it.
- She still wish that I fail.
- Forget it.
Those who can, do.
The others turned to Mrs. Looch.
- Think you can run?
- Yes.
I do not want
a spritdom.
- The car has many lights.
- It's Brad.
- Your Brad?
- My ex Brad.
- Does he know that he is your "ex"?
- He hears only what he wants to hear.
- Can you run from him? Do it.
- Will he beat me?
Yes, if he will not chitchat
about the good old days at school.
Turn here.
If we got rid of him?
Stop there! Keep your hands where I
can see them. Stig quietly out of the car.
Put your hands on your head.
Stand with feet apart.
- You drove a bit fast, huh?
- Yes. Sorry.
Do you know how strong
one must drive near a school?
40 kmh.
- Have you been drinking? Are you sure?
- Yes.
A New York City, of course.
DRIVING
- What the hell... McCanthy!
- Bird!
Nice to meet you, Bird.
Can not you recognize me
under police equipment?
- I've lost me a bit.
- Very.
I had surgery,
and now it's over with pizzas.
I was about to shoot you.
It was close.
Who is it?
- Hello! Is not Scarlet Smith?
- Jo.
Well then.
- Sitting Scarlet Smith in your car?
- Yes...
- Is she not with Brad?
- They have turned up.
- I do not gossip. Growers in sex?
- No, we just chat.
I'd rather not know...
320 here. Duty calls.
Run a little slower.
It was nice to see you.
- You look great.
- Be careful...
...And worth considering if you want to borrow
handcuffs. Have a good evening!
Sorry. I should have
told us about Brad. He looks like himself.
I had figured out.
Yes, he has not accepted
that our relationship is over.
It does nothing.
- You can run.
- Yes. Good night.
I'll call you.
Here, Coach! I am free!
It was your ball
but you stand and nail you!
You and I should have a chat.
About Scarlet.
- It has not happened.
- No. And that makes it...
- ... There will be problems.
- The coach will be a bitch.
I prefer me not.
- Into my office.
- The coach is in trouble!
What is the problem, guys?
We can sit here all day
if I feel like it.
Now you will hear:
The problem must be solved -
Today, this office before you go.
Is that understood?
We'll start with you.
Sorry, but I was doing
with training...
- ... Because narrøven provoked me.
- "Narrøven"?
Can we stick to the matter?
I walk in the hallway...
- He walks in the hallway without permission.
- I need no permission.
I walk in the hallway
quietly...
He interrupts my training. I would
just win the state championship.
That was below the belt.
You have some problems, Henry.
You should stick to writing.
And silent.
I think
I can understand Brad's frustration.
He is surrounded by delicious
teenage boys, half naked, young...
- The kind of eats away at everyone.
- Yes.
He gives losers a bad name.
- Yes, he does.
- What would you do?
- He will stay away.
- Some people never evolve.
- You can beat him.
Behave not like a young bull.
Brad break your neck.
Sometimes you have to be satisfied
with what you have.
Geek do not get the girl.
Bill, thanks!
I have a little message for you.
For older students,
to be involved in school dance:
Use your common sense -
so it is not
your last dance.
And one more thing:
Heja, Wildcats!
"I asked Lauren to be my date
writing. I dared not speak. "
"I put a note in her
kemibog. She never answered. "
"I started counting the days
and hours for translocation. "
"I waited
to be liberated. "
- Hello!
- Oh god...
Hey...
Is everything okay, Shasta?
- Is everything okay?
- Sure.
I'm so stupid.
I need to get a hug.
My girlfriend just
broke up with me.
How inappropriate...
Are you okay now?
Will not you tell me
your afslutningsbal was boring.
- I was not.
- What? Why not?
For stupid reasons.
- You need some for a hug.
- No, I'm fine.
A good hug can redeem
several years of pent-up pain.
A good hug can get me cooped up
for 20 painful years.
It does nothing.
Feel better now? Then we go.
Okay. Thank you.
- You'll handle it.
- Thank you cheered me up.
May I ask
some questions first?
Is it true
you fought with the coach?
Refuse you?
We have witnesses.
- Would you comment on the episode?
- Not really.
Are the rumors true Shasta?
I should have embraced each other.
"Embraced"?
It lasted stuff.
A hug goods 3.2 seconds.
Your train 20th
- It was an embrace.
- She was upset.
- Are you coming along or not?
- No.
You angrily inequality
to influence our conclusions.
We promise to quote you verbatim.
- Have you ever read the book?
- The text on the cover is good.
I like the title.
Beautiful as always.
Looking at it. How sweet.
How fine?
Bridal veil is classical.
- Yes, Brad is a real charmer.
- He is jealous, have called 20 times.
It was not my intention.
- What did you think Brad would do?
- This.
I mean... He should not decide
what I need and how I live...
- ... Or whoever I see.
- Now you can demand change.
Brad does not change underwear.
Brad only think about Brad.
It's over.
It you have
to accept.
- Oh god, you love the guy.
- Yes.
- You absolutely love him, right?
Remember what happened
with the last guy you were crazy.
A glass eye.
Someone will come after us.
It is not him.
- Hello!
- Stop it there.
- Do not I be worried?
- Yes, but you are scary.
- You need proliferate protection.
- I'm with. Thanks, but...
- Is it Scarlet? May I say hello?
- Be there.
- How are you?
- Fine.
Between us girls, "kisses you it
are you in pieces. "
Enjoy.
Start the engine!
You are so strong.
It is here you are doing.
You're so quiet.
- I've always been quiet.
- You're a cheerleader girl.
Sorry. I just sat...
...And remembering back, I thought.
- Jaså. Are not you glad?
- I'm not sad.
I see so many
depressed people everyday.
You would be shocked
where many city residents -
taking medication
against something.
It is difficult
to address the sad lives.
I have probably taken all the bad
decisions can be taken.
We do not stop it. You make
Once one that affects your life.
When one realizes that the decisions
affect, they must mean something.
- It was a decision.
- A good or bad decision?
- What do you think?
- A good decision.
Very.
Was "Kissing Mountain" is not here?
I do not know.
I've never been here.
- Of course you know.
- Trollop is revealed.
- I've never been here.
- Stop it.
You have not been here long.
It is a residential neighborhood now.
But it is here.
It happens when you kiss too long.
We do not know where you are.
- What are you doing?
- We must find a better view.
We must see what is
behind fremvisningshus number four.
Come on.
Close the door. Come, come, come.
Gently.
What a great TV. Come on.
- What do you say? Nice view, huh?
- Not bad.
- You invited me to the prom?
- Yes.
You did not answer.
But it's okay. It does nothing.
- I wish I had answered that way.
- Good answer.
What triggers this?
We're here.
Put your address in.
Brandon.
Oh god...
I can not ignore him.
- Let me talk to him.
- I'll do it.
- Scarlet. I talk to him.
- Go into the car again, Henry.
You are too much.
I have nothing to say to you.
- Linda here. Are you hurt?
- I'm fine.
Have you been out unite accident
or are you lost?
Very.
"Lauren changed places
in chemistry lessons. "
"It was as if I
had ceased to exist. "
"I was not in her field of vision
and disappeared like a worm in acid. "
"I biked past Lauren and hoped
she realized how good I was. "
"How cool
and interesting I was. "
"Lauren filled
my waking hours. "
"She continued to ignore me
and the day was an eternal torment. "
"I had fortunately
my friends. "
"Bryan and Wayne pulled me always
out of my self-pity. "
"I did not show my gratitude.
They made me forget Lauren. "
"They knew what could
cure my depression: Laughter. "
"Wayne got a tattooed cow with
a cigar to get me to laugh. "
Games
Look sharp.
- What did she say?
- Do it now, not worse, than it is.
We did not come together.
I ate, I drove into your car,
theoretically is to come together.
Did you at least a memory?
Panties?
- I beat you soon.
- The rest of us will also have fun.
She can not relax.
- It took time, but you gave you do not.
Well done.
You are my hero.
Come on.
I must beat a stroke.
History repeats itself.
Everything is as when school was over.
20 years is gone.
You know what?
You have recovered
over Scarlet fever before.
We were 18 years then.
Much younger.
My genes means
I never get the girl.
I know how it is.
- Come here.
- Yes. Well...
- I'm with. You want a hug.
- Yes. Smells you by Old Spice?
It's your problem.
You get something else.
We combine it all
and the Mount wonderful celebration.
Who envelopes
with the finished project?
Is everyone ready soon
with their projects?
- Fine. I...
- Sorry, Mrs. Leuchtenberg.
- Do I disturb for a moment?
- Deliver the speech, if it is finished.
Otherwise, you must get
until after hours.
Time is short.
Finish your projects -
and dispose of them so I can
cross them off the list.
We put the finishing touches on everything.
It will be a fine event.
We must be ready...
- I'll take that.
- Of course you did.
You must choose.
Should I read it otherwise it mite look like?
It depends on
what it says.
I must say
that your behavior disappoints me.
You are involved
in many episodes.
It is the second time you are
the office for disciplinary reasons.
And this here episode...
...Are serious.
- She sent a note.
Do you know what is on it?
- No.
- Would you like to know?
- Yes, it was for me.
WILL YOU FOLLOW WITH ME
FOR BALLET SCHOOL?
- Amusing.
- Well, you can see the comedy.
I did not mean it here, as I said,
you should teach students to know.
I must not accompany Shasta
to prom?
I can only control what
happens at school, and it is my responsibility.
I and the school district
has a zero tolerance policy.
You'll be expelled.
- Am I banned?
- Yes.
Go away.
I will do.
- Hello! All is well right?
- Yes, everything is okay. Do not worry.
I was just turned away.
- God...
You must apologize.
- It's okay.
She wanted to do it soon.
Now she has got his wish.
What do you say?
To note, that is.
Well, Leaflet.
It was fun. You're funny.
We can not follow the school dance.
This runs counter to everything...
For example, gravity
who keeps his feet on the ground.
Think of it as research.
Say yes now,
then you can change your mind later.
If you say no now, you may
never able to say yes.
It is very smart,
I like, but never implemented.
There must be many guys
who will accompany you? You are beautiful.
I put actual requirements. Mr. Marshall
banished you not from the ballet.
So make them angry
and came with me.
Will not you?
I am no longer defiant.
I stopped at the door.
You are too much. You know that.
You are really too much.
So it is good,
when one is full 37 years.
Oh god...
- What color is your dress?
- Really? Turquoise.
Great.
- Why I said yes?
- Now it's done.
Just accept and enjoy the moment.
This is your golden crowbar -
which will free you
from your past.
- Scarlet must not stop you again.
- I remember to cancel the Shasta.
Now I'll explain something.
When you get some success...
...Can a celebrity does not make mistakes.
Doing so, the consequences are small.
Go to bed with your stepdaughter,
team pajama party with young boys...
- I'm not a celebrity.
- Let me explain it to you.
Are you your own master,
are you a celebrity according to the Big Girl.
- My goodness.
- Voila.
Arrested me, I will call you.
- You should take with me.
- Wow! Francesca.
- My goodness.
Henry McCanthy.
Yes...
- Shasta has told all about you.
- Okay.
- Yes. Go ahead...
- She is not my...
- Oh no. Come in.
- Thanks.
- What are you working with?
- I write. I'm an author.
- What are you writing?
- It's a good question.
Here she comes,
and she looks fantastic.
Hello.
- What's wrong, father?
- Should you be then?
She's so fine, baby.
What?
Let's go.
- He is still delicious.
- No.
Happy thoughts...
- Hello?
- You swim in mourning. Come to me.
- Want something? A large soda?
- No thanks.
- I'm about a 7-eleven.
- What are you doing? Now I'm worried.
There's never a positive thing
by a 7-eleven.
Relax, Javier.
Leave the spot.
7- eleven sending people to jail.
Goodbye. We'll talk later.
- I have downloaded refreshments.
- Fine.
- What did you purchase?
- Refreshments. Run now.
- Something extra.
How exciting!
Really.
Come on.
- I will not participate in illegal activities.
- I paid.
But any contribution
received with thanks.
Cheers.
All the writing ambitions, I had
goes up in smoke when I have drunk out.
Be on my side now.
- Lovely, no?
- Sure.
Let's go!
I will not do anything stupid.
Shasta! How is it
going out with a pedophile?
Bea! Where does
stunning dress from?
- Shasta. Who made your dress?
- Forever 21st But it's secret.
Who is he?
Think that everything is finished.
Come!
- Wow...
- Relax.
I can see that Henry and Shasta
dancing very close together.
- You're beautiful tonight.
- Add! Rape!
Listen, Mary...
- My dance moves are archaic.
- Move.
Rockville prom
"Lauren was so beautiful that I
could hardly look at her. "
"And the school's norms forbade her
look at me. She was too popular. "
"She was
with a football player. "
"She went to dance with him. I took
not. I would not see them. "
"Ballet's king and queen. "
"I sent a bouquet anonymously. "
"On balaftenen I waited outside
to see if she Barden. "
"She did not. Ridiculous,
but I would be in her life. "
"The day after I was sick
to avoid Lauren. "
Will not you?
No, I can not.
It was nice...
- We are away from the party for ten minutes.
- I've been here extend.
Think of it as velgørened, Henry.
You can drag it from your taxes.
- For what cause?
- Because I want it. Why not?
- Come on.
- Just not the family.
So take home.
It's probably your mother calling.
REJECT
- Only ten minutes.
- I promise it'll be fun.
Enjoy it!
Hello! Oh god.
Hello.
Come on, Henry.
- I'll get drinks.
- Okay.
Go ahead.
Okay...
You do not do.
- You have no ring on your finger.
- I do not want one around the ankle.
- Okay. Is this OK?
- Yes.
Keep hands at rest,
then it's okay.
How?
Do not you think
I know what I'm doing?
Why did you say yes,
To not complete it?
I promise...
- ... That you will not regret it.
- I know...
...But to go ahead with it here
benefit to ringing of us in the future.
- What do you think now?
- To kiss a girl on the 18th..
...Can not the entire
my 20 hogget heartache.
What a bitch!
And I'm paying the price.
- Police!
- Damn it. Come on.
- Come on.
- Oh god. Races.
- What? Oh god.
- You must.
Hop.
Trust me. Otherwise you are going
same exercise at rehab.
The party is over!
- Can you imagine anything better?
- Yes, I could watch "Cops" on TV.
I love "Cops".
I've learned
not to run from police.
He is here.
Get out of the bush.
It is not
what it seems to be.
It provides me.
- Have you been drinking?
- No, not at all.
Vodka?
"When my friend Bryan came out of the closet
he became the school's sole gay. "
"Afterwards I'd rather not
circumvented him. "
"It was hard enough without being
paired with another idiot. "
"To be accepted by the cool
I threw eggs at Bryan's car. "
"We wrote 'pussy' with soap
and covered the car with the Volume "-
- "To indicate
- That he should have been a woman. "
I hit the kid to death. "Bryan"?
He could have chosen "Trevor. "
You are not previously convicted.
So we have only a 37-year-old -
are to teenage party.
- McCanthy?
- Hey, Bird.
I'll make it.
- I swear. There is nothing has happened.
- Jaså.
You can just that.
- Make it right.
- Thanks.
He may like to go now.
- I'm so embarrassed.
- It is better to get it over with now.
- Henry.
- Wow.
- Oh god.
- Yes.
"You are too much"?
Yes, I am.
- Oh yes.
- Oh no.
Come on.
Jump in, young lady.
I apologize. She comes
at least unscathed home.
I can not hurt you anymore
than your dad does when he sees the car.
Pussy
YOU ARE TOO MUCH
THE CAR IS HERE FOR SEJ
TO A NARRØV
Sorry, Dad.
How in heaven's name
have you been with her?
It's just superficial.
I'll fix it.
Do not play smart right now.
Sorry.
I pull it from your pocket money.
From your heritage, I mean.
- How's the speech?
- I'm not begun. I know.
A Scarlet called. I said
you'd be home tonight.
- Do you give me grounded?
- You do not get the Cadillac.
I have two legs.
I can go over to her.
Pick up the phone.
Come on.
Damn it.
"One must act. At the back you get
not the high scores and the girl. "
"I moved forward, and Lauren
risked failure in chemistry. "
"This cairn perfect opportunity
genius to rescue a lady in distress. "
The city's gay?
I weighed 200 kilograms!
It was long
before I realized what I had to.
Would you like it
I did by car?
Stop it.
Hello, Heidl.
That was what Wayne got.
Hello, hello!
What have we here?
- Enough is enough.
- What happens?
Sorry, sorry.
Bitch.
"Lauren would know I existed.
I helped her kemilektierne "-
- "But the only thing that was hot,
- Were Bunsen burners. "
"Yes, I did it more complicated
to be with her. "
"I was distracted
of her skin, eyes and hair. "
"In one way or another
she got top marks. "
"The day she gave me a hug and
a kiss was my life's happiest. "
"Like an angel's touch. "
"The day she wrote in my yearbook:
'Continue to be tough' "
"I thought it meant:
'I love you. "'
What are you doing here?
- Is it too late?
- No. Come in.
- I put my bike there.
- Yes. Sweet.
One of the reasons that I called,
was that I read your book.
I just wanted to hear
how much of what is true?
Everything except sexen.
Well. The girl
you write about, Lauren...
I was really touched.
Touched by...
You wrote so beautifully about her. She must
be special, inspirational.
She is both.
Who is she?
Who do you think?
- Scarlet! Come out!
- What?
- What are you doing?
- It does not matter.
- Go away. I'm calling the police.
- I bitch him.
No, no, no.
He chases me till he finds me.
Let's get it over with.
Here is your ridiculous BMX bike.
What do you say?
Let her be.
- How is he?
- I do not know.
- (Put your arm around her.)
- (Should I?)
I must get to him.
- Hello, boys.
- What have you done?
- Was it only here?
- Yes. Plus a couple of ribs.
- I told you. Not?
- Jo.
We remove anything
The dried blood.
We played ever Doctor.
This do not you write a book.
Good.
Stay behind the typewriter.
Brawl?
I'll pick a doctor.
Hello, wino.
- Is Scarlet here?
- Yes, outside.
- It hurts.
- Sorry. Look at this.
I'll come tomorrow.
ER
I have done.
I have read it and it is miserable.
It is miserable. I've said it...
Nobody will care about it.
A story about someone who sells fertilizer.
No one will bother reading it.
Henry...
Henry? If you can hear me
it is Javier.
- Hi, Javier.
- You're not in a coma. Are you stunned?
- What is it?
- It's a local review.
"Mr McCanthy saves us hopefully
multiply nonsense during the speech. "
She thinks probably something else.
"It inspires only to suicide. "
- Who's Fields?
- I do not know.
I've probably thrown eggs
at her house sometime.
You must get away from here,
before you end up in death the ads.
It would be good
but I can not.
The locals do not like you.
I cancel the speech and television interview
today. We take the first plane.
If I go now, I write
about it here the next 20 years.
I want to change the subject.
- How Lionel struck me out?
- Get me to the translocation.
Download photos from prom
Today at. 15-16. And now: Sports.
Sorry.
One would think that we advertise
unite book about domestic violence.
You know what?
One of my stroke sufferers.
- I know not where.
- I'll just digest.
People love writers who see
torn and battered out. It is now.
Hi, all students.
Today we speak with Henry McCanthy.
How did you get the title
"How Lionel gave me sex"?
It is the singer...
His music has so affected you?
- Yes. I was not as popular as...
He was popular,
and he got enough many sex.
"I created a philosophy
in the last school. "
"I focus on living
Instead of worrying me "-
- "I'd enjoy your time on earth
more and would probably have sex. "
"At least once. "
"Later I discovered that what I
had learned in school, came back. "
"I could not see
no end to it. "
"I got top grades in school
but why I dumped in life? "
"Was it necessary to get it
refreshed in West Rockville? "
You've got a decent game?
I can help you. Who was it?
It's nothing.
- Will they also expelled?
- If necessary.
It goes if you let me go
through to get the speech approved.
There is a jogging track,
and there are guest entrances.
"72% of graduating class
want to take antidepressants. "
"61% will be divorced. "
Interesting.
It's funny, shocking
and gifted, but it does not.
They listen safely
the frightening statistics...
- ... But it has no effect.
- The truth does not sell.
"A voice rage is the best speech
you will regret "- Laurence Peter.
Thank you.
There is no time to write something
you can approve.
This you have already done.
Henry!
Your suitcase is here!
"Although it was uncomfortable, forced
school me to be myself. "
"It was also my clothes. "
I would like to introduce to you -
unite with my... favorite students.
He attended school a few years ago
and is now a succesrigforfatter.
Bid our speeches Henry McCanthy
welcome.
Thank you, thank you. Thank you.
I will read aloud from a little book
I rancid reef.
"I learned that we tackle
situations differently. "
"Colors, shapes and emotions" -
"Vary according
what we need them to. "
"I sat for a long
with each situation. "
"I gave care and attention
to the situation. "
"I was wondering if it would hatch
and become a beautiful memory... "
"... Or would it fade away?"
"I stand here
because of the memorial. "
"It jumps
from head to heart... "
"... And to my stomach. "
"The memory could not be saved
anywhere, not even in the book. "
"It has affected my way of speaking
and the way I live. "
"Our memories make us what
we are. "
"These four years
become only memories. "
"I can not define them,
but they can define who you are. "
Congratulations.
More, Henry!
Chester, right?
Thanks! It was a good speech.
Take care of yourself.
- Tax...
- Bye.
Excellent speech.
I have to catch the plane.
- I get along. Go now, Javier.
- Great.
Call me!
God created Ihop.
Selected Ihop, and there was Ihop.
You came not to speak to one thousand
students, but to speak with one.
Well, it is as it is.
- She is who she is.
- "It is as it is," he says.
Do you know
what I will say about it?
Oh no.
Sometimes in my life
I asked why
Yet I believe
it will go
You think that it's over
- But only if you want it
- Exactly.
- Waiting for a sign
- A miracle
or would you fight
It is now
You know
where you are
you must fight yourself out
stop closing their eyes
Henry?
- What are you doing?
- Look what you're doing.
I considered to be an outsider
with a boombox.
Is this your room?
To see the words out.
"If I just got a kiss
by Lauren... "
I was wondering
about Lionel would get me sex.
"... As I kissed her in my
dream, life would be perfected. "
- Are you okay?
- I ignore that I am shaking.
"Lionel words
taught me something about love... "
"... Loyalty... "
"... Desire... "
"... And romance. "
- I will shoot you.
- "The family taught me tolerance. "
Should I take the picture?
Friends gave me community
and Lauren cairn ideal woman. "
Follow your own advice.
Have you read the book?
"I wonder if she looks like
the woman I fantasized about "-
- "Or whether I've found
on the whole to remain alone. "
Wake up.
We must support Henry, wino.
"Why do you otherwise unite
unattainable girl with a perfect guy? "
- I love you, Scarlet.
- "Imagination on Lauren taught me... "
"... To take life,
as it comes... "
Henry.
"... Conquer fear and quit
carry around unfulfilled dreams. "
- Continue to be tough.
- Okay.
"Some nights I think of
what happened to Lauren. "
"Did herself with sports guy?
Does she have children? She remembers me? "
"Well, now I'm not
afraid The love. "
"My heart is perhaps crushed again
but I know I will survive. "