Miss Rahm?
Thus, it is enough for today.
Mr. Rauch is visited.
Armand Rauch?
I am Sophia Rahme
my mother was Famke Rahm.
Her sister has
studied in Argentina.
I think I'm your cousin.
Cousin?
My girl,
you still need to see.
Tell me
how you found me.
It was not easy.
But now I'm here, Uncle.
Or should I say, General? Thus,
nevertheless, Neurath General of the SS?
I called Rauch.
Armand Rauch.
Do you remember Mathieu Jonas?
You were glad when he died down.
But he had a daughter.
This was my mother.
And this was my father.
And this soldier of them
liberated from the concentration camp.
I saw them die while
to you and the others were looking for.
Each time you feel pain,
for them.
Jewish bitch, whore.
There is a reason
for you not to die.
Liver Klaus Listener to me.
If you give me Klaus Listener, I will
not suffocate with a pillow.
What a nerve.
Still shaking your hands.
I am helpless.
Do it.
Typical.
You know, there is a reason
why all this started.
And now when I look at you as...
I remember what it was.
Well, but you are too proud to
not something to have withheld.
Souvenirs?
Even if you find Klaus Ontario,
that nothing will change.
You're too late.
You do not know, eh?
-- What do you mean?
Hunt Who is this?
Is he a scientist?
Why do you finance his work in Europe?
Is Klaus Ener there?
Answer the question.
Do you still see yourself,
a child who plays detective.
The Millennial Kingdom hides
really not for people like you.
It is simply lurking
in the shade.
Damn.
Come on, quietly.
Do not you dare to die.
Damn.
Doctor?
They arrived.
We have them in sight.
Herr Klaus Listener?
EASTERN EUROPE
Control unit, secure the location.
The assault team is leading.
There are cartridge cases
and fresh blood.
No sign of the searched or his team.
We are now approaching the machine room.
We see the engine room.
We need them out of there.
-- It is too late, Josef.
But the command is executed.
Be happy Josef.
This is the beginning.
I'm sorry,
I speak the language.
Give me a break.
I have money, take that...
Enough.
Let her, Marius.
Are you a journalist?
-- No.
Women now have not come here.
-- I am looking for this man.
He was here a week or two back
have been.
Yes, he was here.
He said some soldiers,
who were not from here.
They went to the east.
-- To the east, so?
Since you really can not go.
Do you see the families out there?
They come from there. Their houses are
burned, their families killed.
They talk about horrible things.
Can Hunt via a different route
come back?
He has not come back.
He's dead.
You look old.
-- Thank you.
Now you're here, I'd like a whiskey.
-- Two double.
He pays.
Boy, she's grown.
-- It is long ago.
And a lot has happened.
Where have you been?
Everywhere and nowhere.
I heard about Mathieu.
Horrible.
A car accident, right?
-- Yes, it was an accident.
That explains why Neurath
not lived long enough...
Paraguay to stand trial.
-- That was an accident.
He supplied from Hunt, and now you're
here looking for Klaus Ontario, eh?
I'm on the right track.
Hunt is just like you.
Looking for those weird magnets.
-- The unified field theory.
Whatever.
-- Yes, he worked on the same.
And you want not. Go home.
-- Absolutely not.
Lena, have you ever listened to him?
This is real.
This goes to the prize.
-- Geez.
Take a look.
A reaction of NATO fighting
here in secret for two weeks.
Mama?
Still...
A couple of guys dressed as...
-- You do not understand.
Götz, camp commander.
That bastard died in 1945.
He looks lively for a corpse.
Klaus has Listener that?
Really?
It's not about old men
retirement homes, Lena.
You know where he is.
-- Go home.
Forget it.
-- I've tried.
Take me.
-- That I will not do.
Klaus Ontario is the last. I
grabbed him and for me it's over.
Good luck.
It was nice to see you.
So...
How is the Listener Klaus succeeded?
They look like ghosts.
That sounds romantic but so far
of reality is not.
Looky Klaus Listener's machine. This
you have the perfect army behind you.
He would force a special
treatment have given.
Nice.
A treatment in combination with
the magnetic field of the machine.
Suddenly the men are not like us.
Within the magnetic field, they do
what they want, bullets do nothing.
This is three weeks reversed.
Nothing unusual,
though it is a civil war.
This is two weeks old
made after Hunt disappeared.
This area
is an electromagnetic field.
Vehicles, communications,
aircraft...
...anything with electronics
in it does nothing.
It is exactly what Klaus Listener
was last stationed.
This is from three days ago.
Now that it has a cross
-- section of 50 kilometers.
Götz and his men extend it.
Where do they go? -- Everywhere,
that is what they want.
The Millennial Kingdom...
Right. Here we go.
Come on, let's go.
What is going on? -- We have
a task force of the UN.
We believe that chemical
weapons are used.
The population may have...
this area for a short time left
because of their safety.
Clear.
We gotta go.
-- Chemical weapons?
Bullshit. Why such a big
disclose secret...
if you steal it for yourself?
-- They do not.
Many governments will
everything for free...
Klaus to Ontario or the machine
access. We must go now.
What would you do? The yield
donate to charity?
I have searched in Russia Klaus Listener,
and trusted the wrong people.
Make sure you're not in jail
comes. It's cold.
After one year there were
suddenly two men of the embassy.
I thought that get me out of here.
But when they noticed I knew
nothing about the machine...
...they let me rot.
Nobody should such a powerful
thing in his possession.
I just want Klaus Listener.
Klaus Sat Listener
in an underground bunker.
If this card is correct,
it's two days of traveling.
Why we have my equipment,
my car and my money?
We go to a camp of the militia.
I have a contact: Limak.
For the right price he will
and his men serve as guides.
Do you trust him?
-- Of course not.
But I do not go there
unaccompanied.
It is still a mile.
Turn left into a dirt road.
Come on.
I think we're there.
The field is expanding faster
than I thought.
Get your stuff. The faster
guidance we have, the better.
Stitch, a camp of the militia.
That is, are you ready?
Limak.
Come.
Limak, damn.
Be still, hold your breath.
We must continue.
Lena...
we must go.
From this direction we have come.
We can now to the blow
-- off.
The car does nothing.
On foot, we can tomorrow
on the other side.
Say it.
Special forces.
Look.
An EMP, electromagnetic pulse.
He fires off a beam of energy...
that everything electrical within
destroy a certain distance. Handsome.
They want to get close...
and destroy the machine.
-- Do we take him?
We can use it in the bunker.
-- He is broken.
We better go.
What are these?
The runic symbols.
Here you go.
There was a Nazi division with special
Weapons, called the Black Sun
They use the symbol
in all their documents.
I think it's a code, a
password for the machine to send.
It has taken years on tight.
-- A decade or so.
I could at least choose.
Mathieu also.
Have you ever wanted to do
something else? -- I do not know.
At first I thought all families
did.
In South America
Search for old men.
And one evening,
I think I was ten...
sneaked into his room.
He stood on the balcony crying.
And on the bed were all those pictures.
Klaus Listener and the others,
the things they had done.
I had never seen him cry.
-- If you've caught Klaus Ener...
what then?
No idea.
Then I can choose in each case.
There will always be somebody.
Someone who does everything for power,
another Klaus Listener.
People are like that.
-- The following is not my problem.
Damn it.
-- Road here, flight.
Come.
Lena?
Godsamme.
Inside.
Damn.
Cover the right.
-- Cover the left.
No...
Faster, forward.
Glen...
Road here, walk.
Hurry up.
Faster.
Take cover, shoot.
-- Cover.
Beware, friendly fire.
Come on.
-- Fire with the EMP.
Come on, do it now.
-- Contact.
What are you waiting for?
I told you to fire.
That is not the mission.
If we perish,
there is no longer mission.
That was it.
It'll be fine.
Stay with me, pal.
Damn.
Are you going to do bold?
See, that was my buddy.
He died to save you.
Soon you see look like that.
Relax.
What are you doing in this enclosed area?
-- We are journalists.
Yes?
Against the wall.
Fingers.
I'll take that.
Legs apart.
I see the error
or the operation failed completely?
The physics teacher is dead.
What did he say again?
It's all or nothing,
You only get one chance.
Don't blow not.
-- As if we had the choice.
They are dead, and we go there too.
-- Shut up, Hall.
No press pass and no camera.
But you know your story,
Mr. Wallace.
What I want to know,
is how he recognized you.
He saw me for someone else.
-- It was a klotedag.
Stop that bullshit.
Shoot him, you know 't ever.
-- It is.
Hall, put her in the eye.
-- Good. Hold on.
I am engineer.
Are you a scientist?
Physical, surely?
Is she your secretary?
-- I am looking for war criminals, Nazis.
Then you're good here, darling.
And here is what you want
get their hands on, right?
And do not you?
Please, let me guess.
You warrant to stop the machine
and save the world.
And bring so
Muir thought it worked.
Firstly:
I recommend you go to nothing, asshole.
Secondly,
how do you know he Muir called?
Damn.
Sucks.
You better talk.
There are few specialists in this field.
-- That they say.
So this is your lucky day.
Throw him in the car,
we have a new expert.
One moment.
Remember that this operation
of fell...
when the second EMP failed.
This operation is not over until
I tell you.
You know what happens
if we do nothing.
Does that pulse magnetic field
deactivated?
Then we can kill them.
No, the EMP has a limited
scope.
We had to close.
-- He's right.
This device is good for
five or six miles at most.
How far are we from the goal?
-- Thirteen miles.
The next ten kilometers
we can afknallen.
Then you think thirteen kilometers...
how my mission without that thing
may close, Mr. Wallace.
Welcome to the emptier boy.
-- What a luck I have.
Where do you go?
No academic qualifications, no place.
-- View the.
A lady here leave neat.
-- We go.
We encircle the bag.
Find a safe place.
A basement, somewhere underground.
With luck, the cavalry
within a day.
If you remember way back...
go back.
Jesus...
Sir...
Bravo-- Charlie-- 4, this is
the command. -- Go ahead.
There is a pulse in the field shot.
-- How close to the target?
Not close enough.
-- Can you see who it was?
The location indicates the Alpha team.
But we're not sure.
-- And Team Beta?
A mild rash five hours back.
Too little for a real shot.
Previously a refusal.
-- Damn.
If both teams are off,
we see our options.
There is still time.
-- Without EMP to nothing.
We need to go.
-- This is my battlefield.
I decide on the deployment of nuclear
weapons. There is still time, we wait.
Clear?
No, it's not scary, nor stupid.
No academic qualifications, no place.
At which university they
learn to push ups? Acorns.
Come.
Come out of the way.
-- Where is my notebook?
Wait, my notebook.
Further down dip.
No...
Let me go.
I have had you not done anything?
Nothing.
They are here.
That he injected him?
What did he do?
No idea.
Maybe he wanted him
just like they make.
Nazis are real bastards.
Without my notebook
I can not do anything.
Without the codes and symbols...
-- Zeik not.
Without your balls
would you worse bleating.
But you've worked there for years.
-- Jae very long.
Therefore, I had just a notebook.
Write down everything, okay?
Dane this has taken time.
We must go faster.
With you, I need to talk.
What are you doing here?
-- Thanks for coming.
If you just bothers me...
-- We must hurry.
Then manage it before the big bang.
-- Blast?
If it is not within the
prescribed time does...
they assume that it fails
and they choose the latter option.
Seven tonnes up.
There are thousands
of people live here.
And millions of people die
if we do not stop.
It should make us succeed.
To discuss what nobody.
Wait, now she suddenly last?
As a babysitter for Hansel and Gretel,
what madness.
Here it should be.
I had expected
that this printer would be.
They celebrate feast elsewhere.
-- Yes, whether it is a perfect trap.
The main entrance is in any case
the end of our career.
Set the safe side, find the
Rear entry, you have five minutes.
Do not forget:
I know the machine, not them.
I try something. Can not run.
-- And Klaus Listener?
With him, you must pay.
Until now, the child,
now it is intense.
If we strike
we do it as fast as possible.
The field is empty.
-- Nothing, not even a rabbit hole.
Carlisle left, right
-- Hall.
Abbott, we take the center with the
girls. Position your at the doors.
Keep going.
Continue.
What happened here?
-- Is not nut out.
Looking for cables, in this thickness.
That we should follow.
-- And then? Without EMP?
I must go to the command center.
-- Forward.
That's him.
Inside.
He should be here his shit.
Damn it.
-- He should be here.
The military intelligence
delivers again great work.
That is...
This is Hunt's handwriting.
Check this out.
And Klaus Listener?
Since there are even more.
Here.
Hunt's notes prove...
that he only works
and solves problems.
Klaus Listener is not been here.
-- Why?
That is not logical.
-- Klaus Energy Hunt sent hither.
Klaus Ener wanted or
could not be here.
Hunt put everything in motion.
Klaus Listener's men
search for daddy.
There is a cell or something.
-- It's a cell.
The energy of the motor there was
together since they were created.
Always the right answers.
Can you infer
where they have gone?
Where does' t magnetic field
come from? -- No idea.
The notes are those of
a lunatic. Look.
Hunt also what they have done,
it was diabolical.
Everything revolves around the field
and energy generation.
I look at it again better.
-- No.
Take as much as you can bear,
we leave here.
This material is unheard important.
-- It was not a question.
Ready?
-- I can not just go.
About eight hours everything
here is completely charred.
If we do not go
we are not at a safe distance.
Take your pick.
-- I really thought I was close.
It's been pretty
that you've met up here.
The next time you pick it.
Your friend Wallace is right.
I had the machine safeguarding
and Klaus Listener nab.
You have many powerful friends.
Maybe I can
to some people imagine.
Well?
Beware.
Let go away there.
-- Make sure you get away.
Coverage.
-- On the ground.
Let go.
Road here.
Not back inside, outside.
Sam...
Time's up.
We gotta go.
Regret it
you need the sector.
We can send one.
Confirm, please.
We need support.
Send us reinforcements.
They break through.
Sire contact with the enemy
the defenses.
One mile east.
That was it.
He still had at least
can leave an address.
Where would you place him?
Lena, he is still here.
The machine is not moved.
That's impossible...
for he is always in the center
of the field that it generates.
The map shows only other trees.
This is really ridiculous.
Have fun searching
to the secret room, darling.
I 'm out for me under
terechtkom a mushroom cloud.
The operation is not over yet.
He is carefully hidden somewhere.
Along with Elvis and the Easter Bunny.
-- He's right. We're ready.
My hero.
-- Damn...
Many people find that 'never give up
Him or Her romantic mentality.
But I would prefer your head
rams against the wall.
Macavoy is dead, the machine is
gone, this mission is over.
You can not go, there is still a chance.
-- Yes?
Since when you tell us
what to do, Princess?
Danny, this is for tough guys.
We go off like a hare.
And where? If you go now,
You can keep running.
Because they do not stop.
Not in the next village or country.
We can only stop here.
-- Forget it.
Let them go.
He was right about you all.
Go to hell.
Danny?
Damn.
Best.
Look for an entrance,
for anything unusual.
As if something just is.
And lay a trail of breadcrumbs,
for if you get lost.
What is the most logical reason
to move it?
Are you really sure?
-- Yes.
Fucking shit.
Was I 'm but smeared
but it was too late.
Where are you right answers?
We need this wall.
But of course.
Do you have a nervous breakdown?
Is that it?
Look for a panel
on the other side.
This should be up there.
It was written
when this door was still open.
Here there is one.
Good.
This is a well hidden elevator.
What do we do now?
-- What we always do.
You light fires bullets.
Once we're outside, you shoot them.
Then the planes that we know
here and they blow the whole thing not.
Stay alive, girls.
Nobody believes me later
if you do not confirm.
I go first, you follow.
And keep you quiet.
Do you know how you use it?
Wallace...
That way.
Here, take this.
Come.
Damn.
Let me go.
-- Small gypsy jew.
Hold on.
Let me go, damn bitch.
No...
Come.
Children.
Here, this should be the control room.
Fri
Do you know what you're looking for?
-- A kind of schedule over the ministry.
Here, good.
The machine and the expansion
chambers are there...
and from here to be sent.
Here's the inside that divides it.
-- Can you do that?
Yes, it works
as a pressure cooker.
We maximize the ability
that generates the complex...
and then block the energy drain.
We overload the system.
That is our EMP.
No, no. That's not fair.
What is that?
-- Safety Vent.
Handsome machine.
That works well.
We're almost there.
Stop it now goes.
-- What?
The system is well designed,
it does not want me to destroy.
Damn.
You must go, I must stay here.
-- Only you know the machine.
If I go, then, can we never
to fire off an EMP.
If we wait until he has fired?
-- We can not do.
If things go wrong,
we never come here.
Here, if the pulse did not work
try this. There is a kind face.
Save it with a hammer or
whatever on. Forward.
And take care of yourself.
Alright.
Come. Well verdommee
cheap rattletrap.
Is that Klaus Listener?
-- No. It is Hunt.
Come, godsamme.
Forward.
Sieg Heil, bitch.
It failed.
Come, come on.
I try to stop them.
You stay at the machine.
Who are you?
I'm here
Klaus Listener to stop it.
Unfortunately, only I am here.
Would you destroy the machine?
Bring me to.
Try using the electromagnetic
pulse. She thinks I'm stupid.
She is stupid.
They must protect the core.
Stop the heart never.
Klaus Listener's secret.
That never stop. Never.
They forced you to help them.
-- Make the field larger.
Bring them to Dad.
-- I know all about you.
You are not like them.
Help them please do not.
Begging is weak.
I've tried.
I have earned.
I was arrogant.
I wanted to unite the fields
and know how God thinks.
I deserve pain.
Pain is what I know.
Bugger anyway.
I do not understand.
But I have no choice, I must
to a nuclear attack questions.
The light signal of Team Alpha.
-- Ignore it.
Wait with nuclear weapons, but make
that bunker to the ground.
And this? Can I use it?
Unusable. Klaus Listener's secret.
-- Please, I can not.
I do not know it,
and I do not understand.
Two days back I thought that
it was what they had done.
That is not true, what matters...
is what they do.
There, in our world.
The world consists of vibrating
particles, nothing else.
No, there are people.
Innocent people who die
what you wanted...
you hunted and has unleashed.
If you do not help me now...
The love of power
is the demon of humanity.
The heart drives him.
But the core is poetry.
The Black Sun has built him.
Only they have the key.
Gefeliciteerde you've just saved.
Where are the others?
There somewhere.
The rockets are fired,
the planes are coming.
Why were they fired? -- Accidentally.
You learn from your mistakes.
We have four minutes
this here is destroyed.
On the ground.
We must leave.
Garnet.
Come.
-- Right behind you.
Here is command Zero.
-- Links Fri
Certainly the statement.
-- Right Fri
Attach over.
Are you alone?
The jets come.
We gotta go.
Hopefully you very quickly.
Because this is really tight.
Was it worth the trip?
-- Yes.
But he did not make it.
I'm sorry real Lena.
In a war you can only one side
choose your own.
ADOC, this is Dragon...
-- 60 meters, to fall.
Got it, now go to the goal.
Give your status on Falcon.
-- We are approaching the target.
Damn it.
It is an honor for me
to meet you.
What do you want?
The question is more what
you need, is not it?
I've always wondered myself
why he was not there.
A man who would give everything
be there as the Empire rises again.
Why was he not?
The truth is that he could not.
He is weak, he is dying.
Sure, you had a new machine
can build.
But that one part
you could never recreate.
Thus was it?
You did not have to send Hunt.
Too many scruples.
You have a lot
pragmatic someone.
50 million seems reasonable.
If you're thinking about me
to murder, you will notice...
that some essential elements
are missing.
You were the plan, right?
Old creep.
See it, let's say 60 million.
Relax, you fuck like you.
Hold on. Perhaps there
by more parties offered.
And you want a bit of struggle.
Surprise.
Risen from the dead.
-- Yes, the bunker is indestructible.
It was nothing personal.
As I said, I'm sorry.
Was it true?
-- What do you mean?
That they have more fun.
I think you're right. There will always be
Klaus is a next Listener.
He has a name on my list.
Now there are two.
First I'm going after you.
I wish you much success.
I made new friends.
The war has widened,
young lady.
What if we are behind you entering?
-- I will await you.