There's nothing but idiots
on this thing.
I've got to find something else.
There you go... some music.
Gordy?
You look tired.
You look beat.
Your turn to feed Emma?
She still has that
ear infection.
Still? She had that
at the christening.
She's still got it, huh?
How's Wendy holding up?
Tired. Same as me.
You need anything, Gordon,
you let me know. I'm here.
Hang in there.
You are going to be fine.
About fifteen minutes.
Okay, I'll tell him right now.
That was Bill Griggs.
He says he'll be here in a minute.
Okay, thanks.
See you.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
When was the hospital actually
closed?
Eighty-five.
I am curious because
you have the firearm on.
And people aren't trying to get out.
- Not out, in!
- Who?
Kids, delinquents, homeless.
A lot of patients ended up
in the streets when it closed.
Some come back. I found half a dozen
there last spring.
- The patients come back?
- God knows why!
I'd rather sleep in the street,
personally.
- But then, I'm not nuts!
- Obviously.
- There he is. Good luck, fellas.
- Thanks.
- Are we first in line?
- Nope.
Environmental Solutions and American
Yankees were up here last week.
What was their bid?
The Yankees bid was fast and low.
The way Griggs like them.
He likes jobs fast.
- I like them safe.
- But we cannot gamble with this.
You want me to talk to him?
I know what I'm doing.
Holy shit! Look at this.
Look at this.
1871 is when she went up.
We call her the "Kirkbride Building",
named after Dr. Thomas Kirkbride.
It's a simple layout.
If you consider a giant flying bat.
The main staff building
in the middle.
Slanting off to each slide
are these crooked bat wings.
One for female patients,
the other for male.
A bat.
This place is listed
in the national historic register.
I can't tear it down. Only one tenth
of it is salvageable.
But the land is priceless.
You know, put up a Wal-Mart,
but the town manager
wants to reclaim it.
- What the fuck is this?
- Are you scared, Phil?
This is hydrotherapy. They'd soak
the nut jobs in cold water.
Or they'd give them a lobotomy.
It was perfected here at Danvers.
You've done your homework.
My wife Elizabeth
is the town historian.
There's a morgue in the basement
where they did post mortem...
Bill, could you show us
the problem areas?
- Yeah. Sure. This way.
- Thank you.
You could feed a fucking army
in here!
It was a self-contained town.
Church, movie theater, bowling alley.
There's a lovely cemetery
behind the machine shop.
No headstones, just numbers.
You ought to check it out.
Watch your step.
This'll become
the municipal archives.
- It was a dining area.
- Will there be a lot of people?
Like a library.
All these tiles have to go.
These are deadly.
- They're loaded with asbestos.
- Really?
- The other bids didn't indicate it.
- They should have.
I'll take you to the female wing.
Ward C.
It'll become Administration,
Town Manager's office
- and Department of Public Works.
- In other words, your office.
You better believe it!
Each wing is made of four wards.
Ward A, B, C, D.
Ward A, the wing tip
is the farthest away
from the staff building.
- This was for extreme patients.
- What do you mean?
Psychotic.
Keep the dangerous ones
furthest away, huh?
You're smart. They called Ward A
the snake pit.
Follow these and they'll take you
to C. I wouldn't walk on the floors.
- There's a water damage.
- How do we get over there?
Are you scared of the dark?
Over here.
Hello, Gordon.
Gordy? It's me.
Come on.
A Survival Rations.
Duck and cover. Bend over
and kiss your ass good bye.
This was a fallout shelter.
That is a weird idea.
These ducts have to be wet-stripped.
That breaks off. You will
pollinate the entire building.
- I wouldn't want that.
- You don't.
Gordon, let me lead.
This used to be a solarium.
I call it the carpet toy room.
Danvers Town Hall.
Reclaiming a dark past
to build a brighter future.
- Crocidolite.
- What?
- Crocidolite?
Worst kind.
This is decayed, friable.
- Circa nineteen forties.
- Really?
- What's the deal?
- I would seal off this whole area.
Full poly, a couple of neg air
machines, the whole bit.
OSHA won't let me start
until you guys clean up.
I have to get construction crews
in here by Columbus Day. How long?
These rooms, game room,
tunnels...
I would say three weeks, minimum.
Three weeks.
Two.
Two weeks.
- Two weeks.
You guys for hire?
What is it?
Two weeks.
- Two weeks.
- He's the captain, right?
You better believe it.
You've seen enough.
Need anything else?
What's all this, Bill?
They're punks. They come here,
get high, shoot guns.
- Destructive bastards.
- Shoot at what?
Hopefully, at each other.
- What is this?
- Phil, are you checking in?
Don't go in there without
your bathing suit.
This is seclusion.
That's what they called
the patients' rooms.
It was part of therapy
in the Seventies.
Art therapy, creative expression.
It helped them
with their self esteem!
Helped them feel good
about themselves. Creepy.
Shades of your childhood, huh?
There's a picture of me.
What was wrong with this woman?
I don't know.
Watch out for the broken glass.
I have a little time.
You want to check out the cemetery?
- 750 bodies bured there.
- Gentlemen...
I left the bag.
- You know where you're going?
- The bat wing, right?
- I'll see you down here.
- Okay.
- Gum?
- No, thanks.
Congratulations to you and Wendy
on your new addition.
Thanks, Bill.
I know how long you both...
Elizabeth and I are so happy.
- Want to see a picture?
- Yeah.
I'll show you my baby.
- She's just a doll.
- Emma.
Oh, yeah!
I'll match Yankee's bid.
This isn't how we do bidding
process. Deadline's Friday.
We'll be in on Monday
and out the following Monday.
- You said two weeks.
- One week. I've got 4 good guys.
I'll hire another one.
One week, we're gone.
One week? That's fast.
I'm good for it.
I need the job.
I really need this job.
Roses?
They're lovely!
What's the occasion, Gordon?
Genny is up and running, sir.
- Take the mask off, Hank.
- Are the A field levels safe?
Take it off, dickhead.
Go down to the tunnel,
Tag those ducks we saw this morning.
Use the green slime.
Red, right?
Those ducts are hazards.
- What?
- Red, right?
Yeah, red.
Phil, Amy says hi.
Keep it up, dickhead.
I'm just relaying information.
This morning in bed
she said to say hi to you.
- Keep it up.
- I got it. That's the problem.
How long have you been working
for Uncle Gordon?
- Five whole years.
- Was he a slave driver?
Gordon is a reasonable man.
I'm the slave driver.
Got a couple of rules.
Safety first, the job done second.
And... No drugs on the job.
What the hell is that?
Mike, will you show me the ropes?
- Is this the new guy?
- They call it Jeff.
It's Gordon's nephew.
- Gordy didn't tell you about these?
- What?
- You can't use these.
- Why not?
Music creates sonic vibrations.
Vibrations jiggle spooge dust
into the air.
It gets into your lungs.
Is this the music
you plan on listening to here?
- Yeah.
- You trying to kill us all?
Put it away or play
something else. Yanni or John Tesch.
I'll see you guys at lunch.
I'm going down deep.
Who's Yanni?
Gordy, you finally landed us
the perfect gig.
What we do is crazy.
We work in an insane asylum!
You should be grateful,
you're about to make decent money.
Five bucks an hour?
- Didn't you tell him?
- No. You tell him.
Ten thousand dollar bonus.
Gordon arranged it with the town.
What's the catch?
It's got to be finished by the 13th.
This Monday?
This is at least a two week job.
Exactly right.
We're going to work our asses off.
So, what is that?
Ten g's each?
If you don't like it Henry,
I'll give you a ride to the airport.
- Let it go.
- You taking Amy to the airport?
- She likes to travel.
- I know.
Hey guys! I have the keys
for the gate.
Thanks, man.
What do you think? Fifteen years
really does a number on a place.
There used to be over 2, 400
patients here at one point.
Why'd they close this place down?
Nearly all these places closed down
in the Eighties. The budgets cuts.
The Feds called it
Deinstitutionalization.
They just dumped the people
on the street?
Some. Some went to home care type
programs.
The loonies are out in the real world
and we've the keys to the loony bin.
It wasn't just the budget cuts.
What was it then, Mike?
Patricia Willard scandal, 1984.
I don't recall that.
Patricia Willard was committed here
in the 1970's by her parents.
Maniac depression, that sort
of thing. Typical adolescent crap.
But in the 1980's this Repressed
Memory Therapy took off.
The shrinks figured these
new techniques would release
hidden memories of traumatic events
like rape, incest.
So Patricia,
with the help of her doctors,
recalls that when she was ten,
her father raped her.
But not once, right?
No. Three times a week.
And he didn't just rape her.
He came into her room at night
wearing a black robe.
He drove her to a wooded area where
her grandparents and mother were.
They wore black robes. When they
took them off, orgies ensued.
And then they brought out
the newborn.
She was forced to watch as her
mother
cut a baby's heart out
with a stone dagger.
She'd drink the blood,
others would eat the flesh.
The grandfather and father
would fuck her repeatedly.
- She was forced to have abortions.
- Enough!
This happened here?
Yeah. Satanic Ritual Abuse Syndrome
was big in the Eighties.
Destroyed a lot of families.
Patricia was ready to sue hers.
It was set to go to trial, and...
- What?
- She dropped the suit.
Why?
Her parents found a physical exam
she'd undergone a year prior.
Turns out she was a virgin.
None of it happened. So the family
countersues, and they win.
That, and the budget cuts.
- Mike, is that story true?
- Yes.
- How do you know that stuff?
- My dad was a lawyer on the case.
His dad's the state attorney
general. Better watch yourself.
Hank, leave it alone.
You were supposed to carry
the torch too, huh?
Hank, drop it.
Were you on the one year plan?
- You need help with that?
- No, I'm fine.
- Jesus!
- Tough week-end?
I think I pulled a muscle.
Mike and I called you Saturday to
take you out for winning the bid.
That was nice.
I was catching up on sleep.
- Baby still have that ear thing?
- Yeah.
If we don't make Monday...
- Griggs likes jobs fast.
- What if we lose this bonus?
We won't.
I know where this is leading.
Jeff is young, but he isn't stupid.
I'm not talking about Jeff.
Saturday night we saw Craig McManus.
I told him about the bonus.
He said he would leave Yankee
and work for us.
He has more experience than Hank
and he gives a shit.
Your job here
is to eliminate obstacles.
That's what I'm trying to do.
Jesus, man.
We're talking about Hank.
If I thought he was a liability,
I'd let you sack him.
- I don't agree.
- I don't care!
- Let's finish the decon chamber.
- Fine.
- Alright.
- Go slow, turn right, slow...
Try to get straight!
You have to bring the nose down.
Don't look at me.
What are you, a lobotomy case?
Fuck you, man!
Slow down!
- Nice job.
- That wasn't me.
- Yeah.
- Fuck you.
- Just wait there.
- What?
Hang on.
What the hell?
Go down and check
the breaker box.
I can't do that.
Why?
I got nyctophobia.
- What?
- Fear of the dark.
Okay. I'll go check the breaker box.
Try not to break anything,
mullet head.
Thanks, man.
Damn!
- You okay?
- Yes, fine.
Good first day.
Mike needs another hour.
The genny's carburetor is acting up.
Okay, but I don't want anyone
around this place after dark.
Good first day, guys.
Keep up like this,
we'll be dead by Monday.
Fuck you, Phil!
See you in the morning.
I know this is difficult, Mary.
That's why we're here to help.
I miss Peter.
I miss him so much!
Mary, I want you to remember
what happened 22 years ago.
Christmas night in Lowell.
That's where we grew up.
Yes. What happened that night
in Lowell?
- Nothing happened!
- Mary, something did happen.
That's why we have these sessions,
to help you remember.
No, I can't remember.
File note. Patient shows
extreme agitation.
She is putting her fingers
in her mouth.
Will you share a doll,
Mister Doctor?
Who am I speaking with?
Mary Hobbes got a china doll
from her mother.
We can't find it now.
No, Princess, I haven't seen it.
- Maybe Billy knows!
- Silly Billy!
Princess, what happened on Christmas
22 years ago in Lowell?
We got presents.
Mary got a pretty china doll
and Peter got a big old knife.
Then what happened?
Mary's mommy and daddy
went to sleep.
We played upstairs.
Peter turned off the lights
and hid. Mary tried to find him.
Who played upstairs?
Mary and Peter,
and me and Billy, silly!
Has Billy told you
what happened next?
Billy only tells me nice things.
Like that I am pretty.
Princess,
was Simon there that night?
I don't know any Simon.
Billy never told you about Simon?
No.
I'm tired, Mister Doctor.
Maybe Billy would like to talk now.
Billy is asleep.
He's asleep.
You can hear me.
Genny's topped off
and running.
Good. I don't want her dying on us.
- Put your mask on, Princess.
- I'm not your princess.
- What?
- What's up with Phil and Hank?
What's up with Phil and Hank?
Hank stole Phil's girlfriend.
You don't want to get involved.
Don't get on Phil's bad side.
He'll give you the grunt work.
1884.
1883. Fuck!
Hank, come back.
Yeah, Hank here.
I want you with Jeff and Mike
after lunch.
Alright. Hank out.
Got your wallet.
Nice grab. Ladies,
thank Uncle Gordy for lunch.
Thanks.
Your turn tomorrow.
Where's Mike?
The equipment room,
looking for those lost cartridges.
I don't want anyone around here
by themselves!
- It won't happen again.
- Do you have my scratch tickets?
I have them right here.
Hank's scratch tickets.
There's one.
These are jubilee.
You know I play Blackjack.
- Yeah to you too.
- Fuck you!
Mary, come in.
I can't talk anymore.
I am too tired.
Miss Hobbes is entering
a dissociative state,
rubbing her eyes,
switching to a remote personality.
- Mike, come back.
- I'll be right there.
- Mary?
- Hello, sir.
Hello, Billy.
How have you been?
Never better, sir.
Billy, where does the princess live?
- In the tongue.
- Why the tongue?
Because she's always talking, sir.
And where do you live?
I live in the eyes. You know that.
Remind me. Why the eyes?
Because I see everything.
And where does Simon live?
Where does Simon?
What's mortified pride?
Three patients were committed
in 1889 for mortified pride.
1889. Where'd you get this?
Under some boxes. They left a lot
of shit in this place.
When Phil calls lunch,
it means lunch.
No cartridges. I have to pick some
up at Grossman's.
Listen to this. 17 were committed
due to disappointed expectations.
They're talking about you. They
would've committed your ass then.
What do you have to do now to get
committed? Mortify someone's pride?
Simple.
You kill someone.
That won't get you committed.
That'll get you in jail.
If you get caught.
John Hinkley, temporary insanity.
He's in a nut house.
That defense never works. Most
people are conscious when they kill.
Homicide requires a motive.
How did you fail law school?
You're good.
What are you?
A lobotomy case?
Jeff, come on.
Toe me!
We're just fucking around.
Sorry, Mike.
The Ice Pick method.
Insert a thin metal pipette
into the orbitalfrontal cortex
and enter the soft tissue
of the frontal lobe.
A few simple smooth,
up and down jerks
to sever the kateral hypothalamus.
Resulting in a rapid reduction
of stress for our patient.
Total time elapsed, two minutes.
Only side effect?
- A black eye.
- Recommended treatment.
Sun glasses.
- Brilliant! Very good.
- Alright. Let's get back to work.
I wasn't kidding.
You should use your head, buddy.
I have to get a part
from Gordon's van.
Make sure mullet head
knows how to operate that thing.
Mike, don't forget this.
- You know how to ride a lawn mower?
- Yeah.
We just had a break.
Push it to that mid section there.
I am taking a smoke break.
We just had a break.
- What's up?
- You know what a whale is?
Yeah, I know.
A whale is a big time gambler.
I have a buddy
who deals out at Foxwoods.
12 hours and this whale has the
house down three hundred grand.
This guy leaves, takes his car keys
and drops them in my friend's pocket.
- You know what they're for?
- What?
Porsche 911.
And that was the tip.
Fucking tip!
What's your point?
I have an exit plan.
If you stick with this job too long,
it will mess you up.
It gets inside and stresses you.
You see?
Already a piece of this shit
may have gone into your lungs.
It incubates in your lungs and tissue
grows around it like a pearl.
Like a time bomb.
By the time you hit 30...
You're drowning in
your own lung fluid.
You're not even wearing
your mask now.
- Where's your mask?
- Me?
No, I've learned.
I have an exit plan.
I have a way of dealing
with the stress.
You think Mike
reads all those books for fun?
He has an exit plan, I tell you.
If the stress gets too intense
on this job,
he'll go back and finish law school.
He'll pass the bar
and make his dad proud.
That's his exit plan.
Phil's got his stress reducer.
He's got this plan.
He'll tell you about it some day.
Then there's Uncle Gordo.
If he didn't get this gig,
he'd have to fold H.E.G.
He can't even have an exit plan.
Fiber has always been his life.
It was over there. It is here.
Imagine that stress.
Let me tell you something.
You better hope
to have some of Gordo's genes.
Gordo is the Zen master of calm.
I've never seen old Gordo
lose it.
I don't know. In the last few months
I've seen some cracks.
I worry.
Mikey knows what I'm talking about,
right?
He does have the new baby.
Should be the joy of his life.
When you and Amy have a kid,
you'll see how hard it is.
Me and Amy?
I just fuck her to beat on Phil.
Get off your ass.
I want my bonus.
Hi, Wendy?
I know, but we need to talk.
We have to.
Would you let me finish.
Hello?
Baby needs a new pair of shoes.
Let's do this thing.
Silver.
Yeah, gold.
Fucking eyeballs.
They ought to be worth something.
Check that out.
What the hell is that?
Oh, God!
Fucking birds!
Jesus.
So what's the verdict?
I'm getting nothing. He didn't leave
his answering service on.
- You try Amy's yet?
- Do you know her number?
I'll try information.
Give me the phone.
I know the number.
Give me the phone!
Thank you.
Hi, it's me.
Yeah.
Wait a second.
What?
What are you talking about?
When did this happen?
Really?
Hang in there. I'll call you back.
Our favorite piece of shit, Hank,
went to Amy's last night.
He packed his car,
told her he found his meal
ticket,
and he bolted to Miami
to Casino School.
That lucky fuck!
Probably scored on a scratch.
I warned her, didn't l?
She said he left
without saying anything?
It's Hank.
He's totally unreliable.
Call Craig
and see if he's still available.
This is a blessing. We replace
this asshole and move forward.
Something is not right here.
What's the matter?
You know those two guys
you were talking to yesterday?
- What guys?
- I saw you.
- What were you talking about?
- What is this?
- I'm asking you a question.
- Okay.
- You're questioning my performance?
- Should I be?
- Call McManus.
- Don't walk away from me!
Don't ever walk away from me.
You're going to hit me?
You think I'm doing a bad job,
Mike?
No, you're doing fine.
This used to be a great deal.
Steady gigs, joking around,
beers after work.
It says here that eight were
committed for uncontrolled passion.
Then Emma came.
That's why we lost
the last two gigs.
He's tired and he overbid.
- Gordon loves being a father.
- Yeah, now he does.
But it was never in his heart.
This was Wendy's idea.
Look, Phil...
When you say you don't want something
it doesn't mean you don't want it.
Six years ago I didn't want to be
a lawyer, but now...
Wait.
Who are you kidding?
You shuck fiber with us.
It's not what I am talking about.
I am talking about fatherhood.
It's fucking his job up. He should've
canned Hank's ass 6 months ago.
What are you looking at?
Where are you going?
- To take a piss.
- You got twenty-five!
Hello, Wendy?
Can we talk?
I want to ask you something.
Can you forgive me?
Uncle Gordon!
Hello?
- Sorry.
- Hey, man.
I didn't see you on the phone.
- Sit down.
- Thanks.
I just came
to thank you
for giving me this job.
- I'll bust my ass for you.
- I know that.
Don't stress out.
Things will work out.
- I'm hear for you.
- Yeah.
- Family, man.
- Was that Aunt Wendy?
- Yeah.
- How's she doing?
- She's good.
She's tired, you know?
- Kids tire you out sometimes.
- Yeah, I know.
- My dad got the christening photos.
- Yeah?
- Emma looks really pissed off.
- She's pretty pissed.
Why are you crying, Mary?
I miss my family.
How come they don't visit?
How did you get those scars
on your chest?
How many times should I tell you?
- I fell off my bike.
- Is that what you remember?
Yes!
Can you tell me
who the Princess is?
- I have no idea.
- And who is Billy?
I don't know anyone
named Billy.
- Who is Simon?
- I have no idea who Simon is!
- I'm sick of this!
- Calm down.
I want to go back to my room!
Mary is asleep, sir.
Billy, tell me what happened
in Lowell. I know you saw it.
You know perfectly well.
Mary needs to know what happened
to remember.
- No!
- Simon might like to tell me.
- He's asleep.
- Help me wake him up.
- No!
- We must wake up Simon.
- I'm too scared!
- Billy, we have to wake up Simon.
Take a shower, Gordon. Don't go home
with that shit on you.
What is the stupidest thing
you've ever done?
You mean besides working for you?
I would have to say...
Introducing Hank to Amy.
That was pretty stupid.
I wish I had that one back.
I hit Wendy.
What?
Friday night. I wanted to celebrate
getting this job.
I had flowers and champagne.
I went into the kitchen.
She was cooking pasta.
I wanted to kiss her.
She turned around and a pot
of boiling water poured on my leg.
I don't know if it was
the dog barking
or Emma crying,
but I slapped her.
I hit my wife.
I love my wife.
It was an accident.
I never slapped her before.
I've tried to talk to her on
the phone, but she won't listen.
Where are you staying?
A motel.
You're going to tell the other guys
about this?
Oh, come on.
You're right about Craig.
You should call him.
Those kids, the other day...
I talked to those graffiti artists
and they won't be coming back.
I said, if I see you again,
I'm calling Security.
So, that's taken care of.
Okay.
Hang in there.
Take a shower.
Take the shit off of you.
Hello, Gordon.
Do you know who I am?
Roses?
They're lovely!
What's the occasion, Gordon?
Not here. Later.
Watch out!
Do it!
- You're up early.
- Yeah.
I wasn't the only one
who couldn't sleep.
Craig's coming in tomorrow.
You okay?
I want to go home.
I am going inside.
I have to go.
It's going to get ugly.
Jesus!
- Jeff, what did you do?
- It wasn't me!
I'm going to check the breakers.
- What?
- Take a break with me.
- I have to check the breakers.
- Let the kid do it.
He can't. He's got nychtophobia.
Alright.
Fuck it.
- We have a problem.
- What?
We have a problem
and this is not easy for me.
- Look at me. It's not easy.
- Alright.
- We need to talk about Gordon.
- What about him?
He needs to take some time off.
- Why?
- Because he's becoming a liability.
I can see you are paranoid.
Do you know that he hit his wife?
He hit Wendy.
I've got Craig coming tomorrow.
If he hears about this,
you know what that means?
You want to lose this gig?
That's what will happen.
- So what do we do?
- You listen to me.
I don't give a shit what happens.
I'm in charge now.
- When will you do this?
- It might happen Saturday.
We were talking
about your nephew.
You know, how he's coming along.
And how is he coming along?
Hey, hello!
You're in deep shit,
you know that?
What are you doing here?
Me? Everyone thinks you're in Miami
in that Casino School.
Gordon and Phil want your head!
Did you score on a scratch?
What are you doing here?
I forgot something.
I'll be back.
He just needs a little motivation.
What do you think?
I think he's a little slow.
But Craig is coming
and we'll pick up slack.
He may be party in the back, but I'll
make sure he's business in the front.
- What time is it?
- I think it's noon.
- Lunch time.
- Yeah.
Want to place the order?
Yeah, sure.
I think it's Phil's turn.
- Fuck it. Let's flip for it.
- What?
- Let's flip for it.
- Where'd you get that?
Found it.
It might even be worth something.
- You found it?
- Yep.
Heads or tails?
Heads.
Tails. Get going, loser.
What?
Hey, uncle!
I found Hank!
What do you want?
- I found Hank.
- What the fuck are you saying?
I saw Hank in the stairwell.
He was standing there.
- Don't be a fucking idiot.
- I swear I saw him!
If he's in Miami,
why would he be here?
- I saw him!
- Get to work. We'll bring you lunch.
- Where was he?
- Next to the equipment room.
You believe this punk?
For Christ's sake, Mike!
This is so God damn ridiculous.
If he's in Miami,
why would he be here?
- Ask him yourself. Right up there.
- We are going to do that.
- That is where I am taking you.
- We're going to do that.
- He's up there.
- Where is he?
He was standing right there.
It's weird, but he's right here.
Right where?
I swear he was.
Why would I make this up?
Nice going, Jeff.
You heard me on the phone with Amy.
She said Hank went to Miami.
We all heard it, right?
No, we didn't.
What?
- I want to go to lunch.
- You stay where you are.
- What are you saying?
- You told us that.
We heard you on the phone,
but we didn't hear Amy.
So she wasn't on the phone?
This is what I'm talking about.
- Mike, give me that cell phone.
- Why?
- I want to talk to Amy.
- You don't need to speak to Amy.
- Give me the cell phone.
- Don't give it to him.
- That's what I'm trying to tell you.
- Give me the cell phone.
- He's losing it.
Give me the cell phone!
- What the fuck was that?
- It's Hank!
Jeff, Mike, go downstairs. Make sure
he doesn't come. You come with me.
Fuck you!
You come with me. Let's go.
Come on.
- You go that way.
- The tunnels are safer.
Safer?
This could be anybody.
Squatters, kids.
Phil, slow down.
He's not down here.
God!
Did you hear that?
I heard something down there.
No, it's this way.
- I'm going down. Follow up top.
- Mike, we stick to...
Fuck this.
What the fuck are we doing here?
So fucking stupid!
Why?
I don't hear anything.
Give me a torch.
This is fucking dumb.
He is not down there.
Shut up! If you hear anything,
call me.
- I left my walkie in the van!
- Stay there!
- Phil, wait!
- What, Jeff?
When I saw Hank, I think he had
blood on his hand.
Stay there.
Billy, you understand
that you, the Princess and Simon
are all in Mary?
Yes.
If Mary is sick,
then all of you are sick.
- You want Mary to get better, huh?
- Yes!
So, help her.
Tell me about the night in Lowell.
We were playing hide n' seek.
Mary was looking for her new doll
and Peter.
It was real dark.
No, I won't tell!
Mary's a good girl.
She doesn't need to know!
- What?
- What Simon did!
To who?
To Peter!
What did Simon do to Peter?
- I won't tell!
- Tell me.
Fuck!
What are you doing here?
- I need to talk to Simon.
- He made me do it.
It was awful.
- We need to wake up Simon.
- No, it was awful!
Wake up Simon.
What are you doing here?
Phil, I think I found Hank.
Gordon, come back.
- Yeah.
- Where are you?
- Ward A. Third floor.
- I'm coming.
Hello, doc.
Simon?
Do you know who I am?
Billy told me a lot about you.
Billy is a smart boy.
What happened on Christmas night
in Lowell?
Use your imagination.
I'd rather you tell me, Simon.
Peter was naughty.
What did Peter do?
He shouldn't have done it.
Tell me, Simon.
He scared Mary.
He crept up behind her in the dark.
And he scared her.
Mary fell down.
She fell on her doll.
It cut her up.
It cut her up real bad.
She needed someone to help her.
So I introduced myself.
I told her to cut up Peter.
Do it, Mary.
To cut him up real bad.
Good thing his knife was brand new.
Real sharp.
And then, just so her mommy
and daddy wouldn't get mad.
I told her to cut them up to.
There was a lot of blood.
So much blood.
But Mary wanted to do it.
Do it, Mary!
So she did it.
Gordon, come back, please.
Who is that?
It's Jeff. I am by the van.
I was freaking out.
The lights went out.
I got these in the van.
Is that okay?
Come back.
This is Gordon.
We found the one responsible.
You've got to be kidding.
It's beautiful.
Hello? Hello?
Your man is here.
Where are you guys?
I mean he...
He was a liability.
Who did this?
He brought it on himself.
It's typical of Hank.
Wrong place at the wrong time.
You did this.
I need you to wake up
and take a really
good look at him.
What are you doing here?
It's okay.
Hang in there. It's me.
We'll get you some help.
I wouldn't tell anybody about this.
If they find out about Hank,
they'll find out about the others.
You did this.
What are you doing here?
You hired those guys, didn't you?
You're asleep.
- You hired them to kill him.
- You are asleep.
- Where are the others?
- Open your eyes.
- Where are they?
- You've got to wake up.
- Tell me where they are.
- Would you wake up?
- Tell me.
I am fucking awake!
Who are you talking to?
I'm a little confused here.
What is it?
Do it Gordon
What are you doing?
Why did you do it Simon?
Because Mary let me Doc.
They always do.
What are you doing here?
You know what I wouldn't do?
I wouldn't mention this to anyone.
I wouldn't tell anybody about this.
If they find out about Hank
they'll find out about the others.
I found Hank. He's hurt and said
you did it to him.
Who did this?
He brought it on himself.
Wrong place at the wrong time.
Where are the others?
Gordy, you are asleep.
Uncle Gordy!
Wake up!
I'm sorry I was freaking out.
I got these in your van.
Is that okay?
I need you to open your eyes now.
Wake up.
And remember.
Roses?
They're lovely!
What's the occasion, Gordon?
Not here, Gordon. Later.
Watch out!
Gordon, look out!
Stop, Gordon!
Do it, Gordon.
Do it now.
Wendy, it's me.
Please don't hang up.
I just want to say how
sorry I am for what happened.
I am so sorry.
I am so lonely here.
I want to come home.
I want to hold you.
I want to hold my baby.
Can you forgive me?
Where do you live,
Simon?
I live in the weak and the wounded.
Doc.