Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.Addic7ed.com/
Hey.
I'm... no,
I'm not touching it.
I don't pick up the phone
while I masturbate...
Unless I'm at work.
A drink now?
No.
No, I can't.
I can't be late
for work tomorrow.
Here. To freedom!
Thanks, teen.
That tasted like
paint thinner and ass.
Mine was like
intercourse and tears.
Oh, well,
I wouldn't know.
I don't remember
what sex tastes like.
Like chicken.
Wait. How long has it been?
- Six weeks.
- Wow.
Six whole weeks...
You're like a born-again virgin.
Look, Jason,
it's just a bad streak.
You've always been
a streaker.
Remember senior year?
In one weekend, you hooked up
with that a.E.Phi pledge,
the german girl
with the thing on her thing,
and Dr. Phil.
- Who?
- The lady Hitler,
the chick
with the little moustache.
Debbie Lee.
Right.
No, I mean, that
was a good week for me,
but being a streaker
isn't what I'm worried about.
Seriously, Tina,
this could be bad.
Got any weed?
I'm just saying,
it's like,
this little dry spell
could easily turn
into the drought of the decade.
I don't know.
Something's off.
I feel, like,
a disturbance in the force.
Maybe you should stop
making star wars references.
Here, I'm high.
Yeah, I'm high too.
Like I could eat
a wheel of cheese high.
As long as you're not on your
"I need to check my testicles
"for lumps" high again.
Can we get out of here, please?
Being in here makes me feel
like I have to poop.
Ew.
It's Brett.
I might go let him
give me a foot massage.
By "foot massage,"
I mean sex.
Just talk to that girl.
Go be funny.
Funny to girls
is like boobs to boys.
Smell ya later.
Smell you.
Hi. I'm Jason,
the guy who's been
staring at you.
Yeah, I thought
I was gonna have to use my mace.
That would've been
so embarrassing.
I mean,
it's all about tasers now.
Mace is so over.
It's like toe rings
or the Lindsay Lohan
legging collection.
Or glaciers
or marine life in the Gulf.
Whoa. You just got
a little dark there.
"I'm a loner, dottie.
A rebel."
Pee wee's big adventure?
Oh, my God.
That's, like, the best movie
starring a sex offender ever.
Mm.
So what do you do
when you're not out
being a bar hero?
Uh, yeah...
I drive Nascar, actually...
- Oh.
- Daytona, Talladega...
Oh, my God.
Are you danica Patrick?
Yes.
No, but same cheekbones.
Same boobs, too.
You're really funny.
So are you.
Shall we continue being funny
over another drink?
Indeed we shall.
Help me
take my shirt off,
and I'll help you
with your pants.
Deal.
Oh, my God.
This is too perfect.
What if you're scamming me
so you can steal
my discover card
in the middle
of the night?
I mean, what if you're really,
like, a sexy transsexual
and later I discover,
oops, you have a penis?
I mean, that's always been
a secret fear of mine.
I'm all girl,
and no one takes discover.
You're safe.
You know,
I do have a bed.
Let's do it
in your fridge!
Come on!
Hurry. It kind of
smells in here.
What a fantastic email
this is gonna make tomorrow.
So do you think
I'm a slut?
Only in the best,
most positive way.
Listen, I had, like,
a really great time last night,
but I have
a confession to make.
I lied. I don't
actually drive stock cars.
- I lied, too.
- I'm not really a woman.
Technically you are.
I didn't see
any boy parts,
and I double-checked.
I'd make breakfast,
but I know for a fact
you don't have any food
in your fridge.
We could go get some coffee.
Whoa, it's 9:00?
I'm so late.
Is it okay if I borrow these?
Uh, yeah.
I hate when my doorman
sees me in the same clothes
from the day before.
- It happens a lot, huh?
- Ha ha.
Hey, could I...
Could I get your number?
Or should I
just stalk you?
Actually,
I'm kind of lazy.
I think maybe a number
might work better.
Okay.
See you around.
Definitely.
Yes! Ohh!
Hey, how are you,
boss?
I feel like
a thousand dollars...
Which is 900 more than I have
in my checking account.
But whatever. I feel great.
What are you doing?
New security.
No one will be robbed, raped,
or murdered in this store...
Not again.
That's a good slogan, man.
You should put that on the door.
Yeah.
Hey, how do you even know
how to do that?
Well, back home I worked
at a video business.
Had a beautiful, big-breasted
girlfriend there, man.
It's hard for a man
to be alone, Jason.
Well, here we say,
"no man is an island."
Oh, in my country it's...
"Ugly girl blames mirror."
Yeah, that's not really
the same thing.
Yes, it is.
I need an egg sandwich,
and I need it now.
Ooh, you need
antibacterial soap
and a barbecue brush.
You need
a pregnancy test.
Don't toy with me.
I'm fragile.
Okay, whore friend
of Jason.
He never remembers
my name.
So you had fun last night
with Brett, huh?
Yeah. Let's just say
I introduced him to God.
You?
What happened?
It happened.
The dry spell is over!
Great!
I had sex
with that girl last night
in my  refrigerator!
Yay! Congrats.
You're back, man.
I am. I'm back!
God, I feel stronger
and more confident,
like one of those guys in
the hair transplant commercials.
No, you'd really like
this girl, teen.
I mean,
I really like this girl.
She's cute,
and she's funny,
and she's
surprisingly filthy.
These are a few
of your favorite things.
Yeah, but she's, like,
pretty perfect.
And I played it
totally cool.
I was like this young
James Van Der Beek.
Er! Uh, that's
your gold standard?
- Yeah.
- Well, way to go, Dawson.
Wait. I have
a question for you.
I was going through
Brett's wallet this morning...
Whoa. Wait. You were
fishing through his wallet?
Would you ever
carry with you
a frozen yogurt
frequent eater's card?
I got to get to work,
psycho.
Well, there's
nine punches on it!
Nine punches?
Gay.
Wait. Let me guess...
Dentist appointment.
Sorry. I'm late.
You know, I think
I have sleep apnea.
Webmd says I'm, like,
a prime candidate.
Oh, no problem.
I'm just gonna start docking
your pay when you're late.
Really?
Yeah, really.
It's not a democracy, Jay.
I am pharaoh.
You are Jew.
Now, go do your job
and build me a pyramid.
Everybody's waiting on you.
You know, JB,
I actually am jewish.
Oh, great.
Happy Hanukah.
Also,
the toilet's clogged,
so go part
the brown sea, Moses.
Clean it
like you mean it,
like you know
we're in a recession
and I get emailed a lot
of qualified resumes.
By the way,
this guy's too tall.
This one's just right.
Okay, uh,
you'll be playing,
um, a piece of fruit.
Doesn't say what kind,
but they want to see you dance.
How the
does fruit dance?
Happy?
Hi, janey.
It's Jason.
Ugh.
Hola, janey.
Como estas?
Jesus.
Van Der Beek, Van Der Beek,
Van Der Beek...
May I help you?
Hi. Uh, is...
Is Jane there?
This is patakan thai.
- Um, is this 555-0114?
This is
thai restaurant, okay?
Crap.
May I help you?
Uh, yeah.
Um, could I have an order
to be delivered?
- Moshi-moshi.
Fridge girl
stole my pants.
Here, everyone,
meet my new girlfriend.
- You've introduced us to worse.
- How are you doing, Jay?
Do you have
post-pants depression?
No, but...
I really thought
she was into me.
I mean, why would she
borrow my pants
if she was just
gonna blow me off?
People take
sex trophies, Jay.
I mean, it happens
all the time.
It's true.
Most of my dish rags
are from previous lovers.
- I still have my junior-high
boyfriend's retainer.
- Ew.
- Well, on the bright side,
at least my career is off
to an excellent start.
Yeah, it's been
a real banner day.
Why haven't you
called Scott yet, Jay?
I mean, I told him
you were gonna call,
like, three months ago.
Wait. You want him
to take career advice
from Scott lenchner,
the guy who asked me
to role-play school bus driver/
sexy slow girl?
Yeah, well, lench
was just trying to be funny.
You know, I'm gonna call him
this week, stace.
- Good.
- Or you'll see him
at Stacey's
big birthday bash...
If we ever decide
what we're doing.
Look, it's my first birthday
in New York,
and I just want to do
something fun.
You know, with us
both in grad school,
we barely go out
anymore.
Yeah. You remember
back in the dorm
when sloppy Stacey
used to be so punk rock?
I was not sloppy.
I just had low tolerance because
I wasn't eating much then.
But speaking of rock,
I decided what I want to do
for my birthday.
The band waves is holding
a super-secret show,
and I think
we should all go,
get drunk, and dance.
Cool.
You, uh... you like waves?
Yeah. Why?
They're hip.
They're new. They're loud.
Oh, screw you guys.
I know cool bands.
Anyway, the show
is sold out,
but I found this guy
on craigslist
that still has tickets.
Jay, can you do me
a huge favor
and go meet him outside
music hall tomorrow at 10:00?
We've got
the tennis championship.
Yeah, we're bringing home
the gold, bitches.
What! Boom!
Yeah, sure.
I can do that.
Can you see if you
can get one for Brett, too?
I thought you only
slept with that guy
'cause he's got
air conditioning.
Yeah, but now
I like him.
Plus, it's been
really muggy lately.
- Well, I'll be going solo
and pants-less.
Maybe it'll be
a good look for me.
Just get over
the pants girl, Jay.
Yeah, look,
it's time to reevaluate,
time to heal.
Yeah, exactly. So we'll
all go out this week
and help you
find a new girl,
someone who thinks
that irony
is something
that tastes like metal...
You know, a simple girl
that you can confuse
into banging you.
You are a special,
special friend.
Start your boner, Jay.
It's on.
Hang on, hang on.
Uh, spare some change, sir?
Dude, we have
the same phone.
Hey, lench.
- Jay-bone, all right!
- Hey, thanks for meeting me.
- No worries. No worries.
But I got to be quick.
I have to start
setting up.
- For what?
- Seriously?
You need to start
following my tweets.
We're throwing a banger tonight
in honor of our first issue.
Hold on. Boom.
E-vited.
So what exactly do you guys
do here, by the way?
We're launching
a magazine
that focuses on
environmental sustainability...
- Wow.
- And hot chicks.
Calling it all naturals.
Think models
with '70s-era bush
in hemp bikinis,
teaching you how to compost.
You know, I didn't know
you loved the planet.
- Sure.
- It's a  gold mine.
But you, you need
some career advice?
Yeah, well,
it's a little embarrassing,
but right now I'm,
like, a receptionist.
- Whoa.
- Yeah. It's not cancer,
but it's just a b.S. Job
till I figure out, like,
what I want to do
with my life.
Lately I've been thinking
about music journalism.
I don't even really know
where to begin.
I just can't spend
the rest of my life
doing something
I don't like
just to get little
green bits of paper.
You know what I mean?
- Fully. But you ran out
the clock there, Jay-bone.
I got to bounce.
Look, let me think on it.
Maybe I know someone
who could be your savior.
Great. Really?
I'm pretty popular
right now, Jay.
I'm rolling with
super-hot locavore sluts
and delicious
raw-milk cheeses.
People want to hang
with lench.
Oh.
Digame.
Yo. Your boy lench
says hi.
Oh, spectacular jackass,
isn't he?
Full metal douche bag.
But he is throwing
a party tonight.
Oh. That'll probably be
chock full of sluts.
Perfect. Game on.
Cool. I'm just gonna have
to pop out in the middle
and buy the tickets.
Oh, okay.
Aah!
Oh. Great!
Now I look like
the world's tallest baby.
This place is teeming
with sustainable hos.
Got to hand it
to lench, though.
It's kind of cool.
There he is.
So is, uh,
everything dreadlocked?
Shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh.
Let me be surprised.
Ugh.
What up?
Oh, shoot.
It's already 10:00.
I should go and buy the tickets.
Wait, wait.
Look.
- What?
- Cute dorks.
It's time to harvest.
Hi.
Great party, right?
Awesome.
I'm Spencer.
Thumbelina.
I like your shirt.
I like your potentially
clouded judgment.
So what brings you
to this party?
We work here in legal.
Jill, what do you want?
- Lawyers.
- Yeah.
They're probably clean
and will leave early.
You take jacoby.
I'll take meyers.
- Whoa. What about Brett?
- If our relationship
can't weather
a minor indiscretion
with a handsome dork,
then what chance do we have?
You know, I hear
there's a spot here
where you can churn
your own butter.
Let's find it.
Are you expecting a call?
No, there's
just something
I should really
be doing right now.
God, I should probably go.
Oh, that's too bad,
'cause there was something
I was really hoping
to be doing tonight, too.
But I can't do it alone.
- Mine!
- Got it.
- Yes!
- Mine! Ugh!
No, don't do it!
- Match point!
- Where is your head right now?
Where is my head?
That was all yours.
- That was not mine.
- Hey, game point.
Your serve.
Listen to me.
We are not losing
to "before"
and "after."
What, what!
- Copy?
- I copy.
- Okay.
- All right.
Locked and loaded, baby.
White lightning.
Chocolate thunder.
♪ I'm gonna text you
♪ So I don't do it
when I'm high♪
♪ I'm gonna sex you
Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
Okay.
I'm not gonna have sex
with you.
I don't let guys
just stick their penis in me
all Willie-nillie.
Know that.
- I'd never stick my penis
in you all Willie-nillie.
Okay, I respect
your boundaries.
Ow! Ow! If you bite me
one more time,
I swear I'm gonna
nut-punch you!
- Feel my sword.
- Your sword? What, is it sharp?
Oh, my God.
Dude, you seem okay.
I don't know.
Maybe you plan on skinning me
and turning me
into a girl suit,
but either way,
I'm not going to your place.
Come on,
it'll be totally cool.
Look, it could be frozen
and covered with sprinkles.
It's not gonna happen.
I've kind of
got this thing going
with this
poet/chocolatier.
I don't want to ruin it.
But if you want to pay
for the cab,
you can do
a little taxi-touching.
- Come on.
- Dude, take the deal.
Otherwise, a hand job
is a man's job,
and you can get out at the light
and mime a vagina.
Could... could...
Could you do me a favor?
Could you stick your finger
in my ass?
Okay.
How's that
working for you?
Could you try
your thumb?
God. You just never know
how the day's gonna end, do ya?
Whoa!
You okay, boss?
Not emotionally.
Do you sell splints?
What is a splints?
Meyers is
a frickin' vampire.
- Whoa.
- Hello, Tina.
See, I'm being nice
to you today
because of your
festering neck wound.
Yeah, well,
"whore friend of Jason"
is actually
way more appropriate.
What's up
with your thumb?
Jacoby's ass.
Her sphincter had the grip
of a merchant marine.
This pervy lawyer
just made Jane look better,
by the way,
so thank you, Tina.
Well, be prepared
to up your bummer level.
Stacey just called me.
Apparently the craigslist guy
sold the tickets
to somebody else.
Oh, no.
That is not good.
No.
She is pissed.
- Well, I-I got to figure
something out.
- Shingles.
- No.
Come on,
you know this one.
It's hot.
Oh, I'm so...
Ah! Ah!
Stage 4 melanoma.
Yes! Dream team!
Okay, next.
That is, um...
That's, uh...
That's... damn it.
Stand by.
Oh, yeah,
you got to see this.
Come on.
He's pulling a cusack.
Come on, man!
- You ruined my birthday!
- I can fix it! I have a plan!
Oh, yeah, Jay,
that's really you...
The man with the plan.
No, really,
I have one.
You're gonna
forgive him, right?
Ah, it's Jason.
Jay...
Whoa, whoa. Let's see
how long he stays out there.
Oh!
I don't care
if I'm getting older.
My man's gonna be a doctor
and give me free botox.
I'm gonna keep you
young forever, babe.
You're gonna be
my own little Heidi montag.
Hey.
How's your thumb?
Uh, surprisingly sore.
How is your neck wound?
- Uh, itchy.
- Ooh.
Wow, Jay!
This place looks great!
Nice comeback.
Ooh! How much money did you
spend on these dumplings?
Uh, almost all of it.
Oh.
- A crock-pot?
Eric, how did you know?
Oh, I knew.
Oh, those two
are so in love...
Very boring, slow-cooked,
but very tender love.
Speaking of love,
where's Brett?
Was it the minor
dork indiscretion?
No, I found
a coldplay cd.
- Yeah, that's that.
- Yeah.
Oh, in all my excitement,
I, uh... I forgot
to buy Stacey a present.
Oh, and yet
she's still getting a gift
from the both of us.
I put your name
on the card.
It's just another one
you owe me for.
Wait.
What was the first one?
I figured you could use
a fresh pair.
Have fun
getting them dirty.
Thank you, Tina.
- Tina...
- Ugh.
Here.
Hey, look.
Look.
I know, right?
I was like,
"where is your ear?"
You didn't hear me.
♪ I won't fight
♪ I will not conquer
♪ I won't try
to impress your mother♪
♪ I will not dine out late
with father♪
? We won't sip wine...
Oh, sweet Jesus.
That girl
really got to you, huh?
No.
I just want my pants back.
No, that's all I want.
I know you're gonna pick
that up after everybody leaves.
And what,
do some c.S.I. Crap?
Wake up, everybody!