(Car horns)
(Crash)
(Radio) '..in downtown Los Angeles
right now. Here with the traffic...'
I've been waiting for 15 minutes.
- Thought you were stuck in traffic?
- You late?
- You got all the paperwork?
- Yeah.
Are you pissed off at me?
I'm just doing my part.
- I know, I know.
- You're my guy, Jerry, my guy.
'Margolese Holdings,
how may I direct your call? '
- Yes, I'll put you through.
- Hey, Estelle.
Is that Nayman's little nephew?
- Yeah, that's Big Tom.
- Big Tom! Sure, it is?
- How's it goin' there, Big Tom?
- Hey, hey. Look.
Shh. See? See?
Why are you scaring the kid?
- I-I was just...
- Did you get that passport?
Yes.
- I have issues.
- Issues, Jerry.
It burns my ass to write you
a check every week.
I can explain what happened.
You say that
when it's once in a while.
- It's every time, Jerry.
- It's every fuckin' time.
And I can certainly
understand that perspective.
But I've been having
some personal problems...
uh, with my life.
My girlfriend, she's a great girl,
but she has complaints.
I don't but, she does.
If you want to know the truth,
I can't even believe this,
but we go to a group.
So...last week,
when you guys told me to pick up
the thing at the thing,
well, Samantha says she needs
the car to pick up some things.
And, I don't have to tell you boys,
I mean, things got heated, right?
And she hid them.
She hid them?
Oh! The keys. She hid them.
She... You know, and I couldn't
get to the thing on time,
and it all got messed up
and I think that maybe...
Maybe some things
aren't meant to happen.
Jerry, you're a fucking moron.
Here are your options. Number one,
I roll you up in a carpet,
stuff you in a Sedan
and set fire to you.
- You with me? Choice one.
- Yeah.
Number two. You like sex and travel?
What, you like to have sex?
You like to travel?
Get on a flight to Mexico. All the
hookers you can shake your stick at.
Pick up a pistol
that belongs to Margolese.
- What's it gonna be?
- OK, I was under the impression
with Margolese getting out of jail,
that the last job was my last job.
- You fucked up that job.
- You fucked it up.
This job will be your last job.
OK, but a trip right now...
He asked for you. Want me to call him
and say you can't go?
Because I'll call. I'd love to.
You're goin' on a fucking trip.
The town's called San Miguel.
You look for a kid in a bar,
the El Alamo.
This is a simple fucking task.
Write it down. Roll up your sleeves.
- Get involved!
- Ow!
The kid's name is Beck. He's got this
particular gun. He's waiting on you.
- Beck.
- When you find him, bring him
and the gun back Stateside, got it?
Last chance, Jerry.
I'm telling you. The last.
Even he's getting tired of your shit.
I'll take care of it, Bernie.
Vaya con Dios, motherfucker.
You're in coach.
Baby, what are you doing?
You said this was your last job!
What do you want me to say?
"Sorry I can't,
"the old lady wants me to quit.
Fuck off."
Yes! Something like that.
Like exactly!
I'm not in insurance, sweetie!
If you get on that plane, you will
never, never, ever see me again.
You got me?
We talked about this. I told you.
I wanted us to go
to Las Vegas for me.
- Not you, me.
- Baby, you're overreacting. OK?
Don't do that! Don't you do that!
Don't diminish my needs.
Sweetheart, I don't have a choice.
I gotta go.
- I go down there, I come right back.
- "I, I, I, I, I!"
I wonder what the group
would have to say about that.
No. You cannot use that against me!
We are not even married, but I go.
The group thinks we're married.
I accepted the potato slicer
for our anniversary.
Right, sweets? I go along.
That's it. That is it.
You... You... You go along!
You don't want to get married.
And this is the way you deal with it!
Huh? You're back to
the same old selfish,
self-involved, vile, disgusting...
- Oh, God. You are...
- ..self!
You're missing the grand design here!
If I don't go, I'm dead.
Yeah. And it's difficult
to have a relationship
if I'm stuffed with formaldehyde.
- Now, if anyone is being selfish...
- Oh! Now you blame-shift?
- You are blame shifting?
- Stop analyzing!
I'm calling a time-out!
Ah!
All right...
Jerry, I want you to acknowledge...
that my needs mean nothing to you
and you're selfish.
- Oh, my God!
- Jerry, acknowledge.
I... OK.
I will acknowledge that I promised
I would go to Vegas with you.
But now we're just slightly delayed.
If you want to construe my wanting
to stay alive as being selfish, OK.
I have every intention of going with
you. Your needs are important to me.
Come on. Look at all my stuff here,
all over the pavement.
Come on, baby. Huh?
What do you say?
OK?
I'm going with or without you, Jerry.
What's it gonna be?
- A bastard!
- A bastard.
What happened to, uh,
"sweetheart" and "big love"?
All those things
you called me last night?
The only thing I'm interested
in calling you is a cab!
(Singing in Spanish)
(Automated telephone
instructions in Spanish)
Excuse me, speak English?
Excuse me, you speak English?
- (Speaking Spanish)
- What?
All set, Mr. Welbach.
If you go to the front,
a shuttle will take you to your car.
- What kind of car is it?
- It's a Chrysler. Brand-new.
Yeah.
Is there a problem, Mr. Welbach?
You know, it's my first trip
to Mexico and...a Chrysler?
I mean,
I drive a Chrysler in America.
I thought you might have something
more authentic, a little more...
- Mexican?
- You know, get into the spirit?
- Your first time?
- Yeah.
Wow. Exciting.
(In Spanish)
Do you speak Spanish, Mr. Welbach?
Huh?
(In Spanish) I didn't think so. Just
what you learned on Speedy Gonzales?
Yeah, Speedy Gonzales.
Let's see what we can do for you.
Oh, I think I have just the thing.
How would you like...an El Camino?!
Ooh! I like that. Yeah.
(In Spanish) You're going to get
into a lot of trouble here, sir.
Raoul!
(In Spanish)
Who wants him, a two-dayer?
He looks like a lead foot
and a brake rider.
No. At the count of three.
Uno... Dos... Tres...
(Engine revving)
Yeah, man. El Camino!
# El Camino excellente,
El Camino excellente... #
(Woman speaking Spanish)
# El Camino...
# In my El Camino... #
(Truck horn blares)
(Fuck me.)
Fucker.
(Chatter and fireworks popping)
You are in the wrong place, America.
Yeah, I'm aware of that.
What you want here?
Uh...tequila.
I asked because no one like you...
comes to this place.
It's death, this town.
Only farmers...and bandidos.
And I don't see a hoe.
You a bandido, America?
Uh, no. Uh, actually
I'm looking for a Señor Beck.
Señor Beck?
Right.
OK?
(Football commentary on TV)
- You Beck?
- (Men jeer)
- I know who you are.
- Good. That makes things easier.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- (Beck speaking Spanish)
- We cool?
- You're all the same.
Prepared.
This ain't America. You want a drink?
- Yeah, all right.
- Sit down.
Somebody using this chair?
I guess you wanna see it, right?
- Yeah.
- You want to see it, don't you?
Yeah. I'm afraid I'm gonna have to.
Hey.
You know what? Come with me.
Sorry. Sorry.
This is what they call The Mexican.
Wow. Yeah, that's pretty.
Are you shitting me?
"Yeah, it's pretty."
- Can I?
- Uh-huh.
It was made for a rich landowner,
a nobleman,
by a poor Mexican gunsmith.
He fashioned this gun as a gift
to go along with the hopes
that the nobleman's son would take
his daughter's hand in marriage.
(Beck) 'The townspeople
waited three months
'to catch the first glimpse
of the pistol.
'Finally, the day had come.
'No one had ever laid eyes
on a more beautiful gun.
'It was all they thought it'd be.
'Some even thought
it was too beautiful to look at.
'It was considered
to be an honor and good luck
'to be the first to fire
a newly fashioned gun.
'Especially one as beautiful as this,
made for the hand of a nobleman.
'The townsman was in a trance
at the gun's flawless craftsmanship.
'It backfired...
'killing him instantly.'
(Church bell chiming)
Legend has it
that it's been cursed ever since.
But it hasn't harmed me any though,
you know? I... I love to look at it.
(Let me show you something.
Look, there's a bullet in there.)
(It's handmade. Hand-fucking-made.)
You don't even want to know
what this gun is worth.
We could sell that gun, man.
It's... It's a great fucking gun.
And I'm not just talking shit either.
You don't have to be a... Fuck.
I've been pissin' on myself. Fuck.
Anyway, the old man
is nothing to be afraid of.
As a matter of fact,
last week I told him to fuck off.
- Yeah, you did!
- That's what I said too!
I said, "Fuck off, Margolese,
you old prune shit-ass! If you..."
Come on, fella. Get up. Huh?
Man, you're soaked in your own urine.
Don't make me carry you.
Hey!
Ah, this is my life.
All right.
Yeah, baby. I got the touch.
- (Groans)
- Oh!
Buddy, you whacked your noggin!
Hey.
Oh, f...
Ooh.
Hey, man. Hey.
Oh, shit!
Stop that! Stop!
Christ!
I found the gun.
'The gun is in your possession?'
As we speak.
But, like I said, there's, uh...
There's a problem.
What? You lost the kid? He's a souse,
he'll be in another bar.
The kid's dead, Ted.
Ted, are you hearing me?
Yeah. I-I heard you.
How?
Bad luck, act of God, fuck if I know.
All these maniacs shooting
guns up into the sky.
It's Independence Day or something.
The kid got tagged by a loose one.
Right in the fuckin' head.
I mean... Fu...
He's dead! The kid's dead.
The little fucker's in my car
right now, dead.
Geez, Jerry,
that's not a little problem.
- 'That's a big problem.'
- I know.
Jerry, that little fucker
is Margolese's grandson.
What? What?
'Geez, you really
fucked it this time.'
What did I have to do with it? One
minute he's pissin', next he's dead.
'Don't even move.'
I'll phone the office now.
I'll get me on a plane
and straighten shit out.
Ted, you gotta get word to the old
man. I didn't know who he was.
- OK. Just sit tight, Jerry.
- (Crackling)
- Hello?
- Ted? Ted? Hello?
(Line cuts out)
(Car engine revving)
Hey! Wait!
Oh, no!
Excuse me, Bernie.
There is an issue.
It's that fuckin' Welbach.
# You keep sayin'
you got somethin' for me
# Something you call love,
but confess
# You've been a-messin'
where you shouldn't been a-messin'
(PA) # And now someone else
is gettin' all your best
# These boots are made for walkin'
# And that's just what they'll do
# One of these days these boots
are gonna walk all over you... #
(# Pipe organ music)
# You keep lyin'
when you ought to be truthin'
# And you keep losin'
when you ought to not bet
# You keep samin'
when you ought to be a-changin'
# Now what's right is right
but you ain't been right yet
# These boots are made for walkin'
# And that's just what they'll do
# One of these days these boots
are gonna walk all over you
# Yeah
# You keep lyin'
when you ought to be truthin'
# You keep losin'
when you ought to not bet
# You keep samin'
when you ought to be a-changin'
# Now what's right is right
but you ain't been right yet... #
You need to know straight out,
I don't stand
for any motherfuckin' shit.
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm-mm.
No shit at all.
This is what you're gonna do.
You're gonna stop crying. Shh.
And you're gonna walk
out of here with me.
Can you feel me, Sam?
- Mmm.
- Good.
(Door opens)
Shh.
(Sit down.)
# ..and what he knows
you ain't got time to learn
# These boots were made for walkin'
# And that's just what they'll do
# One of these days these boots
are gonna walk all over you
# Are you ready, boots? #
Now, Sam, as I was saying...
# Start walkin' #
No, please! Please don't hurt me!
Help me! Help me!
(Screams)
Please!
- Please!
- Where's your car?
- Where's your fucking car?
- It's there!
- Are you hurt?
- No.
Yes. I don't know.
Truck, truck, truck!
Um, um... Sir?
- Can you stop the car? Please.
- Why?
- I'm gonna be sick.
- Just open...
She told me, "Don't go. I don't want
you on that highway alone."
I said, "It'll be fine, Mom.
It'll be OK." But it's not, is it?
- I'm dead.
- Well, you're not dead.
You would have been dead
if I hadn't saved your life.
Would you rather
it was you back there?
I didn't think so.
Are you gonna kill me?
Depends on
too many variables to answer.
Are you gonna rape me?
That's not likely, no.
Well, what do you want?
I suspect the same thing
as the other guy.
The pistol.
The one that Jerry's havin' a hard
time coming back from Mexico with.
Jerry?
I work for Bernie Nayman,
who works for Arnold Margolese.
- You heard of these people.
- Yeah, I have.
- And your husband works for 'em.
- No.
Well, he does.
I know the selfish, no-good liar
works for them. He isn't my husband.
Well, whatever he is to you,
Jerry is in the shit books.
When you're in as much shit as he is,
you get skittish about your future.
Clouds your judgement.
There's a lot of people
interested in that gun.
So what we got here is a...
"he who controls the girl,
controls the pistol" situation.
I'm a hostage? You blew that guy
to pieces for a fucking gun?
This is so Jerry. Look...
Sit down. Sit down.
Um...
Uh, uh...
Look.
Jerry and I broke up,
so if he's doing...
I don't know what he's doing.
It's got nothing to do with me.
You seem like a very nice girl.
Thank you.
But it's a fact,
in these life-threatening situations,
human beings...lie.
So you are gonna kill me.
All right, look.
If everything goes OK and Jerry comes
through without this getting funky,
I don't think that'll happen.
He gives me the pistol,
I give you to him.
I'm just here
to regulate funkiness. OK?
Go on.
Great.
(Donkey braying)
Hyah. Hyah!
Hyah!
Come on, buddy. Come on, OK?
Just you and me. Yeah.
Go!
Go. Oh! You're such an ass.
What are you...? No, no, no!
I'm sorry! I didn't mean...
Fuck!
(Horn)
Hey!
- ¿Que pasa?
- Buenas noches.
- I need a lift to the next town.
(Speaking Spanish)
I need a ride
in your automobile to the next town.
I can't pay you.
I have no money. No dinero.
- De Niro?
- Sí. None.
Robert De Niro?
Robert De Niro!
Yeah. Uh, I need a lift
in your el truck-o
to the next town-o.
- Uh, village-o. Uh, uh, pueblo.
- Ah, pueblo.
- Yeah, sí!
- Al otro pueblo. OK.
- Yes?
- Señor De Niro!
Self-winding. You never have
to wind it. It's very fine.
Yeah. Shake like...
Perpetual calendar.
It's good.
Is this even gonna run?
Yeah?
Hey. That your ball?
Shit. Hey. Hey, man.
You got a rabid dog back here.
Go. Go!
Go. Out.
You gotta do something
about this dog.
(Operator) 'I have a collect call
for Samantha from Jerry Welbach.
- 'No one there, sir.'
- (Jerry) 'Give it a second.'
Sam, pick up the phone.
Sams? Samsonite?
Baby, please don't do this.
- 'Please try again, sir'
- No!
Just give it a second. She's there...
What are you doing?
- You're gonna make a call.
- To whom?
To Jerry.
You're gonna tell him that Leroy
is with you then you hang up.
- Leroy?
- Yeah. Leroy, that's right.
Then you're gonna hang up. Simple.
That's it?
It's enough. Believe me.
You gonna make the call
or do I have to make you? Cos I will.
- No. I'll call.
- Good.
Dial it.
OK. What's the number?
You have the number.
I don't know where he is.
You should have the number.
What are you tellin' me? You don't
have a number, a motel, nothing?
What's the matter, don't you listen?
We broke up. No longer together.
Why would I have the number?
I'm sensing you have trust issues.
You got one minute.
I'm a professional.
I do this for a living.
Goody for you.
You're wasting your time.
(Radio) # You're nobody
till somebody loves you... #
I think I believe you.
# You're nobody
till somebody cares...
What's in Vegas?
Uh, well...I'm gonna be a waitress,
then make a career as a croupier.
They can make $100,000 a year but you
have to have the hands, which I do.
I got them from Grandma Vega,
which is a good thing
cos my Granny Barzel
had hands like a circus midget.
How come you can't live with Jerry?
Do you know Jerry?
He has trouble expressing feelings.
He had a fucked-up childhood.
His mom is nuts. One of those people
who thinks the iron is always on.
- Don't you love him?
- I think that's the problem.
We love each other too much.
But he's... He's so selfish.
It's like we've been living
his life forever.
He'd tell you a different story,
but I give and he just keeps taking.
Our counselor totally
agrees with me, by the way.
I don't put much stock
in those counselor types.
All they do is sit around
and smoke joints.
Maybe, but Jerry is still a taker
and I'm a giver.
It's obvious.
A lot of people
are under the impression
that you get to choose who you love.
I'm sorry, are you...
Are you taking his side?
You're a man, of course.
- You're taking his side.
- You love him. You said so yourself.
It's all that matters.
You're a very sensitive person
for a killer.
Thank you, Sam.
Shit.
Get. Get out. Out.
Look, you gotta get out.
Get out!
(Muttering)
Go!
(Truck horn blaring)
(Speaking Spanish)
Hola, shithead! Where's my stuff?
Get back! Where's my stuff?
- Pistol. Pistolero. Get back.
- La pistola.
Get back!
Stay calm. Get back, get back!
Don't move.
What the f...? Give me those.
Back! Back, back.
Get in the car. Get in! OK.
Is that my...? Is that my jacket?
Put it in the car! What is wrong
with you people? Get back!
- (Sam) You don't have to be in here.
- I go by track record.
- I don't hear any tinkle, tinkle.
- Stage fright.
Look around,
there's not even a window.
So what's with this "We've been
livin' his life forever" thing?
I didn't mean it literally.
Jerry's been working for Margolese
for five years less a day.
It just feels lifelong.
- Sounds like jail terms.
- It is.
Arnold Margolese is in jail
because Jerry put him there.
Jerry ratted out Arnold Margolese?
No. Jerry was coming across Ventura,
over there by Laurel Canyon.
- Yeah?
- He wasn't paying attention,
ran a red light,
smashed into Margolese's Cadillac.
The cops came, Margolese got busted
cos he had a person in the trunk.
That's how Margolese
got sent to jail? !
Mm-hmm.
- Live person or dead person?
- Live person.
Huh. What's the big deal, then?
He probably wasn't
gonna stay that way.
He was taped up in a trunk
for a reason, wasn't he?
I would think this was
right up your alley, Swifty.
- He saw something?
- Whatever it was this guy saw,
or was going to say to the cops,
he got the chance.
Since it was Jerry's fault, Margolese
had him work off the jail time.
My whole relationship
has been hijacked
because he doesn't pay attention
when he drives.
I... I can't go with you in here.
(Urinating)
(Sam urinating)
(Man) We didn't think we were getting
a dead man with the car.
I got no use for a dead gringo.
Take a left.
(Flies buzzing)
Come on.
If you're going to kill me,
at least tell me
who it is that's going
to send me to God.
Tell me!
Look, I'm not gonna kill you.
But I am gonna have to shoot you.
But why, sir? Why?
Why? Because you stole from me,
you know about the pistol
and you'll steal again.
I can't have you coming back
like a fly in the ointment.
I won't be a fly!
You'll never see me again.
You're gettin' shot, that's it.
It'll take time to walk to town,
especially limping...
Wait, wait. Limping?
Can't you just tie me up some more?
Fuck! You shoot me? Tie me!
Yeah. I don't have a rope.
So you shoot me?
It's the American way.
Where do you want it?
OK.
Not the leg! There's arteries.
I could bleed to death in seconds.
The foot.
That's fair where I come from. OK?
It'll hurt, but it'll heal.
What if you take off a fucking toe!
Wait, wait, wait. Not the left.
Oh, sorry.
On the count of three.
- One...
- (Screams)
Look, I'm agreeing with you.
But there's a few ways to look at it.
Sex is, no matter what anybody says,
a very important part
of any relationship.
The fact that Jerry
is a considerate lover says a lot.
- You lost me.
- Well, he's a considerate lover.
You gotta find a way to get him to
expand this quality he has during sex
to other areas of your relationship.
Even if it only comes out in sex,
it's there just the same.
That's a good point.
If a person's a considerate lover,
he can't be all selfish, right?
Unless of course he's...
- He's, uh, being a considerate...
- What was that?
What?
That. That moment you had.
What moment?
Leroy, you just checked out
that guy and had a moment.
That was a moment.
I don't know if it was a moment.
(Are you gay?)
- As in happy?
- As in homosexual.
What does my sexual orientation
have to do with our conversation?
Nothing.
Nothing. Except something that you
said back there really bugged me
and this would kind of
help it make sense.
Yeah? What's that?
I asked if you were gonna rape me,
you said, "Not likely."
You said it so coldly,
like I was repulsive
and it was ludicrous to think I was
actually at risk of being raped.
First of all, it's a crime of anger,
not attraction.
Second of all, you're not repulsive.
You're very beautiful.
Thank you.
- You want me to rape you?
- Are you gay?
- You're gay.
You're gay. I knew it!
Oh, I so knew it.
I just knew it. What a relief.
Do you want a medal? A little trinket
saying you identified a homosexual?
No.
Are you full throttle?
Full throttle?
Yeah, I guess I am.
Oh. I'm not... I mean...
I'm not trying to be a smart-ass
or anything like that.
I just... I think this is great.
Wow. This is...
This is...major, OK?
I...know the kind of people
in your business, OK?
- Yeah?
- And to me, it seems that...
Well, being gay isn't really...
conducive to the environment.
Like I should be an interior
decorator. That's insulting.
- I am very good at what I do.
- Do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't.
Unfortunately,
I seem to be unable to keep...
relationships together.
Seems like everybody's having trouble
keeping relationships together.
It's ringing, señor.
- Thank you for that.
- No, no, no. No necesario.
Really?
That's so kind.
You have no idea what...
'Hi, this is Ted. Leave a message.
'If this is my guy in need,
I'm on my way.
'Go to the Hotel de la Plaza.
Wait for me there, OK? Sit tight.'
OK, OK. Forget aeropuerto.
Uh, Hotel de la Plaza.
- (Muttering in Spanish)
- Hola.
- Is this your dog?
- Sort of.
Came along for the ride.
He has a personality
and that does count.
- He's a good guy.
- Is this your car?
It's a rental. I'm an American.
- No shit? Really?
- Yeah.
I'm Mexican.
Cool.
Do you have a passport?
- Jerry Wellbatch, Los Angeles, USA.
- Welbach... Wellbatch.
Can I ask you a question, Jerry?
How long have you been in Mexico?
- A few days. Pleasure.
- I see.
- Pleasure, huh?
- Yeah.
I see. Can you tell me,
uh, what happened here?
That's not accurate, I'm afraid.
The gunsmith did craft this pistol
for a prospective husband,
and he was a nobleman's son, true.
But the motif was darker, my friend.
It's cursed, this gun.
(Policeman) 'The key to this tale
involves the gunsmith's assistant,
'a poor, but honorable
young man in blinding love
'with the gunsmith's daughter.
'For months at a time,
the assistant took to the mines
'gathering the precious metal
'that would yield the most
beautiful gun that ever existed,
'only to discover that what he hoped
could be a wedding gift for him...
'was for another.
'The gunsmith insisted his daughter
marry the nobleman's son,
'forbidding their love.
'Angered in his bitter pain,
the assistant cursed the gun,
'vowing the creation
would never prevail.
'But the gunsmith
was racing against time.
'He had promised a pistol
of unparalleled craftsmanship,
'the nobleman's dowry
hanging in the balance.
'He worked day and night
to correct the pistol's problems.'
(Bullet ricocheting)
(Church bell chiming)
This gun never worked properly.
Some say its very creation
ended the gunsmith's life.
Well, my friend, you're free to go,
but without the gun.
This gun doesn't belong
to you or to your boss.
Now it belongs to me.
(Man) Yeah, Vegas.
It can be tough that way.
(Sam) Expensive?
(Man) Yeah, emotionally.
I had a serious relationship problem.
Well, you fit right in here.
- What do you do now, Frank?
- Now...I am a postman.
Get out of here.
- That's so rigid.
- Swear to God.
There's a seedy underbelly
to the postal service.
- Is that the key to it?
- That's the key.
You have no idea how many small,
unmarked brown paper packages
I deliver.
- What, porno?
- Yeah, daily.
Like what?
Videos, blow-up dolls,
dildos, pocket pussies.
- Don't leave nothing out.
- Oh, yeah?
But even with all that
dirty excitement at my fingertips,
I still have to take off
once a year.
I just get up and I know I'm going
to Vegas, I just don't know how.
All I've got is my wallet
and an attitude.
I don't know, it keeps me sane.
After all, guns don't kill people...
postal workers do.
OK, you're all set, Mr. Shurker.
If you go to the front,
a shuttle will pick you up.
What kind of car is it exactly?
It's a Chrysler, sir, brand-new.
You wouldn't happen to have
something a little more...
Raoul!
Yeah, man!
Yeah. Never fear, Teddy's here.
How are you?
- 'Rosco!'
- (Speaks Spanish)
Come on, Jerry.
The Mexican thief, the dirty cop?
The word is out.
It's a big-ticket item.
A lot of fucking people
are interested in that gun.
No fucking...
Is that what they think?
That I'm selling them out?
Maybe they think you're scared
and might do the wrong thing.
- Ted.
- You know, I don't know.
- I'm just doing my portion here.
- Yeah, and what is that?
To find out what's going on, assess
the damage, try to calm you down,
help find the pistol, get us home.
I get on that plane, pistol or not.
it'll be the last flight I ever take.
- Oh, come on, Jerry.
- "Come on"? You know it.
- I know what I have to know.
- Doing your part.
I know what I have to know.
You sound like Schultz
from Hogan's Heroes.
(German accent) I know nothing!
I don't like Nayman
running things either.
I got a few years on you and I'm
telling you, keep your nose clean,
look straight ahead
and do what you're told.
That's why I nearly paid off
Boca Raton. I do my fuckin' portions.
I don't care how you look at it,
the first step out of this
is to get the pistol back.
I never took a pay-off in my life.
Jerry, look,
I know where your loyalties lie.
But the kid's dead.
The pistol's gone.
I mean, you can see
how it looks, right?
Come on.
You're my guy.
(Phone)
(Ringing continues)
# We can dance if we want to
we've got all your life and mine
# As long as we abuse it,
never gonna lose it
# Everything will work out right
# I say, we can dance if we want to
# We can leave your friends behind
# Cos your friends don't dance
and if they don't dance, well they're
# No friends of mine
# I say, we can dance, we can dance,
everything's out of control
# We can dance, we can dance
# They're doing it from pole to pole
# We can dance, we can dance,
everybody look at your hands... #
- (Music stops)
- Not the safest dance!
I'm not going anywhere.
(Sam) We are in the city
where I'm going to be living.
(Go.)
Go.
What's wrong? Huh?
You know when you're in
a bad relationship and you separate?
All of a sudden, everywhere you look
there's love and possibility.
I'm worried about Jerry.
All right, don't worry.
I'll call Nayman
and check in on everything.
You want me to stay?
I want you to go.
You sure?
I really want you to go.
(Clicking)
(Snoring)
(Ted) I couldn't sleep all night.
Yeah. No, he said he followed
the cop to the pawn shop.
He's taking me over there
after breakfast.
We're booked on the seven o'clock
if all goes well.
No, now wait... No...
No, you wait a minute, Nayman.
Now what do you gotta go
and say that for?
Well, now or later?
How could I misinterpret?
No, you didn't send the wrong guy.
I'm handling things.
But I never signed up for that.
Listen, I promise you, when I tell
him, it'll make a difference.