Have you heard about the penguin,
who crossed the Mojave wilderness?
It is a true story. The
would not only cross the wilderness.
It was late summer
in a Pinto from 1976.
Pinto began
that sounds very strange.
Imagine how nervous he was.
"No, no, no, gi, gi, gi."
- Was it the car or the penguin?
- It was a penguin.
He tion and title browsing in a row vrksted.
He says to the mechanic:
How do those things, brother?
Can you hjlpe me?
The mechanic says, "Absolutely, obtuse,
but I have a little busy right now. "
"There is an ice cream parlor on the second row
side of the street. "He deg inside.
Jumps up onto a chair and ordering
a bger with vanilla ice cream.
There is a problem.
He has svmmefdder.
He can not stay in one place.
He looks at his ice cream ...
"Shit." He dives into it.
He svmmer around the ice.
He has ice everywhere.
He is famished.
He eats ice
and deg the street to the mechanic.
"What do you think?"
The mechanic looks on him and says:
"It looks like you've sucked
a sl of. "
"No, no, no, it's ice.
It's just ice. "Are you with me?
It is a true story.
It is true, but not funny.
Wyatt, we are some streets vk.
Trey and Franco is back.
Me and Dave front.
The pig has nothing to lose
s vr cautious.
Wyatt, now we are promoting.
- Who? What do you want?
- Police.
- What the hell do you want?
- What we want?
You could start to open
boys before we kick it.
Infuriate you not give up.
I, p a dangerous place.
The gr probably not something that
sprger who one opens for.
Now you know. Shut up!
Okay, bitch, you fr what you want.
Let me see f credentials first.
Okay, Yo-Yo. There you have it.
How does it look?
Code Rd. A cop shot.
Gunfire 1-0-8.
I got you.
Come on, you devil.
A cop is shot.
Hold on, Dave.
You m not d, Dave.
Hold on.
- Sorry.
- Now hold kft.
Sorry.
Hold on, Trey. They come.
Bastards!
I have drbt Reno.
It requires many more of you
to kill me.
Bastards!
Look at me, you devil.
Look at me.
- Fatter you doing here?
- What do we know?
In addition to them here, we've grandmother
and his mother, younger brother and his sster.
- What is the white powder?
- Fire extinguisher.
This sounds a little absurd, but with
p tanks fire damage -
- And powder, it looks as though
they hldte gasoline on him, tndte -
- And s off him. S reiterated
they do it at least twice to.
- Who owns the place?
- A Malcolm Varanato.
- Do you think Malcolm Varnado?
- Yes, you know him?
He is a journalist p Picayune.
His older brother Weddo -
- Is one of the biggest
narkoslgere in New Orleans.
- What does it mean?
- This is a little too big for us.
I lessons might it now, Mike.
Come in.
I shit p, what I've heard.
Truth can not be voted out.
I am exaggerating? Come over
and join us out p street.
It was sad. Call back
if you will take it up again.
I wish that one day
permit hunting p politicians.
- How do those things, Pete?
- Good. Thank you peeped.
- What happens?
- A couple of things.
- You w gre me service.
- Okay, what is it?
- Journalist p Picayune.
- Weddos little brother.
He is p rampage.
He takes them fr us, we are fortunate
if we not only find snippets.
It reminds me of the service, yes.
Homicide will have a Crimean from -
- To hjlpe them, and ...
your name was nvnt.
Sure.
That sounds fine.
One more thing.
Johnny Trans lawyer hvder,
that you are attempting to kill him.
I afvbnede him.
He had a scale rows 15 cm.
He got off lightly.
I've seen the pictures. It s out
as though a bomb had hit him.
- Is that why I'm here?
- Yes, that's it.
Four complaints a row and a monthly
gunfight. You are about to lose grip.
- You blame me for Dave and Trey?
- No, what happened in the house afterwards?
The internal public interrogation boys.
Do not you think they want to know -
- Who SKD one guy p NRT team
and had an empty weapon in his hand?
It requires not a genius
to understand what happened.
I know what you wrestled with.
I myself have vret there.
You know that.
But you fortstter
p same mde ...
... You will never
get back again.
- Was that all?
- Yes, that was it.
Hello. How do those things, brother?
Colin, what the hell are you doing here?
Is it sdan you greet p folks?
How long as you have vret in town?
- Where's the wife and Jacob?
- At her parents.
- Come on, we grab a l.
- It has vret a fierce day.
I deg to kjs.
- Okay, we drink here.
- Wait a minute ... Okay, one drink.
- You provide.
- Sdan, it sounds.
Two Jamie, darling.
- Was the storm s really bad?
- Yes, dammit.
How dmningerne burst
it looks like a bomb crater.
Throughout the area is vk.
The worst was seeing people wade
past corpses -
- As if they were not there.
Please know that I vrdstter,
you got my grandfather out.
I krte past a house the other day
which was completely wiped out.
- How is he?
- Good.
He has moved in with
its sster in Algiers.
- And you?
- A little here and there, you know.
I said from before you
immediately after Fallujah.
I got a job at a security company.
- Which team?
- Spartan.
- They paid well.
- You must survive for f lnnen.
And it says one who chose
being strmer in town.
This is gonna be soon as Baghdad.
Thank you.
- Why are you now?
- I do not know.
I travel from town again.
I do not know if I come back.
I would see you one last time.
One last time? Where you going?
The big svn?
Have you ever done something ...
... Which you really want,
that you could have done about?
- You know that.
- Have you been able gre good again?
No, it can not.
That was what I thought of.
Yes. Now? No, Lewis.
No, it does not work.
We mdes seafront.
I turned on to g.
I have mde no.
Are you saying that kind of
for s just that g?
I was about to forget it. I
a fdselsdagsgave Jacob.
It's the new movie with carat tiger.
I kbte in Bangkok.
- It is not out yet. Watch it.
- Colin!
What foregr there?
- It was good to see you.
- Colin!
You said that you would have
a krekort, not a passport.
- Yes, a Californian.
- It's okay.
I lists behind you.
Okay. You grasped it, Lewis?
Gr, and came over here again.
Now it takes just a moment.
Are you ready?
One, two ...
Damn!
It will do little harm.
I have not done anything.
I knew him not once.
What are you doing? Stop!
Lewis, it's Tom again.
I would just sl p trden.
Sonny asked me to call you -
- To hear if you could look into
the studio s soon as you can.
Hber you are well. See you.
This is ridiculous.
Crowe!
I do not think it succeeds.
He jumps not row it.
Let me get some guys and see
what I can dig up.
What do you say, Renko?
Come on. See you, boss.
You know what, Sonny?
I was suddenly a mrkelig insight.
You and I resemble each other enough
more than you thought.
Hr here. We are both artists.
We may well have chosen
working with different media ...
... Or lrreder if you like.
But we want both the same.
We will communicate our innermost
thoughts and flelser.
Not true? What?
Not true?
Say it again, Sonny. Where were
your friend Lewis mde him?
He should recover a GLD.
He brides VRE back now.
- Where is he now?
- I have no idea. Maybe something went wrong.
He is maybe get out with his girl.
I do not know. I svrger.
- We are back where we started.
- I'm attempting.
M I ask a any questions? Have you
HRT myth of Baba Yaga?
No!
Will, I have checked
recent numbers p phone.
The gr all for the same two numbers,
again and again.
Try to track them. It gives
probably nothing, but you never know.
- Sean Riley? Kommissr Will Genz.
- Nice to mde you.
- Who leads the investigation?
- It should VRE me.
- Sorry, Trahan has sent me.
- I know. Thank you for coming.
- We think you can hjlpe us.
- What do you have?
Now I'll show you.
- Is there more?
- Much more.
Mo came up with the p roof.
Genz.
I come away.
The press is here.
Show him that. Coming soon.
Will you excuse us a moment?
We believe that this is the owner.
Beaumont.
- Is it Sonny?
- Yes, you know him?
Yes, A smfusker. Falsifies
ID cards, passports, credit cards, etc.
- It explains what we found down there.
- I read that on Weddos little brother.
Is it the same fremgangsmde?
Tnde, extinguish, tnde them again?
- Can Weddo VRE involved?
- Think of you differently?
I think not.
But I do not know anyone who would
dare stte up against him.
- What are you looking for?
- Sonny omgs with a Lewis.
Can you see it there
p Sonnys hjre lg?
If this is Lewis, s, he
also one. It was their dog, Bonny.
Has this guy and Lewis
your poodle tattoos?
It sounds silly
but you should have mdt dog.
It was like poodles movie star.
Just like Lassie.
It could tlle with paw
and dance like a ballerina.
A very special animals.
- All witnesses were H.I.S.
- What?
- Remember not a damn thing.
- Yes, sdan about.
The guy downstairs fake ID when ...
Boy was kicked.
The key is not responding.
The drber three down and pulls Sonny
up and kngten up here for grilling.
The tortures kngten front of him.
When they were frdige, they set fire
to them and let them burn in the wind.
- What can I hjlpe you with?
- Prsenter us Weddo ...
... Sonny family and friends
and anyone who knows something.
I'll see what I can make.
I tion and title browsing.
Since you went in, were you looking for something.
Yes, bullets ... Wayward bullets.
There was none.
I do not know if you s trfferne.
The kind krver talent.
S you checked the envelopes.
Gunners stood very close, right?
- They know each other from fr.
- Yes, something like that.
I know some who to talk to.
There he is.
Wait until you Mder this genius.
Mel.
- Hello.
- I have a questions. Come straight.
Come and talk to me.
Makes it not ... Taking a step to
slr me the rest of your teeth out.
Come here! Melvin!
Your bugger.
What the hell!
- Good hit.
- What is this?
Credit Card Forgery?
I thought you were too stupid to do so.
I am also ... I have not
presence shit. It's father's card.
Rajeev Magambie? Are you funny?
Mother's guy.
Do you know
it is a fderal crime?
Say what you will. I give you that.
I will do anything.
- Your girlfriend Lewis?
- Sonny intermediary contact.
It has not helped us.
And the other guy he works with?
I do not know. Last time I s
them, there was also a white guy.
A madman from The Channel.
- Do you have a name?
- Conner, sdan something.
- Colin?
- Yes, Colin.
Come, we will leave.
You're lucky today.
Mo, what foregr there?
Have you tracked Sonnys mobile?
Wait a minute.
Give me the address.
Damn it also! Sean.
- Boys were legs.
- You skrmte killing me.
Where you going, Stac?
Travel bag. Where you going?
- I'm visiting mom on weekends.
- You're lying.
- Fuck you!
- Is your car outside?
You have everything you own in it.
Where you going?
Why sprger you?
- Where's Colin?
- I have not seen him in two r.
- Where you mde him?
- I do not.
I would never ever
see him again.
- Two r? What the hell is this s?
- It's mine. I've earned them.
I would vk here and get clean.
I'm moving to Florida.
- I want to hear the truth!
- I would not mde him!
I'll call back.
You w believe me.
- I hber for you it's true.
- I svrger.
I saw Colin p street
a few nights ago.
He was drunk and skv.
He fablede that he would flee.
He freaked out, started to weep
and gave me money and said:
LANG not please them
and-ride from the city.
Did he say where he went?
Yes, he said,
that he should mdes with you.
- What was it about?
- What has your guy been?
We have traced one of the tracks.
The bills are parking somewhere
tt p MLK.
- You did not speak much in the car.
- Sorry, I have much to conjure p.
- Like what, Colin?
- What?
He is your friend, right? Is he
p bucket? Who is after him?
Multi you outside? I know
not what he's doing, okay?
He tiltrkker ballad
like a magnet.
- Where stopped long have you known him?
- Whole life.
Every time I trdt in something
He STET middle of it.
We deg back to what Stacey said.
Did he do it?
- Mdte you know him?
- Yes, in deg night.
And you had not tnkt you
to say something?
- What would he do?
- I do not know.
You'll be the first thing to hear it,
No I find out.
- Should we gre it here?
- After you, sir.
There you can see.
Hello, boys.
Take it easy, tough guys.
It was uhfligt not knocking p.
Take it easy.
It can be very uncomfortable
very quickly if we do not relax.
Enlarge it?
Damn!
- Rr you not! Become Stende!
- Wait, Sean!
Become Stende, strmer.
Stupid fissestrmer!
- Lg weapon from you!
- Team kft, loser!
- You are a fucking erating.
- Lg weapon from you!
G to hell, idiot!
I drber her! I warn you!
Vr quiet, darling.
- Lg weapon from you.
- Do you see it?
I drber her p instead.
She dr for your sake!
Her brain mass
will gush out.
What happened?
- Something went badly wrong.
- What do you mean?
I want details!
Journalists reported
a kind of shootout.
All are dead, Crowe.
Renko, Cole. The whole gang.
How the hell is this possible?
- Hello?
- Is that all you have to say, Raymond?
I'm finished with waiting. It is
Firm also, I have first.
- I have at least track them.
- That's why we're still talking.
You do not threaten me.
I'm with. Give me a little more time.
You accept the fact m -
- And deliver what you promised.
You knew the risks.
We have worked too long a time now.
You can probably convince the company about ...
Stop, Raymond.
I can not bear to hear the needle you.
- I ask you to ...
- It is enough. It is what it is.
Nothing has changed.
You have time until midnight.
- Midnight tomorrow.
- Wait Richter.
- Das korovai.
- Damn, wait! Richter!
Griff, you and Dekker m discover
what went wrong s shit!
Come on, boys.
Hello, darling.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, fine.
Most VRE thanks him here.
Sean, my beautiful wife Beth.
- Hi, Beth.
- Nice to mde you.
My Princess Sarah ...
And here is little Mad Max.
Car ...
Come on, Dad, I will show you something.
- Come in.
- Sean, you stay for dinner.
- Thanks, it was lkkert.
- No Reason.
Is it only me who think
that they are very quiet?
- How mdtes I?
- One of your versions, or truth?
We mdtes at the university. I lb
tr of petrol, and he saved me.
- Lucky ass.
- Yes, no?
Is there a mrs. Riley?
- Yes, sometime.
- Any children?
We had a son. His name was Jacob.
He was six when he got leukmi.
Eighteen years later he died.
She left me behind.
She could probably not endure,
I reminded her of him.
- I apologize.
- No, let VRE with it.
Normally, I find p something
to escape doing really pathetic.
I said for the rest,
the wonderful family I have?
Isr your little princess.
Sarah, what degrees you poor fellow.
Come on, champ.
- You will not VRE princess.
- He looks like his father.
This benefits you receive?
Now we find a fireman's uniform.
Thank you.
It's a nice neighborhood.
- What is it?
- I'm sorry.
- I let you down.
- Nonsense.
You responded that all
others would have done.
You went p them as if
you had the odds on your side.
It is not the same.
There is a difference.
When you came on hjrnet today
s not you tell me.
You s not mndene with weapon.
You s only your happy family.
I do not have it to lose.
It's the difference.
There is a blessing in everything.
My father was a preacher.
Was there something he lrte, s it was
that everything had a meaning.
Do you think that p?
What sense is there in
to a 4-rich suffer for two r?
- Is there a sense in that?
- Consider the what happened today.
If it was get different
s l i dd p street now.
- It was intended that I should live.
- It's easy to say now.
Are they not possible,
that what happened with your family -
- Not only was
a an arbitrary accident?
- There is perhaps a brain think?
- What do you mean?
I do not think p miracles.
I'm not a saint.
Today you were a saint
for me and my family.
Okay, it's late.
You m believe p, whatever you want,
s p I think what I want.
- It's okay.
- What?
What kind of a mine?
Want slbe me in church?
- What about p Sunday?
- No.
It's late. I gotta get
my ngler and you must sleep.
Yes. No problems.
What happens?
Where?
I'm p road.
- Hey, how do those things?
- Are you sure that it is her?
You see, what that means? It
is not about Weddo, but about Colin.
Could I track the other numbers
p Sonnys mobile?
CreditCards p fupadresser.
Look at the journalist's conversation lists on
same number pops up somewhere.
- Do you think it's Colin?
- I m LBE.
- What have we here, Sean?
- It does not look good.
- Do we know who it is?
- Her name is Stacey.
We forhrte her gr She can
VRE associated with a possible mistnkt.
A possible? S
suspicion degree heart now, huh?
I'm sorry to say this, but I
was called by management.
The press lgger pressure p them
angende exchange of fire in gr
- They're after you.
- They will probably not sacrifice me?
- It looks sdan out.
- How much time do I have?
Until tomorrow.
- Are there other meetings?
- I think not.
Damn.
I need your HJLP.
Do you think that the techniques can accelerate
identification of the exchange of fire?
- Sean ...
- Come on, Pete.
I will do what I can.
I thought I was smart.
Colin phoned him many times.
- Why a journalist?
- The m VRE something big.
- He has no p those chasing him.
- Something they will not have speed.
We find him m, fr they do those things.
We are shown below.
Tell what you know.
You know everyone here.
- Are you lost?
- Kr on.
- Have you cgt the p mail order?
- Want to Check out the rows that?
I would like.
- What the hell is happening?
- Who are you?
Remove htterne.
- Can you recognize me, white?
- Yes, I know who you are.
S deg us right to the chase.
I want to know what you know.
- Are you kidding?
- Do I look like a comedian?
Someone killed my family.
Grilled my brother alive.
It took the only good,
the only pure, I've had.
We do not know a damn thing.
Wait. You have misforstet it.
- It's not about you.
- It's not about Malcolm.
No, but on his job.
Your brother was in the wrong place p
p the wrong time.
I know what you want. I had done
the same, but it is not solutions.
- What is a good solution enabling?
- Let us perform our work.
Tracking people is what we are good at.
We find the bastard.
He is right. We are your best bet
to convict them before leaving.
Okay ...
We follows the rejection your rules, but I will
VRE a shadow that waits.
This will not just blow over.
The bugger must both for it.
I'm with.
- Are we back where we started?
- Let me see if the FBI has matched ...
Hurry. Will speak
on the phone with them now.
- What did you learn?
- Nothing. Nobody knows anything.
- They have identified the brndte.
- Lewis Gunther.
- What is their connection?
- Lewis was Sonny guy.
- And these?
- It's a little mrkeligt.
All ID-papers are fake.
No internet nonsense. Things of hj
quality. I thought they were genuine.
Look at p beautiful over here.
It is here you will find interesting.
They dug them out of the shoulder.
They thought it was kulrester.
- What is it?
- Shrapnel.
I thought so also.
Watch it here.
Techniques think it is from
a 3-0-8 or even larger.
One of klerummet have a
Cyrillic tattoo needle arm -
- And something resembling forbrndinger
from white phosphorus p whole back.
- War injuries.
- It looks sdan out.
That explains a lot.
In deg during the shooting.
Their weapon, tactics ...
- Former. soldiers?
- More than that. They are professionals.
- It's great.
- What foregr there?
What are you entangled?
Colin attempting
contact Weddos little brother.
Those who are after Colin, finds him
first. Colin finds out.
S he freak out and look
ndsaget to disappear.
But without ID
get fairly close.
S he contacts Sonny.
That they go also.
How they found out
whom Colin had to contact?
- They can see his interview lists.
- How?
You said they are good. He committed
maybe a mistake when he kbte phone.
The credit card he used,
or an alias, they've been addressed in.
They found at least out of it.
It took us from the Australian
p parking lot.
Hvornr genbnede Rays? The club
've vret closed since the storm.
I worked with a murder opposite
two weeks ago. Since there was closed.
Wait a minute.
What you think of p,
No you hear my name?
I thought of it enough. Was that why
you are not told about your son?
Or whether that Renee had left you?
I'm very sorry. I would
desire that I could have stttet you.
- What would you have done?
- Something. Anything.
I never helped you.
I've never gengldt you.
- Surrender yourself to me.
- Forget it, Sean.
You can not save me this time.
If you fortstter, you will not
could save yourself.
- Tell me where you are.
- You hear not after.
- Unleash it.
- Colin!
I m telling about Stacey.
Damn!
It is over five years ago.
What does the napkin in his pocket?
Damn!
Sorry.
What are you looking for?
- Stacey O'Neill.
- Never heard about her.
Should I?
Sorry. I am assistant Riley,
this stuff is assistant Genz. And you are?
Raymond Crowe, hello.
We are looking for a girl.
A friend says she worked
as a dancer here last week.
Did she? It was mrkeligt.
As you see, we build on
and we have no employees.
Is she in trouble?
It may well say.
You fr excuse me.
I have much to do.
I know you're busy
with the renovation -
- But I can tie her
to this nightclub.
I Fri just my job.
Enlarge you?
Yes, and I seeks to make mine.
Makes it something
if I give you a rd?
If I were you, I'd VRE
very careful with this stuff.
A man who deg the kind
For p whatever.
Serves you right in.
One can also see it sdan here.
If I were him, I would fear to
what I could find p.
Nice to mdes.
Here's my card.
If you or one of your friends
will talk ... s TV service.
I'm sure p, we see,
policewoman Riley.
- It's him, right?
- Jo.
Wait. What was it about?
S you know how the big
Satan stared p you?
I think I made them angry?
Is it your plan to excite
assassins?
Fine. I stand by.
I will be the grandfather sometime.
Well, damn ...
Colin, I know where he is.
- Where are we?
- Colin's grandfather's house. We played here.
Colin!
Col!
Colin, can you hear me?
That's me.
Colin?
Col?
Rr you do not.
Do not blink once.
Turn you on. Slowly.
Colin, that's me.
What are you doing?
- Who is he?
- My partner. Forget him.
M telling you,
what foregr.
I thought you had grasped it.
I asked you the tray out.
Listening not, m you take flgerne.
G to hell!
Everything here is your responsibility.
- Will you arrest me?
- You're lucky if I do not do those things.
They would love it. Ls me inside
in a cage and make it easy for them.
- Who are you talking about?
- Dukkefreren that last trdene.
These substances have hrget you
s you can not see clearly lngere.
I just need ... Damn.
I m just disappear from here.
If you do not shut me in,
I can not assist you.
The company I work for -
- Let me work hard for
a mysterious client based in LA.
A loathsome task.
It was totally crazy.
You can not imagine it.
The last job knkkede me.
The mysterious client would ensure
some interest in a war zone.
It was not a dangerous operation,
and p. .. names.
- What would the OPN with it?
- For God's sake!
They do not want,
the war ends.
Colin, what have you needle them?
- What do you have?
- I have a videobnd.
I stole it. I overvgnings-
Movies matches and interrogation.
I have things that can be descending upon all
who have met with Spartan to do.
Do away with it.
Lg it on the internet.
Are you stupid in the head?
It is my only chance.
That is my only security.
So I went to the journalist.
He knew the one from the Justice Department,
which was to arrest me.
It's just that you want
save yourself. You are skidedum.
Do you know what you've done?
Do You Know?
- I took a copy, if ...
- A lot of innocent people are dead.
I have not forced anyone
for anything. Everyone knew the risks.
Stacey did it?
The drbte her.
The drbte your girl.
The brndte her alive.
What the hell are you talking about?
You're lying.
Sean, you're lying about her!
She does not fail anything.
You lie!
Crowe is with p bndet, right?
He works for Spartan.
Crowe is not with p bndet?
How do you know that name?
Say where you saw and heard the name.
Come on!
Charger.
Captured!
There is a window in the cuisine behind me.
Out the window all together.
Come on!
Colin, what do we do?
Col!
I'm with you. Come s!
The back of the house!
- Colin, come on.
- Sorry.
- I talked all about a reserve plan.
- What the hell are you doing? Come!
Hurry s vk much as possible.
Where is videobndet?
It's here.
The explosion destroyed
house completely.
The authorities have
No comments at the moment.
Sources say there were soldiers
p spot fr brandvsenet arrived.
We do not know
if there was anyone in the house.
Police have spoken with neighbors -
- To find out what happened
in the quiet and almost that they omrde.
Mr. Richter.
What can I hjlpe you?
You can brighten my day up by
telling that you have good news.
It's not midnight yet.
I still have a little time.
- Can I say you have it?
- I know where it is.
- Do svidaniya, Raymond.
- Mr. Richter ...
Mon indrmmer that at least one cop
were involved in the shooting today.
He is believed to be investigated
interference in two other episodes.
We follows the rejection hndelsesforlbet
throughout the evening.
Damn!
Did the officer directly to O'Neill?
Yes, it was Colin's grandfather's house.
Find out s much as possible
about this person.
This disaster is closed ...
End it tonight.
Sean, take phone
if you're there.
Inter Investigators have released me,
and you were already decamped.
We can find out anything,
m but you talk to me.
Gr nothing stupid
you will regret.
Sean, call me.
Damn!
Not them ... them there.
How did I, that the load would
transported through this sector?
- How did that?
- I did not know.
What happens?
We've talked about it here.
- Do not gre it here.
- What should I do gre?
Cole, talk to him.
I must gre it
p the right way.
- What the hell are you doing?
- SRG to f him vk.
Can you hjlpe me?
Stop!
Tells how I knew it.
Turn off that.
Your dr was kicked.
- Captain ...
- What is this?
- I can explain it.
- What are you doing?
If they want korsfste me
s let them gre it.
- Let me take the idiot first.
- Will you end up like your dad?
- I warned you against this.
- The riddles are not you. I have proof.
Fatter you what I have vret
through in order to protect you.
- Are you s blind?
- I'm the mistnkte disappear ...
... Because we stand by and talk.
- You're not the town's only cop.
- What do you mean?
- What do you think?
You know why I'm here?
Will you arrest me?
- Let me finish this.
- I know how to end things.
Do not you think
that pigs deserve it?
It is precisely the case.
This is not the pipe piece.
You are finished with this case.
Do you remember me?
Look at all this.
I'm impressed.
This is Tora Bora, right?
I vret with mr. Dekker
and Cole. They were inseparable.
Can you remember the Cole?
We found it here. Thank you.
- I want to know if there are copies.
- Connector Bare yourself up!
What a language. I got a glimpse
Your last mental status.
I read that everything about you and your son.
Terrible. Wrestled you still
with to visit his grave?
I was actually stirred,
when I read that about it.
I slr you fucking killed.
All of you.
We are wasting time here. I want to see if
Griff was more fortunate with the other.
- He wake up. Beautiful knife.
- Fuck off.
It is a sd boy.
It is he really.
Or should I say "was".
This m VRE old.
Taken before becoming dull
and lost hret.
Before the cancer d him up.
Grd him much?
He did so safely.
He wept enough both day and night.
- Yes.
- What?
Yes, he wept constantly.
You know why I was
s proud of him?
He never begged for his life.
Not once. That is more
than I can say about your friend Cole.
A real tough guy.
He begged for his life and pissed in
pants before I drbte him.
Come on, you bastard.
Hello? Is that you, Sean?
Where's Will?
- Is he not with you?
- Someone raided the place.
- What happened?
- There has not been anything to him.
- What happens? Here's blood.
- Nothing happens.
Say the hell not sdan to me!
What happened to him?
Hr here.
Take brnene with his neighbor.
- I promise that Will comes tonight.
- What would you gre, Sean?
What It Takes.
Have you HRT story of Baba Yaga?
Why would you have done it?
Where I come from, Little Odessa,
all know her.
Baba Yaga was a witch.
She flj around on his broom and
looking for disobedient boys and girls.
No she had found them,
she slipped in to them -
- And beat them hrdt over the knuckles.
No brnene s the bl bruises,
they knew that she was there.
S would not VRE disobedient again.
After Bosnia
I felt in myself lost.
I could not f work.
The job I got was as a night watchman
the municipal morgue.
My friends thought it was Bare, s the
started calling me Baba Yaga.
They seemed enough, it was fun, No I
swept the floor with my broom.
I decided
to aflgge them visitors.
I beat them over the knuckles.
I cut the heads off them.
My friends made me just a joke.
You and your friends
attempting to korsfste me.
I do not know what you're talking about.
I have no problem with it to do.
Wait! HR Now!
I have children.
- Did you?
- I have a wife, a little boy ...
... And a little girl.
Gr not do this.
Seemed not know that it was important?
Call Dekker. The game is over.
I should download family.
No! If dryer my family
I'll kill you!
Nevermind. It's him.
I would just call.
Dekker? Dekker? Damn.
Ringing.
Crowe, we will leave.
Come on!
- Take the needle here
- Forget it.
Take it now p!
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Shut them out!
Come on!
- Will, he flees.
- He is the VK.
We sprrer road.
Damn!
Come on!
Strmer!
Do you want me?
Do you love it?
S come and get me.
prayer your eyes.
prayer your damn eyes.
I told you
that it would g sdan here.
Gr it off with him.
Gr of him!
Shoot him, damn it!
Is it him?
Can you recognize me white?
People say I look like
my little brother, just nicer.
Do you think you are
Headquarters ugliest?
This is New Orleans.
You have not seen anything yet.
F him into the car.
Wait!
Sdan here you can not gre at me.
Let me go.
Rvhuller!
nsk you something, honey.
Happy birthday,
princess.
We will have cupcakes.
- Hey, where are you going?
- I just wanted to deliver ...
This is for Sara. It is a
pet cats and dogs.
- She will probably love it.
- I'm not s good for that.
Thank you. I do not know what I
else to say. Many thanks.
Mrs. Genz, remember me, your husband?
- We were just about to g.
- S did you FET with it here.
It's my turn.
- Where am I lucky.
- Yes, sir.
I will let you f peace.
I would just drop it there.
- Will not you stay?
- No, I'm a little ... busy.
- You can come back later.
- Yes.
Okay, I follows the rejection you out.
- She's back.
- Better, strkere and faster.
- Is everything okay?
- I'm still a little shaken.
I know.
- I thought it was over.
- But it was not.
You're doing it.
There deg just a little time.
I will go.
And you must enter them.
- What are you s afraid of?
- That one.
- Tsedreng.
- Yes you are right.
Do not worry, partner.