Oh bloody useless.
Just give me that
I suppose we should cover her
Yes
Let's call an ambulance
Right
So?
They're not a hurry I
told they she was dead
- No eggs this morning?
- I forgot to buy eggs
Get off
Quick
That's good
You didn't see anything?
Wait
OK
- What do the police think?
- The sergeant doesn't know
It was not a murder, there
are no marks on the body
You had a good look then
You can't keep your eyes off
women even when she's dead
I think she fell on water
So how do you explain
she was half naked?
May be she was drunk
May be she wander
on boats or something
May be she was pregnant
Right
Don't worry, it's
just the drink
What do you think, Joe?
- About what?
- The dead
I think she went to
the bridge fully dressed
To breath the warm night air
Then she took off her jacket
and put it on the ground
And then she
unbuttoned her blouse
And then she lifted
up her brassieres
And dropped it down on
top of other clothes
An she undone button of her skirt,
and it slipped down over her hips.
Then she undone her stockings
And hold them up so they blew in the breeze
before she let them flew off into the night
And she shivered
She wondered if she
really wanted to do it
She answered this question by
kicking her clothes into the river
And horridly now she take off
her garter and her knickers
And there she be,
standing in a petticoat
Thinking over what
brought her to this
And the with
particle below her
She dropped into
the river like a rose
And float there for a moment
And begone
What kind of
women would do that?
Just an ordinary woman
You are going to sit
there all day drinking tea?
Hi
Sign here and don't dirt it
You are the one
who found the girl?
Right
There are evil
men in this town
- How come you get so little water?
- Shut your mouth
Come on, Jim. This way
There's a good pub in Leers.
We should go there
for a game of darts
Right
Joe challange me to
a game of darts.
- You play darts?
- Sometimes
Just to pass the time
You don't find anything more
interesting to spend the time?
I can tell one or two thing
but not in front of a kid
Don't you laugh to yourself
- What is so funny?
- Eat your potato.
All of it
- Don't kick me, mom
- Stop yelling
You finished, Joe?
May be they'll say something in the
evening newspapers about that body
Do you think they'll
write about us?
No
Myself and Joe picked up a
body from the river this morning
- Naked
- Murder
Possible. She
had no clothes on
- Was she cut?
- Not a mark on her
Here we are
A body of a dead woman was found
in the River Clay this morning
The woman was wearing
only a thin petticoat
So far she was unidentified
- Police...
- You said she was naked
The same thing,
it was transparent
Les, I've got a headache,
I'm going back to the barge
- Another game of darts?
- Another time
I'll give you a game
Where's Les?
He's found someone
to play darts with
He'll be here at least an hour
We'll wake the boy
Why don't we go up on deck?
I'm not going any further
Police are
investigating that woman
There's a bit in the
newspaper about its
What makes you think of that?
Something to say
You have done enough
talking for one night
Are you sorry?
That's not good, do we?
It's pity if he's coming back
What?
The bunk there
You're nice, Joe
You hungry? I'll
fry you an egg
No, not now
I'll take a cup of tea though
- You two are bloody quiet
- Same as you, no?
- What's up Les?
- I know fine well what's up
He's lost money at darts again. And he
came back here to try to take out at me
- Listen woman...
- You shut your damned mouth, Leslie Gold!
You have no rights
to yell at me
I have never lost
money at darts
You are a liar!
- Tea is ready?
- You in a hurry?
The tea is ready
when it's ready
You read that they
wrote in the papers
They didn't mention about us
I am not really
interested in any of that
- Have you been swimming?
- I don't swim
How about you?
I don't have a
swimming costume
You are here on holiday?
It's free day today
What's your name?
Cathie
Would you like to go with
me for a walk, Cathie?
Where to?
Over there
Tim's over board!
The boy is
overboard, Ella. Help
- You alright?
- Right
Thank you.
Thanks, Joe
- Look at that
- A funfair. Can we go there?
You can ask your mom
Ella. Look at that
May be we go there with Tim?
- I've my work to do. You take him
- I'll stay aboard if you want to go
I have no time. You go
Come along, Joe?
Stretch for your legs
Yes, all right
Here we are
Watch me
- Yes, yes, that one!
- Got it
2 pence.
You see, I always win
How do you like it, son?
- And that's it
- You are touching the line, sorry
- Excuse me, I was not touching the line
- You touched the line
What are you doing here?
- I'm working here now
- Right, right, Bob. This is Joe Huggy.
He works with us
couple of months
- Nice to meet you, Joe.
- Me too
Me and Les, we used to
work on the same boat
- Never the same shipyard
- No
- That was good time?
- Yes
2 pence.
Bob, here is my son, Jim.
- Jim, this is Bob.
- We close the game
I don't want to go
back to the barge
Do you want to go to the picture?
There are two of them in town
- Do you want to go to the picture?
- Yae
Joe, do you want to
go to the picture?
No, no. I'll walk into town
then go back to the barge
Let make it quick
Go, Joe. I don't
want to see you
Go
Look what you've done
Give it to me
It's broken
Hello, Joe.
Hello, Cathie.
What are you doing here?
- I'm working here by the river
- You are working?
Joe Taylor condescend to
mix with the working class?
I don't take any pride in it
I see you never
made it to China
- Your flat is still there?
- Yes
I've got a flat mate now
Is she nice?
I don't see her much
Why barge, Joe?
You can find work
more glamorous
Just sort of have it, really
- What about you, you still at the office?
- Yes
Nothing's really changed
Except us
- What did you do with all my stuff?
- I threw them away
As you told me to
I thought I would
never see you again
- Hi gentlemen
- Go, Joe.
- You sure?
- I'm scaling a little
It'll get hot in an hour
Joe, get some sacs of coal
- Tim!
- Easy said than done
We continue?
Put it in the back
of the truck, Joe.
- It's in your truck now
- Thanks
What about the boy
- Will you come to see him?
- He'll be back in school again next week
I have some surprise for you
A banana!
- What should you say?
- Thank you, uncle Sam.
- Thanks
- Will you talk about the naked lady?
- Yes, some pervert has done it
- Me and Joe found her
- You're joking
- We called the police
Will you stop
talking about this?
All talk about it
Drink your tea
Say bye to your dad
- Bye, dad
- Bye, son. Take care of yourself
- Take care
- Bye
You're sad about Tim?
He needs an education.
But when he goes
away It breaks my heart
Think of me when you look at
yourself. With undying love, C.
I had a dream
about you yesterday
I don't think for months
- I think you have gone away
- I had gone away
I shed my own skin
and hide in the fog
I am pregnant
It's yours