Subtitle Rip; TheHeLL
(wind whistling)
(breathing heavily)
(flies buzzing)
- (woman sobbing)
- Keep the pressure on.
(grunting)
James, just stay with us.
James.
(baby crying)
James, don't.
Don't, James, please.
James.
Stay with me, James.
Stay with me.
I need you, James.
James, look at me.
(crying)
I've lost power.
Just stay with us, James.
(people screaming)
What's happening?
Fuel starvation in both engines.
- The plane's going down.
- (woman screaming)
I told you it wasn't ready.
If we'd stayed on the ground,
we'd all be dead.
We're all dead anyway.
There's a...
there's a landing strip
30 miles inside Sierra Leone.
Forget it.
We're going down now.
Woman: James.
James, look at me.
(sobbing)
No. No.
Oh God.
James, James,
please don't leave me.
Get out of the way.
No. No.
Man: You stupid...
(people screaming)
(screaming)
(gunshot)
(engine roaring)
This is it.
(people screaming)
(gunshots)
(man screams)
(speaks French)
(shouts in native language)
(engine starts)
(gunfire and shouting continue)
(gasping)
(woman gasping)
Help.
Swim over here.
Reach for my hand.
Grab my hand.
Wait! Shit.
No! No! No!
(screaming)
(insects chirping)
(birds twittering)
(flies buzzing)
(sobs)
(distant woman sobbing)
(exclaims)
(panting)
(chickens clucking)
(woman moans)
Malana.
(speaking native language)
(cocks gun)
(sniffs)
(rustling)
(engine grinding)
Okay.
(exclaims)
(engine grinding)
(engine starts)
(engine idling)
(exhales)
(engine revving)
Come on.
(gun clicking)
(gunfire)
(speaking French)
I don't understand.
You're American?
I'm American, yeah.
- Are you bitten?
- No, I'm okay.
Up.
What?
Get in.
You drive. I push.
(engine starts)
Do you know
if there's a better road?
At this rate
we're gonna break an axle.
There are roadblocks
along all the main roads.
They are scared.
They have killed many.
My orders are to be with them,
but I must find my son.
Look,
thanks for your help
back there.
For a moment I thought
you were gonna kill me.
And I thought you would leave
like the rest of your people.
They have all left...
doctors, aid workers,
missionaries.
I don't understand the white man.
Your soldiers come
with guns to fight us
and your doctors come
with medicine to save us.
Look,
I'm an engineer,
a mechanic.
I fix things... machines,
whatever needs fixing.
That's it.
An American mercenary.
I'm just trying to survive.
You know if there's an airport
around here somewhere
where you can fly out from?
There's no airport here,
not since your bombs
destroyed it.
Just a small airbase.
But I think all the planes are gone.
You're not the only person
who wants to leave, my friend.
How far away is it?
Because if there's something there,
maybe I can fix it
and we can...
we can fly out of here.
I will take you there on the condition
you give me this car.
It's not possible to survive on foot.
The dead are everywhere.
You take me there...
you get this car.
This way.
Why are you still here?
I thought all your people had left
when it started.
I was on the last plane out,
but we came under attack.
Couldn't hold them off any longer.
Couldn't get the plane ready in time.
They just took off.
The fuel lines were still attached.
I barely managed
to get on board myself.
People were running alongside
the plane, begging to get on.
We just left them there to die.
It was all for nothing.
The plane crashed off the coast.
And...
I'm the only one left.
What about you?
What are you doing here?
Our orders are
to be at the roadblocks,
to stop the spread
by shooting the infected.
But I left to find my son.
He's all I have now.
And if they find me,
they'll kill me.
Where‘s your son?
My village was attacked.
He was among the survivors.
I think they've been taken
to the military base in the north.
I'll find him there.
(gunfire)
(shouting)
Hey! Hey!
Hey hey!
Hey!
(speaks native language)
(distant gunfire)
(flies buzzing)
(sighs)
(chicken clucks)
(bones crack)
(engine starts)
(flies buzzing)
(engine rattling)
(engine stops)
How far is it?
Can we make it on foot?
With God's blessing,
I think it's possible.
(sniffs)
(gasps)
(flies buzzing)
(snarling)
(panting)
(metallic bang)
(clicks switch)
(radio waves hissing)
Hello.
Is anyone receiving? Over.
(radio waves squealing)
This is flight engineer
Lieutenant Brian Murphy,
sole survivor
of military evacuation flight
Lima November 2-6-0.
Does anyone read me? Over.
I'm stranded in hostile territory,
under constant attack,
without any food or water.
I need help.
Can anyone hear me? Over.
If anyone can hear this,
my coordinates are
20° west...
Never mind.
I have to keep moving.
Over.
(radio waves hissing)
It's useless.
There's nothing here we can use.
I found fuel.
The place I go...
it's a military base.
It might have an airplane.
It's a long journey for me alone.
Maybe it's not possible.
But with some help... maybe.
Okay.
(insects chirping)
- (branch snaps)
- (rustling)
(gas pouring)
(machete slicing)
Jesus Christ.
Please
let us not blaspheme.
We need to find
some food and water.
We're not gonna make it.
We'll find something.
I'm low on ammo.
Me too.
(sighs)
You must rest.
Maybe I should drive.
No no, I'm all right.
(engine idling)
(sighs) Okay.
(birds twittering)
(man shouts
in native language)
Who are you
and why are you with this soldier?
I'm Daniel Dembele
of the Senufo tribe.
I'm traveling north
to find my son.
He's an American...
a military engineer.
It‘s okay.
We're helping each other.
We would be very grateful
if you had some food
and water for us.
As you can see,
my friend has a fever.
(guns click)
- (people chattering)
- (woman wailing)
Why is the military
protecting this place?
These men
are no longer soldiers.
They have returned home
as brothers,
fathers and sons
to protect their families.
The war between us is no more.
There's a new war.
We have to fight it together.
Ah, that's a witch doctor.
Some believe he can protect us.
(insects chirping)
Where are you heading?
There's a military base
at the edge of the desert,
about 200 miles north of here.
I hope to find my son there.
I know of this place.
I've heard you can find
safety there.
Why don't you take
your people there?
Are they not
vulnerable here?
This is our home.
We will never leave.
Do you have family?
My son
is a bright boy.
He was doing well at school.
When he grows up,
he wants to become a doctor.
(men chattering)
What happened here?
It was about a week ago.
A woman from this village
saw her father walking
in the forest at night.
He'd been killed the day before,
attacked by what we all thought
was a wild animal.
But that was just the beginning.
Then they came.
(people screaming)
In a way, we were lucky.
We were able to regain control
and defend ourselves.
I know not every village
was as fortunate.
When it started,
I came back to find my family...
my wife.
Did you find her?
Yes, I found her.
In God's name,
what is happening to us?
(sighs)
Maybe we're being punished
for our arrogance.
Perhaps
nature has put in motion
the ultimate solution to its problem.
Man's greed has devoured this earth.
Nature is restoring
its delicate balance.
- (men speak native language)
- (gunshots)
- They won't get through.
- But for how long?
I promised my people
I would protect them.
But I think you...
My family has lived here
for generations.
I was born here
and I will die here.
- (people chattering)
- (women crying)
(exhales)
(moans)
(children laughing)
(whispering in native language)
(witch doctor speaking rapidly)
(witch doctor
continues speaking)
(witch doctor stops)
(chickens clucking)
The fever has broken.
It's time to leave.
(exhales)
(birds twittering)
Hey, take it easy.
(engine grinding)
(engine stops)
(steam hissing)
I'm sorry.
I just want to get to my son.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
We'll get there.
We cannot stay here.
Well, we've lost most of the coolant.
If we try to run this engine
for more than a few minutes,
we'll fry it.
We've got to get this
back on tight.
(grunts)
Then we've got to fill it
with water.
Stop.
There's no waterhole
along this road for many miles.
This water is all we have.
Well, we need to get water in this
or we walk.
We can't drive without it.
What if it doesn't work?
What, would you rather walk
under this heat
for I don't know how many miles?
Then we're left here
with no water and no car.
We don't have time to discuss this.
We can't make it out on foot.
This is the best chance we've got.
It's not enough.
Come on.
All right, all right.
- (cocks gun)
- (gunshot)
Come on, save your ammo.
(engine grinding)
(engine starts)
Is it safe to drink?
It's safe.
(mud)
(moans)
Oh shit.
Looks like we've busted the axle.
(moaning)
Are you all right?
(rustling)
I can't see anything.
Turn the lights on.
With the lights on
we're attracting attention.
The lights will draw them in.
(rustling)
We are blind.
How do we defend ourselves?
Shh. Listen.
- Turn the lights on.
- No.
- Turn them on.
- No, it will draw them in.
(shouts)
Turn them on!
Get out now.
- (snarling)
- Get out! Get out!
(two gunshots)
(insects chirping)
I haven't seen any for a while.
Let's chance a fire.
I've really got to eat something.
All right.
(metallic jingling)
(distant dogs baying)
What's that?
An ancient symbol...
timbu.
It means hope.
This has been in my family
for generations.
My father gave it to me
before he died.
I too will pass it on to my son.
Do you have a son?
I had a son.
And I have a wife and a daughter.
Since the networks have gone down,
I haven't been able to contact them.
I don't know if they're okay.
I don't even know
how far this thing has spread.
What's that just before the desert?
That is what you would call
the Devil's Claw...
miles of jagged rocks
we must climb to get to the desert.
Even the nomads
would not cross that.
How many rounds you got?
Not enough.
Same here.
It's getting cold.
It's getting real cold.
(jingling)
(clanging)
(snarling)
- (screams)
- Daniel!
(Daniel screaming)
Daniel!
You saved my life.
Don't be sad, brother.
I'll soon join my wife Jindibah.
I just want you...
not to let my soul...
wander this earth.
I'm sorry, Daniel.
(wings flutter)
(gunshot)
(footsteps)
(Brian whispers)
No.
Woman: Hey. Hey.
Hey.
(speaking native language)
(baby crying)
Get up.
Come on, we've got to go.
- Come on, come on, let's go.
- No.
- Come on, yes.
- (speaking native language)
What?
No no no, let's go.
Come on, get up.
No, I'm not taking your baby.
Come on, let's go.
(baby crying)
No, I don't... l...
- No.
- (shouting)
No.
(baby continues crying)
(gunshot)
Come on, it's okay.
Shh.
(flies buzzing)
(wings flutter)
(gasps)
(sighs)
Daniel's voice:
The Devil's Claw...
miles of jagged rocks we must climb
to get to the desert.
(wind whistling)
(panting)
(exhales)
(rapid gunfire)
(gunfire continues)
(people chattering)
Woman:
There are more coming, are there?
I knew the Americans were coming.
Do you have aircraft?
Do any planes land here with supplies?
No, they come by road
with any survivors.
The two last ones have not returned.
We are controlling the numbers,
but we can't keep shooting.
We are low on supplies.
Do you have any
communications equipment?
Yes, we have radio equipment,
but it's no longer working.
This is flight engineer
Lieutenant Brian Murphy.
Can anybody hear me?
(radio waves hissing)
This is flight engineer
Lieutenant Brian Murphy.
Can anyone hear me?
This is flight engineer
Lieutenant Brian Murphy.
Can anyone hear me?
This is flight engineer
Lieutenant Brian Murphy.
Can anyone hear me?
Murphy.
My God, you're still alive.
Frank? Frank Greaves?
We thought you died in the crash.
Oh, man, it's so good
to hear your voice.
Listen to me.
I don't have much time.
I need a plane.
I need supplies.
Brian,
no one's gonna send a plane.
We're at breaking point here.
Everyone's trying to get out.
Where to, I don't know.
There's nowhere left to go.
The power's down.
We're running
off standby generators.
I don't know how much longer
we can hold them back.
What about my family, Frank?
I'm sorry, Brian.
They're gone.
What do you mean, gone?
That noise you hear...
that's them.
(crash)
The desks...
stow them against the door.
- (people shouting)
- (pounding)
I'm sorry, Murphy,
but I have to go now.
No. No, Frank, wait.
May God be with us.
Wait.
(pounding)
(women crying)
(people screaming)
Daniel's voice:
Timbu... it means hope.
(upbeat music playing)