Crimson and clover
Over and over
...believe your eyes...
those are the northern lights
on view above the city...
forthefirsttime
in nearly eighty years.
Oh, Susie Q, baby, l love you
lt's 5.00 a.m.
Hello, New York.
The big story this morning
is the Amazings...
taking thefield today
in Baltimore...
fortheirfinal practise
before tomorrow's opener...
of the 1969 World...
Early this morning,
sanitation workers...
discovered the dead body
of another nurse...
in a Dumpster in Queens.
This is the third nurse killed
in what New York papers...
are now calling
the Nightingale murders.
All three victims
have been nurses...
each of themfound strangled...
with their hands gruesomely
bound behind their backs...
with glass tape.
The lights, also known
as the aurora borealis...
Look out!
Manhattan calling
Eye of the Storm.
Engine company one-two,
ladder company nine-three...
respond to Manhattan box...
one-three-two off-ramp
on George Washington Bridge.
On ourway.
Frank,we're the second in.
We gotthe rescue.
Great.
Commander,
what do you need done?
That dike's aboutto go.
We're one spark away
from losing the block.
ls there anotherway in?
Only that manhole
leads to the vault.
Forget it, Sullivan.
Vault door's rusted shut,
and they can't kill the juice.
Frank,you're not gonna make it.
There's not enough time.
What, miss the World Series?
Not a chance.
Give me my tools.
Sullivan,
this is Commander O'Connell.
Can you hear me?
l hearyou, Commander.
The gasoline
is rising in the vault.
Those downed cables
hitthat gas, it's gonna blow.
Way to go, Gib.
l should have been
a goddamn mailman.
Clearthis channel.
Explosion's imminent.
Guys. Can you hear me?
- We're in here.
- Comin' in.
- Get us out.
- He's got a broken leg!
Frank, it's gonnaflash.
Get outta there.
The dike isn't holding.
Get us out!
Frank, did you hear me?
l hearyou, Butch.
Grabthat axe.
Here.
Gimme a whack. No sparks.
Again.
One more.
OK, stand back.
Thank God!
My leg's all busted up.
Please hurry.
We're in, Butch.
Getthem and getthe hell out!
Hey,fellas.
Time to go home.
Watch it! Watch it!
lt'sfalling.
lt's gonna break!
Let's go. That's an order!
Everybody goes!
All right. Let's move
before the gas lights up.
Watch thatwire!
Get out,for Christ's sake!
l gotyou.
Butch,
we're comin' out right now.
Go!
You all right?
Watch your head.
Get upthat ladder!
Go ahead!
Get up! Get up!
Go on up!
Go! Right behind you!
l'm going!
Pull him up!
Come on!
Come on. L gotyou.
Welcome to the company, Gib.
Hey,fellas?
Hey, Dad.
Hey. Hey, Gordo.
Hey, Mr. Sullivan.
How you doin'?
- How's my Little Chief?
- Good.
- Where's your mother?
- lnside the house.
Hey,Jules.
- Hey, bud.
How about
a little bit of the King?
Yeah,why not a little
of the King?
Damn!
You all right?
Yeah. L think l ruined
the sauce...again.
What's the matter, bud?
Trouble working an 8-hour shift
atthe hospital...
watchin' the kid,
whipping up a little Bolognese?
You didn't marry Donna Reed.
l'd goforyou...
and Chinese takeout
over her any day.
Because l love you too much,
baby
Why can'tyou see
Whatyou're doin' to me
- How was yourtour?
- The usual.
Butch called.
- Did he?
- He did.
ltwas under control, bud.
Butch, he's getting
a little tight in his old age.
Nothing wrong with old age,
as long as you getthere.
All right, Chief.
When l let go,
l wantyou to keep pedalling.
Putthe wheels back on.
l'm gonnafall.
Don'tworry aboutfalling.
You're ready to do this.
Come on.
Spirit and guts, OK?
All right.
Keep pedalling.
l'm gonna let go. That's it.
Keep pedalling. Keep pedalling.
Keep pedalling.
You all right?
Johnny?
You OK? Are you hurt?
Are you OK? You OK?
Go on, honey. Lt's OK.
Come on, Chief.
Don't quit on me now.
Don't be so tough on him.
He's just a kid.
He just needs to know
you're behind him.
OK. You're right. All right.
CQ-22,this is W2QYV,
byfor call.
...because of
the solar activity.
lt's beautiful.
We gotthe sky
lit up like a bonfire.
Word is the sunspots
are shooting offflares...
that stretch out
half a million kilometres.
Tell me about it.
l'm picking up signals
l could never reach before.
Francis, is thatyou?
How are you doing, myfriend?
l'm doing great.
How you doing?
Fantastic.
My wife, Sophia,
she's giving me another baby.
So,that's it, Samantha?
You're justwalking out?
l've been walking out
for six months,John.
You just didn't notice or care.
You're right.
We shoulda quit a long time ago.
l'm sorry.
l know it's myfault.
l can't change, Sam.
l wish l could, but l can't.
No,John,
it's thatyou won't change.
And that's what hurts so much.
Goodbye, Chief.
Next up,Johnny Sullivan.
lt's a hit upthe middle.
And Johnny's gonna
hold atfirst.
Now battingforJohnny'sfather,
Coach Newman.
He checks the runner andfires.
Lined hard to right.
No problem.
One on. One out.
- Hi, Uncle John.
- l'm notyour uncle, kid.
Hey, Sully. Ls thatyou?
Gordo,what are you guys
doing in my house?
My TV's out again.
Hey,you want a brewski?
Do you believe Linda still
won't let me cook in the house?
l melt one lousyfrying pan,
you know?
John, guess what?
Dad's taking mefishing.
- Wanna come?
- l wish l could, Gordy.
Butyou bring me back
a big one, OK?
ls it OK if Gordy
uses your old gear?
l think it's somewhere
in the hall closet...
if you canfind it.
Gordy, have a look.
Yahoo went up
anotherfive points today.
Did l miss the boat on that one.
Shoulda,woulda, coulda, pal.
So Sam called Linda.
Dad,John, come here!
Gordy,what are you
doing backthere?
Dad, check it out.
Fire department.
Can l open it up?
Sure.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Gimme that gun.
All right?
What's this, Dad?
Oh, my God.
John,
it's your dad's old ham radio.
Remember how we used to beg him
to let us talk on this thing?
- This...is not a toy.
- ls not a toy.
Can we try it, Dad?
Ask Uncle John.
Can we try it?
Whatthe hell.
All right. Here.
Let's grabthis baby out.
This is whatwe used
when l was your age.
Let's go overto the den.
Plug it in, like the old times.
We want CW or LSB.
Standbyfunction.
Operator. Come on.
l don't know what's going on.
Let's take a look
underthe hood.
See whatwe got here.
Checkthis baby out.
There she is.
This is what people used
before the Net?
Not exactly.
l'll tell you.
Hams were...Ah, bingo!
These babies were different.
Not everybody
had one of these...
and you needed a special licence
justto be able to talk on them.
Damn. L just...
l don'tthink it's gonna work.
lt's junk, kid.
Nobody
uses those things anymore.
Gordo,
do you know whattime it is?
- Hey,John.
- Hi, Linda.
Come on, Gordy. Let's go.
l'll catch you later,
if l'm lucky.
Hi. This is Julia Sullivan.
Please leave a message
afterthe tone.
Hey, Ma. Lt's me.
Just checking in.
You're probably atwork.
Anyways,
l'll see you tomorrow night.
Love you.
The aurora borealis,
to anyone who's seen it...
is one of the stunning events
of your lifetime.
They're brighterthese days.
ls something going on there?
Do they tie in with yourfield?
Where do they comefrom?
lt's truly a stunning sight.
lt's beautiful to look at.
l don'tthinkwe've seen one
this brightforthirty years.
From the point of view
of physics and string theory...
there's nothing really
thatwe gain...
from studying
the aurora borealis.
History does teach us...
that every time we thought
we had itfigured out...
there was some major discovery
right around the bend...
that required complete
dramatic change...
in our understanding
of the laws of physics.
This is a phrase people have
begun to hear, string theory.
Yes,that's right.
String theory dramatically
changes our understanding...
of space and time.
For example, itturns out
that string theory...
requires our universe to have 10
or possibly even 11 dimensions.
The strange thing is...
some physicists
are even pursuing the idea...
thatthere might be more
than one time dimension.
So in addition to time as we
know it, psychological time...
which seems to organize events
in the universe around us...
there may be
a second time dimension...
where the universe evolves
in some different manner.
Another phrase...
CQ-15. Come in, 15.
W2QYV here. Who have l got?
Name's John.
You licensed to broadcast,
buddy?
Look. L really don't remember
how this thing works.
Listen. You can't broadcast
without a licence.
Unless this is an emergency,
you have to get off the band.
Hey, pal,
my whole life's an emergency.
Where you transmittingfrom?
Queens, New York.
What do you know?
Bayside, born and raised.
No kidding?
l thoughtthese things were
fortalking around the world.
The 15 band
closes down at night...
but during the day...
you can chew the band with China
if you want.
l can't believe people
are still using these things.
You must be a real old-timer.
Days like this, lfeel like
l'm getting there,you know?
So, Queens,
you psychedforthe series?
You know, l really don't
follow baseball anymore.
What?
l gotfed up
with all the bullshit.
What are you talking about?
Let me tell you something.
A thousand yearsfrom now...
when school kids study
aboutAmerica...
they're gonna learn
aboutthree things.
The Constitution,
rock'n' roll, and baseball.
How can you live in Queens
and not love the Amazings?
The Amazing Mets?
What,the'69 series?
Man, l'll love Ron Swoboda
till the day l die.
Now l'm with you.
He's gotthe heart of a lion.
Mets can'twin game one
without him.
Can you hear me?
Game one?
What are you talking about?
ltwas all over after Buford...
nailed Seaver's second pitch
out of the park.
No way, buddy.
Ain't gonna happen.
Hey, CQ-15.
CQ-15, are you there?
Who the hell was that?
Queens, are you there, Queens?
Did l lose you?
Hey, Frank.
Give the radio a rest.
Your son wants
to say good night.
All right.
l'll be rightthere.
Would parallel universes
ever become aware of each other?
Who knows?
lt's a strange idea...
Elvis,you all right?
l'm sorry.
- You OK, Frank?
- We'refine.
You all right, buddy?
You OK, buddy?
The sunspots are going to
have a serious impact...
on radio communications
forthe next six or seven days.
lnfact,
quantum theory tells us...
thatthe rigid notions
of past, present andfuture...
although useful
in day-to-day life...
may dissolve and be replaced
by a complexformulation...
in which time
isfar morefluid...
than anybody
would have imagined.
Take me outto the ballgame
Take me outwith the crowd
Buy me some peanuts
and CrackerJacks
l don't care if l never get back
'Cause it's root
Root, rootforthe home team
lf we don'twin
Two,three strikes you're out
Atthe old ballgame
That's perfect.
Butch,
you gotta turn the whole set.
Can'twaittill the game.
lt's notthe tuner.
lt's the antenna.
- Proby.
- What?
Pointthe antenna out
from underthe house.
There it is.
Proby,walk away.
Satch, grab a seat.
Sully, l think l need
a new set of cleats.
l lost myfooting there.
Dr DeLeon,
you decided to join us.
You don'twanna know.
Thirty-six hours,
l was bouncing off the walls.
That's why you're the doctor,
l'm the nurse.
Can l getyou something?
No. Lt's all right.
ln leftfield, Don Buford.
Paul Blair is in centrefield.
- How you boys doing?
- Good, Satch.
OK. l've got somethingforyou.
l can't believe it!
And l got somethingforyou.
- Dad, look!
- What? You gotta be...
Hey, Satch,what are you,
Santa Claus or something?
Game three tickets.
- Did you say thankyou?
- Thankyou.
You're welcome.
Thankyou, Satch.
Hey, all right.
Wait,wait,wait,wait.
Everybody.
Everybody say, "Amazing Mets."
Amazing Mets.
Don't choke on your pride, Sul.
You ain't never gonna
find another one like Sam.
She made up her mind, Satch.
Nothin' l do is gonna change it.
Nothing you're willing to do.
- What's the story?
- Construction crewfound a body.
Actually, a skeleton.
OK. Well, be real careful
when you pull it out.
Make sure you get
the dirt around it.
What's this construction?
l think l'll visit
the neighbours, Satch.
Yeah, OK.
What did they tear down here?
Greek diner.
l used to get breakfastthere
all the time.
Them Greeks were good people.
Careful. Lt's hot.
Thankyou, Mrs Shepard.
Once that McDonald's
opened up on Dyckman...
they lost all their business.
- l see your son's on the job.
- Was.
Jack died a while back.
lt's hard. L know.
ltjust seems like yesterday.
My son lived and bled blue.
- Get out of here.
- OK, Detective.
- Give my regards to Beth.
- Sure will.
This isn't going to be anything
but a history lesson.
Let's go backto the house.
Hey, Barney. How you doing?
Good.
Here you go. Have a good night.
l thought it'd be nicer
to eat here.
Sounds good.
l'm sorry Samantha
couldn't make it.
Those grad school applications
are driving her crazy.
How's it coming?
l gotthe VCR hooked up.
lt's justthisfriggin' clock.
Doesn't matter.
l'm sorry, Mom.
l know. Lt's all right.
l'm sure everything
will work out.
What's that?
With Sam.
Oh,yeah,you know,
just a tough time right now.
So how are things
atthe hospital?
Fine.
Dr Schwartz retired last month.
No kidding.
- He must have been pushing 90.
- Close,yeah.
So how'd you like
"The Lion King"?
l loved it.
ltwas sweet, kid.
l wish you'd gone.
Yeah, l know.
l'm sorry. Lt's work.
Yeah,well,you worktoo hard.
Lookwho's talking.
- lt's tomorrow.
- Thirty years.
l wish l could
remember him better.
He was just a big kid.
He wanted to
play baseballforever.
Andfightingfires,
he loved that.
And you, he loved you.
OK, guys. Bedtime.
Looking good.
We'll do it again tomorrow,
Chief.
Good night, Dad.
CQ-15. CQ-15.
W2QYV calling
unidentified station Queens.
CQ-15?
W2QYV calling
unidentified station Queens.
CQ-15, come in, Queens.
ls thatyou?
l've been trying to "Q" you
all night. Where you been?
How the hell did you do it?
Do what?
Do what? The series.
You called Buford's homer.
How the hell did you do it?
ltwasn'ttoo tough, buddy.
The game happened 30 years ago.
Yeah, right. Yeah,
thirty years ago. Yeah, sure.
l suppose you could tell me
what happened in game two?
Sure. Top of the ninth,Al Weis,
game-winning RBl single.
Brooks Robinson
grounds outto end the game.
Daddy, come up
and sing the baseball song.
Hey, Little Chief.
You all right?
Just go on up.
l'll be there in a minute.
Sorry aboutthat.
Thatwas my kid.
What'd you just say?
Sorry aboutthat.
My kid just came in.
You call your son
"Little Chief"?
What'd you say your name was?
Frank. Frank Sullivan.
ls this some kind of joke?
Gordo, is thatyou?
Are you messing with me?
l ain't messing with you.
l'm justtrying tofigure out...
You're telling me
your name is Frank Sullivan...
you live in Queens,
and you wanna know...
how l called thefirst game
of the 1969 World Series?
Yeah,that's exactly
what l wanna know.
Gordo, if this is you,
so help me.
- What'd you say...
- Gordo?
What'd you say your call station
oryour call letters were?
W2QYV.
Now you listen to me.
My name is
John Francis Sullivan.
l live at34342nd Avenue,
where l've lived my whole life.
l saw thefirst game
of the 1969 World Series...
right here in this house
thirty years ago.
Bullshit.
Myfather's name
is Francis Patrick Sullivan.
He was afire-fighter
and a die-hard Metsfan.
- Every night...
- Bullshit!
...he sang to me
"Take Me Outto the Ballgame."
Who the hell are you?
Son of a bitch!
What's going on?
Nothing's going on.
Oh, my God.
You burntthe desk.
l can see it.
Are you still there?
You burntthe desk.
l can see it.
Come back! Talkto me!
Listen to me.
You listen to me right now.
l don't know who you are
orwhy you're doing this.
But let me tell you something,
asshole.
You stay away
from me and myfamily.
No, no, no.
You gotta believe me.
l don't know how
this is happening...
but it's me, Little Chief.
Hey. Look. L am warning you.
lf you touch my kid...
l will huntyou down till
the day l die. You gotthat?
Butyou already died.
What are you talking about?
The Buxtonfire.
When did that happen,
thirty years ago?
October 12, 1969.
Tomorrow. You're telling me
l'm gonna die...
l ain't dying
in nofire tomorrow.
My God,tomorrow. Listen.
Tomorrow hasn't happened.
Right. Lt hasn't happened.
lt ain't gonna happen.
You gotta listen to me.
ltwas an abandoned warehouse.
Butch always told Ma
itwasn'tyourfault.
You wentwith your instincts.
- l'm warning you.
- Listen to me.
lf you'd gone the otherway,
you would have made it.
Hello? Shit!
Sully,what are you doing, man?
l talked to him, Gordo.
l talked to my dad.
Sully, go in the house.
l'm gonna come over,
and we'll hang out.
No. L gotta get him back
so he doesn't go in.
Go in? Go in where?
The warehouse in Buxton.
lt's tomorrow.
Yeah, right. Yeah,
thirty years ago. Yeah, sure.
l suppose you could tell me
what happened in game two?
Sure. Top of the ninth,Al Weis,
game-winning RBl single.
Come on. Come on.
Hit it out,Al!
Look atthe stats.
Look at'em.
Yeah, all right!
We have a 3 and 2 response.
Ladder93.
You'refirst due.
Flash is reported to be
an abandoned warehouse...
atthefoot of Water Street
and Third.
You got some
construction-limited access.
Al Weis
is having a great series.
Yeah! We won!
Frank. You all right?
We know it's vacant.
Nobody goes in.
Surround and drown.
Callfor a tower.
Help!
Shit! We got squatters inside.
Help! Help!
My sister!
She's upthere! She passed out!
Where's your sister?
Whatfloor?
- l tried to help!
- Tell me whatfloor!
On the topfloor.
l tried. L tried.
Please help her! Please!
Take her. Come on, Proby.
Anybody else upthere?
Ryan, get her medical treatment.
Gimme my gear.
- Hey, Sul.
- Satch.
Here he is.
How youfeeling, Sul?
What can l tell you?
Here you go.
Better.
No visiblefire
first or secondfloor.
Watch your step, Proby.
Thisfloor's rotten.
We gotfire on the thirdfloor.
We're goin' up.
Frank,we gottwo lines
coming behind you.
Back out, kid!
Waitforthe line!
The hell with the line.
l'llfind anotherway up.
No,you can't help me, kid.
So you doing OK,John?
Yeah. Tough day,you know.
Here's to your dad.
Thirty years today.
To your dad.
To my dad.
We're pulling everyone
out of the building.
Getthat upto the topfloor.
lt's cooking up here.
So afterthat Halloween thing
with thefire truck, remember?
l remember riding around
with Butch and your dad...
and the whole neighbourhood
was watching.
l remember.
l wanted to go as a cop.
Yeah, so then Jules
makes your dad...
buy you that cop kit
foryour birthday.
l rememberthat.
l was always the robber.
l was always being handcuffed.
That's right.
l taughtyou to do that.
Ten-forty-five.
lfound the girl.
- She's breathing.
- Getthem out.
Hang on!
Whatthe hell is going on?
Gino,what's the matter?
The gear box, it's cracked!
Frank! Frank!
The ladder's jammed!
You gottafind anotherway out!
Frank, can you hear me?
ltworked out OK.
You're a better cop
than afireman.
No doubt about it.
Worked out goodfor me,too.
l'm glad l didn't have to spend
ten years as his hose man.
Yeah, l betyou are.
The Buxtonfire.
lf you had just gone
the otherway.
Frank,
we're losing the building!
l know.
Hey, hey, hey.
This is not a toy.
Wave to Ma.
Ma, look at us.
He's some ballplayer.
John,you all right?
- l'm sorry.
- What is it?
- ls everything OK?
- Yeah. Can you bring a towel?
Satch, myfather didn't die
in afire, right?
Gordo,
myfather didn't die in afire.
What are you talking about,
Johnny? He had cancer.
Cancer. Because itwas
the cigarettes, right?
Yeah, lung cancer,
ten years ago.
Little Chief.
Gordo, l ain't dreaming here.
l talked to him. Ltwas real.
Little Chief!
What are you talking about?
ltwas a ham radio.
That's how come he didn't die.
Little Chief!
John. John Sullivan,
are you there?
Come on. Answer me.
Chief. Chief, are you there?
l'm right here, Daddy.
Come here.
Come on.
- Where's Elvis?
- He's sleeping.
- Why aren'tyou sleeping?
- You woke me up.
l did?
l got an idea.
What's that?
All right, Chief.
What do you say we tame
this bronco?
l'm scared.
l know.
And you know what?
l'm gonna be right here
with you.
Always.
Daddy, l can't.
Well,we can.
We can do ittogether.
You and me.
Spirit and guts.
What do you say?
All right. Come on.
Now,you justtake yourtime.
l'm not going to let go
until you say it's OK.
All right.
Start pedalling.
That's it.
Getyour balance.
- Ready?
- Wait!
OK, l'm still here.
All right.
lt's all you.
Look at me!
lt's all you, Chief.
Look at me, Dad.
Look atyou.
You're doing it.
- l'm doing it!
- You're doing it.
- How's itfeel?
- Good.
This is great!
lt's like l'm on
aflying trapeze!
- Look atyou!
- Thisfeels great!
- You're goin' around the world!
- lt's likeflyin'!
- Wait'll your mother sees this!
- Look at me!
Let's wake upthe world, huh?
Oh, my God.
John Sullivan?
lt's me.
You're the voice of an angel.
Reached right out of heaven...
and you pulled my butt
out of thefire.
Tell me l'm not dreaming here.
Tell me it's really you.
lt's me,John.
This ain't no dream.
But how could it be?
l don't know.
Butwe gotta be talking off
the mother sunspot of all time.
Yeah, l'd say so.
You OK, Chief?
Yeah, l'mfine.
You sure?
Yeah, it's...
lt's tough to explain.
l mean, l got all these
new memories, but it's...
it's like l don't know
whatto believe.
What do you mean?
'Cause l still remember
what itwas like...
when you died in thefire.
But l'm the only one.
l don't understand
whatyou're talking about.
l remember both...
atthe same time.
And...it's like
waking upfrom a dream...
and you're not sure what's real.
l rememberyou being here, but l
also rememberwhen you weren't.
l'm sorry,John.
l'm sorry.
l neverthoughtthat...
Well,
you gotta think aboutthat...
and you gotta be more careful,
'cause l can't lose you again.
Not like that.
You won't,John.
You won't.
l swearto God,
no matterwhat, not like that.
You got it? You hear me?
You hear me, Chief?
l hearyou.
So how old are you?
l'm thirty-six.
Thirty-six.
You're all grown up.
You gotta be married
and everything.
No, l'm not married.
What,you're too busy
playing ball?
No, it didn'twork out.
l gave it up.
What happened?
l just...blew my arm out
my senioryear.
Didn't have a shot.
Oh, l'm sorry.
l'm sorry,Johnny.
l know that had to hurt.
Yeah. Thanks.
So,what'd you wind up doing?
You join the department?
Actually, l wentthe otherway.
l'm a cop.
You're third-generation
fire-fighter.
l thoughtyou were gonna
grow out of that cop phase.
You got Satch to thank
forthat one.
You gotta be kidding me.
Satch.
He always crazy aboutyou
ever since you were born.
You're still my Little Chief.
Right?
Yeah, l'm trying to be.
l'm trying.
Well,tell me aboutyourself.
Tell me aboutyour life.
l mean,
where do l start,you know?
Mustang? L don't own a Mustang.
Well,you will,
and you loved it.
Fire-engine red.
Four on thefloor.
Seventy home runs?
That's a record
thatwill never be broken.
l wouldn't be too sure.
The other guy hit sixty-six.
Really? You mean like
those bigfield radios...
they use in the army?
No, much smaller.
Works off a satellite
or something.
You carry it around
in your pocket.
What about "Apollo"?
How did it all work out?
ltwas a great series, Pop.
Amazing.
We win, right?
Hold your horses.
l'm getting there.
Game three,
Agee came through...
homered off Palmer
in the second.
l knew Agee was going to have
a great series.
Forget aboutAgee.
Wait until you hear
what happened to Cleon Jones.
- Now you sound like your mother.
- No, l'm serious.
Come on. Your grandfather...
he smoked two packs a day,
and he's still kicking.
Notyou. Lt's gonna get
the better of you.
Well, l just knew.
She melted my heart.
Thatwas it.
You got anybody?
Yeah. Kinda.
Something l gotta work out,
but...
she's worth it.
No,you...go ahead.
You get some rest.
l'm tired,too.
l almost don'twanna
click off here, like...
maybe we won't getthis back.
We will.
l'll be here tomorrow.
l know.
l love you, son.
l...
l love you,too, Dad.
And...
l've missed you so much.
Hi. This is Julia Sullivan.
Please leave a message
afterthe tone.
Hey, Ma. Lt's me.
Just call me. We gotta talk.
- Take overfor me?
- All right.
Frank,what's going on?
Nothing. L justwanted
to see you,that's all.
l'm not going anywhere,Jules.
Notforthe rest of your life.
l got a badfeeling today.
l was worried.
Look at me.
Not a scratch.
Where's Johnny?
He's at Gordo's.
l tucked him in.
You give him his drops?
One in each ear.
Whatwould you do without me?
Probably marry some rich doctor.
Never have to work.
Oh, my God.
What is he doing?
Frank, l gotta...
Excuse me, Doctor.
ls that Benazepril?
l gave this patient
fifty mils of Benadryl.
Mix them and he's dead.
- Why wasn't l informed?
- lt's in his chart.
Hello, Ma?
Noah's Deli.
Oh, no. Sorry.
This is Noah's Deli.
Sam, l gotta talkto you.
Excuse me?
l'm sorry,
but l gotta talkto you.
How do you know my name?
Who are you?
Who am l?
Look. L don't know you.
You don't know me?
What do you mean,
you don't know me?
Wait. L do know you.
You're Linda and Gordo'sfriend.
The neighbour. The cop.
What are you doing here?
l shouldn't have come here.
l didn't mean to upsetyou.
l'm sorry.
Yeah, l'll take care of it.
What?
Another rough night?
ls that it?
Yeah,that's it.
Do not disrespect me,John.
Disrespectyourself
all you wantto...
but not me
or anybody else here.
You gotthat?
We gotthe preliminaryforensics
back on the skeleton.
You wantto take a look atthis.
Bad memories.
You imagine the odds of us
digging up a Nightingale murder?
She makes ten.
Ten?
No, l rememberthis case.
ltwas three.
He killed three women.
What are you talkin'?
You know betterthan anybody,
John.
You looked atthesefiles
a thousand times.
Dad? You there?
Can you hear me?
Dad, l need you to be there.
Yeah! Yeah, Chief.
l'm comin', l'm comin'.
Listen.
There's something l need to t...
Right here, Chief.
Something happened.
Something pretty bad.
What's the matter,Johnny?
What is it?
Mom. Something happened to her.
Your mom? What?
She's not here.
What do you mean,
she's notthere?
She died. But it's like
itjust...happened,though.
She died?
Your mom just died?
No. Dad, it happened
a long time ago.
A long time agofor me.
When?
October 22, 1969.
That's now,Johnny.
That's nextweek.
You gotto tell me how.
She was murdered.
Murdered?
What are you talking about?
There was this case, a serial.
They never caught him,
but he murdered three women...
all nurses,
between 68th and 69th.
They call him the Nightingale.
The Nightingale?
We've been watching that
on the news. L was worried...
Dad,we did something.
Something to make itworse.
l don't understand.
He didn'tjust kill three women
anymore. He's killed ten.
Something we did
changed the past.
But how come your mother...
Everything you did is different
than whatwould have happened...
if you would have never
gotten out of thatwarehouse.
Now what'd you do last night,
Dad?
l talked to you.
l putyou on the bike.
l tucked you in
over at Gordo's...
and l wentto see your mother
over atthe hospital.
Oh, shit. That's it.
She wasn't supposed to be there.
Butch went and got her.
Thatwas the night of thefire
when he brought her home.
You're saying something happened
atthat hospital?
That's justthe beginning.
lt could have been
anywhere, place,time...
that she wouldn't have been
if you woulda died.
l'll take her awayfrom here,
Johnny.
l have to take her away.
He cannot hurt her
if l take her away.
What aboutthe others, Dad?
l'll warn them.
That'll neverwork.
They'll justthinkyou're crazy.
But l gotta do something.
l...
You don't even know
whatthis guy looks like.
Nobody got any...
Hold on. Wait a minute.
Dad, l may not know
who he is...
but l know
where he's gonna be...
and what he's gonna do
before he gets there.
What do l do?
Do l call the police?
They're not gonna believe me.
They will if they catch him
in the act.
You can make that happen, Dad.
No,Johnny. L don't know.
l'm afire-fighter.
l'm a cop!
This is what l do.
This is something we have to do!
What if the ham stops working?
What if l can't reach you?
Then you get Mom the hell out.
But, Dad,those otherwomen
were not supposed to die.
lf we don't do something
and try to stopthis guy...
we'll have to live with that
forthe rest of our lives.
OK,tell me whatto do.
All right.
The nextvictim
is Carrie Reynolds.
lt happens tomorrow.
Casefile said she left
the Roosevelt Hospital at 6.00.
Showed up at Cozy's Bar
around 6.30.
She walked out of that bar
around 7.30...
and theyfound her dead in
an alley behind the bar at8.00.
l wantyou tofollow her...
see if anybody's watching her
or hitting on her.
'Cause l'm betting when she
walks out of that place...
somebody's gonna come
out of there with her.
When they do,
you call the cops.
Hi, Carrie.
Hiya, Glen. How you doin'?
Real good.
From the girls, pal.
Thanks.
l was...
Sit down.
- Fireman, huh?
- Yeah. L'm not really...
Ah, a marriedfireman.
Whatthe hell.
What do they call you?
7-4 Homicide.
Yeah, it's me.
You're kidding.
Hold on. Spell thatfor me.
OK. Thanks, Mario.
Our lucky break.
Mario lD'd the dental.
Her name is Mary Finelli.
Reported missing April 16, 1968.
April 16?
That means she was thefirst.
Which means
he probably knew her.
This case just got hot.
She's gone.
Carrie Reynolds isn't in here.
Who?
He did it.
Carrie Reynolds
is alive and well, Dad.
l'll be damned.
Did you see him?
- Figure who he is?
- No, l messed up.
l just kepttalking to her.
l was afraid to let her
out of my sight.
Whoever itwas,
he must've backed off.
That's OK. We're gonna get him.
This is gonna work.
l hope so.
So,what else you got?
We caught a break.
Found hisfirstvictim.
Her name is Mary Finelli.
- Thanks, Mrs Sullivan.
- Hang on a sec,John.
Hey,Jules,there's somebody
l wantyou to talkto. OK?
Remember l told you
aboutthis guy,John?
l wantyou to say hello to him.
Say hello to my wife,Julia.
Franktells me you're a cop.
Yeah,that's right.
My six-year-old keeps telling us
he wants to be a policeman...
right after he retires
from the majors.
We just bought him a badge
and a whistlefor his birthday.
Yeah, l remember. L used to play
cops and robbers all the time...
butyou...my mom wouldn't
let me have a toy gun.
Sounds like your mom
and l would get along.
Yeah, she's pretty special.
l'm real proud of her.
l bet she's proud of you,too.
Being a cop and all.
l hope so.
l hope she knows
how much l love her.
Oh, she knows.
Moms always know how much
their kids love them.
Even if they don'ttell them
all the time, like they should.
Well, l gotto go.
ltwas good talking to you,
John.
Yeah,you,too.
l wantto talk on Daddy's radio.
OK, go ahead.
OK, sweetheart.
Say good nightto John.
Good night,John.
Good night,there, Chief.
OK, guys. Bedtime.
No. L wanna talk
on the radio,too.
All right, Gordo. Come here.
OK, Gordo,two minutes,
then bedtime.
Sit rightthere.
Just one more cookie, Mom.
- No more cookies.
- Just one more.
This is the space cowboy.
l'm an intergalactic
traveller...
from the Federation
planet Earth.
How do you know my name, mister?
Listen, Gordo,
my name is Santa Claus.
l'm going to give you...
the biggest Christmas present
thatyou ever had.
l better give you
my address,then.
No, don'tworry about it, kid.
This is important.
Something you gotto remember
for a long time: Yahoo.
What's that?
lt's a magic word.
lt's like...
like abracadabra,
but even better.
Try it out, kid. Yahoo.
Yahoo.
You got it, Space Cowboy.
OK, Gordo.
Yourtwo minutes are up.
Go upstairs and write it down.
OK, mister. L mean, Santa.
Come on. Let's go.
Stay there,John.
l'll be right back.
Come on. Upstairs.
Jules,we got a live one
down here. Comin' yourway.
Yeah, Chief.
You still there?
Yeah. What do we do now?
Sissy Clark.
423 Greenwich Street...
Hang on. Go ahead.
Sissy Clark.
423 Greenwich Street,
Apartment 2E. Tomorrow.
OK. 2E.
Nurse. Moonlights
as a cocktail waitress...
atthe Kaleidoscope
on West rd.
Leftwork at 2.00 a.m.
Was killed in her apartment
between 2.15 and 5.00.
OK, l got it.
l don't know how long this thing
is gonna keepworking.
Hope we'll be able
to talk again.
Just be careful, all right?
l'm happy youfound her,
Detective.
lt makes it easier now
to knowfor sure.
You know.
Can l keepthesefor a while,
Mrs Finelli?
OK,just let me
walkyou through it.
l'm all ears.
Three guys show up in both
the yearbook and diary.
First guy passed away
ten years ago.
Second guy died in Vietnam.
And the third one's
Daryl Simpson.
So l ran him though B.C.l.
Got a hit.
Bustedfor sexual assault...
eight days after
the last Nightingale murder.
March 22, 1970.
You thinkthe murders stopped
because he was off the street...
and by the time
he got paroled...
he had smartened up enough
to control himself?
That's notthefirsttime
that's been true.
l got afeelin' aboutthis guy.
This is him, Satch.
Can l getyou another one?
No,thanks. L'm good.
Anything else?
Sexual assault, Daryl.
Five years.
Butyou got lucky, right?
You got away
with something else.
Something youfigured
nobody knows about.
What l know is what l told you.
Let me tell you what l know.
You wentto St. Ambrose
with Mary.
You livedfive blocks
from her...
and you liked her,
but she ain't interested.
- That must've hurt, huh?
- So what?
- So what'd you do about it?
- Nothing!
Can l have a smoke?
Here. L'm trying to quit.
Oh, my God. What is this?
Ah,Jesus!
Getthat awayfrom me!
Sandra Moore. Patti Ryan.
Mary Finelli.
These names mean anything
to you, pal?
Julia Sullivan.
Does she mean anything?
Well, she means something to me!
See you,fireman.
Don'ttalk so much nexttime.
Gus,will you run my tips
while l go change?
- Sure, Sissy.
- Thanks.
You know, Daryl...
sometimes,
despite all the training...
thatwe cops go through...
despite all thatwe are taught
about right and wrong...
despite all thatwe would
like to honour in ourselves...
we can come to a place...
where we don't give a damn.
Know what l mean?
You're going to tell me
everything l need to know.
John. You got a minute?
Yeah. Sure.
He ain'tthe guy,John.
Just'cause he didn'twant
to look atthe photos...
doesn't mean he isn'tthe one.
Not everyonefits the profile.
lf he was gonna
give up something...
he would've done it already.
Youfollowin' me?
Huh? Youfollowin' me?
l asked you a question, asshole.
Mary Finelli.
Dude,what happened to him?
ltwas a bad trip, man.
A little time kissing
the porcelain, he'll befine.
Yeah, l understand that.
All right. Come on, pal.
Open up. Miss Clark!
Open the door!
lt's the police!
lt's OK, ma'am. Go back inside.
lt's the police.
Are you in there? Open up!
l know you're in there!
Sissy Clark! Open the door!
Open the door!
He killed her.
l couldn't do a damn thing
to stop it.
Dad, it's notyourfault.
Yes, it is.
We changed everything,Johnny.
lt's like we cheated.
Dad? We can't go back...
'cause you didn't die
in thatfire.
No matterwhatyou do,
nothing is gonna change it.
All we can do is deal with this
and try to make it right.
l'm not a cop.
l'm notfooling anybody.
l know, butwe can.
We can do ittogether.
Remember spirit and guts?
John,
he's got my driver's licence.
What?
He took my driver's licence.
He knows where we live.
He tookyour dr...
He tookyourwallet?
Well, he tossed the wallet,
but he keptthe licence.
He touched yourwallet?
Where's yourwallet?
lt's in my pocket.
We got him, Dad. You got him.
His prints. You got his prints.
You gotto get me thatwallet.
How the hell am l supposed
to do that?
As carefully as possible.
Take yourwallet out,
butjusttouch the corners.
- What are you talking about?
- Just do it.
OK, all right.
All right.
- Right.
- OK. All right. L got it.
All right. Now. Listen.
l wantyou to wrap it up.
Put it in one of them
plastic bags...
you keep extra transistors in.
Yeah. L see where you're going.
Beautiful. OK.
Now hide it somewhere.
Somewhere where nobody's gonna
find itforthe next30 years.
- l think maybe...
- Where?
The window seat
in the dining room.
There's a loose board
on the left, on the bottom.
Perfect. Beautiful.
lt's in.
Great! OK, l'm after it.
We're in business!
Now just sittight
and don'tworry!
And the winner is...
Oh, man. Lt's a cop.
Whatthe hell?
Son of a bitch.
Hey, Mr. Shepard.
How are you?
Who's that?
Oh, hi, Detective.
l just came by to wrapthings up
overthere.
Thought l'd say hello.
Glad you did. Come on in.
Thankyou.
- Buy you a cup of coffee?
- Sure.
Black? Sugar? Milk?
You know. Lt's all good.
You'll get black.
Fresh pot.
You know Jack?
No. Not really.
He still on the job?
He does a little P.l. Work
now and then...
but he's mostly retired.
Livin' off his pension, huh?
Jack got caught up
in them Knapp hearings.
Set up by some dirty cops
who needed afall guy.
Hurt him bad. Would have
broke his mother's heart.
ls she around?
- Who?
- Yourwife.
No. She passed on.
Long time ago.
l'm sorry.
That's OK.
Can l ask how she died?
Well, she...
she was murdered, Detective.
An ugly one,
to tell you the truth.
Mother of a cop...
and they neverfound
the bastard who did it.
You on the job?
A long time ago.
Do l know you?
l lookfamiliar?
What house you work?
The 7-4 Homicide.
A hotshot.
No,just...working the job.
Yeah, l hearthat, pal.
As a matter offact...
l caught a case
that goes backto your day.
One of the Nightingale murders.
No kidding?
No. Missing teenager.
Disappeared back in'68.
Theyfound her bones
lastweek...
buried behind some diner
out by Dyckman Street.
Mary Finelli.
Yeah,talk about dumb luck.
The odds of anybodyfindin'
that girl thirty years later...
and the chances of hittin'
a dental...
Forget about it.
The best part is,
she's thefirstvictim.
And she knew the killer.
So...
l'm bettin' those old bones
are gonna do a lot of talkin'.
Notfor nothin'.
The past is afunny thing.
We all have skeletons
in the closet.
You never know when they'll
pop up and bite you in the ass.
Huh,Jack?
You changed your m.o.
'Cause if they knew your mother
was a Nightingale...
they would've
looked atthefamily.
They would've looked atyou.
What are you looking at?
Stealing your life away.
You went down thirty years ago,
pal.
You just don't know ityet.
A cop? He's a cop?
What am l supposed to do
with that?
Call the F.B.l.
Use a pay phone.
Don't give'em your name, Dad.
Tell them Shepard killed Finelli
and Clark and the others...
that he's the Nightingale.
Then,tell'em
where Finelli's buried.
They'll be able to connect him
to her.
They search his place,
they'llfind some souvenirs.
He always took a piece of
jewelleryfrom his victims.
What are you doing here?
Are you off today?
We need to have a conversation.
- Dad?
- Hang on a sec,John.
l'm kind of in the middle
of something important here.
- Mind if we do this...
- l'm sorry, Frank.
We need to step outside
right now.
Dad,what's going on?
John, Satch is here,
and he's with his partner.
Whatthe hell's goin' on?
Hang on a sec.
What's your partner doin' here?
What happened to your eye?
l banged it up.
Let's go outside and talk.
We need to do that.
Aboutwhat?
Let's go,
do us both afavour, huh?
All right.
Stay there,John.
l'll be right back.
Be right back. All right?
Where were you last night,
Frank?
Where do you think l was, Satch?
Same place lfound this.
Underthe body of a dead woman.
No. This isn't
whatyou think, OK?
This isn'twhatyou think.
l wantto be wrong here.
Let's take a ride
to the precinct and talk.
l wantto talkto you,too.
l need to talkto you.
Come on.
We'll take a ride.
Let me just go inside,
tell myfamily where l'm going.
All right?
Be right back.
Everything's all right.
Don'tworry.
Chief,you there?
Theyfound Sissy Clark.
They think l did it.
Just give me a second.
You've gotto talkto Satch!
What's going on?
Uncle Satch, stop.
- He's a cop.
- A cop?
Jack Shepard.
He's a detective
atthe 15th Precinct.
l swear, Satch.
And you got all of this
from the guy on the radio.
From your son in thefuture.
Yeah.
As nuts as that sounds,yeah.
You gotta listen to me, Satch.
You gotta open upyour mind...
You gotta understand
what l'm saying.
You got something
going on with this girl...
that's one thing.
Butyou gotta tell me.
Are you listening to me?
You're in a world of shit.
An eyewitness putyou outside
the dead girl's apartment.
Your prints
are all overthe place...
notto mention
the goddamn driver's licence.
Chuck is getting
a search warrantforyour house.
- What's he gonnafind there?
- Nothin'.
You gotta give me somethin',
somethin' l can believe.
What if l can prove itto you?
How's that?
World Series.
Where are they right now?
What,fourth,fifth inning?
What if l was to tell you...
that in the bottom
of the sixth inning...
the Mets
are gonna be down three-zip?
And Cleon Jones,
he's going to come to bat.
He's gonna get hit in thefoot
by a wild pitch.
And it's gonna leave
a shoe polish mark on the ball.
Hear me out, all right?
He goes tofirst.
Clendendon comes up.
He's gonna hit a two-two pitch
into the left-field bleachers.
This is insane, Frank.
ln the bottom of the seventh,
Weis hits a solo home run...
and then Jones and Swoboda
score in the eighth.
The Mets,they're gonna win,
five to three.
Go watch.
lf it don't happen, l'm a liar.
Watch the game?
Watch the game!
Frank,they're gonna make you
for Sissy Clark's murder.
And they're gonna match that
with the Nightingale murders.
Do you understand
whatthat means?
His wife is here.
She wants to talkto you.
One-two pitch to Anderson.
Fly ball to right.
Let's walk,Jules.
Get a cup of coffee.
The guy went crazy.
Know what l mean?
Started tearin' things apart.
Throwing things.
How you doin'?
You got a collar in here
forthe Nightingale murders?
Everything OK
with you and Frank?
Yeah,we're good. He works hard.
l work hard. We're good.
Who's Sissy Clark, Satch?
Do you know where
Frankwas last night?
Yeah. He was workin'.
He had a tour.
Sit down.
Did you just hearwhat l said?
So how'd you know?
- How you doin'?
- What's up in here?
Shut up, asshole!
He tried to kill me!
Gofind Satch!
Find Satch!
He's trying to kill me!
What are you doin'
with my collar?
Sorry, pal. L didn't mean
to step on yourtoes.
They sent me up
from downstairs.
l thoughtyou'd be in there
with him.
What are you looking at himfor?
He matches a description
of an armed-robbery suspect.
So tell me aboutthe radio.
Who's he talking to
on thatthing?
John. He's a cop.
He talks to him all the time.
l've talked to him,too.
You talked to Johnny
on the radio?
John. What's going on, Satch?
You come into my house,
take Frank...
and now you're talking to me
like a cop.
l'm talking to you as afriend.
'Cause as a cop,
l wouldn't be here at all.
Listen,Jules,they're gonna
take me off this case.
Then Frank is gonna tell them
what he's been telling me.
And then nobody is gonna
be able to help him. OK?
...leftfield, and Cleon Jones
makes the catch.
Half the uniforms are either
atthe game or on the street.
lt's gonna be a riot
if they pull it off.
What is he telling us, Satch?
That he's talking to Johnny
on the radio.
Yeah. John the cop.
l told you that.
No. He says thatJohn
is your son,Johnny.
Little Johnny on the radio
in thefuture.
On the radio. You see?
No. You misunderstood him.
Jules? Sissy Clark?
She's a nurse,
and she was murdered yesterday.
And Frank is connected.
He is either
a material witness...
or an accomplice
orthe perpetrator.
...McNally,who's been
thoroughly in command.
Cleon starts down tofirst base,
and DeMiro calls him back.
Satch,you know him. You know
he didn't do this, right?
Hodges showing the baseball
to DeMiro.
Can l see him?
Hodges...We might have
a shoe polish play here.
Rememberthe Nippy Jones
shoe polish play...
in the 1957 World Series
at Milwaukee?
Hodges showing itto Lou DeMiro,
who awardsfirst base!
My God.
Satch,what's going on?
Mind if l go back
atthefireboyfor a while?
l justwantto see
what he's got.
Jesus.
Way back in leftfield.
Hey, bud.
See if aviation's got
a helicopter.
Respond to my location
for commencing an air search...
for body in water, OK?
ltwas a season and World Series
forthe ages...
forthe Mets and Series M.V.P.
first baseman Donn Clendendon.
Forthe Metsfaithful,
the New Yorkfans...Wow.
With the streets of midtown
and Times Square...
still packed
with celebratingfans...
Here's your coffee
and your cigarettes.
ln the skies over New York...
another amazing event
is coming to a close.
lt's time to say goodbye
to the northern lights...
l'll be upstairs.
...that have been
lighting upthe skies.
Astronomists say
the incredible sun storms...
that have created the remarkable
aurora borealis...
have begun to cool...
and the auroras,
already dimming...
will be over by morning.
John, are you there?
John, l'm back.
l'm here, Dad.
- We did it, son.
- What?
- We stopped him.
- We did?
Something's wrong.
l don't re...
What? What's wrong?
lf we stopped him,
why isn't Mom here?
Why don't l remember her
being OK?
But...l killed him.
He's dead.
My turn to steal your life away.
John, are you there?
Hey, bud.
Julia?
Oh,Julia.
Mommy?
Hey. Lt's OK.
lt's OK,you little rascal.
What are you gonna do, Frank?
Putthe gun down.
Let him go.
Well, putthe gun down.
l'll snap his neck.
Putthe gun down now.
Time to die, Sullivan.
Run,Johnny! Run!
Come here!
You all right?
l'm still here, Chief.
l got it! Mine.
Come on,Johnny!
Round the horn.
OK. Come on, Frank.
Come on!
No batter, no batter, no batter!
Come on, Frank! Yes!
The Benz! Notthe Benz!
No! God, notthe Benz!
Oh, my God.
Nice hit, Frank.
Way to go.
Thankyou very much.
- Let's play some ball.
- You'll payforthat!
Come on!
No batter, no batter, no batter!
Go get it!
He's slow, he's old.
Bring me home, Chief.