-You like the wine?
-Very much.
-Would you like some more?
-Please. No. Here.
You're good.
The wine, candles, the dinner.
What's next?
Let me set the mood.
Last time I saw a woman drink
like that, she was drowning.
-Did she die?
-I don't know. I was just a lifeguard.
You know, I don't want you
to get the wrong impression...
...that I invited you up here...
Markell, get your hand out of my shirt.
Come on, Markell, stop.
-Let's get in the back seat.
-Why can't we just watch the movie?
-lt's boring.
-This movie ain't boring, it's good.
Give me a kiss. Give me a kiss.
-Do you love me, baby?
-Of course I love you.
Tell me why.
Tell me why you love me.
-Right now?
-Right now. I wanna know.
'Cause you're fine.
That's deep. That's real deep.
'Cause I'm fine.
But I see where you coming f rom.
-Why you trippin'?
-I ain't trippin'.
Let's get in the back seat
so you can give me some sugar.
-Can you get me popcorn? I'm hungry.
-Popcorn?
Some popcorn, please?
Something. Jujubes. Go on, please?
-I don't believe this.
-Get me popcorn.
And some Jujubes. And some Bonbons!
Justice, I was just thinking.
The real reason why I love you is
because, when I was in jail...
...you sent me all them nice poems.
I'm gonna get your popcorn.
-Kick him in the head.
-You're worried about nothing.
I'll f uck this f ool up.
Damn.
I ain't giving you
no more quarters. Shit!
Is that the motherf ucker
that was at the mall the other day?
-ls that him?
-I don't know.
-Look at his f ace, dude.
-That's not him.
That's him, dude, I'm telling you.
I remember him. That's him.
Let me get a...
That's that nigga that was talking shit
in f ront of all his homeboys.
Popcorn and Jujubes.
Shit. Look.
Oh, man. Shit.
You're sick!
-ls that a crime?
-Save it.
I think I just saw those f ools
I had beef with last week.
So I shot.
Aaain, and aaain, and aaain.
Oh, it felt so aood.
But in the end, I was still horny.
My sweet abyss still existed.
Markell! Markell, get up, baby.
Markell, baby, wake up. Markell!
Somebody help me, please!
Somebody help me!
Alone
Lyina, thinkina last niaht
How to find my soul a home
Where water is not thirsty
And bread loaf is not stone
I came up with one thina
And I don't believe I'm wrona
That nobody, but nobody
Can make it out here alone
Alone, all alone
Nobody, but nobody
Can make it out here alone
There are some millionaires
With money they can't use
Their wives run 'round like banshees
Their children sina the blues
They've aot expensive doctors to cure
Their hearts of stone
But nobody, no, nobody
Can make it out here alone
Now if you listen closely
I'll tell you what I know
Storm clouds are aatherina
The wind is aonna blow
The race of man is sufferina
And I can hear the moan
'Cause nobody, but nobody
Can make it out here alone
Alone, all alone
Nobody, but nobody
Can make it out here alone
We got the situation under control.
Just get out of here.
Let us do our job.
We got the situation under control.
Look at these. This one right here,
this is bad. Girl, that is to die f or.
Jessie's. We do hair.
He just did my girl all wrong.
She's scared as hell. I caught her
running around here wearing sunglasses.
And you know how she like bragging
about her green eyes.
Top it off, she's still
in love with the nigga.
What's love got to do with it?
You just telling everybody's business.
I'd tell your business too
if you had something to tell.
Hey, Heywood. Hey, Dex.
How you doing, Maxine?
Come on, girl. You ready?
You got your hair with you?
What you think this is?
-I know you ain't getting smart.
-Shut up, girl.
That's what I thought. Come on.
Sit your butt down.
-So, what's up?
-Nothing up.
Morning, Jessie. Got any change?
Hell, no. And get your dirty,
unemployed ass away f rom my shop.
Baha? Baby, do me a f avour.
Go to the liquor store and get me
two honey buns and... What else?
Some Big Red. Yeah, I know.
-Twenty.
-Yeah, a 20.
And bring me my change!
Leave this conditioner on
f or five minutes.
You like that, don't you?
-Jessie, you are so beautif ul.
-Thank you, Heywood.
-I love you.
-I love you too.
-And I love myself.
-I know. Get back to your client.
I love it when you're so f orcef ul.
So...
Yeah.
-So he's out, huh?
-I don't know. I'm thinking about it.
I know y'all got
buck-wild last night.
-Where did y'all go?
-Could you put those over here?
-Snooty Fox Motor Inn.
-No, you didn't.
People, please remember
to turn in your receipts.
-We always do.
-I got mine right here.
-Still got them red walls and all that?
-Mirrors on the ceiling.
Same old, same old. I'm coming
up short. Are they turning in receipts?
They've been filling them out
and turning them in.
When was the last time you were there?
-What, Snooty Fox?
-Yeah.
-lt's been so long, I don't remember.
-That's what I know.
My girl need her hair
and her nails done.
-Does she have an appointment?
-No.
-She don't have no hair, either.
-Heywood.
Maxine. Make an appointment.
Why are you always wearing hats?
What are you hiding?
-Give me my hat. I got new growth.
-Put it back on.
You need to let me do something
to that head of yours.
Lord, I'm tired. You got a poem f or me?
Lord knows I need one.
I left my notebook in the car.
-Outgoing mail.
-Where are the stamps?
When you going to get a man?
Always asking questions about mine...
What, you still in mourning?
Sporting black, looking tore up f rom
the floor up, no time f or your hair.
You can always tell when a woman
ain't giving up no coochie.
I like wearing black. Besides, I ain't
got time f or no man in my life.
-Know what your problem is?
-So suddenly I got a problem?
-What's my problem?
-You make bad choices in men.
You don't know how to pick them.
Yo, what's up? What's up, Mr. Postman?
Got some spare change?
No, but I got a spare stamp
so you can mail a job application.
Begging-ass motherf ucker.
Y'all didn't get nothing but bills.
Why you always so mad?
You must ain't got no man
'cause you don't never smile.
-Do you?
-What do you want f rom me?
I think you kind of fly.
We could start with your phone number.
What's your name?
-Lucky.
-Lucky?
Come here, Lucky.
I wanna whisper something to you.
Let's cut the bullshit.
Now, what do you really,
really want f rom me?
-You wanna smell my poonani?
-Yeah.
You'd like that, huh?
Hold on a minute, baby.
Jessie? Come here
f or a minute, please.
What?
This fine, young, dark brother...
...said he wanna smell my poonani.
Really?
Poonani?
-Should I let him?
-Yeah.
What do you think?
You need to get your ass some
breath mints. Crazy black bitches.
Get your ass out of here.
I don't know
why I f uck with these hoes.
Here, man.
Don't smoke it.
Take a stamp too.
God bless you, brother.
Bless you, man!
I'm not f ucking with 101st no more.
I told that lady about them dogs.
She wants her mail, she gets it herself.
Did you not once consider
using your Mace?
Mace? That's like Binaca to rottweilers.
Y'all don't pay me enough!
-You're saying you don't want your job?
-Here you go.
Fucked his nose up.
Right in the middle, man.
Just like Robin Hood.
Y'all wanna get your asses to work
bef ore you get fired?
-What's up, sergeant?
-What's happening?
-I can't call it.
-I'm calling it.
They trippin'. Put two more buddhaheads
on the mail carrier bef ore me.
-Again?
-Got me sorting mail with Mexicans.
Chicago, why you talking
about Mexicans? I'll kick your ass.
Tell you what, you better quit
smoking that shit at lunch.
At least we got our own country.
Then why the f uck y'all
keep sneaking out?
That shit is f unny, right?
Basketball-playing motherf uckers.
-I'm going to Oaktown. You wanna go?
-Yeah.
-You gonna bring a yamp?
-Here you go. You gonna bring a yamp?
-I got mine, man.
-Yamps. What the f uck is a "yamp"?
A young tramp. Now, do you mind?
Don't worry about
what the players is talking about.
Go have your yamps, corn bread,
ham hocks and whatever else you eat.
-Get out of here.
-Get the ZIP codes right.
-Fix that shit.
-lf we gonna do this...
...have that crazy hoe you f uck with
hook me up with one of her partners.
-I'm gonna hook you up.
-You always say that.
-Hook me up.
-You gonna call your cousin?
Not yet. We're supposed to find a way
up there anyway f or our music thing.
Now it's like I'm getting paid
to go. I'm straight with that.
-See you later.
-Where you going?
Minding my business.
-What's up, nigga?
-Lounging, man.
-What y'all niggas doing?
-To be honest?
Looking f or some busters to jack.
I wanted to tell you something.
Remember Little D? Little Derek?
-D-Dog f rom up there?
-Yesterday, he got his ass capped out.
-Popped his ass out, straight twisted.
-Gone?
But we gonna get the f ools
that got him.
-Ain't no thing but a chicken wing.
-Yeah.
-See you.
-All right. Peace.
-Yeah, peace.
-There won't be no peace today.
Get you a motherf ucking
tune-up, nigga.
There he is.
Mr. Postman working motherf ucker here.
-Don't start. What's up, Bone?
-What's up?
-Shit. I can't call it.
-How you feeling?
-Tired than a motherf ucker.
-Tired, huh?
This ain't none of that chronic,
but you can use some of this Thai bud.
They checking my piss at work.
I can't f uck with it.
That's a terrible thing.
How you doing, Ms. Jackson?
-She can't stand me with a passion.
-She hates your ass.
So, what's up?
You here to check up on Keisha?
I'm gonna give Angel money
to buy her clothes.
Now, you know motherf ucking well
you ain't gotta give her money.
I'll take her to the swap meet, Fox
Hills Mall, get her whatever she needs.
No. You ain't got to do that.
-What you mean?
-lt's my daughter. I can handle it.
What did I tell you about this change?
Do I look like Las Vegas?
-Do I look like a slot machine?
-lt's all I got.
Get your punk ass up out of here
and don't do that shit no more.
-You cold on these f ools.
-I can't help it.
Check this out. It ain't like
I ain't got the money.
Besides, she call me Daddy
sometimes, anyway.
-What you mean, she call you Daddy?
-Just what I said.
-We gonna see who she call Daddy.
-We'll see.
-We gonna find out.
-What we gonna find out, then?
Well, let's see, then.
Well, hurry your slow ass up, then.
Keisha.
Hi, Daddy.
-Who's your daddy?
-You.
That's right. That's your son and
this is my daughter. Don't f orget it.
Pothead.
It's like I'm her daddy since they
came f rom the same tired-ass hooker.
How's that?
-Difference.
-What's up, boy?
Felix.
What y'all two f ools talking about?
-Talking about your yamp ass.
-Here we go. Simple Nick in the house.
Get your ass away f rom the TV.
What you cleaning up f or?
This place looks f ucked up as normal.
What you all nervous f or?
You been basing?
I ain't doing shit. I don't remember
Saying, " I do, " to neither one of you.
-Has she?
-No, this is what you do:
Get her and get out of my house. Don't
f orget to get her some tennis shoes...
If welf are wasn't paying the rent,
this wouldn't be your house.
-Fuck you.
-Get your ass back in the room. Tramp.
You know what I told your ass
about that shit!
Told her if I catch her doing
that shit again, I'm taking Keisha.
-She ain't got to be around this shit.
-Nothing wrong with her. She's crazy.
If something was wrong with her ass,
I'd know.
Brother Bone! Brother Bone!
Every time I sit down and wanna watch
a cartoon, somebody gotta call me.
-Here we go. Scarf ace.
-Get your stamp-licking ass up.
-What's up, man?
-Help me out, man.
What you got?
Go over there and sit with Tony, okay?
-What's up with all this change?
-That's all I got.
How do you like the Felix outfit?
Never mind that!
Just aet the diamonds!
Wow, professor! Look at that!
Loose diamonds.
Let's ao down and pick them up.
Who's that little character?
-Oh, my God!
-Hey, nigga. Get the f uck out of here.
-That is Lucky. That is Lucky!
-Lucky who? Get the f uck out.
Come on, Keisha.
We're going to see your grandma.
Don't be coming in my house
starting all that bullshit!
How you gonna be f ucking some nigga
when my daughter's here?
Damn, here they go.
-Who is this motherf ucker?
-Mind your own motherf ucking business.
-I don't need this shit!
-Stupid-ass motherf ucker.
-I wanna go too.
-Where are you taking Keisha?
How you gonna be f ucking some nigga
while my daughter here?
Where you going with my
goddamn child?
In a time of secret wooina
Today prepares tomorrow's ruin
Left knows not what riaht is doina
My heart is torn asunder
In a time of furtive siahs
Sweet hellos and sad aoodbyes
Half-truths told and entire lies
My conscience echoes thunder
In a time when kinadoms come
Joy is brief as summer's fun
Happiness
Its race has run
Then pain stalks in to plunder
-So, what you think?
-lt's pretty. What you call it?
" In a Time."
Chicago paging me.
Let me see what he wants.
I can't use your phone?
You know better.
-You got some change?
-I'm straight.
What'd they say?
So, what's up?
Yeah. I'm ready.
We got a hair show to go
to up there, anyway.
What you mean, "a fine one"?
You trying to say I got ugly f riends?
I ain't got no ugly f riends.
You wanna talk about it?
I think you'll feel better
if you talk about it.
What the hell are they
doing out there now?
-I'll be glad when we get out of here.
-What's wrong?
What's wrong?
You got your styles together
f or the Oakland show?
Yeah, I'm just gonna work
on Dina and Gina's head a bit.
If they like it, they like it.
If they don't, they don't.
Will you ride with us? We got us a
little caravan going. We gonna party.
Oh, Justice. Look at your f ace.
Listen, I know I'm not your mama,
and I'm not trying to be...
...but I gotta tell you,
you got to move on.
A man is a tool. You got to know
when to take him out the box...
...and when to put him back in. If you
lose one, go get yourself another one.
Take a chance, baby.
Do something different f or a change.
There's another man
out there somewhere.
And out here, sometimes
you're gonna lose one.
Like a blow dryer or a good hairbrush.
What I got to do?
Play everybody's mama in this shop?
Hell, I got my own problems.
Okay, where's my brush?
I'm tired of my shit
disappearing around here.
Why you always borrowing
my shit without asking?
I asked you this morning if I could
borrow your brush, and you said yes...
...and I have returned it to you.
Why you gonna cry about it, Dexter?
-You sound like my little niece.
-Here we go again.
What's your new man talking about?
Girl, he want me to go on a run
with him. This is good.
I don't have to be messing
with it all the time.
-Just get up and go.
-You know, girl...
You're catching me
on the wrong goddamn day.
So you got balls?
I was All-City strong safety
at Dorsey High. I'll get in your ass.
And not the way
you want me to, Sexy Dex.
Please. Stop this right now.
-What's a " run"?
-You know what a run is.
I don't know what it is.
Stop messing with your head.
Now, what's a run?
A run? Well, it's like...
You really wanna know, girl?
If you don't stop playing with me...
Chicago, my boyf riend,
works at the post office...
...the one on Century and Van Ness.
Every so often, he and his f riend
drive this mail truck up to Oakland.
-J, you listening to me?
-Yeah, I'm listening.
Like I said, they drive
this mail truck to Oakland.
And sometimes I go with them.
And I was thinking...
You're not having it, huh?
I got your bitch. Okay?
I got your bitch.
-Calm down.
-What you wanna do?
Not here.
What you doing seeing a mailman?
They don't make no money.
What he gonna do f or you,
mail your bills f or f ree?
Why you don't ever wanna have
no f un no more?
The world's just a big place
f or us to go and f uck up in it.
You aonna end up beina an old maid.
Need help?
You offer help
when all I got is one bag.
There you go.
Put that cigarette out.
I don't allow smoking in here.
Come on, Ma, I pay the bills here
and I can't have a cigarette?
Shut the f uck up
and put the cigarette out!
-You going up north to see Kalil?
-Yeah.
I'm finally gonna work
on this music thing.
Somebody could listen to our tape.
I ain't got to do this post office shit.
Don't be cussing around me, boy.
Be glad you got an honest job.
Don't go to Oakland every weekend.
You know how Aunt Audrey can get.
Ma, it ain't even like that.
Keisha here.
-Really? How's my grandbaby doing?
-Bad as ever.
I want her to stay with us f or good.
Angel been f ucking up, bad.
Basing. I can't have my baby
around that sh... Stuff.
Now, are you gonna take care of her?
Yeah.
Just remember, that's your baby.
I'm done raising kids.
Quit playing video games and figure out
what you gonna do with your life.
Packed my bags, my stuff...
Wait a second... White Boy.
Come on.
Shit!
I'll call lesha.
Come on, girl. Hurry up.
-Hello?
-lesha, what up? What you doing?
-I'll hold your jacket f or you.
-Bet you will.
There go that damn cat again.
I'm gonna kick it one day.
Girl, you kick my cat,
I'm gonna kick your ass.
-We gonna have f un.
-I can't believe I'm doing this.
It's gonna be so on, just watch.
I ain't doing this.
Motherf ucker said she f rom Ethiopia.
Knew damn well that bitch f rom Compton.
-She look it, though.
-With a kid named Lamar?
Girl, you got this.
I ain't riding in that.
-Why you gotta be a buster?
-Who you calling a buster?
-You. Take a chance.
-Take a chance, my ass. Look at this!
She's fly, now, ain't she, Lucky?
Look, man.
-Oh, my God, I know that bitch.
-You don't know her.
That's that hoe that work
in the salon on 54th. Here we go.
She act up and her ass is out.
Lucky is cool, girl.
That's Lucky right there.
He was in the salon, trying to mack.
-Sorry-ass, bald-headed...
-Just be cool.
-You know him, girl?
-She better not act up...
Lucky, this is Justice.
Justice, this is Lucky.
-And you already know Chicago.
-What's up, baby?
-Baby?
-Shit. Hi.
Anyway, let's go. Move!
Damn. Watch out, girl.
Get your ass in the back.
Shit, I ain't no f ucking bellboy.
Take it easy on that mail!
Sit up here, girl.
Go ahead and
make your seat belts click, baby.
We f ollow all the safety guidelines
around these parts.
Y'all just hold on.
There you go. We out.
Stop. Stop.
You don't know
if you wanna kiss me or hit me.
-lt's your way of showing you like me.
-I don't.
-Yes, you do. I know what you like.
-What?
Man, shit. Muscle! Feel it!
Nigga, that ain't shit.
It ain't? What's that?
Shit, don't be grabbing
my titty like that.
-What you want me to do, kiss it?
-Yeah, here. Psych!
Stop, Chicago.
See? That's better.
Be nice f or a change.
Mind if I smoke?
Guess not.
You kind of quiet, huh?
I guess so.
I ain't got nothing to say.
Why you so mean?
What you got to be so mean about?
So you one of them angry bitches.
A feminist.
-What'd you call me?
-Said you a mean bitch.
We gotta stop this right now.
You don't know shit about me.
Don't be calling me no bitch.
I've been acting courteous. Nigga gotta
call you a bitch to get your attention.
I'm a black woman, okay?
I deserve respect.
Don't be calling me no bitch.
If I'm a bitch, your mama's a bitch.
Save that " black woman" shit.
You bleed once a month like every hoe.
We ain't talking about my mama,
we talking about your stuck-up ass.
You think a nigga's supposed
to do magic tricks f or your ass.
-Pull this shit over right now.
-Where you gonna go?
I'll walk, motherf ucker.
Pull over.
Garb-ass bitch! Get your shit!
I'm tired of your mouth. Talking all
that shit. Walk your ass home!
It'll do them f at-ass thighs
some good!
I better not see you in L.A.
I'm gonna get somebody
to f uck you up, motherf ucker!
What's going on?
-They gonna f uck you up!
-Fuck you!
-Fuck you up!
-Fuck you, bitch!
Scandalous-ass bitch. Thinks
a motherf ucker will bow down to her.
-Where my girl at?
-Leaving that bitch!
You just can't leave her
out in the middle of nowhere.
Chicago. Chicago, wake up.
Chicago, wake up.
Lucky's leaving Justice.
So what?
I'm trying to get some sleep.
What you mean? He leaving her
in the middle of nowhere.
Damn, she got feet. Shit.
Get up, Chicago.
Shit. He's leaving her.
You better get up
and check your f riend.
-Lucky, stop the truck.
-What's up?
Man, f uck that bitch.
Think she God's gift to a nigga.
Fuck her. Her ass can walk.
J, come on.
Where you gonna go?
We out in the middle of nowhere.
Ain't you kind of hot out there?
Lucky said he'd apologize.
Justice.
She get kind of stubborn sometimes.
Can you stop the truck?
Why you letting him
upset you like this?
Girl, you know he trippin'
because he like you.
I know you ain't gonna let no nigga
make you walk all the way to Oakland.
J, come on.
Man, just chill, all right?
If you want to, we can call
the homeys if it's all that.
-They still gonna f uck you up.
-Get your ass in the truck.
-Shut up, Chicago!
-Frankly, my dear, I don't give a f uck.
"They still gonna f uck you up."
You drive, nigga.
Good, now I can get my drink on.
Put 20 on f our.
Don't get too much liquor.
And bring me
some Cheetos and a 40.
-You need to put her ass in check.
-Mind your own f ucking business.
Fuck that, let's stay on schedule.
Fuck that CP time.
-Ex cuse me.
-ls that your truck?
-Yeah, it's my rig.
Who the dude getting in the cab?
Pardon me.
I gotta have my Gordon's and Socko.
Check and see if you see some Socko.
They don't have no eightball?
Y'all ain't got Olde E?
You know they don't sell that
outside the Black neighbourhoods.
Oh, well. Chicago just gonna
have to settle f or a Miller Light.
I hope they got my gin.
You know how you get when you drink.
You know what your man said.
Chicago? That ain't my daddy.
I don't listen to him.
-He your man, though.
-Shit, I got him sprung.
I been making that f ool stutter.
You know he start stuttering
when he lying.
No, no, wait, wait...
Money? You giving that hoe money?
Sometimes I like f or my girl
to have the best.
Nigga, you getting played.
I can't believe this shit.
You gonna lose stripes over this.
How much pussy you get?
I don't hardly have to do nothing.
I been rationing it to him.
Rationing that ass.
I'm knocking it every other night.
She can't get enough.
You a lying motherf ucker.
Nigga is weak, girl.
He ain't got no kind of rhythm.
Plus, he a preemie.
And you know what a preemie is.
Two-minute brother.
Let that bitch get her own job.
Drunk hoe.
She need to work in a liquor store,
much as she be drinking.
-ls that everything you want?
-Yeah.
-So, what you think about Lucky?
-I don't.
-I'm gonna get one of these. Want one?
-Yeah, girl.
Where the water at?
-There's a f aucet in the back.
-Fill mine up too.
-You got this?
-Yeah, I got it.
At least I get some poon.
Just 'cause I don't pack my shit on a
trip don't mean I ain't getting none.
-I'm handling mine.
-Handling just like this:
Least I ain't losing no money.
Hey, partner, you like country music?
Garth Brooks, he's slamming, right?
-You old cow.
-Stop, stop, stop!
Don't f uck around.
I know what you're about to do.
Quit playing. No, stop!
Give me that. Stop!
Here you go, partner.
Got me in the eye too.
Would y'all come on?
Boy, you know
I got a schedule to keep to.
I'll give you a f ucking schedule.
-Quit playing and get in.
-Have some f un, man.
Drink some of this.
Drink some more,
and drink it to the middle.
Shit. Where my 40 at?
-Damn, lesha, this ain't no 40.
-They didn't have no Olde E.
Got my Cheetos, though.
Love is a juice with many tastes
Some bitter, others sweet
A wine which has few...
Few vineyards
Your nails are so dirty.
What you writing?
Stuff.
-Say...
-What?
-Tell me how much you love me.
-Why?
-Because I said so.
-ls that what you wanna hear?
Hell, yeah.
Really?
Good.
You so dumb. The more I teach you,
the dumber you get.
-Something smell good, huh?
-Hell, yeah.
You cool, girl?
-Yeah. You on my braids.
-Sorry.
-What's that smell?
-Smell like barbecue to me.
-Y'all smell that?
-What's that?
-Shit, look at all them black f olks.
-A gang of f olks.
Come on.
-Get out.
-Quit pushing me.
Barbecue. Come on, girl.
Y'all wait f or me. Dang!
Just f ollow my lead, all right?
It's cool. It's cool. We gonna eat.
We're f amily.
Just act like we supposed to be here.
-Girl, stop drinking that shit.
-What's wrong with you?
Damn, it's hot out here.
My titties is sweating and shit.
We shouldn't be here, anyway.
-ls that barbecue?
-Looks like barbecue.
-ls that f ree barbecue?
-Shit. It gonna be f ree.
-We got a gang of f reaks here.
-I ain't thinking about these brothers.
-What y'all gonna do?
-We gonna eat.
You crazy? This ain't your f amily.
-We black. We all f amily.
-Word.
Especially when it comes to barbecue.
Lordy, Lordy!
Will you look at the ladies? Hot damn!
-We related, huh?
-I hope we're distant relatives.
Really?
Well, you know,
third and removed don't count.
-I don't think so.
-My cousin, my cousin!
Look at my f amily over here.
My cousins. What's up, cousin?
-How you doing, boy?
-Cousin!
-What's up, cousin?
-What's up?
I ain't seen you
in I don't know when.
Goddamn! That's a pretty
girlf riend you got here, boy.
Y'all make a good-looking couple too.
So, what's your name, cousin?
-Lucky. Little Lucky?
-Lucky, yeah.
With a lady like this, shit,
I'd call you Lucky too.
-What's your name, sweet thing?
-Justice.
You mean, like the law?
How you get a name like that?
You don't wanna know that story.
Anyway, this is my f riend...
-lesha. This is my husband, Chicago.
-Chi-Town, how you doing?
-What's happening, man?
-So, cousin, what's your name?
Just call me Cousin Pete.
That's right, Cousin Pete.
Come here.
I want y'all to meet some f amily.
Over here we got Aunt Jessica.
Uncle Herb. Aunt Aida Pearl.
That's Uncle Fred and his wife, Wilma.
Cousin Isaac, Cousin James,
Cousin Kwame. What's up, bro?
And them kids, I don't know
all their names. Bread-snatchers.
Sitting over here, we got Aunt April,
we got Aunt May and Aunt June.
I call them the Calendar Sisters.
-Look at them.
-Ain't they pretty?
-How y'all doing?
-Yes, sir. How you doing?
Food sure look good over there.
Don't it? Go over and help yourself.
You f amily, ain't you?
-lt's cool?
-You better go get something.
Go ahead with him.
I'm gonna play some cards.
Bye. Look at them.
Don't they make such a cute couple?
-Are you all in love?
-Yeah.
Baby, what would you know about love?
Nothing.
How can you be in love
if you don't know nothing about it?
-Just the way things go.
-Are you married?
-Yeah.
-How long you been married?
About six months now.
I don't wear it all the time.
You don't mind
if she doesn't wear your ring?
He don't mind.
He can answer f or himself,
if he's a real man.
Well?
No, no. I don't mind.
My husband would kill me
if I didn't wear no ring.
-I heard that.
-And I know that's right.
-Damn, you greedy.
-Gotta eat to live.
Well, why you so skinny, then?
Look at the cute baby.
Can I hold her f or you?
Look at you. I heard that.
Give me a burp. That spittle?
You be dating them
professional men, huh?
Doctors, lawyers, pharmacists?
Street pharmacists?
I knew you was like that.
Here. I'll take her now.
She is so cute. You sure?
What's her name?
Her name is lmani.
Hi, lmani. Hi there.
You're so cute. Yes, you are.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, lmani.
So you got a kid, huh?
-Why you ask me that?
-Because you look like the type.
-And what's the type?
-I don't know.
This. You just walking by.
You the type.
Anyway...
You got any kids?
Hell, no, I ain't got no kids.
I don't even like kids.
Sure don't look like that to me.
This here's kind of cool.
You ever been to one of these?
No, I ain't got much f amily.
Family I do have, we ain't this close.
I ain't never seen so many black f olks
in one spot and there ain't no fight.
Let's get back to these
street pharmacists you used to see.
Let me tell you something.
I only went out with one.
He was my first boyf riend,
my first love. He meant a lot to me.
-So you was in it f or the money?
-You're getting too damn personal.
What the f uck you know? You don't
even keep your f ucking nails clean.
I want to talk to you about morals.
The morals of the young people today
is gonna get them in big trouble.
Because they act like
they don't know the difference...
...between right and wrong.
This is the truth. And one
of the reasons is their parents.
Parents are not taking care
of the children.
They don't tell them the difference
between right and wrong.
Wait now. No, ma'am.
You have to listen.
Because part of the responsibility
is the children.
Because this is their life.
It's not their mama's or papa's.
They have to think f or themselves.
Even if their mama and papa
didn't do something about it...
...the children have to think
and try their best to come on up.
-Take this girl here.
-What about her?
That child ain't a bit more married
than the man in the moon.
-How you doing?
-Fine, how you doing?
She's flirting with another man.
Tell me she's married.
-She's young.
-She's loose.
She's not loose. You were young once.
Yeah, but I was never flitty.
I was never flitty.
She was never flitty.
I need to talk to my f riend.
What's wrong with you?
Chicago gonna kick your ass.
-You gonna play cards or sightsee?
-Chicago, come on.
-Chicago ain't gonna do shit.
-You stupid? He'll kick your ass.
-You're killing my action, girl. Stop.
-lesha, what action?
-What's up?
-She trippin'.
-She ain't doing nothing wrong.
-You got nothing to do with this.
-Calm down.
-She know what she's doing.
-Come on, girl.
-Wait, don't start nothing.
-I'm talking. I'm talking.
-Come on now, don't start fighting.
-What's wrong with you, man?
-I can't talk to nobody?
What's happening, man?
-You mind if I take some f ood to go?
-No, man. You go ahead.
-My cuz!
-Don't you worry.
Something don't look right over here.
I'm gonna have to get in this shit.
-Chicago, stop.
-Try to be cool.
-Gonna get his ass.
-We were just talking.
Get your hands off me. Shit.
-Fuck you.
-Get out of my f ace.
Why you gotta act up
every time we go someplace?
-Shut up.
-Why the f uck you gotta act up?
What's your problem?
Why the f uck you gotta disrespect me?
Fuck you. You don't own me.
Fuck you, bitch.
You and your drunk-ass pussy.
If I'm a bitch,
then why the f uck you with me?
-I don't know why.
-Then leave. Step the f uck off.
I don't keep no niggas
when they don't wanna be kept.
First of all, you don't keep shit.
All that talking.
Do that shit while you walking.
Pull over somewhere. I need
to talk to her. I'm sick of this shit.
I'm a black bastard now, right?
I wasn't when I bought you that shit.
You was a black bastard then,
and you a black f ucking bastard now.
-Why the f uck we stopping?
-Good, I gotta pee.
You know why you got to pee?
Because you drink too much.
Get your hands off me.
I'll pee on your motherf ucking ass.
Let me off this shit. I gotta pee.
Open the door.
You're gonna have some wet-ass mail.
Come here, lesha. I wanna talk to you.
What's wrong? Lucky f ucking
with you, huh? I'm gonna f uck you up.
-Girl, come here. I wanna talk to you.
-Let me put on my jacket.
Shit. Look at you.
What's up, J?
What's the problem, girl?
This is the problem. I'm sick of this.
You act like an alcoholic bitch.
-Why you calling me a bitch?
-All you do is get drunk.
That's why I never go anyplace
with you. You always acting crazy.
Just like my damn mama.
I'm sorry.
God, I'm sorry, J.
It's okay. It's gonna be all right.
You just gotta f reeze up on that shit.
I didn't know. I swear I didn't know.
You're my best f riend, though.
I don't wanna hurt you.
And I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
You just gotta stop.
I know. God, I know.
Look at me.
I gotta pee.
-You old cow, come on.
-You a cow!
You're right.
Shit don't change. I told you.
Can't give these hoes shit.
They try to break your back.
-Still mad at me?
-Come on, it's hot. What's up?
I'm sorry, Chicago.
-Hey, that's nice. Who's that?
-My cousin Kalil.
-That's real nice.
-He write all this shit.
I help him with ideas. I'm gonna go
to Oakland and work on this music.
It's all right, man.
It ain't all that.
Why you always got something negative
to say? At least the nigga's creative.
Fuck, he ain't creative.
I'm creative.
-What you do?
-I can dress.
That's just like a nigga to down-talk
a man 'cause he trying and you ain't.
You ain't shit. Post office worker.
No-union-ass nigga.
-You work there too.
-I'm in the union.
That don't mean shit. You need a
f ashion tip, sweatshirt-wearing ass.
Why y'all always fighting?
I thought you were f riends.
-I just work with him.
-Fuck that nigga.
Can I get some air?
Breathing like a goddamn dragon.
Anyway...
Turn that shit up, man.
A wise man once said,
"Look at the ocean and realize...
... that no matter how famous you are
or how much money you make...
...know that you'll never be
as important as the ocean. "
Why didn't I ao to colleae?
Grandmamma would be rollina over in
her arave two times if she saw me now.
I wonder...
No, he probably aot babies and shit.
Look at him.
He looks just like the type that aot
a baby stashed away somewheres.
Damn, she kind of cute.
Got a nice little frame.
Maybe I should aet that number,
see how the booty work.
Wonder what Kalil doina.
I wonder if my mama picked up
my clothes from the cleaners.
I know what I aotta do
when I aet back.
I aotta call Terry with his fine ass.
Ask him to take me shoppina.
I need to just let her ass ao.
Fuck it.
I can just find me another bitch.
I'm a aood-lookina niaaa.
Got a job. Income comina in.
Car. Apartment.
My shit is set.
Girl, when I get back to L.A.,
I'm quitting Chicago.
His tired ass.
-lesha, I'm gonna go on a diet.
-A diet?
Yeah. My ass is getting too big.
I ain't never heard you talking
about going on no diet.
I get it. You happy-go-Lucky.
-Don't be even trying that shit.
-Yes, you are.
No, I don't play that.
Hear them drums?
Where that shit coming f rom?
Who gives a f uck? We ain't stopping.
They got some cute shirts over there.
What's wrong with you?
Why you so quiet now?
Just thinking. I don't really
get a chance to think in the city.
This be the only time I can unwind.
Or when I'm with my cousin.
I'm getting tired of all this walking.
Yeah, me too, Lucky.
What you write about in that notebook?
That's my poetry.
You trying to say
my cousin's shit ain't poetry?
It ain't if he ain't got nothing deep
to say. Gotta have a voice.
-A perspective.
-What do you write about?
Whatever's in my heart.
And what's that?
I don't know. What's in yours?
I don't know.
Still trying to find out.
Niaaas are scared of revolution.
Niaaas are nothina but lovers.
Man, why we keep stopping?
We got a schedule to keep.
We got time. Why you trippin'?
We do this all the time.
Because we need to get where we got
to go. Your ass keep procrastinating.
You think you slick. Just trying
to gib to that bitch, that's all.
That's your f ucking problem.
-Fuck you, limp motherf ucker.
-What?
-I said, f uck you.
-You better check that bitch.
Shit. Gonna get me some plums.
You ain't gonna pull that.
She out of your league.
I'm getting tired of your black ass.
Man, f uck you.
Fuck all of them.
Don't need this shit
f ucking my day up.
But there's one thina about niaaas
I do not love.
Niaaas are scared of revolution.
Don't eat that. You ain't washed it.
-Yes, I did.
-Where?
-You're nasty.
-Want a bite?
I don't want none of that dirty plum.
Don't know whose hands been on it.
You know you want a bite.
-Wanna do something?
-What about them?
-Fuck them.
-All right.
All right?
How many brothers
and sisters you got?
I ain't got no brothers and sisters.
My mama didn't have the chance
to have any more kids.
lesha. Oh, man.
Shit.
-ls that it?
-Give me a couple minutes, all right?
Fuck that. A couple minutes, my ass.
You can't even hang that long.
-Fuck you.
-That's the problem. You can't.
-You the motherf ucking problem.
-No, your dick's the problem.
Thought I'd give you something
bef ore I quit your ass...
...but you can't even appreciate that.
Can't even do it right.
-Just shut the f uck up.
-Shut up?
Yeah. Shut up.
You must be embarrassed.
Is that what it is?
Shut the f uck up, all right?
I'm getting sick of this shit.
-Don't come near me.
-What you mean, don't come near you?
-Get out of my f ace.
-How you just gonna leave?
You know why I left.
Don't even ask me that.
-I don't. Tell me why you left.
-You know why.
-You need to take your time and relax.
-You need to. You got the problem.
-I ain't got no goddamn problem.
-You got a problem.
Look, don't turn your back on me.
-Don't touch me.
-Don't turn your back on me.
-I need to.
-Why?
'Cause that's the reason the other
bitch left you. You can't hang.
-I can't hang?
-You can't hang.
-That's a f ucked-up thing to say.
-lt's a real thing to say.
That's what I get f or f ucking with
bitches like you. Y'all don't give a f uck.
-I don't give a f uck about you.
-No, you don't.
I had many niggas that
bought me better shit than you.
-Fuck you.
-Listen to what I got to say.
-Don't touch me.
-Listen to me, then.
What do I need to listen to?
How come my shit can't be all like this,
beautif ul and shit? You f ucked it up.
-You ain't a beautif ul motherf ucker.
-That's f ucked up.
-I'm tired of arguing.
-Shut up.
-Don't turn away f rom me.
-You know what? You weak.
You a weak-ass punk.
You think you the shit because
you work out? You ain't buff.
I wish I never met your sorry ass.
You a sorry motherf ucker.
Yeah, that's right.
Brush that weak-ass f ade.
Nigga's dick can't
stay hard 5 minutes.
What the f uck you do, take steroids?
That's the reason why
I'm f ucking somebody else.
Motherf ucker!
What the f uck do you want?
-Calm down.
-You guys stop fighting!
-Don't fight with me.
-Leave her alone!
-You ain't gonna do nothing?
-Hell, no. That's their business.
-Get off me!
-Shit. You bitch!
-How much shit I gotta take off you?
-Get the f uck off of her!
Shit!
Hey, motherf ucker!
-You ain't got shit to do with this.
-Get the f uck off me.
-Get the f uck off her. You all right?
-Yeah.
-What's wrong with you?
-What's your problem?
-She hit me.
-You can't handle it better than that?
I'm gonna get Dooky and Monster
to shoot your f ucking ass.
-They ain't gonna do shit.
-I told you to handle this shit.
-Shit wouldn't have been f ucked up.
-You just want some pussy, that's all.
Fuck!
-Get your punk ass up.
-Fucker.
You little punk.
Coward motherf ucker. Hit a man.
Find a f ucking bus, you little punk.
I'm leaving your ass!
Don't leave me. Leave them hoes.
Walk your ass the 15 miles
to Oakland. Get the f uck off my shit!
-But we got a job.
-Get the f uck off my shit!
Leave them hoes.
Yo, hold on, Lucky.
Hey, leave them hoes, man.
Shit.
Oh, boy.
This ain't my motherf ucking day.
I can't believe he hit me.
Tired ass.
He gonna get f ucked up, watch.
Is it true the ribs can tell the kick
Of a beast from a lover's fist?
The bruised bones record it well
The sudden shock, the hard impact
Then swollen lids
Sorry eyes spoke not of lost romance
But of hurt
Hate is often confused
Its limits are in zones beyond itself
And sadists will not learn that
Love, by nature, extracts a pain
Unequalled on the rack
Why are we stopped?
I don't know. I'll find out, though.
They was gonna break up anyway.
I remember when I was little...
...and my uncle Leon
used to come around.
He used to give me
and my cousins change.
He'd go to the liquor store
and buy a 40-ounce of beer.
Always throw us the change.
I'd always ask f or the big nickel.
I couldn't pronounce "quarter, "
so that's what I called it.
Look at your nails.
Give me your hand.
Come on, give me your hand.
Anyway, so because of that,
my grandmamma used to say...
...I was always looking
f or the big nickel.
-That's bef ore she died.
-When did she die?
About two years ago.
She left me the house.
When I was 12,
my mama committed suicide.
She named me Justice
because she was in law school...
...when she was pregnant with me.
I'm all alone now, though.
I got a cat. Cute little cat.
Damn.
Give me your hand
Make room for me to lead and follow you
Beyond this raae of poetry
Let others have privacy
Of touchina words
And love of loss of love
For me, aive me your hand
Look, I gotta tell you something.
Shit, don't tell me you got something.
No. I'm only telling you this
because I care about you...
...and I think you should know
bef ore we go any f urther.
A little girl, huh?
Why didn't you tell me
in the beginning?
I mean, how was I supposed
to know what we was doing?
I'm gonna go check on my cousin.
Aunt Audrey. Kalil.
Hey, where do you think you're going?
-Kalil!
-Shit, man, it's his cousin!
-Yo, man, somebody shot Kalil.
-Who shot him?
What relationship is
this woman to him?
Just get away f rom me, man!
Cover him up, man! Cover him up!
What the f uck are you doing?
-What's up? What room we in?
-What happened to you?
Don't touch me.
If I had got there on time,
this never would have happened.
Instead of f ucking with you.
What?
So we scraping the bottom
of the pudding cup now, huh?
Know what you talking about
bef ore you judge.
Well, ex cuse me. I'm sorry.
You even walk different.
Let's go, fellas, all right?
I don't got all day. Watch your head.
I thought there was gonna
be two of you.
No, it's just me.
-See you the next time around.
-No, I don't think so.
You don't fight no man with your fist.
You fight him in his wallet.
Instead of swinging at him,
you should have gave him some.
Wait till he went to sleep
and took that credit card.
-And we all would have had a party.
-On him!
What credit card?
That nigga ain't got no credit card.
-No credit cards?
-Shit, then you is a f ool.
-I'm telling you, men ain't shit.
-Ain't that the truth.
Ex cuse me?
I thought you were in love.
Well, you thought wrong.
Don't be assuming shit, okay?
When you assume,
you make an ass out of you.
Well, you were already an ass.
You got a lot to learn about the world.
Come on, y'all.
Let's go get a drink.
These little girls don't know
their cooch f rom a hole in the wall.
-But they gonna learn.
-You got that right.
'Cause all I do is dress and rest.
-'Cause love don't live here anymore.
-Come on, Jessie.
Morning, Lawrence. You hungry, baby?
Come here and get something to eat.
I ain't hungry.
Too mad to eat.
Audrey. Audrey, sit down. Sit down.
You gonna wear yourself out.
Lawrence.
Shante, check that chicken, baby.
Make sure it don't burn.
Lawrence.
I want you to know,
you my f avourite nephew.
Your mama and l, even though we're
sisters, we don't always get along.
But I was always happy that
you and Kalil were like brothers.
Family's got to stick together,
no matter what.
Aunt Audrey, I know you're probably
not thinking about this right now.
Probably ain't important to y'all.
But it's important to me...
...to know what you're gonna do
with the equipment.
We gonna sell it. We need the money.
Why don't you mind your business?
He put every dollar he had into that
equipment. You just gonna f uck it up?
-Watch your mouth.
-I'm serious. You know he did.
What you think we should do?
Give it to me.
I'll do something with it.
I'll do what he would
have wanted me to do.:
Use it.
Tell Annie I said " hi." And I love you.
I love you too.
Pretty women wonder
Where my secret lies
I'm not cute
Or built to suit a fashion model's size
But when I start to tell them
They think I'm tellina lies
I say, it's the reach of my arms
The span of my hips
The stride of my step
The curl of my lips
I'm a woman, phenomenally
Phenomenal woman, that's me
I walk into a room
Just as cool as you please
And to a man, the fellows stand
Or they fall down to their knees
Then they swarm around me
Like a hive of honey bees
I say, it's the fire in my eyes
The flash of my teeth
The swina in my waist
And the joy in my feet
I'm a woman, phenomenally
Phenomenal woman, that's me
-Damn!
-Daddy, could we go to the store?
Go in the living room.
It's too dangerous in here.
Men themselves have wondered
What they see in me
They try so much
But they can't touch my inner mystery
When I try to show them
They still can't see
I say, it's the arch of my back
The sun of my smile
The ride of my breasts
And the arace of my style
I'm a woman, phenomenally
Phenomenal woman, that's me
Now you understand
Just why my head's not bowed
I don't have to shout or jump about
Or have to talk real loud
When you see me passina
It ouaht to make you proud
I say, it's the click of my heels
The bend of my hair
The palm of my hand
The need for my care
I'm a woman, phenomenally
Phenomenal woman, that's me
Don't look at me.
Look at her. Sitting over there
in that cheap dress.
-Acting like she don't know you.
-She know who I am.
-Plastic Payless shoes.
-Cheap-ass weave.
Ain't even human hair.
The bitch got yak hair in her head.
Is there a problem?
If you don't quit staring,
I'm gonna slap you.
We're not having that here.
You take it to the street.
-We could take it out.
-Don't you mess with my man!
Remember this: Every time
you kiss him, you tasting my pussy.
-You got to go!
-That's wrong.
-Please, darling, cool it down.
-She need to whup her ass.
None of that!
I'm kind of tired too.
Watch yourself.
What's up?
-How much is it? Twenty-five?
-Yeah.
Thanks. Ex cuse me.
-What's up?
-Who's this?
-Keisha.
-Hi, Keisha. My name is Justice.
-Can we sit down f or a few minutes?
-Yeah, sure.
-She's so cute.
-This is my baby.
Look...
It took me a long time
to come down here.
I mean, I know I made a mistake.
But everybody make mistakes.
And I had a lot on my mind.
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
Forgive me?
Come here.
I wanna whisper something to you.
Get the f uck out of here.
I ain't f alling f or that again.
No, f or real, though. Come here.
Come here. Come here.
Oh, my God!
Your nails are clean.
-I wonder why.
-They living a f airy tale.
-What are y'all looking at?
-I wouldn't have f orgiven you.
-What have you done with her head?
-Nothing.
That's just what it look like too.
Come on, let me fix your hair.
-Her hair look fine.
-Come on. It's a mess.
-I guess my assumption was right.
-Ain't wearing black no more either.
They make an all right couple.
But he's not my type.
-Kind of cute, though.
-Nice nose.
There's a few things
we could do with your hair.
We can put some ponytails in it
and huge flower ribbons. Or barrettes.
Or we can put
some big, big, big curls in it.
Big locks.
Which way would you like it?
-Curls.
-You like the curls? The curls, okay.
-Do you go to school, Keisha?
-Yeah.
-You do? You like school?
-What's your teacher's name?
-Mrs. Frazier.
Mrs. Frazier?
Ripped by thewildbunch22