I'm sorry.
If you keep doing what you've always done...
you will keep what you have always been.
I a cell shared with a guy
those words...
Tattooed on his chest
in Japanese characters.
After ten years is that guy out...
a week later he was killed because
what he was what he always was.
These words are still on his skin .
Somewhere buried in a coffin.
Nothing changes unless you bring that change.
In case you need me have
call this number.
They know where I am.
Take care
(fury)
Papa.
not the city and come into contact with someone with a criminal record
If you just a digression does go back.
We're done here
Let me know when you have a job,
I will send the papers.
cool
You probation officer can be your friend
or an asshole.
That is your decision.
Yes.
Is there Rodney?
- No, Rodney is dead.
And Summer?
This is to the west.
I bought this tent six years ago.
Do not bottle Beaumont under the bar?
You knew Rodney.
Old habits you learn difficult.
How do you drink it?
Pure.
When I took over there were some guys who said Rodney
owed them something.
Money and obligations and all.
That's not happened in a while.
Since  hear them catch thieves,
no ghosts.
If you are in money,
that's all gone now.
I had many agents pay to stay out of jail.
This is a thousand years ago.
- I thought so.
Do you have contact with the old crew?
Mike?
He's dead.
He ​​died in prison.
Matt?
- Also dead.
And Sal? That is not dead?
- He is not dead.
Good.
- He lies in a coma in Grace.
If only he had had more time to
his affairs in order.
Gretchen, what happened to your hair?
The past has caught up with me.
No one should make a new start.
My children come home soon.
They know nothing about the old days.
I'm glad to see you.
But I do not want you here comes Foley.
ever
Who are you?
I am disappointed.
Do not you see?
The chin and jaw line?
I know I have his eyes.
Yes, I see it.
You're his boy Eddy.
- That is correct.
Ethan.
You have a good memory.
It's a long time ago.
More than 20 years.
- 25.
My mistake.
If a man is so long,
you want the figures are not wrong.
I do not blame you that you're suspicious
Here I am.
Sitting in the dark.
I'm waiting for you.
- What do you want from me, Ethan?
I want to buy you a drink.
We have a 35% share in this tent.
Easy merit.
That I owe to you and my father.
My father always said you were planning to start a club to
We wanted a bar  begin.
Not what this is.
I'll show you.
We take a drink and talk about
the old days and maybe the present.
Xavier is here.
He ​​wants you and me back.
Come here.
Bring him to my table.
Everything is free. I'll be back.
Are you alone?
That does not seem right.
- I'm waiting for someone.
I was also waiting for someone.
I just found him.
- Thanks, but no thanks.
Ethan told me I had to come along.
That someone wanted to meet me.
- You have apparently met each other.
Do you want to lose her?
- Take it easy.
So get yourself a stroke.
I'm not you  ested in what you
it even sells.
Yes? Pull yourself but occasionally,
because I certainly do not.
You owe me that drink still guilty.
That was me something.
I'm leaving.
I take you home.
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
We want to see.
Empty bottles means that business is good.
La Veuve, Dom, Crystal.
All very nice, but...
What have we here?
A Billecart Salmon from 1960.
This is a shame to open them.
They have 10 or 15 years time.
But if you're an asshole of a mutual fund are...
And attempts in the pans of a
poor unhappy girl to peek...
Then you do what you gotta do.
I had a '59 from a few weeks ago.
It was spectacular.
The minerals weaving the elements together as silk.
I love champagne.
I drink it often, because I have much to celebrate.
Life is good  as
my people do their work.
This is what happened when you had service, Ethan.
It will not happen again.
Xavier, I caught the bastard.
- Why will you one day, if you're good...
From '59 allowed to taste.
Our colleague here has
that option anymore.
Do you think I would not notice?
$ 250,000 and I would not notice?
The
the money will be difficult now to get back.
You can find a solution.
Safe flight.
Wait a minute.
- Yesterday I came out of prison.
Yesterday.
- I know and I'm sorry.
Listen to me.
I thought we should go out...
And what would drink.
Probably
I wanted to show you that I am like my father.
The truth is...
I never really knew him.
My mother...
- What do you want from me?
I want to know why you have killed my father.
Down there is still a lot of money.
What do you know about me and your father?
Only what my mother told.
That you were good friends.
Partners.
- Did she tell you what we have done?
Our work?
- No.
But I found out.
That's all I could find.
Every article, every photo.
Why do you keep all this?
- How could I know him differently?
You were swindlers.
The best in town according to the oldies.
You need this release.
Your father is long dead.
- No, I must know him.
Put ​​yourself in me.
We were swindlers.
A long history of various scams.
But, if it worked with much profit.
And it worked.
So your father was greedy and
the target hard uitkneep.
I never found out why.
He had debts.
Up over his head.
Maps, horses.
The
my mother has taken years to repay that.
I'm sorry to hear that.
The target was a tough guy.
Did not care that it was
scammed.
He gave me a choice.
Your father's murder or die with him.
I'm sorry.
I have been in a small room
spent thinking about the choice I made that night.
I was young.
Less than you are now.
But I made a choice.
It has never left me.
And I'm punished.
What was his name, that target?
What does it matter?
He ​​was the target.
Your father had put us both in a corner and there was only
way.
If someone had done that,
I would murder him.
I'm just saying...
I understand.
Yes, and I think we can help each other.
Look at me once.
25 years of my life are gone.
If you're as smart as you think, you
that room and ripped that shit off the wall...
And throws it away.
We do not socialize.
Can I watch the game?
Give it the cheapest.
- Sit anywhere you like.
Do you?
I said no.
They always make a mess.
No.
- Let go.
It means trouble.
No.
Please stop.
Please stop .
- She said stop it.
Fuck.
- After you.
He can not hurt.
Put that down.
It's good.
What do you know him?
I just met him tonight.
He ​​would...
You're the freak last night.
Beautiful.
For the effort.
- And then your share?
I was not even here.
- And the girl?
She is waiting inside.
Wish her a good night from me.
He can.
What happened?
- I'd have been killed.
It was all fixed.
- That I do not care.
You do not look nearly
and had killed my boy. Rot now.
I need this job.
I care that it pays for you.
I work twice as hard.
This will never pay for me.
Now least you have time for coffee.
Did you have anything to do?
Of course not.
- I needed that job. I need money.
Tell me what you need.
What do you need?
I thought I clearly was.
- That is correct.
You're on the right path.
Every criminal says first.
You're not every criminal.
You have skills.
Skills that I can use.
- What are you talking about?
I'm doing a scam thing.
Not just scams.
I'm the perfect target.
For the Samaritan.
Here I am talking about.
Why you should join.
It's your thing.
With you and my father.
I am your father.
I want that are not.
My mother is long been alone.
When I was 17, she brought
the new guy to take home.
He takes us out to dinner...
Orders a steak for me.
He ​​sees me as a man so...
Not as a boy.
And they say to me...
They get married.
What should I say?
I would like to have a father in
filthy body shops will...
And smells like a urinal smells.
So I eat my steak on.
And I'm going to work.
Phone calls late at night for the same
number on his phone bill.
Motel Rooms are calculated on credit card.
Of course I say nothing.
Let mom only to find out.
And when she finds out I'm on his side.
Then I give him a shot, she also always
Until I let a professional appearance
who says he owes her $ 200...
For her abortion that he had undergone.
The poor wretch.
He ​​had no idea what hit him.
But I knew I
son of my father.
So yes, you're right.
You're not my father.
But I have no father.
I need a partner.
Did your mother never found someone else?
- What?
No.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
You have no idea what I can do for you.
Stay away from me.
Yet suffered from last night?
- On this side nothing.
No police, no Jake, but she is
every night of the week visited.
I was just leaving.
You're going nowhere.
I owe you an apology.
That I called you a creep.
Sorry.
- Excuse accepted.
In any case, thanks.
I've been raped and that's no fun.
What?
- You make it come on thick.
I do not know if you captivates me or that I fear you must be
Beguiled.
Is that it?
I buy a bottle of liquor of your choice?
And you do not even try to get in my pants?
Good.
Try this.
Ask me again how my day was.
How was your day?
- Kloten. And yours?
Kloten.
- See?
Conversation.
- Sorry, I have not practiced much.
I love a chat. Or a pathetic story than
My wife does not understand me.
You remind me of my first girlfriend thought.
I have no wife.
Girlfriend then.
- I have no girlfriend.
I have no family, no home, no dog.
I have no friends.
I have nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
I really do not.
My parents died when I was two.
I remember them.
I was raised by my
alcoholic bastard of a grandmother.
Until I could get out of there.
Anyone who ever gave me
is dead.
My grandmother lives probably because I hate her.
Do you think that's funny?
- A little bit.
Do you have something better?
Last week I came to prison.
After 25 years have been, because I
my best friend got killed.
Everyone I ever cared about is dead or nearly dead...
Or wish I was dead.
Yes, you are certainly more pathetic than I am.
I really think about you
to take a good fucking.
And if I do not want that now?
In case you are on your head too often
beaten, I will be very clear.
This is your big chance.
I'll tell you when it's time
for you to do something.
You may kiss me now.
Here to hear there.
I've tried a few times
suicide.
Do you do upset?
I'm glad you're not successful.
I am a junkie.
Do you do upset?
I'm a murderer.
I can not remember the last time
I did something I was proud.
I know what you mean.
I think you understand.
Nothing changes unless you change it.
Yes, I know how that sounds.
Every morning I woke up in jail
I thought about what that really meant.
Listen.
I must go to the toilet.
I need to use.
Otherwise  I climb up the wall.
You can leave if you want.
I understand that.
You do not close the door to do.
How many of those places you've ever been?
You know.
Not.
Not ?
- I bought them in a bookstore.
And then read about places I
I never could afford.
And chips that I could never afford to eat
Now if you could go to India...
- Brazil
Absolutely.
I would fly to Rio and then
16,000 km along the coast to Macio.
So I...
This could see.
- Why Rio?
Because
seems to me that the place where you can forget everything.
You are doing well.
I was worried about.
- Yeah, me too.
I want you to come and live here.
Welcome home.
It smells good here.
What is it?
It feels like this is real.
If we build a life here.
We do the same.
Then we need to clarify things.
That evening in the Apo A
Wau with that guy.
Then you came not so coincidentally show up.
What are you talking about?
Ethan had sent you yet?
Do you know this all along?
I had sometimes thought.
I owed him money.
More than I can afford.
He said if I would go to bed with you
that we were even.
I had already done this before.
Not very often.
Twice.
That I do not care.
- I think so.
I said I would look at
and then decide.
I did so as if I had a choice.
Jake decided that I was a whore but
and that he could get free.
I lay on the bathroom floor and thought...
This is the end for me.
On my knee for an asshole.
And when you walked inside.
After you left I told Ethan...
I would find a way to bring him back
to pay, but I did not do what he wanted.
Through him I went to that bar.
But all my senses were focused on you.
I just wanted the truth.
I'm sorry.
- Promise that you'll never lie to me.
I promise you the same.
- I promise.
And I'm sorry.
- I do not.
3602.
Come inside. Do you drink?
- We need to talk business.
You will finally become partners.
This is good news.
You misunderstand me.
You and I will never work together.
Never say never.
- I am here because of Iris.
I know what's going on.
Is that so?
- Yes.
I do not know, Foley.
I have good eye on you.
And I think you know nothing.
I think in fact that you do
have no idea.
Jake know you do not you?
- He knows you certainly did.
I'm sorry.
But Jake was pretty pissed at you.
So now...
Jake sits in a car
Iris in her apartment.
If I do not call him in ten minutes,
he goes to the top...
Then he fucks her turn her head
together with a stick.
Or maybe he saves her head in between
and he fucks her.
Think I forgive you
that you have killed my father?
That you wanted.
And I know exactly how you go into debt problems.
You will earn eight million for me.
Eight million is the price for the ball...
You in the head your best friend's lap,
to save yourself.
Listen to me.
- No, listen to me.
I have a target.
Ready for use.
But he does it the old fashioned way.
So I have someone with him to his old ways
from their money.
You want me to get back
only for what I did.
This is about what you will do
and I exactly what I say.
Do I care that Iris learn something about you,
that they really do not want to know.
We told each other everything.
If you can not catch me taking.
We have no secrets.
You need to know a secret,
a secret to tell.
Your old girlfriend Tess Armstrong said
you think they had a little problem rectified.
That's what she kept.
Do I have a child?
You're so accustomed to thinking in miniature.
All those years cooped up in that little jail cell.
And in that small apartment where your father and mother played...
You're the one who is fooled.
She's your daughter.
Iris...
Your daughter.
- No.
Your precious little girl.
I should shoot you because you said something.
She's your daughter.
- That is a lie.
When you met Iris, your own flesh and blood,
you had no idea.
No idea.
It was priceless.
If you kill me now, what then?
How long do you think the police need that
has to find out?
No, you do everything I tell you.
You know all the secrets of Iris.
So you know they
with a razor has been working.
I wonder how she feels when she knows them all the time
that was fucking...
This is the last time you do that.
I almost pity you.
After all these years your targets
grazing take...
Who is now the target?
You have six minutes to decisions.
Call him.
- Excellent decision.
He does not answer.
- Give your car keys.
If he touched her...
Swallowed, but suicide.
Did you miss me?
See that?
This is Foley. An eye for an eye.
Are you okay? It's all right.
Listen...
I need him out of here and then I must lay low...
In case there are problems, ok?
- You mean "we" must keep our heads down...
You and I together.
- No, it's smarter to be kept separate.
What has happened with Ethan?
- I've arranged.
What does that mean?
- It means that I regularly have...
You have nothing to do with him.
What is going on?
- Nothing.
Listen, Iris,
I can not go back to prison.
I need him out of here before the police come
. Say nothing to anyone.
I have no one to tell the opposite.
You are the one to whom I tell everything.
Come on.
Xavier makes you wonder.
This is the man in 3602.
His car is at the usual place.
Celia?
- You are old.
You look the same.
Parent, but the same.
- Celia, I have a daughter?
How did you find out?
You have been in prison.
Tess wanted from you.
When she died,
I respected her decision.
What Tess said
to her child about who her father was?
They said he died in a car accident.
By that time, Tess sick.
Children do not ask questions when their world falls apart.
Listen, Foley...
She is better off thinking that you're dead.
I know that it is difficult to hear,
but she now has a life.
She does not know what kind of people they descended.
Would you like to tell me her name?
I'm not looking for her, I want to just know.
Iris...
Her name is Iris.
Thank you, Celia.
What do you do? Get away from my house.
- What have you told me about Ethan? What?
Who do you think did this to me?
Jesus, Foley,
what has he done to you?
I'm sorry.
You a week.
None damn word to let me know that you
was alive, but you regret?
I have half my life spent
in prison.
If you sit there, decisions
for you.
Everything here is new to me.
There are things I need to put in a row.
And to do that I need time.
Time...
Some time away from here.
A little while...
Away from you.
You're lying.
We had promised 'no lies'.
I know when you lie.
You can give me just as well tell the truth.
- That's the truth. You must trust me.
We currently can not interact.
It would be best if you left.
I can not tell you why.
If I had not have been necessary
I would not ask.
You want me to trust you, but you do not trust me
agree with the truth.
If I were to say that the
to protect you, would you say...
You do to protect yourself.
- I could do that.
I know. And I also know that every
lie discovered in each story that I tell you.
You should be the one to whom I can always tell the truth...
But I can not.
And I ask you again, please...
Trust me.
Let's just leave.
We are going to a place where it is hot, with beaches...
And fat tourists we can light up.
I will plan everything to perfection.
The only thing you need to do is
say yes.
I can give you money. Just take it to
and go as far as possible. Tell me where.
For how long?
- A couple of weeks, maybe a month.
Or longer...
Or never.
No, sweetie.
Not 'never'.
Iris?
I need your help.
I got myself into trouble.
I have done nothing...
But not something I can shake off of me.
What are we talking about?
- A local man, moved many products.
Should be a great catch.
Are you now an informant?
- You're my probation officer, or not?
Is this not what I am supposed to do?
With Deacon.
- Did you get?
Yes, he's here.
Yes?
- You do not have criminal mastermind to...
to some guy to pay off.
You've already made some mistake, Foley.
If you have further makes
you're dead.
Tonight I want my answer .
I go upstairs.
20, 19...
14, 13, 12...
11, 10, 9...
Congratulations.
The good news?
You have a very good cardiovascular system.
The bad news...
Is that bad things I've learned
in prison.
Did you know that a small knife
can do as much damage as a large knife?
This example...
I use him for cutting fruit...
But when I press this...
And a 2.5 cm long incision make...
You will bleed to death in two minutes.
Listen, Foley.
- No, you listen.
If we merge these scams cops,
you must promise me two things.
Val die anyway, Foley.
You have no control here. Snap not you?
These are my terms:
First:
Iris...
Will never hear about what you told me.
If you even give a hint about...
I will murder you. Do you understand?
- Yes.
Second: If we run these scams
you my orders to the details follow...
No exception. Understood?
- Yes.
You do not sound convincing.
- Yes, I understand, absolutely.
Come on.
Should we be concerned that we be disturbed?
- No, do not worry.
The clinic closes at 7 pm...
And I stay here at night to make sure
of junkies that there is no hack.
Are you  actually be a doctor?
Will I be attached by a conc you?
In Serbia? I was a surgeon, here
I am a watchman.
Miro knows what he does. He gave me enough
patched in prison.
You have saved me hundreds of times.
I owe you.
- Take no memories.
Just make it down.
I have taken precautions.
If I am disabled,
two things happen:
The cops find Jake
with your DNA on it.
And would Iris' t know
about her long-lost dad.
Where you have hidden her, she can
be found.
This is what I need:
A high quality hotel room to get in shape...
And I the details of the scam may develop.
I have a wife as bait.
Prefers older, with experience.
I have a male IT needs,
international accounts that can open...
And me through the technical section can lock
And I have a residence place needs
to the scam.
Preferably a house.
Large, expensive, and you oleerd.
Awesome. This is exactly what I mean partner.
- We are not partners, Ethan.
I once my partner.
I killed him.
You look good, Foley.
Let me introduce you to your wife, Helena.
Helena, this is your husband.
Well, new spouse.
So you know how this scam works?
- Yes. Well, the first half of it.
Ethan is the insider, you're the outsider
and I am the bait.
And drug addict woman some rich dude.
The project developer.
The long-term work is finished.
Six months ago, someone stole some money from the target.
250 grand.
- And whosoever was not there anymore.
But he had an accomplice...
I.
I say to the target: "Are you stupid bastard who
are you lit up..."
let her 't tell.
Ethan takes me to the target and says:
"It was not my fault, it was not my idea."
250 grand stolen during a drug deal,
the target wants his money now.
But I only way to pay;
my rich husband, Neil.
See? I told you that she is a pro,
she knows what to do.
I know what I should do,
but who is the target?
Are you out of your head?
You never told me that we go to Xavier cops.
What you gonna do, bitch?
Are you suddenly in a position that allows you
just walk away?
H? disrespecteer her.
If we dealt with the case are
depend our lives apart.
Or should I remind you
the promise you made?
My apologies.
Are you 100% sure,
that this money can not be traced?
Twice a year flies Xavier
here to make sure that his money was laundered...
And spread to 'clean' accounts.
That he always does in person.
But it is such a greedy asshole...
That if he finds out that he can get an additional percentage
...
By someone to cheat,
I guarantee you he will do it.
The scam is not about the taking of someone's money
It's about gaining confidence.
The important thing is to set up a situation where even
the target knows...
That he is being cheated, but he still thinks
done him a favor.
If he leads the scam.
Why it's called 'The Samaritan'.
Yes?
I'm Helena.
I wanted to thank you for...
Not be an asshole.
No thanks.
Do you have something to drink?
Ethan Has sent you?
Rot anyway, I'm not a whore.
I'm sorry.
I am here because I like to look at you.
Like you said;
if it fails...
Is that our death.
This is not part of the scam.
What do you, Helen?
I know who Ethan is, but I do not know
who you are and why you are here.
I did it the old fashioned way and you do
choke, but you were acting...
Professional,
so I had to just ask.
It is rude.
So Ethan has you too?
Completely in the rod.
Do you really think that if 't we manage our
he just...
Pays off and let us go?
- I do not know.
But I think he keeps coming back and...
Takes and takes and takes.
We'll get through it.
There is no we, Foley.
If you feel differently
end up dead.
Is this like a place with a smooth janus
a developer would build for himself?
How far is this from the club down?
- 17 minutes.
Exactly 17 minutes?
- Trust me, I'm timed.
And before you say something, I'm night
at the right time to ride.
Over 12 o'clock the last detail.
Are you really sure that Xavier
self drive around here?
I know 'm He gets aroused it to me to show you how
something the right way to do it.
If I am too rough with Helena, he gets
intervene and take control of the situation.
Come inside.
- We come too late to Helena to pick up.
What is this? Did you have
of your club broads?
Why I wanted to see you first,
for you to motivate for the big show.
Come down and say hello.
Hi.
You thought you were rid of me, huh?
I could not figure out why you lied
I just had to know why...
But I never thought you would show me
off for money.
I do not know where you think you are doing.
- You can no longer tell me what to do.
I've cleaned up.
I have quarreled.
I have done everything the right way...
But you wanted me out of the way
to continue with the scam.
You're the true addict, Foley,
I do not.
I need to talk to you privately.
- Everything you told me to say...
Can you say in front of him.
Luck tonight.
Come home rich.
Are you ready to work?
I have no other choice.
It is my pledge...
Just in case you at the last moment a change in
plan is.
She just keeps clinging?
I'm trying to find out how her
I can get away from me, but then what?
What are you doing?
Do you stay with her?
Maybe you can just be friends.
- Ethan, stop talking.
Helena.
Helena, you better be ready.
Sloppy bitch.
Val DEATH - bitch.
Probably she had this long planned, but she waited
right time for me to sew.
The woman is dead, Ethan.
- Yes, and I'm good long cry...
When you told me how to fix this.
- We will not it dissolve.
This is a triple swindle;
husband, wife, dealer.
All about the bait.
No bait, no scam.
The target arrives on about three hours.
We have no more time.
- You must know someone from the past.
I can call Gretchen, but
finger you cut...
Might betray that they are not addicted wife of a developer is
Ga sew it yourself.
- I have you all done well. Also sew yourself.
No.
We need bait.
- There is nothing in that.
Is she not smart enough,
good enough, fast enough?
What she does not know what Helena had?
- Will not happen.
It's not your decision.
Do I still have a choice? Or should I let meewaaien
but with the wind?
Yes, of course you have a choice.
We split 60, 20, 20, which is
1.6 million for you. What do you say?
Yes.
-will never work.
You know I can t.
Or is it your wife that I should play?
Right, the target must be really stupid
to believe that I am your wife...
But I could be your daughter.
The scam has a coke-addicted woman needs...
Who plays dirty behind the back of her husband, right?
But it might as well be
a daughter who sniff Daddy's money.
She's right.
- Listen...
It's not that your not pretty enough,
fast enough or smart enough...
You're just not ready, and we have no time to
you ready for it.
You know the terms are not the backups, and equipment not
If you make a mistake you chase us all killed.
There are worse things than being murdered.
I think you know it.
How much do you owe?
- What?
I want to know how deep this is
that you would want to commit suicide...
To get out, like your dad.
We can do this.
It's over.
I need this.
I can take part and go far away.
Do not you think I deserve that?
Come with me.
- You do not want to join, ok?
Bugger. It continues.
Out with me right now.
Do not listen to him.
- No, do not listen to me...
I try us all just rich.
I stay.
Everything I touch goes fucked.
How do you think that is?
I found it.
Yes?
- Daddy? Help me.
What have you done?
What did you tell her?
- It's the scam.
What are you talking about?
- We started without you.
Xavier I think Iris father-millionaires
am to pick her drug debt to pay off.
We were neither of plan
to you just to drain, Foley.
This could be your masterpiece,
gives all the clippings from my wall.
The chance that this will work
is almost zero.
That is also the chance that Iris
survives the night.
If we do not, he kills her.
I 've seen him do for much less.
Why are you doing this to me?
- You know why.
I did not murder your father, Ethan.
I had no choice.
Then you are so well known
with this kind of precarious situations.
We are talking about Iris her life.
Now is your chance to finally play daddy.
Papa.
Pull your suit.
I thought you would shave.
- Nobody shaves at night.
The scam revolves around the details.
Here is Dad.
I'm sorry to say that your sweet little angel
themselves in trouble have worked.
Unfortunately this is not the first time.
What is it you owe?
- 250 000.
I think you'll find this nice, huh?
More proof that you were right to send me away.
- I sent you away for your own good.
You wanted me to have just gone.
You were never there for me.
When Mom died, I had nothing.
No one wanted me.
This, what is happening here now,
because of you.
And as usual you expect me to pay for your mistakes.
Enough! This is not a family therapy.
I want my money now.
Please...
Help me.
Dad, I need help.
My cell phone.
- I had not told you to do something.
I'm sorry.
Were you planning to cash a check?
I make an electronic transfer.
- So I've got my account information?
I want this information.
I do not know your name, I want nothing about you.
I just got all the money...
of one of my foreign accounts
met, except $ 250,000.
I removed my password.
All you need to do...
Is yours to enter. Then you have full access to the money...
And you can make about
to wherever you want.
I want you to check account activity
in Belize.
Yes, that's because it does not matter
me what time it is there.
$ 250,000.
Are we ready?
How much do you stand on the foreign accounts?
That I had less than three million are
Do you have a few with more than eight?
- Why?
I would like you to
a new deal considering.
I have eight million U.S. dollars to be laundered...
And it seems that your
excellent cleaning results.
Before you decide, Vernon,
would you like to give us a preview?
This is very beautiful.
Do you have a wine cellar?
- Yes.
I once bought a house a couple
incapacitated because of the cellar.
The woman, who sold it...
Took me down, because the collection of
her future ex-husband was there.
La Vite '59, '61 O'Brien,
'45 Brunello, really fantastic.
Then my eye fell on the thermostat
and I say to her:...
"I do not know how to tell you this,
but this basement would be 12 degrees...
'But it is 24 degrees.'
And she looks at me with a crooked eye,
, and she says coolly, "I know."
Yes, I also have a La Vite 61
I save for a special occasion.
He must be drunk
soon as the cork is almost dry.
The rest is in the car.
What is happening?
Watch and learn.
The usual locks cost me a minimum of
30%, which is $ 2.5 million.
This is eight clean.
What if he tries...
- He will not try.
If he does,
we change his mind.
It seems to me that my
if you want help with your problem...
The more value to me to have
than just the return of my $ 250,000.
And your daughter.
- 15%.
So we agree with 10.
I do not know.
Why did you do that?
You wanted him to change their minds.
- Help me.
The only way you can help your daughter
, is to accept the deal.
I need her to go to the hospital.
- And you will once things settled.
Please press. Hold on.
What do you want me to do?
Same as first, you deposit some money at
one of my accounts...
And you take the cash to.
Do we have a deal?
No.
No deal.
You can not make the deal,
because he is not a developer.
He is a swindler.
And this is a scam.
What makes you the target.
Why would you tell me this?
Because nothing changes unless you make sure it changes.
What are you talking about hell?
I tell you, not because I
give money.
I just want that piece of shit
knows how close he had everything he wanted...
Just before you shoot him dead.
No, not him.
Him.
It's lying.
- Dirty bastard.
She is his daughter. They...
- I know, Ethan.
He's your father.
You can not hurt me anymore.
Do you know?
I'm with Celia visited.
I have been in that position.
There is only one way for this to be
digen.
I'll tell you what you want to know, and if you
do not believe me, but stop a bullet in me.
Just let her go.
Nobody ever goes anywhere.
Are you okay?
Stay here.
I am not disabled because eight million U.S. dollars.
It's only money.
Take it.
Take the money.
We can make a deal.
Do you know who I am?
- I know exactly who you are.
Why do I do this.
Let's go. Come on,
we have here. Let's go.
No.
Iris.
Miro, help us, please.
She's an immediate blood transfusion,
but the clinic has no blood supply.
Use me.
- We have no time to blood testing.
When I give her the wrong blood she dies.
If we find a relative,
as they are related...
Miro, it will work.
Miro...
I have some money, here you can find it.
Take what you need.
And give the rest to her.
- Foley, you survive this.
Let me stop the transfusion.
She needed a second chance.
You must sign here and here.
- How exactly does the transfer take?
A moment.
Exactly so long.
How long were you planning to stay here?
- I'm not sure.
How long does it take to get lost?
If you keep going with what you've always done...
You keep what you have always been.
Nothing changes unless you ensure that it changes
I know how it sounds...
But every morning when I wake up I think about what
really means.
Nothing changes unless you ensure that it changes