Hey, Billy.
It's Thursday.
Come back tomorrow.
No, it's actually
Friday, ya cheap prick.
Hey!
Junkie putz.
You gonna kill
me out here?
Hey!
And that so lamely
and unfashionable,
that dogs bark at me
as I go by them.
Discounts on my
known deformities.
Milagros.
I give you heaven...
And I give you hell.
Hey, mister.
I had some car trouble
out in the desert.
I need to use
the telephone.
One American dollar.
Sure.
It's inside.
It's all inside.
All your dreams come true inside this tent.
Hombres, juanitas,
open your knees
and feel the breeze.
Hey, brother,
you have a phone around here?
Excuse me.
You girls seen
this chick with...?
Yeah, she's
over there.
Thank you.
What?
Hey.
What do you want?
Sorry, I didn't
mean to be staring.
Yeah you did. You paid
to stare. Show's over.
Are you deaf?
Are you real?
What do you think?
Well, I think no.
All right then.
Get lost.
Hey, hey. Sweetheart.
Please, I am lost.
Look, I scream and
five guys with tire irons...
come and beat you
into pudding.
Please don't do that.
My name's Nate.
Nate Poole.
I play trumpet
back in the city.
Look, I've been up all night long
walking through the desert.
All I want is a drink...
and just a place to sit down for a while.
I ain't gonna cause
you no trouble.
I just want a place to
sit down and think about...
what I'm gonna do.
What kind
of music?
Mm. Oh, what difference
does that make?
Hey. Really
nice music.
One drink.
I'm drinking gin.
A girl after
my own heart.
Goddamn, life
is good.
Hour ago,
I was a dead man.
Now I'm drinking warm gin with an angel.
So... mm... carny life, huh?
Yeah, Chiapas, Durango
yeah, the
full circuit.
You ever been
to the States?
No, I've never been
there before.
Well, goddamn,
your English is pretty good.
That's because of Sam. He, um,
he's from London, and so...
and because of the movies, they, um,
the small-town theaters
they hang sheets
on the walls
and they show old movies
on Saturdays at night.
Huh. How long you
been an angel?
I'm not an angel.
I'm a bird woman.
I don't know, I, um...
couldn't get fat enough or grow
a beard and I hate snakes, so...
just nothing else left.
Well, hey,
it suits you.
Thanks.
I'm tired of them, though.
What's that?
The wings?
Yeah, they're heavy.
They hurt my shoulders
and my back
and I'm just, I'm
tired of them.
Well, why don't you just take them off?
Why walk around in pain?
I'll give you
a hand.
It's not...
I can do it, it's...
I feel like you should leave now.
You know?
Okay, listen, uh
hey, thank you very
kindly for the drink.
Are you going back
to the States?
Yep.
Listen, uh...
if you'd like to get away
from all this, you know...
you're welcome to go
back with me.
No, I can't.
You take care.
Mm.
Women.
Uh-huh.
You got
a girl?
They're creatures,
I mean it, freaks.
I found her
in the garbage.
An infant,
wet and crying in the garbage.
And I plucked her away
from all that and I...
I gave her a home.
Hey there. Uh...
her wings...
they're real?
Hm.
You know, man, I've been around the
block but I ain't never been around...
a neighborhood
like this.
Thank you.
Are you trying
to steal my Lily?
Is that why
you're here?
It is, isn't it?
Well, so be it!
Hey, man,
I don't know what you're talking about.
I ain't trying to steal nobody, man,
I just...
listen, I don't
want your girl
I just wanna get the fuck outta this nut house.
Jesus.
Where's my Lily
gonna go?
What is there for a girl like that?
I'm her family.
I protect her
from the real world.
Listen, Sam...
may I call you Sam?
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
You know things now, sir.
What if word got out
the girl's for real.
Wings.
For real.
Listen, mister,
you ain't got nothing to worry about with me.
I just wanna
go on my way.
Hey, listen, lady,
I don't take kindly to snakes.
I'd appreciate it
if you'd just...
Fuck! Goddamn it!
What the fuck?
For a few seconds
before you die
you'll see the future
with great clarity.
Hey, get in!
So after Happy kills you
can I get your
record collection?
Jesus Christ,
come on, Harriet
you think I'd make
this shit up?
No. Hey. You know,
some wandering Indians
shoot Happy's guy seconds
before he's gonna shoot you
you walk all night through the desert on foot...
get captured by
some carny freaks...
almost bit by a ten foot long rattlesnake...
and then a beautiful and mysterious girl
You're enjoying
this, huh?
Jesus, Nate. You fucked his wife.
Everybody knows.
Nate... are
you there?
Are you... are you
listening to me?
Oh, Jesus Christ,
listen... hold...
Hey, listen.
You tell Happy...
set up a
meeting tomorrow.
A meeting?
At the Little
New Yorker. Lunchtime.
You want me to just call Happy Shannon.
Yeah, you call that prick
and you tell him...
Jesus Christ. You tell him,
bring a million dollars.
Nate?
Hey, kid, can I borrow
that camera for a second?
You're a dead man.
Wow!
Goddamn!
Did you see? Did you see?
I flew, I did, I flew.
Man, I didn't
think you could.
I can't.
I'm too big.
I'm too heavy for these to carry me
but sometimes when the wind is,
is strong enough...
Wait, I gotta get a picture of this.
Okay, but if
I don't like these
you're gonna throw
them away, okay?
I swear to God.
Just stand right over there by the way.
You promise?
I swear!
Oh, just like that.
Oh.
I don't believe it.
So what happened to you
out in the desert?
Oh. Son of a bitch
tried to kill me.
Over a woman?
What else?
Did you love her?
Absolutely not.
Hm. That's
kind of sad.
How about you?
Fast carny life.
Beautiful gal.
You must have your share of men.
How come you
ran away?
It was time
to leave the nest.
Time to leave the nest.
How about a bite
of that apple?
You steer?
You are a pretty
little thing. Hm?
Thank you.
Thank your
mother and father.
I got it.
Can I have my apple back?
Full bath.
Twin beds.
And I can get you pizza delivered till eleven p.m.
Oh, that would
be heavenly.
She's a knockout,
Nate. A knockout.
Listen. I
appreciate it.
Sure. You know,
even with the hump.
Know what
I mean?
You ever smell
the ocean?
Sure. Yeah, I used
to work at this joint.
A funky little place
right on the beach.
Have you ever
seen the ocean?
Never?
Uh-uh.
You ain't never
seen the ocean?
No.
Well, I'll tell you what,
I'm gonna take you to this place...
way up close you can see the
dolphins swimming all day long.
Would you like
to do that?
Yeah, I'd like
to see that.
It's really beautiful.
You okay?
Yeah.
It's the wind.
I'm sorry. I must
look awful.
Sweetheart, you could
never look really bad.
Hoo.
My back hurts.
You, um...
you think it'd be okay if I took my coat off?
'Cause that
would really help.
Sure. Come here.
Mm.
Holy shit.
I'm telling you,
I'm never gonna get used to this.
Wow.
Nobody asked
you to.
Hey, I didn't
mean it like that.
It's fine.
Hey, I, uh...
I said something
wrong to you.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I know what I am, Nate.
Ah, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
She split, man.
She what?
Your honey, she left
a few hours ago.
Fuck.
Oh, man, what do you
mean she split?
I mean she went
into the office,
she made a couple of phone calls and then she, uh,
she hit the road.
I n that old truck
you came in.
Fuck.
Anybody else use this phone after her?
Are you a police officer?
'Cause if there's some
sort of problem
I should call
the manager.
Dr. Rosenblum's office.
Uh, yeah, hey, listen, I'm
looking for, uh, for my wife.
I believe she may
be a patient there.
Uh, the name's,
uh, Luster.
Luster...
She's in consultation with the doctor right now.
Uh, what kind
of doctor?
Doctor Rosenblum
is a plastic surgeon.
Get away from her.
Why are you
doing this?
Please don't
do this.
What, do you think that
I like being a freak?
Amazing as she is,
it's not a normal...
Fuck normal.
Since when does normal win
a goddamn prize, huh?
Lily. You're different.
Please don't do this.
Please.
But I could be like all the other girls.
Never.
I'm sorry, I think
I'm wasting your time.
Sorry.
I don't ever want
to hear
a goddamn word
about this ever.
Or I'll get your address
and I swear to God, Doc
I'll burn your
house down.
Thank you.
Hey, baby,
you still there?
I'm here.
Listen to me.
This ain't no
pact with the devil.
'Course it is.
It's your life
for hers.
Oh, come on,
that's bullshit.
So, uh,
being managed by a notorious killer pimp
is gonna help
this girl.
Hey, listen, sweetheart,
he can make her rich.
He can make her dead.
Come on, he ain't
gonna hurt her.
Why not?
'Cause I'm gonna
be there.
Please. You can't
protect yourself...
Hey, listen,
just cool it, okay?
Nothing's gonna
happen to this girl.
Happy'll never
even meet her, okay?
All I'm doing is
I'm giving Happy
a piece of Lily's future.
All right? That's it.
He'll make a fortune
on this thing.
Okay.
I'm gonna do everything.
He's not even
gonna meet her.
Hey, listen,
he's just gonna get his cut.
She know
about this?
Hey, she trusts me.
Okay. She
doesn't get hurt.
What makes you so sure she
can make that kind of money?
I mean,
this town's lousy with beautiful women.
Nate?
What makes her so special?
What?
Her wings.
She's got wings.
Uh-huh.
And I suppose you have
another picture of a jackalope
that could be available for the right price too, huh?
Are you frightened,
Mr. Poole?
God, you should be.
Listen to me.
I swear to God,
if I would've known that that was your wife
I'd never
woulda touched her.
I don't have
a wife, Mr. Poole.
I'm a widower.
Yeah. Very sudden.
Listen, hey man,
I know you want me dead, okay?
I don't wanna die.
I swear to God
this girl is for real.
I mean, I don't get it,
I don't understand it
it's something freaky,
she's some kind of goddamn freak of nature.
But she has wings.
So I get the angel...
and you get
your life.
Sounds... religious.
No, it's... it's
a little different.
I was thinking more
you get a percent
you get like 65, 75%.
You get your piece and then I get,
I get my end, which is 20, 25%.
And I get my life.
And the angel?
Listen, she's
not an angel.
She's just...
Theology aside.
What's... what's to keep
me from just...
blowing your
head off right now
and taking the girl?
Hey, man,
you don't know where she is.
True.
Until I get
Roland here
to peel off all your skin with a needle-nose pliers
and then you tell me where she is
and the fastest
route to her.
I don't know
where she is, okay?
A friend of mine is driving
her around in circles, okay?
And if I'm not at
the goddamn phone booth
saying all the right
things in 23 minutes
he's gonna call
his cousin
who's a homicide detective
and report my murder, okay?
She's gonna disappear, and they're
gonna investigate your ass, all right?
Happy, I mean, you know,
look at this like...
making a whole bunch
of money
and doing very little,
you know what I'm saying?
Any idiot can fake a picture.
I would need
to see her.
Oh, man, no way,
you're gonna...
I'm no fucking idiot.
You're gonna snatch her
and kill me. Come on.
You have my word.
Hm. I have your word
as a gangster.
As a gangster,
and as a partner.
Okay then, then we
have a deal?
You meet me at the opera house,
the new opera house
six o'clock
in the mezzanine.
It's a date.
Can I leave?
Please.
You should kill
that fucker.
Why the fuck did you make a
deal with that piece of shit?
Wings.
What a
wonderful dream.
Do you come up here a lot?
I come up here if
someone's playing that I like or...
with someone
that I like.
You know, I knew
who you were.
What?
At Sam's.
I'd seen
you before.
Your pictures.
Your albums.
Oh.
You were famous.
Yeah, I was.
Handsome.
Now you're just
being mean.
What happened?
Man, I just couldn't
handle it, you know
I just couldn't handle
the small talk.
You know, the bullshit,
all the politics, that crap.
No, I just
had my music
and my dope,
and in the end it was all about the dope.
And now?
You can talk
to me.
Yeah, I can
talk to you.
You're different.
Yeah.
A couple
of freaks.
Let's just say
we're different.
Hm?
It's five til.
Fifty bucks the asshole don't show.
♫ Been rocking in the morning ♫
♫ Been rocking all night long ♫
♫ Oh, rocking in the morning ♫
Hold on. Hold on.
This stage has
got to move.
We got to rock
this theater.
Mitch is going to be
here tonight
with all them dances
and everything.
We got to pick this tempo up,
change the key
and let's hear it
one time. Come on.
Put your soul in it.
All right, where
is he, huh?
What'd I tell you?
We shoulda broken his goddamn
face when we had the chance.
Now what?
Excuse me.
This is for you.
"Let the girl
do her job.
Use the binoculars."
Here.
Thank you.
No, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where are you going?
Who? I don't...
I don't know.
Where did you get
the note from?
Some guy gave me 20 bucks,
I don't know.
Let go.
Let her go.
Beat it.
Go do your job,
sweetheart, thank you.
This goofy guy
is getting interesting.
What do you see?
Do you wanna
see my wings?
No.
Just ask.
You want to see them,
just ask me.
Okay. I wanna
see your wings.
Oh, my.
What?
Put your coat on,
we're leaving.
Go down there.
They're parked
in lover's lane.
Kill him and bring
her back here.
Okay.
Oh, no,
don't go yet.
And now it is
an angel's song
that makes
the heavens be mute.
Hey, I'll tell
you what.
Why don't you put on
your prettiest dress.
Why?
I wanna take
you out.
To where?
Trust me.
Sit down,
look straight ahead.
I have a little
surprise for you.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
You just wait right here.
Keep your
eyes closed.
Okay.
What, what
are you doing?
I'm right here.
Okay, now?
Okay. Now.
Your first ocean.
It's beautiful.
You know,
you're really good at this.
Mm. You ever
been married?
Long time ago.
What happened?
Did you love her?
I loved her to death.
Hey, I'm sorry, listen...
listen, little lady...
what can I do for you?
Play.
You can play for me.
No. Come on.
You brought your trumpet.
Well that's just to keep
the bottle in.
Oh, come on now, don't take
advantage of me.
All right. I'll play
you one song.
Okay.
This here...
this here is Hazel.
Mm.
This is silly.
Huh?
It's perfect,
isn't it?
It's like
a movie.
This night
like this.
I don't care if the ocean's not real.
If you are.
I don't care.
Huh.
Hey, Lily.
Would you
dance with me?
I'd love to.
Kiss me.
Come on, Nate,
I mean a real kiss.
Her name was,
uh, Annie.
Annie Poole.
She was really special.
She didn't drink,
she didn't...
she didn't get high.
She'd get high so she could be with me.
I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything,
I just...
I just watched her...
I just watched
her fade away.
So how many angels can dance on the head of a pin?
Nate!
Lily, Lily, stay...
Lily, stay there.
Nate, calm
the lady down.
Introduce us.
Fuck you.
Happy Shannon.
It's a pleasure.
You didn't tell
the lady?
Ah, it was probably
an oversight...
Our Nate and
his surprises.
Yes.
You see, yesterday,
over lunch
Nate proposed that we
manage you, he and I.
Your career.
At first I
didn't believe him.
A woman with wings...
I'm sure
you understand.
But after Nate set up the
viewing at the opera yesterday...
Hey, I got
eyes, right?
Listen, listen,
it was my only chance.
I thought I could... figure
it all out and protect you...
Nate traded his
life for yours.
It's as simple
as that.
Not true.
Well, I'm glad
I could help.
No, Lily.
Lily, Lily, Lily.
Hey, let her put some fucking clothes on,
you fucking animal.
Do I have to stand in a lit booth?
You will have
an audience
of one.
Me.
Now that I've
actually seen you
you're a miracle
too rare and precious.
You need to be, like
Nate said, protected.
You should
live with me.
I will see to
your every need.
Please, Lily, please,
just don't go.
I want you to come to this eyes open
willingly, I don't
want a prisoner.
That's a goddamn lie.
It doesn't matter to me.
Lily, please, you don't
have to do this.
You don't have to do anything you don't want to.
I don't want
him touched.
I don't want him touched,
that was part of his deal, right?
Truthfully, that could
be a problem.
We don't want him loose in the world.
He's a talker.
It was part of his deal, right?
Yes, sweetheart,
but think about...
He isn't going
to say anything.
You and me
and women.
Get up!
Why?
- Why?
'Cause I fucking said so!
Get up!
Get the fuck up!
Dream Lounge.
What?
It's Campbell's.
Drink it. Come on.
Oh, God.
Jesus.
I'm gonna get
her back, Harriet.
I will. I'm
gonna get her back.
Sure you will.
It's not exactly my problem.
I roll up here in the middle of the goddamn night
to deliver 20 cases
of champagne.
Oh, God, um...
I... I'm sorry,
you're right
I'm such a fuzz brain,
I just... um, it's next week.
Could l...
could I just pull up and turn around?
Right.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
I love you.
Care to join us?
You get dressed,
and get the fuck outta here.
Hey, man,
she's coming with me.
Okay. I mean, sure.
Angel, do you want Roland to pack your things or...
I'm staying here.
I want you to go.
Just go.
Hey. Hey, we're meant
to be together.
Oh, dear.
Now you're talking
in song titles.
Nate,
you're a man of the world.
Not my world.
But you look as if...
you've lived a life.
So you understand
that everything changes.
Everything ends.
Not this.
Don't help me.
Don't do anything.
I don't want to be
with you, Nate.
Please don't do this.
I want you
to leave.
Stay for the movie,
I don't care.
As long as
I'm with you
nothing happens to him.
And that's our deal.
I promise.
You break it,
I'm gone.
You can't bus tables.
You can't clean toilets.
You can't even
buy a drink in here.
Not here,
nor anywheres else.
My man. Hey.
Mad Malcolm.
Goddamn.
I'm liking the look.
Well, you know.
Well, you know me.
Footloose. Ow.
And fancy free. Like
seeing a ghost, son.
Word on the
street is, uh
Happy ain't too happy
with you these days.
Yeah, well, uh...
I'm still breathing.
Amen to that, brother.
I bet you could use
a gig, though.
Oh, man, I could use
a lot of things.
I'm playing with some fellas at this thing.
It's a party, you dig?
Over at the museum.
You show up...
play a couple of tunes
they pay you like
a rock star.
Oh, museum? Come on, man,
that ain't my thing.
Yeah?
A hundred dollars a night sound like your thing?
Hey. Get some socks,
don't get your feet cold.
All right, baby,
let me know.
Yeah, about...
Hm.
I'm gonna be a little short to the gig...
Think you could, uh,
let me hold twenty?
That is,
you owe the pawn shop twenty, right?
Yeah.
That's a pretty fat
roll you got there.
You think maybe, uh
you know, give a little
to the hat?
Huh?
Now don't let me see
you on the street.
You've always been
there for me.
Skate!
Beautiful.
Thank you.
Mind if I stay?
You can do whatever you want.
I'll stay.
Okay.
My real name
isn't Happy.
Michael.
My real name is Michael.
Mike.
When I was a kid,
apparently I walked around with a big frown
I was a very pissed-off little guy.
Not that there was
much to smile about.
My dad named me Happy.
That was his joke.
I hated it.
I hated him.
But it stuck.
You know, you can't keep
a good nickname down.
I always hated it.
Until now.
Why is that?
Because it fits finally.
I am happy.
Happy, no.
Diamonds, the
angel's stone.
Well, if it's not,
it should be.
I can't take this.
Keep it.
Some day you're
gonna be happy.
Happy, where
are we?
Heaven.
Happy Shannon!
Man of the hour.
Thank you, Anne.
Nice of you to say,
but I really think it's the city's hour
don't you?
But it was your generosity that
made this heavenly show possible.
Well, it's for
the young people
and, uh, I had
inspiration.
Is this a new
Happy Shannon?
Angels, heaven?
Yes, it is.
Yes, it is, um...
Is there ever
been a moment
where you felt that you weren't getting a... a...
Let me ask you about your two federal indictments.
Conspiracy, tampering
with evidence.
No, no.
Come on Sweetie.
Let's warm you up.
Now, wait,
baby, no, no.
Shh.
Yeah.
Last thing on earth
you'll ever see.
Wings.
I'll send Lily
your regards.
Good to see you, Nate.
I'll send Lily
your regards.
My Lily.
The last thing on earth
you'll ever see...
Wake up, Nate!
Get up!
Wake up!
Wake up, Nate!
Get up, goddamn it!
Get up!
Good. Cold,
isn't it?
Stupid motherfucker.
Lily.
Nate.
Nate!
Close.
Come on, get
your things
we're going home.
Don't touch me.
We're what?
I found her.
I raised her.
Happy!
"We're leaving."
I think that's what he
was trying to say.
He's right.
Come on, come on.
Why?
Why? Because...
You're not happy
anymore.
It's open.
It's a fucking
hurricane out there.
Yeah.
Whatever.
You look
like shit.
Got a smoke?
You remember my cousin
Marvin, the cop?
Yeah.
The one who works down
in Newport Division.
Told me that there's gonna
be a raid in a couple hours.
Around five.
Busting a black and tan joint down on Adams.
So?
Well, I'll tell
you so
a lot of stars, hookers, dope,
you know, whatever
Marvin says that there's
a private club upstairs.
Guess whose
club it is.
Come on, Ricky.
Happy's club.
Oh.
You know what
they do in there?
Dope?
Nope.
Cards?
Pussy. What the fuck,
I don't know.
They watch some freak
in a glass box.
Can you believe
that shit?
These stiffs are paying Happy a fortune,
to watch some
naked humpback bitch.
I'm not kidding you.
I mean, fuck!
I'm in the wrong line of work.
Caught you, you bad boy.
What are you
doing here?
Oh, I'm a party gal looking
for a good time.
Ricky filled
me in.
Mm-hm.
Nate, why are you
doing this?
I have got to meet
this girl.
Don't you all worry about this bubbly shit,
I got the good
stuff right here.
Oh, hello.
Have a drink, sweetheart.
Here we go!
We're gonna go inside and
have a good night tonight, huh?
Oh, yeah, yeah. Here
you go, brother.
- Hey, Dan.
- Thank you, Dan.
Please come in.
Check your coat?
Uh...
Thank you.
Beautiful, isn't she?
Nate, what are
we gonna do?
You're gonna fly.
What?
You can do it.
I can't fly, Nate.
Nate, I can't fly!
The wind is blowing just right,
you can fly.
You can do this,
come on.
Nate, it's not gonna work,
it's not gonna work.
Oh, baby.
What?
I love you.
Get over here.
You'll fall like a brick.
I love you.
Nate!
No!