Heil Hitler!
Heil Hitler.
Are we ready, Wallenberg?
Finally!
When?
It's a matter of days.
At Blitzkrieg. And we'll win it.
The Fuehrer has predicted
how long it will last precisely.
Guess!
One year. Six months.
At the most, two months.
We won't even have enough
time to enjoy it.
We'll enjoy the time after the war,
commander.
Gentlemen, cheers to the war,
Germany, the Fuehrer. Sieg Heil.
Wallenberg!
I need at least 20 girls.
It'd be easy for you to find them,
except they can't just be beautiful...
...they also have to be intelligent...
...and especially of indisputable
national socialist belief.
You must comb through all Germany,
through every city, every region.
Sift through the countryside, the
factories, the universities, the offices...
...middle class or blue collar,
housewives or employed women...
...virgins or married ones,
examine them carefully.
But most of all, I repeat, choose them
based on their political belief system.
Heil Hitler!
These three anatomical exhibits
are the best evidence that...
...the racial theory,
the essence of Nazi ideology...
...is based on scientific data
that has been rigorously tested.
Vices and corruption of an inferior race
are passed on...
...from generation to generation
by the chromosomes.
For example, the pigmentation of
this Negro is directly related to...
...the bestiality of his race and to
the impossibility to render it civil.
He died in physical stupor in a fire fight
with the police. Turn him around.
Instead, as we'll see,
this prostitute...
This prostitute, who died
during an attempted abortion...
...is of pure Aryan race.
In spite of the vices of her profession
and the corruption of her life...
...this corpse,
even in the rigidity of death...
...keeps all those typical
characteristics of a superior race.
Are there any questions?
Professor, is it true that
Jesus Christ was son of...
...a Roman prostitute
and a German soldier?
Without a doubt!
There can't be found the slightest trace
of Jewish characteristics in Jesus Christ.
He was blond with blue eyes...
...typical signs of his German origin.
Can you tell me who was the first man
in the world, who realized this fact...
...and revealed it to the human race?
Yes, sir. Our Fuehrer.
Adolf Hitler.
He promised to free us in 6 months from
the Communists and the trade-unions...
...and he kept his promise!
Today Nazi Law is socially the most
advanced one on earth...
...much more than the Fascist Code
in Italy.
And so Italian!
I admire the Italians, mom!
Me, too, my darling.
They are more Mediterranean...
...but very likeable.
They are a bit too exotic,
too colorful for my taste.
But in our party there is
a lack of style as well.
All these brown shirts,
it's such a vulgar color!
And his manners, my dear.
Did you notice how he drinks his tea?
By lifting the little pinky up.
Miss Enkel, you are forgetting, just as
often as my dad and mom forget...
...the National Socialist cannot waste
any time on learning proper etiquette.
They are too busy re-establishing
order, which you can't stand up for...
...because you're too busy controlling
your pinky and choosing your colors.
Don't you realize that you are
a generation of dead people?
Good night!
National Socialism is still a great charm!
That's basically what we were hoping for
when we supported Hitler in 1933, right?
The most important thing is
to be on the side of victory, right?
Well... on history's side, my dear!
Cheers!
"Not for Jews"
The Fuehrer is asking
every one of you the following:
To contribute with your own means
to the military effort...
...for the triumph of
National Socialism of Germany.
It would have been easier
to choose prostitutes...
...but the Fuehrer has put all of his trust
in the political belief system...
...rather than their various techniques.
If there is good will, it'll be
easy to learn the technique fast.
It's like killing.
The first time one may feel remorse...
...be induced to vomit,
even have insomnia.
But by the third time,
one sleeps peacefully.
By the fifth time, one eats a sandwich.
Actually, it gets exciting,
there is a stimulus.
They are just the same for you.
Heil Hitler.
Heil Hitler!
Comrades, take off your uniforms.
You will now undergo a group exam
by the SS of the Third Reich.
This will serve to free you
from your inhibitions...
...to be more flexible in your service.
The best will be submitted to
a second test...
...a more detailed, more specific one.
This test was developed expressly for
you by our Center of Psychosomatics.
Your duty consists in rejecting nothing.
Coitus. Anal coitus.
Masturbation. And fellatio.
Attention comrades!
Have fun, comrades!
Arouse your own fantasy.
The Fuehrer and the Homeland
make use even of this.
- Heil Hitler!
Turn to the right!
March, right, left, right, left...
...two, three, four, right, left,
two, three, four, left, right!
Keep your distance, man!
Right, left, left, two, three, four, left!
Keep your distance!
Stop! Turn to the right!
Stand straight!
Go to the right.
Go on! Let's go!
Take a girl! Get up there!
Go on! Over here!
Marika. She is perfect!
Splendid ability to adapt, I must say!
Olga from Hamburg.
No.
Martha from Danzig.
Rejected!
Margherita from Leipzig.
Approved!
Lena from Düsseldorf.
- What is he?
- A gypsy.
Weak. Mediocre. No sense of race.
- Is she surely Aryan?
- Yes.
What a shame!
Susan from Berlin.
Courageous. Decisive.
Great in battle!
Unshakable belief in National Socialism!
Approved!
Are there any more?
That's all of them, Commander.
I wanted to ask you what
we should do with the rejects.
Girls can be sent to the disciplinary
and re-education centers.
The men...
Dear Klaus, we cannot leave any
mouths behind that can talk.
Except that they can still be
useful in the work camps...
...or to Dr. Savage for his experiments.
Your problem, Klaus...
...is you always want to prove
you have a better idea than anyone.
Let me repeat: Do exactly as I told you!
- Heil!
- Heil Hitler!
Where are you going?
Who are you looking for?
They are all the same!
What scares you the most?
Is it what you eat or what you drink?
Nothing scares me.
The paintings that were hanging here
were degenerate art...
...expressionistic, French stuff...
...and Jewish culture.
Thank you.
I'd prefer a cup of tea.
Hey.
Those decadent habits of
the upper middle class!
No, quite the contrary.
Those from the upper class drink a lot.
I am angry like our Fuehrer.
Your damn middle class pride!
You haven't changed.
You are the same way you were
when you were born.
I believe in National Socialism.
Believing is not enough.
In order to be a real National Socialist...
...you have to know how to
give yourself over, your origins.
You must be able to compromise
all the way.
You have to humble yourself,
in order to be...
...reborn.
Leave.
Goodbye. Nice meeting you.
What do I have to do,
to give myself up?
You must humble yourself.
How?
Take off your underwear.
Hurry up!
Lift your skirt.
Higher.
Higher!
Much higher!
Go over there.
On your knees.
On your knees!
Like a bitch on four legs.
And now come here!
Crawl.
Hurry up. Hurry up! Much faster!
You see, you are nothing.
Just a bitch.
A bitch controlled by me.
I like how you resist.
I like your dignity, your pride.
Go on.
Share yourself with me.
I'll share my power with you!
I disgust you.
Kiss me. Kiss me!
Do something, God! I am not part
of your world, right? Tell me.
You are part of a more precious world.
September 1, 1939
Declaration of war on Poland
Long live Zorro! Heil Hitler!
Heil Hitler!
Max, Klaus, Darling!
Champagne for everyone!
It's on the house.
Champagne, a kiss from Kitty!
From Kitty in person!
And discounts for the soldiers
on leave!
Are you talking about the cripples?
Oh, stop it, please!
Right now we're already dealing with
the first injuries and deaths of this war.
Young blond, romantic men suffering
next to the corpses of their horses...
...or near the wrecks of their tanks!
A heroic image, right, Cliff?
Dino! If there weren't any dead,
there wouldn't be a war...
...and Germany would not be able to
win and dominate the world!
And we wouldn't be here having
champagne and such a good time.
Well said! Cliff is much more fun
than you are, dear Dino.
He makes even more sense.
His America is further away from
Berlin than my city of Naples.
My friends! Girls! Gentlemen!
Play the National anthem immediately!
Otherwise be the conductor.
You are the usual party pooper.
Come over.
Today I stopped rationing champagne.
If you are not interested in my girls,
I think you will be in the champagne.
Forgive me, Kitty, but I can't.
I have tens of thousands of things to do.
I'll send you a car.
And put what inside of it?
Girls or champagne?
Just you.
Thank you, that's flattering, darling.
But it's been a while since I stopped
offering services so that I can get killed.
Well, as I told you, if you come over,
I'll be happy.
If not, you can keep your ass
glued to the chair. Bye!
Klaus?
The Gestapo!
Are you crazy?
You let those Gestapo brings me here
like a criminal, in order to tell me what?
That you have to commit my girls,
because they are foreigners...
...and close my nightclub?
The Party needs my place.
It's not up to me.
And whom the fuck would it be up to?
Himmler, Von Riebentrop?
They are all my clients, except you.
Have they gone crazy, too?
I'll make a call to all of them immediately.
I'll show you who Kitty is!
Do you think this is the right day, Kitty?
The war has just started.
What the fuck does the war
have to do with my work?
Do you want us to wear a chastity belt
just because the war has started?
Do you want my girls to
become little red swastikas?
Wallenberg, you haven't learned
a thing from the Roman Empire.
In order to conquer the World
one must be able to laugh, sing.
Unless you have no intent to close the
brothel, only to open a singing school.
Thank you very much, Kitty.
But our valuable soldiers are already
singing about Germany's greatness.
Don't you think our valuable soldiers...
...would like to spend half an hour
in bed in order to come...
...before they leave?
But of course. But don't forget that
many of them are married.
Married!
The wives are for breast-feeding.
A soldier also wants to shoot his bullets,
not just those the army gives him.
Wallenberg. Sometimes I feel
you don't understand these things.
Is that just because I am not
interested in your whores?
But that's not the point.
There is nothing I can do.
I am sorry, Kitty.
You have to close your nightclub.
What a pain in the ass!
You can ruin me this way!
At least give me some more time.
6 months?
Not even a day. I told you.
The Party needs that place.
But I could help you.
I could provide you with German girls.
You could get a little villa
in the Green Forest.
I thank you, but Kitty has always
been at the center of Berlin...
...and she has always used
an international set of girls.
You are making a big mistake, Kitty.
I would give you skillful, beautiful,
and elegant girls...
...in a private, quiet, discreet area.
Really a high-class place.
I'd even offer you a great price.
And if I refuse?
I don't think that's a good idea.
I really don't think it's a good idea.
You wouldn't just lose your license.
Evidently you still don't know me,
Commander.
If necessary, I'll go to Hitler myself!
Don't move. Nobody move!
They will miss...
They'll miss this panoramic view.
Schatzi, I don't care about
changing my address.
Love is the same everywhere.
Thank Heavens.
I don't have to change my profession,
I don't have to find someone else.
After it's all over, he'll send me to a villa.
I'm such a mess!
What's the matter? Are you crying?
Yes, and I don't know why.
I don't know. I swear I don't know why,
stupid girl I am.
For Heaven's sake, girls, relax!
We are not in the army.
Frankie, bring something to drink.
Something strong. It's freezing in here.
Good girls, very good!
They can certainly listen very well,
Wallenberg, but that's not enough.
They come off as amateurs.
Look at this one.
Good for a trip to the country,
but not for fucking like a pig.
Look at this one!
A child in her arms...
...and an iron in her hands,
and you'll have the perfect homemaker.
They have no passion!
This one is so refined, she even
makes me feel uncomfortable.
Imagine the poor guy
who has to screw her!
She's made for a parlor,
not for a nightclub.
What we need here are girls,
who are soft and warm and...
...most of all always ready
and able to smile in any situation.
Technically they are perfect.
I hope they don't greet their clients
when they enter the room.
I felt so at peace with my other girls.
They could give a dying man a hard on!
All right, loosen them up.
After all that's your job, not mine.
They say you've been extraordinary.
Teach them to become like you.
No, no, no. They are all beautiful,
perfect, too perfect, boring.
They look like printed postcards
the soldiers send to their moms.
I need specialists -
girls who can satisfy any request...
...to fulfill the strangest desires,
the most complex perversions.
The clients of Salon Kitty
have imagination.
If any of them doesn't not live up to
your expectations, let me know.
I'm responsible for them all.
Who would have known that.
We'll have to take up teaching.
Bravo!
Perfect!
And now, Wallenberg,
this is your battle point.
You don't rush and do your work
meticulously.
I want to control the girls' relationships
and collect any information they gather.
To trust is fine; to not trust is better.
Execute my orders to the letter
to the best of your ability.
And, have fun, Wallenberg.
- What's your name?
- Susan, General.
Why do you look at me this way?
You're looking at me as if you know
we have known each other for years.
All Germany knows you, General!
You are the conqueror
and destroyer of Poland.
You can also destroy my body
with these, General.
Don't talk about Poland.
War is a sacred thing - besides,
it's too big to fit in this room.
Put on my boots.
Sure, General!
- Do you know how to sing?
- Yes, General!
Well, then march and sing!
Is that fine, General?
- Take off the pants!
- Of course, General!
And stop calling me General!
Call me Greta.
Do you like it? Can you feel it?
It burns, right?
Tell me that you like it.
Tell me that it burns!
Spread them! Take it, yes, yes!
Take it!
It's of a comrade, a top General of
the Duce, by the name of Cavelucci.
Tell me you like it.
Tell me it burns you!
Tell me it's killing you!
That it's splitting you in half!
Tell me, tell me
it's splitting you in half!
Give it to me! Give it to me!
- Tell me it's killing you, tell me!
- You're killing me! Give it to me!
- Tell me, it's killing you!
- Give it to me!
Tell me!
Tell me, tell me, and tell me!!
Yeah, I like it very much!
I'm the infamous woman! Oh, yes!
Later on!
I like it!
You'll notice in a month or two, if I am
right, the military bases will change.
The British will start telling us that
in Oslo and Copenhagen...
...the language will be English,
my favorite project!
English is a nice language!
A tongue for your huge cunt,
and a beautiful ass.
Klaus! Type the report with
the very same words.
The first copy is for the Chancellery.
The other is for the Reich fuehrer
Himmler - urgent, an absolute priority!
Without checking it first?
Klaus, how many times do I have to
repeat not to be zealous?
I assume total responsibility
for this operation!
Personally!
Honestly, I was skeptical.
Material coming from who knows where!
Girls who are not ready.
They made me spit blood.
I swear that for a few days
I expected a catastrophe!
But now it's sold out every evening!
You can see from the champagne!
Now it can be found only at your place.
I know where to get it.
Riebentrop is my friend.
Oh, well, then it's him
who gets you this, right?!
Are you from the front?
You made love to me
as if you hated me.
No, that's not true.
Would you like to do some more?
Always.
Me, too.
Of course. Of course.
It's your profession.
It's a pity, though, that
you don't know what it means.
Why are you here?
Are you on leave?
Don't you want to talk?
I like to screw.
But if you are not into it...
I am into it, too.
That's not true.
Why do you say such a thing?
It's not true.
But in the end I don't care.
You are here for this, right?
So, open your legs.
With pleasure.
Not that way.
No. Without anger.
With tenderness.
Let yourself go.
Margherita's report.
Hans Reiter,
lieutenant of the Luftwaffe...
...on leave from the front,
not willing to talk.
He only wanted to make love.
He made love more than once.
You're beautiful.
Even if you are just a whore,
making love with you is nice. I like it.
I hate life.
But I have nothing against you.
Are you on leave for a medal?
Yes, so that I can hang it
on my shoulder.
Are you still going to fight?
Maybe I'm not a good soldier.
When do you have to leave?
Soon. In 10 days.
That's an eternity for making love.
Yes, an eternity that ends too soon.
If I could take you with me, so that
I can screw you anytime I want to...
It's really nice with you.
You're exaggerating.
Do you regret not coming along?
No. It's just that it's unfair
when you are exaggerating.
Would you regret it, if I fell in love
with you... just a little bit?
Do you think it's ridiculous?
Love is a word used by a man and
a woman spending time in bed together.
Sure, sure, sure.
Hurry, hurry, over here!
Get into the shelter!
Where is the shelter?!
Over here! Hurry up!
To the shelter!
Hurry, hurry, and hurry.
Over here!
Congratulations!
Congratulations to myself
for having found you.
I have a gift for you
before I return to the battle.
I saw light underneath the door.
Aren't you afraid?
The British will never bomb Berlin.
Marshall Behring himself told us so.
That's not a good reason for
getting drunk completely naked.
- Would you like to drink with us?
- With pleasure.
- Today is a very important anniversary.
- Of what?
It's exactly a week now
Margherita and I know each other.
I wish you hundreds of these days!
The same to you, Margherita.
I don't like anniversaries.
I only like to drink champagne...
...with him, or maybe
not even with him.
I love champagne, and that's all
there is to it.
Too many good wishes are
a bad omen.