High school.
Look familiar? Yeah.
Being a teenager,
it can be rough,
I'm not gonna
lie to you.
But if you're a teenager,
and the world doesn't fit you,
you're totally hosed!
# Oh, Mr. Pit...
Oh, Mr. Pit...
# Mr. Pitiful
# Who let you down?
Who let you down?
And the harder
you try to fit in,
the more awkward it gets.
# Oh, Mr. Pit...
Oh, Mr. Pit...
# Mr. Pitiful
# Who let you down?
Look at this poor guy.
Brutal!
# Who let you down?
Who let you down? #
But if you think
being a big, awkward teenager
is about the worst thing
that can happen to you,
try being
a 200-pound teenage dog
with a radar dish
wrapped around your neck!
Oh, yeah, that'll make me
real popular.
Luckily, they're easy
to take off. Watch this.
Marmaduke!
Told you!
Where are you?
Hold your horses.
I'm Marmaduke, by the way.
I get yelled at a lot.
Come on, let's meet the fam.
The two-leggers.
You're gonna love them.
Here I come!
This little Padawan here
is Brian.
Like most kids his age,
he loves to hang out with me.
Come on, buddy.
I can't see!
Yeah, I'm pretty busy myself.
I'll catch you later.
And this social
butterfly here is Barbara.
She loves to
play ball with me.
Okay, Barb,
you throw and I catch.
He can be like that.
Not like that.
Is somebody cooking?
Food!
Debbie's pretty cool,
and my main food hook-up.
She slips me a steak here,
some turkey there.
Which is why I think she doesn't
even care when I help myself.
Come to daddy.
Ahhh! Hot cheese!
Oh, hot cheese!
Marmaduke!
The little one's Sarah.
How cute is she?
And she's my biggest fan.
You know, it's important for
them to get exercise at this age,
so I try to take her
for a walk every day.
She's got a great laugh,
doesn't she?
Then there's
my owner, Phil.
He's a marketing guy for
a local pet food company.
I call him
Doctor No sometimes,
'cause it's nothing
but rules with him.
No slobbering.
No barking.
No tackling the mailman.
Here, let's see if he says no
to this awesome hole I'm digging.
Marmaduke, no!
See? Doctor No
in the house.
Why don't you just
give it a chance?
I will find China!
What you're doing
is cruel and unusual.
I hate water.
Come on. Sit.
Look, everybody's got a weakness. Sit.
Mine's water. It's my kryptonite. Sit.
Not sitting in this tub.
Sit, sit, sit.
Sit, Marmaduke!
What can I say? I'm
a sucker for the kid.
Bye-bye.
Phil hates that.
Hey, Sarah,
where you going?
Stay.
There's nothing good about
getting a bath, except for this!
Come on, Phil!
Not again.
Marmaduke!
Let's go!
I like to give Phil
a little exercise, too.
He's cooped up in the office
all day. Come on, Phil.
That's the spirit!
Get back here!
Over here!
Come here, through here,
Phil! I'm over here!
Yeah, come on!
Not this time...
You don't grab a tiger
by the tail!
Marmaduke!
Someone call the ASPCA!
We got a crazy dog
on the loose!
Freedom!
Hey, Dad.
What are you doing?
Would it kill them
to install a new dog door?
I was two months old
when they got this.
I guess I had more pull before
the growth spurt. Cue flashback.
Oh, he's so cute!
See? Insanely cute.
Look at that lovable
little Marma-pup.
Come here, you!
But when you grow up into
this, I get it. Not pretty.
I'd ignore me, too.
Get back here!
Hey, I'm talking here!
Anyway, I try not to
hold things against Phil.
After all,
he's only human.
That's why I make it a point
to never go to bed hungry.
Let's see
what we've got.
Sausage from
last week's barbecue,
gonna need to let that
breathe a few days.
This is our shot.
California, the big leagues.
In the big leagues, they take
steroids and cheat with supermodels.
It's a marketing job with
an organic pet food company.
I think we'll be okay.
Pepperoni pizza.
Phil's loafer? No, I'll
save it for dessert.
And that, I have no idea what that is.
Aren't we okay
in Kansas?
Is that what we wanna be? Just okay?
Coming in for a landing.
I wanna give you and the
kids the life you deserve.
I want a bigger house
with a bedroom that doesn't
smell like a meat-locker.
This is our shot.
Well, if this is our shot,
then we should take it.
But you have to
tell the kids.
Done.
Give me that.
Oh! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, I wasn't done
with that!
You don't have to worry, I've
got my supermodel right here.
Wow!
Wait for it...
Marmaduke!
What did you eat?
I know it's juvenile,
but it's all I've got.
So, there you have it.
Day in the life of
old Marmaduke, here.
It's really bad!
Guys, I am sorry.
That was a little much,
even for me.
Bad Marmaduke.
All right, enough.
Lights out.
Waffles, waffles,
waffles, waffles, waffles!
Yes!
Saturday morning waffles!
Got to love the Debster!
Take it easy, man!
A waffle is to be
savored, not inhaled!
Hey, this is my step-bro,
Carlos, by the way.
Say hey, Carlos.
Hey, Carlos.
He's pretty cool
for a cat, which helps,
since he's basically
my only friend.
You ready for
a bombshell?
Lay it on me.
Phil just told everybody
he got a new job.
We're moving
to the O.C.!
Shut up! Really?
No lie! I was so shocked,
I hacked that thing up.
Carlos, that's gross!
I know it's gonna take
time to adjust, honey,
but you'll make so many
new friends there.
I think it sounds
kind of cool.
What do you care? All you
do is play video games.
This is so unfair!
I got to say,
I'm with Barbara on this one.
You know how many bones
I buried in the backyard?
Guys, this is a
once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
We'll have a big new house
with a pool and a company car.
Pets are always
the last to find out!
I don't even know
where the O.C.'s at!
Okay, what's the deal?
Is it something I said?
Something you weren't
supposed to say.
Does anyone even own
a pet in this place?
I haven't seen
a single dog so far.
It's kind of hard to forgive
you if you don't mean it...
Oh! She's fine.
Okay, so far, all I've
learned about The O.C. is that
no one has a pet and Seth,
here, is a total drama queen.
You're the biggest
drama queen, amigo.
Me?
That's you, Carlos.
You're, like, 200 pounds
of drama, with a red collar!
Oh, really?
This conversation is over.
No, no, no!
Ejector seat.
Never fails.
And so,
moving day arrived.
And there was
a feeling of hope
and excitement for
the whole family.
Even Barbara was trying
to lend a hand.
That's mine...
Carlos and I would
have pitched in, too,
but we were being
shipped air freight and on lockdown!
Hey, let me out of here.
I'm not an animal!
Oh, yeah, I am.
Look what I got.
Debbie's meatballs!
That's my man, Phil!
There you go.
Looking out
for his own.
I don't know, Carlos.
Something's fishy here.
It's Debbie's
meatballs, man. Don't question it!
Oh! I know I shouldn't eat
it, but I can't help it.
Good boy! Good boy!
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
I feel a little funny.
This is
a horrible mistake.
I requested
executive class!
I think Phil put something
in our meatballs!
Have you ever
looked at your paws?
I mean,
really looked at them?
Yeah, yeah. I followed
you on many adventures.
But into the great unknown
mystery, I will go first, amigo.
Timber!
Down and out.
# California, here we come
# Right back
where we started from
# California!
# California! #
Wake up! I'm up, I'm up!
Come on, Phil, let's do it!
Same dog, different floor.
Yes! New city,
new house, new smells!
Good morning,
Orange County!
Oh, yeah.
Hang on a second. Did you
check out that doggie door?
It fits! It fits!
Oh! Look at this.
It's got an ocean view!
And a pool!
This grass is so green!
And this, by far, the nicest
bathroom I've ever had.
Speaking of which,
a little privacy, please.
Oh, yeah, brown collar. Good,
that'll bring out my eyes.
Come on, Phil, let's go!
Is that weird that your boss
wants to meet you at the dog park?
That's how
they roll in Cali.
Don's a bit eccentric, but that's
what makes him so successful.
Come on, Phil, shake a leg! Easy, buddy!
Wait.
Pink?
Fuchsia. That's how
they roll in Cali.
Come on,
we're burning daylight.
Let's do it! Don't worry
about me, I'll just be here
unpacking a thousand boxes.
Freedom!
I promise I'll be
home early to help!
Let's go!
That's the company car?
# California
# knows how to party
# In the city of L.A.
We are
living the dream, Phil!
# We keep it rockin'! #
Listen, big guy.
Things are gonna work a little
different out here. Give me those.
Hey, that's part
of my look!
We need to impress
my new boss.
I need you to be a good
boy, a very good boy.
Basically,
the opposite of you.
Hi. Morning!
Phil's got nothing to worry
about. Why? Twelve simple words.
I've got a chance to completely
re-invent myself and finally fit in.
In short, I've got
a new leash on life.
Pun intended.
Wow, this is
Phil's office?
New life, here I come.
Time to bring my A-game.
Think small, play it
cool, get your bark on.
Just relax.
Hey, how's it going?
Beautiful day, huh?
Oh, hey, cool sweater!
I'm sweating like a dog.
Come on, big M,
keep it together.
Just focus. Whoa!
What was that? Whoa!
Cool it!
Hey, wait for me.
Marmaduke, heel!
Phil, wait, wait,
check it out!
Winslow, here.
Oh, Mr. Twombly,
there you are.
It's great to
see you again.
Who do we have here?
Come on, buddy!
Yeah! What's his name?
This is Marmaduke.
Marmaduke!
Well, you are one handsome
Great Dane, you know that?
I'm starting to
like this guy!
You've got yourself a beautiful
best friend there, Phil.
Thank you! Marmaduke and I,
we're like two peas in a pod.
Hmm.
Who's licking butt now?
Interesting.
I'm picking up something
else here, also.
Absolutely not a purebred.
Really?
I'm sensing a little
English Mastiff.
Hey, watch it!
Your guess is
as good as mine.
You don't know your own
best friend, Phil?
Sure. Uh...
I love dogs.
I can tell a lot about a man
by the way he treats his dog.
That's why I like
working out here.
I can measure, first-hand,
who I'm dealing with.
Watch it, Phil.
He can smell your fear.
Plus, you get all this fresh
air for out-of-the-box thinking.
And, most importantly, I get to
spend time with my little girl.
Jezebel.
Oh!
Hello, Cali!
Look at that fur!
Right. Take off your
shoes and let's walk.
You don't wear
shoes out here?
Come on, Phil.
Channel your inner canine.
Get some earth
between your toes.
It's not the earth
I'm worried about.
Stay out of trouble.
Good luck, Phil.
You're gonna need it.
Jezebel! Whoa!
Hey, whoa, whoa.
Watch it!
Bakersfield.
What the...
He's definitely Midwest.
Boston?
I'm gonna say Kansas.
How did you know?
It's a gift.
What's your handle, newbie?
My name's Marmaduke.
Yikes!
Immediately moving on.
Meet the gang.
The egghead, here,
is Raisin.
Marmaduke.
A unique synthesis
of "marma",
the scientific name for
the jumping spider family...
Oh! Oh!
I hate spiders.
...and the Duke
of Marlborough,
the 17th-century
English statesman.
And the ultra-confident Chinese
Crested over here is Giuseppe.
Before you ask, yes, I'm a real
dog. No, I'm not a chew toy.
And I just get a little nervous
sometimes because we live in California.
This is the land
of the puma!
There are no pumas
in Southern California.
Pumas!
They come out of nowhere.
I'm Mazie, by the way.
Good to meet you guys.
Hey, you come here a lot?
It's the dog park, man. It's
like high school for dogs,
which means there's a
few packs to know about.
First,
you got your jocks.
Nice catch, Brad.
The only muscle they
don't use is their brain.
O- M-G, Brad is H-O-T!
They mostly date Afghans.
Who actually have no brain.
Oh! Frisbee!
Then you got
your drama geeks.
We're innocent.
Don't shoot!
Bang, bang.
And over here,
your mushroom heads.
Somebody stop this thing,
man. I got to get off, bro!
Then there's your out-and-out
juvenile delinquents.
Come on! Let's go, go!
Word to the wise,
avoid the water bowls here.
Oh, come on! Again?
So far, I'm not seeing
anyone I'd really fit in with.
Well, if you think you got the
game, you could roll with our crew.
Oh, yeah?
Who's your crew?
Mutts!
Weird!
Who are those guys?
The pedigrees,
a.k.a. trouble.
They're
rich, and they're spoiled
and they act like their fleas
don't bite. It's ridiculous!
The little land shrimps
are Thunder and Lightning.
Dog Vader over there
is the man himself, Bosco.
Alpha male
who runs the park.
He's the toughest
dog around.
Him? He
doesn't look that tough.
His girlfriend over there
is Miss Perfect, Jezebel.
And he's super-jealous,
so stay away from her
or he'll turn you into...
Dog food.
Hello, losers.
Speak of the devil.
So, I see you got
a new mutt friend.
Okay, that's wet.
Shut up, Thunder.
What's his name?
Uh... Marmaduke. Mama-what?
Well, well. My little fireplug said
you were salivating on my girlfriend.
No, no. I remember, somebody
walked by eating beef jerky.
Let me explain something.
This is my park,
and these are my rules.
You look at my girlfriend
again, and you're dead.
You come near her,
you're dead.
You talk to her,
and you're...
Dead.
We're dead.
Yeah, we're dead!
He ain't nothing, watch.
Come on, you
wanna go? You wanna go?
No! No! No, no, no.
Didn't think so.
Welcome to the O.C., mutt.
Yeah,
stand clear, Horsie.
See you at the
party tonight, not!
Can I open
my eyes now?
Don't listen
to that guy.
Maybe listen to the
part about staying away
from his girlfriend
or he'll kill you.
What party was he
talking about?
Nothing, just a bunch of snobs scratching
themselves under the yacht club pier.
We're having our
own party tonight.
It's gonna be a classic O.C.
rager, you should totally come.
Not sure if I can get out, but I'll try.
Great, it's gonna be
a really good party!
If you know what a party's like,
it's gonna be better than that.
Tell them you know me!
You'll get right in.
Thanks, Giuseppe!
Good first day,
Marmaduke.
You played it cool. And I think I
impressed a lot of dogs here today.
Now, that is
a pretty good...
Bee! Ahhh!
A bee!
Get off of me now!
Look out!
Phil, help me!
Bark Organics dominates
the California market.
With our product
recognition and quality,
we're in a position
to crush the competition.
So, Dorothy, why have I called
you all the way from Kansas?
Why have I been through six
marketing directors in the last year?
Because I want
Bark Organics
on the shelves in every
PETCO in the country.
Bee!
I can't see! Bee!
I won't
let you down, sir.
We'll see.
Watch out!
Coming through!
Sorry!
Are you okay?
Was that your dog?
I didn't get a good look.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine!
It takes a lot
more than that...
Bee!
That dog!
Phil, help!
Phil, get rid of him!
Help me!
Why do bees hate me?
What a gargantuan spaz!
Yeah, but kind of funny.
Hmm.
I heard a vicious rumor that
you're, like, from Kansas?
Yeah. Are those,
like, real dogs?
The canine accessory
is so essential.
We are not accessories.
Hey, man,
in my country, I was a lawyer.
I've been in this
purse so long, I can't feel my legs.
Bodie is
so gorgeous!
Did he just
look at me?
As if!
Yeah, you're probably right. He
probably wasn't looking at me.
Hey, honey!
Oh, my God!
Is that thing yours?
No, it's somebody
else's dog. Not mine.
Hey, Barb!
Who are your friends?
Phil! That was not cool!
Sorry, Barb.
Right. Regional
market share first...
Yeah, yeah.
Come on, Phil, get off the
phone. Brian's going to bed.
Night, Dad.
Hey, Brian, wait up.
Sounds good. We'll talk
tomorrow. Chill, Marmaduke.
Great news!
I ran into another
dad at the dog park,
and guess what
he's in charge of?
I signed you up!
Oh. Soccer sounds...
Great, right?
Sure, yeah.
Man, you're
gonna love it.
Okay. Good night, Dad.
Good night, buddy.
Phil, he's not gonna love it. He's
gonna hate it, you knucklehead!
Come on!
I really miss
you guys, too.
But I did see this
cute surfer kid today.
You need anything, honey?
A little privacy, and a
one-way ticket back to Kansas.
Good night.
Come on, Phil. It's like
you're not listening to them.
# Lullaby, lullaby
# All the humans
are sleeping #
Ladies, please!
Carlos, be quiet!
Your eyes are
getting sleepy.
So sleepy.
Good night, Phil.
# Hey, yo, when I wake up
moaning, yawning
# I put up my hands
# Thank the Lord
for what I got
# and never stop my plans
# Giving all for the goals
# Got to keep it up,
never let my head drop
# Make me a home on my own
# Better make the bed rock #
I'm a monster!
I am a tiny monster.
I'm doing the spin!
This is an O.C. rager?
You made it, great!
Come watch Giuseppe
rip it up!
Check this out!
One leg, one leg...
Hey, Marmaduke!
If you're hungry or thirsty,
the trash can's out back.
And the toilet's in there.
Cool, thanks!
Did that cow just oink?
Meet Mazie's cow.
The factory made a mistake.
It's pretty ridiculous.
Cow that oinks.
I think it's cool!
New record!
Holler at your boy!
Marmaduke, you're up!
No, that's
cool. I'll just watch.
Don't be a wiener dog! Just dance
along to the flashing arrows!
I'd love to, but seriously,
guys, I've got four left paws.
Duke!
Duke! Duke! Duke!
All right, all right,
twist my paw. Duke! Duke!
Atta boy!
Okay, let's see.
This can't be that hard.
Right paw, white arrow.
Left paw, blue arrow.
No, no, left paw,
green arrow.
There we go!
On second thoughts, maybe
this wasn't such a good idea.
Hang on,
give him a chance.
You can do this, Marmy.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, concentrate!
Ease into it.
Are we insured?
No one puts Dukey
in a corner!
The Duke's got
some moves!
You ain't seen nothing yet!
Time to get funky!
He's better than me,
isn't he?
In a way, yes.
Three-sixty
on the big dog!
Pinwheel time!
Time to go old-school!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I'm sorry. I'm really
sorry, guys. My bad.
No sweat. I needed
to get a Wii, anyway.
There goes Giuseppe's
entire social life.
That was the only thing
I wasn't afraid of.
You know, not that I'm not
having fun, because I totally am,
what do you guys think about going to
the yacht club party, see what's up?
Are you crazy?
Or we could just go to the zoo,
and jump into the puma cage!
Come on, it'll be fun!
Question.
Are we gonna spend the rest of our
lives hiding underneath the porch
with the little pups?
Or are we gonna get out in
the yard with the big dogs?
But we're not big dogs,
we're tiny dogs!
That phrase was made
for dogs like you!
You do realize
it's Bosco's party.
Yeah, Bosco, Schmosco!
He's all bark, no bite.
Okay. Some dogs just have
to learn the hard way.
I smell rain, and I
did not dress for rain.
I'm telling you guys,
without fur,
it's like tiny bullets
from the sky.
It's him!
Who is that?
Chupadogra.
Chupadogra?
They say he was
the ultimate alpha dog.
But then he went insane from
rabies and ate his owner.
He also sleeps on a giant
pile of his victims' bones.
Can we go now, before
I become an appetizer?
Let's go.
I can't believe
we survived Chupadogra!
And now
he knows your scent.
Why would you
say that?
You sure you
wanna do this?
Oh, yeah.
You bet I do.
Guys, I'm telling you,
the tide is rising!
Twenty-four,
come on, you can do it.
Twenty-five!
Man! Now, this party
is off the leash!
What are they doing
to that cat?
What pedigrees do best.
Humiliate the innocent.
Hey, wait, what are you
doing? Don't go over there!
Come on, let's get
our bark on. Oh, oh...
Oh, sorry.
I'll go this way.
No problem. Sorry.
This unfortunately
happens to me all the time.
Me, too.
Oh, brother!
Great, we're getting
mad-dogged. Let's bail!
Well, well, well. If it
isn't the dog and pony show.
Did the circus give
you guys the day off?
We're just leaving Bosco,
back off.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What's
the hurry? You just got here.
You know, it's funny,
with ears like that
I would have thought
you heard me tell you
to stay away
from my girlfriend.
He told him. You told
him, like, 12 times...
Zip it!
Zipped!
Being a pedigree means
you're exceptional.
We're all bred
for a purpose
and have gifts you could
never dream of having.
Stuart's an expert tracker.
Shasta is
a master sled dog.
Ferdinand is fluent in six
languages, including gopher.
And I'm the reigning
SoCal surf champ.
Are you good
at anything? Huh?
Um... Uh...
Sit!
You are
good at something!
Lay down. Lay down!
That's it.
Oh, no!
This is bad, isn't it?
Yes, it's very bad.
I don't care how freakishly
large you are, Donkey Boy.
We all know that inside you're
just a scared little pup!
Did I say you could
get up? No, no. Please!
Did I say you could get up? I'm sorry!
No mercy, boss.
Put him in
a doggie bag!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
I don't
wanna fight you.
Bosco, stop!
Relax, baby! We're
just horsing around.
No, you're not.
You're being a bully.
I'm sorry, he gets this way when
he drinks too much drain-pipe water.
He gets that way
because he's a jerk.
You watch yourself, tomboy.
Come on,
we're out of here.
Come on, baby, are you gonna
spend time with them or with me?
It's a party,
let's have fun!
See you later, when there's not
any girls around to save you.
Mutt.
Bosco's right about everything.
I'm just a Gigantor freak.
Wasn't bred for anything,
but getting in the way.
You know, if I had a bone
for every time someone said,
"Put a saddle on that thing!"
or, "How's the weather up there?"
I'd be a bone-illionaire!
Just once in my life, I'd
like to fit in, you know?
Look, I know what it's
like to be an outsider.
Okay? I was a rescue dog.
Nobody wanted me.
But you're better than any of
those guys, and I can prove it.
I can make you into
the dog you wanna be.
Really? Why would
you do that for me?
Because you're my friend.
Wait, what time is it?
Oh, man, Phil's gonna
get up soon. I got to go!
I'll see you later!
You're welcome.
I just made it.
I am beat.
I am so tired.
I'm exhausted.
Oh! Phil,
hit the snooze!
Time for work,
big guy.
Oh, Phil,
you're killing me.
Winslow, Twombly.
I need that new campaign and I need
it yesterday. So what do you got?
Yeah. I got some
great ideas percolating,
I just need a little
time to flesh them out.
See, you got nothing.
No, you can count on me.
It's gonna be a home run.
It better be.
Yeah, bye.
I got nothing.
Bee! Bee! Phil, get him!
Marmaduke, relax!
Phil, I hate bees!
Get back.
Bee! Bee!
He's gonna sting us!
He's gonna sting me and give me
rabies! Phil, Phil, get rid of him!
Marmaduke, chill, relax.
They're just surfers.
Marmaduke,
you're a genius!
I am?
A surf competition
for dogs?
Picture this. Man's best
friend surfing towards shore,
throngs of owners
cheering them on.
How's that gonna sell organic
dog food to the heartland?
Eleven o'clock, Phil.
Listen, if you wanna sell to
the Midwest, I'll tell you how.
Be true to
who you are.
Bark Organics was made in
Southern California, embrace that.
Bring the iconic spirit
of the West Coast
to every dog owner
across the country.
I don't know.
I hired you to create an
identity for this company
and you're telling me
to be myself?
You know, we only have
one shot with PETCO.
I know.
But you got to
trust me on this.
All right.
One shot.
Make it happen.
Yes!
Okay, mutt-makeover
begins now.
First things first.
All right,
I'm all ears, literally.
Pig Cow is yours.
Check, Pig Cow's mine. Why?
He's a real confidence
booster. Of course he is.
You just chew on him
when you get nervous.
Noted and filed.
Next up,
let's smell that breath.
Whoa!
Oh, buddy!
Really, that bad?
That needs work. Okay, pedigrees
have dental hygienists, all right?
So garbage breath
is not gonna cut it.
Stay out of trash cans and
eat more mint-based items.
Okay, less trash,
more mint.
And stand up proud.
Your ancestors sat
at the foot of kings, man.
Yeah.
Let's put the "Great"
back in "Dane" here.
Yeah, like this?
Um...
You know, just maybe keep your
ears up, too, while we're at it.
Ears up. Like this?
Yeah, that looks fine.
Just out of curiosity,
do you think any of this
stuff would work with girls?
Did you
have anyone in mind?
Not specifically, just
thinking out loud here.
Oh!
Right, right, okay. No
one specific. That's good.
Okay...
Listen up, Barkanova.
If it were me, I'd want him
to take me to the junkyard.
It's really
romantic there at night.
There'd be a blanket
with some treats spread out,
music from an old car
radio playing softly.
Yeah, and lots of great
old stuff to pee on, right?
Oh! You've got
so much to learn.
Here's the deal.
Girls want romance.
You know? Mystery.
Wow.
What?
You know, I never really noticed
before, but you have really pretty...
Fire truck!
Hey, buddy,
we're talking here.
Fire truck!
Heel!
Oh, sorry.
Where were we?
Uh... You said I
have really pretty...
Got to go, buddy.
Work to do.
No! Wait, Phil,
no, not now!
Hey, where are you going?
Phil, I need this.
Come on. Let's go.
"Really pretty" what?
What?
Carlos, let
me ask you something.
Is my breath
really that bad?
A tube of toothpaste is a good start,
but you're gonna
need more than that.
Dude, watch it!
Just gave myself
a tongue-bath.
Sorry.
How's my breath now?
Refreshingly minty.
Who am I kidding? Minty
breath, better posture.
This stuff's
never gonna work.
These guys have real skills.
I could never speak gopher.
Why would you want
to talk to gophers?
Forget it.
Breaking into
new cliques is tough
and breaking into bird cages
is even tougher.
I just don't get it.
I'm a dog and you're a
cat, we get along great.
That's because
you're my hermano.
If we weren't related, I'd
scratch both your eyes out!
Don't make me laugh.
You could never take me.
I'd cream your
furry little butt...
Carlos, you're a genius.
What is he doing?
Say, does anybody
smell that?
I smell a cat
and I hate cats.
Cat! There's
no cat here.
I said,
"I smell a cat."
Where am I? Hey boss, there is a cat!
No, no, no.
This one's mine, fellas.
Is this a dog park?
I must be horribly lost.
Oh, yeah,
you must be lost, cat,
because this park
is for dogs only.
I got the tail!
You said there'd
only be a few dogs.
It's a dog park. What
do you want me to do?
The sun's out,
it's crowded today.
This is gonna
cost you, big time!
Fight! Fight!
Whoa!
What a crowd!
Who let the dogs out?
This doesn't
look good!
Please don't
hurt me, Mister.
I'm just a poor,
incredibly attractive,
ultra-intelligent cat,
who has lost his way.
You're gonna need all nine lives
after this beat-down, pussycat.
You are the biggest, baddest
dog I have ever seen in my life.
You also seem very
cool and confident.
You're right
about all of that,
you little
Fancy-Feast-eating freak!
Please! Spare my life!
Spare this.
Come on, sell it, man.
Sell it.
Really? Okay.
Left jab, left jab,
work the body.
Get back here, you
good-for-nothing little fur-ball!
I only
weigh six pounds.
This officially
hurts now. Stop!
No, no, keep going, keep
going. I think it's working.
Maybe we can find
a happy medium?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, everybody,
watch this!
No, no, no!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Dizzy!
Hairball.
What's the matter, Bigglesworth?
Dog got your tongue?
Yeah, whatever, man.
Hope you got
what you wanted.
That was hilarious, Marmadonk!
Yeah, you're not
as good as Bosco,
but you took that
fleabag to school!
Oh, please, it was a cat.
It's not like he killed it.
You've got a keen
sense of smell.
Oh. Well, thanks.
It must be the large nostrils.
I have to go, but maybe
I'll see you around.
Cool! I'd like that.
Jezebel,
let's go. Now!
You know, I have a
pretty good nose myself
and when I'm around you
I smell potential,
with a hint of
something minty.
I like it.
Let's go!
It worked!
She talked to me!
What are you doing? That's
not what we talked about!
Who cares?
She liked my minty breath!
Welcome to the First Annual Bark
Organics Dog Surfing Competition.
Dogs and owners, make your
way to the shore. Cowabarka!
Hey, I know you.
You go to Marshall, right?
The new girl.
That's me.
You ever not
on that thing?
I'm Bodie.
I know. I mean...
Yeah, I'm Barbara.
Is that your dog?
No, no, no.
That's my dad's dog.
Huh. That's too bad.
He's way better than
those lame purse dogs.
Well, I did kind of adopt him
as my own, though.
The dog, not my dad.
Yeah, Marmaduke and I
are super close.
My friend's having a party
next weekend. You should come.
Sure, I'd love to.
Competition's starting.
Beat it, Hasselhoff.
Dad,
what are you doing?
You're way too young, and I'm way
too busy to talk about this right now.
And, just put
some clothes on.
Can I get you
anything, Deb?
He's cute!
Hey, Marmaduke,
can you keep a secret?
Probably.
I've been telling Dad
I'm going to soccer practice,
but I've actually been
hanging out at the skate park.
I think that
sounds cool, Brian.
But you got to
tell your dad.
I don't even
like soccer.
I guess I just don't know
how to tell him the truth.
I hear you, bro,
but just hang in there.
I wish you could talk.
And I wish you could
understand me.
Come on, Marmaduke!
Hey, Brian, you okay?
Yeah.
What do you say we kick
that ball around later?
No, I'm good.
Come on, buddy.
Wait! Phil! Phil!
Hold on, Phil. Brian's
got something to tell you.
It is a beautiful day here in
Southern California for dog surfing.
Please, put your paws together
for our canine competitors!
Aha! And here's our marketing
director, Phil Winslow.
Phil, this is David King,
Jessica Colestat from PETCO.
Pleased to meet you.
I hope you're ready for a
mind-blowing canine surf experience.
Wow! Can't wait to see
this big guy out on the waves!
No, no, no.
Phil and Marmaduke are one
month removed from Kansas.
I don't think they're ready to hang 10.
Well, that's too bad. That
would've been hysterical.
Yeah!
No, you're right!
That would be hysterical! Phil?
Phil, come on, they're
just kidding. Say no!
Marmaduke's dying
to hang 20.
Dying to.
Oh! We're dead!
No, no, no. Phil, no!
Let's go, buddy.
Come on.
It's just water.
No. Way too big and
too wet! Cold, cold!
That's my competition?
This ought to be fun.
Freezing, freezing!
No! Marmaduke!
Cold, cold!
Come on,
get back here. Heel!
Happy thoughts,
happy thoughts.
I'm running through a meadow.
I'm peeing on everything.
You don't stand
a chance, Shamu.
I own these waves.
Good luck to you, too.
It's okay, Marmaduke.
Nothing bad's gonna happen.
Something bad's gonna happen,
Phil. Payback's gonna hurt.
Okay, stay.
It's okay.
Ladies and gentlemen, take
a look, on the horizon,
a massive,
rogue wave approaches!
You got to be kidding!
Time to dazzle.
It's all you, buddy.
Phil! No, no, what are
you doing? Phil, help me.
Phil, no!
Good luck!
Somebody get me off this
thing! What am I doing?
Out of my way, poser! Look out!
I've got
the right of way!
Oh, boy!
Look out!
Phil, help me!
Look at this!
It's Marmaduke!
Look at the perfect position
here, Marmaduke in the barrel.
Yeah!
Get me off this thing!
Help! Marmy don't surf!
He doesn't look like
he's gonna make it.
Where is he?
I don't know.
Oh, man,
I'm gonna die!
No, you're not.
Get a hold of yourself!
Grip it and rip it!
Geronimo!
There he is!
Take a look at this!
He throws a big air!
What a crazy dog!
Look out! Look out!
And the Duke shreds!
This dog rules! Marmaduke!
You did it, buddy!
Oh! Get me out of here!
That's my dog! Get this seaweed off me!
It burns! It burns!
Debbie, help!
Yeah!
That was awesome!
Really?
That was off the hook! The
Duke has arrived, y'all!
It was?
You totally
shredded, dude!
I shredded?
That was way better
than Bosco, dude!
Marmaduke shreds!
All right, here it is.
The overall surf champion...
You think it was funny dropping in
on my wave like that, Marma-puke?
I didn't do
anything, Bosco!
Let it go,
it was an accident.
And the trophy
goes to...
This better be me.
Whoa! We have an upset.
The trophy goes to Phil
Winslow and Marmaduke!
What?
Phil, did we really win?
I'm gonna tear
you apart, mutt.
I didn't do anything!
Somebody put a leash
on this dog!
Marmaduke!
Help!
Get back here, mutt!
Whoa, whoa!
Get back here,
you poser!
I don't even
like surfing!
Stop running,
you coward.
I'm gonna make you pay.
I am gonna make you pay!
Come on, Duke,
you can take him.
This ends right here,
right now.
You know what? You're right,
Bosco. This does end here.
Ow! My leg's cramping!
Ow! Ow!
Time out, time out!
No, bad dog!
Heel.
I'm so sorry
about this.
Get your dog under
control, you understand?
Come on, folks, I'm so
sorry. Come on. Come this way.
Hey, what's the new surf
champ doing out here all alone?
Hey. I'm just kind of here,
taking a break from the old family.
Well, I guess some people just
can't handle it when you're top dog.
Really?
It's getting
a little cold out.
Wait, what about Bosco?
Forget about him.
There's a new dog in town.
And his name
is Marmaduke.
Hey, that's my name!
That's my name!
Marmaduke!
Say it loud,
say it proud!
# The moon was shining
on the lake at night
# The Slayer T-shirt
fit the scene just right
# Smeared mascara, I looked
into your eyes I saw a light #
Fire truck!
Hi! Phil Winslow.
Anton, master of
the Top Dog method.
I'm supposed to listen
to a guy named Anton?
Top dog him, Phil.
Top dog him.
Marmaduke!
Guys, what's going on?
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Out of the car!
Let's go.
Oh...
Pump your fists triumphantly,
and say it to the world,
"I'm top dog!"
Rubber bone!
I'm top dog!
Bone! Give me!
I thought
you said he'd be here.
He said he might stop by
after the pedigree party,
but he didn't
promise anything.
How much farther?
Just keep coming. Keep
coming, we're almost there.
Where are we?
It's a surprise. Ready?
Hit it, boys!
Wow!
It's pretty cool,
isn't it?
It's beautiful!
Wait, wait, wait.
There's more.
Crank it, DJ Thunder!
I can't believe I'm
really here with you.
Of course you are, silly!
You're the alpha dog.
Okay, well,
I hope you're hungry.
Wow! You really pulled
out all the stops!
It's just a little
something I whipped up.
How about a peanut
butter appetizer?
My favorite!
Really? I was worried you
might be allergic to it.
I almost got
almond butter.
It's so romantic!
I couldn't think of another
girl I'd rather share it with.
It's so creative, too.
Tell me, how did you
ever think of this?
It's just
the kind of guy I am.
I'm a Great Dane. We
sat at the foot of kings!
Listen, I just wanted
to say something.
I wanted to say...
My bad.
I slipped off the seat.
That's okay, Thunder.
He's so funny.
I wanted to say
hanging out with you
these last few weeks,
which in dog years
feels like months,
it's like the first time in my
life I feel like I really belong.
Yeah! I'm having
a great time, too.
Look at him.
Land shrimps at
his beck and call.
That's it.
No, Mazie!
Stay, please.
Sit!
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, Mazie!
What's up?
You don't give a steaming pile about
us anymore, so cut the act, all right?
We took you in.
We were your friends.
And you just sit over here
and act like we're dirt.
What'd they put in your
kibble this morning?
You took her
on my dream date.
Dream date? What is she talking about?
How do you think
that makes me feel?
Bitter, party of one?
What's the big deal?
We were just
spit-balling ideas.
You'd think she'd be
thrilled I used one.
You don't get it,
do you?
She gave you Pig Cow,
she likes you.
At least, she did until
you turned your back on us
and became a big
phony-baloney sell-out.
Word.
That's really cute
and everything,
but I already
have a girlfriend.
A pedigree girlfriend.
So, that's it?
Yeah.
I don't hang out
with mutts anymore.
Ouch!
You're lucky
I had a favor to call in.
PETCO's gonna give us
another chance.
But they wanna see
a fully realized campaign
before they'll
cross-promote the roll-out.
No problem, I'll start
working on that immediately.
You'll start
working on it?
Little late for you to be
going solo, there, Buckeye.
I want you on my boat this
weekend, we'll work together.
This weekend, I can't. You have to.
I need to spend some
quality time with my family.
Tough.
I promised my wife.
All right, bring the family along.
They can relax while we work.
Okay, that'll be perfect.
Excellent.
Now, this is
sort of embarrassing,
but there are no dogs
allowed on the boat.
It's my wife's rule.
Quite frankly,
I think she's jealous.
Okay, we got the
life jacket, towels,
bathing suits,
sunglasses, sunscreen.
Brian's got his fins.
You're taking
the laptop?
You know,
just in case.
Guys, I'm really excited about
spending this weekend together.
Dad, please,
I'm begging you.
Let me go to my friend's
house so I can go the party.
Barb, it's a family trip and
you are coming, too. Let's go.
Here, get your snorkel.
Let's go, let's go.
Come on. I feel like
we're forgetting something.
We have everything, but
the furniture and the dog.
Look at him.
He's just sitting there!
I know.
You think he'll be
okay here alone?
I think he'll be fine.
He's got food and water
and I'm having Laura from
down the street look in on him.
Right. Right.
I mean, what's the worst that
can happen? He has a party?
Invites his
girlfriend over?
Yes and yes!
Party at the Duke's!
Rager, man! Yeah!
Jump! Jump! Jump!
I am a golden dog!
Canine-ball!
Looking good, Colby!
Sweet collar, Aurora!
Yes! Yes!
My boy, Topaz!
Marmaduke.
Chug it! Chug it!
Go, go, go!
Chug it, Shasta!
Ow!
Sorry, slipped off
the seat again!
That is
not cool, dude!
Hey, is this
your party, dude?
Yeah!
We're not worthy, we're not
worthy! We love you, man!
All right! Now it's a
party! Yeah, come on!
Who let the dogs out?
Pee-Wee,
hit the Crazy String!
You're a big hit,
Marmaduke!
Hey, is it just me, or is it
getting a little out of hand?
Everyone's having fun,
loosen up!
Yeah!
Of course, of course!
No, no, you're right.
Forget what I said.
Why is everyone always
having more fun than us?
Because they're not afraid to live?
And we suck at swimming?
Great! Okay, now
I'm catching a cold.
Come on, let's go.
What do
you smell, girl?
Trouble.
Duke! Duke! Duke!
Hey, dude,
get out of the trash!
Do I know you
from somewhere?
Me? Nope.
Never seen you before.
You sure?
That tail looks painful.
Of course I'm sure, man. I've
never even been to a dog park.
Oops.
It's so soothing!
Gordie, no!
No, not on Debbie's rug!
Whoa, whoa!
No, no! Hey! Not on the
couch! You raised in a barn?
No, not the stereo!
Phil's gonna kill me!
Looks like a great party.
Now, I'm sorry to interrupt.
What are you doing here?
I got a quick question.
Anyone recognize
this cute little fella?
The cat from the park
that Marmaduke hazed?
I recommend the guacamole.
It's dynamite.
Look at the tail.
Turns out he lives
here with Marmaduke.
Or is it Marma-fake?
First of all, you weren't
invited here, Bosco.
Leave now and you won't have a
problem. And take Whiskers with you.
We have
a "no cat" policy.
Say what?
Is that right? Then how do you
explain that picture over there?
Hey, it is that cat.
Yep, that's it.
That's the cat.
Let's
get out of here.
Wait! Wait!
What's going on? Where
you going? No, no, stay!
Total poser.
Where are you going?
Loser!
He's going, not us!
Party at the pier!
All right, let's go! Party!
Is it true, Marmaduke?
Only most of it.
You see, in the end,
pedigrees always win.
And that's the way
it'll always be.
Enjoy the rest of
your party, mutt.
Baby, come on.
Jezebel! He's a liar.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, Bosco,
wait up!
Jezebel, wait! I...
I thought
you were different.
What just happened?
I think it's called a colossal
fall from grace, hermano.
Oh!
Not to rub margarita salt in the wound,
but you kind of
deserved it.
Oh! What have I done?
Can't wait for the
next family boat trip.
It was a weekend
on a boat, okay?
It was a work-end, honey.
We had to finish
the presentation and...
What happened?
Marmaduke?
No.
Phil.
No!
I'm up, I'm up.
Where am I?
Marmaduke!
I'm up, I'm up.
Phil, thank God
you're here.
I had a party.
I was trying to be a big
shot... Off the couch!
I just invited
some friends
and then they invited
friends. It just got crazy!
Come here, now!
I'm sorry.
Phil, I really could
use a hug right now.
Bad dog!
Phil, no! Phil,
I'm trying to explain!
Phil, stop it.
Just give me
a chance to...
Phil, I said I was sorry.
The PETCO pitch.
Oh, Marmaduke.
Ooh!
Uh-oh, Daddy.
I don't care if it's raining,
I'm done. He can sleep outside.
Perfect, that will
solve everything.
We'll just leave him chained up in
the backyard for the next 10 years.
Or maybe
we give him away.
You did not
just say that.
He refuses to
listen to me!
It's just an option we haven't
explored yet, that's all I'm saying.
I don't understand
you sometimes.
Look around you, Deb.
He destroyed our home!
No, he didn't!
Our home is us. It's
you and me and the kids.
It doesn't matter
where we are.
This move did not work out
the way I hoped it would.
The only way this move
was ever gonna work out
is if we were
in it together.
You seem to have
lost sight of that.
Everything I do
is for us.
I worked my butt
off this weekend,
and once again,
that dog screwed it up!
He's a dog, Phil! He
doesn't know any better.
You want him to
sleep outside, fine.
He has a backyard,
you have a couch.
Really?
Really.
You know what?
It's not that easy.
Nobody ever
puts in a cat door!
Hey, you must be Mazie.
Tell the hipster giant I'm not
interested in his peace offering.
He's gone. He got busted with
Phil and had to sleep outside.
He ran out the back gate
about an hour ago.
Oh, great. He has
zero street smarts.
Where you going?
To find that big doofus!
I'd go myself,
but I can't get wet.
Yeller.
Oh! You crazy,
wonderful dog.
He acts like it's a great
big romp, doesn't he, Travis?
Crazy as a bullbat.
He's a heap more dog than
I ever had him figured for.
None of the strays at
the pound have seen him.
He's not at
the dog park either.
No luck here.
I made a huge mistake wearing
the bumble-bee sweater.
It's way too absorbent!
It's raining cats and us!
You guys head home, I'm
gonna look a little longer.
We can't leave you
out here alone!
It's too dangerous!
Okay, on second thought,
you have fun.
You do that whole thing.
Good luck.
Chupadogra?
Who are you? And what
are you doing here?
Please don't hurt me!
You're a big boy.
Good. The small ones ain't
got enough meat on their bones.
Please don't hurt me!
I'm sorry, I...
Are you okay?
I'm more than all right.
Sorry to bother you.
Hey, what's a dog like you
doing out here, anyways?
You're no stray.
I ran away from home.
So, you think running's the answer? Huh?
I don't even know
what I'm doing anymore.
I acted like a big-shot and
lost all my friends, my family.
Listen, this bag of bones you're
looking at used to be something special.
I was the alpha dog.
Left my home to go run the
pack. And man, did I run it.
Till they turned on me.
Now I live out here alone
dodging trains and dogcatchers.
Rest assured, compadre,
there ain't a day goes by
when I don't think about
waking up in a warm bed
and spending the day
with the folks who love me.
The real me.
Go home.
Something tells me it ain't
too late for the real you.
Thank you, Buster.
Been a long time
since anybody called me that.
Thanks.
What's that?
It's the pound.
Go on, get out of here.
Get!
What about you?
You're sick!
Yeah, that's right, baby.
I'm one sick puppy.
Go on, go!
Let's make this easy,
old timer.
What fun would that be?
No, no! No!
Debbie, you got
to listen to me.
Marmaduke is missing. He's
been gone since last night!
We're talkative this
morning! Go eat your num-nums.
Hey, Deb.
Did you leave these
on the table in there?
What are you
talking about?
Barb, I read the text. And...
Is that really
how you feel?
Honestly?
Yeah.
Hey, Bri.
You never went to
soccer practice, did you?
I didn't want to disappoint you,
but you weren't really listening.
Where's Marmaduke?
In the backyard,
sweetie.
No, he's not. I thought
he was upstairs with you.
No.
Marmaduke!
The side gate's open. You didn't
let him back in last night?
No.
That's what
I've been saying.
He'll be back, right?
He could get
hit by a car.
Honey, anything
could happen
because we don't know
how long he's been gone.
I just wanted him to
sleep in the backyard,
I didn't want him
to run away. God!
I got this
presentation.
Guys, if I don't
nail this, I'm done.
Just go.
We'll find him.
You put her in the car seat, and
you get Marmaduke's leash, okay?
Wait.
We'll all go find him.
Now you're
talking, amigo.
Come on, where am I? Just give
me one little scent of home.
Marmaduke! Come on, buddy. Marmaduke!
Come on, boy.
Marmaduke!
Okay, that was the
neighborhood. So, where else?
The beach. He could be at the beach.
Okay, the beach and
maybe the dog park?
You guys, I'm texting
everybody I know.
What if he's
at the pound?
Come on, come on, give me
something I can recognize.
One landmark,
one little scent.
What do you mean,
"What does he look like?"
He's a Great Dane! He's huge.
He's twice the size of your dog.
Come on,
give me a scent.
One more funky
little Marmaduke smell.
Come on, not today!
Hi, Don. Winslow,
where the heck are you?
You were supposed to
be here an hour ago!
I'm sorry, Don. Uh...
We still haven't
found Marmaduke
and I just don't think
I'll make it in today.
Don't worry about
coming in today,
because you're fired,
Winslow!
Mazie?
Mazie? Mazie!
What is this?
It looks like
a water main broke.
There he is!
Wait! I'm coming!
Honey! Honey!
Right there, look!
Kids, never do this.
Marmaduke!
Where was he, Brian?
He was up there.
Marmaduke! Here, go wait
in the car with your mom.
Marmaduke!
Mazie!
Where have you been? I've
been looking all over for...
Mazie! No!
What?
Mazie!
Marmaduke!
No, no,
don't let me fall!
Marmaduke!
Come on, let's go!
Come on, buddy!
Marmaduke, where are you?
Somebody, help! Mazie!
No! Marmaduke!
Mazie! Mazie!
Hey, Marmaduke,
come on, let's go!
Stay back.
Phil, help me!
Get away from me!
Hey, stay back!
Geronimo!
Marmaduke, no!
That's my dog. That's my dog in there!
Look, that was my dog.
Can somebody help me?
Can you please help me
get him out of there?
There's a catch basin
about two blocks down.
We need
a water rescue, over.
Help!
Marmaduke!
Mazie!
Where are you, Marmaduke?
I can't do this!
Hold on.
I'm coming, Mazie!
Help me! Help me!
Somebody, help! Mazie!
Marmaduke!
Help! Help!
Help, help,
don't let me fall!
Mazie!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
All right.
Get me two more guys here.
What are we
gonna do?
Just hold on.
I'm gonna
figure this out.
Anything?
Wait, wait,
I think I hear someone.
Down here!
I think
he's gonna help us.
Yeah. We're right here.
What should we do?
I found them, over.
Come on, girl.
I don't think I can make it! Come here.
No, I can't!
Come on, girl,
it's okay.
Listen to him.
Mazie, you can do this.
You can do it, right here.
I don't think I can make it!
Come on, girl,
just jump.
Come on.
You can do it.
Good, you got it!
Take her first.
Go ahead. Come on, it's your turn. Jump!
Me? No. I can't do it,
I'm too big!
Come on,
you can do it!
What's that noise?
Marmaduke, look out!
You got to come, boy.
Hurry!
You got
to be kidding me!
Come on, boy! Hurry!
Grab me!
You better grab me now!
What's happening?
Jam it! Jam it!
Get him out!
Up, up, up!
Let's go!
You guys, easy.
Easy!
There he is.
We got him up. Guys!
He's out.
Where's the other one?
Where's my dog?
I'm sorry.
The water was
moving too fast.
I lost him.
We're not gonna give up.
Where does this go?
The aqueduct,
it's just down there.
Go with him. Go.
Marmaduke!
Phil, help!
Get me. Phil!
Marmaduke!
Help!
Get me, Phil!
Marmaduke!
Help!
I'm right here, buddy.
Grab here, Phil!
Grab on to this.
Phil! Phil,
where are you? Phil!
Phil! Phil!
Thank goodness
you're okay!
Marmaduke!
Right here, come on!
I can't...
I'm too scared.
Right here.
Come on.
Oh, no!
How did it come
to this, Phil?
It started with a bath,
and now look at us.
We can do this.
I'm not gonna
let you go.
I can't do it.
I promise.
Let go,
and I'll catch you.
I love you, buddy.
Come on!
Phil, I've been waiting since
Kansas to have you say that.
Come on, let's go!
You can do it, buddy.
Right here. Come on.
Trust me.
I trust you.
Here I come!
Atta boy, buddy.
Come on!
Right here.
Swim to me.
Let's go. Come on.
Phil, help!
Get me. Phil, get me!
All right,
come on! I got you.
I love you, buddy.
Thank God, you got me! We did it! Yes!
You got me, Phil!
You got me!
You're safe, buddy.
Those aren't tears,
it's just a little water!
Good boy.
Harness coming down!
I still hate water!
I know you're not
gonna understand a word of this
but I've never been so happy to see
that big, ugly face in my whole life.
I'm done pretending
to be a top dog.
A real top dog
looks out for his family.
And you are my family.
That's it,
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm gonna give him
the tongue.
That's a good boy!
I know, I know!
I've been on this
crew nine years.
And that, my friend,
is some pretty strong stuff.
Come on, buddy!
Honey?
Dad!
Hey, guys!
Are you okay?
Hi, Dad.
I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm just
a little wet, that's all.
Marmaduke!
Look who I found!
Oh, yeah!
Get a little Marmaduke.
Let me wrap my
paws around you!
We missed you.
Hi, there.
Hi!
Okay, you're all wet!
Gosh, I love you guys
so much.
This is all my fault. I
never asked what you wanted.
I've just been trying
so hard to make this work
that I had no idea
you were so unhappy.
I guess what I'm
trying to say is
I think we should
move back to Kansas.
What?
Move back to Kansas?
Kansas? Uh-uh. Toto
ain't going nowhere, papi.
That's crazy talk, Dad.
Hey, Brian!
Dude, we got it all on tape.
We're putting it on YouTube!
Sweet!
It's good to see you,
Bri. What are you doing?
Brian, who are
your friends?
They're just some kids
I met at the skate park.
They're pretty cool.
Hey, boys!
Hi.
Sup?
Hey, Barbara!
Hey, what's Hasselhoff
doing here?
Bodie? You came.
Yeah, I came as soon as
I got your text message.
Is everybody okay?
Yeah, everything's
much better now.
Those were some pretty
sick moves, Mr. Winslow.
Thank you, Bodie.
No worries, Phil.
It's Mr. Winslow.
Yes, sir.
What do you think, babe?
I don't know. I like
it here. I think we fit here.
We fit in the house.
We don't fit in
that company car.
I just missed you.
Looks like we're home.
Looks like the family
landed on their feet.
There's just one more thing
I got to take care of.
Check it out.
Here goes nothing.
What the heck is he doing? Is he crazy?
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Don't just stand there,
do something!
I am.
I'm standing my ground!
What's up, Marmadukey?
You here to
exact revenge?
Actually, no, Bosco.
I'm here to thank you.
Thank me? For what?
For showing me
how wrong I was.
I don't care what
everyone thinks of me
'cause it doesn't matter
if you're big or small
or a pedigree
or a mutt.
We're all just dogs.
And that's the way
the park should be.
So I'm gonna sit down and
claim this spot for all the dogs
who don't think they have
what it takes to be over here.
Sup? Yeah.
You gotta be kidding me.
You're kidding me, right?
Does everyone here have
rabies-induced insanity?
This is sacred turf.
It's just for pedigrees.
Well, not anymore.
You know what? You're all
just mutts. All of you!
Let's go, Jezebel.
I think everyone
should sit here, too.
I'm done taking your
spit on my head, Bosco.
Go find somebody else to drool
on. We're through with you!
Come have a seat, fellas.
It's lovely up here.
I can see forever!
Fine, have it
your way, losers.
I'll remember this.
Payback's gonna be a...
Bee! Bee! Ahhh!
Victory!
Victory is ours!
The Duke's our boy!
Huh! Looks like I'm not the
only one terrified of bees.
Bees are scary.
Listen...
I don't know how to say this
without hurting your feelings...
Shh!
I'll be fine. It's time to finally
stand on my own four legs for a while.
Besides,
we'll still be friends.
Ouch! I hate it
when girls say that.
Mazie?
Wow.
Hey, check it out.
Looking good
in the pink.
What are you
waiting for? Go!
Mazie, wait up!
Oh, hey!
You look amazing!
I feel like
a fluffy monstrosity.
Listen, I wanted to say how sorry
I am for the way I've been acting.
I was a real jerk,
and you didn't deserve it.
I think my brain just turned
into an Afghan Hound for a while.
No offense.
I totally heard that.
It takes a big dog
to admit that.
Yeah, I...
What?
Your eyes. You have
really pretty eyes.
And I never had
a chance to tell you.
Thanks!
Your fur's
really nice, too.
Winslow!
Oh! I wonder what ever
happened to that PETCO deal.
Winslow! Winslow? There you
are, I've been looking for you.
I thought I was fired.
Don't be so sensitive.
Any man that chooses
his dog over his career
is a man I want
working for me.
Besides, have you seen the video of
you rescuing Marmaduke on YouTube?
Nah.
Six hundred and eighty-two
thousand hits so far.
We got PETCO!
Are you serious?
Totally!
We're gonna sell
a lot of dog food!
Wow!
Come on, walk with me.
We got work to do.
I can't.
Why?
'Cause I made plans
with my family.
Who? Oh. All right.
All right, tomorrow.
Monday.
Monday. Deal.
Deal.
Don't push it, okay?
Okay, I'm just
spit-balling here
but what if the dogs
could talk to each other?
I don't really buy it.
What if they
could dance?
# Hey!
# What I like about you
# You really know
how to dance
# When you go up, down,
jump around
# Think about true romance
# Keep on whispering
in my ear
# Tell me all the things
that I want to hear
# 'Cause it's true
What's up, boys?
That's what
I like about you.
# That's what
I like about you
# Hey!
Hey!
That's what
I like about you.
# Hey! #
It's still pretty
rough. What do you think?
I love it!
Great job.
Thanks, Deb.
Wait for it.
Oh! Marmaduke!
What did you eat?
Man, you got
a serious problem.
It never gets old!
# Hey!
# What I like about you
# You keep me
warm at night
# Never wanna let you go
# You know you make me
feel all right
# Keep on whispering
in my ear
# Tell me all the things
that I want to hear
# 'Cause it's true
# That's what
I like about you
# Hey! #