Ryanair final call for passenger Wilton...
...traveling to Brussels-Charleroi
on Flight FR-1014.
Please proceed immediately
to Departure Gate 6,
where this flight is now closing.
Do you want a car?
£10, Theatreland.
Car? London?
You want a taxi?
Buckingham Palace.
No one.
Would you like a car, sir?
Are you from Sajit?
I'm not here to meet you in particular.
I am here to rescue those...
...that have been let down by the system.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'm over there.
Who's next?
- 2-9.
Here.
My turn.
Okay.
Hey.
Your name is now Mohammed.
Thank you, Okwe.
Hurry up, now, man.
Come quick, quick, quick, quick.
Quick, now.
Right.
You just come here.
That bitch.
This shit, dustbin city.
So, what do I need, Okwe?
Amoxicillin.
You get that in Boots drugstore or not?
From a doctor.
- You're a doctor.
I'm a driver.
Look.
They say you're a doctor, right?
You get me something now.
I can't piss fire another day, man.
I'm a driver.
It's for me wife's sake.
You know what I mean.
Okay.
So I'll get you all the jobs in South London.
I'll see what I can do.
Let me kiss you, Okwe.
Maybe in return,
you can get some soap.
Early is as bad as late, Okwe.
Hello.
Front desk.
No, I'm afraid the kitchen
is closed from midnight.
I'm sorry.
Good night, madam.
What?
Senay, perhaps today,
I can cook you lunch.
No, Okwe.
So that's true what they say.
What is true?
They say you and the Turkish
girl are nesting like birds.
I rent her couch.
In the morning,
when she's working here.
We're never there at the same time.
She has rules.
You know, she's a Muslim,
which means she's a virgin.
Like a little angel.
Ivan, I think there's someone at the door.
Can you believe it?
One of the fuckers wanted to
put me on his Visa card.
Oh, my bloomin' feet.
Lucky I don't work standing up.
What?
Don't they have hookers
where you come from?
Where are you from?
Somewhere with lions, I bet.
I like lions.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
You might want to send
someone to check on the room.
There is a problem?
- How should I know?
I don't exist, do I?
See you tomorrow.
What's that?
You're stealing stuff already, huh?
Guy before you used to steal
whole pigs from the freezer.
But you better hide it.
If Sneaky sees that...
Oh.
Speak of the fucking devil.
Where's the greeter here?
This fucking place.
Hey.
Instead of smoking,
you clean this place up.
Okwe.
Everything is all right?
What's this?
Lunch?
It was blocking the lavatory in Room 510.
It is a heart.
A human heart.
What?
What the fuck do you
know about hearts, Okwe?
Perhaps you should telephone the police.
Police? You think I should call the police?
Señor Juan, someone is dead.
Okay.
You speak to them.
You found it.
You do the talking.
I'll introduce you.
What's your full name, Okwe?
And you never told me where you're from.
Or even how come you're here
in this beautiful country.
Hello? Police?
Yeah, got somebody who
wants to talk to you.
Hello?
You will learn, Okwe.
The hotel business is about strangers.
And strangers will always
surprise you, you know?
They come to hotels in the night
to do dirty things.
And in the morning,
it's our job to make things look pretty again.
For your trouble.
You think if you don't take
the money, you are innocent?
Take it.
Do something nice with it.
No.
It came to me last night
in a flash of inspiration.
I can see.
That's a good move.
Guo Yi,
there's something I need.
Amoxicillin.
You got the clap?
No.
My boss.
Which one?
They're all the same.
In this country,
the health service is free.
You still driving cabs in the day?
You're going to kill yourself.
I do not care to sleep.
When you go quiet,
it means you've won already.
Go on, Okwe.
Don't be nice.
Makes it worse.
Well, shit.
You want Chinese or English tea?
Chinese.
Don't know how you drink that stuff.
I found it on a body.
It's blown my head wide open.
You should read it.
Medicine for your soul, Okwe.
Guo Yi, today I also found something.
In a lavatory in one of the hotel rooms.
Someone's heart.
A heart.
A human heart.
I'm only telling you
because you are a rational man.
Maybe there's an explanation.
Maybe some guy with one
of the girls had a heart attack.
Rooms are down as empty.
So the Spanish guy had
to get rid of the body.
Hotels hate dead people.
It was a healthy heart.
- So?
So your boss was right first time.
Somebody brought it with them.
Who carries human organs?
- Lots of people.
Name someone.
- Me. Okay? Me.
I do it all the time.
I take my work home.
What I'm saying is,
I could if I was weird.
And this is a weird city.
Why would anyone do
that to a human heart?
These sound to me like questions.
I don't ask questions after 11 years here.
And I'm a certified refugee.
You're an illegal, Okwe.
You don't have a position here.
You have nothing.
You are nothing.
You wait outside.
I'll go get you those pills.
Stick to helping people who can be helped.
Fresh stuff.
Thank you.
Senay.
Senay, having only one key
is making this impossible.
I do not want you coming
in when I am there.
At the hotel, we are friends.
Shh.
- I'm no different here.
How would it look, Okwe?
So it is better I always
chase you down the street?
Wait five minutes,
then knock the door.
Knock very, very quietly.
Senay.
Yes?
Did you clean on the fifth floor
yesterday morning?
Nothing works.
Senay, did you clean Room 510 yesterday?
What the hell are you talking
about the hotel for?
Water, water, water.
I was wondering if there was
a problem in 510 yesterday.
You can fix these things?
Okwe.
You can fix...
They were not clean.
Glasses need very hot water.
So do women.
Everything here is connected
to everything else.
Okwe, in Africa, it is the man
who will cook and clean?
Senay, this came for you.
Why did you not tell me?
I just told you.
You have friends in New York?
Your postcard.
I have a cousin.
Ever since I was small,
she has written to me.
I sometimes wish London
was more like New York.
It would be easier to drive a cab there.
You have been to New York?
And you came back?
I lived there for a time.
In the winter,
they put lights in the trees.
Is that true?
And you can skate in the parks.
And some of the policemen
ride white horses.
Not all of them, but some.
What did you do there?
I worked in a hospital.
You were a cleaner?
- I was there to study.
So, why are you working in a hotel?
It is an African story.
I've noticed you never answer 'yes' or 'no.'
You are very strange.
You drink wine, Senay?
Do you want to know why I left Turkey?
Because you wanted to
live like your cousin.
No.
Because I do not want
to live like my mother.
Yes.
- Yes, what?
I do drink wine.
This is a recipe from Nigeria.
In Nigeria, they do many
interesting things with pork.
But, of course, I used lamb.
Mmm.
Take one three times a day.
Avoid alcohol.
In here. Come.
So she's a popular lady.
My warriors cannot work
with rotten balls, Okwe.
My friend is just a porter
in the hospital crematorium.
Hello.
Front desk.
No, I'm afraid the kitchen
is closed from midnight.
Psst. Hey.
Hello?
Yeah, room service.
Sneaky doesn't know about this?
Sneaky knows about everything.
And you?
You know everything that
goes on in the hotel?
Not so much butter.
Hey.
You guard the door, lvan.
You see who comes and goes.
You would know if somebody
came into the hotel...
...but did not leave again.
Why would someone not leave, Okwe?
I don't know.
You should remove the crusts,
like in the Ritz.
Everyone leaves, Okwe.
Some leave quickly.
Some stay for long time.
If you want to stay,
don't concern yourself
with who comes and who goes.
It's the little touches
that make the difference.
That's capitalism.
Now go.
Don't forget.
You accept only cash.
Room service.
Thanks.
Okay, you just make
yourself comfortable, and, uh...
I'll go freshen up.
All right?
Fucking asshole.
Oh, my God.
Come on, babe. Hurry up.
Okay, okay.
Calm yourself, sweetheart.
What are you doing?
Have a drink first.
You look fine.
Just get out here.
Hey.
Fuck.
Enough. No more.
Where the fuck did you come from?
Leave now.
Oh. Oh, fuck.
You don't have concussion.
How the fuck do you know?
Christ, you must be bored.
Getting your kicks spying on me.
I was making sure the blockage
had not returned.
Perhaps...
It's Juliette.
You should go home and rest.
Rest?
Got three more before morning.
So, have you ever seen a lion?
Oh, yes.
On TV.
I had it cut.
It is yours.
You were right.
This way is more sensible.
Okwe, you must not tell them at
the hotel that you have a key.
Senay, I tell them only the truth.
Even so.
And show them that your back hurts...
...so they know you sleep on the floor.
But that is not true.
I sleep on the couch.
The couch is not as real as the floor, Okwe.
Believe me.
I'm a woman.
And some of those bitches
won't know what is a couch.
But they know floor.
They clean floors.
For you?
Immigration-enforcement directive.
Open the door.
Forgive us.
Miss Gelik?
Senay Gelik?
Turkish national?
Do you have your S.A.L. Handy?
- My what?
Your acknowledgement letter.
Your I.D.
Oh, yeah.
I carry it always.
Neighbors, Senay.
They see things.
In the last few days, they've
seen someone come and go.
A man.
Sometimes a woman in your
position can be exploited.
There are people in London
without any kind of papers.
They prey on people like you.
- Prey?
There is someone living here.
- There is no one living here.
You are aware that your E.L.R. Status...
...means you are unable to accept rent.
You're seeking asylum.
Or engage in employment of any
kind for at least six months.
You're not working, are you?
- Mind if I use your bathroom?
Your case is under review.
Thank you.
Is that all you want?
No, no, no, no.
You know this stuff will
not only keep you awake.
It'll blow your brains out.
You know that, don't you?
Hey. Okwe.
Keys.
There you are.
Hey, Okwe.
What happened, man?
Hey, somebody's husband
came home early, right?
Here.
Take this.
We don't want the doctor
getting sick, right?
I played them one of these fellows' songs.
And, actually,
they were very helpful.
Had they already heard it or not?
They were already very into funk and...
It's bound to happen.
You stay here too long.
You start dressing like
an Englishman, huh?
Where is he, then?
Who?
I have a date.
Every payday, 4:45.
Hey.
Come on, lover boy.
Okwe, will you help me?
Hey, guy before you took £5.
No, no, no, no.
But you watch the door, huh?
- Yes.
Come, my little princess.
Come, come, come, come,
lille princesso.
Security room is out of bounds
for half an hour.
Five minutes, max.
Immigration-enforcement directive.
Can I help you?
What time do the maids clock in?
Wakey-wakey.
- 5:00.
You mind if we wait?
No.
Excuse me, sir.
This is a nonsmoking area.
If you wish,
perhaps you can wait...
...in the designated area across the lobby.
Hello?
Shh.
It's for you.
Hello?
Okwe. Okwe.
But I am almost there.
Senay will be here in two minutes.
You must stop her.
I have a medical condition.
Lightning doesn't strike twice.
Shh, shh, shh.
Is that the last of them?
Yes.
This is an interesting place.
Would you like to see a rate card?
I have a friend.
In her factory,
they always need people.
It's a sweatshop.
Is it any worse than
cleaning up after whores?
It's better money.
Oh, you are so sad for me.
I do not wish to cause harm to anyone.
That is all it is?
I will collect my things and go.
Go?
- How can I stay?
Okwe, who will cook for me?
If it's okay, I will call on you
if I have the time.
But I'm owed three days'
money by the hotel.
I will see Señor Juan tomorrow morning.
I have no money for food.
I will see him today.
Meet me at the café at 4:00.
You are here to see Señor Juan?
Looking for work?
Are you working?
French?
No, no.
Help me.
Yoruba.
You speak Yoruba?
Bantu?
What the fuck are you doing here, Okwe?
Senay has decided to leave.
She asked me to collect what she's owed.
Oh, yeah?
What, are you marrying
her or something, Okwe?
I'll get her money.
No, no. It's okay.
I'm a doctor.
It's okay.
No, no, no.
Please, please, please.
You must get this man to hospital now.
He must go straightaway.
If you are a doctor,
you can do something.
This is the wound of an operation.
Where? Where did he have this operation?
Which country?
You must get this man to hospital.
They won't go to hospital.
No, no.
- No hospital.
Guo Yi is here?
Shit.
Sister. Hello.
It's my first day here.
I was told to collect my overall.
Which shift are you on?
- Shift?
Come on. Either you're late
or you're really late.
You couldn't do the bins in the kitchen...
...when you're done in here,
could you?
Okay, okay, okay.
You see these blue tablets?
He must take two every two hours.
Understand?
He must take two blue
tablets every two hours.
You speak English?
And Somali?
A bit.
He says to say, 'Thank you.
God is great.'
Tell them he must take two
blue tablets every two hours.
And one white tablet every six hours.
It is very important
that you get this exactly right.
Ask him which hospital they went
to to have the kidney removed.
He says they didn't go to a hospital.
Ask him where they did this.
In a room.
He had his kidney removed
in the hotel, yes?
How much did he get for risking his life?
He is English now.
He swapped his insides for a passport?
The man at the hotel said...
...it would be like taking out a tooth.
Can I get you something?
- I've been here one hour.
An hour and a half.
There.
I will go and collect my things.
Why won't you sit down?
Okwe, where have you been?
- Africa.
I thought you weren't coming.
- I would have got you the money.
The money?
Do you feel that?
Do you feel anything?
You know, I counted.
I've seen you laugh three times.
Four.
You think I'm so innocent.
In my village,
they chew those leaves to forget
how hard their lives are.
I use it to keep awake.
You know it makes you look...
Senay.
You should keep away from me.
You lost your job.
Because of me,
you are in a sweatshop.
And now you are going again.
Be sure you make it to New York.
I will make it to New York,
Okwe, thank you.
It's best if you don't show up
until after 5:00.
Most porters are gone by then.
Only ghosts left.
Showers are here.
Water's not too hot,
but it runs.
Couch in my office is pretty soft.
Oh, I forgot.
You don't sleep, do you?
My friend, welcome to my hotel.
Beautiful, isn't it?
And the other residents are, uh, very quiet.
It will only be until I...
Until the world improves.
Best truffles I've ever seen in England.
Dug up 15 hours ago in Provence.
Came through on the night train.
Mmm.
Shall we say one thousand?
I'm in the wrong fucking hotel.
One thousand, Señor Juan.
What do you say?
Okay.
One thousand.
But if I give you that price,
I need a favor.
There is a night porter.
African.
He came from you, so I guess
he came through Amsterdam.
Yes.
What about him?
He's some kind of doctor.
What kind of doctor?
I need to know what there is to know.
Police. Police.
Can I help you gentlemen?
We're looking for someone
called Senay Gelik.
Thought she might be working here.
Do you see anybody working here?
If you see her, give us a call.
You have been here for two days.
And already because of you,
I'm in trouble.
Maybe I should call lmmigration.
Should I call them?
You wouldn't do that.
I need a good reason.
What can you give me?
If they find out you've been
working, what will they do?
They will put you in prison.
And here,
they mix the men and women.
So every night,
you will be raped.
If you want to be like a Western girl,
that's what happens to Western girls.
If you want to go to jail, fine.
If you can't give me a good reason,
I will call the lmmigration.
I'm a good man, Senay.
I know where to draw the line.
I don't want to take your virginity, Senay.
I just want you to help me to relax.
You have such a beautiful mouth, Senay.
Achtung. Achtung.
My ladies and gentlemen,
your coach awaits.
Please. Please.
But you must take your own
luggage to the coach.
Please. Thank you. Good evening.
I will help only those
who cannot carry their own bags.
Okwe, get up here.
This man is a doctor.
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
She's okay.
She only needs to rest a minute.
He qualified in Lagos.
He worked for the Nigerian government.
His name is Dr. Olusegun
Olatokumbo Fadipe.
We must hurry or we'll miss the coach.
In the end,
I find out everything
about everyone in this place.
Here.
Take a look at this.
French.
It's a work of art.
There are two Lebanese I use
who are the best in London.
You give them a photograph...
I have no idea what you're
talking about, Señor Juan.
If you were just some African,
the deal would be simple.
You give me your kidney,
I give you a new identity.
I sell the kidney for 10 grand,
so I'm happy.
The person who needs the kidney
gets cured, so he's happy.
The person who sold his kidney...
...gets to stay in this beautiful
country, so he's happy.
My whole business is based on happiness.
But for you,
Dr. Olusegun Olatokumbo Fadipe,
I've a better idea.
I do not want to get involved,
Señor Juan.
Each time you operate,
you get £3,000.
A passport for you and one for Senay.
Take her on honeymoon.
I do not want to get involved.
You could even go back to Africa.
And no one would know
who the fuck you are.
Your choice.
No rush.
Just wanted to put a
little wasp in your head.
Unusual.
Chinese guy with no family.
Maybe he's from the back of a truck.
I cut off his buttons so
his spirit can escape.
I'm sewing up his pockets...
...so he can't take his bad luck
with him to the spirit world.
If he's an atheist,
I'm ruining a suit no one will ever see.
If he's a Buddhist,
I'm giving him eternal happiness...
...for the price of a piece of thread.
I have found out why the
heart was at the room.
They are removing kidneys.
One of their patients died at their hands.
Another, I treated for
a staphylococcal infection.
You're treating people?
I hope you charge.
Did you hear what I said?
There's nothing so
dangerous as a virtuous man.
Well, Okwe,
if you're so concerned,
you should go to the police.
Get yourself deported.
Do you think if it were for
deportation I would not do it?
I'm a wanted man, Guo Yi.
Wanted for what?
Okwe, you didn't know
people sold their organs?
Not here.
- What do you mean, 'here'?
Here in London you think
it doesn't happen...
...because the queen doesn't approve?
I heard in London it's 10 grand for a kidney.
For that, people take risks.
If I had the courage,
I'd sell my kidney.
Just to get out of here.
Just to save my brain.
The problem with being on time...
...is that you can always be tracked down.
What do you think of the girl?
She's my next customer.
8 years old.
She's called Rima.
Her family brought her over
from Saudi hoping for a miracle.
If she doesn't get the new
kidney, she's going to die.
The doctor we use is no good.
If he fucks up again,
there'll be another heart down the lavatory.
Okwe?
You still there?
So I'm an evil man, right?
But I'm trying to save her life.
That's weird, huh?
Kind of thing that keeps
you awake at night.
Tonight, London is colder than Moscow.
I heard it on the radio.
Okwe?
It is a crazy idea,
but we really can do it.
You said you liked New York.
But if not New York, then maybe
Boston or Los Angeles.
I'm going there, Okwe.
What do you think?
And, Okwe,
you could go there, too.
Senay, are you okay?
Senay, where are you?
What has happened?
I knocked,
but you did not hear me.
Senay, are you okay?
Senay, what has happened?
The factory does not suit me.
My hands are too soft.
I cut my fingers.
So I have decided to go to America.
For America,
you would need a visa.
Or maybe a European passport.
You keep away from Señor Juan.
- It is like taking out a tooth.
He's lying, Senay.
Because you are poor, you will
be gutted like an animal.
They will cut you here,
or they will cut you here.
They will take what they want.
One of the laundry girls did it.
And now she's free.
Others are dead, Senay.
So they are free, too.
What would your God say?
My God does not speak to me anymore.
Don't break, Senay.
Save money.
Keep New York in your
head and work hard.
You know what kind of work I do?
Lunch.
Okwe, somebody's in
the back room looking for you.
She look like a film star, boy.
Senay.
Look, Okwe, I know for sure
that this coat costs £300.
And this dress...
- Tell me what has happened.
We can sell the coat for £200.
Senay, where did you get these?
I bit, Okwe.
At the factory.
He said he would report me to lmmigration.
And he made me suck.
But today, I bit.
I bit.
Señor Juan sometimes
has rooms in the hotel.
No, Senay.
Just for tonight.
- No.
Through there is hot water and a shower.
Hurry, Senay.
What is this place, Okwe?
It is a place where you can stay for tonight.
So cold.
If anyone comes,
you are a friend of Guo Yi.
Tomorrow we will find
you somewhere to live.
So... it is in there.
I can hear it.
Your heart.
Hello.
Room service.
Buenos dias, negro.
Come on.
She is nil by mouth the whole day.
Please.
Sister.
Help me, brother.
Stop acting like you've got a choice.
Please.
Put on your clothes.
Son of a bitch.
You came in a truck,
but you're going home in chains.
They'll deliver you like meat.
- No.
The whole world is
wrong except you, Okwe?
What?
What, Okwe?
You are going to cut me
up and flush me away?
Huh?
I really don't know you at all,
do I, Okwe?
This is Senay. She is a friend.
- I'm not your friend.
She's been out here all night.
- I would rather freeze to death...
...than go into that building again.
You know, there are
mornings I feel the same.
Come.
It's cold.
This is the house of the dead, Okwe.
They're all dead.
Okwe.
Maybe this will help.
My cousin has a room in Chinatown.
I guess there's space for two.
You know, Okwe, good at chess
usually means bad at life.
You do realize that she's
in love with you, don't you?
I've been with her 20 minutes,
and I know it.
But then, I'm bad at chess.
Senay, there is something I must tell you.
This is your religion?
- I have no religion.
Senay.
You have stopped chewing the leaf.
I can see it in your eyes.
You know, Okwe,
your eyes are quite pretty.
They're not bad-looking.
- Senay, listen to me.
I come to this churchyard often.
I come here to be alone
and to think about my wife.
So now you see.
What do I see?
You should not see me anymore.
Do you love her?
There is a room above a restaurant.
Immigration police do
not go into Chinatown.
You will be safe.
- Do you love her?
Here's money for the rent I owe you.
There is more for the trouble
I have caused you.
Do you love her?
- Love?
For you and I,
there is only survival.
It is time you woke up
from your stupid dream.
Yes?
Senay.
Are you going on holiday or something?
Señor Juan.
America, maybe?
Come on.
You cleaned up their shit so long.
Now you can be one of them.
Who is it?
It's me.
I got some paperwork.
Okay.
How old are you?
22.
How old do you want to be?
Hey, Come on.
Relax.
I can make you whatever you want.
You want to be Spanish?
Or Greek?
Italian.
You're going to need a new name.
Isabella Encarico.
You're sure that's Italian?
She owns a café in New York.
Okay.
You are at New York lmmigration.
What's your name?
Isabella Fontana Encarico.
How old are you?
- 22.
Where were you born?
- Napoli.
Where in Napoli?
- Arenella.
Right.
The trick, Senay, is to believe
you are the new person.
If you believe it inside, then
the lmmigration will believe it.
Drink, Senay?
What are you afraid of?
Okwe's gone.
Got scared and go away.
Go to hell.
This is hell.
I'm helping you to get away.
Take off your robe.
Come on.
Hey, hey.
Stop. Stop that.
Stop that.
I can't believe it.
I'm arguing like you are my fucking wife.
Let me explain something, Senay.
Your robe, now, is what the
Americans call a 'deal breaker.'
So...
No.
You are this close to New York,
and you said no.
Wait.
I want the whole thing.
That's the deal.
Take it or leave it.
You do not see me.
You just do.
Take it or leave it.
So it wasn't so bad, huh?
Nothing to cry about.
I'm not crying.
If you told me it was the first
time, I'd have cut a ribbon.
I can't believe Okwe never fucked you.
You kind of love him, huh?
Women love men most who
don't love them back.
Well, you had a lucky escape.
You know why he ran away?
Because I found out that in Africa,
he murdered his own wife.
You don't eat or drink for 24 hours, okay?
Doctor's orders.
Senay is here?
Senay.
I will need a pill.
There is a pill you can
take the morning after.
You're a doctor.
At least you can get me a pill.
I won't allow you to butcher her.
You won't allow?
I will operate on her myself.
You'll do what?
I will do it.
It is the only way I can be sure
she will not die.
In return, I want a passport.
A new identity.
Well, holy shit.
So you are human, Okwe?
I will bring you our photographs
tomorrow morning.
Hi. I'm Juliette.
I'm a friend of Okwe's.
He said that you needed these.
So, he did not care enough
to bring them himself.
Oh, Okwe's an angel.
There.
Never happened.
So, what did happen?
Before, I was a virgin.
Jesus.
Mohammed.
What a pair.
The virgin and the whore.
Boss?
- The doctor needs a good car.
Take it.
Last time, you were lucky.
Black is black.
Wash these again.
Please.
Boil, boil, eh?
Hot, hot.
Oh, dear.
So this is how you do it right.
There can be no guarantee against E. Coli.
Wonderful.
Oh, yes.
No, no.
Passports.
It's something I do right.
No parking.
Okwe wants me to wait here.
I gave her a sedative an hour ago.
She's only in a deep sleep.
But now you are here, I can
administer the anesthetic.
Now I'm here?
You are going to be my
assistant, Señor Juan.
What the fuck is this?
I have noticed that if you
do not drink, your hands shake.
When you pass me the scalpel,
I do not want you to cut off my fingers.
Where will they come to collect?
If you faint,
I will have only half an hour...
...before the kidney begins to deteriorate.
They come to the laundry bay.
Back of the kitchen.
You better start.
Go and scrub your hands.
Yes. Professional.
It's decided.
It's fucking decided.
You and me are going into business.
You know washing dishes?
You know when you forget
on Friday and come in Monday,
and there is a pan with sauce?
White. Green.
Shit.
That is...
How they do things in the city.
Jesus.
Was I speaking English then?
What you say?
Why do you say?
Senay.
I don't understand it,
how the ice will help.
Make you last longer, babe.
I don't want to last longer.
It's not even payday.
All right.
Make you harder.
Think what happens to water
when it freezes, huh?
There.
Get a bucket.
Bucket?
Come on.
Okwe, you have removed kidneys before?
Many times.
In pathology.
What is pathology?
It means the patient is already dead.
Did he tell you things about me, Senay?
No.
Let me wipe your brow, Doctor.
Juliette, put the ice
on the bed and put on the gown.
Take the bag.
Squeeze.
Gently.
We must go and scrub up.
Cold tonight, huh?
On the night like this,
who would want so much ice?
You are Pylades.
Pylades was the boatman...
...who ferried the souls
to the land of the dead.
If you didn't put a coin...
...under the tongue of your dead relative,
Pylades wouldn't take them to Hades...
...no matter how good you
had been in your life.
Knife.
Oh, Jesus.
Juliette, you are not allowed to faint.
Is that it, then?
No, no.
I must sew him up.
Why?
Fetch me stitches.
Juliette, will you go and check
there is no one else waiting?
Yeah.
Where's Señor Juan?
He's drunk.
How come I've never
seen you people before?
Because we are the people you do not see.
We are the ones who drive your cabs.
We clean your rooms.
And suck your cocks.
In one hour, call an ambulance.
Send them up to Room 510.
Juliette.
Thank you.
Shh.
It's okay.
One hour.
- Okay.
Handa?
Handa, it's me... Senay.
You hear how good my English is?
I'm coming to New York.
My hands are shaking.
- So are mine.
I don't have a driver's license.
Hey. It's dead.
It's the tunnel.
I must tell her what time we land.
Senay, what Sneaky told you was true.
He did not tell me anything.
I did not kill my wife myself,
but still it was my fault.
I was a pathologist in Lagos.
- Now we are someone new.
A government official was shot.
I was told to destroy the evidence.
When I refused,
my house was firebombed.
My wife was still inside.
The police charged me with her murder.
I had to run.
But my daughter stayed.
Valerie.
She's with my sister in Lagos.
How old is she?
7.
I must go to her.
Tell me about Lagos.
Do they have hotels that need maids?
When you arrive at the airport,
you will see a whole line of yellow cabs.
The car will take you across a bridge.
When you have crossed the river,
you will see...
...lights in the trees.
Policemen on white horses.
No.
I know that it won't be like that.
Goodbye, Okwe.
Senay.
Hold me.
You must go.
Isabella.
Always we must hide.
This is the café where my cousin works.
I love you.
Hello?
Valerie.
Yes, it's me.
At last.
I'm coming home.