DOUGLAS: Our plane crashed
in the endless Southern Pacific...
...and we drifted for days
between life and death.
[MAN 1 & MAN 2 GRUNTING]
On the sixth or seventh day, the two men
who had survived with me...
...began to fight over
the last canteen of water.
[DOUGLAS GRUNTING]
They fought like beasts, not men.
[GUN COCKS]
Stop!
[YELLS]
[MAN 1 GROANS]
[MUFFLED GROANING]
I fought for my life
just as savagely as they did.
MONTGOMERY [WHISPERING]: But why?
Why would you want me to do that?
Positively no other survivors.
Run preliminary tests?
What's the point?
Okay.
[MONTGOMERY HUMMING]
[lN NORMAL VOICE]
Feeling better?
- Where am l?
- Mm.
You're on a seafaring vessel
named the Ombak Penari.
Who are you?
My name is Montgomery.
And you are?
Edward Douglas.
I was on my way to Jakarta.
My plane went down.
[GASPS]
I'm working on an assignment
for the United Nations.
I'm working on the peace settlement.
There was a lot of blood
on that life raft.
You were the only survivor.
Yes.
- I need to get to a radio...
- Whoa, whoa.
- ...as soon as possible.
- Be calm. Just be calm.
Just calm.
- I'm still hydrating you.
- Yeah.
There's no radio on this vessel.
I'm gonna pay the captain of the ship
to take you to Timor...
...which is about four days
after they drop me off...
- ...at my little island paradise.
- What are you giving me?
Oh, you'll like it. L like it.
It's a little Jimi Hendrix.
- Oh, wait.
- Ow!
Wait, wait, wait. Are you a doctor?
Are you a doctor?
Well, I'm more like a vet.
[CAPTAIN & MONTGOMERY
SPEAKING lN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Excuse me a minute.
[BOTH SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[CAPTAIN SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Yes, yes. All right. All right.
Don't be rude.
There you are.
[DOUGLAS SIGHS]
- What's going on? Where are we?
- This is Moreau's Island.
There's been a change of plans.
[MONTGOMERY & CAPTAIN
SPEAKING lN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
You've gotta come with us.
- Well, maybe I should stay on here.
- lf you come ashore, we've got a radio...
...and we'll get you off the island in a couple
days. Of course, the choice is yours.
You can stay on the boat here,
but these guys are real party animals.
Captain Penari here has taken quite
a shine to you, if you know what l mean.
It's really best if you come with me.
Can l give you a hand
with the rest of the things?
No, that's all right.
The others will take it.
The others?
The islanders?
Yes, the islanders.
DOUGLAS:
How did this get here?
MONTGOMERY: Well, the Dutch were
the first whites to settle the island in 1890.
They had a coffee plantation.
And then the Americans
took it over in World War Il.
Japanese bought it
and tried a hotel resort...
...which went belly-up.
I used to have a rabbit as a little boy...
...called Keasey.
Died...
...from my own neglect,
I'm sorry to say.
I've never been very good
with animals.
- Mm. He's a beauty.
- Mm-hm.
He, she...
What's going on in your head? Mm?
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, good Lord!
[SIGHS]
- Hold that.
- Oh, please.
[ANIMAL GROWLING]
MONTGOMERY:
We don't actually eat meat here...
...but l'm sure the doctor
will make an exception for you...
...our special, unexpected guest.
It'll be our little secret, okay?
Come on.
That's a very impressive
communications sensor.
The only problem is nobody can fix it
but me, and it was down before we left.
I'll get it up and running soon.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna have to ask you to restrict
your movements to the main house.
The people who fund this project are afraid
you're gonna sprain an ankle and sue us.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Well, it's a litigious world.
Yes.
Uh, stay right here. I won't be long.
[THUNDER CLAPPING]
[RAINDROPS PATTERING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[DEEP FOREST'S "NIGHT BIRD"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[GASPS]
I'm sorry. Heh.
- lt's all right. It's all right.
- Who are you?
I just got here.
Heh. I came on the boat this morning
with Montgomery.
Come from the sea?
Well, originally, l'm from England.
England? That's another island.
- Yes.
- I've read about it in many books.
My name's Edward Douglas.
Edward Douglas.
You have such beautiful hands.
[CHUCKLES]
- So beautiful.
- Well, thank you.
Are you from this island?
- My father brought me here.
- Oh.
Dr. Moreau?
And where are you from originally?
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Getting acquainted?
She's beautiful.
Yeah.
She's a pussycat.
I've arranged some quarters
for you upstairs.
Wonderful.
I saw the Nobel Prize.
I think I remember Moreau.
Didn't he vanish or something?
I thought he was dead.
No. He's still working.
What exactly did he win his prize for?
He invented Velcro.
I see.
And how long has he been here?
Seventeen years.
He became obsessed with his...
...animal research.
Animal rights activists
drove him out of the States.
It got so bad you couldn't cage a rat
without reading him his rights.
[CHUCKLES]
And how long have you been here?
I wrote a paper that was published...
...and we started a correspondence.
So about 10 years ago, l came out...
...helped him with his work.
Eventually...
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[CHUCKLES]
Let me show you to your room.
Well, it's...
...very agreeable.
Look, l don't want to be
an imposition here.
And as soon as you can get
this com sat equipment working...
...I can, uh...
They'll send a plane for me.
[LOCK CLICKS]
[DOOR KNOB CLICKING]
- Why have you locked the door?
- This is for your own good.
Montgomery!
[SIGHS]
[KEY CLATTERS]
[BACH'S "BRANDENBURG CONCERTO NO.2,
MOVEMENT 2" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[MAN SCATTING]
MAN:
Lovely.
[ANIMAL SHRIEKING IN DISTANCE]
[ANIMAL BLEATING]
[GIBBERING]
[GROWLING THEN ROARS]
[BLEATING CONTINUES]
[BABY CRYING]
Oh, my God.
[SNARLS]
[ROARING]
[GASPS]
Shh! Shh!
Listen. Listen. L can help you
to get off this island...
...but only if you promise never to do
or say anything that will hurt my father.
We must go. Now!
MONTGOMERY: Eddie, there's a lot
of unstable phenomenon out there.
[CREATURE HOWLS]
[GRUNTING AND SNORTING]
[SPEAKS lNDISTINCTLY]
[SNARLS]
[GROWLING]
[ROARS]
[FLIES BUZZING]
[DOUGLAS GRUNTS]
[ROARING AND SNARLING]
- lt's all right.
- You from boat!
He's a 5-finger man.
He's a 5-finger man, like you. See?
Look. Look.
[SPEAKS lNDISTINCTLY]
Five-finger man...
Yes. Good. Good. Good.
Good.
[GRUNTS]
My name Assassimon.
Assassimon!
[GRUNTING]
AISSA: Assassimon, you must help us
find the Sayer of the Law. Quick.
[CREATURE HOWLING lN DISTANCE]
Come, come. Come, hurry!
ASSASSIMON:
Come!
[ASSASSIMON SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[CREATURES GIBBERING]
[MUFFLED GRUNTING]
[CREATURE SPEAKING lNDISTINCTLY]
CREATURE: The punishment to those
who break the law was terrible.
None escaped.
[GATE SLAMS]
It is a hard way.
The way of being a man.
Sooner or later, we all want
a thing that is bad:
To walk on all fours...
...to suck up drink from a stream...
...to jabber instead of saying
the words...
...to go snuffling at the earth
and claw the bark of trees...
...to eat flesh or fish,
to make love to more than one...
...every which way.
These are all bad things.
These are not the things that men do.
We are men, are we not?
CREATURES:
We are.
We are men because the father
has made us men!
Sayer of the Law.
Another 5-man has come to hear
the law and the wisdom.
The father sent for you?
You are here to help him in his work?
The other 5-man is looking for us.
Please help us.
Montgomery.
[HORN BLARING]
[CREATURES SHRIEKING]
CREATURE:
The father! The father!
Bring the 5-man.
[DRUM BEATING RHYTHMICALLY]
[CREATURES CHANTING lNDISTINCTLY]
CREATURE:
Father!
AISSA:
No!
Release him.
Give him the gun.
What?
He's very frightened. Give it to him.
[GUNSHOT]
[DOUGLAS SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
AISSA: No!
- No, no, no.
No! Douglas, no!
MOREAU:
He won't hurt her.
Mr. Douglas, I beg you,
please do not confuse them.
Move back.
Move back!
[CREATURES GROANING
AND SHRIEKING]
Stop!
For God's sake, stop!
MOREAU:
Calm yourself, Mr. Douglas.
Don't add more pain
to their already diminished lives.
Why have you done this?
Don't you feel the heat as I do?
I can't tolerate the sun...
...and what it's doing to me,
and what it's doing to all of us...
...to all life on earth. Heh, heh.
We must return to the compound.
Keep the weapon
if it comforts you.
Mr. Douglas, first of all,
for the sake of propriety...
...I would like to present my children.
Hello. I am Waggoi.
[PANTS]
How do you do, sir.
I'm Azazello.
My name is M'Ling.
MOREAU: You've already met
my beautiful daughter, Aissa.
Majai, would you present yourself, please?
He means you no harm, Mr. Douglas.
He's just trying to be polite.
He just wants to shake your hand.
Thank you.
This is the most outrageous spectacle...
...I have ever witnessed.
Look at yourself!
I understand that
I must be shocking to you.
However, l must also point out...
...that I have an allergy to the sun,
and that's why l've put this medication on.
Look at these people!
[AZAZELLO GROWLS]
Look at him!
[SIGHS]
Mr. Douglas...
...I don't think that I have
the intellectual ability...
...to condense 17 years
of study and experiment...
...into 17 minutes of explanation.
For the moment,
it will have to suffice to say...
...that the people
that you witnessed before...
...living under my care and protection...
...are animals that have
been fused with human genes...
...in the course of a series
of scientific studies...
...designed by myself.
Well, has it ever occurred to you
you might have totally lost your mind?
I mean, this is just Satanic.
Judge not, Mr. Douglas,
that ye be not judged...
...for by these judgments
shall ye also be judged...
...and let he who hath not sinned
cast the first stone.
There is no peace, saith the lord,
unto the wicked.
I think perhaps this is not the time
to continue.
We will have dinner at 8:00.
I hope that you'll be in another state of mind
to be slightly more receptive.
[MOREAU PLAYING CHOPIN'S
"POLONAISE NO. 6" ON PIANO]
[MOREAU CHUCKLING]
Oh!
"Somewhere in sands of the desert...
...the shape with lion body
and the head of a man...
...is moving its slow thighs.
The darkness drops again...
...but now I know that
20 centuries of stony sleep...
...were vexed to nightmare
by a rocking cradle...
...and what rough beast,
its hour come round at last...
...slouches towards Bethlehem
to be born?"
Oh. M'Ling, that was just beautiful.
Thank you so much. Shall we toast?
Your health.
Thank you.
Well, Mr. Douglas.
very good of you to join us.
Uh... Please tell me.
Is the devil still pursuing you?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Well, perhaps you could explain to me
what you mean by the devil.
You seem to be on terms with him.
Well, permit me, Mr. Douglas,
to tell you something of the devil...
...as l've come to know him.
The devil is that element
in human nature...
...that impels us to destroy and debase.
And what are you about upon this island
but destruction and debasement?
Oh, well, l can tell you very plainly.
No, please don't do that.
For 17 years, I have been striving...
...to create some measure
of refinement...
...in the human species, you see.
And it is here, on this very island...
...that I, sir, have found
the very essence of the devil.
What do you mean?
I have seen the devil
in my microscope...
...and I have chained him.
And I suppose you could say, in a sense,
metaphorically speaking...
...I have cut him to pieces.
The devil, Mr. Douglas, I have found...
...is nothing more than
a tiresome collection of genes.
And it is with great assurance
that I can tell you...
...that Lucifer, son of morning...
...is no more.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Well, I don't see
how any of this specious nonsense...
...justifies these
monstrous disfigurements.
Well very simply, they represent a stage
in the process...
...of the eradication
of destructive elements...
...found in the human psyche.
And I have almost achieved perfection,
you see...
...of a divine creature
that is pure, harmonious...
...absolutely incapable of malice.
And if in my tinkering, l have fallen short
of the human form...
...by the odd snout, claw, or hoof...
...it really is of no great import.
I am closer...
...than you could possibly imagine, sir.
Ah. Oh.
Mm.
What is that?
AZAZELLO:
Rabbit fricassee, master.
Stop that! Oh, God!
Get this out of my sight!
Azazello, who's responsible for this?
Uh, Mr. Montgomery requested it.
Go into the kitchen. Leave.
All of you, go into the kitchen
and wash your hands.
Mr. Montgomery considers this
a sort of amusement, l suppose.
No one saw me kill it...
...except you.
Well, I have no way of knowing.
What do you mean?
We saw one in the forest
with its head torn off.
- And who was responsible for that?
- lt was Lo-Mai.
Good God.
You bloody fool.
All right, I want everyone outside...
...in the compound tomorrow.
Well, Mr. Douglas, perhaps we can entertain
you a little more than you anticipated.
We're going to have
a trial tomorrow.
[CREATURE ROARING]
[GRUNTING THEN PANTING]
[WOOD CRACKS]
[SCREAMS]
[CREATURE CHITTERING]
[GRUNTS]
[CREATURE SHRIEKS]
[CHITTERING CONTINUES]
[SHRIEKS]
[GASPS]
[SHRIEKING]
[DOUGLAS YELLS]
[CREATURES SHRIEKING]
[YELLS]
SAYER OF THE LAW:
Not to kill for pleasure.
CREATURES:
Not to kill.
SAYER OF THE LAW:
Not to kill for hatred.
Not to kill anything, anytime.
That is the law.
That law has been broken!
None escape.
None escape. None shall escape.
Who is he?
[GRUNTS]
Who has done this?
Evil is he who breaks the law.
Do you hear, Lo-Mai?
[GROWLING]
Do you hear?
Lo-Mai?
[LO-MAl ROARS]
[GROANING]
I forgive you, my son.
Father.
Lo-Mai has broken the law.
He killed a living thing.
Oh! Oh.
[CREATURES CLAMORING]
[WHIMPERS]
Oh, my God.
What have you done?
I am sorry, Father.
I thought you wanted me
to protect the law.
Where did you get this gun?
The law is not to kill...
...for any reason!
See that his body is shown
all manner of respect.
Yes, master.
[SNIFFING]
[CHUCKLES]
[SCREAMING]
Lo-Mai.
[YELLING]
[GROANING]
DOUGLAS: I saw very little of Moreau
as the crisis broke.
Oh, God.
He was in the laboratory
working away...
...in pursuit of his dream
to create a perfect human race.
Nothing was said
of my attempted escape.
Montgomery, who had once been
a brilliant neurosurgeon...
...was reduced to being
the beast people's jailer...
...and now
he had become mine too.
It's turned completely yellow.
Yes. Here.
It's almost opaque. See?
MONTGOMERY:
Jesus.
Nothing.
So we'll simply
have to increase the dosage.
Would you get
the inoculation gun, M'Ling?
[MONTGOMERY SPEAKING lNDISTINCTLY]
You...boar me.
Go, go, go.
Good girl. Good girl.
- Hi, sweetie.
- What is it you're giving them, exactly?
It's a combination
of endorphins and hormones.
It's keeps them from retrogressing.
Retrogressing into what?
MONTGOMERY:
Well...
It isn't pretty.
DOUGLAS: Well, it certainly seems
to improve their mood.
Oh, that's my contribution.
I add a little methamphetamine...
...some morphine, some'shrooms,
and some other shit.
Keeps them mellow. Keeps them...
Well, keeps them coming back for more.
Well, it hasn't brought him back.
- What?
- There.
Hyena. Come! Come! Ýt's okay.
Come on. Come get your shot.
Come on.
Hyena.
Hyena. Look at my hands.
Look, okay? Ýt's okay. Lt's okay.
We won't hurt you.
That's right. That's right. Come on.
Hyena, come!
What?
Pain...
...no more.
What?
No. Christ.
DOUGLAS:
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- You don't understand.
[GRUNTS]
- What's going on?
- Christ. He pulled it out.
DOUGLAS: What?
- His implant. He pulled out his implant.
They all have implants.
It's how we shock them into submission.
We have to find him.
Dart him and get him back
to the compound.
A hunt, master? Hunt?
Yeah. Yeah, a hunt.
Azazello likes a good hunt.
[GIBBERING AND GRUNTING]
Get him! Get him!
[SNARLING]
Move it! Move it!
[LAUGHS]
M'LING: This is Biostation Helix
calling on all channels.
Is anybody receiving me?
Are you certain
you know how to use this?
M'LING:
Yes. L make many calls for the doctor.
I read the books and learn.
I make it work.
Not without this, you don't.
[TOY SQUEAKING]
Fetch.
Who do you think you're gonna call?
Hm?
[SALT'S "BLUSTER"
PLAYING OVER HEADPHONES]
I listen closely
Heard from a voice
What are you gonna say if
you get somebody on the horn?
"Mayday, mayday.
I'm being held captive by a pig lady"?
[MUSIC STOPS]
You gonna sell Aissa to the circus?
You know, she's not like us.
She's very delicate. They all are...
...but she needs her shots too...
...and she's not gonna get them
off this island.
There's so much you don't understand.
Why don't you smoke this?
Maybe you'll start.
There's no way off the island.
You must face the fact.
Why was I brought here?
I was brought here, wasn't l?
I can't find Hyena-Swine.
I think we should before the others
get the same idea.
[CREATURE SHRIEKING]
[GROWLING]
[CLASSICAL MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Oh, my word.
You startled me. Heh, heh.
How are you?
I think I'm just simply going
to perish from this heat.
I cannot bear it.
The longer that l'm here,
the worse it gets.
And, l mean, this damn Montgomery
won't fix anything.
I'm dying of heat.
I think that...
Yes, my caloric converter is empty.
Would you fill it, please?
Yes. That's much better.
Oh, God, yes. Oh, yes, God.
Oh, please.
Forcefully. Forcefully.
Oh, no. Oh, my God.
[CLEARS THROAT THEN COUGHING]
Not so strong.
You have no idea how strong you can be.
You must be very very careful.
Father, I must talk to you.
Of course.
What is it?
I'm changing.
Well, that's nothing to be
frightened of, darling.
Let me see.
Yes. Yes, there are a few changes.
However, let me have a look.
Yes. Yes, your ears are developing.
- I'm hideous.
- No, no, no.
Darling, how can you say that?
You're an absolute angel.
You're beautiful inside.
You're beautiful outside.
You're an extraordinary creature.
Help me.
These small things are just a question
of chemical imbalances, that's all.
- No, no, no. Don't be upset, darling.
- I want to be like you!
Will l never be like you?
Well, I hope not.
I mean, how would you look
if you were like me? Ha, ha.
You see? L've made you smile.
[LAUGHS]
[GROWLS]
[GRUNTING]
[CREATURE SQUEALS]
[SNARLING]
[PIANO PLAYS BASS NOTE]
Mine!
[CREATURE SHRIEKS]
[CREATURES CLAMORING]
Oh, oh. Heh, heh.
What a surprise.
I didn't mean to startle you.
I just thought l heard someone
stirring about down here...
...and I thought
I'd come have a look.
No, no. L did hear it, probably.
But l heard... Would you like a biscuit?
No?
I was listening to this music.
It was rather interesting.
And did... Were you playing?
[GROWLS]
- No?
- Well, perhaps it was you.
[GROWLS]
Oh. Well, in any event, you see, it reminded
me of a man named Schoenberg...
...this sort of music...
...and I would like to demonstrate something
which might be of interest to you.
You can all just relax.
And... Well, you see...
...there is a sort of music
called tone music...
...and it sounds...
[PLAYS DISSONANT NOTES]
...sort of like that, you see?
But there is another kind of music...
...and there was a man
named George Gershwin...
...who played this:
[PLAYING GEORGE GERSHWIN'S
"RHAPSODY lN BLUE"]
[MOREAU HUMMING]
Lovely.
I know, my son.
[HOWLS]
I know.
[SNARLS]
Father, I must ask a question.
Please.
What am I?
We call you father...
...yet we are not like you.
What are we?
Father!
You are my children.
You are all my children, you see?
Now, l think perhaps it might be helpful
if you would go over there...
...and then we could discuss this,
and I could explain to you exactly.
Now, be calm. Be calm, please.
I want to tell you something
very important.
very important...
...and I just...
Everyone, be calm.
And just relax and be seated
if you would, please.
Because...
...you see, one of the things...
- Tell me.
- Uh...
Why you make the pain...
...if we are your children?
Uh...
You see, you are my children...
...but law is necessary.
If there is no more pain...
...then is there no more law? Hm?
There is always law.
[DEVICE WHIRRING]
[SNARLING]
[GROANS]
[SHRIEKS THEN LAUGHING]
- Pain no more.
- Good God.
What are you doing?
To walk on all fours...
...that is the law.
Please.
To slurp up our drink,
that is the law.
We are not men.
[ROARS]
To eat flesh and fish anytime...
...that is the law!
[HYENA SHRIEKS]
Now l am the law!
None shall escape.
That is the law!
[HYENA YELLS]
Father!
[CREATURES SHRIEKING]
[GUNSHOT]
[SINGING lNDISTINCTLY]
[CHUCKLES]
Is there still law?
There is still law. Yes.
But how can there be law
without the father?
He hasn't left us.
That is what l will tell the others.
That his spirit is watching over us.
We must wait for a sign.
[SOBBING]
It's all right.
Were it not for you...
...I should say that your father
had failed...
...terribly.
But you're not the same as them.
Nor are you the same as me.
You are something far, far finer.
[GASPS THEN CONTINUES SOBBING]
It's a process.
I'm changing.
There's a serum
Montgomery used to give me.
It's in the lab.
It can stop my regression.
Please.
Help me.
[GRUNTS]
MAN IMITATING MOREAU:
"Judge not, that ye be not judged.
For with what judgment ye judge,
ye shall be judged.
And with what measure ye mete,
it shall be measured to you again.
And why beholdest thou the mote
that is in thy brother's eye...
...but considerest not the beam
that is in thine own eye.
Thou hypocrite, first cast out the beam
that is in thine own eye...
...and then shalt thou see clearly to cast out
the mote of thy brother's eye.
Neither cast ye your pearls
before swine...
...lest they trample them
under their feet...
...and then, give not that
which is holy unto the dogs."
What does she need?
- Animal or man?
- What am I looking for?
You're very angry.
"Neither cast..."
Listen. Listen.
Listen. Don't fuck around.
What do l need?
- Unh.
- What do l need?
Tell me what I need!
- Ow! Ow! Ow!
- Where is it? Shut up!
[SCREAMING]
Shut up! Shut up!
Where is it? Shut up!
Where is it?
Where is the serum?
[lN NORMAL VOICE]
Who's the animal? Hm?
Who's the animal?
Be calm. Calm.
We've got to think and reason
this through together.
[DOUGLAS PANTING]
DOUGLAS:
Tell me.
MONTGOMERY IMITATING MOREAU:
I destroyed the serum.
All of it.
[DOUGLAS GASPS THEN SOBBING]
AZAZELLO:
Hyena.
[CREATURE SHRIEKS]
Kill him.
[SNARLING]
[GROWLING]
[GUNSHOT]
I have the fire that kills.
[GROANING]
I know where there's more.
Fire that kills.
Show us...
...and we will let you join us.
First, I want no more pain.
- No! No, no.
- Take it out.
- No, no. No. No.
- Take it out!
HYENA:
We are not men.
That is the law.
[LAUGHS]
[YELLS THEN GROANING]
Burn it.
[SHRIEKS]
None shall escape.
[EINSTÜRZENDE NEUBAUTEN'S
"lNTERIMSLIEBENDEN " PLAYING]
[ALL GIBBERING AND GRUNTING]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
[MONTGOMERY lMITATING MOREAU
SPEAKING lNDISTINCTLY]
And though I give
my body to be burned...
...and have not charity,
I am nothing.
And though...
...I give all my gifts
to feed the poor...
...and though l give my body
to be burned...
...and have not charity,
I am nothing.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[MONTGOMERY LAUGHING]
[CREATURES SHRIEKING]
[CREATURES GRUNTING]
[lN NORMAL VOICE]
You know, Sherlock Holmes...
...once asked Dr. Watson:
"Did you notice the remarkable thing...
...about the dog barking
in the middle of the night?"
Dr. Watson said,
"l heard no dog barking."
Sherlock said,
"That's the remarkable thing."
[MONTGOMERY LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
Ah...
Little woofer.
Well...
...things didn't work out.
Moreau wanted to turn animals into humans
and humans into gods.
But it's instinct and reason,
instinct and reason.
What's instinct to a dog?
To hunt. To kill, master.
To run with the pack.
I want to go to dog heaven.
[CREATURES GIBBERING
AND SHRIEKING]
[LAUGHS]
Now we are men.
[ROARS]
Douglas.
He said...
...he was closer to his goal...
...than l could possibly imagine.
Do you remember?
See, l was led to believe...
...he had saved my life...
...when, in fact...
...all the time...
...he intended to take it.
He intended to, um...
What? Use me.
He intended to use my DNA
to stop your regression.
Well, anyway...
...he is dead...
...and Montgomery is...
...heh, insane...
...and has...
He's destroyed all the serum.
[LAUGHS]
Go.
Go!
[ROARS]
Aah...
[PANTS THEN HICCUPS]
The guns!
[CREATURES GRUNTING]
[ROARS]
[AISSA GASPS]
How do you do, sir?
I believe we've met.
[LAUGHS]
Drip, drap, drip, drap.
And where are you going
in the woods today, little girl?
Oh, my little kitten.
[SNICKERS]
Fetch!
[CREATURES GROWLING]
[HISSES]
[AISSA CATERWAULING]
[DOUGLAS & AISSA GRUNTING]
Nicely now, little kitten,
or I'll hurt you.
[AISSA CATERWAULS]
Remember?... Remember
how the master whipped me?
Ooh...
But he never touched
your soft skin, did he?
No!
[NECK CRACKS]
[SNARLING]
[ALL GIBBERING AND GRUNTING]
[SHRIEKS]
Come on. Come on.
Tell them that I am the law.
Do not believe him.
He is not the law! Unh!
AZAZELLO:
Hyena!
[DOUGLAS GRUNTING]
Good doggie.
[LAUGHS]
[ROARING]
[DOUGLAS YELLS]
[HYENA LAUGHS]
[GROWLS THEN SNARLS]
Fine man...
...please tell them...
...that I am god. Hm?
[ALL YELLING AND GROANING]
[SHRIEKS]
You're right.
- You are a god.
- No!
Again.
You are a god.
You're all gods.
[HYENA CHUCKLES THEN SNARLS]
Tell them...
...to obey me
like they did the father.
You all killed the father.
You all ate his flesh.
So who is the new father?
Who is god number one?
Who should they obey?
Him?
[GROWLS]
Or him?
You see, there must be...
...a god number one.
[GROWLING]
[ROARS]
[SHRIEKS]
[CREATURES GRUNTING
AND SHRIEKING]
[GROWLING]
[SNARLING]
HYENA:
Father.
[HYENA GROANING]
[CREATURES GRUNTING]
[SNARLING]
Father.
Why?
CREATURE:
You!
Stay.
Douglas, you stay here.
You stay with us.
I'll be back.
[CREATURE WHIMPERING]
I'll come back.
There must be people
who can, uh...
Doctors, scientists...
...who might understand
what Moreau was trying to do.
Perhaps they could develop a serum,
stop the regression.
No.
No more scientists...
...no more laboratories,
no more experiments.
I thought you would be able
to understand that.
We have to be what we are...
...not what the father
tried to make us.
To go on two legs...
...is very hard.
Perhaps four is better anyway.
DOUGLAS:
This is a true record of what l saw.
I set it down leaving out only the latitude
and longitude of the island...
...as a warning to all who would follow
in Moreau's footsteps.
Most times, I keep the memory
far in the back of my mind...
...a distant cloud.
But there are times when
the little cloud spreads...
...until it obscures the sky.
At those times, I look about me
at my fellow man...
...and l'm reminded of some likeness
to the beast people...
...and I feel as though the animal
is surging up in them...
...and they're neither wholly
animal nor wholly man...
...but an unstable combination
of both...
...as unstable as anything
Moreau created.
And l go...
...in fear.
[English - US - SDH]