Hello? Hey Rob, Steve.
Oh, hiya, how are you? Good, good.
Listen, are you
free next week to go away? Where?
It's a tour of the north,
a restaurant tour,
really good restaurants.
Right. Why me?
Mischa can't come
and I don't want to go alone.
I've asked other people
but they're all too busy.
It's a job. I'm not asking you go on
holiday with me or anything weird.
It's for The Observer magazine.
So, you know, do you want to come?
This programme contains
strong language.
Are you Steve Coogan? Yes, I am.
A-ha! A-ha.
All right mate, how you doing?
Fine, thanks. Listen,
do us a favour, would you?
Can you sign that? Yes, of course.
Make it out to Paul. OK.
Can I ask you a question?
Yes, of course, absolutely.
Is it true, what I read about you?
And what do you read about me?
That you're a bit of a cunt.
Well, where did you read that?
Well, it's in today's newspaper.
Here, look. Whoever said that doesn't
know me very well.
Are you sure?
What? A-ha!
"Coogan is a cunt", says dad.
Cunt.
Did you not sleep well or something?
No. I couldn't get off
because of the food
and then when I did get off,
I was having awful dreams,
really bad dreams.
Blue cheese.
Coleridge was a poor sleeper.
I was reading his poem
called The Pains of Sleep. Mmm.
"Sleep, the wide blessing, seemed
to me distemper's worst calamity."
Yes. "The third night, when
my own loud scream had waked me
from the fiendish dream,
"o'ercome with suffering strange and
wild, I wept as I had been a child".
Yes, no, I know that.
That's the drugs.
What? Coleridge, the opium.
He was a big druggie.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
You could have a costume drama here,
couldn't you?
I would love...
Mel Gibson coming over the hill.
I would just love to do
a costume drama in these hills,
vaulting over dry stone walls
with a scabbard,
a dead look in my eyes
because I've seen so many horrors.
And they always say something
like, "Gentlemen, to bed.
"Gentlemen, to bed for
we leave at first light.
"Tomorrow we battle...
"...and we may love our lives,
"but remember death is but a moment.
"Cowardice is a lifetime
of affliction." Nice.
"To bed, for we rise at daybreak!"
Very good, very impressive. Always
leave at daybreak, don't they?
They never leave at, you know, 9.30.
"Gentlemen, to bed,
for we leave at 9.30."
Ish. Ish.
"Gentlemen, to bed,
for we rise at...
"What time's the battle?"
"About, oh, 12 o'clock". Yes.
"Right. 12 o'clock...
"On horseback, about three hours?
"So we leave about eight, 8-8.30?"
8.30 for nine. Yes.
"Gentlemen, to bed,
for we leave at 8.30 for nine
"and we rise at just after daybreak,
7.30, so just after daybreak.
"Gentlemen, to bed for we
leave at 9.30 on the dot."
"On the dot." Do you want
to have a run, sire?
Yes. Just to loosen up, sire. Yes.
You know the other thing they
never say is, "Right, well,
we'd better make a move.
"I want to get back in daylight,
we'd better make a move".
"To bed. Tomorrow we rise.
"We leave at ten-ish."
"But now, to bed, unless
you are one of those people, like me,
"who finds it very hard to get off
after he's eaten cheese, in which
case stay awhile by the fire,
"talk of battles past and old
and then and only then, sire,
go thee to bed."
"And sleep well." "Sleep the
sleep of a thousand martyrs".
"Sleep well, my brother".
"Sleep well, my sister.
"Sleep with my sister!"
"Sleep well my brother, sleep
well my sister, but do not
sleep with my sister."
"Leave my sister out of it, all
right?" "Leave my sister alone."
"Don't touch her." Gentlemen, to bed,
for at daybreak I will..."
Breakfast. "We will breakfast".
"Sire, sire... Yes.
'tis a continental breakfast.
"Twill only take 20 minutes max.
"Thank you, Brother Rob."
Brother Rob? Don't call me
Brother Rob. I'd be Brother Jed.
Course, you won't. No, no,
no, no, in Rob Roy...
Liam Neeson in a kilt.
Of course you could be called Rob.
SCOTTISH ACCENT: "Tomorrow
we shall have breakfast.
"We shall rise at nine and
we shall head off tomorrow morning."
"Thank you, Brother Rob,
and let me say this...
"Look into my eyes...
"You are my brother and you sound
a bit like Billy Connolly."
AS CONNOLLY: I know. I know.
I can't help it.
AS CONNOLLY: "Gentlemen, to bed,
for tomorrow we rise at daybreak."
"We rise at daybreak."
Why do they do that?
They always rise at daybreak.
THEY SING
Bah-bah-bah-do
Ba-bop-be-doo
La-la-la-la
Bop-be-do-be-do-bah-bah-bah
Bah-bah-bah
THEY CONTINUE TO SING
Their expressions would really
match their kind of "do-be-do bo
ba da wah wah..." Yeah.
Big open happy faces.
It was nice.
A very uncynical kind of music.
I miss it, I really miss it.
Hello. Hey, are you all right? Yes.
This is Yolanda, the photographer.
Hello, Yolanda.
And Rob, this is Yolanda. Hi.
Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you.
Hiya... Hi. How are you, all right?
I'm very good. Are you all right?
Don't do that. Oh. That's very
funny, yeah. There's been none of
that on the trip.
Heavy petting. Heavy petting, but...
We draw the line. Yes.
Pass the time somehow.
Yes, but no penetration. Very good.
OK, it's just up here. OK.
And I've looked at all
the rooms and yours is the nicest.
Good, good. Yes. What's...
What's Rob's room like?
It's nice, it's nice.
It's not as big as yours,
but yeah...
Great. There you go.
Oh, very nice.
All right, isn't it? Very beige.
The bathroom's through there,
there's like a little study area
and yeah, it's all right.
Great, great. Right.
Listen, have I met Yolanda before?
I don't know.
Maybe before my time, maybe?
We need to get some sort of
a system going
about who I've met before,
and who I haven't because... Right.
They remember meeting me
so it can get embarrassing.
Do you want me to ask her?
No, don't ask her. OK.
Just see if she mentions anything.
Right, OK.
So, is this all right? Look OK?
Yeah, you look nice. You look like
that guy off Top Gear.
What? What, Jeremy Clarkson?
No, no, no, the other one.
What, Richard Hammond? Yeah, yeah.
That's worse. Well...
Check on table four.
One goat's cheese, one brie.
Just got a little
amuse-bouche for you to start.
I didn't know what an amuse-bouche
was until I started doing this.
Why have you changed?
You've changed, haven't you?
Yeah. Yeah, well, I wasn't...
I thought it was good.
Really? You looked like
Richard Hammond from Top Gear.
Have you been talking to him?
I didn't say a word.
I prefer those colours
for the picture.
The shirt was trying too hard.
Like Richard Hammond.
One pig's cheek, one scallop,
followed by halibut and a chicken.
We've got some seared pan-fried
scallops with roast
cauliflower puree,
pickled cauliflower
and caper and mushroom.
Thank you very much. It looks lovely.
It does. Before we start, can I just
say, I'm undecided on the froth.
I... Have you had a lot of froth?
Well, his life is full of it!
I've built a career of it. Right.
It's part of the zeitgeist.
Yeah. The culinary zeitgeist.
It's good. It's nice. Delicious.
So how has the trip been so far?
Rob?
AS RONNIE CORBETT: I can honestly say
it's one of the most enjoyable
periods of my life.
Yolanda, you know who that is?
No, I don't.
You see, ah well, she wouldn't
because she's from another country.
I don't either.
Of course you know who it is!
And under 35!
I don't mind you not knowing it...
I'll never forget the day,
there I was with Ronnie Barker...
Oh, OK. Only because you said
Ronnie Barker...
Who is it? Ronnie Corbett.
Oh, OK. Is that the man that
does this dancing programme?
AS FORSYTH: No, it's not the one
that does the dancing programme.
That's Bruce Forsyth.
That's the one that does the dancing.
That was lovely, my love, we liked
it, that was my favourite.
OK, ready, who's this?
AS TONIOLI: I love it. It was fast,
it was furious, it was sexy.
Nine!
Now I don't even know what you
were doing.
Know who it is? No.
Mr Bruno Tonioli.
I used to work with him. Did you?
He taught me how to walk
like a woman.
He said, "Steve, you've got
the technique, I want you to walk
and forget all I've told you,
"just walk along and I want you
to think to yourself,
'I want you to fuck me'".
And then he said, "I'll be back".
Because you were doing
Arnold Schwarzenegger. Right, oh.
I want you to dance like you mean it.
Last week, I love your dance, but
this week it's all over the place.
Three. Come to California.
Oh.
OK, who's this? She was only...
She was only 15 years old.
She was only 15 years old,
she was only 15 years - listen
to the sound of the voice. I'll
give you a clue, it's not a Muppet.
That's all I'm saying.
She was only 15 years old. You're
a big man but you're out of shape.
Right, but nowadays his...
This is how he sounds now,
the voice has gone.
Shall I prepare the Batmobile,
Master Wayne?
That is how he talks now.
I've just been to do an Italian Job
with Hannah and her Sisters.
On the way, I had a bit of a Zulu,
so I had to pop to the loo
and then, then,
I, I...
Not a lot of people know - you know
that? It sounds so familiar...
He's an international star.
The thing is, is it an actor?
Yes. No, he's the man who
comes and does my boiler(!)
Yes, he's an actor. He might as well
be the guy that comes and does
your boiler!
No, because if he is an actor,
in Spain they dub the films,
so I really... Oh.
Are they? OK.
What, they dub the films?
WITH SPANISH ACCENT:
Here we go...
Not a lot of people...
That's not my accent!
No, it's not.
No, no, it's a rough approximation.
Do you like that racist generalised
interpretation of Spanish?
Oh, that is not racist!
You're such an arse!
Right, ready, here's a clue.
My name is Michael Caine.
Oh, OK. Who is it?
Oh, my, yes, it's Michael Caine.
Michael Caine!
Hooray! Wow, yes. Yes.
Rob's was a very entertaining
version but I don't think, I don't
think it was as accurate as mine.
She was only 15, she was only
15 years old. You're getting
Michael Cained on stereo.
She was only 15 years old.
You're only supposed to
blow the bloody doors off.
She was only 15 years old.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I do recognise him now.
Excellent, let's move on. Good.
Where's that halibut garnish?
So you're Spanish, Yolanda? Yeah.
Where in Spain? La Mancha.
Oh. Oh, man of La Mancha.
A woman of La Mancha. Yeah.
Photographer of La Mancha.
That's right.
Who's this... Whaddaya ya got?
Whaddaya ya got?
I'm in the dark, every day.
Who's that?
I don't know. Is there a condition
in Spain of autistic impressionist?
Right, mains away. Four halibut.
For this next course for you
we've got the wild fillet
of halibut with potato espuma,
mussel chowder and some mussels.
Thank you very much.
Takes a very confident
restaurant to serve a dish
that has the word spew in it.
Yeah. "Then we have a vomit of
vegetables." The word drizzle I
always find slightly disconcerting.
Mmm, yes. Yolanda, do you think
you'll take the photographs round
the table or...?
Yeah, I thought so. Yeah?
Are you going to pretend
you're with Mischa?
Well, no, I can't do that,
she's not here so...
If you want me to be in the photos,
I'm quite happy to.
You'll look like you're
eating on your own.
It would look strange.
I'm worried about the Rob
thing, either A, if I'm with Rob,
they'll think there's some...
Homosexuality. Homosexuality.
I think you're safe.
The other issue is it's like kind
of Tweedle Dee and Tweedle Dum.
He very much shies away from us ever
being thought of as a double act.
Talking about the work, how is
the writing going?
Well, it's... He's not writing
it in the traditional sense.
Rob's helping.
My secretarial skills.
You're writing as well, though,
aren't you?
Well... That's a no. Yeah, no.
You could use Boswell and Johnson
as your role models. Yes.
Yeah, they did a tour of
the Hebrides together.
Mmm-hmm.
Johnson said funny things
and Boswell wrote them down.
Who's who?
Well, who's done more of
the writing?
C'est moi.
OK. So I'd be Johnson.
I've also, though, said a high
percentage of the funny things.
To be Johnson requires a certain
levity, an air of academia... Ah.
...that you would not be able to,
with the greatest respect, fulfil.
Steve's reference to my five
O-Levels. Is that all you got?
Two the first time. Took me another
two years to get up to five.
Do you know what? That's
the missing piece of the jigsaw.
Now it all makes sense.
How many did you get?
Well, yeah, nine.
That's pretty average.
Yeah,  I know it's average,
but you're well below.
Many, many great creative minds,
though I say it myself,
were very poor academically.
Anthony Hopkins, "The teacher
would say 'two and two is four,'
"it was like a foreign language."
I'm doing Anthony Hopkins.
He has to announce them now
because she's not going
to recognise any of them!
Five minutes. Four venison gourmand.
Thank you. Thanks.
Thank you very much.
That's your main course for you.
We've got a roast saddle of venison
with some wild mushrooms, a parsnip
puree and some creamed cabbage.
Lovely, thanks. Thank you.
You could also be a modern day Don
Quixote, wandering around the north
of England, tilting at restaurants.
Yeah, chasing sheep.
Rescuing maidens.
Rescuing maidens from sheep.
Rescuing sheep from Rob.
It's because I'm Welsh, you see.
Yeah. Yes.
It's not racist when he does it,
that's the beauty of it.
If I go "tha-tha-tha," that's racist,
but if Steve talks about Welsh people
shagging sheep, it's just nice.
Rob could be your Sancho Panza.
He was the servant though.
Yeah. Wasn't he?
No, he was with his friend who took
care of him, made sure he didn't
get into trouble.
That's more her job.
Yeah, that is more me, really.
So if I could just
introduce the cheese for you.
Please do(!)
Hello. Hello!
I would suggest you start off
with the Wigmore
which is a ewe's milk cheese from...
Are you saying we have to
eat them in this order? Why?
Not necessarily, it's just
a suggestion. Oh, OK.
If you eat a strong cheese
before a mild cheese,
you can't quite appreciate
the flavour of the mild cheese.
That would be accurate.
Thank you very much.
Do you have much cheese in Spain?
Where do the Spanish stand on cheese?
We have lots of cheese. We have
Manchego cheese, which is...
Pardon? Manchego cheese.
Manchego cheese.
Which is the most famous.
Sounds like an actor.
Antonio Banderas and Manchego Cheese
in The Assassin.
I think if you had a Spanish accent,
you would be Manchego Cheese.
"Welcome, Manchego."
"It is good to be here.
You know, for me, I make a lot
of comedies but now I like
to do a little bit of drama.
I said to myself, "Manchego Cheese,
what are you doing with your life?
"I talked to Antonio Banderas,
he talk to me, he said, 'Manchego,
"'Manchego, we like your comedy,
Manchego, we love the cheese'".
That looks absolutely wonderful.
Oh, wow, thank you very much.
The rhubarb's very pink.
Yeah, it is.
Sometimes it's a big green.
It looks like they've dyed it.
Yeah, they've gone...
It's like a crab stick.
Do you know what tells you
this is good? We're not talking.
No, that's true.
Yes, that's true. Yes, yes. Yes.
You should eat this more often, Rob!
I was thinking, I could take
the photographs up in the hills.
I saw a place when I was coming,
very nice.
OK, yes, sort of lone walker? OK.
"I wandered lonely as a cloud."
Yeah, although it sounds
a bit like I'm lonely.
Are you going to change your clothes?
Again. Well, actually, um...
I wouldn't wear that on the hills.
I've got proper walking gear.
I've got, you know, crampons...
AS ALAN PARTRIDGE:
I like to go for a nice ramble...
Lynn, Lynn, where are my crampons?
Why have you brought tampons?
That's not what I said!
No, you fool, crampons.
That's good. You could have written
for the show,
because it's so up there
with your best stuff(!)
I'd love to quote your stuff back at
you, but I just don't know any. No.
Odd, because you were executive
producer on a lot of it.
And I still don't know any. You
never were that attentive at work!
So this is it,
it's kind of, you know...
Nice. Yes, whatever. It's creamy.
If you like cream,
then you'll be happy.
OK, there's just a little
seating area there and... Mm-hmm.
Bathroom.
Wow. It's very nice.
Don't know why I'm telling you.
Petit fours.
Why are they called petit fours?
Little oven.
Fours is French for oven. Ah.
Yolanda...
Have we met before?
Yes, we have. Oh, OK.
It was five years ago,
it was for a shoot for Time Out.
Right, and did we do
something afterwards?
Yes, we did. OK.
You don't remember?
No, I do remember. How are you?
I'm OK, I'm fine, yeah. Right, good.
Listen, I think I'm going to have
a line. Do you want one?
Er, coke? Yeah. No, no, no.
Do you mind if I do?
Oh, no, oh, no, please. OK.
There's a bathroom there
with lots of marble.
OK, all right. Thank you.
They're picking clothes.
He's probably wearing
the crampons now, halfway up.
He's up the side of the wardrobe.
"What do you think?
"Does this look good?" Like Tom
Cruise in Mission Impossible 2.
Yolanda? Mm-hmm?
I mean, this is kind of outdoorsy...
Little bit of the Shackleton thing.
It's a bit too bright. This is what
I would wear if I was genuinely
out walking.
OK. The red's just for
safety reasons, you know? Mmm.
But I've got darker stuff,
that's fine.
OK. You're sure you don't
want one? No.
No. No.
Are you sad not to be
in the picture?
Tiny bit hurt that he didn't
want me to, but I'm only saying
that because it's you. Yeah.
I'm not at a level that
any human could notice.
Only dogs could detect my hurt.
Dogs like me.
Yes and you're not...
AS HUGH GRANT: If you were a dog,
then I should be very happy
for you to, gosh, to curl up
in my basket and chew my bone.
That sounds, yeah, sorry.
It's all right.
A rather clumsy invitation to, uh...
Yes.
Where's Elizabeth when you need her?
Yeah. That's nice.
Casual but elegant. Good, suits you.
Great. Yeah, I like this,
by the way, this... Oh, thank you.
Fish. Nice. Fish. I love fish.
Good. Um...
Was that the last of the coke?
No, it wasn't. I've got some more.
Mmm.
If you want to?
No, I don't want any, just want
to know that there's...
Just want to, just...
just information. OK, great.
Think it would be nice with
the mountains behind you and...
Yeah, what about the viaduct?
That's beautiful.
That's Victorian engineering, that.
I think the pork belly made
me a little...um... Amorous.
Did it? Yeah.
Pork belly will do that.
Pork will do that to you.
AS HUGH GRANT: I shan't start doing
that voice again,
or that's where we...
That's where trouble... Yeah.
Don't, because then I'll pull
out my terrible Liz Hurley.
"Oh, Hugh." Terrible, you see,
that's why I'm a PA.
It is terrible indeed, yes.
It reminds me of the kind of place
where, like, Wuthering Heights.
Oh, Wuthering Heights? Heathcliff.
Yeah, no, no, that's not
far from here. Oh, really?
Yeah, it's the Yorkshire Moors.
That's, yeah, at a place
called Haworth, that's... Oh, OK.
Wuthering Heights. So do you think
I could play Heathcliff? Definitely.
Yeah. I'd have to be more like...
I try to play, I think he's,
you know, he's interesting.
Very interesting.
Kind of cruel. Mm-hmm.
Cruel but...I don't know,
compelling, I guess.
There is something
very attractive about him.
Yeah. I think I'm a little old
to play him but I'd like to.
And there's the bill, please.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
How much is it? Expensive?
Good Lord, yeah.
Ah, well there's four of us, £388.50.
That's four,
so what's that per person?
Oh, that's just under
a hundred quid a head.
A lot of money. It was nice, though.
They've been quite a while
taking the photos, haven't they?
Yes, yes.
He'll probably be sucking in
his chin, I would imagine.
He does this.
SHE LAUGHS
What is it you're supposed to say
every time you have your photo
taken? Prunes.
Prunes. Prunes.
Yes, that's very Heathcliff.
So this is OK? My chin's OK? Yeah,
your chin, it's absolutely fine.
He's an odd man, isn't he? He's got
a big sense of fun when it comes
to trying to procure ladies.
When we were at Whitewell... Yeah.
He might have told you this,
he probably didn't.
No. We ended up,
I ended up singing in the bar.
I sang Delilah in the bar. Did you?
Yes. I sang it rather well. I bet
you did. I'm sorry I wasn't there.
# Saw the light on the night that
I passed by her window, la la la. #
HIS MOBILE RINGS
What's that? Sorry, can I take this?
It's my American agent. Sure. Hello?
'Ste-eve Coogan!
'Hey, man.' Matt, how are you doing?
'I'm doing good. What's the weather
like in Ste-eve Coogan land?'
It's...frigging cold.
'It's hot in Hollywoodland.'
Yeah, I know, I wish I was.
'Listen, listen, cut to the chase.
'You have got co-lead in
a drama series. It's called,'
let me give you the info here,
it's called,
yes, it's called Pathological, OK?
You play a pathologist,
so it's part of a pilot season,
'you've got to be back here
for the pilot season in four weeks.'
It's a seven year commitment
if it goes.
So if they pick it up,
I've got to do seven years?
'If it goes, it's seven years. If
it goes, you're a household name.'
He was being the mystery man.
Ah. That's what he does.
Do you know about this, yes?
He likes to send me forward and
then he holds back as the mystery man
and what happens is they wonder
what he's like.
Was that good news? Kind of. They've
offered me a lead in a drama.
Oh, wow! It's nice to, you know,
get an offer like that.
Absolutely. That's just fantastic.
I'm just worried,
my chin's OK, right?
Your chin is absolutely fine.
# She stood there laughing
# I felt the knife in my hand
# And she laughed no mo-r-r-r-re
# My, my, my Delilah
# Why, why, why Delilah?
# So before they... #
It's awkward, isn't it?
Oh, I misjudged it twice.
Just a smidge. Yeah, sorry.
No, it's...
No, I thought I was, I could
have sworn I was getting a signal.
Oh, don't pat me on the shoulder,
that makes it worse. You're
doing it again, you're patting.
Ah, this, I really don't know how
to go from here to sitting back down.
Just like a plaster, off.
Look at that.
Oh.
I wonder where Steve is.
It's beautiful.
You know, if you ever want to see
the Bronte sisters' house...
Uh-huh.
...it's not so far.
If you want to go visit,
I'll take you there.
Oh, thank you.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk