Do you think a hundred grand's enough?
I don't know.
It's not like they gave me a price list.
Who knows what a lung costs in Mexico?
I maxed out our credit line.
It should be in the bank in the morning
in case we need any more.
I'll check in the morning
to see if the funds are in.
What are we doing, Diane?
Where are you going, daddy?
I thought you were supposed
to be asleep already.
I was waiting for you to kiss me goodnight.
I'll kiss you goodnight.
Come on, I'll take you to bed.
-Say goodnight to your mom.
-Goodnight, mommy. I love you.
'Night, honey, I love you, too.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Ruiz? You have an attorney's visit. Let's go.
(RUIZ SPEAKING SPANISH)
TRANSLATOR: He's six years old and he was
in that house for three-and-a-half hours.
PAU L: Mr Ruiz, there's no physical evidence
your son was molested.
(SPEAKI NG SPAN ISH)
What evidence?
He's my son. I saw it in his face.
So you loaded your shotgun
and went over there to shoot him?
-Yes.
-And you claim
you were defending your family?
(TRANSLATOR SPEAKING SPANISH)
Si.
Yes.
Yes, my family.
I was trying to protect my son.
REPORTER:
Why is the State prosecuting Mr Ruiz
when his son was molested
by Andrew Pechinsky?
Allegedly molested. Mr Ruiz should have
gone to the police with his allegations.
Instead, he chose to go
to Mr Pechinsky's home and shoot him.
Wasn't Ruiz just protecting his son?
-Isn't Pechinsky a convicted sex offender?
-We do have laws in this country.
Mr Ruiz broke them.
He put Mr Pechinsky in a wheelchair for life
and the State's charging him
with attempted murder.
-Yes, but in light of the fact...
-That's all. We're done.
Hey, Paul.
You crawl in from the loading dock?
I didn't want to bust in
on your little media circus.
You didn't want to be seen with me.
-Good morning.
Paul, look. You know, this case you got
is fucking suicide.
You think so?
Maybe we should take
Pechinsky out and stone him.
There'd be no shortage
of Latinos to help you out.
You're talking about the Latino vote.
You're not going to get elected
in this state without them.
-Can I sleep with you, daddy?
-My goodness, you're getting so heavy.
That's because I can't play soccer any more.
You will. There you go.
Mommy and I watched you
on TV today, daddy.
Oh, yeah?
You were way too serious.
You should smile more, daddy.
There you go.
Good night, pumpkin.
Chloe's right. You should smile more.
(CHLOE GASPING)
Chloe! All right, baby, sit up! Come here!
Give me this!
It's empty! Get more! It's empty!
(CHLOE COUGHING)
Daddy's gonna get you the medicine. Okay?
-Come on!
-I'm coming!
Daddy's gonna get you some
medication. Okay?
All right, honey. Here we go. Just one!
Come on, honey. Just one, just one.
Okay.
How is she?
Well, I gave her a mild sedative
to sleep through the night.
But I am concerned that her scar tissue
is restricting her breathing.
Especially when she gets agitated or excited.
We're trying to keep her as calm as we can.
I know.
But these episodes
are happening more frequently.
Her lungs are in danger of collapsing.
Come on, honey. A little bit. A little bit more.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
-You gonna be okay?
-Yeah. I'm fine.
-I've been eating on my own for years.
-I know.
Finish the juice.
-Hello.
-PAUL: Hi.
-Hi.
-Did this number come up on the caller ID?
-Yes. Is this the hotel?
-No, it's a new cell phone.
So, if you need to reach me, call this number.
Okay. Have you heard anything?
No, I just got here.
Let me talk to Chloe, all right, honey?
Okay. I love you.
Call me as soon as you hear anything.
-Daddy wants to say hi.
-Hi, daddy.
Hey, pumpkin. How are you feeling?
-Okay.
-Take care. I miss you.
I miss you, too, daddy.
-Buenos dias. Habla usted ingles?
-Si.
-Yes.
-Okay.
I'm looking for Dr Navarro.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Do you know if a Navarro has worked here
any time in the last seven years?
It's very important.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Has a Dr Navarro ever worked here?
No one with that name has worked here.
Did he try the Hospital Angeles Juarez?
She's been here working for 20 years
and said Navarro's never worked here.
But you might try
the Hospital Angeles Juarez.
Here's my name and number.
If you know of anyone
who might of heard of him.
You forgot your money.
It's vital that I find him.
I'm sure. But there's no Dr Navarro here.
Buenos dias, senor.
Buenos dias.
Do you have a Dr Navarro who works here?
Maybe if I leave my phone number.
Thank you.
I don't need to sign in,
I just have a question about Dr Navarro.
Okay.
I just really need to get in touch with him.
Here's my number, okay?
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
An American came by looking
for Mr Navarro.
Sammy?
Sammy, get back in your seat.
-Mom, I dropped my game.
-You can get it when I stop.
-I got it.
-Now put your seatbelt back on.
(SIRENS APPROACHING)
PAUL: So, the boy was at your place
for three-and-a-half hours?
-That's right.
-And you made no sexual advances.
No. We played video games. Kids love that.
Mr Pechinsky,
you're a registered sex offender.
You're not supposed to be hanging out
with your neighbour's kids.
The son of a bitch shot me.
Have you ever had other minors
in your place?
What the hell? What's with the questions?
I'm in a wheelchair for life. Piss in a bag.
You're supposed to be defending me.
I'm a prosecutor and you're a witness.
And I don't give a fuck where you piss.
I'm required to ask you
some difficult questions.
Your son was Type O.
He's a universal donor.
His organs can save many lives.
DIANE: Paul, we just found out
we have a possible donor.
A good match for Chloe.
But UOOS already
has a recipient in Salt Lake City.
I need you to help convince them.
I'm on my way.
Cancel my meetings for the rest of the day.
The blood work's a match.
The weight is a match.
The tissue typing is spot on
with a 3% margin of error.
The lungs are scheduled to go
to a recipient in Salt Lake City.
That's way too far.
It's going to take too long.
Excuse me.
My daughter can be here in 15 minutes.
I'm sorry, Mr Stanton.
The boy in Salt Lake City
has a higher ranking than your daughter.
Please! Mr Stanton, this is a restricted area.
You know you're not allowed in here.
Chloe's LAS ranking is 91.2.
Isn't that enough?
They've been waiting for over seven months.
You have a viable organ
and a local recipient.
If you try to ship these lungs
across the country
you're not helping anybody.
There are 98,000 people
on the transplant list, Mr Stanton.
2,100 of them want lungs.
A hundred and ninety-eight
from the Region Five alone.
Every case is exceptional.
Excuse me.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
-Hello.
-Is this Frank Wells?
-Yeah. Who's this?
-You're looking for Navarro?
-Go to Clinica Cruz Blanca.
-Yeah. Yeah.
On Avenida Jose Gorositzo.
You will find him there.
Avenida Jose Gorositzo. Who is this...
You got a problem, puto? Huh, gringo?
-I don't want any trouble.
-Then you should not kick the door.
You hear me?
Shit.
-I just want to talk to a doctor.
-You just want to talk, huh?
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
What's in his wallet?
There is no licence. Nothing. Only money.
Turn around! Turn around, puto! Come on.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
He doesn't have anything.
Not even a passport.
Who the fuck are you?
Where did you come from?
I just want to talk with Dr Navarro.
Dr Navarro, huh?
We're the bosses around here!
You talk to us!
Stop it.
You'll kill him.
You speak to us. Understand?
Go home!
After consulting my colleagues
I'm afraid they are of the opinion that
Chloe's entering Stage Four.
That's the final stage, right?
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, Diane.
Yeah.
There is a rumour that has been nagging
at me for some time
and I ran a name through UOOS.
There's only two reasons
for a patient to go off the list.
They either get a transplant or they die.
This has to remain confidential.
-James Harrison?
-James Harrison.
The James Harrison?
According to his medical information,
in 2001 he had a two-year life expectancy.
And then a few months later,
he was taken off the list.
What are you saying?
He must have found an alternative solution.
I'm sorry. Are you saying he might
have had an illegal heart transplant?
Possibly. Different countries
have different laws and resources.
We call it "organ tourism."
In China they sell the organs
of inmates on death row.
In Iran, a person can sell
his own kidney legally.
If you are in need of a transplant
and have money
there are options.
You were right, Paul.
The lungs did die
on their way to Salt Lake City.
I don't think we can depend
on UOOS to save Chloe's life.
What are you going to do about Harrison?
What can I do?
Talk to him. Ask him about the transplant.
And say what?
"Excuse me. My doctor,
who may now lose her licence,
"illegally provided me
with your medical information.
"And I was just wondering
if you wouldn't mind telling me,
"now your political career's over,
where you picked up your new heart."
This is about your career.
'Cause if Harrison actually
gave you the information,
you might have to do something that
might compromise your superior morality.
That's fucking unfair.
This isn't about my career.
It's about me not breaking the law.
Fine. You want to be
on the right side of the law?
Go defend child molesters.
Wait.
Please.
Please, I'll pay you.
-It's empty, cabron.
-I'll pay you later.
Fuck you!
Hey. Just give me my keys!
Hey.
(HORN HONKING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Let me go.
The keys, I want those keys.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Does it make you feel good, fag?
Fuck you, asshole.
Say something, idiot.
I just needed the keys.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Don't run, asshole.
You a cop?
You a cop, cabron!
Shut up!
-What the fuck are you doing here?
-I'm looking for someone.
Who?
Dr Navarro.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Any of you heard of Dr Navarro?
Tico and Chepe fucked him up.
But they didn't steal anything.
They left his wallet, keys and cell.
Do you have them?
I have the cell.
What did Tico and Chepe want with you?
I don't know. Tico, Chepe?
The guys who beat you up.
You know them? You know those guys?
-I know where they work.
-You do? Will you take me there?
Take you there? $20.
Okay, you take me where they work.
I'll pay you then.
Get in.
-Get in.
-How do I know you'll pay me, cabron?
You're the one with the gun.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Move it.
Give me the cell.
Why?
I'm gonna sell it back to the American.
I'll see you guys later.
What's your name?
Call me Jefe.
No funny shit, Jefe.
You're the only funny shit here.
You're looking for putas?
Forget about Tico and Chepe.
Tell me what you like
and I take you good places.
-Ten dollars.
-No, I...
I don't want ladies. I'm married.
Okay. To the left.
-Left, estupido, left.
-That is left.
-The other way.
-Right?
Which is right, pendejo.
Mr Harrison, Paul Stanton is in your office.
Hi, Paul. What can I do for you?
Well, I've been thinking
about the Pechinsky case.
Maybe you were right.
I don't know.
I thought you were handling it pretty well.
What would you do?
Me?
I'd get the hell out of it while I could.
You don't want to get cornered
with this case, Paul.
This Pechinsky's a scumbag.
Everybody knows that.
He got what he deserved.
Let the father do minimum time.
Get back to his family.
It's not about pursuing
the law to its limits, Paul.
It's about what kind of society
you want to raise your kids in.
Don't you think?
Huh?
I'm going to take some time off.
My daughter's not doing too well.
I'm sorry to hear that, Paul.
If there's anything I can to help...
You could make a few calls.
Find me a pair of lungs.
That'd be great.
I'll keep her in my prayers.
World famous, Hollywood girls.
I told you, no ladies.
Tico and Chepe are in there.
How do you know that?
They work here.
All right. Here you go.
Can I have my cell phone?
-Gracias.
Amigo.
This is a very dangerous place.
-Oh, yeah?
-For cars.
Oh, yeah?
If you like, I watch.
How much is it going to cost me?
Twenty to watch.
Forty, no stealing.
You come back for a little bit more or what?
I want to talk to Navarro.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Just know I'm not leaving until
you let me talk to him.
No, no.
(INAUDIBLE)
-DIANE: So, Claudia?
-Yes.
-I'll check in at 9:00.
-Don't worry. I'll call you if there's a problem.
Hey.
Hi, honey.
Hey, I think those new glasses look
really cute on you.
I look like a nerd.
A cute nerd.
-Hey.
-What's going on?
We're going to the Harrison's fundraiser.
Remember?
I thought you said you didn't want to go.
We're going.
-Isn't mommy beautiful?
-Yeah.
Thank you.
You still have to go to bed at 8:00.
Say goodnight.
You're handsome, too, daddy.
All right, get ready. We're going to be late.
All right. I guess I'll jump in the shower.
Thank you.
When Jim asked me to say a few words
he dulled the fear I would experience
by plying me with a bottle of Jack.
And offering me a twenty.
I told him I couldn't be bought.
So he offered me $50.
And I asked him if he thought I was cheap.
So, finally...
I'm sorry. Is there another restroom?
The powder room is full.
Just go upstairs through the bedroom.
While I was chasing girls,
Harrison studied at night.
Working towards becoming
the incredible man we see before us today.
Let's raise our glasses
to the worst patient I've ever had.
And the best governor we'll ever find.
Jim Harrison.
Thank you for the kind words, Henry.
Like all good Republicans,
I trust you with just about
anything in the world,
except public office.
I'm humbled by the support
and goodwill out here tonight
and I want to thank you all for coming.
I deeply appreciate it. Thank you.
So, you're Jim's doctor.
-I'm Paul Stanton. I work with him.
-Oh, yes.
I'm not surprised to hear
he's a terrible patient.
-Is he keeping you busy?
-No.
Beer, please.
I've been following the Pechinsky case.
You're doing a great job.
I hate the mob mentality.
Yeah, you're a man after my own heart.
Nice speech, Henry.
I'll have to prove you wrong tomorrow
on the course.
-No, I can't play. I'm on call.
-What a shame.
Thanks for coming, Paul.
Harrison knows I'm on to him.
He shut me down the minute
I got near his doctor.
I don't know how I'm going
to get him to talk to me.
-Maybe this will help.
-What's that?
Azathioprine. From his medicine cabinet.
-Jesus, Diane!
-Nobody saw me. I promise.
Well, he's going to miss it.
He's got plenty more.
It's like a pharmacy in there, Paul.
I mean, he's got Neoral, CellCept, Paramycin.
-Okay.
-They're all anti-rejection medications.
He needs to take one of those pills
every 12 hours to stay alive.
-Who are you?
-Where is Navarro?
You want to see him? Sit.
I just need some information.
-What are you doing?
-This is the easy way.
Or I can call your old friends
Tico and Chepe.
No, don't do that.
You do as I say
if you want to meet Dr Navarro.
Are you wearing a wire?
I'm not wearing a wire.
Let me talk to Navarro.
I'll answer your questions then.
Okay?
Please.
If you won't answer my questions,
that's okay.
You can take your time.
-Mommy!
-I'm right here, baby!
Relax, okay?
Pick up!
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
DIANE: Paul? Paul?
Hello? Are you there?
-Hello?
-So, Paul.
Paul, are you there?
Paul!
Are you going to tell me your last name?
-Paul, it's me.
-Or do you want me to make a phone call?
Calm down. It's going be fine.
It's going to be fine.
My name is Paul Stanton.
My daughter has a progressive lung disease,
and it's killing her.
She needs new lungs.
Dr Navarro's my only chance.
Please take me to him.
I've never heard of Dr Navarro.
Get the fuck off me!
Let me go.
You like men sucking your dick?
-You see that, Paul?
-We got it all on tape, puto.
-Fuck you!
-Fuck me? No, no, senor, fuck you!
I have a little Mexican souvenir for you.
Drunk American. Fist fight in a strip club.
Bouncers kick him out.
-Happens all the time.
-We got our own variation of it.
We call it "the tequila head slam."
Don't worry. The tequila, it will dull the pain.
HARRISON: Hey!
SCOTTY: Twenty bucks says
-I can pop this guy in the head.
-You're on.
(SCOTTY LAUGHING)
-HARRISON: Nice shot.
-Shit!
Who is that?
That's Paul. That's Paul Stanton.
What are you doing, Paul?
I need to talk to you, Jim.
Why don't you guys play on,
and I'll catch up with you.
-Counsellor Stanton.
-Judge.
Scotty, meet the man you almost hit.
-Paul Stanton.
-Mr Stanton.
I hope you won't be pressing charges.
Not today.
-What's going on?
-I saw your name on the UOOS list.
UOOS list? What are you talking about?
Don't insult me, Jim.
According to your medical records,
you should be dead.
My medical records?
So you've accessed private,
confidential medical records?
I could have you disbarred for that.
-Diane saw the pills in your medicine cabinet.
-What?
Yeah. For someone who acts like
he knows nothing about this,
you're sure as hell taking
a lot of anti-rejection medication.
So now you're breaking into my house?
Forget about being disbarred.
I could have you thrown in jail.
Is that what you want?
You want to get thrown in jail?
Nobody needs to know, Jim.
Huh?
Is that what you want?
What are you doing?
-What's that then?
-You son of a bitch!
What's that?
Dr White diagnosed me
and put me on the UOOS list.
About a month later,
I got a call from Juarez, Mexico.
How did they know about your condition?
I don't know. Inside information,
access to the UOOS list.
I don't know.
All I know is, they knew I had money
and was desperate.
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't know these people.
I don't know how to make contact with them.
I don't even know where it is.
Where... You know...
I mean, all I...
Look, I met the guy at the border.
I gave him 100 grand.
He drugged me and took me to the clinic.
That's how it happened.
Where do you get the medication?
Dr White. I had to come clean with him.
You got to get me in touch with these people.
You don't get in touch with them!
They call you.
Why haven't they called me?
I don't know! I don't know.
Look. I've never taken a bribe.
I've never used my position for personal...
You know. But I did break the law.
And I'm not proud of it.
If this thing came out
I guaran-damn-tee you,
it's the last thing they'll talk about.
-Give me a name. I need some...
-I don't have...
Just give me a name.
The guy who contacted me,
the man that I met at the border.
He told me his name was Dr Navarro.
I don't even know
if that's his real name or not.
That's what he told me. That's all he told me.
That's all I can give you, Paul.
That's all I can fucking give you!
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Dr Martinez.
Hurry up. Get me Dr Martinez.
Do you see how bad he looks?
Dr Martinez.
El Jefe.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Can you take a look at my friend?
He had a bad night and is out of money.
-Hector Martinez.
-Paul Stanton.
Looks like you've had quite a night.
How did this happen?
-I fell.
-Of course.
Come with me.
Jefe helped me.
-Oh, yes. Jefe. "The Boss."
-Yes.
Esperate aqui, Miguel.
Miguel?
See you later. Paul.
How do you know, Miguel?
I met him tonight with his gang.
Oh, yes. The familia.
We call them Los Olvidados.
"The Forgotten Ones."
They're street kids.
We get them occasionally
for a free meal or a check-up.
-Can I ask you a question?
-Of course.
What's the local policy
regarding organ transplants?
Why are you here, Mr Stanton?
It's just a question.
I have a friend who's waiting for a donor.
Well, basically, just like in the US.
Mexican law requires prior written consent
from the donor or the next of kin.
So it's the same ranking system as there?
Or can people jump the line here?
You're wondering if you should send
your friend down here to buy a cheap organ.
I've heard about this organ tourism.
Pick up a sombrero, some tequila,
and a kidney.
-No, it's not anything like that.
-You're done.
It's an urban myth that
body parts are for sale in Mexico.
We've got our own people who need organs
and we don't have spares lying around.
I'm sorry. I know. I didn't mean to offend you.
It's just that my friend's desperate.
You want to see desperation? Follow me.
Look.
There are countless facilities like this and
still not enough to meet the social demand.
Everyone you see is facing a death sentence.
And we don't have the resources
to save them.
If you'll excuse me, I have patients waiting.
Good luck to your friend.
Okay, okay. I'll give you your $100.
Here, Here.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
I told you I would pay.
Keep the change.
I got it.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Here's my number.
If you need El Jefe.
Okay, El Jefe.
Is that your wife?
Si, and my daughter, Chloe.
She is very beautiful.
Yes, she is.
You be careful, amigo.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
I'll be fine.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
(CHLOE WHEEZING)
Hey, hey!
-Get the fuck out!
-Open the fucking door!
-Where's Navarro?
-I don't know!
Where is he? Who set me up?
-Aguilar! Aguilar! I work for Aguilar!
-Who the fuck is Aguilar?
He owns the club!
He's the one who told us to film you.
We do it all the time
with the guys he wants to blackmail.
It's disgusting! I should... Get dressed.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
I'm sorry, Mr Aguilar.
It's fine. Thank you Theresa.
I'm Paul Stanton.
Arjento Xavier Aguilar.
Or shall I call you Dr Navarro?
You have some balls coming here.
I came here because my daughter's dying
and she needs a lung operation.
Really?
I thought you came down here
for a Turkish aperitif.
This should entertain the other prosecutors
in your office.
You know what?
You can post that on the Internet if you want.
I don't give a shit.
I just want to save my daughter's life.
It's too high risk.
We'll take our chances.
You say that now.
But what if she dies on the table?
You are part of the American justice system.
Are you going to come after us?
How am I going to come after you?
I'd be an accomplice.
I mean, come on, we both know you've
done business with people like me before.
That was different. We contacted him.
He didn't know who we were. He came alone.
And if he died on the table,
that would not have been a problem for us.
I'm not going to leave unless you help me.
Let me make a phone call.
(SPEAKING IN SPANISH)
Okay.
Mr Stanton, we're going to
make an exception for your daughter.
The price is $200,000 cash, non-negotiable.
You'll give the money to Arturo.
Here is the address.
Leave your cell phone number here
and we'll call you with instructions,
when we receive the money.
How can I trust you?
You can't.
But then again you don't
have to do business with us.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
We're going now?
There's a mule going to the house.
Wait until he gets there, then you go in.
-Get out of the car.
-I can't get out here.
Please, pull around the corner.
Now get out.
I'm sorry for what I did.
It was just a job.
What's your name?
-What's your real name?
-Carlos.
But I prefer Ines.
Well, Carlos,
do you know where that is?
This part of town is owned
by the Perros cartel.
Not even the police go there.
I need to find Arturo.
-You ever heard of him?
-No.
But you don't want to go there alone.
That place is very dangerous.
I grew up in that dump.
Okay, Carlos, you help me find Arturo.
You watch my back
and I'll try to help you get out of Juarez.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
They're here.
Give them five minutes and then we move in.
Put your hands up.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Who the fuck are you?
We're here to see Arturo.
Fine.
Who the fuck are these guys?
They said they knew you.
You fucking idiot.
Aguilar sent us.
I don't know Aguilar.
It's a mistake.
Mistake?
We better get the hell out of here.
Where are you going?
I'll kill you.
We have the wrong address.
We're leaving.
You're staying here, asshole!
What is that?
Give it to me.
Check this out.
Check the back!
Come on.
-Okay.
-Get him on the stretcher.
Grab the door.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
What's your blood type?
If Aguilar finds out you're still alive in here,
he will come after you.
Gunshot wound through the lower left back
and straight through.
-Hi, I'm Mark Sullivan.
-Paul Stanton.
Paul, can you clear the area? Thanks.
And who is this?
This is Ines.
Hello, Ines. You just hang in there, all right?
Excuse me, is Dr Martinez here?
No, he's on nights.
Dr Sullivan is covering for him.
-He's a volunteer.
-What do you mean volunteer?
We don't have enough qualified people
to deal with our situation.
These doctors come down here to help us.
Yeah, sorry, but are all the doctors
who volunteer foreign?
Yes. Dr Martinez was only the first.
He moved here 20 years ago
and started the clinic.
He's done a lot for this place,
through this organisation.
What organisation?
I'm sure you've heard of them.
Doctors Across Nations.
I'm sorry.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
-DIANE: Paul?
-Hey.
-What's going on?
-Yeah, yeah, sorry. I lost my other cell.
How's Chloe?
-We're in the hospital.
-What?
They thought one of her lungs
had collapsed.
Oh, shit.
What did Dr Rubin say?
How much time do we have?
Hold on.
I'll be right back, honey. Okay?
A week. Maybe less.
They're not doing anything here.
I've tried everything.
Then come home, Paul.
We need you here.
What the...
It's Dr White.
-What?
-Hey, excuse me. Is that Dr White?
Is that Dr White? Dr Henry White.
-I gotta call you back.
-Paul?
I'll call you back.
Dr White comes down here a lot.
Did you know him?
Yeah, I work with one of his patients,
James Harrison.
Maybe you know him. Jim?
-No.
-No?
Perhaps Martinez does.
Maybe you could give me his number
where I can reach him.
-No, I can't give out that kind of information.
-Please.
-No?
-I'm sorry, no.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Jefe? It's Paul.
Listen, I need you to find me Dr Martinez.
Did Tico and Chepe beat you up again?
No, no, but it's very important
that I find Dr Martinez.
-I need his address.
-Okay. Then you pay me.
-Yeah, you'll get your 100 bucks.
-I call you back.
You're Miguel's friend.
What are you doing here?
Yeah, I didn't realise you were connected
with Aguilar until tonight.
What do you mean?
Through these clinics, you're coming
in contact with American doctors.
One of the doctors mentions,
shall we call him "Dr White,"
that he's got a patient
who's desperate for a new heart.
Aguilar, or should we call him "Dr Navarro,"
tracks the patient down
and promises to help him.
The patient pays his money and a week later,
he's brought down here
and given a new ticker.
I got to hand it you.
It's one hell of a cover, your charitable clinic.
-Helping the poor, homeless, runaway...
-I do help the poor.
The money from those operations
keeps the clinic running.
Come in.
Juarez is the murder capitol of Mexico.
The city of death.
Everyday dozens of people die
from drugs, violent crime, traffic accidents.
Sit down.
Here in Mexico,
orphans, homeless and poor people
don't fill out donor cards.
So, when they die, their hearts, lungs,
and kidneys cannot be legally used,
regardless of demand.
Should more people die
because of such a technicality?
We don't think so.
We are firm believers
in the law of presumed consent.
You're familiar with the concept, no?
Yeah, you assume everyone's a donor
unless they state the contrary.
-Exactly.
-Right.
Some countries
have already adopted this law.
We take from those already dead...
This is not what...
This is not what I was expecting. I thought...
What did you expect?
I thought I was buying my way
to the top of the Mexican donor list.
Even if it were possible,
buying your way to the top of the list
only cheats a Mexican child out
of a life-giving opportunity.
What we're doing only cheats death.
We live in a war zone down here.
The murder rate in Mexico
is three times that of the US.
What is wrong with using dead people
to save other people's lives?
Do not negotiate with your daughter's life,
Mr Stanton.
Oh, Jesus.
How soon can you get the lungs?
Usually, within a week.
I need them tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yeah.
Only God can guarantee that.
I'll pay you an extra 50 grand.
I know that'll help a lot of your patients.
I have her information.
It's blood type and genotype,
the HLA count...
Can your daughter be here in the morning?
Hey, sweetie.
Where are we going?
We are going on a little trip.
Tomorrow, you're going to see daddy, okay?
Get in.
Let's put your seatbelt on.
Okay, lay down. There you go.
This is all I could get from the supply closet.
It'll cover your trip and a few days after.
Thank you.
Good luck.
All right, honey.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
We have a match.
I don't like doing business
with this American.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
-Hello?
-Hi.
-We're at the border.
-Good.
I'll meet you at the clinic. How's Chloe?
Hanging in there.
Thank God you got them to help us, Paul.
I love you.
Hey, honey, we're going to have to
take off the mask for a second, okay?
Let's hide it.
Hi. Thank you.
Jefe.
(GREETING IN SPANISH)
I got some money.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
You're better than the bank.
Don't get used to it.
It's the last you're going to get.
Miguel, you're killing me.
Me too.
And everybody else I suppose? Right?
See you later.
Don't leave.
You're forgetting him.
My little friend.
-Hey, what's your name?
-Camaroncito.
-Camaroncito? What does that mean?
-Little shrimp.
-What?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
I have him.
Take him out.
(YELLING IN SPANISH)
Don't touch him!
Please don't touch him!
Camaroncito.
It'll be okay.
Calm down.
We'll get you to the hospital.
(SIRENS APPROACHING)
Yeah, yeah.
Move it!
Back off! Back off!
Back off! Let them through!
Come on, come on. Give them room!
Back up, please!
Right now, right now.
-It was a hit and run. It happened so fast.
-We'll take care of him.
Back up, back up. Give them room.
We'll get you to the hospital
and you'll be fine.
What hospital?
What hospital are you taking him to?
Who called the ambulance?
Did anyone call the ambulance?
Did you call?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
We've secured a donor.
What the fuck are you doing?
What are you talking about?
Young boy. Hit and run. It's a tragedy.
But for you a miracle.
No, don't do this. Don't do this. Please.
We'll be operating within the hour.
You should join your daughter, okay?
Son of a bitch.
We have to get your daughter
prepped and ready for surgery.
-Already?
- Si, we have a donor.
-Thank you.
-Don't thank me.
Thank God.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Paul, they found lungs.
Diane, they're killing them.
What are you talking about?
The kids! They're fucking killing them!
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
What the fuck are you doing?
That asshole's following us.
I saw them run a kid down
right in front of me.
Don't tell me. I don't want to know, Paul.
You don't mean that! Diane!
We can't go back now. You understand me?
I don't care where they found those lungs.
But if we don't get one to Chloe
she's going home in a fucking casket.
You don't mean that! Diane!
You don't mean that!
Please just get those lungs, okay?
We don't ever have to
come back to this place.
Please.
Jesus! Fuck!
Pull over! Pull over!
Pull the fuck over, right now!
Where's Martinez? Where is he?
He's not here today. Sir!
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
You can't enter that area, sir.
Where's Martinez?
He's not here.
-Where is he?
-He's not here today. I told you, senor.
Shit!
You can't go in there without permission.
You're killing them!
You're fucking killing them!
-Keep your voice down.
-You set up the hit-and-runs.
And they never get investigated.
Come on, where are they?
You fucking take me to them. Right now!
Or you won't see the rest of your money.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
You're not allowed in here!
It's okay.
We only had a day. What did you expect?
You said you were only using the dead.
Ideally, yes, but sometimes
these cases require immediacy.
You pushed us.
Did you really expect a perfect match
would die within 12 hours?
How many months have you waited
in America?
Who are you to judge us?
Come on, Mr Stanton.
You knew exactly what you were doing
when you crossed the border.
The boy's going to die anyway.
Maybe not this week or next.
But kids like this don't last long in Juarez.
Another boy dying here means nothing.
But a pair of lungs for your daughter,
that's worth something, isn't it?
Do you want to do the right thing?
There's still time.
You paid for the surgery.
We can still save the boy.
But it will certainly mean
your daughter's death.
Thank you.