Good morning.
Good morning, Doctor.
Mr. Rane, would you like one last look
at your face before I proceed?
I never live in the past.
No, thank you.
I have to give you something for the pain.
There will be no pain.
Proceed.
Scalpel.
All right. You know the drill.
Be very careful.
This is Charles Rane we're dealing with.
- Where is he?
- Plastic Surgery. Third floor.
He keeps changing his face.
If we blow this,
we won't get another chance.
Move out!
What time is it?
What?
I want you to tell me what time it is.
Twelve o'clock.
Get down.
Move out there!
Stairs! Other way!
Don't move! Freeze! Don't move!
Charles Rane, FBI.
You're under arrest.
Enjoy the flight.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
You're welcome.
Listen up! Shut up! Sit!
Do as I say and nobody gets hurt.
You have the keys to the flight deck?
We're going to move there, nice and slow.
Don't make me use this.
Nice and slow.
There you go.
Real nice.
Turn it off.
Turn it off!
May I ask you what you were doing?
I was improvising
on your security techniques.
That's cute. That's real cute, Miss...?
Slayton, but my friends call me Marti.
Well. See...
...if this had been a real gun, that little
Angie Dickenson bullshit you just pulled...
...would've got your head blown off.
And endangered the lives
of all the other passengers.
I was trying to save lives.
The next time a man holds a gun
to your head on a crowded plane...
...you follow instructions.
You do exactly what he tells you to do.
Do you understand?
This is why I gave up my afternoon...
...so a former security specialist
can tell me how to obey a hijacker?
First of all, I'm not a former anything.
Second of all, I like what I do.
I get the chance to meet people like you.
I know we got a lot of information
to think about, so class dismissed.
We'll hijack you again next week.
- What the hell are you doing here?
- I'm doing fine. How're you?
What's wrong with your foot?
I appreciate you throwing
some business my way...
...but you have no right
to interfere with my class.
Look around.
This is an airline training facility.
This is not the Secret Service. Calm down.
Now you're telling me my job, too?
What she did was wrong. Period.
There was a time you'd have let her know
without blowing your cool.
It just dawned on me.
She kind of reminds me of Lisa.
She looks nothing like Lisa.
I didn't say she looked like her,
I said she reminded me of her.
- We gotta talk.
- I'm not interested in coming back.
- Did I ask you to?
- You were about to.
Don't tell me that teaching
security techniques to bodyguards...
...watchmen, flight attendants,
is what you want to do.
It's a job, Sly. I like it.
Ramsey wants to hire
the best person available...
...to head up the counter-terrorism unit.
That'd be you.
I don't want that responsibility.
I don't wanna be so good-looking, but
I deal with the hand that's dealt me.
Nobody can do the job better than you.
I knew you'd start this shit again.
Give me my check.
You want me to stop?
Just say, "Yes, I'll take the job." I'll stop.
Dammit, Sly. Give it a rest, okay?
No, you give it a rest.
This isn't about a job. This is about you.
Nobody knows better than I do
how much Lisa meant to you...
...but you gotta stop blaming yourself.
You gotta get off the sidelines
and back into this game!
I set up a lunch tomorrow
with Ramsey at noon at The Oxford.
I hope you'll be there.
I really do.
Hey, pretty boy!
You got a pretty ass, white girl.
What's her name?
Attorney Phillips.
Have you found out
where they intend to take me?
Los Angeles. But they won't say when.
It'll happen quickly.
Notify my people.
They'll know what to do.
California has a death penalty.
It's a progressive state.
I'll have to visit it sometime.
The feds' witness can prove
you're responsible...
...for two airline bombings last year.
I'm responsible for twice that amount.
I'm afraid the most we can hope for is
that I claim insanity for you.
Given your childhood history,
we should be able to make that stick.
Never mention my childhood.
Have I made myself clear?
It is the nature of man
to confuse genius with insanity.
Now...
...repeat after me.
Charles Rane...
...is not...
...insane.
Charles Rane...
...is not insane.
Again.
Charles Rane...
...is not insane.
Continue.
Charles...
...insane.
Put some of this on the fire. Okay?
Kiss.
Fine ass.
Merry Christmas, motherfucker!
Open the register. Give me money!
Shut up! Give it to me now!
Open the register! Now!
Freeze! Drop it!
Get back or I'll blow her head off!
Get back!
Get the fuck back! Put the gun down!
Put the fucking gun down!
All right. I'm putting it down.
You just stay cool, all right.
You're gonna be all right, baby.
I'm not gonna try and stop you, man.
You shouldn't have tried to stop me
the first time.
Oh, my God! Lisa!
Oh, baby!
It's going to be all right. It's not too bad.
Oh, what have I done?!
What do you know?
Here he is.
- John Cutter, Stuart Ramsey.
- Pleasure.
Nice to meet you.
Mr. Delvecchio said you might not come.
Well, Mr. Delvecchio was wrong.
Let's have a seat.
Do you know how many airlines
have been hijacked in the last three years?
- No.
- Twenty-seven.
Almost every commercial airline in
the world has had to cope with terrorism.
All except one.
Israelis have never been fucked with.
They never let them on the plane.
Do you have thoughts on this?
Unequivocally, without a doubt,
John is the best guy I ever worked with.
The annual meeting of our stockholders
is next week in Los Angeles.
I'd like to fly out a couple days early,
have a brief vacation...
...before I introduce you as...
...our new vice-president.
That is assuming you still want the job.
I'll drink to that.
When you meet this board of directors,
you should think of something really...
...you know, impressive to say
to start things off.
Maybe I'll ask them to fire you.
Actually, this isn't a good time
to start with new plans.
Just be yourself: Dignified and charming.
Sorry, sir. You'll have to go back through.
Are you carrying any metal objects?
Ever notice how the real suspicious ones
never have trouble?
Right. That's how they get on the plane.
Oh, man.
Sorry, I'm gonna have to check you myself.
It's that metal plate in his head.
An old war wound.
You can go with your friend now.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Real quick. How do you do that?
Before you get on the plane,
how do you do that?
- It's a black thing.
- I understand black things.
That's what I admire about you.
Though you were being hit on
by an absolutely beautiful woman...
...you are determined to maintain
your vow of chastity.
You'd make a hell of a Republican.
It is not necessary for you
to walk me to the plane.
It's the least I can do. We're brothers.
Have a nice flight.
I have no idea why I am so nice to you.
Look, you got me here.
Are you satisfied? Now go.
Come on, man.
Don't give me that sad-ass puppy look.
I'm not giving you that.
I'm giving you the grateful...
...deeply moved, Italian-American,
religiously inspired look, okay?
Why?
Even though you won't admit it, we both
know you made the right decision.
I'm only taking this job
to make your life miserable.
Is that right?
This is where I get back at you.
Speaking of which...
...have I got a surprise for you.
No. No surprises. What is it?
Lips are sealed.
- Your lips could be busted. What is it?
- Listen to this.
When you get to Los Angeles call me,
'cause I want to hear all about it.
Hey, are you listening to me?
Have a pleasant trip.
Sly, you don't understand...
Have a nice flight, Mr. Cutter.
FBI. Thank you.
Mr. Forget?
"For-jhay." It's French.
Monsieur Forget, you'll be in seat 5-C.
That's the aisle seat.
On the left. Thanks.
Norman, it is not polite to stare.
May I take your coat, sir? Thank you.
Any truth to the rumor that men in L.A.
Actually talk without cue cards?
They talk a lot, but whether or not
they say anything is another matter.
- I take it this is your first trip to L.A.?
- It is.
I'm Sabrina Ritchie. How do you do?
Marti Slayton.
Sabrina is a beautiful name.
'Tis a thing most wondrous
to be flattered by one of your peers.
I love the accent, too.
Between us,
I've been trying to lose it for years.
Makes me sound cold and heartless.
Now that you mention it...
Always trust your first impression.
I have a feeling
this'll be a very interesting flight.
I certainly hope so.
You taken the head count yet?
My fingers are beginning
to point as we speak.
Champagne, madam?
Behave yourself.
You won't get toys in prison.
I never had any toys. My father believed
they would warp my sense of values.
Is your father still alive?
Died...
...violently.
Two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight...
54, 55, 56, 57...
Fifty-eight, fifty-nine...
- Can I get you anything?
- Nothing right now, thanks.
Looks like I just found my next ex-wife.
Make sure all carry-on items
are beneath your seats...
...or properly stored
in an overhead compartment.
I'm Marti. If I can do anything to make
your trip more comfortable...
...please feel free to ask for my assistance.
Who needs assistance this early?
John Cutter.
He's a security specialist for the airlines.
Security?
I feel safe already.
Menu, sir?
Pardon me, stewardess?
Is that man with the handcuffs dangerous?
There's nothing to worry about, madam.
Right now, he's as safe
as this handsome little boy.
- What's your name?
- Norman.
If he tries to do something bad,
I'll shoot him.
What if he shoots back?
I also have a secret decoder ring that
protects me from bullets and spiders...
...but I left it at home.
Don't worry, I've got mine
and I'll save all of us.
Give me a smile, I might get you a soda.
If that's all right with your mom.
- Sure.
- Orange?
You got it.
Thank you.
Excuse me, stewardess,
I've had that light on for a while.
Flight attendant. If you go to your seat,
I'll bring you the peanuts.
Actually, all I want is an aspirin.
Here we go.
Hey, look...
...maybe I was a little hard on you in class
but that was for your own good.
Is this the way you apologize?
This is gonna be a long flight.
You've got that right.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Maybe you can just do me a favor?
This oughta be good.
I'm not all that comfortable on planes.
There's extra pillows
in the overhead compartment.
When anything moves faster than I walk,
I'd rather be behind the wheel.
Who'd have guessed
you're a control freak?
- You won't make this easy, will you?
- How can I make your trip more pleasant?
I just want you to check on me
from time to time. That's it.
Take your seat and I'll see what I can do.
Champagne with your dinners?
Not on duty, but I'll have some
tomato juice and I'll have the chicken.
How appropriate.
I'll have the steak.
Keep the champagne on ice.
We'll celebrate later.
Sir, this is Mrs. Edwards.
She's a frequent air traveler.
When I told her about you, she said
she'd help you feel more comfortable.
It's a real honor to meet you.
I take this flight once a month.
I have grandkids in Van Nuys.
That's just outside of Los Angeles.
Well, maybe not just outside, but hell,
Los Angeles is so spread out...
...who's to know where it begins and ends,
what's inside and outside.
Wait till I tell everyone
I sat next to you on the plane.
I watch your show all the time.
- My show?
- Never miss it.
And I love it when you do those jokes
about things that make you go, "hmmm."
- Robert.
- I need special service in first class.
I'll send it right up.
I just loved it when you told off Madonna.
Who is she to tell you
how to wear your hair?
Excuse me, I have to go to the bathroom.
I'll probably be in there a long time.
Oh, I'm that way, too.
I don't need this.
I don't need this at all.
Do you know the time?
Why? You got someplace you got to go?
How do you like your sirloin, sir?
Bloody.
Everybody, sit down!
Be quiet and you won't get hurt!
Who's in charge?
I am.
Once again. Who's in charge?
You are.
Excellent.
Quiet! Quiet! Sit your ass down!
Sit down!
What the hell's that?
Sit down, shut up or be killed!
Your choice.
Ladies and gentlemen...
...I'm afraid your in-flight entertainment
program has been cancelled.
The weapons being carried
by my staff are real.
So is their desire to use them...
...if provoked.
I'm prepared to do whatever is necessary
in order to achieve my goal.
If you do as instructed,
you will not be harmed.
If you disobey or interfere
with their activities...
...you will be shot.
Oh, man.
All right, all right.
This is your idea of surprise?
Very funny, Sly. You better be there.
No, no, no. This can't be happening.
Not now.
First this Arsenio shit, then this.
Come on, come on.
Hello. I got an emergency.
My name is John Cutter.
I need Sly Delvecchio.
I don't know how to spell his name.
D-E-L-vecchio.
- Gary's compiled those numbers and...
- There's a call for you.
Excuse me.
- Who is it?
- John Cutter.
Great.
Shit.
Cutter?
You! Back to your seat.
Please don't shoot me!
I don't want to die!
I said, back to your seat!
They've taken over the plane!
Get everybody up here
for an emergency meeting, now!
They've taken over the plane!
How many? How many?
Let's say hello to your friends.
All right, freeze!
Drop the fucking gun, or your friend dies.
I have no friends.
His name's John Cutter.
He's airline security.
I'm sure your superiors would not like you
to do anything rash...
...and risk the lives
of all these wonderful people.
Stand up! Move!
Airline personnel assume a certain risk,
it's part of the job.
But these passengers...
...they're so innocent.
What do you want?
I have what I want. I have control
of the plane and everything on it.
Must I prove that to you?
Sir...
...tell Mr. Cutter your name.
Douglas.
Cutter, meet Douglas.
Let him go.
Do you have any children, Douglas?
A daughter.
A family man.
He has a daughter who loves him.
And she, until your interference,
had a father.
Drop the fucking gun.
I loathe incompetence.
Elevator!
Who are you? What're you doing?
There's always someone here.
I just get paid to send food upstairs.
Give me a break.
All right. Look,
we got a hijack situation upstairs, okay?
I need your help. Anything.
I'm not risking my life.
You'll have to fight terrorists on your own.
Give me a knife or a screwdriver.
I think we should do exactly
what Mr. Rane wants.
Come on!
You got to go.
See if you can find something
to tie him up with.
Notify the feds and radar.
Don't let the plane out of sight!
Let me know the minute
you contact the pilot.
Notify ATC about our situation.
I want a complete passenger list.
I want it five minutes ago! Get to work!
- So what's the plan?
- Go to the avionics compartment.
Then I can override the controls
and bring the plane down.
What?! This is a jumbo jet!
I know it. But we don't have any choice.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but wasn't it you who said...
...to do exactly what the terrorists said?
He's not just a terrorist.
- How you gonna bring the plane down?
- I'll empty the fuel.
Are you out of your mind?
We could all crash!
- Exactly.
- No! I won't let you do that!
It's too dangerous! You're certifiable!
Damn it, Lisa! I'm tired of this shit!
That man is one of
the most dangerous terrorists in the world.
He has killed two people.
He will kill everybody else on this
fucking plane if I don't bring him down.
Look, I need your help.
Please.
Tell me you're good at this.
I'm the best.
Then do it.
Charles Rane,
the sophisticated British aristocrat...
...known internationally as
"The Rane of Terror."
He's linked to bombings
in London and Ireland...
...but because of his ties
to the Middle East, he's been untouchable.
Judging from the fact he killed his father,
he was a sick kid, too.
What his old man did to him...
...didn't exactly qualify him
for father of the year honors.
You let the feds put a terrorist
on one of my planes?
- They didn't notify me. Here's his file.
- They can do that?
The FBI shows up at the last minute,
takes what seats they need...
They don't have to notify us.
They're the FBI!
Jesus Christ. You'd think they'd put
an airline hijacker on a bus or a train.
Why were they taking him to Los Angeles?
He was supposed to stand trial
for the Trans Pacific bombing last year.
Guess he had different plans.
He'll have to change them again.
Why?
Cutter's on the plane.
What's the problem?
We're losing fuel.
One way or another, we're going down.
Then you'd better make preparations
to land.
Why are we going back?
- It's easier to jump off from the rear.
- What?
It's easier to jump off from the rear.
I think they're preparing to land.
- Where is it?
- Outside Lake Lucille, Louisiana.
The airfield there may not be large enough,
but it may be their only choice.
- How fast can we get a chopper there?
- Chopper? Why?
I want you there as quickly as possible.
You mean on a helicopter?
I don't want the FBI or
some country local talking to the press...
...about what's affecting this airline.
Get out there and keep me informed.
Atlantic International Flight 163.
We're declaring an emergency.
Request immediate authorization to land.
Negative, 163. We're not a commercial
airport. Suggest you re-route.
Suggestion refused.
Repeat, 163. We're not equipped
to handle an aircraft your size.
- It's too dangerous...
- Shut up and listen.
It is too dangerous for you.
See that the runway is cleared.
Call Atlantic International.
See what the hell is going on.
Call the hospital, too, just in case.
Who's Lisa?
What?
Lisa. You called me Lisa
in the avionics compartment.
She was my wife.
Was?
She was with me
when I tried to stop a robbery.
I lived.
I'm sorry.
Plan not working out...
...the way you wanted, asshole?
Don't flatter yourself.
You prevented nothing.
Although it seems
I may have underestimated you.
Dumping the fuel was quite ingenious.
At least Mr. Douglas's body
won't have quite so far to fall.
Maybe Vincent could hitch a ride with him
on his way down.
You know, Charlie,
I'm a little surprised at you.
Didn't your father teach you
never to send a boy to do a man's job?
Speaking of boys...
...our stewardess friend must be feeling
particularly unsatisfied.
Charlie, you ever play roulette?
On occasion.
Let me give you a word of advice.
Always bet on black.
Mr. Delvecchio, are you okay?
Could you please close the door?
The door is closed.
Do you want us to fly higher?
It might be a little smoother up there.
This is fine.
You better buckle up.
The landing's gonna be rough.
Let me give you a hand.
Biggest damn Cessna I ever saw!
Get somebody out on the runway.
I'll be in the tower.
Patrick, just do something.
Please fasten your seat belts.
Brace yourselves for a short field landing.
Flight attendants, take your positions
for an emergency landing.
The tower's going to need
as much assistance as they can get.
You communicate with the airline staff,
I'll coordinate rescue on the ground.
How do we get down there?
We step out. Gravity'll do the rest.
As soon as it stops, we jump.
Mr. Delvecchio,
I've got Mr. Ramsey on the line.
I guess we can't tell him I stepped out,
now, can we?
Put him through.
I just had an idea about how to use Cutter.
"Use"?
If this works you're to tell the press...
...we had a security agent on the plane
as part of our anti-terrorist plan.
If it doesn't work out,
don't tell them about Cutter.
I'll handle that. Understand?