Well, the only thing I know is
she's got a wedding ring, no husband.
We gotta find out if
the husband's around.
She have any family?
According to these pictures over here
on the table, she does.
Check with the building to see
if they have any surveillance tapes,
find out if there were any guests
in the last 12 hours
that she might have had.
- You know, her other slipper’s up here.
- Yeah?
Well, I'm just saying,
it's improbable
that somebody would wanna walk down
the stairs with one slipper.
Well, it's late at night,
she wants to go to the bathroom,
she forgets her slipper.
She's disoriented, you know?
There's only one point of impact
and it's severe enough
that she fell from a 12-foot height,
not rolling down the stairs.
You're right.
What are you on, Twitter?
Put the phone away.
I mean, it's within
the realm of possibilities
that she might have been thrown.
Right?
"Now that the apartment across
the hall is vacant
"I would like very much to discuss
purchasing it for myself.
"I don't mean to take advantage
"of Mrs. Lonnigan's
passing so quickly,
"but one must admit that the
sweet darling had a good life,
"and in fact, lived longer
than most people would actually desire. "
NYPD. Open up.
NYPD.
"Please also take into consideration
"that I first declared my interest
"over two years ago,
after she first fell ill.
"I shall await your earliest response.
"Best, Abigail Clayton. "
So, can you tell me about the tenants
that live across the hall
from Mrs. Lonnigan?
That's, um... That's Abigail Clayton.
Abigail Clayton.
Well, can you tell me about her?
Well, not...
Not really, sir.
I've actually never met her.
You've never met her?
No. I'm very sorry.
Klandermann. Yes.
Just a few more hours, actually,
is what I've been told.
Can I get a coffee?
It's unavoidable, yes.
We're so sorry for the... Yes.
It is a disturbance.
You're...
Yup. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
What were you asking me?
You were saying that you've never met
the tenant who lives across...
No. No, no, I haven't.
I've been here now...
It's been 11 years.
Oh, my.
She was in the apartment before I arrived,
yes, so we've never met.
In 11 years, you've never had any
interaction with her personally?
That's not completely true, sir.
Every day or night
at a specific time
she will pass a letter to me
underneath the door.
I'm the only one in the building
who communicates with her.
Food, clothing, you name it, I deliver it.
I leave it in the hallway,
I knock, I leave.
She never goes out. Ever.
Yeah, so, in that sense,
we have had communication, yes.
That's a little strange.
Well, this is Columbus Circle, sir.
Nothing seems strange around here.
All right,I'm gonna have to ask you
to come into the station...
Really?... after you get off.
What time will that be?
Is that absolutely...
30. I get off at 9:30.
Yeah, so...
I'm gonna go try one more time.
Miss Clayton?
Open up, please. It's NYPD.
I know you're in there.
Look, I tried to call, I...
I just need two minutes of your time.
Fine. We can do this one of two ways.
You can let me in now and I'll make it
short and sweet
or I'll come back later with a warrant
and a bunch of other guys.
And from what I understand,
you won't like that too much.
All right, fine, I'll get a warrant.
Creepy hallway.
Hello? Oh, hey.
Uh, Ma'am, I'm so sorry.
I just needed to talk to you
about your neighbor, if I may.
I didn't know her.
I'm sorry. I'm very busy right now.
Look, nobody... I'm gonna come in
here for a second.
I'll shut the door.
Look, nobody's in trouble.
I'm just following protocol.
I just needed a few minutes of your time.
You live right across the hall from her.
Right.
Wow, this is a really
beautiful apartment you have.
Is that what they teach you
in detective school?
Charm me with false praise and then
we're sitting down for coffee?
Well, if you're offering,you know,
I'd love a cup of coffee. I...
in the morning.
I came from another case,
I've been up all night.
Coffee would be great.
You cook?
- Yes.
- Are you expecting somebody at this hour?
I imagine that you already
know the answer to that one.
Okay, you got me.
That was dishonest. I, uh...
I was just trying to break the ice.
Yeah, well, I'm not interested in breaking
ice or engaging in small talk,
so I'd very much like it if you would
just get to the point so that I can
get on with my morning.
So no coffee?
How long have you lived here?
You wanted to talk to
me about my neighbor?
Thank you. Uh...
Yeah, that's right.
This is really nice.
She was old
and it's my understanding she was
sick for quite a while.
I don't know.
Well, from what I put together, uh,
she was feeling a lot better.
You know, she liked to take the stairs
instead of the elevator.
She preferred to walk
instead of taking a cab.
Hmm. Well, if you say so.
So, your concierge says that you
don't like to get out that much.
I suppose so.
Are you, uh...
What is that? Um...
Agoraphobic?
Well, if you insist.
No, no offense. You know, I suffer
from arachnophobia.
Really?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah. That's a fear of spiders.
Well, what I wouldn't do
for a shoebox full of tarantulas right now.
You're pretty witty for a lady that
doesn't get out that much.
Are you here to talk
about me or Hilary?
Hilary?
That was her name.
But I thought you
didn't know her at all.
No, Detective, I did not.
So why would you call her by her first name
if you didn't know her at all?
All right.
Are we done yet?
No. Just a few more minutes.
Um, over the last
couple of days or weeks,
were there any strange visitors
or anything out of the ordinary
that you were aware of
coming from the apartment?
No strange sounds last night when she died?
Since I don't know when she died,
day or night,
and since I've already made it clear
that I didn't hear anything out of the
ordinary coming from her apartment,
then I'd venture to
guess that we are entering
into an area of... Hmm, redundancy?
Okay, now we're done.
Thank you for the coffee.
I'm gonna give you a couple of cards.
If you think of anything,
uh, call me.
Thank you. I will.
Okay.
Hey, this is a really nice vase.
It's a little confusing,
but it's nice.
I'm sure you could
figure it out.
Her name is Justine Waters,
and she was known as
"America's little darling. "
The sole heiress of the Waters fortune,
estimated in the hundreds of
millions of dollars,
she mysteriously disappeared
17 years ago this month.
Take a look at these
home videos of Justine.
They show her at the Waters
family summer cottage in upstate New York.
As you can see, Justine is being filmed
showcasing her hula hoop skills.
At the time, she held
the world record of 14 straight hours.
Now, there's been much speculation on
Justine's whereabouts.
Theories range from her running off
with a Saudi prince
to her being a victim of foul play.
Now while the great
and powerful Phillip Waters
claimed until his
death five years ago
that he never stopped
looking for his daughter,
Justine's 17-year silence
remains the most talked about missing
persons mystery to date.
In the days leading up
to what would become
her historic vanishing act,
it was rumored that
18-year-old Justine Waters
had just become engaged to Prince Achmed
Mustafi of Jordan.
What did happen to Justine Waters?
And will we ever see her again?
I'm Jerry Penacoli for Extra.
I'm wondering if you could help me identify
this crest?
- Interesting.
- Yeah? Why is that?
Well, this could be a family crest.
This is the letter "M," correct?
Well, that was the intention.
The drawing is rough, but...
Well, where'd you find this?
I can't really tell you.
I just need to find out what it is.
Okay. I got a book in the back,
something of an almanac, so to speak.
Might be able to find a match.
How long do you think...
Oh, one second.
Yeah?
Yeah, I went through all the evidence
like you asked.
Hey, put it out. Step on it.
- Yeah, what do you got?
- Not much.
The only thing that
might interest you
are some prescription medications,
but she was an old woman.
Well, do we know who the doctor is?
Yeah, some doctor in Westchester County.
We got a name?
Yeah, a Dr. Raymond Fontaine.
Okay, one second.
Let me give you my card
and I'll just wait for your phone call.
All right, Frank.
Take it easy.
All right, thanks, Howie.
Well, the view is definitely amazing.
As you can see, we're directly
over Columbus Circle,
which by the way, is the exact point
from which all distances
to and from New York City
are officially measured.
The owner completely renovated
and refurbished the entire unit
with all the latest
and greatest amenities.
Top-of-the-line kitchen by Pedini.
There's only two units
on the penthouse level.
Twenty-four-hour doorman, concierge.
It's a full-service building.
And we are getting another offer
later today, so...
I think you guys are the right fit.
If I were you, I'd make a move.
What do you think?
I love it.
Good.
Mmm.
They rented the apartment!
How could this have happened?
I wrote half a dozen letters!
I agree, Abby, this is simply outrageous.
They haven't returned
any of my phone calls, either.
Is there anything we
can do to stop this?
I will look into it immediately.
I need to see you, Ray.
Abby, I'm busy.
I said I need to see you, Ray.
I'm in the middle of something.
Raymond! Now!
You know, the police
were here. In my home.
Of course the police were here, Abby.
And that doesn't bother you?
The police were here
because Hilary died.
She had a fall and they're
investigating her death.
You live across the hall,
so of course they're gonna inquire
if you heard anything suspicious.
Once they deduce that her death
was an accident, which it
most certainly was,
they'll have no need
to bother you any further.
One of the detectives
left me his card.
Oh.
Ray, how many wallets have I bought you
through the years?
Abigail, I'm attached to this.
It was a gift from your mother
on my first day of medical school.
I'll never part with it.
It's just that I don't
want things to change.
Okay? I just need
things to stay the same.
I just need things to continue...
Abby, Abby.
...as they have been.
This is a disruption.
Well, if change is
what you don't want,
I strongly advise
that you stop inquiring
about the apartment across the hall.
And it's sort of academic.
The apartment is leased.
And they're gonna lead their lives
just as Hilary led hers.
Not a peep.
Ray.
Abigail.
You've gotta trust me, girl.
You've gotta calm down.
I promise you,
everything ‘ll be fine.
Haven't I always been there for you?
Hmm?
And by "always," I mean for
the better part of your life.
Okay, sweetie.
Good morning, Mr. Stanford.
Good morning.
Oh, hello, sir.
Klandermann.
Mr. Stanford, if you
don't mind me saying so,
I've got this sense
that I know you somehow.
Really?
Yeah. It's as if we...
I don't know, we met
somewhere or something.
I kinda get that a lot.
I guess I just have one of those faces.
Oh, yeah?
Well, that's probably it. Huh.
Sure smells good coming out of
that loft of yours.
I'm guessing Miss Lillian’s the...
Yeah, she's the chef in the family.
Yeah.
It's amazing I don't weigh 300 pounds.
I don't understand it.
Son of a bitch!
Well, it's a little too late for that!
You started it, Lillian!
You son of a bitch!
God damn it! Why are you doing this?
Jesus!
Tell me one more time
to keep my voice down,
I swear to God...
I don't want the help to hear.
Who gives a shit?
I'm not gonna talk to you
when you're like this.
I just wanna go
inside, okay? Charlie...
You're not going anywhere, bitch!
Little slut!
God damn it, I'm going back inside.
We're gonna finish this.
Just shut up!
Oh, you don't want the help to hear!
Well, I'm paying them
enough to plug their ears!
God damn it.
You're drunk! I want to go back inside.
You're not going anywhere.
Bitch! Did you just hit me?
Is that what you did?
You don't ever hit me!
Bitch!
I'm sorry!
Don't ever hit Charlie!
Do you understand that?
Remember where you come from.
Remember, you bitch!
Miss?
Help me.
Please.
Do I call 911?
No.
I don't want him to go to jail.
You have to stand up.
Stand up!
Help me.
Shh.
It's okay.
Be quiet.
Lillian.
Shh.
Just don't let him in.
It's Charlie.
I'm sorry.
Please just open the door.
Come on, I'm sorry.
Let's just talk about this.
Lillian!
Shit. Please...
Lillian, open the door.
Open the fucking door!
Oh, great.
Mmm. Mmm.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
What are you sorry for?
I'm just sorry because you're
involved now in this.
And I didn't mean for this to happen.
Well, you needn't be sorry.
He works so hard and when he works,
he sometimes gets stressed
and when he's under a lot of pressure,
he drinks a lot.
And I think I set him off,
and I don't mean to.
I feel so bad.
Why are you making excuses for him?
'Cause you really don't know him.
He's a really, um...
Reliable guy.
Stop apologizing for him.
Stop it.
I do love him.
Why would someone kill a violinist?
This job really sucks sometimes.
Why would an 80-year-old
woman wanna jump off her balcony?
See this here?
This is how I like my crime scene.
That over there is a torso, a head,
and right down here...
Oh, God.
What the hell is that?
You see, this is what
a murder scene looks like.
What, so you don't think
this is a suicide as well?
You, my friend, are a sick bastard.
I'm just saying, nine years on the job,
it just doesn't add up.
What's interesting is
the girl across the hall.
Oh, I see what this is about.
What, she's hot?
Yeah, she was attractive.
I knew it.
No, here's the thing.
I ran her through the system, right?
Please.
There's nothing on her.
She doesn't have a social security number.
She doesn't have a driver's License,
nothing.
A woman like that, living in
Columbus Circle, with all that money?
It just doesn't make sense.
You know, she hasn't left her
apartment in years.
This is New York City.
It's a town full of nuts.
No, she didn't look crazy.
How did she look?
She looked like a victim.
Mmm...
Oh, my God.
I can't believe I fell asleep here.
What time is it?
30.
Oh, wow.
Almost nine hours.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry if I invaded your space.
It's all right.
Would you like me to pour you some tea?
No, no, no, that's okay.
I just...
I need to get going.
Thank you, though.
Oh, God, Charlie’s gonna kill me.
It looks like he already
tried to do that last night.
Does it look bad?
Do you have a mirror?
It's right there.
Oh...
I feel so stupid.
No.
I do. I just feel so stupid.
I don't even know you
and here I am dragging you into this.
It's all right.
God.
Don't. Don't.
Why don't you sit down?
I'll pour you some tea.
Thank you.
You've been so nice.
I'm sorry.
Charlie’s not such a bad guy.
I don't want you to hate him.
Well, he made a terrible
first impression.
I know.
He did.
Can I ask you a question?
Why don't you like
having any visitors?
I'm sorry, I don't mean to pry.
That's what the real estate agent said.
Well, I guess I just decided a long time ago
that I'd rather be alone.
That's not so strange.
Sometimes I just wanna run away
and be somewhere where nobody knows me
and I could just start over.
I know.
So what did you do?
I told you.
He was coming back.
So I went out into the hallway
and I brought her in.
The hall? You went into the hall?
You know, she reminded me of...
Well, you know, you were there.
And...
Well, I was...
I was just a child then and,
well, I wasn't gonna just stand there
and watch this happen.
So you called the police,
of course.
No.
What happened?
Well, when she woke up this morning...
"When she woke up"?
You mean she slept over?
Well, it was hardly
a slumber party, Ray.
She was injured
and she passed out.
What's her name?
Lillian.
Is she still there?
No.
She left.
She gonna be safe there?
I don't know.
Oh, Abby.
What are you gonna do now?
You know as well as anyone
this sort of thing only gets worse.
I don't know. It's not
my responsibility, right?
Maybe you should consider
that now that you've helped her
she'll likely come back
to you for help again.
Have you thought about
what you're gonna do next time?
No.
Gimme a mini. Yeah.
Schmear?
I just know I don't
wanna be involved.
It's a little late for that.
And Abigail, it's unfair for you
to give her refuge and solace
and then when she comes knocking again
to ignore her.
Maybe you could be proactive
and talk to her, help her.
I don't know.
Well, it's something to consider.
She's your neighbor.
You have something in common.
Maybe you should have her for dinner,
over to your place.
I don't think I'm entirely comfortable
with that idea, Ray.
Think about it.
All right.
Are you eating?
Yeah.
Bagel with a schmear.
Bye.
You really banged me up.
I'm sorry.
I mean it.
I love you.
Thank you, Bubba.
You're welcome, Miss Hart.
Miss Lillian, can I help you
with that, please?
I'm sorry! I'm terribly sorry!
Wait.
I've got it.
No, don't, wait.
You having fun down there,
Klandermann?
No, sir.
No, sir, not at all.
I was just trying to help with...
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
Let me help. Oh, good.
This...
I shouldn't see that.
It's fine.
Okay. All right. I'll get the elevator.
There we are.
I'm so sorry.
I was trying to help.
Don't worry about it.
There were just so many bags.
I didn't realize...
It's fine.
It's not all for me.
I bought you a new tie.
A new tie?
A new tie.
A new tie? Yeah...
Right here, sir?
On the counter, please.
Uh-huh.
Excuse me, sorry.
Thank you.
Everything all right, Klandermann?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Well, no.
That's, uh...
That's where I found her.
Found who?
Mrs. Lonnigan, the previous tenant.
What do you mean?
Well, that's...
I was the one that found her. Right here.
They said she fell down the stairs.
I didn't know that.
She was such a sweet old lady, too,
you know?
Everybody loved her in the building.
Always had something sweet to say
and always made everybody smile.
The whole building
loved her, really.
That's so sad.
I'd just never seen
anybody die before.
What do you mean?
She wasn't dead yet
when I found her. No.
We got a call, the tenant down below,
Henderson,
they heard a real loud...
And I raced to...
And the door was unlocked,
which is quite unusual for a building
like this, I'll tell you that. And, uh...
But it seemed as if she were still
trying to speak.
What was she trying to say?
Oh, I have no idea.
See, I'd never seen
anything and there she...
It was... It was awful, so it's all kind of
a blur now, you know.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's a shame.
I mean, I have an idea.
I shouldn't say that.
I haven't told anybody this before,
but when I found her
it sounded like she was
trying to say, uh, "Why?"
"Why?"
But it was a "Why me?
"Why did this happen to me?"
kind of "why. " Does that make
any, uh...
I'm so sorry.
I should not be here.
I'm so sorry to take up your time.
Do you need any help unloading these
bags at all or...
I'll remember how I
know you, Mr. Stanford.
I swear I will.
I'm so sorry I haven't.
All right, let me know when you do.
Sure thing.
What was that about?
He thinks he knows me.
Does he?
I don't think so.
Hi. Sorry.
This, um... From...
You're good?
Thank you.
Okay.
Please come see me
when you are alone. Abigail.
Before you moved around, you were
just in Bakersfield that whole time?
Bakersfield, California.
My mom drank, mostly to get away
from my father,
who also drank.
Hmm.
Was he abusive?
Yeah.
That's pretty much why I left,
because I couldn't take it anymore.
I was 15
and I had $7.20 to my name.
And I had fallen in love with Charlie
and he's pretty much
just taken care of me.
I couldn't...
I couldn't stay with
someone who hurt me.
I mean, we have a good time,
but I don't really...
I wouldn't really have
anything without him.
I just couldn't do it.
So what's the alternative?
Would you like some more wine?
Yes, please.
So where's your family?
My mom died.
And your father?
Oh, he...
He's dead, too.
Oh.
Were you close with them?
I was close with my mother.
Mmm-hmm.
My dad...
My dad drank as well
and he'd fly off the handle.
He'd go into these rages.
And he would beat my mother and me
when I tried to protect her.
Mmm-hmm.
Hmm.
My father could control anything.
So you grew up rich?
I suppose.
Well, I grew up in the trailer park.
Lucky me.
Do you have any brothers or sisters?
Nope.
Just me.
You?
No. Just me, too.
So how'd you disappear?
Haven't I always been there for you?
My father had a friend.
My father had a friend and he knew
how bad my father could be
and what he was capable of,
so he helped me to...
He helped me.
You know, I didn't intentionally...
I didn't set out intentionally
to not go out again. I just...
You know, I went
to the grocery store
and I'd sneak out at night,
go to Central Park.
I was always amazed
at how quiet everything was.
Such a big city.
I wanna take you outside.
There's this flower shop.
It's a block away.
I wanna take you there.
It smells so incredible
and I wanna pick out
your favorite flowers.
And then a block further
is this rare bookstore
that smells kind of musky
and it has the most incredible books,
and there's this window seating and we can
pick out some books
and read together.
I don't think I'd feel safe.
I would be with you,
protecting you.
You can't stay in here for the
rest of your life. Look at you.
You're so beautiful.
You're stunning.
I wanna take you out into the world.
You smell his lavender?
Let's see if he's in the backyard.
This is a nice house.
I should've been a doctor.
Hello?
You smell paint?
Oh, for Christ's sake.
My good shoes.
My mom's gonna have a fit.
I just painted that porch.
I'm so sorry.
We had no idea.
You must be Dr. Ray Fontaine?
Yes.
Yeah, I'm Detective Frank Giardello.
This is my partner, Jerry Eaans.
Two detectives and you couldn't figure out
the porch was freshly painted?
We're really sorry.
We were wondering if we could have
a few minutes of your time.
Sure. Would it be all right
if we spoke out here? Uh...
Oh, yeah.
That would be fine.
Yeah, we wanted to talk to you about
Mrs. Hilary Lonnigan.
Sure. What about her?
Well, I'm sure that you're aware
that she...
She passed away a couple of weeks ago.
Of course. I was her doctor.
Yeah. Could you tell
us about her health?
She'd been ill for a while.
- Oh, yeah, she was ill.
- With what?
It was in remission, actually.
Any dizzy spells, anything like that?
She never complained of any.
She did have tendencies to push herself.
She was one of those people who
didn't like standing still.
- Why?
- Well, she was pretty badly injured.
Well, she did fall
down the staircase. Yeah.
What are you suggesting?
Oh, no, no. We're not
suggesting anything.
We're just trying to find out
whether or not we, uh...
We have a homicide on our hands.
We'd like to see her medical records,
if that's all right.
Of course.
I'd need a subpoena.
Doctor-patient confidentiality.
Of course.
Why don't we do this?
Why don't I give you one of my cards...
Thank you. All right.
... and we'll be in touch.
It was a pleasure to meet you.
Yeah, it's good to meet you.
- What's your dog's name?
- Oh, this is Digger.
- Digger?
- Yeah.
All right. Thanks.
All right.
Oh! By the way,
do you know Abigail Clayton?
Uh, again, Officer,
doctor-patient confidentiality.
Oh. Yeah.
We don't want to take up
anymore of your time. Thank you.
Thank you.
You gentlemen have a good evening.
You, too.
Woah!
Stop that.
What?
Well, I didn't ask him
if she was a patient.
I asked him if he knew her.
You're doing good.
You're doing great.
Good.
Amazing, Abigail.
Abigail...
Lillian, why are we even doing this?
I don't want to leave.
We're doing this because
it's good to get out of the apartment.
You're doing beautifully.
Look at you.
That's enough, Lillian...
No, no, no.
Okay, okay.
Great.
You're doing great.
I don't feel well.
It's okay. I know.
This is far enough.
You're doing great.
I'm here for you. I'm here for you.
Abigail.
Hold the door.
Oh! I got it, sir.
I got it.
Come on in. There you go.
We're gonna at least
walk to that table over there.
No, I think... I think
we've gone far enough.
Everything all right tonight?
Sir?
Uh-huh.
Good.
I'm not ready yet.
Okay? Okay.
Okay.
Hey, this is me.
Ah...
I just remembered where I know you from.
Yeah.
One, two,
three.
Come on! There you go! Good!
Great job! Great job!
BeautifuI.
Oh, God.
You must be Abigail.
You feeling all right,
sweetheart?
Here, let me help.
Huh?
Don't touch her! Don't touch her, please!
Just don't.
Okay? Okay?
Don't, don't. Please don't.
Charlie, please.
You ladies have a good night.
Just stay here for a second.
No, no!
Please don't go in there!
Please don't!
Charlie, what are you doing?
I don't want him to see anything
in my apartment.
Stay right here.
He's violent! He's in my apartment.
Abigail!
When you get her out of her apartment,
I install some computer software
so that when she goes online,
we'll be able to get
her banking password.
Right. Got it.
Got it?
It's like stealing
the identity of a ghost.
Exactly.
She wants to remain hidden.
And after we've got the money,
who the hell is she gonna run to?
We've got her account information,
her social security number,
her signature, but we still need
to get your fake ID.
It's just so perfect.
We're talking about hundreds of
millions of dollars.
No more nickel and dime shit.
Just sunsets and mimosas, baby.
And once we get the password
we're home free.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
I love you, baby.
I love you.
Abigail, please!
What is he doing in my apartment?
You can't.
You can't follow him.
He's been drinking!
Abigail! He's been drinking.
You can't, no.
He gets really violent.
You don't want him to hit you.
You know what it feels like.
Stay here.
Hey! That's not my apartment.
I'm right here.
I'm right here. Abigail.
I wanna go home.
I live in here and
this is how I want it.
I want to be alone.
This is how I want it.
You did a great job tonight, Abby.
I cannot have people in my life.
I cannot have you in my life.
If he is in your life,
I can't...
No, I wanna be alone.
I wanna be alone. I wanna be alone.
Okay.
I'm really sorry about Charlie.
Stop apologizing.
He's...
He is dangerous and he will only end up
hurting you more than he already has.
Please go.
Okay.
Thank you so much for dinner tonight,
Abigail.
- First new message.
- 17 p. m.
Mr. Stanford?
It's Joe Klandermann.
I guess now I should call you Charlie
since we go back, huh?
Anyway, if you're having
trouble remembering me,
think back 12 years
ago to a holding cell.
Rahway Prison? Remember?
You were about to do a five-year
stretch on some con
and I was on my way
out after doing a deuce.
Good times. Yeah.
Enough reminiscing.
Meet me at the coffee shop around
the corner on 59th Street
right after I get off work.
We need to talk.
You're gonna cut me in on whatever scam
you're running, Charlie.
I don't know
what it is, of course,
but you living here
means it's gotta be big.
Yeah. Don't make me wait,
partner.
Damn it.
You're crazy attacking me!
You're a dead man!
You hear me? You're a dead...
Tonight's top story is the bizarre death
of a wanted felon on Columbus Circle.
We go now live to Diane Weiss,
who's on the scene.
Apparently, Diane, the man was strangled
before being hit by a bus?
Yes, Ginger.
Police believe the victim
may have been fleeing from an attacker.
However, the victim,
Joseph Klandermann,
whose real name was Nathaniel Muskit,
was a wanted felon.
Charlie?
Muskit disappeared nearly 12 years ago
and had alluded authorities for that long.
Charlie?
He was convicted in 1998 for running
a Ponzi scheme that bilked investors...
You killed Klandermann?
Charlie?
Charlie, we don't kill people!
Lillian.
No, Charlie.
This is the one.
This is the one we've been
waiting for, Charlie!
He could have turned us in.
I made a decision to protect us.
You made a stupid
decision, Charlie.
I don't wanna run from the cops!
You don't have to be scared. Okay?
It's gonna be fine.
It's okay.
What does that say?
He wants to see us.
Yeah.
Klandermann's dead, Ray.
He's dead.
I know, I heard.
Are you all right?
I don't know.
What am I gonna do?
They will get a new concierge.
Ray, you know I can't
trust a new concierge.
I can't trust a new concierge.
Klandermann had been here so long.
How am I gonna trust
a new concierge, Ray?
Ray, I need to see you.
I can't right now. I...
I promise I'll come by later.
Please, Ray?
I really need to see you.
I'll see you later tonight.
You just relax.
Take a long breath now.
For me, okay?
Bye.
This has gotten completely out of hand.
I understand.
No, I don't think you do.
It's all over the television.
I mean, Mrs. Lonnigan was one thing.
That had to be done.
And so did Klandermann.
Charlie?
But there was a mistake
made with Mrs. Lonnigan.
What are you talking about?
What is he talking about?
When were you gonna
tell me this, Charlie?
This is not the time
or the place for this.
Ray, what do you mean "mistake"?
There was obviously
a serious error made.
We wanted to talk to you about, uh,
Mrs. Hilary Lonnigan.
The police were here,
investigating a homicide,
not a slip and fall
of an 82-year-old woman.
I don't make mistakes.
Oh, apparently, you do.
Otherwise they wouldn't be
investigating a homicide, Charles.
Jesus Christ.
Now thanks to me, Mrs. Lonnigan lived
a long and prosperous life,
three years longer than I anticipated,
and there's only a certain amount of time
one can wait.
But this is over now.
We need to discuss an exit strategy.
No, there is no exit strategy.
We're one e-mail away from a fortune.
Charles, how long do you think it's
gonna take for them to figure out
I'm the one who owns the apartment?
That I paid for the whole thing?
It's my money!
Once they figure that out,
it's a short walk in the park
for them to put together
who Abigail is.
And what we're all up to.
We need to discuss an exit strategy.
He may be right, Lillian.
It's just a shame.
Well, if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go water my plants,
get over to Abigail’s, take out her trash,
pick up her cleaning,
and give her a foot massage
to calm her down,
thanks to you.
I guess I'm doomed to take care
of this woman the rest of my life.
What do we do?
Let me try to talk to him.
Lillian.
Please go in the house
and make it look like it was robbed.
Okay?
- Did you roll the body?
- Yeah.
Did you get the phone?
It wasn't in the house?
No.
It has all our information.
I know.
Do we walk?
No.
No. We don't walk.
We're...
We're too close.
With no money, how far would we get?
Look, we knew that
if things went wrong,
we'd have a backup plan, and we do.
Okay?
We... We have to force her hand.
We have to do it now.
It's gonna be okay.
Please! Please, I need you! Open up!
Hurry, please!
Please! Open up! Let me in!
Open the door and let me in!
He's gonna kill me, Abigail!
Please!
Please, Abigail!
Open the door, please!
Please, Abigail! Please!
Open the door!
Oh, my God! Charlie, calm down!
Calm down!
Think you're gonna leave
me? No, I'm not, I swear!
Huh? You gonna leave me?
I'm not gonna leave you, Charlie! Please!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! Okay?
No, no, no.
No! Don't you...
Bitch! Get back here!
Gimme the gun!
The gun! Gimme the gun!
I'm gonna shoot you, Charlie!
I'm gonna shoot you!
You're gonna shoot me?
I'll shoot you, Charlie!
Do it!
Charlie.
Stop! Oh, my God! Stop!
No! What are you doing?
Stop! Oh, my God! No!
No! Get off him.
Oh, my God!
What are you doing?
Charlie!
Charlie, no! Charlie, no!
Charlie, wake up!
Wake up, Charlie, my baby.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Charlie, wake up!
Wake up, Charlie!
You killed him, Abigail!
What have you done?
No! I didn't do it.
No, you did.
You shot him!
No! My baby. Oh, Charlie.
I have to call someone.
Charlie, don't leave me.
Abigail, no, you can't call anybody!
Are you crazy?
Nobody can know about this.
No, Abigail!
We just murdered Charlie.
We have to leave.
We have to get out of here.
No, no, I can't
go anywhere!
We're one e-mail away from a fortune.
I'm all alone and I don't know what to
do now and I need to go.
Please, Abigail, help me.
We need to scrape whatever money
we can together
and I need to get
out of here. Okay?
I have money.
I don't have any cash.
We can transfer
money from my account.
And once we get the password
we're home free.
I wish I could talk to Ray.
No, you can't talk to Ray.
You can't talk to anybody.
I trust him.
Look at me.
We can only trust each other now.
Okay?
Mmm-hmm.
Okay.
Really?
Are you kidding me?
You're positive?
Same guy?
So what'd you find out?
Well, I don't think that this is an "M"
you brought me, Detective.
What do you mean?
I think it's a "W."
And if it is, it could very well be
the crest for the Waters family.
Are you familiar
with the Waters family?
Yeah, of course,
of course. Yeah.
This is incredibly exciting.
Is there any chance that you could tell me
exactly where you saw this?
I'm sorry, I...
I can't do that.
I just found out
Mrs. Lonnigan's apartment
was paid for by a corporation.
Apparently, she was a nanny
for some rich family.
Guess who runs the corporation?
Who?
Dr. Raymond Fontaine.
Really? Let's go pay the good
doctor a visit. Thanks, Howie.
Anytime, Frank.
The porch was repainted.
Anything?
No.
Dr. Fontaine?
Hello?
NYPD.
I'll go this way.
Frank.
Check this out.
Ray, Ray.
It's not mine.
I'm heading out.
Why don't you go take a shower and
by the time you're ready,
I will be back.
Okay.
And then we'll take care of...
Don't go anywhere.
Where would I go?
Miss Clayton, it's Detective Giardello.
Yes, Detective?
Look, I'm not calling
with the best of news.
My partner and I tracked down Dr. Fontaine
and I'm sorry to inform you that, um, he...
he was found dead.
He's been murdered.
If you are who I think
you are, I think you're
at the center of something very dangerous.
I'm sorry, Miss Clayton.
What do I do?
Look, we're on our way.
We're gonna be there in an hour.
Don't leave and don't
answer the door, all right?
Thank you, Detective.
Let's go.
I just know I don't
wanna be involved.
I think you should
have her for dinner.
I wanna take you outside.
She reminded me of...
Well, you know, you were there.
Well, I was...
I was just a child then.
No, you can't talk to Ray.
You can't talk to anybody.
You've gotta trust me, girl.
Excuse me.
I'd like to see someone
about closing an account.
That would be Mr. Ross,
the bank manager.
His desk is right over there.
Thank you.
Giardello.
Detective, this is Abigail Clayton.
We're on our way. Is everything
all right? On your way?
Yeah, since we last spoke.
Since we last spoke?
Two weeks ago?
No, we spoke less than a half hour ago.
No, you must be mistaken. I was in
the shower. I didn't take any calls.
That wasn't you I was talking to?
No. Oh, my God.
How can I help you?
I'd like to close out an account.
All right.
You can hang on to this.
All righty.
Account closure.
Um... May I have
the account pass code, please?
Hulahoop14.
Huh.
Oh, there we go.
All right, Miss Clayton.
Everything appears
to be in order here.
Wonderful.
Now, before we finish,
I'm required to ask you a few questions.
I apologize.
It'll just take a few minutes of your time.
Justine Waters has decided
to come out of hiding.
Out of ink.
Oh, it's gonna be one
of those days, all right.
She will be at the Waters Bank,
59th and Broadway.
All right.
Were you at any time
dissatisfied with our service?
No.
Glad to hear it.
She goes by the name
Abigail Clayton and...
May I ask, what are your reasons
for withdrawing your money?
She'll be wearing a black dress.
I'm leaving the country.
Wonderful!
Are you going to Europe?
I was just in Paris
with my fiancée.
We stayed at...
Oh, God, what is the name of that hotel?
It was great. It had
these butlers in it and...
Oh, man, what is
the name of that hotel?
Excuse me.
Fellas, how's it going?
Looks like you guys got a busy day
ahead of you, huh?
Make sure you stay
hydrated out there.
Remember, only stop at the red
lights and the short skirts, huh?
Okay.
Are you all right?
Yes... Yes, I'm...
I just need to hurry.
I have a plane to catch.
Ah. Leaving things till the last minute,
huh? A woman after my own heart.
My father always says, "If you didn't do it
at the last minute,
"you didn't do it right. "
That's funny.
Yeah. He's a funny guy.
Finally, is there anything
we can do to improve?
No. You've been great.
Well, thank you.
Okay. So...
Are there any other
questions I can answer
for you before we
Liquidate your account?
Yes. Can you give me
the account balance?
Not a problem.
Seven-twenty.
720 million?
Yeah.
You want it all in singles?
Are you gonna buy France?
Oh, my God.
720 million.
You are a card. No, $7.20.
So did you want that
in a cashier's check?
$7.20. Is that...
Is that not accurate?
I had $7.20 to my name.
Miss Clayton, are you all right?
Psst.
What are you doing here?
I left.
I couldn't stay there anymore.
You made sure of that.
Can we go someplace and talk?
I don't think there's
time for that, Abigail.
I made some phone calls.
Phone calls?
Yeah.
I called a whole
bunch of people.
I mean, you've been in
hiding for a long time.
This is your big
coming out party, Abigail.
Why do you keep
calling me Abigail?
That's what you told the man your name was.
Didn't you?
That's what you wanted to do.
Steal my life, look like me,
steal my money.
Or maybe it's Justine.
I'm sorry.
I have so much to tell you.
Gee, I don't think
we have much time,
so I hope it's
not a long story.
Please.
There's gotta be another way.
You should leave.
Go.
Oops.
There's a body in your apartment.
Black dress,
black dress.
Excuse me! Excuse me,
are you Justine Waters?
Go away! No!
Where to?
Kennedy Airport.
What's all that about?
They just found that girl,
Justine Waters.
Oh, no kidding.
No bags?
No baggage.
So where you going?
Someplace safe and warm.
Ah. Safe and warm.
I always wanted to go there myself, ma'am.
No, not... Not "ma'am. "
You can...
You can call me Lillian.