All right.
Toast time.
Um, this is,
amazingly enough, to us.
Five incredible,
incredible years.
Cheers.
Come here.
Brendan, we're leaving
in five minutes, sweetie.
Samuel.
Yeah?
Do you want more?
No, thanks.
No. I've had lots.
No. Not lunch.
I mean
more for us.
By which you mean
the big '' M''--
Marriage, huh?
Well...yeah.
Um, I'm over 30,
and I feel like
something's missing.
O.K. Well,
you know, what?
What could possibly
be missing?
Let's look at that,
because, you know,
we live in
a fantastic apartment.
My practice
is really good.
We get on better
than most married couples.
Sure.
Life is dangerously close
to perfection actually,
so, uh, why would you
want to change things?
Why change
what's perfect?
Yeah?
Right.
O.K.
Uh, new toast.
To stability.
Honey!
Oh, God!
Shit, honey.
I hit a guy. Come on!
Are you all right?
Excuse me, ma'am.
I know CPR.
Aah...
O.K.
You're conscious! I thought
you were French kissing.
I was trying to scream.
Don't get up.
He's all right.
It's under control,
madam. Thank you.
Does your head hurt?
Yes.
Are you nauseated?
Very.
Open your eyes!
Wide! Wide!
Aah!
Your pupils
aren't dilated.
You're O.K.
I brought you back!
He's O.K. Let him up.
All right.
Whoa. Sorry, buddy.
No. Careful.
No lawsuit.
Good. No lawsuit.
Yeah. Marty Dwyer.
Yeah.
Samuel Faulkner.
How you doing?
Good to meet you.
A big wind
came along and bam!
Cracked you
on the noggin,
but I guess
you know that.
Kids, stop that!
Your manners.
There's plenty.
Help yourselves.
This sucks.
It tastes like poo!
Oh, bloody hell.
What did I say about spitting
in people's food?
Oh, please.
Here, eat this.
Eat that, honey.
You know, I know you.
I don't think so.
You're Sean's friend,
the kiddie, you know,
shrink.
Yes. I'm a psychotherapist.
Like some help
with your children?
I met you last year
at Sean's loft.
I'm his sister Gail.
Oh, hi.
I'm Rebecca.
Nice to see you again.
Look, I'm sorry.
That's beluga.
It's $64 an ounce.
It's not dog food.
I'll write you a check.
No, it's fine.
It's just...
O.K.
Kids,
say thank you to the man
for the nice cheese
and give him
a big hug!
Thank you!
Pleasure.
Kids, break it up.
We got stuff to do.
Have a little bit.
Just a bit.
No. Come on.
Come on, Sprinkler.
Let's go.
Hope we didn't ruin
your picnic.
No. Why would you
think that?
Take it easy.
See you around.
Bye.
You see--breeders,
perfect example
of the product of change.
The swelling's
gone down.
It's still quite painful, actually.
You know,
all I'm saying
is there should be
two areas on the beach,
one for adults
and one for children.
Then everyone's happy.
Is that any better?
Yeah.
That's much better.
You're
too tense.
You need to
loosen up.
Come on.
There is no past,
there's only future
There's only here,
there's only now
Oh, your smiling face,
your gracious presence
I love you.
I adore you.
These are the days
by the sparkling river
His timely grace
and our treasured faith
This is a love,
the one magician
Turned the water
into wine
Oh, yeah.
My dad's an asshole.
O.K.
Good.
Interesting.
Um, is that
something
you can maybe
elaborate on
a little bit
for me, Truman?
O.K.
Great.
My dad's
a giant asshole!
Yeah.
1 , 2.
O.K. When you
bring your arms up,
round like this,
O.K., Eleanor?
Round. Round.
There you go.
Yeah. O.K.
Like this,
Miss Rebecca?
Look. Look at that.
I don't know
about Truman.
I'll get him
to open up,
but he's got very
severe problems,
and we know who
to thank, don't we?
Huh?
You know,
his parents.
3 2.
The state
requires you
to take a written test
to drive a car,
but any moron
can become a parent
and just destroy
a child's life.
It's like people
have babies on a whim.
Surely, to be a parent
you have to plan ahead.
36.
Say, do I want to
become a parent?
38.
Am I ready?
I'm pregnant.
What?
Pregnant?
Watch out!
Aah!
Well, I guess you
don't want the baby.
Sir, your car will be
ready in a minute.
You're lucky
the engine's
in the back.
Yeah. Right.
Hi.
Ready in a minute.
Good.
So, um...
we are absolutely certain
about this, right?
Well, my period's
1 0 days late.
Right.
And there's no way
you could have had it
and just not noticed?
Sorry. Ridiculous.
That was stupid. Stupid.
Could you be a little
more positive about this,
more supportive?
I'm trying to
be positive.
Killing us in a head-on
collision is not positive.
It must have been shock.
Out of the blue,
you say you're pregnant.
It was just
a little bit unexpected
was probably the reason
for the crash.
I thought you were
using birth control.
I was.
Your car's ready now,
sir.
Great.
Oh...
you don't believe me!
No?
You think I got pregnant
behind your back.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Do you think
I planned this?
I'm as flipped out
as you are.
I suppose
I just thought
that birth control
had a little teeny element
of control about it.
Thought it was supposed
to be foolproof.
Nothing is foolproof.
It's only 97% effective.
It says so on the box.
Yeah. Right.
97% effective.
So 3% completely
bloody ineffective.
They should put that
on the box.
Here you are.
Thanks.
We're off.
Hey. Hey.
Sean.
Who's the blonde?
No idea.
Oh, my God.
Jesus.
Hey,
how are you?
Hi.
Hey,
this is Bobbie.
Hi.
This is Rebecca
and Sam.
Hi.
I was getting worried
about you guys.
What happened
to this car?
Oh, long story.
What happened to Christine?
A long story.
So this is where
you two are going to stay.
Yeah, lovely.
So, what do you
think of her?
What,
you mean the blonde?
She's attractive.
Very attractive.
She's 25 years old.
Her skin
is like ribbon candy.
Breasts
like sponge cake.
Her calves
are like calzone.
I mean,
highly edible.
Highly edible.
She's crazy
about sex.
This is somebody
to get me over
the rough spots.
Mmm. What do you mean?
What rough spots?
Oh, Christine
left me.
Oh, shit.
When?
Oh, uh...
a week ago.
What happened?
Well...
she wanted
a child.
I'm sorry.
Are you O.K.?
Yep. Yep.
What an idiot.
Leave that.
Got it.
She said she wanted--
She, uh...
Christine wanted a baby.
She was hungry
for seed,
so I closed
the iron door,
denied her
my essence.
You know,
I'm not ready
to be biologically
extraneous.
She would have
devoured me
from the head down,
chewed up
my manhood,
swallowed my youth,
and gobbled me up
like some
praying mantis.
Not for me.
What do you mean,
praying mantis?
The female mantis,
after she has sex
with her mate,
she eats him.
Oh, yeah.
But Christine
wasn't pregnant
or anything
like that?
No. What do you mean?
Like on the sly?
On the sly,
or, you know,
in the run of things.
On the s-- No.
I mean, Christine
has her faults,
but I don't know
who would do that.
That's a knife
in the back.
Yeah.
You know, that's--
No, of course not.
That's
some voodoo woman
who puts pins
in her diaphragm.
Ha ha.
Spooky, Sam.
That's a she-snake.
That's like
the most hateful,
cruel, sneaky,
horrible thing
you can do.
Who would do that?
No! No!
Aah!
They eat the father!
They eat him!
Honey. Honey, what?
Honey, what?
Who eats fathers?
No one.
Sorry. Sorry.
Just a bad,
bad dream.
Silly, silly dream.
O.K.
You worry too much.
Just relax.
Lie down, O.K.
Lie down.
It's O.K., baby.
Whatever happens,
we can work it out.
I know.
I love you.
I've loved you
since the first moment
I saw you.
You're the only one
I want to be the father
of my children,
whether
it's now or later.
O.K.?
Oh...
I love it
when you do that.
Do what?
Ha ha ha!
That thing you're doing
with my knee.
That is so good.
Oh, Samuel.
Stop it.
I love it.
Go on.
But, Samuel?
What? Yeah?
I'm not doing anything
with your knee.
Huh?
Aah! What is it?
Aah!
- Aah!
What's the matter?
Come here, kiddo.
Where you been?
Come here, you.
I'm sorry, folks.
Come on. Get away from him.
She's going through
a hiding phase.
It's for attention.
Hey, honey,
you'll get it dirty,
and God knows
what's on there.
Hey, honey,
it's the beach people.
Oh, hi.
This is great. Don't worry.
We didn't bring a kite.
How about another one
of them kisses?
What's going on?
We found her.
We've been looking
for her for an hour.
Honey, tell the neighbors
to call off the search.
You, call the sheriff
before the choppers go up.
We're sorry.
Looks like a full house.
Party time, then!
I'm sorry.
Get back in there.
Listen, um, sorry,
and I'm going to take off.
You'll be here all weekend,
right?
Sounds great.
Good to see you.
You didn't tell me
they were coming.
They didn't
tell me either.
They always
show up uninvited.
I hope they don't
spoil your weekend.
Oh, no.
We'll be fine.
The kids seem adorable.
Oh,
they're monsters.
They're monsters.
See, this is why
I don't want kids.
It's nonsense.
No, what I'm saying is
I think it's such baloney
and such a cliche
that the artist
has to be messed up
and have a life
of deprivation,
be an alcoholic
or deprived in some way.
It's how you use, obviously,
with imagination and passion
whatever it is...
I love you.
Well, that's nice.
I think
you're great.
Marry me,
Captain Renaldo.
Who's
Captain Renaldo?
Marry me.
Make me your wife.
We'll honeymoon
in Paris.
Well, I'm not sure.
It's King Stanislaus'
daughter, isn't it?
You're madly
in love with her!
Who?
Don't deny it!
I saw you two kissing!
Brute!
She hit me.
Shannon,
no hitting.
O.K. You run along.
Go play.
We'll talk later.
You weasel!
Oh, God.
I am so sorry about that.
She's been reading
Harlequin Romance novels,
and she's just
obsessed with it.
It's kind of cute.
Isn't it cute?
Lovely.
Not many teeth left,
but cute.
What a puss.
All right, everybody.
I've got an announcement.
Gail and I
are going to have a new baby.
Oh, shit. Not another one.
So I'd like to
make a toast.
To my wife, the most beautiful
pregnant woman in the world.
Love you.
Hear, hear!
You could be
the toughest guy,
but when your child
looks into your eyes
and that child knows
you're their dad...
suddenly
it smiles.
It's like...
I cannot explain it.
It's like magic.
Is it magic when they do
that little dribble of vomit
down your shoulder?
I'm sorry
if we're boring you, pal.
Just a joke.
O.K.
Just forget it.
The guy is rude.
Sorry.
What did you say?
You are rude.
Rude?
You think I'm rude?
Yes, I do.
I'm sorry--
It's all right, honey.
Let's just deal
with this accusation.
Like an idiot,
I was under the impression
you were monopolizing
the conversation.
I'm sorry
if I'm a little excited
about my wife and I
having another baby.
Is being excited a reason
to exclude eight people
from conversation?
I didn't realize
this was a frickin'
group therapy session!
How much do I owe?
You didn't realize
you were a crashing bore.
I'll walk over there
and kick your bony little ass!
I'll have
my 5-year-old daughter do it!
Let's drop it.
Marty, he does
have a point,
but just drop it.
Sean, he's a dick,
and you're an even bigger dick
for taking his side
over family.
You and Gail used to
be interested
in politics,
music, art.
Now it's nothing but
kids, kids, kids.
My kids are
very meaningful to me.
When my first was born,
it was my most
exciting moment.
I felt like I really
made a contribution
to this world.
Absolutely.
Congratulations.
The world
is overpopulated.
Our society has too many
starving children.
I would say our society
has too many
starving artists.
It hasn't been
lucrative.
That's true,
but that
doesn't mean
what I do
isn't respectable.
Van Gogh,
while he was living,
didn't sell
one painting.
Now his stuff goes
for $40 million.
How long will you
have to be dead
before you can pay
that phone bill?
Do you come here
to ruin my weekends
and embarrass me
at my home?
Your home?
This isn't your home.
It was our parents' home!
You aren't making
any contributions.
You've got no wife,
no kids.
You insult your
only family.
You keep this up,
you'll die alone,
like a dog,
like a bum,
like Van Gogh.
Hey, Doc,
you all right?
Are you O.K.?
Yeah. What?
You don't look good.
You look like
you're going to puke.
No, I'm fine.
Thank you, Truman.
I was just listening
to what you were saying.
Interesting.
That was a key sentence.
Would you mind
repeating it
just so
I can get it down?
You're an asshole.
Right.
And Dad's a bastard!
Yeah.
Right.
I can't be a father.
I can't.
I ca...I...I...
Why would I want to
have a child?
Just so he can call me a bastard
in 1 0 years' time?
We'd have to move out.
We don't have space
for a child.
Rebecca and me,
we're wonderful together.
It's just insane
to spoil it.
Just the two of us--
That's how it should be.
This baby is not
a good idea.
That's what I'll tell her.
Beck.
Hi.
Be right there.
Just stay back. Bye-bye.
I'll tell her now.
Hi.
Beck.
Listen, Beck--
Samuel,
I've been thinking--
No. Wait.
Wait. This pregnancy
was an accident.
It took us
completely by surprise.
Right.
We've been doing
really great together,
and a baby
would change everything.
I suppose it could.
Our apartment's
not ready for a baby.
No.
We'd have to
redecorate.
Yep.
I'd have to
quit my job.
Nobody wants
a pregnant dance teacher.
We're not ready
for a child.
There's not one good reason
to keep this baby.
But I still want to.
Right.
Maybe it's crazy,
but I feel it
living inside me.
Oh...
and I really
want this baby.
O.K.
What about you?
What do...
Oh, you mean
what...what...
what do I think?
I'm just saying
how I feel.
So, um,
what do you feel?
Right. How do I
feel on that one?
Well, um...
I feel, um...
I, uh...
I feel exactly
the same as you.
Really?
Yeah.
We won't let it
change us.
No.
Oh, my gosh.
I have to go
to the bathroom again.
It's one of the joys
of pregnancy.
O.K. Oh, gosh.
We're going to
have a baby.
Aw, I'm such a...
I'm such a coward!
Sorry. Forget it.
Nothing to do with you.
Oh, baby,
you were incredible.
Not bad, eh?
That was the single
most satisfying
sexual experience
of my life.
Well, I, uh...
aim to please.
I know.
Now it's time
for dinner.
Dinner?
Aah!
No!
Time to get up.
Today's our first
doctor's appointment.
Today?
I told you about it
two weeks ago...
and then last week,
three days ago,
and twice, I think,
yesterday.
Sorry, honey.
I completely forgot.
Yeah.
Figures.
I swear I won't
forget next time.
Hi.
I'm Rebecca Taylor
to see Dr. Green.
Oh, Dr. Green's
been out with pneumonia.
You can see Dr. Kosevich
or reschedule.
Yes. I think we'll
just reschedule.
We can see
Dr. Kosevich.
Are you sure?
Why?
Is there a problem?
Oh, no. No.
It's just Dr. Kosevich
is new...from Russia.
He's a little nervous,
oh, but very sweet.
Well,
we're already here.
We may as well
see Dr. Kosevich.
O.K.
Please, sit down.
One moment.
A little family business.
If it's not
one thing,
it's your mother.
Please, please,
sit down.
I'm very sorry.
Oh, hello.
So we hear
you're from Russia.
You have a problem
with it?
I am not a Communist.
I was only briefly
member of party.
It was only for medical reasons.
I was a scientist.
In Russia, I was chief
of obstruction.
Obstruction?
Abstraction?
Obstetrics,
I think you mean.
That's it.
Obstetrics.
One moment.
Not obstruction,
is obstetrics.
Yes, I was the head
of obstetrics research
at Pasklovansky Hospital
in St. Petersburg.
What brings you
here, then?
I didn't work with people
in Russia.
More the technical side.
No. Animals.
Animals?
Only rats and monkeys.
Rats?
Change of scenery.
You've seen one rat ass,
you've seen them all.
I also want a patient
who won't bite me.
Last month,
I received my new license,
and now
I deliver human babies.
O.K., now,
I have a computer program here
that I have written myself
that will calculate
your due date very accurately.
O.K.?
Fine. When was the first day
of your last menopause?
- Menopause?
- Menstruation.
Menstruation.
Period.
End of sentence.
March 1 1 th.
O.K.
Here it comes.
The baby will be due
December 8th.
O.K.
Congratulations. The baby
was conceived March 1 7 th.
Oh, that's clever.
Most people know that,
but some people
are too drunk to remember.
Oh, my God.
What is wrong?
I'm not the father.
What?
Oh, my God.
On March 1 7 th,
I was away
at a child psychiatry conference
in Boston, remember?
What are you
saying?
I'll leave you two alone.
That's fine.
I'm going.
No! Wait!
Come back! Sit down!
Samuel, sit down!
Check your computer
again!
It is--the computer
is very accurate.
Check the goddamn
computer.
Check it!
Don't yell at me!
Please don't do this.
I spent a year
in Afghanistan.
I have sometimes
very low tolerance for pressure.
Come on!
O.K. What is wrong
with the thing?
Oh, fuck me!
It's not working.
Hold on. O.K.
What is wrong?
Oh, O.K. O.K.
Excuse me.
This is the problem.
It is feces
flying into the fan.
There are function keys
for humans and simians,
and you're not a simian.
No, I'm not.
I had you as a baboon.
Sorry. I didn't...
There you go.
Were you here March 23rd?
Yeah.
With her?
- Yes.
O.K., um,
everything is fine now.
We're all back on-line,
and your baby...
your baby will be born
on December 1 5th.
O.K. Now it is time
for the physical examination.
Let's take a look
at your Volvo, O.K.?
Come with me into here.
I'll warm my hands for you.
Please come in.
All right, madam.
If you would get undressed,
we'll begin, O.K.?
And you may stay,
sir, if you like.
That's fine.
I'll wait--
Don't you dare.
I'd like to
stay.
Very good.
Let me get ready for you.
O.K.
We've worked out
all the insects.
Giddyup.
Run.
That lunatic
is not delivering me.
That's fine.
He's just a replacement.
Dr. Green will be there.
Let me help you, honey.
Just be gentle!
Honey, listen,
I was thinking,
about the baby--
Let's just keep it
to ourselves, huh?
Um, um,
yeah, all right.
Talking about it
before the third month
is bad luck.
Marty, look who's here!
Hey, look who's here!
Hey, guys,
what the hell?
Good to see you!
How you doing?
Hi.
When
are you due?
Oh, I'm not
pregnant.
You're not pregnant?
Yeah, right.
Huh?
What are you
doing
on the maternity
floor?
Are we on
the maternity floor?
Good grief.
We're completely lost.
Poor old Beck.
She had
some bad Chinese.
We're here to see
the gastrointestinal specialist.
What's his name?
His name?
Yeah.
I can probably
tell you
what floor he's on.
She volunteers here. I've sold
cars to almost every doctor.
Beck, what's his name?
It's Dr. something,
isn't it?
It's Doctor...
Ridiculous.
Excuse me.
Oh, gosh.
Thanks.
I didn't realize
I'd left it.
Thank you
very much.
You have
a small pussy.
What?
I found the little hairs
on the bag.
What?
You know, the...meow...
Oh, cat!
Yes, we have a cat.
Well, you must
get rid of it.
What?
Cats spread the disease.
Oh, yeah. Where
the small worms...
Yes.
Small worms.
In the poop.
Toxoplasmosis.
Thank you.
Thank you both
very much,
but Skippy
is old and clean
and won't cause
any problem.
O.K. Well,
it is your choice--
the cat or the baby.
Sorry to bring you
that news.
Baby.
Oh, congratulations,
guys.
I'm so excited!
Congratulations,
you guys.
Congratulations.
Wow. That's great.
Oh, your first.
Thanks.
Sorry about--
That's all right.
I've been
lied to before.
You're good at it.
We could use you
at the car lot.
It's so exciting!
We're happy for you.
How are you feeling?
I'm O.K.
A little tired.
Everybody
gets tired,
but the whole
thing is just
a life-changing
event.
I'll give
you my number.
We can go
baby shopping.
You've got to
get that book,
What To Expect
When You're Expecting.
And we've got videos of
all her births.
You've got to
film your first.
That's the best.
It's the bloodiest--
blood everywhere,
things shooting out,
people screaming, stuff getting
torn and sewed together.
It's like a good
World War II movie.
Will you keep
the car?
Yeah. It's fine now.
Cost a bit of money.
But it only seats
two people.
It always did.
But you're going to
have a baby.
You could never fit
a car seat in there.
Listen, stop down
by the lot.
I'll make you
a good deal.
All right?
Great.
Honey, we got to go.
Bad Chinese...
Buddy!
Come on, baby.
Let's roll.
See you guys.
O.K.
I hate him.
I loathe him.
He tried to
sell me a new car.
Can you believe that?
Tacky or what?
Yeah,
but he's right.
We're going to need
something bigger.
But you know how much
I love my car.
I've worked
hard for it.
What do you
suggest?
Tie the baby
to the hood like a deer?
Well, no, but maybe
you could get a car.
On my salary?
Come on.
Well, put it this way.
I'm not getting rid
of the car.
What about the cat?
Huh?
What, you believe
Dr. Zhivago in there?
The monkey doctor?
He's right.
I've read about it.
Cats can be dangerous
for a baby.
They can suffocate
the baby, claw the baby.
Skippy is 1 6.
He can barely move.
He's half-blind.
He's too weak
to suffocate anyone.
What about hygiene
in the kitchen?
You get cat hair
and cat saliva.
You said that this baby
wouldn't change our lives.
Now I have to sell my car
and get rid of my cat.
This is the second month,
and our lives
are practically unrecognizable!
I really appreciate
your asking us along.
I'm hoping this
will get Samuel excited
about having a baby.
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Yeah, 'cause, um,
if things
don't change,
I'm thinking
about leaving him.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Sure you are.
I thought about leaving
Marty all the time,
but this
is his first time.
You've got to
give him a chance.
He's completely
uninvolved.
This whole baby thing
really scares him.
He's probably having
trouble facing it.
If you have a baby,
that means
he's got to grow up.
The baby's the fun part.
That's fun.
You know.
Look at all this stuff.
Ah, yeah! Whoo!
He's going to
love this.
You know you're
having a boy, right?
Yeah.
Gail took one of those
amnio tests, I suppose.
No.
How do you know?
I can tell
it's a boy
by the way she's
carrying it all in front.
They don't often
carry them at the back.
If it's a boy,
they carry them low
like this.
If it's a girl,
it's up like this.
Plus, there are
special ways
to ensure that it
will be a boy.
What do you mean,
special ways?
Well,
when we made love...
Yeah?
we used
special positions.
Oh, please.
That's an old wives' tale,
that stuff.
You'll see.
Sometimes I'm not sure
I want this baby.
Oh, Missy,
of course you do.
It's just
such a privilege.
There's hundreds
of women
who spend thousands
of dollars every day
trying to
get pregnant.
It's like our profound
biological right.
It's something men
can never experience.
It has to be
at the right time for you,
but really,
it's a miracle.
And then
when the baby comes,
there's moments
of sheer happiness.
Even if you're alone?
I know it's fashionable,
PC, all that,
to be a strong,
independent single mother,
and, uh,
I'm prepared for that.
I can do that,
but, um, I would
love this baby
to have a mother
and a father.
I would love to
have a family,
and I would love to
marry Samuel.
Um...
all he has to do is ask.
Oh, Missy.
Okey-dokey.
Huh huh huh.
O.K. Tell your mommy
if she loves you,
she'll buy you
the whole Arnie collection!
Thank you,
Arnie.
Who loves you,
girls?
- Arnie.
Hey, fellas.
How about taking home
a new Arnie doll
for the kiddies?
No, thank you,
buddy.
Mister,
you'd look great
in my ''Arnie Loves You''
t-shirt.
They come in
extra-extra-extra large.
No, thank you.
How about a new
''Arnie Loves You'' video?
Love is for
you and me
No, thanks. O.K.?
We are one
big family
I'm not going to
buy your damn video!
But the kids
will love it.
My kids think
your show sucks.
Oh.
But thanks,
anyway.
Hey, no hard feelings,
O.K.?
All right. Sorry.
That's O.K.
Huh huh huh.
So long.
Eh, you cheap shit.
What did you say?
Huh?
Oh, gee. I didn't say
nothing, mister.
He didn't say
anything, Marty.
Bye-bye.
Arnie loves you.
You penis-head.
I heard that!
Heard what?
I heard what you said!
He's pathetic.
Come on.
There's children around here,
for God's sake!
So long...
you fat-ass pussy!
That's it!
No.
Yes!
Uh-oh.
No. No. Arnie.
Come on,
you wiener.
you bitch.
Here's one
for the queen.
Oh!
I'll get him, Sammy.
Hey, cut it out.
Oh, you hit
like a girl,
you flatulent
butt-head.
I'll take both
you wieners on.
You and that
pussy boyfriend!
Right, you bastard!
Who's the fat pussy
now, buddy?
Tell your sister
to let go of my tail,
you weak-wristed
Nancy boy!
Get off me,
you fat bastard!
I'll shove an ''Arnie Loves You''
lunch box up your ass!
Marty!
Samuel!
Oh, you--
Hi, honey.
He is
such a jerk!
We're in trouble.
Run to Mommy.
I'll wipe the floor
with you.
Oh...
Wow! That's, uh...
that's quite a breakfast
you've got there.
Mm-hmm!
Wow, you, uh...
certainly got
your appetite back.
Mmm! Boy...
I don't know
if you noticed--
The first three months
were tough on me.
But now, you know,
my breasts
don't hurt,
no more nausea
or insomnia,
and I feel great!
Oh! Good news.
So, I was thinking,
you know,
I know it's been
two months
since we made love,
but maybe we could
fool around tonight.
Check!
Leave the breakfast.
But I haven't
finished the food!
O.K.
I'll be right back.
Huh? What?
Wait here for me.
Right. Right.
Ready when
you are.
Ow!
Ready.
I been really tryin' baby
Tryin' to hold back
This feeling for so long
Oh, my God.
And if you feel
Like I feel, baby
Then come on
Oh, wow.
Oh, come on
Whoo!
Let's get it on
Ah, babe
Let's love, baby
Let's get it on
Sugar
Ooh hoo hoo
Ha ha ha!
What is it?
It moved.
Huh? What moved?
The baby. It moved!
Oh.
Oh, right.
Here.
Put your hand here.
It's like bubbles.
I-I-I don't
feel anything.
No,just wait.
Oh. It stopped.
What a shame.
Yeah.
It's an incredible
feeling.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I guess I got plenty
more time to feel it.
Yeah. Yeah.
Ohh...
Honey, do you think
we're hurting the baby?
No. No.
Because
if I can feel it,
then it can feel me.
No, I don't--
I don't think so.
Yeah.
Yes, yes, yes,
it can.
What if the baby
can see?
Um...see what,
my love?
Your penis
coming toward it.
That could scare
the hell out of a baby.
Rebecca, I-I--
What if your penis
caused brain damage?
Are you serious?
I don't know, I just...
don't think
we should make love
until we talk
to the doctor.
Please?
We don't know what
could happen, hon.
O.K.
Fine.
Fine, fine, fine.
But you know what?
I bet
if we wait awhile,
we can feel
the baby move again.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
That will be
just as much fun.
Uh!
That's my game.
Fuck! Shit! Shit!
Aah!
Hey, hey, Sam.
Fuck!
Ho!
O.K., that's it.
No more tennis
for today.
That's it.
What happened to your
British etiquette?
This John McEnroe thing
is scaring me.
Um, Sam,
what's the matter?
What's the matter?
I'm in the middle
of a nervous breakdown.
You're going
to have a thrombo.
What's the matter?
Why?
O.K.
Rebecca is
pregnant. There.
What?
I am completely
sexually frustrated.
I do not
sleep at night.
I have these
appalling nightmares.
About what?
The latest nightmare
is that the baby is deformed--
It's missing an arm,
or it's got
cauliflower ears
with an eye
on its forehead.
I can't stand it!
I don't know why...