Oh, Peter, come in.
- Swing heil, Joseph.
- Swing heil.
Ow! Oh ho ho!
Aah!
Anna, we have to dance tonight.
- OK.
- There they are.
OK, OK,
you've got Shaw...
- Hey!
- The Clambake 7...
- Herr Hitman. Otto.
- Peter.
- What's doing, you reefed-up...
- Thomas.
Try to understand this.
Dorsey's trumpet is great
when he's playing sweet.
Sweet.
But he doesn't ride, man.
Do you understand?
Let's work tonight! Yeah!
Aah!
Whoo!
Thomas, come and dance.
What do you say?
- Whoo!
Yeah! Whoo!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Yeah! Whoo!
Thomas, we'll miss the tram.
- Take it slow, Otto.
- See you, Otto.
What, you didn't like Helga?
You know Herr Hitman
seemed to hit it off with her.
What? I did not.
I was just being nice.
"I was just being nice. "
Hell, we've already missed it.
We're walking again.
You want to race down
to Macken Bridge?
No, let's just walk.
- Well, I beat you last time.
- That's not true.
That is true.
I believe I beat you right...
I beat you last time.
I believe I beat you
right down to your socks.
Go!
Last one on's an H.J. Pansy!
Hey!
Peter!
Thomas!
Damn it.
Aah!
- We're gangsters.
- We're cowboys.
You're idiots.
Arvid.
Oh, come on, Herr Hitman.
We love you.
Leave me alone.
You didn't have to wait for me.
I can take care of myself.
Ooh.
Oh, you think it's funny?
- Yes, please.
- Aha!
All right. Come on.
I have to unload.
En garde. Try it.
Come on, try. You can't...
When I was kid
'bout half past three
My daddy said,
son, come here to me
Said things may come,
and things may go
But this is one thing
you ought to know
Tain't what you do
It's the way
that you do it
Tain't what you do
It's the way
that you do it
Tain't what you do
It's the way
that you do it
That's what
gets me through
Ma ma ma my
On the floor! Stop!
- Stop where you are now!
What the hell?
Peter!
Stop there!
- Are you all right?
- I'm OK.
Gestapo. Watch out.
Hold it!
Don't let him get away!
Get to the other side!
Stop there!
Aah!
Peter, let's get out of here.
Come on, come on.
Come on, let's go.
- Morning, Mama.
- Morning.
- Morning, Mama Klara.
- Good morning, boys.
What happened to your face?
I was trying a new dance step,
and I fell.
Who were you fighting with?
Mama, I wasn't f/ghting.
I was dancing.
You told me you wouldn't become
part of something dangerous.
I fell. It's a wild dance.
Here, let me show you.
No, no, no.
Not on me, you don't.
Over the... boom. Into the back.
Ah. Ah. Mmm.
Ow. Ow. Ow. Mmm.
Looks to me like you have
to go to the bathroom.
Mama Klara, no!
Oh, that butter
has to last us a whole month.
It's not for you
to gorge yourself on.
Oh, I'm so glad
you're all amused.
- I'm off.
- Peter.
Mama.
Peter...
maybe Thomas's parents
are so well-placed...
they don't care what kind
of trouble he gets into...
but if you lose your place
in school...
you'll end up working
at the factory like me.
Mama, I'm going to university.
I'm going to be an engineer.
There's a great need
for engineers now.
The Nazis
don't get everyone, Thomas.
I'm telling you,
he never had a chance.
Here, let me give you
a bag. Let me help you.
I got it. I'm f/ne.
What did I tell you?
At least he tried to escape.
He didn't just wait for them.
- Heil Hitler.
Gestapo. Let's go. Come on.
Hey, they haven't caught us,
have they?
Well, they will.
We got out of the H.J., but
we won't get out of the army.
Nobody gets out of it.
Hey! Willi.
Peter, what's
your brother doing here?
Come here.
What are you following us for?
I can be sleazy.
Just give me a chance.
We don't need some pink-eared
midget hanging around.
Go home to Mama.
A couple of H.J.'s
are beating up a swing boy...
in the alley around the corner.
You better not be lying.
In here. In here.
- They were beating him up.
How many were there?
Playing cowboys and indians?
Can we play, too?
What's the matter?
Four against five.
That's still not a fair fight.
There's five.
Let me fight. I can fight.
Willi, go home.
What about one against one,
swing heine?
Aah!
What are you, a kike lover?
Thomas.
He's Jewish.
Thank you.
You keep helping them,
and we'll deal with you...
the way we deal
with all traitors.
I'm not a traitor!
I'm a cowboy,
and you're a pansy!
Get out of here!
I'm going to get you,
swing boy!
Looked like a swing boy to me.
How was I supposed to know?
Come on, Willi.
We'll be late for school.
Swing boy.
Hey, Peter! Thomas!
Quiz time.
What is an icky?
Someone who's stupid, not hip.
Can't collar that jive.
- Jive?
- Talk. What they say in Harlem.
Too easy. Um, faust.
Oh, a book by Goethe.
- Icky.
- Even as we speak, two ickies.
- Icky, icky, icky, icky!
- A faust is an ugly girl.
Like that faust you went for
at the Bismarck the other night.
Boys, could you go for these?
Ooh.
Ooh, I like these.
Look at those breasts.
- Otto, where did you get these?
- I got 'em.
What would you call that?
Cupcake size?
Cantaloupe.
Ooh, look what we have here.
Peter's priss.
- Have you talked with her yet?
- Who said I'm interested?
Your tongue was on the floor.
Didn't we see you pigeons...
at the Cafe Bismarck
the other night?
We wouldn't be
caught dead there.
Especially not with you,
Thomas Berger.
Ooh!
- Well, you missed it.
- Why? What's so great about it?
Well, it was
the swingingest party ever.
- Right, Peter?
- Swingingest. Supermergentroid.
Super what?
Come on, Evey.
They talk gibberish.
No. It's a secret language
we're not allowed to know.
It's all too secret.
Ha ha!
You go to my head
And you linger
like a haunting refrain
And I f/nd you
spinning round in my brain
Like the bubbles
in a glass of champagne
What did you do today?
Did you and Thomas
go down to the docks?
Yeah. We went
down there after school...
but no new records came in.
So, what are we doing tomorrow?
Are we going to go
to the Hall Club?
Willi.
I saw you looking at me.
You can't deny it.
What are you doing?
Don't touch her!
- Mama!
- Goddamn you!
Leave him alone!
No, don't! Peter! No!
Peter, no! Don't! Don't!
No! I'm all right.
I'm all right.
Herr Hinz was just leaving.
I thought a woman
of your special background...
would value my protection.
Your boy needs a haircut.
- That's our business.
- Perhaps not.
We have nothing to fear.
For six years,
I've proven my loyalty.
The new order
demands absolute loyalty.
Youth of his sort
belong in a work camp.
Good night.
Herr Hinz, wait.
Please, wait.
- Who are you expecting?
- No one.
Peter,
tell whoever it is to go away.
- Mama.
- Do what I tell you.
Good evening.
Is Frau Muller at home?
Who is it?
- Heil Hitler.
- Heil Hitler. Who are you?
I am the block leader.
I was collecting for the relief.
May I be of some service?
No. You may go.
May I help you?
- Frau Muller?
- Yes.
I'm so sorry to disturb you.
I'm Herr Knopp.
Are you all right?
Yes, it's nothing.
- Are you going to take my mama?
- Willi, it's all right.
No one is going to take away
your mother, young man.
Though with so beautiful a lady
it is quite tempting.
But really,
you should see to that cut.
You have some iodine?
- Please allow me.
- It's not necessary.
- He's in the Gestapo.
- Don't worry. It's all right.
We've done nothing wrong.
Just be quiet.
I've found it.
Please sit down.
Let me... let me see.
Now, this will only sting
for a moment.
Ah, yes.
There. There.
That didn't hurt too much,
did it?
- It should heal in no time.
- Thank you.
Uh, I can see you're wondering.
Regrettably, I am here
on official business...
but I hope that we can conclude
that as quickly as possible.
Do you know a Karl Manglesdorf?
I did... a long time ago. He was
an associate of my husband's.
Mmm. Then you have not
seen him recently?
No. The last time
was probably six years ago...
before my husband passed away.
Oh, I am so sorry.
What has he done?
Oh, it is unimportant.
Uh, have any other
of your husband's associates...
tried to contact you?
No.
Since his death
I've had nothing to do...
with any of his friends.
I took a job
at the Farben factory...
and have devoted myself
to the reich and my children.
Well, you have raised
two fine sons.
I see the resemblance.
Or is it just
a family proclivity...
for facial abrasions?
Do you have news of my son?
Excuse her. She's not feeling
well. Wilhelm is dead, Mama.
Dear lady, it is I
who must excuse myself.
I have all the information
I need.
So, if anything else
occurs to you...
or if I can help in any way,
any way at all...
please.
- Good night.
- Here.
- Oh, thank you.
Good night.
When I was a kid
about half past three
My daddy said,
son, come here to me
He says, things may come,
and things may go
But this is one thing
you ought to know
Tain't...
Was Papa a Communist?
What?
Where did you get that idea?
I don't know.
I mean, isn't that why
they arrested him?
He wasn't a Communist.
Then what'd he do?
Do you think I know everything?
It was six years ago, Willi.
I don't remember.
Well, you remember
more than I do.
I was only three.
I remember
they took him away...
and then he came back
after a long time...
and he was sick.
So?
Did they make him sick
in prison?
I don't know. Go to sleep.
I have to work in the morning.
But he loved us...
didn't he?
- Ah, Peter.
- Herr Schumler.
Make sure
you don't take any side trips.
I can't afford to keep
my older customers waiting.
They're the only ones
who read anymore.
Everyone else is too busy
going to parades.
Yes, Herr Schumler.
Don't you need the addresses?
Distracted today.
Nasty bruise.
What happened?
Good morning. I'm looking
for a rare edition of Faust.
Wait one second.
I think I have just the thing.
Peter, here it is.
Just terrible.
"Traitor. "
I'm taking the radio.
I want that bureau as well.
I'll be back for it.
This one?
Delivery from Herr Schumler.
- Frau Linge?
- Yes.
The book for my mother.
She's bedridden.
How very kind of Herr Schumler
to send it. Thank you.
That's Beethoven...
Piano Trio in B Flat Major.
Are you a student
of classical music?
No.
My father...
I think he's the violinist.
Wilhelm Muller?
Really?
He was a great musician.
You must be very proud.
Well... good-bye.
Good-bye.
Ah, I found it.
- You can use the booth.
- What?
I'm finished with the booth.
You can use it.
Can I help you find anything?
I know this store like
it's my own private collection.
No. Thanks.
OK.
- That's the best.
- Isn't Benny Goodman the best?
That is... this is Benny Goodman.
- No, it's Gene...
- Oh, no, Gene Krupa is...
Benny's illegal, so they
relabel all these jackets...
to get them by the censor.
The authorities don't know. It
takes them forever to catch on.
You know, they haven't banned
Arshawsky yet...
Artie Shaw... and he's Jewish.
- Mm-hmm.
- And Count Basie.
You can still get Count Basie.
He's a negro.
Hmm.
They probably think
he's the head of a country.
You don't know anything
about swing, do you?
Of course I do.
Just not a lot.
Come here.
Get ready. You're about
to really blow your wig.
Well, I should just...
Let me... I'll close the...
door.
That's Bunny Berigan on trumpet.
Actually, it's Pee Wee Erwin.
Maybe it's Ziggy Elman.
I thought you knew everything
about swing.
- Ah!
- Aah!
Ah, what a burn!
He's just got the greatest
solid send of jive.
He just swings it out.
It's...
- Supermergentroid.
- Yeah.
- Do you jitterbug?
- No.
Do you want to learn?
I just...
It's easy,
and I could teach you.
Anyone can do it.
You can't listen to this
and not dance.
It just sends you. Yeah!
Muller.
Yeah! Yeah!
Pow! Pow!
Muller!
This isn't
one of your dancing clubs.
What?
This isn't
one of your dancing clubs.
We were... we were just listening.
What about buying?
I don't know why I bother
stocking those swing records.
They are more trouble
than they are worth.
I'll buy it.
All right, you hep cats.
Get ready to jump up and down.
Here's one of your own
who can really break it down.
Herr Hitman meets Count Basie.
Yeah!
Herr Django, man!
Shout and feel it
It's sounding hot tonight.
Go ahead! Take it!
- Bop, bop!
- Hey!
- Ha!
What?
One, two...
The H.J. S are coming!
Hurry up!
Oh, scheiss patrol.
- Killer diller, man.
- You were great.
Thanks, Helga.
- Murderistic, Herr Hitman.
- Thanks.
Look at those pansies.
They're all training
for the Gestapo.
How did they know
we were here tonight?
Probably beat it
out of some swing kid.
- That's Emil.
- Where?
So, it's true.
Goddamn traitor.
He was probably forced into it.
It is compulsory, after all.
Oh, some excuse.
Those creeps are too busy
marching up and down all day...
to keep track.
Arvid's right.
Emil couldn't be a traitor.
He was the original hep cat.
No. No one who likes swing
can become a Nazi.
Aw, who needs him anyway?
Come on, let's have some fun.
- Keep that blindfold on.
- Blindfold's on.
I'm sorry, Otto.
I grooved this platter
from the f/rst lick.
Harlem.
Recorded September 14, 1937.
Teddy Foster, trumpet.
Freddy Gardner, alto...
Hey! You guys are not going
to believe what just happened.
This H.J. Rode by me
and whistled the signal.
This H.J. Rode by me and
whistled It Don't Mean a Thing.
- You're joking.
- He must've been a hep cat.
It's like Herr Hitman said.
A hep cat can't be broken.
No. What if he learned it
from Emil?
You know, he might have
been trying to trick you...
into telling him
where the next party is.
Come on. It took you a year
to learn how to whistle that.
Well, what's that
supposed to mean?
It means what it means.
Quiz time. "Joint is jumping. "
Um, what it isn't in here...
lively.
Can't we find something
a little more exciting to do?
I say we go down
to the red light district.
Make some new friends.
Yeah.
I could go for some ladies.
Those kinds of friends
cost a lot of money.
Actually,
I was thinking about...
using some of that dough
you've got stashed away.
Oh, no. I'm saving that money
for the shortwave radio.
I'm not going to spend
that money on some tart.
That's because even if you paid
her, you couldn't get one.
Maybe the reason
you're so bored...
is because you just
don't have any idea...
which platters to pick.
All right.
Put on that blindfold.
- What?
- Put it on.
I see. We go right into it.
Come on. Come on, Thomas.
Pick any record in the room...
any record.
OK.
I believe I hear activity
over in the Gene Krupa section.
I think that could be.
I'm waiting. I'm waiting.
No, no.
It's too easy.
- I'm sorry. My hand slipped.
- You did that on purpose.
Don't be an ass. I'm sorry, OK?
I'll replace it.
You will? From where?
Alberti doesn't have
anything left.
I got to go down to the docks.
Besides, you have absolutely
no idea what to look for.
Oh, well, I'm sorry
I'm not as smart as you.
You know, the only reason
you know all these hits...
is because
you can't dance to them.
Thomas.
Get out. Get out!
Arvid, it was a mistake.
His hand slipped.
Why do you always have to
go along with his stupid jokes?
I'm not going along.
It was an accident, Arvid.
- Get out of here... everybody.
- Why make so much of it?
This is my hot club,
and I want you all to get out!
Arvid.
- Go!
OK. To hell with you.
Just sit around here all day
with your records whacking off.
OK? Come on, Peter.
You shouldn't have said
that thing...
about him not being able
to dance, Thomas.
Why not? It's true.
I'm sick of him
acting like he's smarter...
than everybody else
all the time.
Look at that son of a bitch.
They all think they can get
away with whatever they want.
He stole that radio
from someone they arrested.
I saw him give it to this tart.
What if we lifted it?
Next time he comes in
for his hot loaves...
he gets the cold shoulder
instead.
Yeah.
We could give it to Arvid.
Pick up Benny live.
Yeah.
Can you imagine the look
on that little creep's face...
when we walk in with it?
What do we do?
Aah!
Ohh!
Fraulein. Fraulein.
- Help me. Help me.
- Oh!
I'm bleeding!
A gang of H.J. S stabbed me.
Help me! I'm bleeding!
I'm bleeding!
Get a doctor!
I don't want to die!
- Oh, my God!
- Aah! Aah!
Aah!
They hurt me so badly.
No, no. Wait there.
Wait, please. Don't leave me!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no! No!
Let go!
Hey! What are you doing there?
Help!
He stole my radio!
Aah!
- Ha ha ha!
Help!
Damn, pounders.
You must stop them!
They stole my radio!
Help!
- Hey, stop!
Hey, hey, stop!
Hey! Stop!
- Move!
- Go! Go! Move!
Hey, you! Stop!
Stop!
- Unh!
Stop that truck!
Come on, Peter!
Give me your hand!
Come on! They're right
behind us! Come on!
- Come on, Peter!
- I can't!
Peter, drop the radio!
Drop it! Drop the damn thing!
- No! Come on!
- Leave it!
Damn!
Peter!
Thomas.
Where are you taking me?
Home.
Does my mother know?
I think so.
She's the one who called me.
Lucky for you she did...
otherwise,
you could be on your way...
to a juvenile home
or worse by now.
I don't care.
However small your concern may
be for your own well-being...
you might want to consider
that there are others...
who might be endangered
by your recklessness.
What do I have to do?
Only the same
as most boys your age are doing.
I've informed the local H.J.
Commander of your situation.
I'm not joining the H.J.
Well, of course.
It's your decision.
I'm just trying to help.
I don't want your help.
You know, Peter...
you may not believe this...
but I was once
very much like you.
I know how confusing
things can seem...
when a young boy
loses his father.
Mine died
when I was only nine...
in the war.
I couldn't understand it.
I blamed everyone,
including myself.
I dropped out of school,
left home...
drifted from one job
to the next.
Then one day...
I heard a man speak in Munich.
I felt somehow
he was speaking directly to me.
Somehow, he understood
the helplessness I felt...
the yearnings I had.
That day,
I learned I was not alone.
And while I'd been helpless
to save my father...
there was still
much I could do...
to help save something
far greater...
the fatherland.
You don't have to be alone,
Peter.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry, Mama.
I'm supposed to join the H.J.
Then you must.
It was a mistake to allow you
not to join in the first place.
I just couldn't bear to see you
in that uniform.
But you have to think
of your future.
They're pigs, Mama.
I've told you.
You must learn
to steel yourself.
You cannot let your feelings
overcome you.
I won't join.
Do you want them to start
watching the house again?
Do you remember
what it was like...
all of us jumping
at every knock?
I'd rather die
than go through that again.
He's always
giving instructions.
Hey, swing boy!
Thomas? Ha ha ha!
What are you doing here?
Did you think I'd let you have
all this fun by yourself?
This is not going to be fun.
You shouldn't have done this.
Well, you'd have done
the same thing.
We can't let them
split us apart.
Anyway, think about it.
It's the perfect cover...
H.J. By day,
swing kids by night.
You look ridiculous.
Come on.
The German people
once again rest easy...
that there is nothing to fear
from within.
But let them not rest too easy.
Like a plague,
the Jewish infestation...
stays ready
to strike a death blow...
to the heart
of Germany's resurgence.
The Jew cares nothing
for Germany.
From early childhood,
its young are taught...
to follow the lead
of the Jewish elders...
whose stranglehold
on the world's economy...
Germany has only now
started to break.
Flat foot floogee
with the floy floy
Floy doy, floy doy,
floy doy
Ha ha.
Don't let us interrupt you,
swing boy. Keep dancing.
Hey, what you got there?
Oh, Benny Goodman.
Aah!
I was right about you. You're
just a bunch of Jew lovers.
No!
You call us pansies.
Even my girlfriend doesn't
wear her hair that long.
Aah!
Uhh!
A cripple, too.
Pick him up!
Unh.
What's your name?
Django Reinhardt.
Unh!
Your name.
Duke Ellington.
I know his name.
Emil.
Unh!
Uhh!
Unh.
Aah!
Let's hear you play
that nigger kike music now.
Aah!
- Oh, no!
- Arvid, it's all right.
- Hey.
- Arvid, it's Peter and Thomas.
Calm down.
- Arvid, it's OK!
Calm down. It's OK.
- It's OK.
- No!
- Leave that alone.
- Leave me alone!
He said I'd never play again.
But he forgot about Django.
Django Reinhardt
played with two f/ngers.
So can I.
See?
They look just like his.
He didn't need
these two fingers.
Who did this to you?
Who said
you'd never play again?
Schaufuhrer Lutz
was the boxing champion...
this year in your division...
and he will be instructing you
in the basic techniques.
I'll leave you to it.
Yes, bannfuhrer.
Will someone volunteer
to demonstrate...
or do I have to pick?
I'll volunteer.
Good.
I'm glad to see
a new recruit so eager.
Heh heh.
Let's see how you do when
you're not f/ghting a cripple.
Keep your punches
close to your shoulder...
otherwise, you leave yourself
unprotected.
Attacking your opponent's body
will bring his hands down...
Uhh!
Making his head more vulnerable.
Whoo! Good one, good one.
Never be caught
against the ropes.
Thank you, Herr Berger.
You've been most helpful.
Go to hell, traitor.
I am not a traitor.
I just wised up.
You will, too.
We'll need another volunteer
to help me demonstrate...
Schaufuhrer, watch out!
Go, Thomas, go!
Go!
That's it!
Get off the ropes, Thomas.
Come on, Thomas!
Out of his way! Move! Come on!
Emil. Stop it!
- Enough?
- No!
- Uhh!
- Stop!
Come on! Come on!
You proved your point, Thomas.
Enough?
Uhh!
Just stay down.
Emil!
Emil, that's enough.
That's enough!
You all right?
Thomas...
Lesson's over, swing heine.
Hey!
It don't mean a thing
If it ain't got that swing
Doo wah, doo wah,
doo wah, doo wah, doo wah
doo waaaah
Yeah, swingin'
Aw, yeah, man
It don't mean a thing
If it ain't got
the swing...
Pow, pow, pow!
Three to the stomach.
Thomas won't go down.
The tables turn.
Doof, doof, doof, doof, doof!
Right to the fa...
you have to see Emil.
- Emil's face is bent sideways.
- You look pretty bad yourself.
Thanks.
It was murderistic.
I can't.
They smell your breath.
Well, maybe we shouldn't
play this music.
They might listen to your ears.
So, what's it like anyway,
the H.J.?
- Oh, it's...
- It's stupid as hell.
All we do is memorize...
the fuhrer's period of struggle
and all this other stuff.
Almost as boring as it is here.
You don't have to be here.
Don't you have
some marching to do?
We didn't want to join.
We had to.
He had to. What's your excuse?
Well, I'm his friend.
So am I.
You don't see me joining.
No. They wouldn't accept you.
Come.
Arvid, you'll
never guess what I found.
I was over
at Silke's house, and...
Oh. Hi.
- Hi, Helga. Come on in.
- Hi.
What's the matter?
Everyone in here
looks sadder than a map.
When did she become a member?
If we can let H.J. S in,
we can let her in.
What is that? I went after
Emil because of what he did...
and all the thanks I get
is a bunch of superior remarks?
I never asked you to fight him.
What's the matter with you?
Emil almost killed you.
So we're even.
Now we can all be friends.
Oh, you're fitting right in...
listening to the same songs...
wearing the same clothes,
getting into the same f/ghts.
It's almost like being
a swing kid, isn't it?
Though if you never liked
the music to begin with...
I guess there's no difference.
- All right, you bastard.
- You want to start something?
You like that, don't you?
Take a swing at me!
- Come on!
- Do it! Do it!
Let go! Arvid. Leave it.
That's enough.
Damn it, Arvid.
What's the matter with you?
What do you want us to do?
He joined because of me.
Because of me.
If anyone's changed
around here, it's you.
- No. I haven't changed.
- Yes, you have.
You sit in here all day. You
never go out with us anymore.
There's a party
at the Trichter tonight.
Arvid?
Well, we have to practice.
Hitler's a madman.
He's trying to get us into
a war with the whole world.
The army
will put a stop to that.
Oh, tch.
We must rely on the army.
I wish you would stop
talking politics.
What do doctors know
of such things?
My father always said,
a man with a family...
shouldn't even think
about politics.
When did your father
ever think about anything?
Who's there?
Thomas, is that you?
- Thomas?
- Yes, Papa.
Well, come in and say hello
to our guests.
Thomas,
what happened to your face?
Thomas, you remember
Dr. And Frau Keppler.
- They're here from Berlin.
- Dietrich.
Perhaps I had better get my bag.
Thomas,
you haven't said hello yet.
Hello,
Dr. Keppler, Frau Keppler.
- Dietrich, for God's sake.
- I'm all right, Mama.
He's more than all right.
He's in his element.
This is exactly
what I'm talking about.
But they all look wonderful
in their uniforms, don't they?
Our little Adolphi is no fool.
Is that why you voted for him?
You don't know
the first thing about it.
Now go upstairs
and get cleaned up.
I suppose
if I think about my family...
I should hope that the Nazis
stay in power forever.
With them in charge,
even a misf/t like Thomas...
might have a chance
to make something of himself.
- Hey!
- How you doing?
Peter, Thomas.
- Good to see you again.
- Swing heil.
Have fun. Swing heil.
Yeah!
Sabina, let's jitterbug.
Up you go.
Go, Thomas!
You're the king of Harlem!
Swing line!
Come on, everybody!
Back up, back up!
Swing line!
Swing heil!
Let's go, hepcats.
Come on,
that's the way to swing!
Go!
Go! Go!
Come on!