Do you think
we're going to make it?
I certainly hope so.
Well, don't get carried away.
I' m not getting carried away,
l' m just trying...
Make sure we live first.
I don't think doing 65 on Route
One make us Bonnie and Clyde.
We'd hold up Fort Knox,
and we wouldn't be.
Just keep your eyes peeled.
Okay?
I mean it,
I need some help here.
This is like hydroplaning
through the goddamn Bayou!
Don't blame me because
you were 2 hours late.
-What's wrong with you?
-Nothing, just watch the road.
-Slow down.
-What is it?
-Stop.
-What do you mean, stop?
-We' ll miss the boat.
-No, really, I saw something.
-Saw something? What?
-David, stop!
Jesus. Is he alive?
-No!
-What?
Don't touch him. We should call
the police and not get involved.
-lnvolved? He needs help.
-So, we' re calling the police.
-But shouldn't we...
-No, trust me.
No.
No cops.
Do you know where you are?
-Sort of.
-What happened to you?
Can you move?
-l' m calling the police.
-I said no cops.
-We've got a boat to catch.
-David.
Alexis, please,
let me handle this.
We can't help you if you
don't let me call the police.
Then don't help me.
Would you like a cigarette?
Please.
There's nothing in Lincolnville
but some payphones...
...and the ferry...
...and Pen Bay hospital
is only a few miles from here.
Why don't I just swing by.
I recommend you get looked at.
No, that's okay.
No doctors either?
Next thing,
it' ll be no lawyers...
...and we' ll all
be out of business.
-Time's your boat leaving?
-28 minutes.
How far is it?
About thirty miles.
Cutting it kind
of loose, huh?
We wouldn't want to set off
any radar guns now, would we?
Maybe you should
pick it up a bit, dear.
Sorry.
It's not your fault.
So long.
-Thanks for the lift.
-Are you sure you' re okay?
Yeah, l' ll survive.
Okay then, bye, now.
Wait.
He said he' ll survive.
-Naw, really.
-Please, take it.
-Be careful.
-Thanks.
See you around.
I suggest you scrub
that hand with ammonia...
...as soon as possible.
Why, you wanna hold it?
Jesus!
Who taught you to be such
a snob? I think it's sweet.
Yeah, so are circus dwarves.
I' ll try and rustle up something
edible. Any requests?
I think I saw a Beluga and Dom
twin-pack in the coke machine.
-What do you want?
-Surprise me.
Oh, God, you scared me.
-Sorry.
-Any luck?
Wow!
Remember when the ceiling
collapsed in Mustique?
How could I ever forget?
We had to sleep out
in that gazebo.
I remember, it's that goddamn
scorpion going for my jugular.
It was a grasshopper,
and it grazed your foot.
Lexie, what the hell are you
doing? I was watching that.
Two shots and you
turn into Mae West.
What's wrong?
Christ, we forgot
about the food.
-What food?
-On the dock.
You can't ring Mike
and Mary at this hour.
I' m not gonna let
...worth of salmon
sit out all night.
Mike? I wanted to let you know
we missed the last boat.
If it's not too much trouble...
...could you buzz over
and grab the groceries?
Great, so it works out
either way.
Thanks. Go back to sleep.
Good night.
They never made the drop.
-What are you doing?
-Going to sleep.
-With your coat on?
-Yep.
Good night.
Okay.
I wonder what happened
to that guy.
-What guy?
-From last night, on Route One.
Right, " Mr. No-Cops".
What about him?
Nothing.
I was just wondering.
Wondering what?
If he's alright, that's all.
That's not funny.
I know, l' m sorry.
-But...
-But nothing, that hurts.
Right, I have retinal damage,
isn't that hilarious?
God. I better go get
myself a cup of coffee...
...before you have
an aneurysm.
Boat coffee,
living on the edge.
Yeah, that's me, Wild Dave.
Did you remember
to bring the camera?
-I don't know, did l?
-I think so.
Yeah, you' re right, I did.
Is this gonna be
a whole thing?
I' ll see you at the house.
It's just a mushroom.
Guess who I saw
on the ferry deck?
-Who?
-Jack Hoffman.
Busy at molesting some
teenage bimbo in daylight.
Surprise, surprise.
Poor Margo.
Poor bimbo.
Would you be that open?
I don't know.
Wanna have supper
at the Blue Heron?
-Tonight?
-Yeah.
I thought it might be fun.
Maybe dance a bit.
Nah, let's just have
a quiet one.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I don't know,
l' m just not...
You' re not what?
In the mood.
I see.
Another quiet one.
Well, what do you want,
then?
-For dinner?
-For dinner.
-How about lobster?
-Lobster's fine.
Lobster it is.
I' ll have Mike swing over.
No, l' ll go.
-You sure?
-Yeah, I could use the ride.
Come on, baby, Wild Dave
is taking you for a ride.
-What in God's name?
-Just go with the flow.
Where to?
Where did you agree
to become Mrs. Weinberg?
-Are you serious?
-Next stop: Twin Bards.
-What about the lobsters?
-We don't need them.
David.
Get in the boat...
...my love.
Fuck.
What's wrong?
Take the tiller.
How does it look?
David, it's pretty tricky,
why don't we head back?
Give me the read.
O, eight-seven...
...o, eight-nine...
...o...
...eight-six... it keeps moving.
Head up. Take her to a hundred
and hold your course.
Why don't we just head back.
We can beat it to Brackett.
Nonsense, where's
your sense of adventure?
-There they are!
-You've got the Twins?
Edge her four degrees
to port...
...and we' re dead-on.
Steady.
Hold her right there.
I hope you know what you' re
doing; l' m not impressed.
Honey, have a little faith.
Lex?
Yeah?
Are you okay?
I' m fine. I was looking.
I didn't see anything coming.
Don't worry.
Get the flares.
Get the flares, right.
We don't have any flares.
-What?
-Fourth of July, remember?
-You didn't replace them?
-I didn't think...
Exactly, you didn't think.
Make sure we' re not sinking.
-Wait here, l' ll go check.
-Check what?
-We don't know where we are.
-We' re on land...
...unless that's a UFO.
-l' m coming with you.
-Stay here, watch the boat.
David!
How was I supposed to know?
What's he doing, stalking us?
David, do you think so?
Thank God.
Glad to see
you guys are happy.
No, we' re not,
we' re just glad you' re right.
I didn't know it was you.
I just heard my wife scream.
It was instinct.
I've been seeing a lot
of instinct lately.
This oughta hold us
till it lifts.
When will that be?
You know what they say
about Maine...
...if you don't like
the weather, wait 5 minutes.
No, we' re fine, thank you.
Your wife looks hungry.
Thank you.
How did you end up out here,
If you don't mind me asking?
I couldn't find a spot
to settle last night...
...so I ended up crashing
on the ferry...
...and before I knew it,
she was moving...
...and when we landed I just
started roaming around...
...the town.
-Haroldsberg.
-Right.
I ended up finding, well...
...sort of borrowed
a little boat.
Borrowed?
He really is a lawyer,
isn't he?
We get the Harvard
Law Review every month.
So anyway, l' m just...
...sort of zoning out a bit...
...when all of a sudden,
sun goes off like a light...
...then banged
into this place...
...grouped up past
all these screaming seals.
That's when I heard:
" Hello, hello".
-Seals?
-Yeah, tons.
-My God, this must be...
-Seal Rock. No shit.
Captain Compass, I ' m not
the one who veered off course.
I didn't exactly
have a radar, did l?
-You want one?
-She doesn't smoke those.
So, what exactly is it...
...that you do, anyway?
What do you do
to support yourself?
Nothing much.
Is that a full-time
occupation?
Yeah, I guess
you could say that.
Let's see, no cops...
...no home, no job,
no name, no nothing.
You should run
for President in 2000.
Country could start fresh.
That's it, further out!
She is almost free.
Keep swinging.
You' re probably wondering
about the road last night.
No, not really.
David was a
little curious, but l...
It's okay.
Let's just say...
...sometimes people...
...sort of catch you
when you' re down...
...and try to take
advantage of you.
Then when they find out
they can't...
...well, they make you pay.
Honey?
-Yeah!
-Where is the sugar?
Where it always is.
Oh, right. Sorry!
You have a beautiful home,
Mr. Weinberg.
Thanks.
It isn't mine exactly.
My great grandfather
built it.
-It's beautiful.
-Thank you.
Hot, hot, hot!
-Thanks, hon.
You earned it.
I want you guys to know
how much I appreciate this.
It's been along time
since I've been inside.
-It's our pleasure.
-Warm shower...
...never hurt anyone.
Another day, another day.
Let it die.
I' m beat.
How about you, honey,
you tired?
Yes, David, l' m tired.
You don't have to be.
I know, sweetheart, but I am.
I' m exhausted.
No! Let him sleep.
What do you mean,
let him sleep?
He's not supposed
to sleep over.
I know, but he fell asleep.
That's what sleeping over is,
falling asleep.
Come on, you can't throw
him out. Where's he gonna go?
Please, he lives
on roadsides.
What would people say if they
knew who we had here?
The paranoid schizophrenic
standing in front of me?
I offer a quick shower, and
now we' re harboring a fugitive.
Fugitives who give you bread
after you smash their heads in.
If you' re afraid,
why'd you drag him back here?
What, and leave him out
there after he helped us?
Exactly...
...helped us.
Great, now l' m Mr. Bad Guy.
You' re not Mr. Anything.
In fact, do what you want.
I' m going to bed. I' m tired.
You want me to go, right?
No, not at all,
I just couldn't sleep.
I thought you might
need a blanket.
Thanks.
Wanna have a seat?
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Do I make you nervous?
No, not at all.
Are you sure?
Put it out.
-Who do you think you are?
-You know who I am.
What are you doing here?
I never left.
Take off my boots.
You are up.
Clever.
Good morning, gentlemen.
Sorry about dozing off
like that last night.
Don't be silly.
How's your head?
I' ll live.
Thanks for the blanket,
by the way.
You' re welcome.
I thought you might be cold.
I was. Thanks.
That was sweet, dear.
-Are you hungry?
-Already ate.
-Hope that's okay.
-Of course it is.
Great, the phone's dead.
It's probably the storm.
Give it a few.
-Sugar?
-Two spoons. Thanks.
Oh, my God!
David, it looks amazing.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
If you do say so yourself.
Well, a man
of hidden talents.
-You did this?
-Just wanted to say thank you.
Anyway,
after I weaseled out...
...of the vodka-Santa Claus
Fiasco at Cheltenham...
...I show up at Yale thinking:
"Okay, time to crack down".
But of course tragedy struck
me before I ever unpacked.
I had the misfortune
of being struck down...
...by the most deadly
pair of wild blue eyes...
...God ever had
the audacity to create.
-He was a junior from El Paso.
-A Texas boy at Yale.
Yeah, with a bad habit
of stealing horses...
...at four in the morning,
and sneaking into my window...
...with waffles and a bottle
of Wild Turkey. He was nuts.
So whatever
happened to him?
My mother scared him off
and she married a Du Pont.
What's a " Du Pont"?
An obsolete tribe
from Delaware.
What about you,
have you ever been in love?
Naw, not in any sense
of the word.
This was so good.
Glad you liked it.
Now l' m set
for a good month.
A month's a long time.
I know.
So, are you two,
going across any time soon?
-Across?
-The water; to the ferry.
I hope you don't think
you' re leaving, do you?
Yeah, I thought l...
I' m sorry,
you must not know the rule.
You didn't tell him the rule?
What rule?
If you come to my house,
and do what you did...
...then you have to accept
the following challenge:
Delay your windy departure
until this evening...
...so that I may match
this formidable feast...
...with a modest meal of my
own; the victor be determined...
...by the eminent
culinary critic...
...Alexis...
...Chandler Weinberg...
...whose impeccable taste
has only grown...
...more precise
and unforgiving...
...over the years.
Rules are rules.
Yes!
Nine. Serving two.
You haven't got a prayer if you
let me get under it like that.
You' ll get that later, right?
Game point.
-Fuck!
-l' m sorry. I' ll get it.
-Be my guest.
-See all that green stuff?
It's poison ivy.
Clever.
-Cowardly is more like it.
-Alright.
Put the knives away,
l' ll get the goddamn birdie.
Careful.
-Easy, easy.
-Hold still, be a man.
That thing feels like
a Brillo pad, you be a man.
-Honey?
-Yeah?
Will you put
some cream on my back?
In a minute.
Lower.
-What are you doing?
-Going to play gold, what else?
Really,
thanks for warning me.
I told you last week.
Where the hell's my glove?
-No, you didn't.
-Well, actually, I did, but...
...Larry Cohen has Lasker teed
up for me on the first hole...
...so I don't have time to play
Alzheimer's poker with you?
-The famous Lasker deal.
-The one and only.
What's it been,
two years now?
Somebody has to do
the dirty work around here.
Don't embarrass yourself,
David.
I think you' re
projecting, dear.
I' ll get the lobsters.
Dig up some steamers...
...and please don't forget
the mushrooms.
Where's... what's his name?
Still zoned out
on the hammock?
Have him run a comb
through his hair.
Larry might stop by
for a scotch after golf.
-Put some clothes on, will you?
-Yes, sir.
I love you.
Sorry.
Sorry. I just came in here to
shut my eyes, if that's alright.
I didn't mean to wake you.
No, it's okay.
-What time is it, anyway?
-About three.
-Where's...?
-David. He's playing golf.
I think you might've left
one of these by the hammock.
I' ll pick it later.
Looks like quite a collection.
Yeah, every once in a while,
I float something out there.
Are you a writer?
No, I wouldn't go that far.
Mind if I take a peek?
Only if you don't mind.
No.
Wait, why are these all
in different handwriting?
'Cause different people
wrote them.
-You said that...
-No, they' re my words.
I just don't
write them myself.
Mind if I ask why?
'Cause I never really
learned how, that's why.
That's every funny.
I hope the transcriber
wasn't a nun.
I don't think so,
check the bottom corner.
Sandy Diamond?
Oh, Randy. Sweet fella.
Ran a scuba clinic
in Des Moines.
A scuba clinic
in Des Moines?
You should've seen
the " Ashram" in Vegas.
I think l' ll pass.
You' re gonna
get that later, right?
Can I get you something?
Are you hungry?
No, thanks.
If you need anything,
let me know.
That's our honeymoon in Capri,
I look awful.
We got that in Prague.
Said it belonged to Mussolini.
My dad shot that in Kenya.
Where's this from?
-You don't mind, do you?
-No, not at all. Help yourself.
Want some?
Sure, just a touch.
So anyway, Clarice drags me
to Bloomies go get...
...all my new
boarding school stuff...
...and I fall in love with
these horrid red pumps.
-Nine years old, huh?
-10, thank you very much.
Anyway, the big day comes,
l' m all packed up and waiting...
...in the car to take me to
the airport to pick up mummy...
...who came from Munich
to get me up to school...
...when all of a sudden...
...Lulu starts reading
the Bible to me.
Who's Lulu?
She was the new nanny. Clarice
got fired the week before.
-Why?
-I don't know. She drank.
Anyway, when we got
to the airport...
...I was so excited...
...I ran like a madman
to meet mummy at the gate...
...but instead of
hugs and kisses...
...all I got...
...was a dead cold glare.
Not a big fan of red pumps.
What?
You' re it!
Wait, I can't...!
-Sorry, are you okay?
-Better be, you' re it.
Push!
Harder!
Hold it right there, partner.
My name's Tex,
what's yours?
Wilma.
Funny, you don't look
like a Wilma to me.
Yeah?
Who do I look like?
I'd think you look more...
...Iike a Marilyn.
Alright,
l' m afraid you got me.
Yeah, I think I do.
I think I got you, too.
Yeah?
How's that, Miss Monroe?
-'Cause your name isn't Tex.
-ls not?
What is it, then?
Jack.
Jack?
Happy birthday...
...to you.
...Mister President...
...happy birthday...
...to...
...you.
Ready?
Hello? Earth to Mars.
I' m sorry.
Can I ask you a favor?
Sure, what is it?
I've got something
on the tip of my tongue.
Would you mind helping me
before it slips away?
Okay, sure.
Shoot.
It's funny...
...your worst nightmare...
This is it?
-Yeah.
-Sorry.
It's funny,
your worst nightmare...
...always seems so far away.
Then, all of a sudden...
...there it is...
...Iike a monstrous
tidal wave.
You try to escape,
but you can't.
You struggle...
...you struggle...
...your desperate
cries unheard.
Then something
strange happens:
You stop struggling.
Your cries take flight...
...and you forget
you' re drowning.
Yeah, your John Hancock.
Now we can go.
So how' d you
and David meet?
I lost my mind for a few years
after college...
...and he saved me.
Sounds like a good deal.
I hope we get lucky.
So, where are they?
Be patient.
It's not so simple.
When they' re here...
...they' re hidden.
When they' re not...
...you think they are...
They' re clever.
They' re fickle.
They feel you coming
and then they hide.
Hey.
Not bad...
...but guess what?
-What?
-You killed it.
You have to break it
above the bulb...
...otherwise
no more can grow.
But you have
great instincts.
It's a "chanterelle".
David's gonna love you.
I' m in love with you.
I know it's kind
of sudden, but...
...now that I've laid
eyes on you...
...well, it's just all over.
I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
The Amanitus Muscarius
is a rare coastal mushroom...
...originally used by the
lroquois to combat red malaria.
It also happens to be...
...a highly potent
aphrodisiac.
Then there's its infamous
sister the Amanita Rubinica.
Affectionately known
as the " Purple Julie"...
...it' ll kill you
in less than a minute.
Guess what they have
in common?
What?
They' re twins.
How can you tell them apart?
" Purple Julie", purple poison.
The Amanitus Muscarius.
-The aphrodisiac?
-Right.
How do you know
so much about mushrooms?
My father.
He used to drag me out here
from the time I'd walk...
...and go on about their
differences, their stories...
...their flavors and
their powers, everything.
Should've seen his eyes
when he talked about them.
Pure magic.
Does he still come out here?
He committed suicide
when I was eight.
-l' m sorry.
-Don't be. He's better off.
What about your mom?
We don't speak.
Why's that?
She hates David.
Pick a hand.
What are you doing?
Behave.
I am behaving.
No.
Let's go, it's getting late.
Are you coming?
I have to be getting back.
Look, I just want
to tell you...
-I'd like to say...
-Apology accepted.
-Hello.
-Hi, honey.
How' d it go with Lasker?
You've been gone forever.
David, are you okay?
Yeah, it's just...
-I had some bad clams.
-You had clams?
After golf? But I got
clams for dinner.
-I know.
-Why'd you only get 2 lobsters?
Well, I just...
Because I didn't think
I want to eat any dinner...
...'cause of the clams.
Right. And Larry?
He didn't come back with you?
No, he didn't...
He said to say hi.
Hi from Lasker, too.
I should sit down.
I think I need a compress.
Will you go into the kitchen
and get me a wet cloth?
Lex, he doesn't know
where anything is.
I' ll go.
You have a very loyal wife.
I think tonight's
not such a good night...
...for this food showdown.
I' m gonna put him to bed...
...and run you over
to lslesboro, okay?
She may be right.
We should probably
take a rain check.
Okay, but I got to say...
...I was kind of looking
forward to the challenge.
You know what, so was l.
I fact,
I think a warm shower...
...and a cold drink will put
me right back in the swing.
-David, I don't think...
-Exactly, don't think...
...drink!
It's amazing, David.
So did you two
have a good day?
I gave him the grand tour.
How did you like it?
It was nice.
-Good luck.
-Thanks for everything.
See you in twenty.
Call the phone company,
it's still out.
Done.
Here, this is for you.
How about that?
-How thoughtful.
-I made it here.
It's very nice, thank you.
What are you doing
back here?
Is everything okay,
where's David?
We got in a little...
He's outside
closing up or something.
-You got in a little what?
-Jam.
Boat died.
-Had to paddle back.
-l' m sorry.
I' ll be right back,
do you need anything?
A sea plane would be nice.
There you are, poor thing.
What happened?
The boat conked out halfway
there. It was a nightmare.
-I know, I heard.
-Did you?
-Yes, I did.
-So, I guess James Dean
...is gonna be making
himself at home.
We could always call
Mike and Mary.
What are you gonna do,
scream across the bay?
-Right, the phone.
-The phone.
Why is this all my fault?
You think I want him here?
-I don't know, do you?
-No.
Good. That makes two of us.
You know...
...I look at you...
...and it' s funny...
...you don't remind me
of myself exactly...
...but you remind me of
a certain time in my youth.
I remember what I used
to think love was then.
I thought it was
the fireworks...
...the explosions...
...the highlights.
But it's not.
It's time.
To go through seasons
together...
...through change...
...through the
ups and downs...
...to be able...
...to look your beloved...
...in the eye and say:
" We did that, together...
...as one".
" We chose each other...
...above all others".
That is...
...Iove.
It's unexplainable.
It' s a secret...
...that can only be known...
...once...
...you've done...
...the time.
It's nice what
you said downstairs.
I meant it.
What a weekend, huh?
You' re telling me.
Sorry I left you alone today.
Don't worry.
So everything was okay?
Yeah, you know?
You weren't bored
or anything?
No, not especially.
I mean, I wasn't not bored...
...I' m glad you got to do
what you wanted.
Good.
Just as long as
you were not bored.
Morning, sweetheart.
Morning.
What's wrong?
Look in the mirror.
-Christ.
-Want me to put Calamine on?
-No.
-Suit yourself.
-How long have you been up?
-I don't know, an hour.
Are you ready?
Almost. Are you?
Got over an hour.
Where's your watch?
-l' m not wearing it.
-You always wear it.
Not today.
So, where's our little friend?
Outside, I think.
-I better take care of the boat.
-It's done.
-What do you mean, it's done?
-He did it.
-When?
-This morning.
Said it was a loose spark.
Speaking of the Devil...
-Morning, David.
-lt' ll be ready in a minute.
Cool.
What' ll be ready
in a minute?
-My shirt.
-His shirt.
It was still wet this morning.
-Don't you have another one?
-Nope.
Don't, it's going to spread.
Where else can it spread?
I' ll just go and see
if your shirt's ready.
I like your face...
Your watch.
The face is cool.
Alexis gave that to me.
It's beautiful.
We fixed the phone,
by the way. Alexis and me.
-Really? When?
-This morning. Woke me up...
...and asked me to hold two
wires together while she taped.
Any calls?
-Thanks.
-So, you' re quite the mechanic.
It was nothing,
I found the cable cut out back.
It's probably raccoons.
-Good for you. Any calls?
-No.
There were 2 messages
in Boston.
Larry called Boston.
Lasker looks 50-50.
Tom is desperate
for squash.
He's always desperate.
Did you call anybody?
No, why?
No reason. I was wondering
if it was calling out or not?
Of course it is. How do you
think I checked the machine?
Yeah.
Would you like anything?
-No, thanks.
-Come on, eat something.
How about a banana?
Dab of milk would be nice.
-So is everything okay?
-Yes. Thanks.
Okay, bye.
Who was it?
-Mike.
-Good, are they coming by?
Still in Portland
with Mary's mother.
They' ll be back tomorrow.
Mary says hi.
What's so funny?
I don't know.
Couples, I guess.
Couples?
Maybe someday,
you' ll look in the mirror...
...and have a snicker
to yourself.
Come on, David.
Here it comes.
I don't want one.
You always have a banana.
Not today, so next time you
feel the need to generalize...
...you can say: " You almost
always have a banana".
Thank you, David, maybe
I won't say anything at all.
-May I have a cigarette?
-Yeah.
There's more in the fridge.
Would you like a glass?
-Would you like a glass, David?
-No, I wouldn't. But thank you.
Are your hands dirty,
Alexis?
Excuse me?
I was wondering why you were
cleaning a clean glass.
I thought maybe it was
because your hands were dirty.
I don't know what kind of
poison is flowing through you...
...but whatever it is
keep it to yourself.
Sorry about this.
I know this isn't as much
fun as the boat house...
...but life isn't all
cowboys and lndians, is it?
Is it?
What in God's name
are you trying to accomplish?
It's not too bright in here,
is it?
Honey, would you close
the shades for him?
You know how much he likes
the shades closed in the day.
All right, l' ll do it.
-You bastard.
-I was setting the right mood.
Maybe you should go outside
and take a walk and cool down.
-Should l?
-Yes, I think you should.
Wouldn't that be
convenient?
Especially if I kept walking
and then you and Valentino...
...could call all your friends
and maybe even " mummy"...
...if she' ll take the call, and you
let them know that bastard...
...with his endless mood
swings and depressions...
...is gone once and for all;
the gold-digging kike...
...who squanders
the family millions...
...and makes
everyone miserable...
...is finally out
of the picture.
Wouldn't that be a relief?
No more deadbeat days,
no more sleepless nights...
...no more David Weinberg.
Wouldn't that be a dream?
I feel so sorry for you.
Yeah, you better be
sorry for me.
Who wouldn't feel
sorry for me?
Seven years stuck
in a coffin with you.
A coffin?
A coffin.
Are you sure you want
to say that, David?
I was sure the day
I married you.
I just didn't have
the courage to admit it.
Have I gone too far?
Should I not be honest?
There she goes: the Lexie
Chandler we all know and love.
When in doubt,
shut them out!
Shut, shut, shut.
Shut, shut, shut,
shut them out!
Shut them out till
all the doors are closed.
She's dragged us all down
into her coffin...
...just like daddy.
Get out.
Get out!
Excuse me?
Get out.
David, no!
David!
David, l' m begging
you please...
No!
He's all yours, Lex.
Get off my island, David.
Your island?
My island.
Alas!
The wolf...
...sheds her wool.
Alas!
Are you okay?
Where is he?
Gone.
Did you call the police?
No.
No cops.
What are we going to do
with that?
It's funny...
...your worst nightmare
always seems so far away.
Then, all of a sudden...
...there it is...
...Iike a monstrous
tidal wave.
You try to escape,
but you can't.
You struggle, struggle
and struggle...
...your desperate
cries unheard.
Then something
strange happens.
You stop struggling.
Your cry takes flight...
" Your cry takes flight.
...and you forget
you' re drowning.
And you forget
you' re drowning".
Those were the
departing words...
...of a unique
woman of courage...
...for whom the
struggles of life...
...had become
too much to bear.
Let me implore you,
however...
...amidst your sorrow...
...to remember little
Lexie Chandler...
...the incarnation
of pure innocence...
...and wondrous joy...
...bounding barefoot...
...along the rocky shores...
...of Dark Harbor.
That was a beautiful service,
Paul.
David.
Alexis.
Tale off the glasses, David.
Her suicide note.
Thank you for coming.
Finally.
How are you?
I have had some bad nights.
Well, I am here now.
That is...
...all I wanted.
You proved it.
I hope so.