Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States ofAmerica.
And to the republic,
for which it stands.
One nation under God,
indivisible, with liberty -
and justice forall.
Take your wig off.
Turn and face the wall.
Face the wall.
All right, that's it.
- Are you a natural blonde?
- Chicken Delight! He delivers!
Don't put that in here.
She ain't my type.
That's my wife you're talking about.
She's here for our conjugal visit.
Come, let daddy show you
what he's got in his pants for you.
She's got the same thing under her skirt
that you've got in your pants.
Come on, you guys,
we've got a lady here.
Have you got any concealed weapons
they didn't find up front?
- You've got something concealed...
- But it ain't no weapon.
Let's see you strip
just to make sure.
A star is born!
Kirkland, watch your hands.
Come on, Kirkland. Let's go.
Can you make a phone call for me?
Where the hell is he?
What do you mean, he's in jail?
My lawyer's in jail?
Contempt of court?
He's too goddamn emotional.
Get him. I've had a car accident.
I haven't left the scene
of the accident, I'm in it!
Can't you hear the confusion?
Do you hear this noise?
They're trying to get me out ofthe car.
I'm trapped because some prick...
Could you move back,
so we can get you out?
Can't you see I'm on the phone?
Keep it down!
I'm trying... Goddammit!
Tell Arthur to get over here.
I'm on Eager Street. Where are we?
Eager Street... Just tell him to
get over here. You can't miss it.
I understand you took a swing
at Judge Fleming. Is that true?
Kiley, why not do something about
that kid? Put him someplace else.
They're just having some fun
with him, that's all.
- Fun?
- Sometimes the boys get bored.
For you,
it's still new and exciting.
Sign here.
Why don't you ease up on the judge?
He's your kind of guy, huh?
Yeah, Fleming's a tough man.
Hates scum almost as much as we do.
Good morning, Mr Kirkland.
Carl!
Come on. Here. Are you all right?
Sue the son of a bitch who did this
for every cent he's got. Every nickel.
- Carl, are you all right?
- Disappear.
- Miss, why don't you...
- She's not hurt. Nothing to report.
- Wait in the car.
- There's no need for the wife to know.
After all I was your first client,
Arthur. You broke cherry on me.
Not the time to go down memory lane.
Let's just get you to the hospital.
You're the best, Arthur.
Get every nickel and put him away.
- I'll see he gets the death penalty.
- Death is okay too.
- You stink. Did somebody piss on you?
- Get him out of here.
Let nobody use my car phone. I'm in
the hospital and some jerk calls Rome.
You son of a bitch! You lunatic!
Carl, you're gonna have a stroke.
You'll have to deal with my lawyer.
- You'll die for this! He's the best!
- It's not even my car.
Be calm, Carl. Be calm.
- I have a terrible headache.
- You'll be all right. I'll call you.
- What about this guy here?
- He says he's all right.
It's a friend's car.
I just borrowed it for the night.
- How am I gonna tell him?
- You should go to the hospital.
- I'm okay, but the car...
- Let me take you to the hospital.
My horoscope said it would be a great
day and look what happened. Shit!
It's not going to
be that way this time.
We should request a postponement.
That would put us into January.
Look at me when I'm talking to you!
- The DA is willing to go two years.
- That's a lot of fucking time, man.
- I ain't kissing nobody's ass.
- I'm not asking you to.
Just give it a little pat.
Arthur. Arthur.
Excuse me. Hold it, Wenke.
- Where are you going?
- The bathroom.
Go home and change.
You look like shit.
What would you say if I walked
into court looking like that?
What would you say?
I don't wanna
keep harping on this, -
- but the Ethics Committee is checking
up on everyone. You've gotta watch it.
Last week two lawyers were
disbarred on minor charges.
You get thrown in jail
on contempt of court.
Fleming got me crazy.
Push him on that McCullaugh thing
and there will be big trouble.
McCullaugh's innocent
and Fleming won't look at the evidence.
- What do you want me to do?
- You don't threaten a judge!
Will you do me a personal favour?
Put this on.
I got Fleming
first thing this morning.
Give him my love.
The tie, I like it.
It's Fleming's favourite colour.
All rise. Criminal Court of
Baltimore City is now in session.
The Honourable
Henry T. Fleming presiding.
Be seated.
If Your Honour please,
for the first matter -
- the State would call case number
57746898, State versus Robert Wenke.
Mr Wenke, may I ask you
to step forward, please.
How many times have you been
before the bench, Mr Wenke?
Three times, Your Honour.
Once for assault, once for arson,
once for grand larceny.
And now indecent exposure.
What's the matter? Can't you decide
what you wanna be when you grow up?
Anything to say?
Yes, Your Honour.
I'm a loyal Colts fan.
You are also a revolting,
despicable scum of the earth -
- who should be
squashed like a cockroach.
I object. My client has not
been found guilty yet.
You're absolutely right, Counsellor.
It's now 9:40.
At 9:41 he will be guilty.
I find the defendant guilty.
Sentence to be imposed later.
I would like Mr Wenke's bail
to be continued.
- Bail is revoked.
- Thank you.
The State will now call
number 57746899.
That was very good work.
Very nice. Colts fan.
I need Colts? Terrific, Wenke.
Then you do know?
The big white house?
With the fat columns out in front
on Greenway Avenue?
Guess how much that house is worth.
- I don't know.
- Take a guess.
Seven million.
243,000 dollars.
Now that's some nut I've got, huh?
I just need some more accident cases.
I ought to throw banana peels around.
Recess is almost over,
and I only have this lottery case...
Did you knowthere's a guy
eating something off your table?
The guy you're prosecuting.
He's eating the lottery tickets.
Holy shit!
Gibson, get the hell away!
- Don't swallow, you son of a bitch!
- That's my client!
Don't swallow!
Gentlemen, need I remind you
you are in a court of law?
Now let's proceed
in an orderly fashion.
What the hell are you doing?
Does the defence have
anything to add?
Your Honour...
I guess I should request a recess -
- so my client could get something
to eat. He's obviously very hungry.
My client, McCullaugh.
Could I see him for a minute?
Sure, Mr Kirkland.
Stick your hand out.
Mr Kirkland, what happened?
I just want to reaffirm what I said
yesterday. We'll get you out.
I knowyou're trying,
but this is crazy, you know?.
I know it.
You said you had evidence
that proves I'm innocent.
- Yes, you're innocent.
- And Judge Fleming agrees, right?
If everyone agrees I'm innocent,
why am I going back to jail?
There's enough proof,
but the court won't accept it.
- Why not?
- Well, there's a law...
It says that evidence must be submitted
within a certain time period.
And ours came in three days late.
What difference does that make?
Even if it came in three years late.
They've got the proofthey need.
They should let me go.
The judge sends me to jail and he knows
I'm innocent. What's going on?
It's gonna take more time.
Any otherjudge would let you out.
But Fleming goes
by the letter ofthe law.
Jeff, I promise I'll get you out.
I promise.
He promises to get you out.
Don't worry.
Judge Fleming.
I want to apologise for my behaviour
in the courtroom the other day.
I don't want to hear it.
I don't want to hear anything.
That's understandable, sir.
But I thought maybe we could
discuss this McCullaugh case.
You and l, man to man.
Off the record.
Ifyou try to make a deal with me,
you might wind up back in jail.
A deal? No, sir.
I'm not trying to make a deal.
I understand your strict
enforcement of the statute.
But my client's constitutional rights
are being denied.
- My client is innocent.
- I don't give a shit about your client.
Hi, Sherry.
- Hi, Mr Kirkland.
- Mrs Tate, how are you?
He'll be right with you.
- Boy, do you look tired.
- Coffee, please.
Mrs Tate wants to talk. Her son broke
his leg again. Neighbour's driveway.
And Bricker wants to know ifyour client
will settle for 60,000 dollars.
Coffee, please.
You have three new clients today.
One's a whiplash, one's divorce.
And the third has to do with amnesia.
I don't know what it is.
What are you doing?
- No foam.
- That's because it's deodorant.
Don't forget to visit
your grandfather today.
- And be in court at two fifteen.
- Coffee, please.
Do you want some coffee?
Sherry, stay with me today, dear.
I need you today.
Arthur.
Arthur, come here.
Hi, Judge.
Are we gonna get together
this weekend?
I don't know. You're the only one
I've been dating these days.
You promised
you'd go flying with me.
I gotta tell you...
I'm not too fond of anything
that takes place off the ground.
I don't know.
I've got a thing about heights.
- This is flying. It's different.
- How high up do you go?
How high do you wanna go?
Come on, it'll be good for you.
- Besides, it gets lonesome up there.
- Why don't you take your wife?
The last thing we did together
was get married.
Come on, Arthur. You promised me.
- All right. What time?
- Sunday morning. Ten o'clock.
Do you always carry
that thing with you?
There's law and there's order.
And that's order.
Do you like egg rolls?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Easy, easy, easy. You got it.
You son of a gun.
So, it's another week already?
Another week.
I don't know where time goes.
No problems, Grandpa?
Everything all right?
See this one? Wonderful woman. I went
to her husband's funeral. Fine man.
Gitel?
Hello, Sam.
How are you?
This is my grandson, Arthur.
- I'm pleased to meet you.
- Good to meet you.
- He goes to law school.
- I'm a lawyer.
Take my advice.
Don't be in a hurry.
He's a nice-looking boy.
- My grandson.
- Yes...
- Good to meet you.
- Pleased to have met you too.
So, it's been a week.
Yeah, it's been a week. Last week we
went for a ride in the car. Remember?
That's a good machine.
Always give signals when you turn.
Right. Left.
So...
Are you a good lawyer?
Are you honest?
Well, I don't know.
Being honest doesn't have much to do
with being a lawyer, Grandpa.
Ifyou're not honest,
you've got nothing.
Your parents should see you now.
To hell with them.
They never cared before.
Why should they care now?
- They're still your parents.
- No.
You raised me. You're the one
who put me through law school.
You're a wonderful man, Grandpa.
But your son, he's a shit.
He was born with colic.
Sam, I love you.
Look at you.
Filled out, like a man.
Soon you'll look like a lawyer
and you'll be a lawyer.
I am a lawyer, Sam.
I've been a lawyer for twelve years.
So, it's another week already.
- Do you know Jules Stouffer?
- Yes, I do.
- He was a client ofyours, right?
- Yes.
Wasn't he originally
represented by Alvin Burton?
- Yes, that is correct.
- Why did he change representation?
I handled him on an assault charge.
That's my area, not Burton's.
Did Stouffer express
dissatisfaction with Mr Burton?
Not at all. Burton's an excellent
lawyer. Are you going after him?
- We're not going after anyone.
- Do you know David Crebbs?
We're reviewing certain accusations
to determine if they're true -
and to clean our own house.
So please do not overdramatize this.
It's not the McCarthy hearings.
Oh, that's a relief.
So you're not gonna ask me: "Are you
now or have you ever been a lawyer?"
- That wasn't amusing, Mr Kirkland.
- Do you know David Crebbs?
No, it wasn't, Miss...?
Packer. This isn't amusing. It is
ridiculous. Yes, I know David Crebbs.
Have you ever seen...
Is this mike working?
- Do you know David Crebbs?
- Why are we using microphones?
- Why don't we just talk to each other?
- This is a hearing, Mr Kirkland.
Yes. It's a hearing.
- Do you know Jules Stouffer?
- We've already asked that.
Are we through with Stouffer?
How about Alvin Burton?
- Do you know David Crebbs?
- I've already asked that.
- What did he say?
- He said yes.
Have you ever seen him
intoxicated in court?
David Crebbs has a speech impediment.
Check your records. It's in there.
As answer to your question:
No, he doesn't drink. Not at all.
At this point
I would just like to say -
- that what this committee is doing
in theory is highly commendable.
However, in practice it sucks.
And I am not going to answer
any more questions.
What do you think
we're trying to do in there?
- Want a drink?
- No.
Whatever you may think, we're not
conducting some kind of witch-hunt.
What are you doing then?
You might not be aware ofthis, -
- but there's a lot of corruption
that nobody's doing anything about.
- Do you think you're doing something?
- Yes, I do.
That committee is
a very dangerous farce.
Whoa, Mr Kirkland.
I spend fourteen hours a day
on that committee.
I don't do it to get
a few good laughs.
You could spend the rest ofyour life.
You'll wind up a cop.
Maybe ruining the careers of a few guys
who wiped their ass the wrong way.
Other than that, nothing.
So what do you think?
About what?
About me. What do you think?
Think I'm kind of interesting?
Somebody you'd like
to have a drink with?
I think that you're crazy.
What about Daniel's?
Say, around seven thirty?
I don't think so.
Eight?
Eight thirty.
All right.
I'm Arthur Kirkland.
You wanted to see me?
Yeah.
My man, Bambi,
he recommended you real highly.
He said, Arthur Kirkland
was the man to see.
Okay, Ralph,
tell me what happened.
It says here
you were involved in a robbery.
No, sir.
What happened is, it was time
to come down on a nigger.
It's like smoking. They've got to
have a nigger every twenty minutes.
What happened is...
I was in an alley, petting my dog,
when they came down on me.
It states here
the dog was attacking you -
when you were seen in the alley.
Well, my dog, he gets like that.
It also states that the dog
belonged to a Mrs B. Jackson.
He sure looked like my dog.
He had that little...
It also states that when asked
what you were doing you replied:
"I don't know nothing
about that taxi cab."
That's true. I don't.
- How did you knowthere was one?
- Mr Kirkland, there's always one.
Ralph, tell me the truth or get another
lawyer. I don't need the bullshit.
Okay.
I was in that cab,
but I didn't rob it.
It was my cousin's idea.
I didn't know nothing. He's crazy.
- What's your cousin's name?
- I don't know. I mean...
- He lives over on Hillsdale.
- You don't know your cousin's name?
Who do you think you're talking to?
Do you think I'm an idiot?
I read a report, I can tell
if somebody's bullshitting me.
Give me straight answers
or get another lawyer.
I don't have time to listen to
some jive-ass put-me-on.
Okay.
It wasn't my idea,
but I did knowwhat was coming down.
See me and my cousin Royce...
Royce Shavers.
He figures that
since I am the way I am...
Mr Kirkland,
I can look really fine sometimes.
I'm sure you can.
Royce figures we can be a couple.
You know, a man and a woman couple.
A cab driver will pick up a couple
faster than he will two nigger men.
We got into a cab
on Garrison Boulevard.
And we asked him to take us down to
the harbour like we were tourists.
I can't go to jail, man.
I just can't do it.
I can't go to that place.
Please, Mr Kirkland,
you've got to help me.
Please...
Okay, I'll help you, Ralph.
Just don't lie to me.
- Okay?
- Yes, sir.
- Don't lie to me, okay?
Thank you.
Thanks for bringing me home, Gail.
Oh, God.
You really take renting an unfurnished
apartment literally, don't you?
It doesn't have to stay this way.
What happened? Did your wife
take you in the divorce settlement?
She had a better lawyer.
Do you get to see your kids much?
They're in California.
Phone calls, holidays.
Put the food out.
I'll get the plates.
I guess I was lucky.
We never had any kids.
- How long were you married?
- Three years.
- Were you in love?
- No...
I was in love with the law.
You knowwhat I mean?
You got a serving spoon?
Serving spoon.
Thank you.
So, do you eat out a lot?
- Yeah. Do you?
- Yeah.
The committee works
just about every night.
How did you feel when you
walked out on the committee?
- Did you feel daggers in your back?
- That's a very dangerous group.
Jesus, here we go...
Arthur, why do you feel
it's dangerous?
You con the public to think
you're doing something, and you're not.
We are doing something. Protecting
the public from corrupt lawyers.
You're skimming the surface.
You're not going after real power.
Wow, that's scary.
What real power, Arthur?
- You don't know?
- No. Tell me.
Well, now we know
they're definitely safe.
What makes you think
you know so goddamn much?
- I don't know so much.
- No, tell me.
What makes you
the great voice of authority?
I don't pretend to be
a voice of authority.
I just don't think
you knowwhat you're doing.
Oh, I see.
This is nice, don't you think?
No, I don't find this
particularly nice, Arthur.
I'm angry again, you know.
I don't like being angry.
- It's not very pleasant.
- Why do you criticize me for what I do?
I'm not criticizing you.
You're taking it too personally.
The committee is doing something
about what's going on.
We're not sitting in jail at nights
because of contempt of court.
- Do you know what that's about?
- Yeah. You punched Judge Fleming.
- You knowwhy?
- I have no idea. Tell me.
I have a client who's in jail
because of a faulty tail light.
- And I can't get him out.
- What do you mean?
Do you want to hear a story about
our wonderful judicial system?
Sure.
A guy named Jeff McCullaugh
is going down a highway one night.
And the cops stop him
because his tail light isn't working.
They run a make on him.
The computer kicks back -
- that a Jeff McCullaugh is wanted
for assault with a deadly weapon.
- Was it the same guy?
- No.
But he fits the description,
so they arrest him.
Did he tell them
they had the wrong person?
He tried.
He told the public defender.
But he was too busy.
He never bothered to check.
- Are you serious?
- Wait, it gets better.
While Jeff is in jail,
a guard is stabbed -
- and the knife is planted
in Jeff's cell.
And Jeff is trialled on a new charge:
Assaulting a guard with a deadly weapon.
And a trial date is set. Six months
from the time he was first picked up.
I'll make a long story short.
Six months go by -
- and a very shaky, very crazy
Jeff McCullaugh goes to court.
The public defender tells Jeff
that he can get him off -
- if he pleads guilty.
He'll make a deal with the judge.
So he pleads guilty
even though he's innocent. Right.
The deal was made
with a Judge Callahan.
The day ofthe trial
Judge Callahan cannot be found.
Fleming is in his place.
Fleming doesn't know about the deal.
Jeff pleads guilty.
Fleming sentences Jeff
to five years in prison.
So, one little guy
has already spent -
- a year and a half in jail
because his lights didn't work.
I've spent the last year gathering
evidence to prove he's innocent.
And I prove it.
I bring it all into Fleming's court -
and he throws it out.
- Why?
- It came in three days late.
Holy shit!
That's incredible.
It's not incredible. It's Fleming.
No, Arthur.
That's the law.
You can't fault Fleming legally.
Because he was going by
the letter ofthe law.
- Are you kidding?
- No, I'm not.
You talk to me like that
you won't get me into bed, dear.
Yes, I will.
I've had tougher cases.
- You're so easy.
- You knew that, huh?
That's why you went out with me.
Finish your egg roll.
Arthur! Arthur!
You'll never guess
who the police just grabbed.
- Take a guess.
- Warren, please...
This may sound crazy,
but Judge Fleming was just taken away.
- What do you mean, taken away?
- Arrested.
Come on.
I'm telling you. They just arrested
your very own favourite judge.
- Judge Fleming?
- Judge Fleming.
What's the joke, Warren?
There's a joke connected to this.
There is no joke.
I don't know what it's about.
They're sitting on this very hard.
I can't get anything from anybody.
Warren...
Let me knowthe...
- Judge, we're ready to reconvene.
- I'll be right there.
Congratulations, Counsel.
Thank you very much.
What did I do?
Come here, come here.
Judge Fleming.
I was right. He was arrested
this morning and booked.
- We know that.
- You'll never guess what for.
- Take a guess.
- What for?
Rape.
Fleming was booked on a rape.
- I can't stand it.
- Isn't that the best?
- Rape!
- I don't believe it.
That's not the best.
Oh, no. I'm gonna tell you
the punchline.
You're gonna love this.
His people just called.
Mr Fleming would like you
to represent him.
Me?
Why me?
I hate the son of a bitch.
I'm going crazy!
Mr Kirkland,
as you undoubtedly know, -
- Judge Fleming has been accused,
falsely I might add, -
- of sexually assaulting a young lady.
He wants you to represent him.
Excuse me.
- What, may I ask, is so funny?
- I just think it's...
It's just crazy.
I don't think it's so crazy.
Two lawyers up in the third-floor
men's room think differently.
Right now one ofthem is laughing
so hard he's choking in the sink.
I'm aware that I'm not
particularly well liked.
But the fact is that I'm innocent
and I will have that proven in court.
Mr Bates and I feel,
in this particular situation, -
- you would be perfect
to handle my defence.
What is this? The two of you got
together and came up with that one.
That's a beauty.
The real question is: Why?
Why me, fellas?
We need you for political reasons.
Political reasons? What kind?
This case will create
a lot of media coverage.
The animosity between you and the judge
is well known. But we can use that.
Why else defend a man
you dislike so much -
- unless he was truly innocent?
And he is, you know.
Remarkable. Remarkable.
But personally
I don't give a shit.
You smug son of a bitch!
Henry! Henry!
I've never committed a crime
in my life.
Judge, ifyou're innocent,
truly innocent, -
- you don't need me.
Get yourself another lawyer.
What are you laughing at?
I really hate
to tell you this, but -
- you remind me a little
of my ex-husband.
In what way?
Because, during sex,
he would always say:
"Go! Go!"
"Go"?
I don't say "go".
- I heard you say "go".
- No, I don't say "go".
"Go" is dumb.
I say "God".
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
I could have sworn
I heard a couple of go's.
That was "God".
I said "Ooooh..."
It sounded like "go".
And then I said "God".
"Ooooh, God".
Oh, God...
Yeah? Who is it?
Arthur, it's Jay!
- Jay?
- What the hell...?
It's my partner.
Jay. Jay?
All right, all right.
What do you say?
Hell of a night tonight.
- It's two o'clock in the morning.
- I know. The bars just closed.
So, what are you doing here?
- I came to ask you a question.
- Oh, yeah? What?
- I'm a good lawyer, right?
- Right.
- I got Earl Soames off, right?
- What are you talking about?
I got Earl Soames...
- Yeah, you got him off.
- I didn'tjust get him off.
I got him off on murder.
And we all know Mr Soames did it.
Right, he did it.
He was guilty. We all know that.
Brilliant defence. Brilliant.
- Brilliant defence, Arthur.
- Right.
Brilliant. Brilliant!
Brilliant!
I got him off on a technicality.
I know, Jay. Right. Good.
- Mr Soames did it again.
- What do you mean?
At twelve o'clock tonight
he killed two kids.
Oh, Jesus.
He killed kids, you see.
Oh, Jay...
- I gotta take a piss.
- Jay...
My partner.
- There's women in here.
- Hello.
Arthur, what's going on?
Come on, it won't hurt you. Just duck.
You've got about three feet.
For Christ's sake, get in.
How are you feeling? Ready to go?
I thought you flew planes.
With wings.
I've been flying helicopters
ever since Korea. Get in.
Button up. Close the door.
I gotta tell you, Judge.
I'm not too happy about this.
Just relax, Arthur.
Could we maybe just go out a bit?
Kind ofjust go and hover?
We'll do any goddamn thing you want.
Now hold on to your cojones.
This is what it's all about!
Pretty, isn't it?
I don't want to talk.
What?
Did you ever skydive?
- Did you ever skydive?
- No! Why?
You oughta try it.
You might learn something.
I was skydiving once
and my main chute didn't open.
My reserve didn't open either.
There I was, plunging to the earth.
As I hit the treetops
I discovered the meaning of life.
- Which is?
- It sucks, Arthur. It really sucks.
They used to keep
Native Dancer down there.
Native Dancer, the horse.
They kept him down there.
Beautiful animal.
- Where are we going?
- Do you have any place in mind?
Down. I would prefer to go down.
Just relax and enjoy it, Arthur.
The old Chinese proverb.
Great, isn't it?
Oh, my!
Let me showyou something.
Look at that.
Wild, isn't it?
- We've hit it.
- Hit what? What did we hit?
The halfway point.
There's a little game I play.
I always calculate how far I can go
on the fuel I have and still get back.
Then I figure out the halfway point
and I go just a little beyond it.
You mean
we're beyond the halfway point?
we're not gonna make it back?
Maybe, maybe not.
Well, land.
Land! Put it down!
Come on, we're all right.
Ifwe're beyond the halfway point
we're not all right. Land!
Here we go! Heading back.
Sixteen years of marriage and my wife
still won't eat Chinese food.
It's crazy. Especially since
we met in a Chinese restaurant.
How are we doing?
Where are we? Are we back yet?
Trust me, Arthur.
It's a protest. She relates
Chinese food to our marriage.
We're not gonna make it back!
I knew it! I knew it!
Arthur, look at that.
I told you I had good instincts.
Hang on, Arthur. Hang on now.
Hang on...
Hang on, Arthur. We'll make it.
Hang on!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
Hang on! Hang on!
Home free.
We almost made it
right on the button.
Another ninety feet.
I told you I had good instincts.
Come on, let's go ashore.
Shit, my wheel.
Come on, Arthur.
It's easier when you
take the belt off. That's it.
Are you all right?
Come on, let's get some coffee.
You'll be all right.
Your adrenaline's still charged.
You have to admit
it makes you feel alive, vital.
When I think
that we could be dead right now...
Listen, why is everyone
so preoccupied with death?
I'm not usually preoccupied with it,
but this seems like a valid time.
Another chicken salad sandwich.
Arthur?
No.
Let's get back to Fleming.
- You won't consider taking his case?
- Nope. Not interested.
You'd better be interested.
There are some very powerful people
who can ruin your career.
Ruin my career? What do you mean?
For one they can have you disbarred.
Do you want some more coffee?
Disbarred?
What are you talking about?
Did you ever have a client
named Ernest Drago?
Drago, yeah. What about him?
You gave the police information
that led to his conviction.
Drago was a nut. Drago was insane.
He sat in my office and rattled off
the most grotesque fantasies imaginable.
I handled him on a burglary charge
and I heard that stuff every day.
His favourite fantasy was:
What would happen if he stuck
a firecracker in somebody's mouth?
So, I read in the newspapers
that there was this nut -
- who held people at gunpoint and
forced cherry bombs in their mouths.
I knew it was Drago,
so I told the police.
You didn't prevent a crime.
You betrayed a client.
- You violated the code of ethics.
- What are you talking about?
- What's going on?
- Arthur, they want you.
You're a very principled lawyer
with no political ties.
I tell ya...
They want me to defend Fleming
because of my moral integrity.
And if I don't defend him
I'll be disbarred for being unethical.
Look, Arthur. Put aside your
personal feelings. Take the case.
You've worked too hard.
Don't throw your career away.
I can't believe this.
I just don't believe it.
- Judge, I want McCullaugh freed.
- Nothing can be done.
I don't buy that, Judge.
Just reopen the case.
Reopen the case
and I'll get him acquitted.
Now look. You are in no position
to ask for anything.
But I'll see what I can do to help.
Perhaps there's
an exception to the statute.
Okay.
Okay. So, why don't you
tell me about the girl?
This Leah Shephard.
Can you tell me anything about her?
What do you want to know? I saw her
a few times. She works at City Hall.
- Did you have sex on the first date?
- Yes. First and second time.
- That's why this makes no sense.
- What do you think happened to her?
I assure you I did not rape her,
but...
I really don't know. Maybe an angry
boyfriend showed up after I left.
Angry boyfriend?
That's a little mild, don't you think?
She wasn'tjust raped, she was
sadistically beaten and sodomized.
That's a bit beyond angry boyfriend.
You're right. I'm sorry.
How did I get into this? I've been
involved in the law for thirty years.
And I can't find five people
who'll believe I'm innocent.
- Will you take a lie detector test?
- Why? It's not admissible evidence.
I know. I would like you
to do it for me.
- I'll think about it.
- No, no...
- I said, I would think about it.
- You can't do this.
I need a polygraph
to prepare your case.
- If I'm going to be your lawyer...
- Ifyou're going to be?
- Mr Kirkland, you are my lawyer.
- I know. I'm your lawyer.
And as your lawyer
there are certain demands...
As I said to you before,
you don't demand anything.
Now sit down.
I have a lot ofwork to do.
I said, sit down.
Leave it out here.
- Jeff, what happened to you?
- Somebody beat me up.
- What for?
- I don't know. I didn't ask.
Listen, I talked to Fleming.
We'll work something out.
We'll get you out of here.
When?
It's gonna take maybe three weeks.
I promise I'll get you out by then.
- Three weeks?
- That's the best I can do.
- You must be kidding.
- It's the best I can do.
- What am I supposed to do?
- You're gonna have to hang in there.
- Just take care ofyourself.
- Take care?
I got myself locked up in solitary to
get away from some guys. I can't fight.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org