Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Do you know what true love means?
Do you know what that'll mean...
...standing up by the person
who takes your hand?
- I'm close.
- Oh, Richie!
You just want one thing.
When you're done, it'll be all over for us.
- I brought some of these.
- No!
- Not yet.
- What do you mean, '"not yet'"?
Half hour? Five years?
You always say, '"not yet.'"
Not yet!
A guy could die from this.
You want to be responsible for that?
- I'll do it with my hands.
- No.
I could do it with my hand.
Richie, I got my reputation to worry about.
You're a guy. Guys don't have to
worry about their reputations.
- But Despie, I love you.
- Oh, you love me?
Richie, I love you.
I love you.
Oh, Richie!
LES SEIGNEURS
Turkey?
Turkey, is that you?
- What happened, man?
- What are you talking about?
What did you do to yourself now?
- What's wrong with you?
- What are you talking about?
I shaved my head.
I got to go talk to those guys over there.
Listen to me!
I got you in the Wanderers.
I thought you was my friend.
I am your friend.
You don't need those guys.
You're a Wanderer.
You can't be a Wanderer for graduation.
I'm thinking about the future, Joey!
I'll be a Fordham Baldie.
Wait and see. The Baldies got it made.
Those guys look like a bunch
of Neanderthal retards. Look at them.
Are you kidding?
Those are the Fordham Baldies, Joey!
They shave their heads so their hair
won't get in their eyes when they fight.
Nobody fucks with the Baldies, man.
Those guys look like
a bunch of pricks with ears.
What did you just say?
- I ain't talking to you. Scram!
- Easy, Joey.
Hey, Peewee.
Joey, this is Peewee.
She's head of the Baldies' Ladies Auxiliary.
That's Terror's woman.
She goes with Terror.
How you doing, Peewee?
- What did you just say?
- Nothing, Peewee.
I ain't talking to you!
What did you just say about pricks?
I said, '"pricks with ears.'"
Terror, this asshole said we look like
a bunch of pricks with ears.
He didn't say that, did you, Joey?
- Oh, yeah, then what did he say?
- I didn't say that.
I didn't say you guys looked
like a bunch of pricks with ears.
I said you looked like
a bunch of ears without pricks!
Terror, how you doing?
- Can I talk to you?
- Get him!
When I get a hold of your ass...
Let me alone. I like you guys.
Come on, Turkey, come on!
Let's get these motherfuckers!
Come on, Terror!
Wait till I catch you, you skinny prick!
Look at them go!
Hey, you! Come back, you creep!
- Oh, shit!
- What's wrong?
I gotta go.
- What?
- I gotta go.
It sounds like a Wanderer's in trouble.
A what?
You should be careful, now.
Hey, Buddy! Somebody's in trouble!
Looks like we're gonna
have to stomp some ass.
- What?
- It's Joey and Turkey.
Joey, don't worry.
We'll pummel whoever's following you!
The Baldies!
Baldies? Shit! Let's get out of here!
Shit.
Joey, what did we do?
Nothing! They just started chasing me.
Cut it out, asshole!
Easy, easy, free Turkey, man.
This little guy don't mean no harm, man.
He's just a fucking idiot.
Leave the kid alone.
You say something, mother...
Hey! You hear me? I'm talking to you.
Leave the kid alone.
You know who you're talking to, asshole?
Beat it. Nobody fucks with the Baldies.
Asshole!
Leave the kid alone.
Got you.
Your ass is grass, motherfucker.
- Beat it, you scumbag!
- Joey, what's wrong with you?
Terror.
You'd better watch your mouth, kid.
Stay back.
They shaved your head, Turkey?
- Yeah, they shaved his head.
- Oh, Jesus.
I didn't think I'd see the day when Terror
backed down to anybody like that.
Did you see how chickenshit he was?
He wasn't chickenshit, Joey.
Terror ain't chickenshit of nobody.
He's just waiting for the right time.
Are you kidding?
Did you see what this guy did here?
- Where'd he go?
- Hey, come back here, man!
Where'd that guy go?
Strong.
I'm strong.
Leave the kid...
...alone.
Jujitsu.
It's you.
I've been looking all over for you.
Where did you go?
I want to thank you.
What you did back there was great.
Forget about it.
You shouldn't have wised off
to those guys.
But I don't like to see big guys
pick on little guys. Know what I mean?
I can take care of myself, all right?
Sure you can.
What are you doing here
waiting for my elevator?
- I'm waiting to go home.
- You live here?
This building?
Hey, what floor?
- Four.
- I live on four.
You're the new people, right?
My mom told me that.
How do you like that? We're neighbors.
I'm Joey.
- Perry.
Hey, where is it!
Where is it, you bastards on the fifth floor!
I know what you're doing up there.
Assholes!
Excuse me, ma'am.
I heard about your old man, how he died.
The Wanderers are the guys
to get in with around here.
We've got a great football team,
great athletes, lots of girls.
Maybe you can join up,
I'll show you around, okay?
Okay, thanks.
You got to get into a gang.
You just ain't safe unless...
This is my father, Emilio, and this is...
I told you not to be talking in the hallway!
Perry? Darling, is that you?
Yeah, it's me, Ma.
Would you mind running down
to the store and getting me something?
Don't worry, sweetie.
They won't ask you for I.D.
Okay?
Under sunny skies, WNCA, New York City.
Good morning.
You've got to lock your doors around here.
Great car, great car. Come on, we're late.
You get to drive your mother's car
to school every day?
She don't drive it so much.
She's got high blood pressure.
Too bad.
Are you 18?
Yeah, I'm 19.
- I got held back, you know?
- Yeah, sure.
Joey!
Hey, how's it hanging, guys?
You were really cool yesterday, man.
John Wayne.
Joey, what's his name?
What's your name? Don't sweat it, Joey.
I just want to meet the guy, man.
Joey.
Would you get off my ass!
We got all kinds of gangs here.
See these guys here?
Those are the Executioners.
Over here on the left...
...the Ghettos, they're Jewish.
On the right, in green, the Irish...
...the Delaney's. You're Italian, right?
- Yeah.
Then you got to get into an Italian gang,
like the Wanderers.
Hey, Turkey,
where's the dollar you owe me?
- How you doing? Good to see you.
- Here's your dollar.
Then you got your nigger gangs.
You got your Cavaliers...
...you got your Pips here,
and then you got your Mau Mau's.
D.B. Stands for '"Del Bombers,'"
the toughest nigger gang around.
Hey, coon Stitch. Hey, how you doing?
Good to see you.
What's this?
Hey, Teddy Wong!
Twenty-seven guys with the last
name Wong, who all know jujitsu.
Could kill you with one judo chop.
Do you got gangs like this
where you come from?
We don't got this stuff
in Trenton, New Jersey.
Don't worry about anything.
Hang out with the Wanderers,
and we'll take care of you.
Richie, where are you?
Richie, we got him.
Richie Gennaro.
- Perry Maguire.
- How you doing?
I want to thank you for helping us out.
Anytime you need anything,
you let me know. All right?
Richie, I got your homework.
Wow, that's a nice job.
You even goofed up my handwriting.
Thanks, you're my main man.
Hey, Richie?
Turkey, take your hat off and get your feet
off the desk. It smells bad enough.
Very funny, Mr. Sharp.
I said, '"take your hat off! '"
Come on, take it off.
What's the matter?
You guys never seen a Baldie before?
Mr. Sharp, did you see
what Turkey just did?
Shut up, stupid!
Are you gonna make me, motherfucker?
Let's go.
All right, settle down.
You've both got detention.
Mr. Sharp, man. Damn.
Mr. Sharp...
Them white boys here,
they's getting obstreperous.
Anybody know what week this is?
- Brotherhood Week.
- Very good, Stitch.
Now, who wrote this?
You did.
'"A. Lincoln.'"
'"Race, creed, color.'"
I wanna see how many different races
we have just here in this classroom.
All Jewish people, stand up.
Okay. All the Italians.
All right! Okay. Settle down.
All Colored.
What's the matter, Stitch?
Don't we have a group to suit you?
No, I'm an Eskimo.
Where can I get some Eskimo pie?
Okay.
Colored. Italian.
Or is it Colored and Eye-talian?
Is that the way your old man talks?
The Colored.
How about you guys?
What do you say after school, Eye-talian?
Let's talk some straight talk.
Let's call a spade a spade.
Let's talk straight. Give me some names.
Come on.
Nigger.
Grease ball.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
Jungle bunny.
Swamp Guinea.
Handkerchief head.
Mountain wop.
Bogey.
Guinea.
Coon!
Dago.
Watch you mouth, boo-boo.
Spear-chucker!
Motherfucker, I'm gonna chuck a spear
up your ass!
Hold it! I can't write that fast.
Is that it? That's all?
We ran out of names pretty fast.
What did we learn here today?
Mr. Sharp, the white boys forgot
a couple of names.
They forgot spade...
...spooks and jigs.
Put that on the board.
How did you guys forget those names?
There must have been
a mental lapse, Mr. Sharp.
Mr. Sharp, I think it's because...
...they are a bunch of dumb-ass,
grease ball, Guinea, wop...
You black bastard.
Fuck you, dago motherfucker!
- Jigaboo!
- Your mama.
- You ain't got one.
- What'd you say?
Fuck you!
Hold it!
Hold it.
We'll meet you at Prince Charles' Field,
okay? Saturday.
You got it. Saturday at noon.
No guns and no knives.
I want everybody after school, everybody.
Fuckin' hang that little bastard.
That's the only way you're going to learn
about brotherhood!
What's the matter with you guys?
Haven't you heard '"sticks and stones
will break my bones...
'"...but names will never hurt me'"?
Come on, motherfucker!
All you motherfuckers!
Get down there!
What's the matter with you animals?
Any homework?
We don't want to get into this.
I know the neighborhood's changed,
but are you guys chickenshit?
- You guys started it.
- We didn't start it.
- We heard you did.
- You heard wrong.
- What else?
- We ain't Italian.
I know you ain't Italian.
Come on, what do you say?
We say good luck to you.
Yeah, good luck, faggots.
Motherfucking faggots.
Come back here.
We're with you. No nigger will face this.
What are you doing?
We don't need those. Put it away.
You kidding me?
Those guys will show up with pieces.
Don't trust them.
You got to go for them first.
- He got a point, Richie.
- Me and Clinton agreed.
- No guns or knives.
- You gonna trust that nigger?
You don't know where you're living.
We ain't going with you without these.
Then you ain't going with us.
Nice knowing you guys.
Have fun.
Fucking pussies.
I don't know, man.
Come on.
Look, Richie, call my friends, the Baldies.
Those guys like me.
Call them, I think they'll come in with us.
With them in, it's all over.
Listen, I ain't calling those guys.
I got my pride.
Sometimes all you got is pride.
Got to hold your head up high.
I seen this movie once
where this guy was tortured by the Japs...
...but he wouldn't give them
any information.
Every time they tortured him...
...he started singing
the Star-Spangled Banner.
Wow. What happened?
- They killed him.
- Shut up, you're depressing me.
What was that?
You got the jitters.
I'm going to take a whiz.
I thought I heard something.
You guys hear anything?
Baldies got guys, too.
It's the Wongs!
Teddy Wong. How you doing?
- I thought you was coming earlier.
- We did, man.
We waited until now
to make ourselves known.
You've just been hanging out
in the bushes?
- Pretty spooky.
- We've been listening.
I called you Wongs here tonight
for a reason.
- We know your reason.
- Gonna join us?
No.
- You're gonna join them?
- Stay back!
Don't fuck with the Wongs.
The Wongs never joined with anybody...
...yet.
What do you mean by '"yet'"?
We'll decide what's right
when the time comes.
The Wongs will wait and see.
When what time comes?
What do they mean?
- Where did they go?
- I don't know.
Get back here!
No, get the fuck out of here,
you Chink assholes.
No sweat, they can't hear me.
Don't fuck with the Wongs!
Richie, listen to what I just heard.
It ain't just the Del Bombers, man.
They're bringing in the Pips, the Cavaliers...
...the Mau Mau's.
- Shit, we've got a fucking race war.
Maybe we'll bring in some guys
from Brooklyn, the Golden Guineas.
One thing: We got to stay cool.
Did you notice those spades got
two million cousins all over the country?
We need help,
and I'm calling my friends in, the Baldies.
Enough, man. Forget it.
Guess who.
Al Capone.
No.
- It's me.
- What do you know.
What are you doing, Richie?
What's that list?
- You're gonna rumble?
- No, it's just some business.
I'll talk to you later, all right?
I thought we were
gonna buy some records.
Maybe a little later, all right?
Love you, baby.
Love you, too.
Richie, my daddy wants to see you.
How you doing?
I heard Chubby was looking for me.
Over there.
Over here, Richie.
- You wanna see me, Mr. Galasso?
- Yeah.
Me and my brothers
wanted to see you because...
...we heard you got some trouble
with the Colored.
How did you hear about that?
How did we hear about that?
How do the Galasso brothers hear
about anything in this neighborhood?
The reason I'm asking is that...
...maybe you could use some help.
No, we can handle it.
Remember, Richie, in this day and age,
in this neighborhood...
...there's lot of ways to skin the cat.
Do you know what I mean?
- Not exactly.
- Think about it.
You know where to find us.
You guys wanted Joey to come
so he could heal old wounds.
I respect these guys.
Give them a good rumble, they're happy.
Look what's coming.
Look what the cat dragged in.
Hey, my favorite Wanderer.
You know, Joey,
if I had a dog with a face like yours...
...l'd shave its ass
and teach it to walk backwards.
Very funny, Terror. Very funny.
We've come to you because
we've got problems with the niggers.
You guys know Roger, don't you?
What do you mothers want?
We've got some personal business here.
You guys go to Tulley High, don't you?
Maybe you know a cousin of mine.
Clinton Stitch? He's in the Del Bombers.
Stitch is a good friend of mine.
You know Clinton, don't you?
Everybody knows Clinton.
I think we can talk business better
in the park.
- Is this a joke?
- Sure, it's a joke.
Just like your little joke
about pricks with ears.
- Or was it ears without pricks?
- Where are we going?
Hey, Terror, I knew you wasn't chickenshit.
Turkey, do me a favor, will you?
Sure, Terror,
you know how I feel about you guys.
Hold these.
We're thinking about making you guys
honorary members of the Baldies.
That's great, Peewee.
We thought we might start
by shaving your heads.
Come on, not my hair, all right?
Too good for us?
Maybe we won't take your hair off.
We'll just take something else off.
- Drop your pants.
- Sure, whatever you want.
Not you, Turkey. You're gonna help us.
Hop over.
- Why don't you guys just shave our heads?
- Go on.
We got delicate feelings.
You guys seem to think
you're too good for us.
You guys are a bunch of fruits!
There you go again, hurting our feelings.
Tie their hands.
Turkey, I want you to tie
one end of the rope right...
...there.
Jeez, Terror...
Turkey, don't do it.
Turkey, it's just a little test
to get in to the Baldies.
To see how brave a guy can be.
I know these guys heard of rock 'n' roll...
...but you guys ever hear of rock 'n' cock?
How about cock 'n' roll, mothers?
Hey, Turkey, do a Boy Scout knot.
Turkey, don't do it, man.
Turkey, you're a Wanderer.
Turkey, you fucking homo.
Don't get me mad, Joey.
Okay, Turkey, pick up both of the rocks.
Any last words to say to your dicks?
Say, '"Bye-bye, dick, nice knowing you.'"
Turkey, throw the rocks over.
Sorry, guys.
Oh, shit.
Looks like we got to get shorter twine.
Don't you guys go away.
We'll be right back.
Come on, Turkey,
I got a soft spot in my heart for you.
- What do we do now?
- Can't get anybody to help us, Richie.
They left us here to die of exposure.
Don't fuck with the Baldies!
This is just a warning.
I'm glad you've come to us finally, Richie.
You've got a good sense of reality.
We're gonna help you
with your problem with the Colored.
How are you feeling today?
- The old bowling arm feeling hot?
- Sure, always hot.
'"Sure, always hot.'"
Wasn't so hot last week
against those Long Island guys.
Which reminds me...
...see who's bowling out there tonight?
- No.
- Take a look.
Shit.
It's those guys from Long Island.
You know what they're doing here?
I don't know.
They've come here for a rematch.
Mr. Galasso, those guys are too good.
They killed us last week.
You know, Richie...
...you need some confidence.
The other kid can wait here.
You guys are gonna win big tonight.
Are you kidding, Peppy?
These guys are good enough to be pros.
My instinct is they is pros.
Chubby checked up on them.
They go around to the different lanes.
They hustle the house bowlers.
They hustle the hustlers.
- They are greedy boys.
- What's Chubby gonna do?
Chubby got a way of creating miracles.
What'll it be?
Who is this?
Five big ones?
- We ain't got that much.
- No?
What do you got?
Twenty-five hundred.
Guess that'll have to do.
We'll leave the money there.
Whoa, pal. We get to pick the alley, right?
Anything! Come on, you guys gonna play?
Let's cut the bullshit.
Wanna keep score, too? Go ahead.
I'm just a dumb Guinea. What do I know?
For all I know, you guys could be pros.
What are you guys talking about?
Your guys are really good,
is what we're talking about.
What's happening?
Where's everybody going?
Just closing for a while, for a little privacy.
What are you doing?
You guys are so good, it wouldn't be fair
unless you bowled handicapped.
Twenty pins?
That's not what I was thinking about.
- Fifty pins.
- No good.
What I had in mind was a real handicap.
I seen this in my favorite movie.
You ever seen The Hustler?
Good enough for Paul Newman,
good enough for you.
Now, where was we?
Oh, yeah, you guys come to us
with a problem.
We'll take care of it.
But remember, we're sportsmen.
And we're interested in making
a little bet on you.
Nothing wrong with that, is there?
I understand you're playing the Coloreds
in North Bronx Football League soon.
I think it would be to our mutual benefit...
...if you won one for the Galassos.
- Don't you?
- Yeah.
There's two kinds of people.
Those with common interests...
...and assholes like those hustlers.
What I like
about these Colored sportsmen...
...is they got common interest.
Not all your Colored are assholes.
It's a shame to see kids
beating each other's brains out.
Especially when there's
no financial advantage.
- Right, Albert?
- Right.
How are you?
- How you doing?
- Okay, you?
We're gonna have a little football game.
Sporting event.
I'm glad these boys brought
us into the picture.
It gives these kids a chance to settle
their differences in a beneficial manner.
Let's adjourn to the bar for a discussion.
It's cool.
What's all this?
I'm making a banner.
Our big game with the Del Bombers
is coming up. You should come, Dad.
- It should be a good game.
- Look at me when you talk to me.
What kind of drawing you doing?
Why can't you do something normal?
A mountain lake, a tree, birds?
That's art.
Those aren't normal people you draw.
They're freaks.
You hear me?
Emilio.
Joey, time to eat.
They're freaks.
Hey, good. I got to drop a few pounds.
I got to get more pressed.
Come on, let's eat.
It's us against the world.
I mean, just the Wanderers.
- We got to stick together.
- We got to stick it to the Del Bombers.
Joey, I got a game for you.
- See who can hit the softest.
- Yeah, sure.
You go first.
That's pretty good. It's my turn now.
What did you do that for?
I thought you said the softest.
I did. You win.
I'm in love! Look at that.
Hey, I'd like to stick it to that.
I'm in love. Hey, you know what, man?
Today's the perfect day for elbow-titting.
Hey, Perry, pull over.
Watch it!
Watch where you're going!
Don't people look where they're going?
Watch it in the future!
- You get any tit?
- She had nice ones.
She didn't know what was happening.
Who's next?
Perry, you go.
- Me? No.
- Come on.
What are you, chicken?
Chicken?
Free feels, right in the street?
Too late.
Quit bothering me!
Don't be afraid, all right?
Watch this.
Here goes the elbow-titting champion
of the Bronx.
Hey, Joey, get a good one.
Do it, Joey baby!
You boys are pigs!
You have no respect!
Lady, I'm sorry!
- You boys are pigs!
- Yes, ma'am.
I never realized how dangerous
elbow-titting was.
You win a few, and you lose a few.
- Don't hit me.
- Look at that!
- Richie, your turn.
- No, no.
Come on, chickenshit.
Hey, come on, let's go.
'"Hello, hello...
'"...hello! '"
- Watch where you're going.
- You get a good one?
What do you mean?
- I bet you think that's funny.
- What are you talking about?
I'm sorry I bumped into you.
You think I bump into every girl
out on the street?
No, just the ones you're trying to
cop a free feel from.
I wasn't trying to do it...
Bullshit. Aren't you a little old
to be doing stuff like this?
Where I'm from, they call it molesting.
Where are you from?
Come on. Scram, pal.
What school do you go to?
- Look, whatever your name is...
- Richie. What's yours?
Nina. I don't talk to every guy
who tries to elbow-tit me...
What is this?
I know this, great book.
The whole thing, or just the dirty parts?
Come on, Nina,
don't take me over the coals.
Can't you have a straight talk about
books with a molester like me?
Sex fiend, hey, over here!
I hear your mom calling you, Richie!
Your friends want you back.
- You tell them everything?
- Are you kidding?
Just the dirty parts.
I think we should
see each other again sometime.
I've got to go, I've had hard day.
Hey, I want you to meet a friend.
- Joey, meet Nina.
- Hey, Nina.
You wouldn't know it to look at him,
but he's a great artist.
I think you two could hit it off.
- I've got to get going.
- Give us your number, okay?
I'm not giving you my number.
Hey, do you mind?
- Off the car, big fellow.
- Joey, give her your number.
Maybe she'd like to go and party with you.
- My number?
- Yeah, K-0505-64.
K-0505-64!
That's my number, K-0505-64.
You got that?
Think she'll call?
Sure she will.
Richie, you're a true Wanderer.
I hate to see one like that get away.
Let's go.
We'll get them for you, Joey.
Don't let her get away.
She was something else.
Richie, now I think I know
what you mean by true love.
- There she goes.
- Don't lose her.
Where the hell are we, man?
Is that her ahead of us, there?
Thought it was, but it ain't.
Perry, where are you taking us?
I don't know my way around here.
I thought you were gonna tell me.
- I got to get home. I got to go to work.
- It's getting late.
- My old man is going to kill me.
- Fucking relax.
Jesus, come on.
We'll find our way out of here.
Let's ask that lady up there.
Forget about it.
Jesus.
Look out! Watch it, look out!
Shit!
I think I know where we are.
Ducky Boys!
Shit, those are Ducky Boys.
Let's get the hell out of here!
Get the fuck out of here!
You little prick.
- Perry, get back here!
- You can't talk?
Perry, no!
Perry!
Get in the car!
Get the fuck out of here!
Get him to a hospital! Emergency.
We got to get him to a hospital.
I ain't telling my ma about this.
The doctor said it ain't good
for the high blood pressure.
What are you gonna do? Wear gloves?
Stay here.
I'm going upstairs
to see if the coast is clear.
Old man'll kill me for coming in this late.
Emilio, I'll see you tomorrow.
Bring me a little something, will you?
Honey.
- Joey, what is it? What's the matter?
- Nothing.
Nothing. It's okay.
Daddy, I know. No talking in the hallways.
You got a call, some dame's calling.
Sounds like a librarian.
You got books out? Come on, get inside.
Perry, is that you, honey?
- Hello?
- Hi, is this Joey?
- Yeah.
- This is Nina, we met today.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, right.
I thought I'd call you up,
you said something about a party.
Who'll be there?
All the guys. Richie, the first guy
you met on the street today.
- Yeah.
- He'll be there. Great guy.
- You liked him?
- Yeah.
Joey, what are you so nervous about?
Jumping around and shit.
I got to take a piss.
She'll be here in a minute.
Listen, I want to tell you something.
I think we got it made
with this chick, you know?
- She called you up the other day, right?
- Yeah, right.
She's coming to get us for the party?
- What are you going to do?
- What do you mean?
You need a game plan.
How else are you gonna get laid?
I can take care of myself.
Do you know so much about it?
Forget it. I'm just trying
to tell you how to get the job done.
Do me a favor, keep your mouth shut.
You sound like my mother.
Your mother? Tell her she forgot
her shoes under my bed last night.
Your mother's got a mattress
on the back of the curbside...
Leave the hair alone, will you!
- Quit acting like a faggot!
- You wish.
- You blow.
Here she is.
Hi, Nina.
- Get in back.
- And leave my main man up here alone?
Let's go, we're late already.
How you doing, baby?
What is this shit on the radio?
Ain't you got some decent music?
I'll change the station.
All right. Rock 'n' roll, that's more like it.
Come on, let's go.
- Straight ahead?
- Go left at the corner.
Over here. Pull over behind this car.
Right here.
- What is this car?
- It's my parents'.
I borrow it when they go out of town.
They're out of town?
- Get down.
- What's wrong?
Stay down, it's Galasso.
We don't want them to see us.
- Who?
- It's Despie's parents.
He doesn't want us to break training.
He's got cash riding on us.
That dress has got real class.
Shall we?
- Goddamn, Richie.
- New undies for your birthday, Joey.
Can I get out of here?
I can't breath down here.
What's going on? Is the coast clear?
Come on, they're gone.
Okay, let's Wampo!
Okay, Popeye.
Cleopatra.
Eye-line turn.
Popeye.
Cleopatra.
Sweep the floor.
Hey, look who's here.
How you doing, man?
Jesus, what the hell is that?
- That's the woman I know?
- A woman?
That's what it looked like, kid.
If your pants were any tighter,
we'd be able to see the veins in your balls.
Didn't know you were looking!
Joey! Joey!
I didn't know Purina made sports jackets.
I didn't know Purina made bad breath.
Richie!
Come here.
Do you want to dance, Joey?
I'm not very good.
Maybe when a slow one comes on.
Thanks, man.
Thanks, guys.
I've got an urge tonight to maybe...
...go out tonight and...
...stomp some ass. I just got to...
...just rumble.
Break some heads. Know what I mean?
I know what you mean.
I got an urge, too, man.
I know where
there's a Wanderers party tonight.
The little guys.
They're a bunch of pussies.
Go out, stomp some ass.
Maybe even get laid. Sorry, Peewee.
I didn't mean it. I just got an urge.
- You guys wanna fight?
- Yeah, we wanna fight.
You got to be kidding, pal.
- You gonna fight us?
- I ain't talking about me.
I'm talking about the toughest guys
in the world.
Man, who you talking about?
Nobody's tougher than the Baldies.
Why don't you guys come in here?
Come on.
I've always wondered what you do in here.
Jerk off?
Guys...
...I got a way you can stomp
all the ass you want...
...and make the world safe for democracy
at the same time.
Here you are, gentlemen.
Pass those out. Here you go.
Thanks, man.
Come on, girls. Get moving.
Buddy, come on, babe.
Joey, it's so noisy down here.
Do you suppose she'd mind
if we went upstairs to talk?
No. Hey, Rich...
We're gonna go upstairs to talk.
Just don't get any jizzy marks
on the Galassos' bed.
I'll make you eat it off with a spoon.
Hey, good luck.
My daddy will kill me
if they make a mess upstairs.
They won't, don't worry about it.
Maybe we should go upstairs, too.
'"I swear as a citizen of the United States.'"
After signing this document,
you'll become Marines.
Terror, don't do it!
'"I swear that I have never been...
'"...a member of the Communist party.'"
'"...a member of the Communist Party.'"
At least you guys don't need no haircuts.
Terror, you know what you've just done?
You've just joined the fucking Marines.
You baboon.
You know what I think we just done?
What?
I think we just joined the fucking Marines.
I hope you know what we just done,
is just a joke.
Sorry, boys.
What do you mean, '"sorry, boys'"?
I ain't even 21.
You ain't got to be.
Come on, Mister, give them a break!
Them's the rules.
My mother will die without me.
- Should've thought of that before.
- What did you say about my mother?
Get out of here.
Don't worry.
The Marines will make men out of you.
You mothers might enjoy a real war.
Remember, no jewelry, no bobby pins,
none of that kind of stuff.
Both socks count as one.
It's got to be authentic article of clothing.
How did you guys meet, anyway?
We just sort of bumped into each other.
- What have you got?
- Pairs of deuces.
Pairs of deuces.
Too bad. Pair of queens. I beat you.
Not so fast, I got four of a kind.
Four twos?
- Yep.
- Nobody gets four twos.
Let me see. A straight is when
you've got numbers in a row, right?
You got one?
No, but I got something very close.
Four, six...
...seven, eight and ten.
If only I got a five and a nine.
Oh, that's too bad. Too bad.
I don't even know you guys.
Do you play with them often, Despie?
I never played this before.
How'd we get into this, anyway?
- Who's deal is it?
- Your deal.
Ladies, ante up.
- Joey shed his shirt.
- Shut up, asshole.
Let's go. You gonna play or what?
Let's go.
What kind of polish is that, Despie?
Glitter.
Glitter!
How do you know when you're flushed?
When you're all red?
It's got to be all the same suit,
like all hearts or all diamonds.
Oh, yeah, I knew that.
I've got a real good hand.
Let me see, give me...
...four cards.
Four? Sure.
Richie, give me two.
You can't take any cards
without putting something up.
Still in?
- Come on, let's go.
- I better pass.
Can't get anything back by passing.
You have to win it back.
How come we never win?
Who could say? Confidence...
...luck of the draw.
The wheel of fate just keeps spinning.
All right, but don't look.
Richie...
Richie!
No fair, you guys are looking.
- Are you in, Despie?
- I'm out.
What have you got, Joey?
- I fold.
- What have you got, Nina?
Pretty good. Look.
Not good enough.
Not good enough. Full house, beats again.
Hey, something fishy's going on here.
In a couple minutes,
we're gonna be naked, then what?
- What are you doing?
- My deal?
Then we play one more hand.
For what?
Then we get to do whatever we want to.
- What's the matter with you?
- That's it!
Sex fiends are at it again.
We got to get back to the party!
We've got to get back to the party.
We're at the party.
We're just having some fun.
We don't have to stop playing.
We've been lucky. You'll win this next one.
A little innocent game.
One more hand.
There's nothing going on downstairs.
Come on.
Stay, will you? We'll have some fun.
She's going. Go!
Despie!
Come on, Terror, get in the car.
Come on.
How about it, baby?
Put me down, Terror. You're drunk.
You don't sound good when you're drunk.
- Come on, man.
- Let's go!
Terror, get in the car, man.
Come with us, baby.
Don't go.
All right. Let's stomp some ass!
Let's go someplace quiet to talk.
My car.
That's my daddy's cup!
Stupid son of a bitch!
How am I gonna get home?
Richie?
Richie!
I can't forget about you
since the first time I saw you.
Let's go inside!
We'll go inside and get some women.
Nookie, right?
You go inside, Turkey.
Bring it back out here.
Yeah, man, '"nookie to go,'" right?
Excuse me, may I take your orders?
Everything on it, I like it rare.
On the double, Private.
Yeah, man, right.
I'll be right back.
Did you see Richie?
Richie!
I was looking all over for you...
- Hey.
- Hey, what?
What are you looking at?
You're looking at a Baldie now, faggot!
Scumbag, look out the window.
Joey's out there!
Have a nice time, motherfucker.
Terror's gonna settle your ass.
Terror! Roger, where the fuck
are you guys?
Asshole, I don't want to see you
around here, you understand?
Get the fuck out of here.
Terror!
Roger, hey wait up!
Where are you guys going? Terror?
Joey, wait, listen. Joey, come here.
Joey, listen to me.
I had to have a talk with her.
I can't get her out of my mind.
I met her first.
For Christ's sake, Joey, you and me...
I couldn't fight the thing no more.
Don't fucking touch me!
She's just another fucking broad.
She don't matter anyway.
No, she ain't, man. She's special.
You shitheel! You lousy, rotten shitheel.
This is what I get for putting out.
I knew this would happen.
Terror!
Baldies!
Terror, where are you?
Roger, get down here,
you bald-headed nigger!
Roger, I'm just kidding, man.
Roger!
Terror!
I didn't know there was
anyone around here.
I got lost.
I need someone to talk to.
It's cold out.
Where are you coming from?
So what?
You go to high school around here?
You go to high school?
We can go in the park.
I'm not joking, I'm serious.
Yeah.
Help me!
Terror!
I want to tell you guys something.
It wasn't that bad. Not as you think.
I'm gonna miss Turkey.
Here comes the bastard.
Hey, Richie.
Richie, I got your homework.
Guys, what are you doing?
The President and Mrs. Kennedy...
...just minutes before he was shot.
This is not confirmed.
We have it on
what would normally be good authority...
...that the President has died.
However, we repeat, this is not confirmed.
Now, as you can see here...
...Mrs. Kennedy steps into the car...
That's her waving.
That's the President waving.
Richie, you know what true love means?
That it means standing by the person
you love, thick and thin?
Do you?
Hello, Father.
You know what else true love means?
True love for a woman means
having the baby of the man she loves.
Do you know what true love in a man is?
True love in a man...
...is wanting that woman who loves him
to have his baby.
- Don't you feel that's what true love is?
- Oh, yeah. Definitely.
Richie...
...I really feel true love for you.
I'd like to know if you feel true love for me.
Sure I do.
Sure you do what?
I really do.
You really do what?
I really feel true love for you, Despie.
The parents should be in love.
I mean, when I told my daddy
I thought I was pregnant...
...he told me he thought the parents...
- What?
Richie, my daddy wants to see you.
Look, I ain't no hard guy.
I was your age once.
I used to put them away...
...like there was no tomorrow,
but one thing...
...I never did it with nobody's daughter.
Not only did you do it with my daughter,
but you knocked her up, you dumb wop!
You ain't got nothing up here.
It's all down here.
All right. I ain't no hard guy.
It takes two to tango and all that bullshit.
She's been banging since junior high
and you're the first jerk to get caught.
Daddy, how could you?
Maybe you should've given her
an ankle bracelet.
Stop the jerking off.
The thing is, you knocked her up.
And now you gotta pay the price
and do the right thing.
It's the sportsman's way.
Hey, what's this?
Now you're scared.
Get up!
To my new son-in-law.
You'll live in the basement.
We got wood paneling.
Gloria! Come on down!
Come on over here, pupsie!
Hey, do you like clams?
I'll take us all to City Island
for some clams. I ain't no hard guy.
- What does it say?
- Eighteen inches.
Eighteen inches.
You know what it was in '40, '41?
Seventeen and a half.
In Greece, it was eighteen.
Did I tell you I seen him the other day?
He's turned into a tub of lard.
Feel it.
Eighteen inches, right where it counts.
Who do you think
the judges would vote for now?
I'll be right down!
- Yeah!
- Keep it down in there!
Why don't you go see Joey play, Emilio?
I don't want to get embarrassed.
I understand he's good.
You won't get embarrassed.
- Go on, Emilio.
- Not today. I'm busy.
'"We're so great! We're first rate! '"
Shit. Looks like them niggers
ain't gonna show.
- The chickenshits.
- Yeah.
Always have been.
What's that?
Holy shit! It looks like
they ripped off a circus.
'"We gotta win, we gotta win,
we gotta really win! '"
Where's that boyfriend?
Okay!
You know why
they call you the Wanderers?
Because after this game,
you'll '"wander'" what happened.
Come on, motherfucker! Right now!
Play ball!
Come on, break it up.
Break it up. Come on.
- Give me a 5-2.
- Break!
All right!
Thirty-nine!
Twenty-four!
Time! Time!
Fucking protection!
- Stay in your pocket!
- Pocket?
You got your hands in my pockets.
You guys block like a bunch of fruits.
- Don't talk like that.
- I'll talk the way I want, understand?
- I'm the quarterback!
- Then be the quarterback.
Shut up, all of you guys!
Maybe some of you guys got a right
to hate my guts.
I've been watching.
If we had Joey at halfback...
...and me at quarterback,
we'd have a chance.
That's the way it was meant to be.
I've been thinking a lot about it...
...and I want to say to Joey here, I'm sorry.
I want to apologize.
What do you say?
That's great man, great.
All I want to say is that
whatever I've done is in the past.
All is forgotten. Okay?
We've got to win this game
for the Wanderers.
What do you say?
Wanderers forever, right, Joey?
Let's kill them!
Set.
Strong right, full house.
Wanderers' special, on one, ready?
Going left, full house, death destruction.
Tie game, mothers!
Throw me the goddamn ball!
You got it, brother.
- Okay, let's have the ball.
- I ain't going over there.
You want it, you go get it.
You guys chickening out?
Hell, no. There's some short, runny-ass
sucker over there with a big blade.
- What?
- Yeah.
- I don't see nothing?
- You don't?
They're here!
- Look, they're here!
- What?
Ducky Boys.
Where?
I ain't fucking around, man. He was here.
Everyone's starting to see things.
What is this?
Can't we just play some football? Let's go!
Shit.
Ducky Boys.
What are they doing here?
Where are they all coming from?
- What are we gonna do?
- Don't run.
Fight them. We'll stay.
We're gonna stay. Nobody goes.
Shit!
There's hundreds of them.
I think my mother's calling me.
I'm thirsty. I think I'm gonna get a Coke.
They killed Turkey.
Sons of bitches. Come on!
Come on!
Joey!
Hey, come and play.
We beat them! We won!
Come on, fucker sucker!
Are you okay?
Hey, we beat them, Dad!
I tell you, I just ain't going home.
I don't know what to do,
but I ain't going home.
It's my poor ma I feel sorry for.
Twenty years of walking on eggshells
living with that asshole.
- Where's your ma?
- I don't know.
She went out for a while.
- Sleep over. She don't mind.
- What's the matter?
Nothing.
Take a swig of this.
She's got high blood pressure,
something like that?
- Hey, come on.
- No, really.
It ain't exactly high blood pressure.
What is it?
It's an alcoholic kind of thing.
Last night, it got real bad.
She checked in to some kind of hospital.
Perry, I'm sorry, man.
Oh, man, there's nothing to be sorry for.
She's better off.
It's okay, it happened before.
Don't worry, she'll be fine.
- I'm taking off.
- What?
They want me to go back
to Trenton, fucking New Jersey.
Screw graduating. I've been thinking about
heading out to California anyway.
California?
That's it.
Man, that's a great idea.
- I'm coming with you.
- No, no.
I travel alone.
Besides, I ain't sure I'm going to California.
Maybe I'll go to China.
Hey, I was just...
Perry?
What?
I'm scared.
Hey, what's wrong with that?
What do you mean?
Joey, do me a favor. If we travel together,
you have to promise not to be an asshole.
We'll take off right after
the bachelor party for Richie.
Tina? Tina?
- Who's Tina?
- My mom.
- Who the hell is that?
- It's my dad, Emilio.
Tina!
Hey, Tina!
I thought you told your mother
you were going out bowling tonight?
You've been lying to her or what?
Don't come near me.
What are you talking about? I want to
know why you weren't home for dinner.
- Don't come near me.
- Leave the kid alone.
Were you talking to me?
Didn't your father teach you no manners?
- Leave the kid alone.
- Perry, he'll kill you.
That's the trouble with you rotten kids.
Your fathers are afraid
to kick some sense into your heads.
Your father must have been
some kind of piss ant...
There's no sense of humor.
Come on, what's all this about?
You shouldn't have done that!
He's your father. Don't forget that.
I think I killed the bastard.
Let's get out of here.
Get out of here!
- What are we going to do?
- Get to my car.
'"Hello! '"
Richie! Sex fiend!
What are you guys doing here?
You're going to get me fired.
- What're you doing? What's going on?
- Tell me, did you sleep with her?
What else are you going to do with her?
- Fix your hair.
- Come on, let's go.
Trouble? Where? With who?
- You're in big trouble.
- You're fine now.
- Okay, I'm coming.
- Come on, let's go.
- Comb your hair.
- I'll do it.
We all chipped in to get you something
for your bachelor party.
Here you go.
- Come on, open it.
- This is something you needed all along.
Dirk, you're my main man.
That's the least we could have done.
- Come on, open it.
- Would you open the box?
We're going to be here all night.
Sometime today, I want to eat.
- What is it?
- Open it.
One more time.
Fuck you guys. One lousy rubber.
Thanks a lot, you fucking assholes.
We got you a life-time supply.
- Talk to you later.
- Come on. You just got here.
We gotta leave.
Come on. We'll have a little food,
drink a little wine. We'll have a good time.
- With all these gold jackets, you know.
- Don't worry about it, man.
- Let's stay.
- We'll have a good time.
- We'll hang for a little while.
- Have something to eat.
Watch yourself. Coming through.
This is from the guys over there.
Hey, son-in-law.
I was talking with my brothers.
They agreed to bring you in.
It means you're going to do all right.
This fits real nice.
You'll grow into it.
Once you're married to my daughter,
you'll never wash another dish in your life.
Where are you going?
Just getting some fresh air.
I'll be right back.
Hey, Nina.
Nina!
Nina, wait a minute...
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I thought you were somebody else.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
Hey, where are you guys going?
- We got to be on our way.
- On your way?
Yeah, we...
...we just came by to wish you luck.
What're you talking about?
What's going on?
Hey, Peewee, get out of there.
Come on, Joey. Leave me alone, will you?
Hey, Joey, what're you doing?
You don't talk without your Baldies.
Leave me alone.
Hey, man, you owed me, you big shithead.
Come on, don't cry.
I'm sorry.
All that time I was with the Baldies...
...and not one of them even
drops me a card.
Hey.
- I'll drop you a card, all right?
- Hey, Joey. Come on, man, let's go.
Where are you going?
Hey, where do you guys
think you're going?
- You can't go, man.
- I gotta go.
But, if you ever need us...
...just whistle loud. We'll be there.
You can't do it to me. Fucking little guy.
Come here.
Just remember one thing.
Wanderers forever.
Don't take any wooden pussy.
Hey, come on back, will you, guys?
Come on.
Come on with me. Everybody's inside.
Quit your fucking crying.
- Thank you so much.
- It was a wonderful evening.
- I'm glad. Come back.
- Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
We'll come back and see you soon.
- Take care of yourself.
- Thank you.
- Is this the guy?
- This is the guy. The man of the hour.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this young man is getting married...
...and I don't know
what advice we can give him.
- Don't do it!
- What's your favorite song, Richie?
- I ain't got one.
- Well, I got one for you.
And I want you all, ladies and gentlemen,
to join in as I sing.
'"San Francisco, 2,941 miles.'"
Do we got enough gas?
Hey, Joey, do me a favor.
If we're going to travel together,
you have to promise not to be an asshole.
Yeah, yeah. I know, I know.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org