- Smart elephant.
- Hey, hey, wait!
Sarah, I have an idea.
You go with me?
- Okay.
- A little longer?
Yeah.
You know, Sarah,
you're not the first person...
...to harbor anxieties
about their future.
I was literally the poster boy
for that sort of thing.
- Well, how did you figure yourself out?
- Well, I screwed up a lot.
Lived abroad a while.
Did an enormous amount of drugs.
Joined an ashram.
Doodled Grandma.
Then someone told me the most
profound two words I'd ever heard...
..."Be present. "
So now all I ever worry about
is my immediate universe...
...which presently consists
of you, me...
...and the deafening silence
coming from that jukebox.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is my privilege to introduce to you...
...the president of the United States,
William Jefferson Clinton.
Thank you very much.
Do you know him?
You know, I'm not sure
anyone really knows him.
I've spent time with him.
Where are we going?
Can I ask you a question?
What happened that weekend
with Mom?
Skipping all the intimate details,
of course...
...but what happened
that weekend in Cabo?
My parents had a house down there.
I'm staying by myself, pretty much
loafing the summer away...
...when Jocelyn...
When your mom just showed up.
We had a little history together
back in high school.
For three days, all we did
was swim and laugh...
...and I taught her how to surf.
Then one morning I woke up
and she was gone.
Back to Pasadena to get married. L...
I didn't even know
that she was engaged.
Those were probably
the three happiest days of my life.
It's the only time I can remember
ever feeling really...
...peaceful.
Well, why do you think
that she went back?
Security, maybe. I don't know.
She never said.
You know, I can see a lot of her
in you.
She was a very beautiful woman.
So are you.
I have to pee.
What?
Sorry.
Okay.
Well...
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I can't believe I just did that.
So inappropriate. I didn't...
I mean, I re...
Good morning.
Morning.
Best hangover remedy I know.
Five minutes
with your feet over your head...
...followed by a three-mile jog,
then a quick swim.
It's better than coffee and aspirin.
Wanna try?
You want coffee and aspirin.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Good coffee.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Where are we?
We are in Half Moon Bay.
It's about a hour south of the city.
San Francisco.
- Anything else I can get you?
- No.
- Sure? Eggs? Orange juice? Paramedics?
- Yeah.
Well, I guess I'd better go.
It was really nice to meet you,
Mr. Burroughs.
It was very nice meeting you,
Ms. Huttinger.
Well. Okay.
Goodbye.
I don't have a car here, do I?
Nope.
Would you...? Would you mind
giving me a...?
Sure. But let's...
Let's grab a bite to eat first.
I need to say something to you.
What you told me last night
about your life in New York...
...your job, the guy...
...suggested that it wasn't anything
to rush back to.
Well, I wouldn't necessarily say...
Look, I realize it's a bit awkward,
given, well, everything.
But last night, it was...
Last night was
pretty spectacular for me.
What I'm saying, Sarah...
What I'm trying to say, Sarah...
...is that I like you.
Very much, I suspect.
And I'd like you to stay
if you felt like you could.
Stay?
Yeah, as in not go.
- You don't like the idea.
- Well, I...
I don't... I just sort of...
- I thought we were going to eat.
- We are.
- Good morning, Mr. Burroughs.
- Good morning.
It's just a quick trip
up to the Wine Country and back.
Well, do I even have a choice
in the matter?
So, what do you think?
I think I would feel safer if that guy
was sitting up here instead of me.
You think I'm too old for you,
don't you?
No.
Then?
You've... You've slept with my mother
and my grandmother.
- What's your point?
- My point... I mean, I...
This is not normal.
I mean, you know...
You know what,
you are too old for me.
I mean, obviously
I am very confused right now...
...and last night was some sort of,
I don't know, rite of passage.
Maybe every girl in my family
has to sleep with you.
Well, I don't know if they have to,
but they certainly have.
- Beau Burroughs' office.
- Hi, this is Jeff Daly again.
- I'm sorry, who am I talking to?
- Candace.
Hi, Candace.
Listen, can you tell me where he is?
I really need to reach him.
I'm sorry.
I can't give out that information.
I know, Candace.
You told me that before...
...but this is kind of an emergency.
I'm looking for my fiancée.
She's supposed to be with him.
I haven't heard from her. I'm starting
to feel like something happened to her.
At some point I have to get back.
I know. I gotta get back myself.
I got this ball to go to.
A ball? People still go to balls?
They do to this one.
It's the biggest charity event of the year.
It's Casablanca Night.
Why don't you come with me.
- No. L... No, I can't. I can't.
- Why?
- No, sorry.
I've got work. I've gotta go back.
You know, I can't have people
dying anonymously...
...while I'm off dancing
at some fabulous, exciting ball.
- All right. Let me make a proposal.
- Oh, boy.
Why don't you come with me tonight.
After the party, I'll fly you home.
Really. I have to be
on the East Coast anyway.
I can just stop
and drop you off in New York.
It'd be no hassle,
and you'll be there by morning.
I know this must seem nuts to you,
but life should be a little nuts.
Otherwise, it's just a bunch of
Thursdays, you know, strung together.
- You look beautiful.
- Thank you.
Okay, who else?
Okay.
You see that guy with the combover?
The one talking to the woman
with the back cleavage?
Yeah. He owns half
of downtown San Francisco...
...and the guy next to him,
he owns the other half.
Okay, how about the guy
with the George Hamilton tan?
That's George Hamilton.
No, no, you're not gonna get me there.
I don't go to the movies anymore.
It's all special effects.
All they do is blow things up.
I know. They used to make movies
about real things, about people.
- Not anymore.
- Like Chinatown.
- Yes.
- Chinatown.
- Now, that's a movie.
- Oh, I loved that movie.
I didn't understand a thing
that happened, but I loved it.
"My sister. My mother. My sister. "
How about Butch Cassidy
and the Sundance Kid?
- Is that a movie?
- Katharine Ross. I was in love with her.
You wanna talk
about Katharine Ross?
The Graduate.
- Was she drop-dead gorgeous or what?
- Hey, hey.
Let me tell you something about
The Graduate that very few people know.
It was Richard Dreyfuss' first movie.
He had one line:
"Shall I get the cops?
I'll get the cops. "
- Yes, that's right!
- He said it to Norman Fell...
...the guy from Three's Company.
- That's right!
In the boarding house, right?
Come on, folks,
all money goes to charity.
Winner, eight the hard way.
Hey, Beau. Patterson's here.
If you go over and talk to him, you could
close this thing in three minutes.
- You remember Sarah Huttinger.
- Yes, hi.
- Nice to see you.
- I'm really not interested.
Three minutes. All right, three minutes.
It's 49 percent for 75 mil.
Any chance we can get
controlling interest?
No, that's a deal breaker.
- We'll see. I'm sorry...
- Go, go, go. Go. Go.
- I'll be right back.
- It's fine.
What's up?
Hi.
This your first Casablanca Night?
Yeah.
Cool.
Is that your real hair color?
- What?
- No, it's good.
I mean, you know, it's silky and shiny.
You could be a good hair model.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Wanna have sex?
- Excuse me?
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
I was looking for my father.
This is supposed to be his table,
but I don't see him anywhere.
So if he comes by, tell him
that Blake was here for me, would you?
Well, who is your dad?
Beau Burroughs.
What? Wait... Wait just one... So, what...?
What are you...? What are you saying?
That Beau... That you're...
That he's... You're... That you're...
You're babbling.
I thought he didn't have any children.
He had at least one.
Champagne guy.
Okay. Okay.
Just because he's not sterile...
...does not mean
that I just had sex with my father.
Oh, God.
No, God!
- Oh, God!
- Hey, I'll bite.
What was that?
Are you okay?
Hey, Pops.
Blake. What...?
Welcome back. I thought you were
coming home next week.
No, today. I came home today.
- Sarah, this is Blake. He's my...
- This is your son.
- Right. He's in from Africa.
- No, it was Asia. I was in Asia, Dad.
Asia, right.
- We need to talk.
- I know.
- Alone.
- We need to talk alone right now.
- Okay.
God! Blunt testicular trauma?
Come on.
You have a child! You have a son.
You are a sick man.
This isn't The Graduate,
this is Deliverance!
Calm down.
There is a simple explanation.
Is he adopted?
- No.
- Then you are a sick man.
I am a sick woman.
We have done a very sick, sick thing!
Blake is not my biological son.
My God, I'm gonna need
so much therapy.
- What did you just say?
- I said that Blake...
...is not my biological son,
nor is he adopted.
My first wife, Cynthia,
wanted to have children of her own.
I, of course, could not do that for her,
so we used an alternative method.
- A donor.
- A donor?
A donor. So technically
Blake is not my son...
...but we chose never
to tell him that.
I would appreciate
if you would do the same.
Of course I won't.
But you're still sterile, right?
No, I... I lied. I made up
this whole story...
...just so that I could have sex
with my own daughter.
- All right.
- What kind of guy do you think I am?
Okay, you...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I called you a sick man.
You're not a sick man,
you're a very nice man.
Thank you.
And very charming.
And generous.
And smart.
And accomplished.
And a good pilot.
Very handsome.
Apology accepted.
I hope that's not your father.
Jeff, what are you doing here?
I don't know. I thought something
might have happened to you...
...but apparently
something happened to me.
No, Jeff, wait. Jeff, wait.
Jeff! Jeff, please wait. Jeff!
- What? What?
- Okay, okay. That... That wasn't...
That wasn't... I didn't kiss him.
He kissed me.
Did you sleep with him?
I didn't mean to.
I know. God, Jeff. I was so drunk.
I don't remember anything. That's not
an excuse, but it's kind of an excuse.
- Jeff, I love you.
- No! Don't say that.
Don't you say that. Now, I don't know
what game we're playing...
...but obviously this engagement
that you and I have entered into...
...has absolutely no meaning to you.
Jeff, I'm so scared.
I'm tired of scared.
No, Jeff, please.
Just please listen to me!
- What?
- I know that you hate me right now.
I hate me right now.
I'm... I'm insane.
It's like I'm possessed by this person
who's terrified and just screwed up.
I know we're good together. You're
the only person I can be myself with.
Even if I don't know
who the hell that is.
Then marry me, Sarah, right now.
Wrong answer.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Sarah.
- I found Beau Burroughs.
I didn't know where else to go.
Come in, I'll put on a pot of bourbon.
And I just stood there. I just stood
there and I let Jeff walk away.
I mean, why?
Why couldn't I say yes?
- Grandma, what is wrong with me?
- There is nothing wrong with you.
- And don't call me Grandma.
- Oh, I'm such a mess.
You are not a mess.
You are a human being.
And you made a mistake.
People make mistakes.
Sometimes life is just...
Beau Burroughs!
What the hell were you thinking?
- What were you thinking?
- I wasn't thinking!
- Well, I wasn't thinking either!
- What was he thinking?
- We know what he was thinking.
- It's not his fault.
It is always his fault. Of course it is.
- He is nothing but a horny bastard.
- Oh, it's me, Grandma, it's me.
- Don't say that!
- Why not? It's the truth.
- I'll say it again. It's me.
- It is not the truth. Hello.
I have happiness staring me
right in the face, and what do I do?
I stare right back at it.
Katharine, I need some help.
Annie's hysterical.
- Annie? Why? What happened?
- She had an anxiety attack on the plane.
- And you know why?
- I don't know, why?
- What? Are you talking to me?
- I'm talking to Sarah.
Because I am my mother's daughter.
- Sarah's there?
- Sarah's here.
- She wasn't happy.
- Your mother was happy.
- She was not happy!
She found out she was pregnant
and left the love of her life...
...to come back and have me.
- The love of her life?
- This is my fault.
- I wanna talk to Sarah!
- She wants to talk to Sarah.
- It's not your fault!
- Yes, it is my fault.
- It is not. It is not!
- Katharine.
- It is. I stole my mother's happiness.
- Katharine!
- You did not!
- I did, I did, I did, I did!
- Katharine!
Am I the only sane one here?
- I wanna see Sarah.
- She wants to see Sarah.
- Annie wants to see Sarah.
- Annie?
- Sweetheart, maybe Grandma...
- I only wanna talk to Sarah!
- She only wants to talk to Sarah!
- She wants to talk to Sarah!
She wants to talk to me?
- Hi. Annie okay?
- No. She's upstairs.
We're making her favorite soup,
tomato with crackers. Want some?
- No, I'm okay.
- I thought she was in New York.
She had a fight with Jeff
and she never got on the plane.
Two days ago I thought
I had two happy daughters.
Things are never what they seem
with the women in this family.
Annie?
It's me.
Annie. Honey.
How well did you know Mom?
What?
I can't remember her.
I was only 4.
Was she happy?
I don't know.
She always looked so happy
in pictures.
She married so young.
I always thought that, you know,
if she was happy...
...then maybe I would be.
Honey, what happened on the plane?
I just stopped breathing.
We were over the Gulf of Mexico
on the way to Belize...
...and I just stopped.
I kept thinking
that I've ruined my life...
...that I've married someone I like to
play tennis with, and that's all I'll do.
And I couldn't breathe.
I know the feeling.
Oh, God.
Annie, let me ask you a question.
When you and Scott play tennis...
...do you guys have fun?
- Yeah.
When you guys go out to dinner?
Yeah. When you watch TV?
- We like The Nanny.
- Nanny's funny.
Honey, sometimes I just think
it's more important...
...who we're with
than what we're doing.
And if you're gonna marry someone,
it may as well be your best friend.
Yeah, like you are with Jeff?
Yeah.
Oh, I'm such a mess.
I'm the most screwed-up person
in the world.
You're not even the most
screwed-up person in this room.
Oh, really?
I spent the first night of my honeymoon
in the Houston airport under sedation.
Oh, yeah?
Well, did you sleep with a man who also
slept with Mom and Grandma Katharine?
What?
You slept with Dad?
Dad slept with Grandma Katharine?
Oh, God. No, God, come on,
even I'm not that twisted.
All right. From the beginning.
And don't leave out a thing.
No, the Xanax is for my
other granddaughter.
We're talking about Sarah here,
the one from New York.
Well, she broke up with her boyfriend.
She needs something stronger.
Fine. I'll hold.
Here. You're on hold.
Son of a bitch.
Oh, Jesus.
Hello, Katharine.
You're looking well.
Go shit in your shoes.
Mrs. Richelieu, are
you trying to seduce me?
You weren't that good the first time.
How dare you? Sarah?
You couldn't stop with Jocelyn,
could you?
You almost ruined my daughter's life.
- Wait a minute, Katharine.
- Get down.
Hold on, Katharine.
Ruin her life?
What movie are you living in now,
Katharine?
I didn't pursue Jocelyn,
I don't recall inviting her to Cabo.
And I didn't pursue your granddaughter.
She managed to come 500 miles...
...up to San Francisco on her own
looking for me.
And we both know that I sure as hell
did not pursue you.
I know.
How come we've never
talked like this before?
I don't know.
I've always wanted to.
Me too.
- I love you, Annie.
- I love you too.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
- It's him.
- Who him?
- "Him" him!
- "Him" him?
Just stop. I mean, this isn't about
Sarah. And it isn't about Jocelyn, is it?
- This is about you.
- You're goddamn right it is.
You dropped me. You dropped me
for a newer model.
Do you know how old
that made me feel?
And you realize,
when you did that...
...that I was 13 years younger
than you are now.
I don't know, Katharine.
I haven't done the math.
I suppose everyone
needs someone in their life...
...to let them know when youth
has come to an end.
And here she is.
It's your turn.
- Are you okay?
- She's fine.
Is she happy to see me too?
Beau, you should not
have come down here.
Why not?
He's been everywhere else.
So, what's going on out here?
Lawn party?
- Earl.
- Daddy...
This is... This is Beau Burroughs.
He was a schoolmate of Jocelyn's.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I know you.
Beau Burroughs.
- I've never forgiven you.
- Okay, Dad...
No, no. This man haunts my dreams.
City soccer final, playing
Pasadena Prep, tie score.
I make it around the last defender,
I'm flying down the field...
...to kick the winning goal.
All of a sudden, this maniac...
- That was you?
- You broke my heart.
But I gotta give it to you,
hell of a save.
- You were injured, weren't you?
- Yeah.
What are we standing here for?
You wanna come in the house?
No, thanks. I was...
I just stopped by.
Sarah, could I have a word
with you out at the car?
- It was nice seeing you, Katharine.
- Oh, yeah.
It's wonderful catching up
on old times.
Earl.
Hell of a save.
Why did you come down here, Beau?
Well, for one thing, you left last night
without saying goodbye.
I know. I'm sorry.
I know, I did that.
No, no. I didn't come for an apology.
Obviously your life's more complicated
than you've let on.
I don't know... I don't know what's
going on in your relationship, Sarah...
...and I'm not even gonna ask.
I just... I came down here because
I wanted to tell you something.
When I saw you walk away last night,
when I watched, it...
It might as well have been Cabo
30 years ago.
I didn't tell you the truth before.
I was awake when your mother left.
I watched her drive away in this old
wood-paneled station wagon.
It looked like she was crying.
I'm not my mother, Beau.
I know.
You know what I realized
as I was coming back down here?
I am... I'm a year older than she was
when she died.
I mean, you have no idea
how strange that feels.
And I have spent so much of my life
trying to figure out who I am...
...I don't think I realized
I was just trying to find her.
You know, but that's just
chasing a ghost, you know?
Maybe we're both just chasing ghosts.
You know?
You're not gonna say, "This could be
the beginning of a beautiful friendship"?
Wrong movie.
Well...
It was nice meeting you,
Mr. Burroughs.
Ms. Huttinger.
Goodbye.
- Let's go. You're gonna miss the plane.
- Coming.
Oh, did you remember to pack
the binoculars, honey?
We might see monkeys.
They're still in the bag
with all your shoes.
- Hey.
- You're gonna have a great time.
- Yeah.
- Just remember to keep breathing.
- Yeah. You too.
- You are such a lucky girl.
Most people wait 10 years
for a second honeymoon.
- I know.
- You sure you don't wanna come?
- I think I'm just gonna stay here.
- Well, cheer up.
You'll find another man
to screw things up with in no time.
Thank you, Grandma.
Do you think Scott and Annie are
gonna make it to Belize this time?
I certainly hope so.
So...
...what are we gonna do with you?
Dad, can I ask you a question?
Before you and Mom got married...
...do you remember if Mom...
...sort of took off for a few days?
- You mean when she went to Mexico?
- Yeah.
- With Beau Burroughs?
Yeah.
You knew about that?
Daddy, why didn't you
just say something?
What for? I got your mom, he didn't.
Did she ever tell you
why she came back?
Because she loved me.
She said that, while being
with Beau was an adventure...
...she knew that she could
build a life with me.
She apologized, she offered to tell me
everything that happened...
...and I didn't need to know.
As long as she was back.
Come here.
Now, this may not be
the sort of thing...
...that you wanna know
about your parents...
...but the night that she came back
is the night we conceived you.
Lucky for us we were married
the next week, so nobody noticed.
Oh, Daddy, I don't understand.
Why are we so different?
I mean, I don't like tennis.
I drive like a crazy person...
...and you always drive so slow.
I only drive slow, sweetheart,
because you're in the car with me.
Oh, Dad.
- Take me to the airport.
- You gonna get on the plane this time?
- I promise.
- Come on.
- Thank you.
- Nice seeing you again, Sarah.
If you shut the door, I understand,
but I really hope that you don't.
I know there's nothing that I can say
that will take away...
Then don't try.
I never told you, when I was a kid...
...I was in a car accident
when I was 10.
And I smashed my head on
the dashboard and cracked my skull...
...split it open from here to here,
17 stitches.
And I never thought that I would
long for that day until now.
It didn't mean anything.
It meant something to me.
Words mean something to me.
"Engaged" means something to me.
It doesn't mean
"maybe I'll get married. "
It doesn't mean "I'll see how I feel,
I don't know, I'm not sure. "
It doesn't mean
"I'm gonna test the waters...
...and see if there's somebody else
out there that I like better. "
It means you've fallen in love
with the person...
...that you wanna
spend your life with...
...and that you actually want
to marry them.
I wanna marry you.
I'll marry you next month,
I'll marry you this week.
I'll walk out of this apartment right now
and I will marry you.
It doesn't work that way, okay?
You can't just walk in here now...
...and tell me that you can't
live without me and expect...
What am I supposed to do with that?
I'm supposed to make it all right for you?
I can't anymore.
I don't want you to.
I love you.
I didn't come here to tell you
that I can't live without you.
I can live without you.
I just don't want to.
One condition.
If we have a daughter...
...Burroughs doesn't come
within 1000 miles of her.
It stops with me.
On a cold January night
in the city of New York...
...this man and this woman
slept together.
They also slept together
the next night and the next night...
...and the next night
and the next night.
In the name of God,
I pronounce you husband and wife.
Thanks.
You're gonna have to stop doing that.
Okay, everybody, all the girls.