Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Hello?
Is anyone in there?
Please...
Open... open the door!
Mr... Please, could someone...
Hurry up!
MAN: Yes, yes. Relax.
Get out of the way. Out of the way!
Open the door!
Hello? Is there somebody in there?
Yes. Go away, please.
Find somebody else to annoy.
GIRL: What's happened?
Hello? Hello!
I said piss off! Now!
Hello, is there somebody in there?
Open up!
Are you sure there's
someone in there?
Yes, I'm sure.
Well, go and get the janitor.
Hello! He...
Mate?
Mate, is that you in there?
Shit. Shit.
Open the door!
If there's someone in here,
open the door!
Open the door!
MAN: Are you sure
there's someone in the...
Just open the fucking door!
Oh, my God.
Yeah, no, it's me.
Yeah, it's me playing.
Um... alright.
Well, I'll talk to you about it
in the first break, OK?
Alright. Yep. Cool. See ya.
Mel!
BO Y: Next year, um,
when school's finished...
I'm leaving, Melody!
...I'd really like to be like my dad.
You know, he's just...
you've just gotta admire him.
I mean, he works really,
really hard,
he's successful -
he's a partner in this major firm.
You know, 6-figure salary.
They have these fucking
beautiful offices.
MARCUS: Mel!
MARCUS: I'm leaving, Melody!
I remember when I was little -
I was probably about eight or nine -
and, um, saved up all my money
for... for this
'Dollar a Day' commercial.
You know, the ones with the kids
with all the flies
all over their face.
Anyway, I sponsored
this little girl.
Her name was Jemina.
She was so cute.
Anyway, my brother,
Marcus, found out,
who then told my dad.
God, he got so angry.
He said I was wasting money.
You know, she could've died.
I love kids.
I think I could be
a primary school teacher.
It'd be fun.
Oh, and animals too.
They're just so gorgeous.
We weren't allowed pets, though.
Fuck.
BO Y: Yeah, I've got a good body,
but it's not about being vain,
you know?
It's about being a top-class athlete.
Like, I love scoring goals
and winning and... you know?
Just making good time.
And then I fucking hate school.
I sit there and I listen to shit
that has no relevance to me.
Like, fair enough for someone else
who's gonna go off and be a lawyer
or some shit like that,
but for me it's just fucking useless,
you know?
Who actually gives a fuck about
some dead poet from 200 years ago?
Premier league soccer players,
we don't need maths or Shakespeare
or Tutan-fucking-khamen, you know?
Luke!
BO Y: I love tits.
I love pussy.
I just love women.
I guess saying all that shit
makes me normal, huh?
It's like people
can just look at me and say,
"Oh, he's just this normal,
horny little kid."
You wanna know the truth, though?
I love cock.
I love arse.
And saying that shit,
people just look at me like...
...Iook at me like
I'm this sick, perverted,
twisted little fucking outcast.
That's school, though, innit?
GIRL: After next year all my friends
want to be big, independent women
or have some great career.
Yeah.
I think marriage is a nice thought.
Now, I know there's probably
a million feminist
butch chicks out there
who'd kill me for saying that,
but I'm not talking about
one of those fat housewives
who go shopping in their trackies.
I just like the idea of being in love.
I mean, just 'cause you're married
doesn't mean you have to
let yourself go.
SOCCER COMMENTATOR:
And we've had 100 minutes
of end to end football here tonight,
and some very tired legs
out there now.
To Viera - ooh, it's a careless pass.
Intercepted by Ryan Giggs.
And now Manchester United streaming
ahead in numbers now.
Dwight Yorke making a run
to the corner flag.
Support waiting in the centre as well,
but it's still Giggs
on the edge of the area.
Past Keown now, past Dixon.
And a sensational goal!
How can Arsenal possibly come back
after such an unbelievable finish
as that?
Ryan Giggs surely has never hit
a more telling strike
at such a vital time,
surely clinching this FA Cup
semifinal for Manchester United.
And you'll have to wait a long time
to see another goal like that.
BO Y: Back home in England,
me and my family,
we always lived in the same street,
the same house,
and all the neighbours and friends,
they knew my medical problems.
I've got one leg longer
than the other one
and, um, that gives me a limp.
I was also born with two urethras,
and one of them I can control,
and one of them just does
its own thing,
and... I wet myself, and...
it's really embarrassing.
Uh... I started school here
three months ago,
when we moved down here.
I used to have this saying
that the shit would hit the fan
but it would never hit me.
Recently it's really, really
started to stink.
MARCUS: Hey.
Mel! Mel!
Listen, uh... Are you gonna be OK?
Mel!
Melody!
Hey, Mel.
Hey.
What's up?
Not much.
Your mum still away?
Yeah. She is.
I haven't spoken to her for a while.
Oh, really?
When's she getting back?
I don't know.
Probably three weeks or so.
So you're home alone?
Yeah. It's just me and Marcus.
OK, there he is.
Good luck.
See you upstairs.
How you doing, Luke?
Hey.
How are you?
Not bad.
Hey.
I heard your story in English
did really well.
You know, it's, um...
...it's been said that exposure to...
...classical kinds
of music as a child
triggers these neural pathways
in your brain
that create this spatial,
temporal reasoning ability.
It increases your intellect.
Your story...
...was it, um...
...about somebody in particular?
Was it... personal?
Of course it was personal.
Oh.
Who was it about?
Look, I've gotta go.
Marcus. Come on, I didn't...
BO Y: Hey, Luke. What happened
at the party after I left?
LUKE: Oh, I was fucking gone, man.
BO Y 2: You were fucked!
I'd gone into the corner to
take a slash, right,
'cause I was fucking parro,
and this little bastard
taps me on the shoulder...
What - Dino?
Nah. Yeah, Ben.
So I turn around
while I'm taking a piss
and just piss all over this guy, man.
You fucking pissed all over him?
What did Ben do?
What could he do, man?
He was covered in piss.
Hey, Seanie!
Hey, Sean.
How's it going, buddy?
You get fucking shit on your dick?
Hey, you like taking it
or giving it, eh?
I could give it to you, Seanie.
Oh, yeah. Oh! I'm gonna come.
Yeah. You like that?
Hey. Oh, come on. Give us a kiss.
SEAN: Get the fuck off me.
Oooh!
What - we're not good enough
for you, Seanie?
You're fuckin' pathetic.
Fucking cock jockey!
GIRL: Hey, babe.
Hey, guys.
She's always looking at him.
Oh, whatever.
She is!
What the fuck are you doing?
Get out!
What IS wrong with him?
Probably stoned.
It's disgusting.
Fuck.
Did you hear about
Griggs having cancer?
Shit - is it bad?
I don't know. Think so.
That's sad.
It is.
Alright. How do I look?
You look hot.
Alrighty. I'll see you after.
Alright. See you later.
GIRL: Hey, Sarah!
Hey!
Can you wait two minutes?
Yeah. I'll meet you down there.
Alright. See ya.
See ya!
BO Y: Come on, give us a kiss.
What - we're not
good enough for you, Seanie?
SEAN: You're fuckin' pathetic.
BO Y: Fucking cock jockey!
Hey, babe.
Hey, guys.
We're gonna cruise, Lukey.
See ya.
Uh... I gotta go.
Oh, I just got here!
See ya.
Hey. Where's Luke going?
His class or something.
Where were you?
Oh, this student video thing.
Oh.
Are you gonna do it?
No.
So, uh, how are things with Luke?
Mmm, yeah, OK.
What is wrong with him?
I know. It's disgusting.
That... that is gross.
I'm not touching that rail.
WOMAN ON PHONE:
Shouldn't you be at school?
Yeah. I AM at school.
I'm at a payphone.
So, how's your holiday?
Oh, God. It's so sunny down here.
I wish you were here with me.
Yeah.
How's your father?
He's OK.
I haven't really seen him.
He's interstate at the moment.
What?! He left you guys alone?
No...
Please don't tell him.
I wasn't meant to say anything.
Unbelievable.
How did you get to school?
Marcus drove us.
Typical.
Anyway, I just...
...I just rang to say that I miss you.
Is everything alright? Are you OK?
Yeah.
OK, sweetie.
Gotta run. Love you.
Love you too.
Hey, Melody?
You still there?
Yeah.
Take care of your brother, OK?
OK.
MELODY: My parents really push
my brother into things,
like school, music.
Everything.
It was just so different
with me, though.
You know, any time
I started getting good at something -
piano or dance,
or basically anything arty -
Dad would just stop paying lessons.
It's like... it's like he hated me
being good at things.
Hell, he wouldn't even
let me listen to music.
He's weird.
And I know that sounds stupid.
I know that.
But... that's just the way it seems.
That's good. That's good.
You've shown some really
perceptive discussion
on the legal side of
same-sex marriage
and the legal side of adoption.
But what about the kids
in this whole issue?
How are they going to be affected?
What's going to be their place
in this complicated jigsaw?
Yeah.
Um... I don't really think it matters.
If you have parents
that are the same sex
or male and female
they're still gonna
get the same amount of love,
and the kids are gonna be
brought up fine.
I can kind of see, though, if...
Other people, they'll probably
look at 'em differently, I reckon.
TEACHER: Why would they
look at them differently?
Well, I mean, obviously
people are gonna find out
that his parents are gay,
so, you know, he's gonna get
harassed and teased at school.
You know, it's just rude
and it's unfair.
Exactly, yeah - that kid
would have to put up with
all of the torment that he'd get
because his parents
made the selfish choice
to have that relationship
and then bring them into it.
What - you're saying
that it's selfish
for two people to have a child,
for two loving people to bring
a kid into a loving family?
Is that what you're saying?
BO Y: No.
It's just it's not natural for
two... two gay men to have a kid.
It's got nothing to do with 'natural'.
If two people love each other
they should be able to bring
and raise a child...
It's not about love.
They've never been able
to adopt a kid before.
God made Adam and Eve,
not Adam and Steve.
That's fucking bullshit, mate.
You're referring to
a Bible reference.
It's a creation story - it's a myth!
BO Y 2: If two dudes
are bringing up a kid,
of course the kid's gonna be
a fag in the end, aren't they?
You're fucking ignorant, mate.
TEACHER: Sean...
You're fucking ignorant.
TEACHER: Settle. Come on. Hey.
My fucking parents
are straight as an arrow.
BO Y 2: Look at you - you're a fag.
TEACHER: Matt, that's enough.
You're trying to inflict it
on the rest of us.
TEACHER: Hey, whoa. Whoa.
This is not a personal discussion.
It's a discussion about issues, OK?
What's the issue that
you are trying to direct here?
Keep your personal stuff out of it.
G'day, mate. Bit early today?
Yeah.
Hey, I heard you playing before.
I didn't know you were musical.
Oh, I've been playing
since I was a little kid.
Yeah? Well, it shows.
Thanks.
Hey, I, uh... I read your story.
Yeah?
Yeah! Yeah.
I, uh... I liked it.
Thanks.
Sounds like you're in love, huh?
Hey, listen, about that, your story,
uh, I mean, this is just
a formality, but, um...
'Formality'? What do you mean?
It's sort of...
I was thinking about it
last night, and, um...
Wh... You know it's my piece.
I haven't copied it.
Oh, of course. No, it's not that.
It's, uh... well, it's...
It's the content.
What are you trying to say?
Well, it's, uh...
I mean, I'm sure you'll
agree it's not a story
that every Tom, Dick and Harry
would write.
And it touched upon some very
sensitive and erotic issues.
Yeah, alright, but you understand
that it's just a story.
I know, I know, I know.
But, um... let me
put it to you this way.
If someone came in here
and wrote a story about
shooting up the whole school
it would be my responsibility
to check it out.
Right, I understand that.
But this story isn't about
shooting up the whole school.
It's a love story, for Christ's sake.
Did you write it about
anyone in particular?
No, I didn't,
and everybody's been asking me that,
and it wasn't about anyone
and it wasn't written FOR anyone.
It's just a story. That's all it is.
And if I showed it to someone -
say, uh, your father?
No! Why would you show it to him?
OK, relax.
No, I can't relax!
It doesn't even have
anything to do with him.
And, look, I wrote the story
because I wanted to be...
Morning, guys.
I wanted it to be
controversial and different
so I could win, and I did win.
You did.
And that's what it's about.
Forget I said anything, OK?
It's all good. Stop worrying.
OK.
OK, guys.
Now, if you can get your books
straight out today
and, uh, open up to page 24.
We are studying the Scottish play.
I remember one time, um...
...we had this babysitter, and...
This is when Mum and Dad
were still together.
But, anyway, we had this babysitter,
and Melody and I fell...
well, Melody fell asleep.
I was still half-awake.
And Mum and Dad got home
and they... they paid the babysitter
and... Dad... Dad didn't even wait
until they got into the bedroom.
I don't know, I guess he thought
that we were both asleep,
but, um... I remember he just
ripped off her clothes
and just started fucking her, like,
right then and there on the couch.
And I know I should be disgusted -
like, I know that.
I was... Well, it's not like I was...
I dunno, I... I guess
I still think about it.
Hey, guys. Hey.
How you going?
Alright. I'll feed you.
Hey, babies.
Come up. Out the way.
There we go.
Hey, sweetie.
Hello!
You're getting big.
Yeah.
You little cutie, huh?
You remember me.
Aww.
Don't be scared.
It's OK.
Hey, what's going on in there, huh?
Hey, Melody.
You've been really great
with the animals this term.
She's a cute one, isn't she, Daisy?
Yeah. She is.
Hey, you know, someone has to take
them home each week for the weekend.
Maybe you could take...
No.
My brother's allergic.
Marcus?
Yeah.
Everything alright?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Fuck, this is boring as shit.
Bloody reffo.
I reckon someone should
sew his lips together.
TEACHER: Luke! Tom!
TEACHER: Right, get out of here now.
Both of you.
Hey, what do you reckon of
that Clare chick in there?
The fat one?
She's not fat!
Nah, huge, man.
She's got good tits, though, man.
My girl has twice the tits
and half the frame.
Yeah, but that's Sarah, you know?
I mean, she's like a twig.
Go too hard on Sarah
you could break her...
...if you've got a small cock.
Virgin!
Shut the fuck up, man.
What?
Cheers.
I was thinking, right,
I reckon I wanna arsefuck her.
Sarah?
Yeah.
What's wrong with that, man?
You wanna arsefuck her?
Nothing gay, man.
No, you just wanna
put your cock in her...
Fuck you.
Oi, check it out.
TEACHER: What is that smell?
TEACHER: Steven?
Steven!
Can I see you outside?
Oh!
What is the matter with you?
Steven, I'm speaking to you.
A bit old for this sort of thing,
aren't you?
You'd better go
and get yourself cleaned up
then you'd better go
and see the counsellor.
Mr Darcy, my bag and books...
...are inside.
Aren't we lucky
it wasn't number twos.
LUKE: I was thinking, right -
I reckon I wanna arsefuck her.
TOM: Sarah?
LUKE: Yeah.
LUKE: What's wrong with that, man?
TOM: You wanna arsefuck her?
Nothing gay, man.
No, you just wanna
put your cock in her...
LUKE: Fuck you.
TOM: Oi, check it out.
Hey, how you going, Uneven Steven?
Steve, are you alright, bro?
You had an accident?
You've pissed yourself, man.
That's horrible.
You reek, mate!
Watch out! Watch out! Stairs!
LUKE: Shit, that sucks.
Oh, wait up, man!
I didn't mean to do it.
I mean, it's not like...
it's not like I can control it.
Before I knew it, it was...
my trousers were just wet.
It's just like a routine now.
My parents, they used to send me
with these... with perfume to school
to try and mask the smell,
but... that was pretty hopeless.
And then they tried -
well, we tried -
these pad thingies,
and I think they were meant to
absorb the wee, but...
...God, that was a stupid idea.
That didn't work either.
So now the only thing
that I can really do
is pack the same pair of trousers
that I'm wearing that day
and underwear
and then take them to school
and... yeah.
That... I suppose that works, but...
...some days I go...
I wet myself more than once,
and it's frustrating.
It's embarrassing.
MELODY: Sure, we think
we have family and friends.
But when stuff happens...
...when really serious
stuff happens...
...you just feel so alone.
And you can't tell people.
I mean, they'll probably listen.
But they don't know everything.
In fact, they don't know anything.
There's just...
some stuff you can't share.
So, what do you do then?
GIRL: He is really beautiful.
Which one?
Luke.
I know you think he is.
Yeah, he is.
So, um...
...would you, uh... would you fuck him?
Sorry. I mean, um,
would you give him your virginity?
So, did you hear Michael's
back in hospital?
Yeah, I... I heard.
SARAH: Slut.
Fucking bitch.
Don't worry about it.
No. Who the hell
does she think she is?
Seriously, don't worry about it.
Anyway, I gotta go.
OK, well, I'll see you at 4:00?
Yeah.
SARAH: I can't believe it.
She was right there with it.
Well, what was it?
It was positive.
Fuck.
So she's pregnant?
Wait. Sarah, tell me
exactly what happened.
She stopped and I... and I saw her.
What was I supposed to do, huh?
Never thought she'd get a fuck.
Bullshit.
Whose do you
think it is, then?
Sarah, come on.
Nah.
Don't do this to me, Sarah.
You don't understand.
She's with him more than I am.
Look, he loves you.
You know he does. This is stupid.
You do this every time!
Look, it's his. I know it.
Slut.
Fucking bitch.
MELODY: Don't worry about it.
No. Who the hell does
she think she is?
Hey, babe.
I gotta go.
Oh, babe. Just a minute?
Sorry.
SARAH: God, they were all
so jealous of Luke and I.
He had his pick of every girl
in the school and he chose me.
It's not like I tried
to trick him or anything.
I didn't.
I can trust him. I know I can.
But girls can be so bitchy,
and, frankly, they'll do anything
to get what they want.
It's not always the guy's fault.
STEVEN: At home I've got
this list of, um...
...all the football greats,
like Beckham and Ronaldo
and Zidane and all of them.
One day I'm gonna be on that list.
STEVEN: And this is
Steven's comeback game.
He's been out for about a year
with a leg injury now,
and what an important comeback game
this one is set to be.
He's just gotten
his first touch of the game
and it looks to be a good'un -
interception at the halfway line.
He takes it round one defender.
Oh, skips past another
and he's gone past Ronaldo
like he's not even there.
He lays it off.
This is brilliant play.
He gets it back at the edge
of the box and he shoots,
and it's straight into
the top-right corner!
Oh, and the crowd go wild!
This is absolutely brilliant play
by Steven and England.
Wembley hasn't seen
play like this since '66.
The Brazilians are gutted.
MARCUS: I was watching
one of those courtroom dramas,
and, uh, there's that moment when
the jury come out of deliberation
and they tell the judge whether
or not this guy's gonna be guilty.
Oh, the tension is so thick you...
...you actually could cut it
with a knife.
I mean, that's what
it was like when, um,
when we get a test
or an assignment back.
You know, you just avoid all
the scribble on all of the pages
and you just head straight
to the verdict.
I mean, I usually do pretty well.
Um...
...but, you know,
those few times, um,
I heard that guilty verdict
it was my dad.
Yeah, he really tore me up.
You know, he's always, like,
"Oh, yeah, yeah, it's good,
"but, um... is it good enough?"
And everything always just has to
be so fucking perfect with him.
He's... he's usually right, though.
Marcus.
Yeah, look, um, I just...
I just saw my mark for the test.
Yeah, 87. Not bad.
Yeah, I know it's pretty good,
but I need three more per cent.
Well, there's no
negotiating of marks.
Look, I understand that
in any other circumstance,
and that would be fine...
No, no, in ALL circumstances
we don't change the marks.
Look, please, you don't understand.
If you could just check over
that paper once,
I'm sure we can find it!
No, I'm not checking anything.
Please. Put my mind at rest.
Look, Marcus, if you wanna
continue with this nonsense
we can talk about lowering
your overall mark by 5%.
Mrs Jacobs, look,
you don't understand!
Goodbye, Marcus. Goodbye, Marcus.
Please!
Fuck!
Hey. I got the music you were after.
What's up with you?
She wouldn't even fucking
listen to me.
Who?
Jacobs.
I needed 90%.
What did you get?
87's awesome.
What are you talking about?
Marcus...
I think, um, most people
probably see me
as a geek or a nerd or whatever.
They never really give me
much trouble, though.
I... I don't know.
But the odd times that they do
give me a bit of grief,
I just look at them
and think to myself,
"Well, in five years
you'll be on fucking welfare
"and serving me at McDonald's, so..."
Yeah, well... that's
a comforting thought.
Get back to your mum.
Hey, dude.
Look who's checking you out, man.
Which one?
The fucking blonde one.
What's her name?
Mel.
Melody, man.
You're gonna be singing
to that tune all night.
Melody!
I've known her since
I was, like, six, man.
Whatever, man.
Look, you've gotta tell me that
with a straight face.
Tell me you wouldn't want
a piece of that arse.
Did you see that look?
I saw that look, man.
You've fucking done her already,
haven't you?
Did you fuck her in the arse?
Was it tight?
Look, man, you're with your boys.
You can tell us.
Nuh.
You took her home,
you stroked her hair,
and you fucked her up the ar...
Fuck off, yeah?
BO Y: You alright, Luke?
LUKE: It's all a fucking game
at school, you know?
I mean, the shit that
goes on there - seriously.
Yeah, I'll give someone shit,
I'll pay him out,
but I doubt he's gonna go home
and cry himself to sleep over it.
You know, you've gotta be tough,
otherwise people will stomp you
down to the fucking ground.
It's a jungle - and if you can't
fake your way through school,
how the fuck are you gonna make it
in the real world?
Huh? Tell me that.
You want me to call
a plumber, Steven?
STEVEN: I love my family -
my mum, my dad,
my brother and my sister.
Through all of this they've been
sitting at my bedside in hospital
or waiting in waiting rooms
when I've been in theatre.
And they've just been brilliant
through all of this
and... it's just been amazing,
their support.
And now when I have trouble at school
I just... I just don't think
I can complain to them.
I don't... I don't think I can.
They deserve... they deserve
to have better than that now.
Yes.
Sean. G'day, mate. Come on through.
What's that?
Oh, just my folks.
They, um, they got me, like,
this dog the other day.
Oh, cool.
Yeah.
What sort?
Oh, it's, um...
It's like a husky, I guess.
It looks sort of like a wolf.
How's he settling in?
I cut its fucking throat.
You killed it?
No, I'm just joking.
It's going good. Yeah, I like it.
OK.
And why do you think your, um...
Why do you think your parents
bought you a dog?
I dunno.
It's just... lately, I guess since...
It's probably since I came out,
you know.
They've been fucking
badgering me constantly about
"Why don't you bring
any people home anymore?"
And...... I guess it's about
they want me to have companionship.
It just fucking shits me off,
because...
My dad, especially,
always in my ear, constantly -
he thinks this is a phase,
he thinks I'm just
a teenager that...
...this whole fucking gay thing
is just gonna disappear,
you know what I mean?
It's just fucking shit.
He knows I'm gay.
He has to fucking deal with it,
and that's it.
It's really hard for fathers
to understand.
Oh, yeah, but I'm his kid. I'm his son.
How fucking hard is it
to accept your kid?
Parents want their kids
to grow up like they did.
Big deal - did your parents, like...
Did you grow up how your dad was?
No, I didn't. No, I didn't.
But it's a natural parental instinct.
I mean, parents want
their kids to be happy.
I've been as subtle as I can
with this whole thing,
and it's fucking
blown up in my face.
How are things with your mum?
My mum.
She's a fucking bitch.
I don't even go out
with my parents anymore.
I don't even go to the places
that they go to anymore
because everybody knows
I'm fucking gay.
They don't even ask me
to come anymore.
Do you talk to your brother at all?
No, I don't talk to my brother.
He's the complete opposite,
you know?
He's got this career
and he's gone to uni.
He's done it all.
He's got this woman.
He's probably gonna get married
in a couple of years.
Everything's going really,
really well
and, you know, here's me fucking...
So he's the golden boy?
Oh, of course he's
the fucking golden boy.
I mean, what are they
gonna get out of me?
They're gonna get grandkids
out of him.
I'm just their dirty little
fucking secret.
So they're ganging up on you?
They're not ganging up on me,
they're just both against me.
Hey, Marcus.
Over here.
How you going?
Yeah, I'm... I'm fine.
Um... thanks.
Hey, um...
...I heard about your sister.
Melody?
Yeah.
What? What did you hear about her?
What are you talking about?
Yeah, like, it's OK. I know.
What are you saying?
What are you talking about?
Marcus, look, you can talk to me
about it, you know. It's alright.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You mean you didn't hear?
No, I didn't fucking hear!
What the hell are you talking about?
Shit.
Look, I probably shouldn't
have said anything.
Just fucking tell me!
Fucking let go, Marcus.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry.
Jesus Christ.
Just fucking tell me
what the fuck is going on.
Fine, alright. I heard she
might be pregnant, alright?
Just... Jesus.
Who the fuck told you that?
Yeah.
I can't stand the whole attitude
at school.
You know, all that politically
correct, self-righteous bullshit.
You know, calling it my 'issues'
and calling me homo-fucking-sexual.
You know, fuck that.
You don't call a pussy
a vagina, do you?
I'm fuck... I'm gay.
It's as simple as that.
Fucking get over it.
Fuck, I gotta go back into class.
Oh, I got fucking Jacobs.
Fucking... Oh, I got physics.
I got phy...
Look at that pink fucking shit.
How the...
Nah, not good for the animals,
that shit. Not good.
Blue fucking...
So, we're OK?
Mmm.
Where you been?
Inside Sarah.
You're fucking kidding me.
No joke. I gotta take a piss.
Remember to wipe
the shit off your cock.
Yeah, get laid first
then come talk to me.
What's going on?
Dude, just leave.
You can't fucking avoid me forever.
Just fuck off, alright?
Don't fucking touch me!
What the fuck?
You're pretty fucking confident
giving me shit
in front of your mates, huh?
You fucking macho man.
Just fuck off!
Oh, look, everyone knows
you're fucking gay, alright?
Fucking get over yourself.
You fucking cunt.
Fuck!
Watch it!
Get the fuck out of my way!
What the fuck?
Motherfucker!
SEAN: People reckon
I can't fall in love.
But I have.
Who is it?
That's my business.
But it feels fucking great.
And I know one day
I'll be able to bring him
down to the house
so he can meet Mum and Dad.
And I'll make sure he sits right next
to my brother at the kitchen table.
He'll fucking freak.
SEAN: What's going on?
LUKE: Dude, just leave.
SEAN: You can't fucking
avoid me forever.
LUKE: Just fuck off, alright?
LUKE: Don't fucking touch me!
SEAN: What the fuck?
You're pretty fucking confident
giving me shit
in front of your mates, huh?
You fucking macho man.
LUKE: Just fuck off!
SEAN: Oh, look, everyone knows
you're fucking gay, alright?
Fucking get over yourself.
You fucking cunt.
LUKE: Fuck!
LUKE: You're fucking dead, cunt.
No, no, no. I...
A word and you're fucked!
BO Y: Oh, he's done it again.
GIRL: You are kidding me.
GIRL: That's disgusting.
STEVEN: I don't think
that people mean to be cruel.
Mum says that they're just kids
and... she reckons eventually
things will get better.
School finishes in three months.
That's 90 days.
90 days can sometimes be
a really, really long time, though.
GIRL: Oi. Steven, are you OK?
You're bleeding.
I have a tissue if you want.
Hey.
Are you gonna be OK?
Yeah. I'll be OK.
MAN ON LOUDSPEAKER:
Could Simona Carboni please come to
the science lab, thanks?
Simona Carboni to the science lab.
Thank you.
Hey, I've been looking for you.
Baby, what's wrong?
Just fuck off, alright?!
Fuck!
There are some thing you just
don't talk about, you know?
I won't, alright?
And I'm just... I'm just not going to.
SARAH: I just love him.
I love everything about him.
He knows more about me
than my own parents do.
I mean, how many people
can say that at 17?
They call us the prince and princess.
But they don't realise
that it's not a joke to me.
This is serious.
I could really see us
getting married.
What else can I say? I love him.
COUNSELLOR: I don't think it's such
a good idea if you go home.
Why don't you try and just go
to your next class?
What do you think of that? Yeah?
Yeah. OK. Yeah.
Yeah. OK.
Oh, yeah.
May I just go to the bathroom?
Yeah, of course. Are you OK?
Yeah, I'm fine. I just have to go.
He'd been touching me since I was 13.
Marcus.
But that...
...that was the first time
that he actually fucked me.
What? How do you know?
My friend saw the tester.
Are you dead fucking sure?
Sure that it...
No, no. We're sure.
Fuck, I mean,
no-one knows what to do.
Sarah's scared shitless.
She thinks he's cheating on her.
Well... where are you going?
Marcus, look, you didn't
hear it from me, alright?
Marcus.
Where are you going?
Come on, don't. Marcus!
MARCUS: Just leave me alone!
Marcus!
MAN ON LOUDSPEAKER:
Could Simona Carboni please come to
the science lab, thanks?
Simona Carboni to the science lab.
Thank you.
Fuck.
You fucking whore.
What the fuck have you said?
What the fuck did you do?!
Is it true?!
Fuck!
Um... I'm not too sure what
I wanna do when I leave here.
I know I should have all that
planned out by now,
have my goals set.
I know Marcus wants to be
some hot shot lawyer.
Good on him.
But me? I cannot imagine sitting
behind a desk all day long.
I wanna travel.
Get as far away as possible.
SARAH: Hey, I've been looking for you.
Baby, what's wrong?
LUKE: Just fuck off, alright?
LUKE: Fuck!
Oi. Steven, are you OK?
You're bleeding.
I have a tissue if you want.
Hey, are you gonna be OK?
STEVEN: Yeah. I'll be OK.
MAN ON LOUDSPEAKER:
Could Simona Carboni please come to
the science lab, thanks?
Simona Carboni to the science lab.
Thank you.
MARCUS: Is it true?!
Marcus. Come on, I didn't...
Hey, are you gonna be OK?
Sometimes, you know...
Sometimes you just get so wrapped up
in your own problems that...
...you just don't notice anybody else.
You know?
You know, people talk
about reincarnation and heaven
and what happens when you die
and hell and all that bullshit.
I mean, it just...
none of it makes sense, you know?
It's just... people
are scared of dying.
Well, I'm not.
Once you're dead, you're dead.
It's as simple as that.
I think the last time I had
a real conversation with her
was... Year 2 or something.
That was 10 years ago.
Yeah, um...
Well, she was my friend, and...
...I'm gonna miss her.
Don't really have
anything more to say
about it than that.
She was in my brother's music class.
I guess... all I can really say is...
...she's lucky.
Really...
...really lucky.
I mean, I... I knew her.
And she seemed like
a happy enough person.
You know, not once,
not fucking once
did she ask for help
or indicate in any way
that she was going to top herself.
You know, maybe if she did
then I could've helped.
I don't know.
She just... she never...
My, um, sister has this little boy,
um, baby boy, but -
well, he's not really
a baby anymore, I guess -
but he's just learning to talk
and, um, and do animal noises.
And she sent me a video
that she'd taken on her camera
the other day,
and, um, she's got him with his face
painted like a little tiger
and she's saying,
"Oscar, do the tiger noise."
And, um... and his...
...his little face goes, "Miaow!"
With his little lips, and, um...
Yeah, and it's so cute.
The whole camera's shaking
'cause she's laughing so much.
Um... it's just so sweet.
MR DARC Y: Mate, is that you in there?
Shit. Shit.
Open the door!
If there's somebody in there,
open the door!
Open the door!
SONG: # Please don't forget me
# I'm still here
# Burnt in your memory
# You'll always see me
# Once upon a bluer sky
# I could reach so far, so high
# Now that all seems like a dream
# I will never see
# Broken wings
# Couldn't fly
# Destiny seems so far
# There's no more dreaming
# Please don't forget me
# I'm still here
# Burnt in your memory
# You'll always see me
# What's over the other side?
# Nothing, just a light
# My troubles burn, they never stop
# I want these clouds behind me
# I wish upon
# Another dream
# Of a way up high with bluer skies
# But no-one knows
# Beyond that door
I've no idea
# No, none at all
# But I'll take the chance
to spite you all
# I'll never know
# What I left behind me
# Nothing left up in the sky
# Only what's left in your mind
# Look at what I've come to be
# Just a memory
# Please don't forget me
# I'm still here
# Burnt in your memory
# You'll always see me. #
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org