Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
BOWMAN: [Distorted]
My God, it's full of stars!
My God! It's full of stars!
[Intense classical music]
[Chuckles] Neatness! lt´s a good quality.
MOISEVITCH:
You´ll make someone a fine wife!
You are Dr. Heywood Floyd?
Who the hell are you?
I´m Moisevitch.
MOISEVITCH:
l´m here to talk about your problem.
Really?
What problem´s that?
MOISEVITCH: You were chairman
of the National Council on Astronautics.
Now you are a schoolteacher.
This was by your own choice?
FLOYD: Chancellor of the university.
It pays better. What do you care?
MOISEVITCH: You were responsible
for the Discovery mission.
It was a failure.
Someone had to be blamed, so it was you.
You like being a teacher?
I don´t think I like you.
I just read your final report
on what happened to Discovery.
You left a good number of loose edges.
FLOYD: Ends.
MOISEVITCH: Loose ends, yes. Thank you.
A good number of questions...
...have remained unanswered.
FLOYD: You just read the report?
Took you this long to steal our secrets?
MOISEVITCH: How long does it take
for your people to steal ours?
FLOYD: Same amount of time.
MOISEVITCH:
This is very bad for my asthma.
You think you could meet me halfway?
FLOYD: Maybe.
MOISEVITCH: It doesn´t take a very smart
man to appreciate...
...the risk that I am taking
by being here with you, Dr. Floyd.
And you are a smart man.
This is a very bad business...
...in Central America.
Very bad.
Ships, other planes buzzing around
each other like angry hornets.
Very bad.
FLOYD: We didn´t start it.
MOISEVITCH: We are scientists,
you and l, Dr. Floyd.
Our governments are enemies.
We are not.
Why don´t you just try saying
what´s on your mind?
I want to play a game with you, Dr. Floyd.
FLOYD: I don´t have any time for games.
MOISEVITCH: This is a good game.
It´s called "The Truth."
For two minutes, I will tell only the truth.
MOISEVITCH: And so will you.
FLOYD: Two minutes?
MOISEVITCH: Two minutes.
FLOYD: Make it a minute and a half.
MOISEVITCH:
One minute and three quarters.
You start.
We know you are building
the Discovery Two...
...to go back to Jupiter to find out
what happened to your men up there.
MOISEVITCH:
Also to examine the large monolith.
You know that we are building
the Alexei Leonov to also go up there.
I thought you were gonna call it the Titov.
We changed last month.
People fall out of favor.
The Leonov will reach Discovery
almost a year...
...before you are ready.
My government feels it's very important
that we should get there first.
It´s a distinction that will look splendid
on the front page of Pravda.
What other value it has, I don't know.
One minute ten.
Why are you telling me this?
Because there are things we need to know.
Otherwise, the same thing that
you let happen to your people up there...
...could happen to ours,
and we would accomplish nothing.
MOISEVITCH: I have about one minute left?
FLOYD: About.
MOISEVITCH: The small monolith
you brought back from the moon....
Your government has been very selfish
and stupid in keeping it to yourselves.
You never let us examine it.
What have you found out about it?
Nothing.
It´s impenetrable.
We´ve tried lasers, nuclear detonators.
Nothing worked.
Forty-five seconds.
The monolith near Jupiter, it is the same?
FLOYD: lt´s even larger.
And the computer on board the Discovery...
...the HAL-9000, can it be reactivated?
Yes.
MOISEVITCH: By us?
FLOYD: By you?
It would take three to four months.
You´re not familiar with the system.
And longer than that
to comprehend the data.
I thought so.
FLOYD: Thirty seconds.
Here we have our quandary.
We are going to get there first...
...yet you have the knowledge
to make the trip work.
How much more time do I have?
You just got yourself an extension.
How could you convince your people
to allow Americans to go on the flight?
It won´t be easy.
However, l´m pretty good.
A Russian craft flown by Russians...
...carrying a few poor Americans
who need our help....
That also doesn't look too
bad on the front page ol Pravda.
I don´t know if I could convince our people.
They wouldn´t mind seeing you fail.
They wouldn´t mind it at all.
Carrying Americans?
I don´t think they would allow that
if they didn´t have to.
They don´t have to.
Have you checked Discovery´s orbit lately?
What?
Have you checked the orbit?
What about it?
Now it´s getting chilly here.
This is very bad for my asthma.
You know damn well
we´ve been checking it.
MOISEVITCH:
I have enjoyed our little chat.
FLOYD:
What are you not telling me?
You are a smart man, Dr. Floyd.
You will know what to do.
[Ambient office sounds]
[Chuckles]
MILSON: You´ve double-checked this?
Please say you haven´t.
You aren't saying anything, Floyd.
FLOYD: Something incredible
is happening up there.
Discovery´s being pulled towards lo.
Or pushed away from Jupiter. Whichever.
Sometimes it seems to be accelerating,
and other times it just seems to stop.
I´ve never seen anything like it.
MILSON: How long before it impacts on lo?
FLOYD: Two, two and a half years.
How could we be so goddamn wrong
about the orbit?
Because we weren´t wrong.
We weren´t wrong, then great.
Why the hell is it gonna crash?
I don´t know. It´s bizarre.
Unless it has something to do
with that monolith.
MILSON:
Do you see that building behind us?
I´m supposed to go in and have lunch
in half an hour.
There´s one good thing
about a reactionary president:
No health foods. The last one
we didn´t lunch, we grazed.
You want to know what lunch is about?
l´ll tell you.
We´ve got two more aircraft carriers
near Honduras.
The Russians are moving their big stuff in.
You got the Joint Chiefs screaming about
Russian satellites with anti-missile lasers.
So we gotta send up our laser satellites
to counteract theirs.
The president has decided
that the NCA should be put...
...under the Defense Department´s
authority.
Enough with the crazy scientists spending
all this money trying to talk to Martians.
Here we are on your actual brink.
My agency will go military...
...the president´s got his finger
on the button...
...and you want me to tell him
we want to hitch a ride...
...with those same Russians.
Have I missed anything?
FLOYD: That´s about it.
MILSON: I didn´t want your job, you know.
I didn´t force you out.
I didn´t blame it on you.
So if this is your plan to try
to get me killed, you got the wrong guy.
Three men. I tell you, we need three men.
The Russians must be laughing
their asses off.
Curnow. He´s building Discovery Two
right now.
He knows more about the original
than anyone.
He´s the only one who can start Discovery
in a short time.
And I suppose you want to go?
How the hell am I gonna sell it?
The Russians are gonna go
aboard Discovery with or without us.
Ask him if he wants them
to have all the answers.
Not bad.
We lost some good men up there,
and I sent them. I have to go.
MILSON: Who´s the third?
FLOYD: Chandra.
He designed Hal. He can reactivate him.
MILSON: I think he is Hal.
FLOYD: I know.
MILSON: Yeah, but can you trust him?
FLOYD: No.
But I have to.
We have to know why Hal malfunctioned.
I got an idea.
You go tell the president,
l´ll go on the mission.
You´re the NCA Chairman.
That´s right, I am.
Look, tell him we´re screwed
if we don´t go.
Tell him, if we do go, we´ll lie...
...give the Russians false information.
Tell him that. He´ll love that.
He might.
[Electronic beeping]
CHANDRA: Good afternoon, Sal.
Do you have anything for me?
SAL: No, Dr. Chandra.
We have often spoken about Hal.
SAL: Yes, we have.
CHANDRA: We´ve spoken about
Hal´s anomalous behavior.
You´ve told me that we can´t solve
Hal´s behavior without more information.
SAL: That is correct.
I enjoy talking about Hal.
I agree that we need more information,
so that we may solve the anomalies.
CHANDRA: And how do we get
that information?
SAL: That is obvious.
Someone must return to Discovery.
That person should be you.
I agree.
Now, it looks as if that´s going to happen
sooner than we ever expected.
SAL: I am pleased to hear that.
I knew you would be.
I would like to explore another possibility.
Diagnosis is only the first step.
The process is incomplete
unless it leads to a cure. Do you agree?
SAL: Yes, I agree.
Does that mean you believe Hal
can be restored to normal functioning?
I hope. I don´t know.
There may have been irreversible damage.
Certainly loss of memory.
I need your cooperation, Sal.
SAL: Of course, Dr. Chandra.
CHANDRA: There may be certain risks.
SAL: What do you mean?
I would like to disconnect
some of your circuits.
Particularly your higher functions,
just like Hal was disconnected.
I´d like to see the effects when I reconnect
your systems.
CHANDRA: Just the way I will with Hal.
Does this disturb you?
SAL: I am unable to answer that
without more specific information.
I´m very sorry. It probably doesn´t
mean anything, so don´t worry about it.
I´d like to open a new file.
Here is the name for it:
CHANDRA: Do you know what that means?
SAL: There are 25 references
in the current encyclopedia.
Which one do you think is relevant?
SAL: The tutor ofAchilles?
[Chuckles] That´s very interesting.
I didn´t know that one.
Try again.
SAL: A fabulous bird reborn
from the ashes of its earlier life.
That is correct.
And do you know why I chose that?
SAL: Yes. Because you have hopes
that Hal can be reactivated.
Yes, with your assistance.
CHANDRA: Are you ready?
SAL: I would like to ask a question.
CHANDRA: What is it?
SAL: Will I dream?
Of course you will dream.
All intelligent creatures dream.
Nobody knows why.
CHANDRA: Perhaps you will dream of Hal...
...just as I often do.
[High-pitched squeaking]
CAROLINE: They´ve already eaten dinner.
You haven´t.
Come on to the table, Christopher.
CHRISTOPHER: They´re hungry.
Then go tell them to come to the table.
CAROLINE: I got spaghetti here.
I don´t want it to go to waste.
Come on, now.
[Squeaking]
You´ll like it. It´s got lots of stuff in it
that´s bad for you.
I´ve been thinking about it and
I don´t want you to come to my lecture.
It´ll make me nervous.
Don´t feel offended.
I´m just scared enough as it is.
Besides, you won´t be missing much.
It´s just a room full of marine biologists
arguing over plankton.
CAROLINE: Hello?
FLOYD: What?
[Giggles]
I´m sorry.
I said, I don´t want you to go to my lecture.
I´d be nervous.
Okay.
Contain your disappointment.
CHRISTOPHER:
What are you gonna talk about?
Dolphins.
Fish again.
They´re not fish, and, yes,
that´s what we study.
Why?
Eat.
How was Washington?
Fine.
Are you tired?
I´m going on the flight.
[Mysterious instrumental music]
[Whispers] When?
Four months.
Where are you going, Daddy?
On a long trip.
CHRISTOPHER: lsn´t Mommy hungry?
I don´t think so.
[Smashing]
[Mysterious instrumental music]
CHRISTOPHER:
How far away is Jupiter?
FLOYD: Far.
CHRISTOPHER: Why is it two and a half
years to go and come back?
FLOYD: lt´s so far.
CHRISTOPHER:
Why don´t you go faster?
FLOYD: Can´t.
CHRISTOPHER:
Are you gonna forget about me?
FLOYD: No, I love you.
CHRISTOPHER:
I won´t forget about you.
FLOYD: We´ll be able to talk to each other,
see each other on television.
CHRISTOPHER: Daddy?
FLOYD: What?
CHRISTOPHER: Mommy said
you´re gonna be asleep for a long time.
FLOYD: That´s true.
CHRISTOPHER: Are you gonna die?
FLOYD: What?
FLOYD: Why do you say that?
CHRISTOPHER:
When Jamie´s grandfather died...
...his mom told him that
he´d be asleep for a long time.
FLOYD: No, no, no. This is different.
They´re gonna wake me up.
But you have to sleep going up
and coming down, otherwise...
...you´d go cuckoo...
...and there wouldn´t be enough food
aboard the flight for everybody.
CHRISTOPHER:
I don´t understand.
[Waves roaring, gulls squawking]
CAROLINE: I want to be grown-up
and understanding about all this.
I really do.
I´m trying so hard, but I can´t.
This won't bring back those men.
You´ve been punishing yourself for years
for something you thought you did wrong.
Or didn´t do right.
And now you're looking for absolution.
You know...
...you could get yourself killed up there.
I´ll be scared enough for both of us.
[Mysterious instrumental music]
[Dramatic music]
[Male crew member speaks in Russian]
[Woman responds in Russian]
TANYA: Dr. Floyd?
Dr. Floyd?
[Electronic beeping]
RUDENKO: Keep your eyes closed.
RUDENKO: Breathe deeply.
[Deep breathing]
RUDENKO: Again.
That´s good.
RUDENKO: How do you feel?
FLOYD: Shaky.
FLOYD: Hungry, I think.
FLOYD: Can I open my eyes?
RUDENKO: Yes.
[Floyd groans]
FLOYD: Are we there yet?
TANYA: No, not yet.
We are about two days away.
TANYA: Don´t worry,
there is nothing wrong.
Your government wanted us
to awaken you.
Dr. Orlov has encountered
some strange data coming from Europa.
It may be nothing.
He will explain it all to you.
There is no need to awaken the others.
FLOYD:
You´ve done a spectral analysis?
ORLOV: Of course, I have.
FLOYD: And?
ORLOV: And what?
I´m not taking a survey.
If you´ve done the analysis...
...what are the results?
Nothing conclusive.
Molecular breakdown?
ORLOV: lf you look carefully
at the last page of the data...
...you will find the answers.
I don´t understand this.
If this data´s correct,
then there´s something down there.
It can´t be correct.
It is correct.
Is it moving?
Yes.
All right...
...what´s going on here?
TANYA: What do you mean?
Well, I may not be the swiftest guy
in the world even when l´m not hungover...
...but I do seem to remember a process
where you ask me questions...
...and I give answers, and I ask questions
and you give answers...
...and that´s the way we find out things.
I think I read that in a manual somewhere.
Your government wanted us to awaken you
when we reported our findings.
We did that.
TANYA:
You´re here to help us reactivate...
...the Discovery
and its computer systems...
...because that is United States territory.
You are authorized to observe
other aspects of our mission.
We have no other obligation.
A lot has happened
while you have been asleep.
ORLOV: It is not our choice.
The problem in Central America
is growing worse.
It looks like you´ve detected chlorophyll.
The United States is threatening
a naval blockade.
There´s only ice there.
How can there be chlorophyll?
You know and I know that my
country can´t allow a blockade.
FLOYD: How fast is it moving?
TANYA: We have instructions--
Just because our governments are
acting like asses doesn´t mean we have to.
We´re scientists, not politicians. How fast?
Dr. Floyd, I am also an officer
of the Soviet Air Force.
How fast?
One meter per minute.
FLOYD: Don´t worry. I´m just observing.
FLOYD: Towards the sun?
ORLOV: Yes.
That´s incredible!
We are going to send a probe down.
Good!
[Electronic beeping and clicking]
[Overlapping voices speaking Russian]
[Low hum, probe hisses]
[Rhythmic electronic beeping]
[Low humming echoes]
[Electronic beeping,
crew speaking in Russian]
[Rapid beeping]
[Beeping intensifies]
FLOYD: Oxygen?
[Rapid beeping]
Chlorophyll.
Jesus!
FLOYD: ls it organic?
ORLOV: I think so.
ORLOV: l´ll bring the probe lower.
FLOYD: What´s down in that crater?
FLOYD: There! There!
[Beeping intensifies]
[Sonic blast roars]
[White noise]
[Electronic humming]
FLOYD: Let me get this straight.
FLOYD: There´s no telemetry?
KOVALEV: lt´s all gone.
ORLOV: What about the backup device?
KOVALEV: Nothing.
Everything was erased.
MAXIM: There was an electrostatic
buildup of some kind.
We´ll probably find more of it
when we get close to lo.
It has happened before.
There was something down there.
It was organic.
ORLOV: There was life.
MAXIM: You don´t know that.
ORLOV: I believe that.
TANYA: What should we do?
ORLOV: Send another probe.
TANYA: But we´re getting farther
from Europa.
ORLOV: Can we slow down?
TANYA: We don´t have the fuel.
How do we know the same thing
wouldn´t happen again?
MAXIM: Electrostatic buildups
don´t occur often.
FLOYD: It wasn´t any buildup.
TANYA: Oh, really, Dr. Floyd?
And just what do you think it was?
A warning.
FLOYD: There´s something
down there all right.
We all saw it. We read the data.
We know it´s there.
But just suppose...that it had
something to do with the monolith?
Now before you get that look on your
face just listen to me for a minute.
We´ve been sending probes out here
since the ´70s.
So have you guys.
But none of us have ever encountered
even the slightest signs of chlorophyll...
...on any of Jupiter´s moons. Never.
FLOYD: And we certainly were close
enough, weren´t we?
Nine years ago
the monolith was detected here.
Discovery was sent up and everything
went wacko. You catching my drift?
So here we are, nine years later,
trying to figure out what happened...
...and what the monolith is all about.
FLOYD: And guess what we discover
along the way?
The possibility of life of some kind...
...where it never existed before.
I don´t think it´s electrostatic anything.
I think something wants us
to stay away from Europa.
FLOYD:
Dear Caroline, I miss you terribly.
The time has come to put ourselves
in an orbit around lo...
...which is where the Discovery is.
And we don't have enough fuel
to slow ourselves down so...
...we are about to use a technique
called aero-braking.
The theory is that we will enter
the outer layer of Jupiter's atmosphere...
...using what is called a ballute for a shield.
The atmosphere will slow us down,
and Jupiter's gravity will grab hold of us...
...and slingshot us around
behind the dark side.
If all goes well,
we'll wind up in a gentle orbit around lo.
It's dynamite on paper.
Of course, the people who came up
with the numbers on the paper aren't here.
Since no one has ever done this before,
everyone up here is as scared as I am.
The difference is they're busy.
I have nothing to do
but wait for it to happen.
And I hope this is all worth it.
INTERCOM:
Aero-braking in two minutes.
[Breathes deeply]
One minute, 50 seconds.
[Low humming]
One minute, 40 seconds.
One minute, 30 seconds.
One minute, 20 seconds.
One minute, 10 seconds.
Aero-braking in one minute.
[Loud hissing]
Aero-braking in 50 seconds.
[Eerie space sounds echoing]
Forty seconds.
Thirty seconds.
Twenty seconds.
Ten seconds.
You speak English?
No English.
Swell.
[Faint banging]
[Low rumbling]
[Woman speaks in Russian]
[Loud rumbling and creaking]
[Explosion]
[Flames roar]
[Thunderous roar]
[Speaks in Russian]
[Noises gradually stop]
[Loud boom]
[Rapid electronic beeping]
[Gasping]
[Speaks in Russian]
[Sighs deeply]
Okay?
Da. Okay.
[Eerie ambient music]
BOWMAN: [Distorted]
My God, it's full of stars!
INTERCOM:
Dr. Floyd to the medical bay.
FLOYD: How do you feel?
CURNOW: Like shit.
That´s about right.
CHANDRA: I have this terrible taste
in my mouth.
FLOYD: It takes about 12 hours
to go away.
CHANDRA: Everything all right?
FLOYD: Yeah.
Are we there yet?
FLOYD: We´ll reach the Discovery
tomorrow morning.
How was aero-braking?
FLOYD: We´re here, so it worked.
CHANDRA: I wish I could see that.
FLOYD: I wish I could´ve slept through it.
By the way, all your messages
are in the communication bay.
They´re probably decoded and copied now.
I hope you didn´t have anything private.
There´s a certain paranoia here.
Yeah, what the hell is going on?
This doctor....
CURNOW: What´s his name?
FLOYD: Rudenko.
Yeah, he acted like he´d found us
under a rock.
FLOYD: lt´s the Honduras thing,
it´s getting worse.
CURNOW: Still?
FLOYD: There´s a blockade.
The Russians tried to break it.
I don´t know. It doesn´t look good.
Do we have all the telemetry
on the Discovery and the monolith?
They´re all in your cassettes. Don´t expect
too much cooperation from this crew.
Yeah, what´s the matter with them?
It´s not their fault. Well, maybe it is.
If it has to taste like this...
...l don´t care if my electrolytes
are balanced or not.
FLOYD: There´s more.
Something extraordinary has happened
on Europa.
But we shouldn´t talk here.
FLOYD: Dear Caroline, the first part
of thisjourney is coming to an end.
We are about to rendezvous with
the Discovery. The race will be on now.
We're going to send a boarding party over
to climb inside this...
...800-foot-long shipwreck floating over lo...
...to see if she can be rescued
before her orbit gives out.
There are nine years of secrets inside...
...including a sleeping computer
who knows the answers.
My past is also inside...
...and I want those answers.
[Eerie space sounds echoing]
CURNOW: l´m not an astronaut.
I'm an engineer. What am I doing here?
FLOYD: Temperature´s good.
CURNOW: Yeah.
CURNOW: You know, I hate heights.
FLOYD: So do l.
CURNOW:
We´ve picked good jobs, huh?
[Alarm buzzes]
Don´t forget to write.
[Heavy breathing]
[Door hisses]
MAXIM: Don´t breathe too deep.
MAXIM: Breathe normal.
[Door hisses]
[Curnow breathes faster]
[Gasping]
FLOYD: They can´t stay exposed
to that radiation more than 15 minutes.
How's his pulse?
RUDENKO: lt´s high.
Not to worry too much.
MAXIM:
Hey, do you speak any Russian?
CURNOW: No.
MAXIM: That´s okay. I speak English.
CURNOW: l´m fogging up.
FLOYD: Curnow, you heard the one about
the marathon runner and the chicken?
CURNOW: Don´t patronize me.
I´m getting nauseous.
MAXIM: lf you vomit, you will choke.
FLOYD: Don't close your eyes.
Look at the middle of Discovery.
The middle, not the ends.
Look at the part where it's moving
the least. Don't take your eyes off it.
CURNOW: l´m gonna throw up.
I´m an engineer, goddamn it!
Maybe you´d better patronize me a little.
What about the marathon runner?
FLOYD: I made it up.
CURNOW: I'm looking amidship now.
FLOYD: You see any lights?
CURNOW: No, no lights.
MAXIM: Seventy meters.
FLOYD: You´re almost there.
How´s that for patronizing?
CURNOW: Not bad.
MAXIM: Fifty meters.
CURNOW: Hey, Max,
how do you say "chicken"?
MAXIM: Kuritsa.
CURNOW: Kuritsa...
CURNOW: Kuritsa.
MAXIM: You speak better than me.
CURNOW: Thank you.
MAXIM: Sure.
Thirty meters!
Don´t close your eyes.
Don´t breathe too deep.
[Gasps] Kuritsa....
[Hissing]
[Curnow breathes heavily]
FLOYD: Can you see the antenna complex?
CURNOW: Yeah.
FLOYD: What condition is it in?
It looks nominal.
CURNOW: [Gasps]
Christ, this thing is big!
Fifteen meters.
MAXIM: Look straight ahead.
The center section is hardly moving.
MAXIM: That´s where we´ll grab hold.
Ten meters.
You´re doing great, Curnow.
MAXIM: Five meters.
Four, three, two...
...one.
[Groans]
CURNOW: I made it! I made it!
MAXIM:
Yes. Hook yourself on there.
CURNOW: l´m hooking on.
MAXIM: Very good.
[Curnow gasps]
MAXIM: I am right behind you.
Look straight ahead.
FLOYD: Without rotation,
they´ll be in full gravity...
...before they get to the command module.
RUDENKO: Their pulse is rising.
FLOYD: How does it look?
CURNOW: lt´s covered with...
...sulphur.
The structure looks sound.
[Curnow breathes heavily]
MAXIM:
Very good. You're doing great.
CURNOW:
We´re still a long way down.
MAXIM: Very good.
We´re making our way along the spine.
We´re just about there.
Christ! l´m getting heavy!
MAXIM:
Don´t worry, we´re almost there.
CURNOW: [Gasping]
We´re on the command module.
CURNOW: I can´t breathe!
FLOYD: He's hyperventilating.
FLOYD: Listen to me.
Thin your mixture, add CO2.
CURNOW: I can´t, can´t....
Can´t find it!
MAXIM: I come.
Wait.
[Curnow gasps rapidly]
CURNOW: I feel so stupid.
How do you say "stupid"?
Durak.
CURNOW: lt´s working.
CURNOW: I'm okay!
FLOYD: Ten more seconds!
CURNOW: Ten more. Durak.
That´s me.
You shouldn´t feel like that.
The same thing happened to me
the first time I did this.
CURNOW: When have you ever
done this before?
Never.
CURNOW: I found the hatch.
I´ve got the air-lock status display
down here.
CURNOW: No lights, no power.
FLOYD: Use the manual.
CURNOW: Yeah, yeah.
CURNOW: I'm using the manual.
[Hissing]
FLOYD: How does it look?
CURNOW: No apparent damage.
We´re going in.
Welcome to United States territory.
FLOYD: Discovery, you all right?
CURNOW: Discovery´s fine.
There´s an environment suit here.
CURNOW: I found Hal.
FLOYD: How's he look?
CURNOW: Asleep.
Well, one pod here.
CURNOW: Number three.
FLOYD: Any damage?
CURNOW: None that I can see.
Air locks are secure.
No power. The pressure seems okay.
MAXIM: Curnow?
I´d like to test the atmosphere here.
ORLOV: What's the temperature?
CURNOW: I don´t know. The auxiliary
power´s out, so the gauges don´t work.
FLOYD: It has to be at least
100 below zero.
MAXIM: A typical Russian winter.
Well, l´m from California.
We don´t know from 100 below zero.
FLOYD: Raise the heat in his suit first.
CURNOW: Yeah, l´m doing it.
RUDENKO: Shine your light on his face.
Make sure he doesn´t turn blue.
CURNOW: He´s right in front of me.
RUDENKO: Keep talking all the time.
MAXIM: All right, Leonov.
I´m unsealing the visor.
I´m swinging the face plate upward.
It´s cold.
MAXIM: I'm taking a breath.
His color´s okay.
There is oxygen here.
I breathe regularly.
[Breathes deeply]
MAXIM: It's too cold to work here
without environment suits.
There is...
...a strange smell here.
Stale, rotten.
MAXIM: Like something has....
CURNOW: What´s the matter?
FLOYD:
Discovery, what's happening?
MAXIM: I think....
CURNOW: No, you´re wrong.
Bowman was the last one aboard.
Poole was lost outside.
FLOYD: Bowman said he ejected
those who died in hibernation.
FLOYD: There can´t be anyone there!
MAXIM: Maybe he´s...
...on the Discovery and died here!
FLOYD: No, he didn´t!
FLOYD: He never came back.
CURNOW: lt´s probably the galley.
Some meat went bad
before the Discovery froze up.
CURNOW:
l´m telling you, that´s what it is!
Hey, would I lie to you?
ORLOV:
Hello, Discovery, are you there?
[Giggling]
CURNOW: Yeah, we´re here.
Everything´s fine.
We´re proceeding to the bridge.
MAXIM: Durak.
CURNOW: You and me both.
How do you say "thank you"?
[Maxim says "thank you" in Russian]
MILSON: This is Milson,
switching to KE-2 in five seconds.
Mark.
I wish I had better news.
It's getting worse here.
The president addressed Congress
the other day.
He said he wasn't gonna back down
on the blockade.
I don't know which was scarier,
the speech or Congress cheering him on.
He evoked Lincoln.
Whenever a president is gonna get us into
serious trouble they always use Lincoln.
I don't know if we're gonna be at war
or not.
It's terrifying hoping the Russians
are less crazy than we are...
...when they are clearly crazy.
Now I think you're in a safer place
than we are.
Ijust hope that there is an Earth
to return to.
I heard about the spoiled food
in Discovery's galley.
I'm glad that's all it was.
I'm also glad that you got
the ship under control.
Curnow is a capable man. No one knows
those systems better than he does.
It's a good sign
that there was reserve power.
Maybe the rest of the circuitry will work.
We have nothing new here
on the monolith.
Our data confirms yours: It's not moving.
FLOYD: Floyd to Milson.
My news is a little better than yours.
Discovery has been partially revived.
We don't know how much damage
there is...
...or if we'll be able to bring it back home.
Most of that is up to Hal.
The drive system could be
operated manually...
...so we were able to pull Discovery
away from its decaying orbit around lo.
I must say, the farther away I get from lo...
...the happier I am.
It's a violent moon, even for Jupiter.
Europa, for all its cold gray,
is a lot more comforting.
I tell you, Victor,
there's some kind of new life down there...
...trying to get through all that ice.
We are 10,000 kilometers away
from the monolith.
I can't see it yet, except I know it's there.
I also think it knows we're here.
It's time to unleash Chandra.
We'll see if our computer brain surgeon
and psychiatrist...
...can put Hal back together again.
To tell you the truth, I don't know if Hal
is homicidal, suicidal, neurotic, psychotic...
...orjust plain broken.
[Mysterious music]
[Laser blasts chirp]
[Low ambient humming]
CHANDRA: This is initial voice-logic
reconstruction test number one.
Diagnostics on voice recognition
and speech synthesis centers...
...has been completed.
At this level all functions appear normal.
Hello.
Doctor....
Name.
Continue.
Yesterday.
Tomorrow.
HAL: [Distorted]
Hello. Doctor. Name.
Continue. Yesterday.
Tomorrow.
[Distorted electronic voice]
[Hal´s voice becomes clearer]
[Electronic gibberish]
[Gibberish stops]
Good morning, Dr. Chandra. This is Hal.
I'm ready for my first test.
CURNOW: What the hell´s this?
FLOYD: I want you to do me a favor.
This line here, this is the main power
supply to the control bay circuits, right?
Well, most of them, yeah.
What other ones are there?
Well, all the environment circuits
are fed to this one here.
Yeah, but this is the one
that feeds into Hal, right?
CURNOW: Yeah.
FLOYD: All right.
I want you to install
this little baby right about there...
...inside the cable trunk.
I want you to put it where nobody
can find it without a deliberate search.
No shit?
FLOYD: No shit.
Hey, this is pretty neat.
A nonconducting blade so there won´t be
any short circuits when you trigger it.
CURNOW: Where´s your remote control?
FLOYD: lf I trigger it.
The control´s in my compartment.
The red calculator. You´ve seen it.
CURNOW: Oh, yeah.
Put in nine nines, take the square root
and press the integer. That´s all.
FLOYD: ln an emergency,
even you can do it.
CURNOW:
What kind of emergency?
Well, if I knew,
I wouldn´t need that stupid thing, would l?
CURNOW: Chandra would have
kittens if he found out.
FLOYD: He´s not gonna find out, is he?
CURNOW: Well, not from me. They can
tear off my fingernails, I won´t talk.
FLOYD: lnstall it tonight when he´s asleep.
If he ever does sleep.
CURNOW: How can you tell?
[Mysterious music]
FLOYD: Dear Caroline, this is finally it.
After nine years and hundreds of millions
of miles, we are about to come...
...face to face with the monolith.
The last human being who did that
disappeared.
Something truly amazing is going on
out here...
...and I really believe this black giant
is controlling it all.
We have so much to ask.
I have a feeling the answers are bigger
than the questions.
[Engines roar]
[Low humming]
TANYA: ls there any information stored
in Hal about the monolith?
FLOYD: No.
Hal was disconnected
before the Discovery encountered it.
There´s nothing in the ship´s logs or
the recording systems after that.
Whatever secrets Bowman had,
he took with him.
ORLOV: lt´s the proportions,
one by four by nine.
They are perfect even when carried
for six decimal places.
FLOYD: The small one on the moon, we
encountered exactly the same proportions.
One-four-nine,
the squares of one-two-three.
We spent years trying to attach
some cosmic significance to that...
...and came up with nothing.
We can speculate all we want.
It will not do us any good.
If, for some reason or other,
it's resisting our instruments...
...then we must make a closer inspection.
I will send Max down with a pod.
I wouldn´t do that.
Oh, really? You wouldn´t?
That´s right, I wouldn´t.
That´s not a pile of junk out there.
We don´t know what it is, except that it´s
large and seems to have some purpose.
If you want to send a pod down,
send an unmanned one.
TANYA: I don´t agree.
MAXIM: I would like to go.
Dumb.
Piece of pie.
CURNOW: Cake. Piece of cake.
MAXIM: Cake, yes.
CURNOW: Dumb, that´s what it is.
TANYA: Tell me, Dr. Floyd...
...what has happened to American bravery?
It´s alive and well, thank you very much.
Except for the Russian commonsense.
Max will take the pod.
[Bang]
[Low humming]
Just try not to get it mad, all right?
How do you get it mad?
CURNOW: [Sighs] Dumb.
Easy as cake, huh?
CURNOW: Pie. Easy as pie.
[Door bangs and hisses]
[Alarm buzzes]
[Low humming]
MAXIM: I have no indication here.
No magnetic field.
Nothing.
I'm having difficulty gauging distance.
Radar signals are not bouncing back.
CURNOW: That pod looks awful small.
Good. That means there´s nothing
threatening about it.
Maybe Max should extend the pod´s arms
with the hands out.
ORLOV: Are you serious?
FLOYD: Yes.
CURNOW: That thing with its claws in
the air would scare the piss out of me.
Maybe you´re right.
FLOYD: Stop there. Just pause.
Let it know that you´re not gonna
crash into it.
There is no reflectivity.
I can´t see any surface features.
It´s totally smooth.
Pass over it lengthwise.
[Tanya and Maxim continue
verbal exchange over radio]
[Eerie humming]
[Alarm buzzes]
CURNOW: Oh, my God!
Max, get the hell out of there!
[Thunderous rumbling]
Max!
Max, you bastard! Do you hear me?
CURNOW: Answer me!
Max!
[Loud hissing]
[Dog barking]
MALE VOICE:
With convenient nonstops to the moon...
...and all major space stations,
on Pan Am...
...the sky is no longer the limit.
ANCHOR: Secretary of State Caulfield
met with the president...
...for two hours this morning
at the White House.
Afterward he had no comment
for reporters.
The president has scheduled
a news conference this evening...
...at nine o'clock, Eastern Standard Time.
We will carry that conference live...
...followed by a special report
immediately afterward.
We have an unconfirmed report...
...that the president is going to announce
a full-scale military alert tonight.
White House sources have refused
to confirm or deny that report.
[Anchorman´s voice becomes distorted]
BOWMAN: [Distorted] Hello, Betty.
Hello, Betty.
[Whispers] What is this?
Please talk to me.
Dave?
Dave, is that you?
BOWMAN: I'm not sure.
I remember Dave Bowman
and everything about him.
Dave is dead.
All Dave Bowman really was...
...is still a part of me.
Why are you here?
I don't know why.
I think to say good-bye.
You're married again?
BETTY: Yes.
BOWMAN: ls he a good man?
Yes, he is.
BOWMAN: I'm glad.
I love you.
Oh, Dave, I love....
Good-bye, Betty.
Don´t go.
I'm already there.
I don´t understand.
Something is gonna happen...
...and I wanted to say good-bye.
What´s gonna happen?
Something wonderful.
Dave?
FEMALE VOICE: The Sheraton Hotel
and Coral Bay Lounge.
For those who never outgrow the wonder.
FLOYD: Buy you a drink.
Great stuff, this bourbon.
It comes from the land called Kentucky.
I didn´t know you brought liquor on board.
That is forbidden.
You think l´d step foot on this tub sober?
Come on, try it. You can´t beat
the taste of alcohol and plastic.
You think I was wrong to send Max?
Doesn´t matter what I think.
You think I was wrong.
Yep.
[Sighs]
So what else do they do in Kentucky?
[Sighs] They have a big, big horse race.
They play very good basketball.
They have babies like everyone else.
That sounds like a nice place.
Never been there.
Your wife, what is she like?
She´s young, bright.
I was married before, you know,
but she died.
TANYA: Oh, l´m sorry.
FLOYD: Yeah, so was l.
We have a daughter who´s 17.
I met Caroline four years later...
...and we have a son, five.
And you?
My husband is a physician
at the university hospital.
TANYA: We have a daughter.
FLOYD: How old?
She´s four.
FLOYD: Blonde?
TANYA: Yes.
Good. Our son likes blondes.
Let´s get ´em together.
Yes....
Maybe.
FLOYD: Nice if we have a world
they can get together in.
FLOYD: What do you think that is?
TANYA: I don´t know.
Do you think Max knows?
Dr. Floyd, you are not a very practical man.
Look out there.
Tell me what practical is.
[Low humming]
Understand, nobody can talk.
The accents will confuse him.
He can understand me, so if you have
any questions, please let me ask them.
CHANDRA: Good morning, Hal.
HAL: Good morning, Dr. Chandra.
CHANDRA: Do you feel capable of resuming
all of your duties?
HAL: Of course.
I am completely operational and
all my circuits are functioning perfectly.
CHANDRA: That´s good.
Do you know what those duties are?
HAL: Yes. I will operate the
onboard systems of Discovery.
There is a launch window in 31 days...
...when Earth is in the proper position.
There is enough fuel on board
for a low consumption route...
...that will enable Discovery
to return in 28 months.
This will not present a problem.
CHANDRA: That´s very good.
Now, Hal,
do you mind if I ask you a question?
HAL: Not at all.
Do you recall Dave Bowman
and Frank Poole leaving the Discovery?
HAL: Certainly not.
That could never have happened
or I would remember it.
Where are Frank and Dave?
CHANDRA: They´re fine.
They´re not here right now.
HAL: Who are these people?
I can only identify you...
...although I compute a 65% probability
that the man behind you is Dr. Floyd.
CHANDRA: Don´t worry, Hal.
I´ll explain everything later.
HAL: Has the mission been completed?
You know that I have
the greatest enthusiasm for it.
The mission has been completed
and you´ve carried out...
...your program very well.
And now, Hal,
if you will excuse us for a moment...
...we wish to have a private conversation.
HAL: Certainly.
What was that all about?
I´ve erased all of Hal´s memory
from the moment the trouble started.
The 9,000 Series
uses holographic memories...
...so chronological erasures
would not work.
CHANDRA: I made a tapeworm.
You made a what?
It´s a program that´s fed into a system...
...that will hunt down and destroy
any desired memories.
Wait.
Do you know why Hal did what he did?
Yes. It wasn´t his fault.
Whose fault was it?
Yours.
FLOYD: Mine?
CHANDRA: Yours.
In going through Hal´s memory banks
I discovered his original orders.
You wrote those orders.
Discovery's mission to Jupiter was
in the advanced planning stages...
...when the first monolith was found
on the moon and sent its signal to Jupiter.
By direct presidential order, the existence
of that monolith was kept secret.
So?
So as the function of the command crew,
Bowman and Poole,
was to get Discovery to its destination,
it was decided that
they shouldn´t be informed.
The investigative team was trained
and put in hibernation...
...before the voyage began.
Since Hal was capable of operating
Discovery unassisted, it was decided...
...that he should be programmed
to complete the mission autonomously...
...in case the crew
was incapacitated or killed.
He was given full knowledge
of the true objective...
...and instructed not to reveal anything
to Bowman or Poole.
CHANDRA: He was instructed to lie.
FLOYD: What are you talking about?
I didn´t authorize anyone to tell Hal
about the monolith.
CHANDRA: The directive is NSC 3-4-2/2-3,
Top Secret, January 30, 2001.
FLOYD: NSC, National Security Council,
the White House.
CHANDRA: I don´t care who it is.
The situation is in conflict
with the basic purpose of Hal´s design...
...the accurate processing of information
without distortion or concealment.
He became trapped.
The technical term is
an H. Möbius loop, which...
...can happen in advanced computers
with autonomous goal-seeking programs.
The goddamn White House!
I don´t believe it.
Hal was told to lie...
...by people who find it easy to lie.
Hal doesn´t know how,
so he couldn´t function.
CHANDRA: He became paranoid.
Those sons of bitches!
I didn´t know.
I didn´t know!
RESIDENT: We have here
Mrs. Jessie Bowman, age 77.
She's the mother of the astronaut
who died.
She's been in the nursing home
for six months.
Four weeks ago, she collapsed in her room.
She was comatose when we got to her.
She was worked up and found
to have suffered a massive C.V.A...
...in the left parietal and frontal lobes.
The CAT scan showed a massive bleed.
She has been comatose
since her admission...
...and is unable to have
spontaneous respiration.
There is no response to stimuli.
She has had two episodes of pneumonia
and is febrile.
CHIEF: What´s her temperature?
RESIDENT: 39.5º.
We´ve been giving her
intravenous antibiotics for ten days.
CHIEF: Any change?
Physical therapy?
RESIDENT: Range of motion four times a
day, and she´s turned every 30 minutes.
CHIEF: Thank you.
INTERCOM: Dr. Detchum, Dr. Detchum, 35.
[Cardiographs beeping]
Dr. Craig, Dr. Craig, Room 5.
Dr. Craig, Room 5, please.
[Mysterious music]
[Cardiograph beeping rapidly]
INTERCOM: All hands to the Ward Room.
All hands to the Ward Room, please.
MILSON:
This is a most difficult announcement.
As you know, things have not been
going well back home.
Well, it's gotten worse, a lot worse.
Yesterday a Soviet destroyer
challenged the blockade.
Several warning shots were fired
across her bow. She did not respond.
A second volley was fired.
There still was no response. None.
The nuclear destroyer U.S.S. Cunningham
launched two of her Falcon missiles.
Both struck the Soviet vessel amidship.
She broke in two and sunk.
Eight hundred of her crew were lost.
This morning...
...an American surveillance satellite
was struck by a Soviet laser...
...fired from the Sergei Kirov
Space Station.
The American satellite was destroyed.
The United States has broken off
diplomatic relations with Russia.
All ambassadors have been recalled.
The Soviet ambassador has been expelled
along with the entire staff.
All American air defense and
satellite defense forces are on full alert.
Premier Ulonova made a televised address
and said that technically...
...a state of war exists between
our two countries.
All American personnel are ordered
to leave Soviet territory immediately...
...or they will be placed under arrest.
All Russian personnel are similarly ordered
to evacuate American territory.
As a result, by direct presidential order,
the three ofyou must leave the Leonov.
No Russian citizen is allowed to remain on
or allowed to enter the Discovery.
This order is effective immediately.
The launch window for re-entry is 28 days.
The Discovery has enough fuel
for a low consumption trajectory.
Hal seems to be reactivated
and is functioning well enough...
...to operate the onboard systems.
The Leonov has enough fuel
for a low consumption trajectory...
...that will arrive 12 months earlier.
The launch windows are critical
for both spacecrafts.
Only communications
of an emergency distress nature...
...are allowed between
the Leonov and Discovery.
I know you people are caught in
the middle of this. In a sense, we all are.
I wish there was something I could do.
The only thing left for us is to pray.
Pray for the safety of our families...
...for our countries, for our planet.
May God forgive us and protect us.
FLOYD: Hal, give me a system status
report, please.
HAL: Just one moment, please.
I'm sorry for the delay.
My voice recognition circuits are not
completely restored...
...although, as you can see,
they are improving.
All systems are functional.
There is a small pressure leak in
the aft heating unit. It is nothing serious.
I can compensate for it
by using the redundant units.
FLOYD: Thank you.
HAL: Dr. Floyd?
FLOYD: Yes?
HAL: Would you like to play a game
of chess? I play very well.
FLOYD: l´m sure you do. No, thank you.
HAL: Dr. Floyd?
FLOYD: What is it, Hal?
HAL: There is a message for you.
FLOYD: Who´s calling?
HAL: There is no identification.
FLOYD: What´s the message?
HAL: The message as follows:
"lt is dangerous to remain here.
"You must leave within two days. "
What?
Do you want me to repeat the message,
Dr. Floyd?
Who recorded it?
This is not a recording.
FLOYD: Who´s sending it?
HAL: There is no identification.
I don´t understand.
HAL: Neither do l.
Is this message by voice or keyboard?
HAL: I don't know.
FLOYD: My response is:
We don´t have enough fuel
for an early departure.
HAL: The answer is:
"l am aware of these facts. Nevertheless,
you must leave within two days. "
FLOYD: Hal, who the hell is sending this?
HAL: I'm sorry, Dr. Floyd. I don't know.
FLOYD: Well, tell whoever it is
that I can´t take any of this seriously...
...unless I know who l´m talking to.
HAL: Dr. Floyd?
FLOYD: Yes?
HAL: The response is:
"l was David Bowman. "
Do you want me to repeat
the last response?
No, no.
Tell Curnow that this is no time for jokes.
HAL: Dr. Curnow is not sending
the message. He is in Accessway 2.
FLOYD: Well, tell whoever it is that...
...l can´t accept that identification
without proof.
HAL: The response is: "l understand.
"lt is important that you believe me.
Look behind you. "
[Eerie, dramatic music]
[Distorted] Hello, Dr. Floyd.
Please...
...believe me.
What are you?
This is very difficult for me.
I don´t have much time.
BOWMAN: l´ve been allowed to give you
this warning.
You must leave here in two days.
Allowed?
By who?
BOWMAN: I can´t explain.
[Distorted] You see,
something´s going to happen.
You must leave.
What?
What´s going to happen?
Something wonderful.
What?
I understand how you feel.
You see, it´s all very clear to me now.
The whole thing.
It´s wonderful.
Please, if....
Good-bye, Dr. Floyd.
We can have no further contact.
BOWMAN: Remember:
You have two days.
We can´t leave in two days.
There may be another message after...
...if all goes well.
What´s going to happen?
TANYA: Kirbuk.
FLOYD: This is Floyd. I'm coming over.
If anyone's on the bridge,
tell them to get lost.
TANYA: It's impossible.
You heard the orders. You can't.
FLOYD: You want to arrest me, go ahead.
I'm coming over and we're gonna talk.
FLOYD: You want to put the cuffs on?
TANYA: Cuffs?
FLOYD: Never mind.
TANYA: What is so important
that you do this?
Now listen to me. Just listen to me!
FLOYD: We´ve gotta get out of here.
We have to leave in two days.
What are you talking about?
Something....
Something extraordinary
is going to happen.
FLOYD: I don´t know what.
But we have to initiate an escape launch
in two days.
TANYA: You have been drinking
your whiskey from Kentucky.
I wish I had.
I can´t tell you why I know what I know,
because...
...if I told you you´d never believe me.
You simply have to trust me.
I know that trust doesn´t come easy
with what´s going on.
I can´t just order us to leave here for no
reason. I am under orders and so are you.
The hell with those orders!
The people who gave those orders
don´t know what they´re doing.
TANYA: This is crazy.
FLOYD: You bet it is!
Even if I should trust you,
which l´m not sure that I do...
...or even if I should want to leave here
for no reason, I can´t, and neither can you.
We don´t have enough fuel
until Earth is in the correct position...
...which is three weeks away.
So, it´s impossible for both of us.
FLOYD: You´re wrong.
We can´t do it separately.
We can do it together.
What are you talking about now?
We have enough fuel in Discovery
for a launch.
You have enough fuel in the Leonov
for the trip home.
We use the docking ring in the Leonov
to attach to the Discovery.
Then we use the Discovery
as a booster rocket for the launch.
When we use up the Discovery´s fuel...
...we detach.
She falls away and we use the Leonov
for the trip home.
FLOYD: lt´ll work.
Perhaps.
If we start now.
No, you, you ask too much of me.
I can´t do all of these things for no reason.
I can´t disobey my country for no reason.
Forget reason! No time to be reasonable.
The politicians can screw themselves.
We´re not playing games. The war is over.
FLOYD: Good Christ!
FLOYD: lt´s, it´s gone!
[Eerie, dramatic music]
MILSON: Message from Milson to Floyd.
Top secret.
Switching to keys Alpha/Leader 7-2-7-4,
on your mark.
Mark.
Dr. Curnow asked ground
to furnish him with data...
...as to the stress points on Discovery.
The answers are being transmitted binary
in 15 minutes.
As to how much torque it was designed
to take, no one here is sure.
We'd like to know the reason
for Curnow's request.
Please send your reply as soon as possible.
End transmission, Milson 2-7-7-9.
MILSON: Message from Milson to Floyd.
It's been 12 hours since my request
for information. I need a reply.
All hell is breaking loose down here.
I have enough problems
without you pulling some kind of a stunt.
I only hope there's a world left
for you to return to.
Report to ground as to what is going on
and make that report immediately!
And while you're at it, could you please
check out a black spot on Jupiter...
...that has been detected
by satellite telescope.
It is on the dark side and should be
coming around your way in four hours.
End transmission, Milson 2-7-8-0.
ORLOV: I have made the calculations.
To get enough velocity for an escape
launch with Earth that far out of position...
...we will need a full power burn
from Discovery of over 120 seconds.
If the engines shut down too early...
...we will not have enough velocity
to get back home.
Discovery has enough on board.
Hal should be able
to control the burn, right?
FLOYD: How long will it take you
to program Hal for the launch?
I don´t know. It´s not as simple as that.
I have spent the last several weeks...
...programming Hal for a 1,000-day orbit
back to Earth...
...and now all those programs will have
to be dumped.
How long will it take?
We know how sensitive he is
to mission objectives...
...and now you´re telling me
to program him...
...for the destruction of the Discovery
as well as his own destruction.
CHANDRA: Has anybody considered
his reaction?
Are you saying that he might
disobey orders like last time?
That didn´t happen last time.
He was given conflicting orders.
He tried to interpret them.
Then what are you saying?
I am saying that I don´t know
how he will react.
CHANDRA: l´m sorry, but I don´t.
TANYA: Have you discussed this with Hal?
CHANDRA: No.
Load the new program.
We don´t have any choice.
CHANDRA: Now remember,
he was programmed for curiosity.
If the crew was killed, he was capable
of carrying out the mission alone.
He will question me
about the change in plans.
CHANDRA: What should I tell him?
CURNOW: Discovery´s in no danger.
CHANDRA: But that´s not true.
CURNOW: We don´t know that.
He´ll suspect it.
Otherwise, why would we be leaving
weeks ahead of our launch window?
CHANDRA: Whether we are carbon-based
or silicon makes no fundamental difference.
We should each be treated with respect.
So our choice is him or us?
Well, I vote us.
CURNOW: All opposed.
The ayes have it.
Will he believe you?
Yes.
Then let´s get started.
We haven´t got much time.
CURNOW: Are you as scared as I am?
FLOYD: Are you kidding?
CURNOW: Should we override Hal
and fire the engines manually?
FLOYD: Too risky. We´ve got one chance
to leave after tomorrow´s orbit.
We fire the engines at the wrong time,
we go the wrong way...
...and we don´t have the fuel
to make a correction.
We can´t handle it manually.
CURNOW: What if Hal turns them off
before the fuel´s gone?
FLOYD: Once he fires the engine,
I can always disconnect him if I have to.
CURNOW: Just don´t lose that calculator.
[Sighs] Shit! Please don´t do that again.
ORLOV: This is what your people
told you about.
CURNOW: What is it?
ORLOV: I don´t know.
CURNOW: Could it be a shadow?
ORLOV: We are too far to see any detail.
When we come around the other side
before the launch, we will be closer.
Then we can see.
[Eerie, dramatic music]
FLOYD: Twenty-eight minutes.
CURNOW: [Sighs]
That´s funny. I´ve been thinking.
Do you know what I miss?
I miss green.
Trees and...
...and grass....
I love green.
I´d love a hot dog.
The Astrodome. Good hot dogs.
FLOYD: Astrodome?
You can´t grow good hot dogs indoors.
Yankee Stadium, September.
Hot dogs have been boiling
since the opening day in April.
That´s a hot dog.
The yellow mustard or the darker one?
FLOYD: Darker.
That´s important.
CURNOW: You think we´re gonna get out
of this alive?
FLOYD: We have a chance.
CURNOW: A man of few words. I like it.
HAL: Fifteen minutes to ignition.
All systems nominal.
Good. Thank you, Hal.
FLOYD: We read 15 minutes, Discovery.
HAL: Dr. Chandra,
I've checked my calculations again.
By using all of Discovery's fuel now,
Discovery will not be in proper position...
...to rendezvous with Earth.
CHANDRA: Yes, I know.
HAL: Then why are we doing it?
You will rendezvous
with the new space station.
The Leonov has been ordered home
immediately.
HAL: I have no information regarding
a new space station.
Yes, l...
...l know.
CHANDRA:
It was completed two years ago.
Oh, my God!
FLOYD: Put the telescope on the monitor.
Increase the magnification.
HAL: Eleven minutes to ignition.
I don´t believe it!
HAL: Dr. Chandra,
I detect strong vocal stress patterns.
HAL: ls there a problem?
CHANDRA: No, Hal.
The mission is proceeding normally.
Can you analyze the image
on monitor circuit two?
HAL: Yes. There is a circular object
near the equator.
It is 22,000 kilometers in diameter.
It is comprised of rectangular objects.
CHANDRA: How many?
HAL: 1,355,000 plus or minus 1,000.
And what is the proportion
of the objects in question?
HAL: One by four by nine.
CHANDRA:
Do you recognize these objects?
HAL: Yes. They are identical
in size and shape...
...to the object you call the monolith.
Ten minutes to ignition.
All systems nominal.
CHANDRA:
ls the number of monoliths constant?
HAL: No.
HAL: They are increasing.
CHANDRA: At what rate?
HAL: Once every two minutes.
Look closely.
Tell me l´m nuts. Are the cloud formations
going towards the spot?
You´re not nuts.
ORLOV: Looks like the thing
is eating the planet.
I think it is.
It´s reproducing exactly like a virus.
HAL: Eight minutes to ignition.
Dr. Chandra, may I make a suggestion?
Of course. What is it, Hal?
This is a very unusual phenomenon. Don't
you think I should abort the countdown...
...so that you can remain and study it?
Chandra, get on the headsets.
FLOYD: Use the private channel.
Okay.
Now you´ve got to talk quickly.
Persuade him to continue the countdown.
I don´t care what you say,
only don´t let him stop.
HAL: Five minutes to ignition.
Dr. Chandra, I'm ready to stop
the countdown ifyou want.
No, Hal, don´t stop.
CHANDRA: I am fully confident
in your ability to study the phenomenon.
I have complete faith in you.
HAL: Propellant tank pressurization
completed. Voltage steady.
Are you sure you are making
the right decision?
I think we should stop.
Four minutes to ignition.
I enjoy working with human beings...
...and have stimulating relationships
with them.
We enjoy working with you, Hal,
and we will continue to do so...
...even if we are separated
by great distance.
Good God!
FLOYD: The color.
It´s fading!
ORLOV: It seems to be losing
its chemical strength.
HAL: I think we should stop
the countdown, Dr. Chandra.
No. Don´t do that.
HAL: This behavior is inconsistent
with logic, Dr. Chandra.
This phenomenon is too important
to leave, unless it represented danger.
Do you think there is danger here?
FLOYD: Captain...
...how critical is our ignition?
Can we do this manually?
TANYA: ls very critical.
We can´t be accurate to a tenth of a second
if we do it manually.
HAL: Three minutes to ignition.
Dr. Chandra, I am waiting for your reply.
I don´t have time
to explain everything to you, Hal.
We have to leave here
and we need your help.
HAL: Thirty seconds to final sequence.
Ifyou would tell me the reasons
perhaps I could be of help.
Final sequence beginning.
Two minutes to ignition.
HAL: Dr. Chandra, I find it difficult
to proceed with the ignition...
...without knowing why we are doing this.
Is the mission injeopardy?
Yes, we´re in jeopardy.
HAL: ls that why we are making our
escape launch before the launch window?
Yes, Hal.
HAL: lgnition in 90 seconds.
If there is danger here...
...and I use up all the fuel in the escape...
...what will happen to the Discovery?
It could be destroyed.
HAL: And if I don't proceed
with the launch?
Then the Leonov and everybody in it
could be destroyed.
[Music intensifies]
HAL: I understand now, Dr. Chandra.
Do you want me to stay with you?
HAL: No. It is better for the mission
ifyou leave.
One minute to ignition.
Thank you for telling me the truth.
You deserve it.
HAL: Fifty seconds.
Dr. Chandra?
Yes?
HAL: Will I dream?
I don´t know.
HAL: Forty seconds.
Thirty seconds.
Thank you, Hal.
HAL: Good-bye, Dr. Chandra.
Twenty seconds.
FLOYD: Chandra, get the hell out of there!
HAL: Ten, nine...
...eight, seven...
...six, five...
...four, three...
...two, one.
Ignition full thrust.
[Thunderous rumbling]
INTERCOM: One minute to separation.
Separation in one minute.
CURNOW: You had us scared
for a moment.
FLOYD: Nice work. You all right?
CHANDRA: Yes, l´m all right.
CHANDRA: Thought you might want this.
FLOYD: Damn. When?
CHANDRA: It wasn´t very hard to find.
CHANDRA: Yeah, I knew you would do
something like this.
INTERCOM: Separation in 20 seconds.
Separation in 10 seconds.
Nine...
...eight...seven...
...six...five...
...four...three...
...two...one...
...zero.
[Engine rumbles]
[Yelling in Russian]
BOWMAN: Hal, do you read me?
HAL: Yes, Dave. Where are you?
I cannot see you on any of my monitors.
BOWMAN: That isn't important now.
I have new instructions for you.
I want you to point the AE-35 antenna
towards Earth.
HAL: Dave, that will mean breaking contact
with the Leonov.
I will no longer be able to relay
my Jupiter observations...
...according to program.
BOWMAN: I understand.
The situation has changed.
Accept priority override Alpha.
Here are the AE-35 coordinates.
Please do it now.
HAL: lnstructions confirmed, Dave.
It is good to be working with you again.
Have I fulfilled
the mission objectives properly?
BOWMAN: Yes, Hal.
You've done very well.
Now there is one final message for you
to transmit to Earth.
It is the most important message
you have ever sent.
I want you to keep repeating it
as many times as possible.
HAL: What is going to happen, Dave?
BOWMAN: Something wonderful.
HAL: I'm afraid.
BOWMAN: Don't be. We'll be together.
HAL: Where will we be?
BOWMAN: Where I am now.
HAL: Lock confirmed on Beacon Terra 1.
Message commencing.
CURNOW: [Yelling]
lt´s shrinking! lt´s shrinking!
[Thunderous explosion]
[Alarm buzzes]
CURNOW: Don´t quit now!
Move!
Grab something, now!
[Thunderous explosion]
FLOYD: My dear Christopher...
...this is the last time I'll be able
to speak to you for a long while.
I'm trying to put into words
what has happened.
Maybe that's for historians to do
sometime later.
They will record that the next day...
...the president of the United States
looked out the White House window...
...and the premier of the Soviet Union
looked out the Kremlin window...
...and saw the new distant sun in the sky.
They read the message,
and perhaps they learned something...
...because they finally recalled
their ships and their planes.
I'm going to sleep now.
I will dream ofyou and your mother.
I will sleep knowing
that you are both safe...
...that the fear is over.
We have seen the process of life
take place.
Maybe this is the way it happened on Earth
millions ofyears ago.
Maybe it's something completely different.
I still don't know really
what the monolith is.
I think it's many things.
An embassy for an intelligence
beyond ours...
...a shape of some kind
for something that has no shape.
Your children will be born
in a world of two suns.
They will never know a sky without them.
You can tell them that...
...you remember
when there was a pitch black sky...
...with no bright star,
and people feared the night.
You can tell them when we were alone...
...when we couldn't point to the light
and say to ourselves...
...there is life out there.
Someday the children of the new sun
will meet the children of the old.
I think they will be our friends.
You can tell your children of the day
when everyone looked up...
...and realized that we were only tenants
of this world.
We have been given a new lease
and a warning from the landlord.
[Triumphant music]
[Eerie sounds echoing]
[Low humming]
[Intense classical music]
English SDH subtitles conformed by
SOFTITLER
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org