Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Resincronia p / DVDRip.XviD-ESPiSE:
CPtScene
Overhaul, adaptation
sync and line breaks:
B @ L @
Original timing: Spook
DWI:
JMsilv
Big Al has a huge cock.
Seriously. I'm not kidding.
It's giant.
It seems it has arms and
legs. What is life itself.
As a baby I could bring
shoulder to burp, get it?
It looks like a tool
plumber. The first time I saw ...
said: "Keep that thing.
You will not get close
me with this monster. "
But you know Big Al
He was coming
holla at me.
He looked at me and said:
Think you can?
I mean ...
It was like ...
I'm competitive, you know?
I did gymnastics
competitive in high school.
So I took another look.
And I thought, I can
lots of fun trying.
You know?
I have to say
clamber tasty.
I'm talking about climbing
tied to the bedpost ...
with sweaty dirty socks, you know?
You know. Big Al
The king of the hill.
You can say what you want
him, but he climbs and cavies.
So.
Sing it.
I have some ...
new toasters at home.
I want to.
- Where's Reilly?
- Not seen.
Watch it, baby.
Hey, baby.
- Hey, Muggles.
- Where is he?
Ali
Boxy.
- I said I did not want that type.
- You said you wanted customers.
Do not worry. He
is clean. Checked-in.
Will make money for us.
Wait here, okay?
How are you?
Okay.
Where are you from?
- Long Island.
- Really?
What can I do for you?
I want a gun.
Are you stupid?
Could you speak louder? Whether
broadcast in radio news?
- Sorry.
- Got it?
Where on Long Island?
Ice Peak.
- Earth Rangers.
- What?
Earth Rangers.
Are you retarded?
Rangers.
- Rangers.
- Yes.
This is an interview?
I just want my 45.
Stop!
Liar!
- Enough!
- Go fuck yourself!
- What is it?
- It's clean.
You do not have guns.
You came too soon.
That's right.
- You knew what you had to do.
- And did what I had!
You have it here?
Hands off my
dick and get the hell out of here.
Or process you for harassment.
Bunch of fags
like the Village People.
Get the hell out of my bar.
- Bitch!
- I'll get you!
We'll get you!
Kiss my dick, your
fucking asshole!
Pull the car from my bar!
Goodbye.
You're hot, B.
- Yeah?
- Sexy.
Let's Get Away
resolve an issue.
Big Al
It was always a troublemaker.
Since he was born.
Son of a bitch! How?
- What have I done?
- I thought I had checked it!
- We checked yes.
- And so they weave for me?
Cesarean section. 48 hours of delivery.
Fucking kid!
Never won anything!
Should have aborted.
Can not manage a
organization as well, ok?
It is a slouch.
Thing amateur.
You have to time it right.
I do not know what you mean.
He never spends the holidays in
home. It's Thanksgiving holiday.
But you will not find it here.
Neither knows what is
or family loyalty.
I do not know what went wrong with it.
Not smoked or drank in my
pregnancy. No drop.
Only beer and wine, but
it's no problem.
I'm tired of it, God!
What are you doing?
Go to fucking hell!
You go. You promised you
would take me from this neighborhood!
Right?
Seaside Heights, Rockway, Ocean
City, etc.. You're treading on the ball.
Go fuck yourself!
I want to see the real world.
- The real world.
- I'm tired of this shit!
What a fucking real world?
You got the whole world right here!
Fuck Jesus!
Come here, assholes!
Dinner's ready!
Sorry, but I hate
Thanksgiving.
I did not create a killer
but the streets did.
Stop.
My TV!
Fucking thief!
This does not!
Our new TV!
Son of a bitch!
He fainted.
Fuck. Look what
he did with the TV!
Had to
do that, sir?
- Sorry.
- Shit!
Call the police, go!
Why the hype.
I was just trying to steal.
Do not believe you!
49 West Street, 527. It is a
emergency. You have a thief in the house.
Outta the carpet!
It is an original Persian. It's expensive!
Sorry. I made a mistake.
Never come back. Sorry.
Get out of my fucking carpet!
Please do not kill me.
Sorry, please.
Sorry.
No wonder that
not passed by the window.
Look at the size of your ass!
This shit seems
a parking lot.
It has to start making Cooper
asshole!
Please!
I hope you
RG naturalized.
Please let me go.
You are from the Punjab or
is there wherever you go.
Sorry!
You disgust me, you know?
- Sorry to have broken the TV.
- Your fucking, you come here,
They take our jobs and then ...
You are parasites. Make me sick.
What's happening
with that country?
with the fucking parents?
Come back to there.
It's the people who
being stolen.
Sorry, please
let me go!
I have a family on the bus.
Bus? You have a
bus down there?
You broke the TV,
I'll take the bus.
Ok? Number 6, 9 ...
I do not wrap.
I was lying.
This shit is mine.
- Do not put your hand!
- I'm not a coach.
But please, let me go!
Al, I have two toasters.
And the blue uniform of the navy.
42 normal for my nephew
is coming to town.
- And three packets of menthol.
- Right.
- Al
- Yes.
Not my fault. Vim
pro wrong address.
- What happened here?
- I caught him trying to rob me.
Lady, please. This
crazy trying to kill me.
What are you doing?
Stop! It was not your home!
- Whether these to his nephew?
- Yes, they are legal.
- On the house, okay?
- Cool.
So ...
- Cash or charge?
- Money.
Unless you have a
those cards "cold."
Maybe. But it has
to give a kiss.
Fuck you!
His problems began with
my husband and I separated.
He was a wino
Scottish fucking!
It took Al to
to Scotland, you know?
And when Al came back, he
was more tough and mean.
And also never
lost the accent.
Move to the right.
Ai is left.
What the hell is going on?
Hold it. He
is in the bathroom.
- Who?
- The thief!
What the hell are you doing?
What the fuck?
- Is that funny?
- You are a joke?
- Should I call the police again?
- No joke, ok?
I found a criminal
of truth for you!
I'm fed up with the
do your work, ok?
He's on the fucking
bathroom. Open the door!
Police! Glad you are
here, please help me!
This guy has weapons
throughout the house!
This guy is a comedian.
Your shitty comedian.
They have no warrant.
Why not read the
U.S. Constitution.
And you, hey.
Come, take this asshole
outta my house
before I tell your supervisor
they are harassing me.
Big Al fuck.
I'm not afraid of him.
I'm not afraid of that asshole.
As his ass
right here, man.
Fuck him. Never liked him.
He never liked that
Puerto Rican here.
Let it be so. If
I did this to him?
Of course not. He is walking in flip-flops,
My business is big fish.
Fuck him!
Asshole!
And what about
my needs?
- What?
- Yes, my needs.
I suck.
- I suck you good.
- Call it sucking?
I call it
the appetizer.
Blowjob of lightning. Right?
Mosquito has sucked me better.
Even stink best ever sucked.
What business is it of selling
a gun without telling me?
- What are you talking about?
- Ok
So think
I do not know about this shit?
Clancy said.
Why are you doing
business on my back?
He needed a weapon.
What should I do?
Spoil the deal?
Your money is there.
- How much?
- Same as always.
$ 400 in the drawer
his underwear, okay?
Near the swineherd.
- You are trying to wrap myself?
- Enough, for God's sake.
You're giving pro Clancy.
He is a son of a bitch.
- I understand how he looks?
- Knock it off. I sleep with a guy.
Stop talking shit.
First, I hear they're selling
arms behind my back.
Oh, I get home
and you do not tell me.
- Then ask to suck my dick ...
- Shut up!
- And you do not suck.
Who told you?
Hellen.
Son of a bitch!
Son of a bitch.
These men fucking.
Big Al thinks the worst thing
can do is
sleeping with another guy.
Leave the other guy to eat you.
But he could
eat other, right?
He made it all the time.
Pras women one thing,
to other men.
Favoring it.
This business does not stick with me.
I do not understand.
I do not know why guys think
who are overcoming a relationship.
They think they're
"Eating us."
When I sleep with a guy.
I guarantee that he knows
Who is eating whom.
And shove my finger in his
ass just so he knows it.
It did not pass my 45
by mistake, right?
- What?
- The 45.
No. I'm not stupid. Was another.
That is recorded
in my name, ok?
Suck their fingers.
- I'm getting horny.
- I know.
Right? Do not touch the 45, okay?
Want to know Al? He is very
good at getting things.
Cars, jewelry, clothes.
Women. But he
do not know look after them.
I was his property.
You can find me crazy, but I
wanted something more than that, okay?
Oh, and nobody broke
most want to go out,
all the guys are afraid.
I have to go out with guys
New Jersey. Horrible.
What?
- It's Vic.
- It had to be that same bitch.
Shut up, she's my friend.
One second!
Do not stand her.
She always ruins everything.
Shut up!
- She is bisexual, ok?
- So what? Still a dyke.
You have to remember
his affair with her?
Once was.
Large to be boring.
A second, sweetie.
- Hi
- Hi, sweetheart.
- How are you, lindona.
- Fine.
Nothing lesbianism
in front of me.
- Unless I'm in the middle.
- Not Call him.
Okay, I do not
fucked slimy.
How are you?
You look great.
Your hair is awesome!
Like it?
Do you think her hair is great?
Looks like she got
with a spanner.
- Shut up.
- Nice to see you too, man.
- Sit down. Want a drink?
- Yes.
She lives with me now,
dyke, okay?
Looks like it.
Since I knocked on the door
and she answered, etc..
Al, still confused?
- What?
- Are you still drunk?
- Go home, you can.
- It's so obvious?
- You fucking wino!
- Come on, boner.
Son of a bitch!
My God! Al, stop it!
- Jesus Christ!
- You are a moron.
You are living proof that
We should all be lesbians.
Yes, I think
just a turn.
- So, your hair looks amazing.
- Thanks.
Really cool.
- And I've been working out very well.
- Yeah?
I won in 5cm
2 arms and chest.
Legal.
I have to have shoulders
wide to beat the Al
Since I met Al,
wanted him to die.
I hated his masculinity.
His essence.
It was not your fault
he could not escape it.
He was so. Product
of his horrible childhood.
But ...
Give a kiss.
See what is missing?
Even more.
No tongue kiss
while I'm away, girls.
I enjoyed it there within five minutes.
Thanks for the warning.
Get out.
Clean bar?
- Who is it?
- Jose Vargas.
What?
We should say that
not sold to Jose.
He would kill me if she knew
sold to a Puerto Rican.
As long as he does not think ...
sold to a Puerto Rican,
we're good at.
He's just brute force and
I the girl with the plans.
I am a businesswoman, I have
any big plans.
- You have big plans?
- Yes.
- You know.
- I hope I'm included.
You know you are.
If he hurt you again,
I kill it.
I promise.
My daughter Kat.
The danger always attracted her.
Even when I was a little girl.
She was always
doing what could not.
Ordered her not to do,
and she did it anyway.
"Do not drink." and she drank.
"Do not do drugs." and she wore.
"Beware of the boys."
Forget it.
She always challenged.
Always wanted too.
Never wanted to be normal.
She had to be special.
And look what happened.
I'm not surprised.
She was always beautiful and
Proud of your hair.
And she inherited it from me.
You get more ass
that toilet.
I'm talking about
Quality Ass.
Quality fuck.
What matters is what
is in the middle of the legs.
- You have to Kat.
- Okay, man.
You can not have everything, right?
I think I'll go back to Dell.
Let this woman go.
She's a bitch.
She gave my ass so many times that he
looks like a scientific experiment.
So what? It excites me.
If it excites you. You're the man
that more lives full of lust.
You would do anything
by a pussy.
I decided to change his life.
- What?
- I'm going back to Catholic again.
- I'll give up everything.
- Dude.
I am tired of hearing
this litany. I've heard this before.
Enough. I want a normal life.
A life and a normal job.
- What do we do?
- Nothing much.
Nothing illegal, ok?
I've said that from this
tomorrow my life is another.
You have to change
completely.
You know ...
Always have a place for you
in my organization.
You'll be mine
right arm again.
Do not you hear me, man?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Never been his right arm.
I was independent. Did
my own work.
Never worked for you, Al!
You need me, man!
Bullshit.
The only thing
need you
is a woman like Kat.
It's what I need.
What the fuck is this obsession?
It is not obsession.
It's a great girl.
Just that.
Slope there.
- What's happening?
- I'll steal that car.
It's the car that stole
last week.
Yeah, right.
And now I have to return.
The guy who stole a paid
great reward
for his recovery.
I better be
legal and return.
And the guy who sold it to?
Fuck him. He is a foot
scuff normal work.
Just like you want to be.
A normal guy.
Normal guys to fuck, Big Al did not.
That's what happens.
You will earn one month
wage in 10 seconds.
Deal or no, Mr. Normal?
It's the last time, Al's over.
Last time.
Al should have left the neighborhood.
Kat wanted it.
The way
things resulted ...
Al should have listened to her.
If I wanted to kill Al?
Yes! Many times.
He had something for
which I kill him?
Yes
Hi, ladies.
- Are you the money?
- Right here.
Passes for here!
- Why do not you get me?
- Bitch.
Kidding.
Come here, baby.
You know
you would not curl.
Yeah it goes here.
- I like doing business with you.
- Yeah?
The way they always do.
Strip legs of me.
I would do much
more with you, honey.
And who would not?
You need a man
like me, dear, you know?
- I could show you some things.
- Yeah?
My boyfriend, Big Al,
would not like that very much.
I can hit on your boyfriend.
I'm not interested,
Sanches, get out, thanks.
You could get rid of it?
It would be easy.
Why is he with?
He is walking in flip-flops.
A lindona like you.
You need to be with
a man who
is reaching
somewhere. Like me.
- Oh yeah?
- Yes.
You are going to jail.
Even more, Chico.
I'll never want to eat
you "or" this attitude.
You can eat attitude,
but I would be more delicious.
Even more.
Juanita, who delights.
I can not express
my gratitude, detective.
It's incredible that neither is a risk
it. Thank you very much.
Sure.
If I can do
something for you ...
Listen. The District
contact you tomorrow.
- Ok
- Ok, thanks. Whatever you need.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Sex with men is like snow.
You never know how many centimeters
will be or how long it will last.
The difference between men and
women is too big for me
even begin to understand.
For example, a woman ...
just want to hear three
words of a man, I love you.
A man wants to hear three words
too, but different.
It's so big!
Not?
Assholes!
To me, Big Al is the reason that
abortion should be legalized.
You talk about sex more than
any girl I know.
You are the girl more
so fuck I know.
- Standing next to you makes me horny.
- Go take the tail.
When will drop the Al?
Really? Knock it off, Vic.
Knock it off!
We're having fun, right?
Said this at the wrong time.
I'll wait for you.
What do you have in common?!
Weapons. We both love.
The weapons and I are
in love with him.
That is what we have in common.
You're in love with him?
Yes, Vic, I am.
- Sorry, but ...
- No, you know what?
Possession is not love.
Alcoholics do not have love,
they have hostages.
And it does not suit you.
I serve.
I may even treat you like
shit if you like.
Thank you. Come on.
- Hey.
- And there, assholes.
At least someone is
earning a living here.
Look Reilly.
Ass.
Ass and nice.
So dumb it takes 2 hours
to watch the 60 minutes.
- I'll get this tonight.
- Good luck.
She's a dyke.
She likes to suck pussy.
It is a challenge.
I do not eat.
It may not be as
Kat bad if the bears.
What does this mean?
Hi, girls.
- Why are you laughing?
- Let's talk back.
- Reilly, how are you?
- Well
What?
For God's sake. Are
See what I have to endure?
Come on.
I'm going. Easy.
Can I pay a
beer for you, Vic?
I do not drink.
I am Irish from birth.
Really? What a coincidence.
Reilly, I'm not ...
I was not born in Ireland,
but my family.
My parents have some shoes
Irish first.
My mom makes the best
buoy Irish town.
She makes those sweaters
tiny little cute too?
- Indeed yes.
- Really?
Do so. She must have some
reassembling these sweaters a. ..
the early nineteenth century,
I think.
She knows all the
Irish music.
Danny Boy, etc.. And my father ...
met the guy who invented the
Irish Spring soap.
See?
Everyone in this fucking neighborhood ...
Whipped! You're Irish.
- Relax, eat a potato.
- What?
Sorry.
I'm not feeling
same today. I'm kinda busy.
Do not worry.
What is your nationality?
Jewish.
Jewish? Where is it?
In the Bible.
It must be very old.
Undoubtedly.
- Where are most of the Jews?
- Long Island.
Now we can get out?
I heard you slept
with some women.
What's this?
Nothing.
I also slept.
Really?
Legal, Reilly. Your mother should
be very proud of you.
Now could you please
going home the fucking?
Am I bothering you?
No, I'm always hostile
when you do not like anyone.
I love horror movies.
You like?
I like it.
Maybe go watch one, Friday night,
want to come with me?
Jesus, Reilly!
You are a horror movie for me.
If you play, man. I will not be your next
victim. I'm not interested, okay?
- Why not?
- Why not just want me to draw.
- Not true.
- Is not it?
No.
You're so tough, you know?
Right. Contact a good reason
not to give me.
A good reason?
Do not take it personally,
but not like you.
This is not right.
It's an excuse.
- Incredible.
- It's just an excuse.
You do not even want to.
You want to Kat.
But can not have.
- Do you have a problem there.
- What?
- Al
Why not kill?
Just get rid of it.
Oh, perhaps
it could be yours.
Al is my friend. I do not do this
sort of thing with friends.
It's just a detail.
Come on, Reilly, be courageous.
Try something new.
Kill a friend.
He does not like yourself.
Always speaks ill of
you behind your back.
Oh yeah?
Type?
Say.
- You're not afraid of him, right?
- No.
Get rid of him then.
He thinks you
is a foot-and-shame.
I no longer do things like that.
I am changing.
To follow my religion now.
Following your religion?
How sweet.
It's a bit late for that,
huh?
After all this talk, I
to go to the bathroom to vomit.
Wait.
What do I do to eat you, eh?
Come on.
I want you.
Right.
I sleep with you under one condition.
If you get rid of Al
- You are very demanding.
- You should see me in bed.
- You're a good guy, Reilly.
- Thanks.
Think about it.
I'll think.
I'm worth it.
I bet you do.
Now he will turn
a good Catholic boy.
- What's happening?
- Nothing.
If you do, I'll take in the face.
Fuck.
Hey, Reilly, and then?
- You're beautiful.
- Are you drunk?
I want to kiss you right now.
Is not that drunk skunk.
I always wanted
were my girl.
Reilly! Come here.
I'll be there soon. I'm going.
- Daddy's calling, Reilly.
- If you stay with me shooting this neighborhood
You know he will not.
- O'Reilly is a good match.
- Very sexy.
Sexy?
I thought you were in love.
Have dinner request does not stop me
to see what's on the menu.
Do not know if he told you, but I am
one of the special dishes of the night.
Shit! Look who came.
- Fool!
- We talk to never come here.
So?
Want to light my cigarette?
Are you crazy?
What the hell are you doing here?
Give the lighter.
- Why are you so nervous? Hhhh.
- Stay away from me.
Al
Jesus Christ.
- See you around.
- Get your hands off me.
The Puerto Rican is
be rude.
Have to put it in place.
Never mess with
nobody's wife.
- Do not move.
- Never mess with mine!
- What?
- Please sit down.
- What have I done?
- Do not be silly, bitch!
- Do not know what I did.
- You know yes.
- No.
- I saw you with the Puerto Rican.
It's about that then
Puerto Rican.
He came to me and asked a
cigarette and I told him to fuck off.
- You touched his arm.
- I touched nothing. What are you talking about?
- Do not lie!
- I touched unintentionally, ok?
- Honey ...
- You're drunk.
Come here.
Get up,
your big baby.
- Go fuck yourself.
- You spoke with him e. ..
- Shut up.
- You lit his cigarette e. ..
- Touched his arm ...
- Al, that business ...
Then he tried to touch the chest,
right?
It was not love?
- When I saw him looking at her ...
- Could you stop?!
beautiful legs.
You're like a bitch
night with this dress.
You seem like a bitch, huh?
- You bought this dress.
- I seen my girl.
You said I looked like the
inside him, like Faith Hill.
Want to suck my dick right?
Did you suck
his dick too, right?
- Shut up.
- Shut you.
Did you suck
Puerto Rican cock.
- Answer!
- Get off me!
Would you give him,
your white trash.
Vic stayed with all night.
The three of you. Bitch bitch.
I saw the way it looked.
You disgust me!
Answer a question, ok?
What did he say to you?
- Nothing! He only asked fire!
- Liar!
Sorry, honey. Come here.
Okay. Just could not stand to see.
You embarrass me
in front of my friends.
How will I maintain
their respect?
Reilly said: "Look to your wife
Chat with a Puerto Rican. "
"She wants dick latino." That's
Whatever, fucking whore?
Expects me to suck
pussy of Puerto Rican?
Want me to eat pussy
Puerto Rican? Bitch!
How can a
these slutty!
I told his son
motherfucker! I did nothing.
- I was going to fuck it, bitch.
- Stop!
Bitch sucker of Latin!
Stay down!
- Do not move!
- No! Please.
- Stop, please!
- Come here. Cut your face.
- Retail that face.
- Stop!
- Do not move.
- Let me.
I will leave you so ugly
nobody will look.
Please, Al
Honey.
- He touched his hand.
- He said he liked my hair.
- See? You lied.
You lie, you see?
Hiding things from me.
- You understand?
- No, please.
Why not say so before?
- I do not know.
- Come here, baby.
- I never want to see you so.
- Please!
- Listen.
- Please, Al!
I never want to see
you dressed like that.
It looks like a slut in that dress.
Tire.
- Please.
- Remove.
Give it here.
Take this shit, ok?
Ok, let's go to the room.
Come to my room.
Let's see what else is there.
Show your other clothes. Strip
clothes from the closet, baby.
- Show me. Give here.
- These clothes?
Clothes are a bitch, baby!
- Look at this shit.
- Please stop, Al
- Clothes are a bitch!
- Do not do it, Al
Please, Al, Sorry.
Never talk to anyone.
Shit!
Ok, come here.
Look in the mirror.
Come on, look in the mirror.
You see?
Tell me.
- Say it's a bitch.
- Stop it, Al!
Say it's a bitch!
- I'm a bitch!
- Say you love me.
- I love you.
Says he wants to suck my dick.
I want to suck your dick!
Honey.
- I'll cut your hair!
- No!
Stay still,
you'll learn.
It is the only way
will learn.
Come here!
I want to spend the rest of my
life with you, your fucking bitch!
Al!
I'll buy a mirror
new for you tomorrow, love.
No excuse for
treating people like him.
There are people who had a
childhood worse than that of Al,
and end up doing
great things.
Become a
model of citizenship.
As a secretary who knew
who had a horrible childhood. Type:
Too horrible to talk about: Rape;
incest, eating with hands, etc..
But he lived with a smile on
face and everything was wonderful.
She was funny. Nothing
like this animal: Al
Death penalty.
Shoot him. It has to be
be swift and brutal.
Okay. Okay?
- You have to go, Vic.
- What?
You have to go, why ...
I do not want trouble.
You have to go.
I'm not going nowhere.
You come to my house with me.
- No.
- What are you doing?
I can not. He turns back
me. You know him.
Do not want to get in trouble
More, please.
I'm scared.
I'll turn it all inside.
I'll be fine.
As can be
with him after that?
I love him.
I love fucking.
This is sick. Love does not
would cause suffering.
- But I love you, Vic.
- It was because of weapons?
It was not.
He was just jealous.
- Who is it?
- Reilly.
Do not let anyone enter.
Jesus Christ, are you okay?
But what the fuck.
Sit.
It was the Al
Son of a bitch down!
He beats women.
How did this happen?
Do not be so surprised,
was not the first time.
It'll be okay, honey.
Okay nothing
It was you who made him do it.
- Are you one of them.
- How so?
I did nothing.
Al does not work pro
Clancy and other guys did.
I swear. Come here.
- Reilly.
- Easy. It'll be fine.
I do everything I want.
You decide.
It's just bullshit. You all
are full of crap.
I'll get your stuff.
And let's get you out because
can not stay here anymore.
- Come to my house. It will be better.
- I will not go with anyone!
I'll wait and when he'll return
break his face in front of you!
- Stay here?
- Honey, okay, sorry.
- Should not have done it, Al!
- Get outta my house!
- Go fuck yourself!
- Do not touch it!
I was playing, you do not
deserve, you bastard!
- So try it!
- Reilly!
- Stop!
- Reilly out of him!
Beware! Come on!
- Look at the fucking gun!
- You're hurting him out!
You're hurting,
Reilly, stop!
Oh, my God!
Let Kat, get out there!
They were very noisy.
I'll just say this.
I do not want trouble.
What happened behind those
doors was not of my business.
- Let me see let Al?
- I'm here to help you, and not Al
Think you believe it?
You think I'm stupid?
I know you want me to help you
Al to put in jail forever?
I will not have anything to do with it.
Got it?
I do not know what Al did in
past and honestly do not care.
I'm here because I was responsible
his case, to help you.
This is my job. Phallus
with battered women.
Battered women?
What the hell does that mean?
I am a bacon beaten?
What are you talking about?
Come on, Kat.
It's obvious that he hurt you.
He hit me, so what?
He rarely hits me.
This was not a
simple beating.
Will wait until next time,
until you kill him?
- It was not his intention?
- Listen.
You can protect yourself.
Talk to me.
Nothing to say
will leave this room.
Yeah, right. The
walls have ears.
I am not asking
handed over her boyfriend.
Right? Just wondering:
As a man who loves a
woman would do this to her?
And why a woman
would you be with him?
Needless to say
nothing if not want.
We could only stay
sitting here for a while.
He cut my hair.
Jesus! It was an accident, okay?
I have not tried to kill her!
Was it murder
the bullet had caught her.
But only got grazed. Was a
accident. I never kill Kat!
She sucks better
all in NY.
- I see you have it in high esteem.
- Okay, look ...
If a woman that upon
his face, would not want to hurt her?
Not worth it
by killing anyone.
I think you
Kat never proved.
So ... married?
Divorced.
Lonely?
No way. My work
keeps me very busy.
You want to fuck me, right?
It can be hard to believe you,
but I can resist its charm.
You'd be the first.
And his girlfriend who is
a point of giving out on you?
What would she say if you
hear talking like that?
Please do not be so dramatic.
I'm not going nowhere,
not to be home.
Home sweet home. Bet.
Kat is not going to complain.
She can not live without me, you dig?
She loves me.
- So what do you think of me?
- What is homicidal and psychopathic.
And if you stay on the streets,
'll probably kill someone.
- Maybe himself.
- Do not say that or I'll kill you!
What's the matter with you,
you moron! You're tough?
More than me?
If you feel funny, Clancy.
But I know you.
She just said she was talking
with the Puerto Rican.
Fuck you, asshole, I
I know you're a jerk.
A despicable coward with foot odor.
And Kat was beaten by
Because of what you said.
Bullshit. She deserved it.
You can not trust her.
Beware what you say, Clancy.
I'm talking to look after you
life, or get hurt.
- Are you threatening me?
- Fuck.
You do not have
bother me.
Has the Kat Reilly, Latinos.
Do you think Jose will leave cheap?
Think? I'm talking to fend for himself.
The fish dies by the mouth.
You're not me
leaving scared.
I'm not? Then you're retarded!
See you at the morgue, genius.
I do not plan to live
here all my life.
Dream of leaving here.
Al and I have plans to go
to the beach or something.
This year out
but maybe next year.
- Likes the beach?
- Yes.
I love the beach. Al has promised to
get a place for us there.
No need for that Al.
You'll be surprised at the
much you can do alone.
- Better stop here.
- Why?
I do not want trouble.
I have neighbors who will talk.
Call me, ok? Come on.
You'll get in trouble.
Slag!
What was in my head?
Fucking prick!
Someone should have killed Al ago
long. I've thought about it, but ...
I could not. We had spent
through a lot together e. ..
Would not it be nice
do this, you know?
It's something in the neighborhood.
We have rules.
Of course we fight.
We did not go much in agreement
times. Most of the time.
But it would have been nice.
- Hi, trouble.
- Hi
- On the house.
- I can not accept anything stolen.
Are you kidding?
I did not steal it, was the Al
Handle at once.
Do not leave me no way, ok?
Okay.
Want to join?
- Yes.
- Come in.
- I'll make some toast for you.
- Ok
Listen. Al will be free in 24 hours
you have to make a decision.
Make a complaint or get
a court order.
How do you know so much about Al?
Because I was married
with a man like him.
- Wow.
- I'll show you something.
Jesus Christ.
- When was that?
- 6 years ago.
After I left,
I returned to school,
I got my diploma.
- You're mad.
- My life has changed for the better.
Changed. Leaving it was the
Best thing I ever did.
- I'm afraid.
- You can.
He was not afraid
he was behind you?
I could not give more
the luxury of being scared.
- Hi
- Hi, Reilly.
Any news?
- No, and you?
- No.
- Beer.
- Ok
Take.
I'll kill him.
I'll kill the bastard.
This must be the thing
smarter than I said.
It's here. Where I live.
Is there another place to live?
Can I stay in the house
my friend Vic, but ...
I do not think that is
a good idea.
- Why not?
- Because I get the couch ...
and end up in her bed. Got it?
What?
Upset by having you
slept with a girl?
There is ...
No. Why?
I always say: Each one in his.
Each one in his.
Also always say that.
You're so tense. Relax.
Moreover, it is the end of
block. Not far enough.
He could find us
easily there, you know.
- You could stay here.
- I could not accept that.
No problem.
I have a room.
- I think, thanks.
- Listen.
You are a woman with
power and need to use.
Lips, nipples, hips.
You're all woman.
Have to think so.
Use your power of woman
to change your life.
- I slept with a woman?
- No.
- It's me singing?
- Maybe. Wants me to be?
Mean. Come on.
We're talking "helps"
huh?
I'm not helping you
for that reason.
And contradicting what you think,
not everyone wants something from you.
I'm doing here
my duty ...
and not to take advantage of you.
I swear.
Really?
No thanks. I do not believe
anything you're saying.
Nobody does anything for free.
When I was 9 years ...
He told me he wanted
I had never been born.
He said
never wanted children.
But he lived in the mood to climb by
Because of his incredible
sexual drive.
So he could not
take your hands off my mother.
So I told him ...
That's no excuse. If not
want children did not.
Has many children
junk out there, right?
Eat your ass bitch.
This is my solution pro
birth control.
Turn the bitch and eat my ass.
- How are you?
- Al
I'll call the Vic and Liz,
they are down there.
- And I'll call the police.
- It will not.
You should not be here.
Do not make things more
difficult than they are.
I do not want that bitch
Come in here to investigate.
I warn you, okay?
Do not want her to come here.
I warn you.
Come here.
I think she never had
luck with men, but ...
she never knew how
keep a man.
I, for one, am married and happy
My fourth husband for two years.
It works.
Gerdie. Could close this
maw and cook something for me?
Shut your fat mouth!
We'll eat when
I want to, ok?
I do not know where she got
her problem with men.
Perhaps her father.
He's crazy.
Clancy said he saw you talking
with the Puerto Rican again.
- I have not spoken with him, okay?
- I wanted to suck his dick?
- No, I want to suck his dick!
- Admit it!
So why not respond?
You must be thinking?
- You have to think?
- No! 're Making me nervous!
Right.
It seems I'm the "Million-Dollar Show."
Shit!
Go away at the first sign
of a domestic disturbance?
- Oh, no Al, Al
- What?
Insanity is not a
domestic disturbance!
It is a disease that rots.
And you're crazy.
- Ok
- Let me go, please.
Promise not to beat
most of you, ok?
You said that last time.
- This time it's for real, ok?
- No.
- I need some time.
- This time it's for real.
I need some time
to think, ok?
- Do not go.
- See if I can forgive you!
- For God's sake!
- Save that shit!
Keep that shit!
You're not going anywhere!
Do not touch me.
- Do not touch me.
- Do not say I can do!
I am your master! Centimeter
by inch, you're mine.
- I am your master! Ok?
- Al ..
I will ask a court order
to expel you.
- I'm right.
- I got the chick!
You do not have any power.
I have. You are a woman!
I make your face to bits
if you request a court order.
You will not be able
come near me.
Or accurate.
Send someone to do.
I'll be sitting
here watching TV.
As your face
is being shredded.
Will I have three witnesses.
Police. My friends.
And when your face
is being punched,
and you'll be here
have no proof.
So ...
Will be so ugly when
crawl back to me ...
neither will
want to see you anymore.
- Kat, c'mon!
- Sit down.
Neither move.
- Kat? Okay?
- What the hell is he doing here?
He says he came back.
- Vic.
- She will be with me.
Listen, Kat. Remember
as we speak.
Can I call the police
now if you want.
- Say you'll stay.
- It'll be fine.
- Put them away from home.
- They could go?
We will reach an agreement.
I do not want trouble,
ok, please?
- Kat.
- Okay?
Listen, Albert.
If hurt, not
I'm your girlfriend.
- I'll kill you.
- I'm scared to death, okay?
- For really should.
- Your black fucking.
Get out of my house to
I eat my pussy.
I swear at what you want.
If you hit it again,
will be between you and me. Got it?
- Kat?
- Please, go.
It'll be fine. It is a matter
particularly among the people.
Go fuck yourself!
Do not make me get up.
I married at 18, with a guy who
thought to be a Prince Charming.
- But it was a frog, right?
- Right.
But he tricked me for a while.
Louquinha I was the guy.
You were young.
Maybe it was just louquinha.
Or wrong.
Probably both.
At first it was great.
But then he began to
drink and act like Al
I was 6 months pregnant.
A girl. Tess.
He came home drunk one night
and began to fight over ...
drink all or nothing.
Then he began to
beat me without stopping.
Somehow, I escaped and
I ran screaming down the hall ...
and neighbors
called the police.
Again. E. ..
I reached the top of the staircase
and he reached me ...
He hit me so hard ...
I fell down the stairs e. ..
I lost the baby.
- Sorry.
- Ok
Nor was the place to get
my clothes and things.
It did not come see me at the hospital.
I was so angry.
Men are dogs. One day
will wake up and start barking.
Right.
But I would love to help Kat
then ... if you think of something ...
- Anything.
- E. ..?
- Let me know, ok?
- Yes.
You're screwing me.
Are you listening?
You fucking bitch!
- Why does not speak my name!
- Al
- Say it!
- Al!
What are you suggesting?
If Kat is not strong
enough to drop the Al,
maybe he needs
Drop it.
- He'll never do that.
- Perhaps not willingly.
What are you saying?
You seem to follow the rules and
My suggestion is a bit risky.
- Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
- You bastard. I loved it.
Go ahead.
A friend of mine has just
with Al for a price.
Wait.
We have not had that conversation.
He's not so expensive
can crack.
Crack? We are not
talking about dinner.
You're talking about murder.
You crazy?
It's the only way we get her out
His stay with me for her.
You are in love with her?
Would do anything for her.
I'm mad about her.
Or maybe it's just crazy.
Realized that is
talking about murder?
You said: Who does not
ventured, nothing gained.
He was talking of arming.
Or something, was not
talking about killing anyone. Christ!
Known me for 2 hours and wants
I'm an accomplice to murder.
I do not want more.
Do you think this neighborhood
are above the law, but are not.
This is not the old west.
It's what you think.
Fuck!
Unleash the Al!
I think I did not understand something, okay?
Still not finished with him.
Got it?
- Like it?
- Gives pro spent.
I thought I'd take care of the problem.
What happened? Giving back?
I thought you would handle it.
I'm working on it.
I like you.
Idem.
Despite being a man.
Know. Big Al was a major cause
death in the neighborhood for a while.
Are you saying that
Many want him dead?
I am saying that we live
a very dangerous neighborhood.
- Everyone has to be careful.
- That's exactly what I say.
Do not let me learn that
Reilly is talking to or Vic.
I would say I love you very much.
Do not worry.
I will not talk to anyone.
- If you will not have trouble, ok?
- Ok
A kiss.
Right.
I have 2 hours.
- We have two hours.
- Yes, that's all I need.
Hey. I wish I had saved my
first time for you.
- Really?
- I wanted to be a virgin for you, Reilly.
Fuck.
What?
Do anything
to get rid of him.
- Anything?
- Yes, It will get rid of it?
I promise I'll take care
it for you.
Promise?
I wish I had saved my
first time for you, Vic.
I wanted to be a virgin
you, Vic. You know why.
I can not stand. Every time he would
rings, just think of you, Vic.
Do not take it anymore.
Kat knew exactly what
is doing. She's smart.
She goes by the numbers.
Playing. Taking risks.
playing with odds.
If she wanted something for Christmas.
She talked to 4 people
buy the same thing ...
She estimated that
that one would meet.
And she was right.
Nobody has ever climbed
better than you.
- Will do what I want?
- Yes.
She got everybody backpack.
Not happy
everything is back to normal?
- Yes.
- I was wrong?
Yes
You always right, Al
- What is it?
- What?
Right.
- I love you.
- Me too.
Listen, I want to take you ...
I will return here after dinner.
I want to get a sophisticated place.
Take you out.
No. How come?
We were going to stay here and make dinner.
- Making big beans.
- I want to take you to ...
French restaurant
one near the ...
- Near the market.
- Hey, Al ..
- Al
- Where's my jacket?
You know ...
I have a new fantasy
Crazy that I've been plotting.
And I wanted to experiment with you.
- Okay?
- I think so.
I know that you love so much.
- I want that.
- Yeah?
Ok
Where's my jacket?
- Why not ...
- The jacket written Big Al?
Do not use the Big Al
I bought a new one, where is it?
Want to Big Al
Why? There it is.
I bought a new beautiful.
Come on, honey. For me.
Ok
The problem is that Al
he never thought big.
It was always a
foot-and-shame.
But he found
someone Height: Kat.
I'm saying.
That's smart. Tough.
There was a period in her life in
that every guy who goes out with her ...
changed the name to the complainant
the first 3 weeks.
I'm not sure?
I really want to change this time,
Fr.
I'm so tired of
be wrong with my baby.
Want to be a good man, you know?
But I'm saying.
I can not leave it in the pants.
Even when I'm in church praying,
every time I see a girl
beautiful in the hall, I want ...
- I shove down her skirt.
- What do you do?
- Again I pray.
- Thank goodness that triumphs.
- How do you think I feel?
- What are you saying?
A row of women are
kneeling in front of me ...
open their mouths, put
tongue out,
look at me and say "Ah".
- What do you do?
- Again I pray.
It's sickening. How can you say that?
How can you think so?
These poor girls are looking for you
to have hope and you
want them to suck his dick.
Its fucking disgusting.
I'm just a man, Al
I have a chick under the cassock.
- You will burn in hell.
- I'm no better nor worse than you
You're weak. I hate weakness!
You disappoint me, man!
Stay away from children, okay?
- It's him!
- Come on, man?
Get him!
Put your hands behind your back!
- Fuck!
- What are you doing, Al!
Fuck you, asshole!
- Be quiet!
- Do not move!
You're under arrest for
Clancy O'harra murder.
Do not move!
- You're not going anywhere.
- Fuck!
It is a mistake!
Get off me!
- Fuck off.
- Get in there!
What is this attitude not
will get you nowhere.
Go fuck yourself!
Get in the car!
- Look at his head.
- Fuck!
He must have done something in life.
He lived in big trouble.
Then I thought:
"If you're ever in trouble,
then do something
let your mother proud. "
Rob a bank, a post
gasoline. Something worthwhile.
Want to meet?
So you have to do something
which obliges them to respect it.
No matter if you like.
If you fear. Then yes.
Turn headline. Am I right?
I do not believe that finally
got rid of him.
No one can
connect to it, right?
You are a danger, eh?
You know you like it.
Never thought you did.
There's nothing sexy
in being afraid.
God.
If you knew that you would know,
would have done anything to you first.
In sex, you are unique.
I'll find a way
to reward you.
Kat ... is a doll.
One of the first bitch.
And that's a compliment.
- Did not hear anything in the streets?
- I heard nothing.
I want to talk to the mother of Clancy
and find out who was behind him.
Reilly does not know anything?
Why not go talk to him
in line, gotta get out of here now.
Why worry?
They have no evidence.
My digital
are in the gun, right?
- How?
- I do not know.
My lawyer says
the good thing is that ...
I have evidence that was not close
Clancy's house that night.
I was with you.
But I do not understand why the guy
who lives downstairs ...
said he saw me leave
running from the building ...
shortly after 22:45
hearing the shot.
He said he knows that I was by
he saw my jacket Big Al
But I lost that shit
jacket weeks ago.
Anyone could
be using it.
I do not understand, understand?
Clancy was dead
I sold the gun?
No.
He was killed with 45 to
is registered in my name.
- I do not understand.
- Someone is up to me.
- Who?
- I do not know.
Someone who knows us.
- Are you accusing me?
- No. .. I do not know.
How do I know.
What the fuck am I saying?
The good thing is that you are my proof.
- You're my alibi.
- What proof, Al?
- Where were you tonight?
- How so?
- I was with you.
We were playing at home
deck and watching TV, remember?
You do not want to leave that night,
back after the movie.
I made baked beans with
toast and tuna for me.
What?
I do not remember.
Do not play games with me.
You're my alibi.
I'm doing
confusion about the date.
- I was with you.
- No. I was with a friend.
And he would swear on a stack that
Bibles. He is very religious.
- You would not do this to me, Kat.
- Want to bet?
- Not too late for us.
- Please ...
- Do not beg.
Your ...
asshole.
I'll kill you,
fucking bitch!
- Sit down!
- You will not regret it!
Listen, for now
I'm in control.
And he knows how:
hips, lips, teats.
Complete woman.
What are you talking about?
Who you been talking?
- I want to hear, Al
- I'll kill you.
- Listen well.
- I'll kill you!
You're leaving me with much
anger and you do not want that ...
because I have power.
You will rot here
asshole.
If I want to.
You understand me, Al?
You set me up.
- Do not be so dramatic.
- It was the Vic.
It was Vic, right?
Wrong.
It was not Reilly. He does not ...
Say it is not climbed with him, okay?
Tell him he did not ask for
you suck his dick!
He did not need to ask.
I offered.
- Oh, Kat.
- Only ...
Thanks for the haircut.
I turned someone else.
- So how did?
- What?
- As armed pro Al?
- There have laid.
Snap out of it.
I know it was you with Kat.
Not me.
- He slept with her recently?
- No, and you?
- No.
- Bitch.
- But you still want it too, right?
- To tell the truth ...
It is too much trouble.
After all this,
I can never trust her.
I would be suspicious
all the time.
It scares me.
He preferred to sleep with
somebody more like you.
Really?
Yes
I never speak much with a woman
without ending up going to bed.
You know?
If you're lucky, you might have
many firsts with me.
- This is not a game?
- I'm not with games.
- Play pool.
- It would be a new approach.
Become friends
first and then climb.
- Your legs are great, Vic.
- You like it?
Taste.
Really.
If you play right can be
back to you within 10 minutes.
- What should I do?
- Shut up.
I am speechless.
- What was that?
- What?
You have not cured me.
I am not sick.
Whenever I play in two teams,
and I'ma sucker for redheads.
Me too.
- How was it?
- It was good.
- Let's get outta here.
- Ok
Then we can get your stuff?
- And take me home?
- No.
No? How so?
No.
I thought that with Al out of the game
'd stay together.
I said that?
It was not necessary.
Your body has expressed it.
Whipped.
You got what you wanted and
now is getting rid of me.
- So, it will be Vic and Reilly?
- Not so, ok?
Neither.
I need to be alone. Understand?
So, after all
I've done for you ...
- The reward is just a kiss?
- What happened to you?
And that fucking hips, tits,
lips, woman? Power.
- Use.
- Stop!
Do not throw my words
in my face! You used me!
I did not take anything from you, ok?
He said I could trust you.
That does not need anything from me.
And in the end, treated me as
others. Right?
You got what
wanted to take away from me.
So do not be a victim.
Fuck!
Can not play
people out like that!
What's happening
with ketchup?
Big Al Pacas climbed well.
He was great.
Until you stop being.
Do not get me wrong,
when we started out,
was exciting, dangerous.
He was funny, sexy, high.
It made me feel safe. Protected.
But he could not me
protect yourself.
Big Al could give me almost everything in
world, but "almost" was not enough.
Life is like sex. If you want
exit right, do it yourself.
Hang out with Big Al ..
made me realize that
best feeling in the world ...
is taking care of number one here.
Myself.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org