Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
When I remember Lisa, I don't think about our clouds
or her work, or where she was from or what she said.
I think about her smell, her taste
her skin searching mine
The first time I met her was the Brixton Academy
# Artist(Band):B.R.M.C.(Black Rebel Motorcycle Club) #
[# Whatever Happened To My Rock 'N' Roll(Punk Song)# ]
# You want a part of me #
# You want the whole thing #
# You want to feel something more than I could ever bring #
# You want it badly You want it tangled #
# I want to feel something more #
# than I was strangled I fell in love #
# with the sweet sensation #
# I gave my heart to a simple chord #
# I gave my soul to a new religion #
# Whatever happened to you? #
# Whatever happened to our #
# rock and roll? #
# Whatever happened to my rock'n'roll? #
# She wants it hallow #
# She wants it tainted #
# She wants to feel something more than she was naked #
# You want to hide away You're scared to touch it #
# I want to feel something more than #
# I care to take. I fell in love with the sweet sensation #
# I gave my heart to a simple chord #
# I gave my soul to a new religion #
# Whatever happened to you? #
# Whatever happened #
# to our rock'n'roll? #
# to my rock'n'roll? #
# You can't have it crying #
# Neither with your disguise. #
# Was so sweet, yes #
# She's not the leader of religion #
Go save your soul, ok?
Where are you going?
I have a meeting this morning. An appointment
with my supervisor
The Antarctic
13,800.000 km2(square Km)s of ICE.
A continent of ICE
A place where no man had ever been until its 20th century
# Artist:The Von Bondies # C'mon C'mon #
# On another day. C'mon, c'mon #
# With these ropes I tied can we do no wrong? #
# Now we grieve cause now is gone #
# Things were good when we were young #
# With my teeth locked down #
# I can see the blood of a thousand men #
# who have come and gone #
# Now we grieve cause now is gone #
# Things were good when we were young. Is it safe to say? #
# C'mon, c'mon. #
# Was it right to leave? C'mon, c'mon #
# Will I ever learn? #
# C'mon, c'mon. #
# As I make my way....C'mon, c'mon. #
# These better nights that seem too long #
# Now we grieve #
# cause now is gone #
# Things were good when we were young #
# With my teeth locked down I can see the blood #
# Of a thousand men who have come and gone #
# Now we grieve cause now is gone #
# Things were good when we were young #
# Is it safe to say? C'mon, c'mon. #
# Was it right to leave? C'mon, c'mon. #
# Will I never learn? #
# C'mon, c'mon. #
# Is it safe to say? C'mon, c'mon. #
# Was it right to leave? C'mon, c'mon. #
# Will I never learn? #
# C'mon, c'mon. #
# And know this day these deepened wounds #
# don't heal so fast #
# Can't hear me croon #
# of a million lies that speak no truth #
# of a time gone by that now is through #
Oh Baby, pay attention to me?
Who's gonna make your breakfast?
Ah, yes.
Fuck me
- Fuck you?
- Please...Please?
- Say again, again..Again?
- Please!
Sit
Come here
Fuck me
Put me inside you
Do it faster.
Fuck me faster.
Come inside me!
Come inside me! Come on....!
Coffee?
Yeah...
- Why not?
- I will put it back on you
Do you think I look like a boy?
Yeah, so I like it
Boy?
Girl?
I feel it big muscle
Look like wings!
You look like an angel
There's a big clog
Only unhappy people abhor dancing.
- How's Americans dance?
- Like this
- Um...Turn around
- Like this?
And everyones in Brasil..
I guess they can't help it
This is how we dance raves in America
This is how we dance in England
That's fantastic
I think we will make love without using a condom
No!
Why? I did all the test...make sure I am clean
I know
But I like better this way
Can I take a bath?
Yeah...you should....Dick is stink
Hi, Natasha.
Ahh...No I was fine..I just kind a finish work and came home
What happened to you?
Ummm! You always get all the good boys..! Um..What's the name?
Umm...I'm comming in to work at six
Yeah...I'll see you then..OK..Bye
Natasha always comes back at the boutique
You know stories about this really grand man she meets
Really..Really fucking weird man
The weirdest people comming to our bar...the princes,
Sons of whoever, daughters of whoever and the girlfriends and boyfriends...
prostitute of God knows what...
I went out with a guy who always had a briefcase with him
And rumor had it that is filled 20,000 Euros at all times
Did you have seen the money?
I saw 10,000 of it
# Artist:Elbow 'Fallen Angel'#
# All the fallen angels #
# Roostin' #
# in this place #
# Count back the weeks #
# on worried fingers #
# Virgin mother #
# whats'erface #
# You don't need #
# to sleep alone #
# You bring the house down #
# Choose your favourite shoes #
# And keep your blues #
# on cruise control #
# All the gelded mongrel #
# Bear their teeth for you #
# Drag your feathers #
# 'cross the dancefloor #
# Throw your shapes electric blue #
# You don't need #
# to sleep alone #
# You bring the house down #
# Choose your favourite shoes And keep your blues #
# on cruise control #
- Woman
- Man
- Blue
- White
Ocean
Waves
Desert
Storm
Loves
Us
Yeah!
# Artist: Franz Ferdinand 'Michael'#
# So sexy #
# You're sexy. Come and dance with me #
Those glasses are so ugly
tried look ugly
It look stupid
tried look stupid
# So close now. Come dance with me #
# Come and dance with me Come and dance with me #
# Michael, you're a boy #
# with all the leather hips #
# Sticky hair, stickyhips, stubble
on my sticky libs Michael, you're the only... #
I have a ...once in colombia
once in Brasil, once in Argentina
once in Germany, when I was in highschool
And I..have....an English boy friend
Ahh...isn't this romantic?
Beautiful morning...
No it's not....it's gray
Hang on..I don't want to...scared to death..
The only reason I would screaming marriage is about I really loved it
That so boring
I will be with you nude beach!
Matt, don't go in the water, it's cold
I can't take you anywhere!
I love you!
# Artist: Primal Scream 'Movin' on Up'#
# I was blind #
# now I can see. #
# You made a believer, out of me #
# I was blind, now I can see #
# You made a believer #
# out of me #
# I'm movin' on up now #
# Gettin' out of the darkness #
# My light shines on #
# I was lost #
# now I'm found #
# I believe in you #
# I've got no bounds #
# I was lost #
# now I'm found #
# I believe in the rock and roll #
# I got no bounds #
# I'm movin' on up now #
# Gettin' out of the darkness #
# My light shines on #
# shines #
# We like to shine #
# shines, shines #
# shines #
# My light shines on #
The ICE sheet can be 4 km a date
The ICE found that can be half-million years old.
The air trapped in the ICE..
We called the climate when the ICE was formed
The Antarctic is a planet's memory
a memory of time before there were the people
She is 21...beautiful..egotistical
careless and crazy
Hey!
listen to this
Immediately after I undressing I was
a little embarrassed discouvered that I had a hard-on
And I lay down on my stomach beside her
One of the misshaped pubic hair
You can easily make out of slender delicate slit.
I really go for that type of pussy Valery said low voice
It make you feel like slipping  your finger inside?
As she lay down..I can make out of the thick plump lips of pussy
I heard footsteps approaching accross
the sand and I closed my eyes again.
It sounds very hard on your skin
Don't weigh that belt on my face
You know I got hurt once
while wave of fart in front of my face.
Oh..no, don't put me stockings on
No..I can't see..
Forget who you are
Forget where you are
You are on a beach in Silent
Your eyes closed
So you can't see them
You feel them watching you
There's a couple behind me
Am I right?
I can feel them looking at me
And I put my hand between my legs.
I am so wet.
she slide down her boyfriend body
she has most amazing breast
And she is rubbing them
And she's covered with the oil
She leans toward ...to her...rr
her boyfriend
she grabs his balls.
Put his cock in her mouth
Fuck-me, Matt.
Come up here...Fuck-me
Come up!...coume up here Fuck-me!
Matt,
Fuck-me!
Fuck-me Faster!
Faster!
Fuck-me!
Fuck-me Faster!
Good
Fuck-me!
# Artist: Dandy Warhols 'You Were The Last High'#
# I am alone but adored #
# By a hundred thousand more #
# Then I sin, when you were #
# the last #
# And I have know love #
# like a whore, from #
# at least ten thousand more #
# Then I swore, when you were the last #
# When you were the last #
# high #
# You were awake #
# And I should've stayed #
# But wondered #
# I was only out for a day #
# Out for a day #
# It was Chicago #
# for a moment #
# and then it was #
# Paris and London for #
# a few days #
# I told I'm alone #
# but adored #
# by a hundred thousand more #
# Then I swore when #
# you were the last #
# You were the last high #
Thanks for supper
No problem
Thanksgiving tomorrow
I know
We should do something
Um..I got some dinner plan with some friend of mine from America
You'll hate it?
It's really good though
Do it harder
Massage my pussy
Sometimes you kiss me I just wanna bite you
Not a nice way....But I wanna hurt you
Like I wanna bite your lips really fuckin hard and make you bleed
Um..that's him
- You wanna talk?
- Um.... I just gonna go right out
Ok.
in bed
# Artist: Goldfrapp 'HORSE TEARS'#
# The night has fallen #
# mute and cold #
# My horse is crying #
# But you know #
# all this time #
# that you'd never want #
# keep you still #
# Dare to come #
# But you love me #
# still #
# Tears too cold #
OK?
Lisa didn't wanna go to the gate that night?
so I gave her ticket away
Five thousand people are woman but you can still be alone
# Artist: Super Furry Animals 'Slow Life'#
# Move you #
# Buy and sell you #
# Terrorise you #
# Mass destruct #
# you #
# Flaunt you #
# Disconnect you #
# Cluster fuck you #
# We will crush you #
# Rocks are slow life #
# Rocks are slow #
# life....... #
Did you put sugar in my tea?
Possibly
I don't like sugar in my tea
Good for your...
I don't wanna be pick time....
You gonna drink your tea?
It's too hot
And it's got sugar in it?
You are so boring today..!
boring
Bo..Boring
I am sure someone name Bo...Boring
Bodereck
Its own fucking interesting when you start taking pills this time a day
You know what? I hardly taking the fucking pills this time a day
I took my prescription pill.. then I take everyday
That I have been taking  since you fucking met me
I didn't take any of those pills..
Did you see me taking any of those pills?
You been sitting right in front of me..... Are you sitting in front of me?
...now looking at..... don't pay any fucking attention to me?
Hey
Hi
I bought your president
Me
Just kidding
# Artist: Elbow 'I've Got Your Number'#
# Don't put this note #
# by your face on the pillow #
# Don't put this letter #
# on the pocket near to your heart #
# Keep it in the bottom drawer #
# where you hide the sex tools #
# I pray you always need them #
# I #
# know what #
# you #
# have done #
Do you find my nipple swell to you? They are
Really?
# Artist: Franz Ferdinand 'Jacqueline'#
# Jacqueline was seventeen #
# Working on a desk when Ivor #
# peered above a spectacle #
# Forgot that he had wrecked a girl #
# Sometimes these eyes #
# forget the face they're peering from #
# when the face they peer upon #
# Well, you know #
# that face as I do #
# And how in the return of the gaze #
# She can return you the face #
# that you are staring from #
# It's always better on holiday #
# So much better on holiday #
# That's why we only workr #
# when we need the money #
# It's always better on holiday #
# So much better on holiday #
# That's why we only work #
# when we need the money #
# Gregor was down #
# again. Said: #
# Come on, kick me again. Said: #
# I'm so drunk. I don't mind if #
# if you kill me #
# Come on you, gutless #
# I'm alive #
# and how i know it #
# But for chips and for freedom I could die #
# It's always better on holiday #
# So much better on holiday #
# That's why we only work #
# when we need the money #
# It's always better on holiday #
# So much better on holiday #
# That's why we only work #
# when we need the money #
Explorering Antarctic..
is almost like exploring space
You enter a void
Thousand of mile with no poeple..
no animals..no plants
You isolated on a vast...
empty continent
Claustrophobia and Agoraphobia is in a same place
like a two people in a bed
We spend my birthday in a hotel where friend of Lisa worked
Lisa gave me a book on Antarctic as my present
The Ice is everywhere and everything
It spreads to all sides unbounded void of
alien whiteness in geometric rigor
The Antarctic is highest, windest, driest continents
Its topography and dynamics is simpliest on earth
An exercise of reductionism
The iceberg is the microcosm of the Antarctica
Its fragment torn loose from the continents both substance and symbol
within it's ICE the burg contains record of all ICE terrains
As it moves away from the massive ICE it gradually disintegrates
Most burgs last less than two month in an open sea
so your back...
It's just this ...back & forth
But you have to move your ass more
- Do you love it?
- Turn around
Bend over
What time is it?
I don't know
Souldn't have a light?...
That's so attractive
Yeah...
We will save the rest for late
It is Michael Nyman's 60th birthday concert
That was the night she told me she's going back to America.
You looks like a gangster, you like that?
Trying look like a gangster
You look ugly
Trying look ugly
it's just for a year..um..?
Sometimes you have to have faith in people
- You miss me?
- Always
There's only a week before her flight to home
She was like a tourist on holiday In London
she bought souvenirs and Christmas presents
She was happy to be leaving
- Are you ready?
- Yeah!
- One, two, three!
- Heee..Ya
- Ha..ha I like this
- Yeah...
I see in your future.
Hey
The day she left was the first time she invite me to her apartment
She didn't want me to come in the airport mount the station with her
She didn't want any long goodbyes
That you fly over the continet you see the journey of the ice in reverse
The sea, the Iceberg, the see Ice,
the Ice-shelf and the Ice sheet
Each year the Ice inches its way from the heart of the continent
to the see into which it finally melts
It's beautiful!
# Artist: Black Rebel MotorCycle Club 'Love Burns'#
# You might know this one #
# Never thought I'd see her go away #
# She learned I loved her today #
# Never thought I'd see her cry #
# And I learned how to love her today #
# Never thought I'd rather die #
# Then try to keep her #
# by my side #
# Now she's gone love burns inside me #
# Now she's gone love #
# burns inside me #
# Now she's gone love burns inside me #
# Nothing else can hurt us now #
# No loss, our love's been hung on a cross #
# Nothing seems to make a sound #
# And now it's all so clear somehow #
# Nothing really #
# matters now #
# Now we're gone and on our way #
# Now she's gone love burns inside me #
# She cuts my skin and bruise my lips #
# She's everything to me #
# She tears my clothes #
# and burns my eyes #
# She's all I want to see #
# She brings the cold and scars my soul #
# She's heaven sent to me #
# Now she's gone love burns inside me #
# Now she's gone love burns #
# inside me. Now she's gone love #
# burns inside me #
# I never will believe that I left you that way I did #
# kiss my love and wish you #
# go #
# Can kiss my love and wish you go #
# I never will believe that I left you that way I did #
# Now she's gone love burns inside me #
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org