Holy shit! Shit!
It's okay.
We'll be all right.
Okay, it's okay. It's okay.
- Shh. Be cool.
- No, we are far from cool!
What the fuck
is wrong with you?!
Oh, fuck.
What's happening?
She's bleeding. Is she okay?
I... I don't know. I don't know.
Why the fuck is she
bleeding so much?
'Cause she's shot in the fucking face.
What do you think?
Shit!
Hold on, man.
- What the fuck?
- Everybody hold on.
Hold on!
A subtitle made possible by R3V0LV3R.
Hi, Ms. Williams.
Hi. Sorry I'm late.
Don't worry. We're still
waiting on Michael.
Shit. Did someone call him?
No. You want me to?
No. I'll call him.
Hello.
Hi. It's Carley.
Um...
You coming to school?
Oh, shit.
- Yeah.
- Who is it?
Um, all right.
I'll be right there.
Babe, where are you going?
I gotta go.
Where?
It's a group class thing.
Right now?
Come on, Lena.
You're not gonna be
insecure about this, too.
No. I'm not insecure.
Okay. Well, are we
still on for tonight?
Uh, I can't tonight, baby.
Another group?
I got a thing.
Listen, this insecurity thing
is really starting to wear...
Why can't you just tell me
what you're doing tonight?
Why do I have to?
Can't you just trust me?
I gotta go.
See you later.
Wait.
I love you.
Morning, handsome.
Hey, Ms. Brown.
You look ravishing today.
- Today?
- Always.
Uh... Huh. You get
the final word yet?
Nah, not yet.
I'm gonna say
a prayer for you, kid.
Appreciate it.
Need all that I can get.
Don't be late
for school, little man.
Yeah. Yeah, I... I'm going.
What's on your mind, Ray?
I... Look, I know I'm
supposed to be on tonight,
but you think it'd be okay
if I cut out a little early?
Say what?!
Can I cut out
a little early tonight?
How early? I don't know.
Early.
So I gotta stay late and close?
Can I go? Who is she?
Come on, Uncle Duane.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Who's the lucky lady?
Can I go?
Don't hold out on me, man.
You're asking me
for a favor, so...
Who is she?
Her name's Sarah.
Sarah.
Dre!
Whoo!
Ha ha!
Sarah.
That's a nice name.
Go on. I'll see you
after school.
Uh, what about...
Go on. Go on, Ray.
Out the back way. Out the back.
Brother got a .22 out.
What you mean?
Drop that nigger, bro.
Just, like,
rolled up on that ass.
Gonna roll up and shoot
that game and shit.
Ribs ready yet?
Just started the fire.
We open at 11:00.
Hey, come on, bro.
I'm hungry, cuz.
Y'all ain't got
nothin' back there?
Come back later. I'll have
something for you then.
Why don't you go
fetch me some chips,
a couple cokes.
Keep the change.
Let's get out of here.
Fuck is you looking at?
Now, everyone has
to get these exams signed
by a parent or guardian, okay?
Those of you with exceptions
know who you are,
but unfortunately,
some of you will be back
again for another semester,
and some of you will be needing
to go to the front office
to pick up your cap and gown
for graduation next week.
Congratulations.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
I live here. Heh.
You pay rent here,
but you don't
exactly live here.
I forgot my key.
Okay.
I'm leaving him, so...
You took his cat?
Yes.
Can I come in?
Yeah. Yeah, come in.
Come in.
Oh, wow. Okay.
Why?
Well, I just don't think
he deserves the cat.
Like, he doesn't
take care of her.
He never cleans her litter box.
She's always hungry.
No, no, no. I mean with
you and Michael. Why?
He's just...
Nothing's ever
gonna change, you know?
I mean,
he's never gonna change.
There are all these girls,
and they just...
I just feel really stupid.
That's all.
Well, I hate to say
that I told you so.
I just wish I didn't
love him so much.
You need him...
But you wish you
didn't need him so much.
Nobody loves anyone that treats
them that badly. Coffee?
Is that the strongest
thing we have?
At this hour, yeah.
When... when was this?
Last weekend.
I called you, but you were
out with the man-whore.
I'm such an idiot.
Mm-hmm.
Well, you're better off
without him.
I wish I could stay, but I
gotta go to class, so...
No, that's fine.
Just gonna be sitting here,
watching soap operas
and wallowing.
Okay, maybe I should stay.
No, you're fine. Go.
I know. Tonight we'll go out,
and we'll have some fun, and
we'll forget all about it.
Yeah.
I'll call you after class.
Yeah. All right.
Hang in there.
Mom?
Hi, mom.
Where you been?
Boy, where you think I've been?
I don't know.
That's why I asked.
None of your goddamn business
is where I've been,
you little bitch.
Keep that shit down.
I need some sleep.
Where have I been?
Fuck you. Fuck you!
Shit!
- Holy shit.
- Shh.
Be cool. It's okay.
How the fuck is that?
You just shot her
in the fucking face.
Are you out of
your fucking mind, Kevin?
Come on. She was
making a scene.
And what do you think this is?!
What do you think this is?!
It's okay.
Man, shut her the fuck up!
goddamn!
Yo, put that out
of her face, okay?!
You just freaking out!
Chill the fuck out!
Fuck you care about
these bitches?
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
I'm trying to get this
under control, okay,
so sit back and shut the
fuck up for a second.
It's okay. Shh. It's okay. Shh.
We could get her to a hospital.
We need to get her...
What the fuck did I tell you?
Shut the fuck up! God.
" My chick and the cold beer. "
" Come and throw
kegs on me... "
That's it.
" Blow your whole set, "
" niggas try to get
the best of me. "
" Didn't succeed. "
" Tey wound up
in the chesapeake. "
" 20 sucking chests at sea, "
" see, you neglect the beef. "
" Don't disrespect this heat. "
" Somebody, here it come, "
" have a nigga rest in peace. "
" We never left the streets, "
" just nothin' left to eat, "
" so I made
some new connections, "
" to connect the streets. "
" We own that
through the South and the West. "
" Save it all for the get. "
" Nigga, now we get respect. "
" Yeah, we in the 'hood, "
" where the drama take place. "
" So we trying to make moves, "
" so you better make way. "
" You think you crunk
if you wanna, "
" fo' sure, you's a goner. "
" The pills and marijuana, "
" gonna last me to the summer. "
" Yeah, we on the rise,
motherfuckin' 9 to 5. "
Where the fuck are we?
What are you doing?
What, you trying to draw
attention to us?
Fuck that.
Do you see people
bouncing to hip-hop
in this fucking neighborhood?
Turn that shit down.
What? We trying to blend in?
I'm trying to get us the
fuck out of here, okay?
We're in the land of fucking
Mayberry right now,
and you're blasting
dumb-ass music.
Sit back, and turn
that shit down.
All the way down.
Man, what is that?
What?
That Mayfair Huckleberry shit?
From old fucking reruns.
Fuck kind of question is that?
Just sit back and fucking look
for signs for the highway
so we can get this girl
to the hospital.
What? No fucking way.
We're not going
to the fucking hospital.
Okay, what? You want
to let this girl
bleed to death in the
back of the fucking car?
Is that your fucking
plan, genius?
It's better than showing up
with a half-dead chick,
just begging the cops
to bag us.
I ain't about to go to
fucking jail for this shit.
What's going on back there?
Man, sit up!
Will you put the gun down?
How many times
I gotta tell you?
Damn it.
It's okay.
What the fuck are you doing?
I'm just trying
to stop the bleeding.
Just put it down.
Let her bleed.
Let her do it.
You go ahead.
But the court struck
down the death penalty
in Kennedy vs. Louisiana
because it was not
a proportional reaction
to rape,
not because it was
cruel and unusual.
Yes, but the court
explicitly cited
a national consensus
against the death penalty
as a basis for their decision.
A national consensus
in rape cases only,
a premise, by the way,
which the dissenting option
clearly discredited.
The point is there are some
crimes so heinous in nature,
they not only deserve, but they
demand the ultimate punishment.
A punishment that is so
heinous in and of itself
that almost all the Western nations
have outlawed it completely.
Why do you guys think it is
that the U.K.,
Germany, Spain, France
and most of the civilized world
have deemed capital
punishment cruel and unusual?
Because they're wrong.
Welcome, Mr. Hastings.
Please come join your team.
Oh. Sleeping beauty awakens.
Proportionality is
the determining factor,
as was stated in
Kennedy vs. Louisiana.
And the death penalty
as it applies to murder
is completely proportional
and therefore
totally acceptable.
Guys, you're not dealing
with the issue of morality.
If we as a society believe that
it is morally wrong to murder,
then how can we turn around
and murder someone
in the name of morality?
Because it's a bigger
issue than that.
We're talking
about murder here.
The punishment has to be
as serious as the crime.
We have to govern by example.
Someone that needs
to be shown by example
that it's wrong to kill
doesn't deserve to live.
Spoken like the narrow-minded
son of privilege that you are.
Okay, privileged or not,
when you're born into this
world, you're given a ticket,
a free pass that says
you're free to eat,
breathe and pursue whatever
you want in this life,
but there is one thing
that you cannot do.
And if you choose to do it,
you turn in your ticket,
and when you get caught
without a ticket,
you get kicked off the ride.
That's what I'm saying.
Get 'em on up out of here.
Okay, okay. Settle.
Look, we're out of time,
but we're gonna come back
with these same teams
next class, focusing
on the moral issue,
not just legal precedent.
And, Mr. Hastings,
please try to be on time.
Dre.
Hey.
So what happened?
What?
Oh, my God.
I'm so proud of you.
Can't believe it.
I mean, you studied
your ass off
for that thing.
Are you kidding me?
I know. I'm gonna graduate.
- You know?
- I know.
Oh, my God. Okay.
So let's celebrate tonight,
just me and you.
We have to do something.
- I can't.
- What do you mean?
I told the guys that I was
gonna meet up with them.
- What are you doing, Dre?
- What?
What are you doing?
Keisha, come on.
You're better than all that.
Look at how hard
you're working.
Look at where you're
headed, and look at them.
Okay, those are
my family, okay?
But you're not one of them.
They're all I've got, okay?
No, they're not.
Look, I just don't want to
see you throw your life away
for a bunch of gangbangers
who are so busy watching
their own backs,
they can't even see you.
You know I'm not
throwing away my life.
Look at this, right?
- Okay, okay.
- Okay.
Okay, so... so are you
coming tonight?
Keisha, I just told you I...
Andre, you gotta start
making some choices.
You can't keep walking
the middle line,
'cause at some point
you're gonna fall
to one side or the other.
You keep hanging out
with them... Look at me.
You keep hanging out with them,
and one day, you're gonna
get caught in something
that's gonna undo
all that you're doing.
Then it's in God's hands.
I can handle myself, okay?
These guys are from where I'm from.
You know that.
They're not where
you're from, Andre.
They're just where you've been.
I'm gonna call you later, okay?
No, I know.
All right.
Hey, Mussolini.
What's up, flower power?
Nice job today.
If only you were right,
things would have
gone so much better.
Maybe if my teammate wouldn't
have made your point for you.
Eh, he's an idiot.
Oh, he drives me crazy.
Really?
Not like that. Eww.
Are you blushing?
I do not blush.
Oh. That's right.
You a tough girl.
And don't you forget it.
So you coming out tonight?
No, I don't think so.
Um, I got a lot of work to do.
School's almost over.
You should come out,
- have a little fun.
- I can't.
Oh. You're afraid I'm gonna
kick your ass in darts again.
What?! That was me
kicking your ass
in darts last weekend.
That's not how I remember it.
I think you're trying to appeal
to my competitive nature.
Is it working?
A little bit.
All right.
- You did it.
- I did.
You are bold, girl.
When you know what you want,
you just gotta
go for it, right?
Hey, guys.
Hey, Carley. Hi.
Shit. Girl, you got
more books in your arms
than I've read all year.
Carley didn't get the memo
that school's almost out.
If the memo you're talking
about is a degree
that reads summa cum laude,
then, no, I haven't
gotten it. Yet.
Are you still working
on your thesis?
Day and night, yep.
Gotta make daddy proud, right?
No wonder you never get laid.
I am single by choice.
That's her line, and
she's sticking to it.
Oh, is this your show?
Yeah. It's tomorrow,
so you better be there.
No excuses about a
thesis or some bullshit.
That is not true!
What happened?
I never should have gotten
out of bed this morning.
I saw you running out
of the student center.
I...
God.
What's going on?
Michael was in there
with some girl.
Already.
Why didn't you say something?
I...
What... I don't know.
And I'm just
completely paralyzed
by the thought of him
not loving me.
Hey. Come here.
Get your hands up!
Get down!
- Come on, man!
- Get down!
Get off me, man.
I didn't even do anything!
Shut the fuck up.
What is this shit?
What the fuck you think it is?
Books, man.
Fuck I think it is? You
gonna get smart with me?
Shut the fuck up!
You little smartass.
Where you going?
I'm going home, man.
Home? Where you live?
I live up the block, man.
This is bullshit.
I didn't even do anything.
Get off me.
We didn't ask you did you
do something, smartass.
Get the fuck off me, man.
He's clean.
Let his bitch ass up.
Get off the streets, boy.
Yaah!
Where's your mom?
Sleeping.
Where are your manners, boy?
Get out of my way.
Come on, man. She's sleeping.
And what are you gonna do, boy?
You gonna stop me?
Why don't you go out and play
with your little boyfriends.
Heh. Go.
Hi.
What?
Tokyo?
Well, did you tell them that...
Yeah. Everything else
is going really good.
I haven't really talked
to missy in a while, dad.
Dad, um...
It would really mean a
lot to me if there was...
If there was any way that you
could... you would come here,
because, you know, I only
graduate once, and...
Well, law school
is a long way away.
Um...
Dad, you've never
even visited me
this entire time
that I was here,
so, I mean, is this meeting
really that important?
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
No, I totally understand.
Okay. Okay, call me back.
Fuck this.
Max. Hey.
Heh. You feel like getting your
ass kicked at darts again?
It is so on.
No. Nah, nah.
You're gonna have to
rewind it, run that back.
Ain't no way
it went down like that.
Nigger, I ain't bullshitting.
There I was minding
my own fucking business,
and she walk up butt-ass naked.
- No drawers at all?
- No drawers.
Damn, boy, why shit like
this don't happen to me?
'Cause you ain't
got no swag, nigger.
Swag. You know it.
- I got swag.
- What... Your girl just a ho.
Yo, what up, wigger?
What you doing round here?
Yeah, ain't you supposed
to be in school?
School is for pussies.
Why don't you go grab
me a beer or something?
Why don't you go
grab yourself one?
Listen to the little tough man.
Man, why you always
calling me little,
like I'm 12 or some shit?
'Cause you look like
you 12 or some shit.
- I'm not a kid.
- Is that right?
Just as tough as any
of you motherfuckers.
Oh, you want to be
a gangster now, huh?
Yeah, y'all just won't let
me in 'cause I'm white.
Hey, that's bullshit.
See, we an equal-opportunity
street crew around here.
And I know Dre daddy
a cracker just like you,
and, see, Keith, he got some
chink in him, don't you, Keith?
Shut the fuck up.
So then why not let me in?
Yo, this ain't playtime, man.
This shit here is for real.
Yo, J.J., what about Dre?
Fuck Dre.
Go on.
Another time.
Pshew pshew.
25 points.
What?
You know, shooting a cop.
25 points.
Damn. I mean, I think that
at least be like 50 points
or something like that,
bro. Come on.
Nah, nigger, 25.
You trippin', man.
Hell you thinking 'bout?
So that's it?
I'm in now?
Nah. That's just us
having some fun
whupping your ass.
Come on, man.
What do I gotta do?
Why don't you go steal us
a car or something, bro?
Yeah. Matter of fact,
why don't you go steal
your daddy's ride?
He's not my fucking daddy.
Look, you ain't got no daddy,
so whoever fucking
your mama right now,
not including myself, that's
your daddy right now.
Man, fuck you!
Yo, ease up. Ease the fuck off.
Okay, okay,
go get your
not-your-daddy's car then.
And then I'm in?
Patience, kid.
One step at a time, homeboy.
I don't know if I can.
Oh, you so gangster now, you can't
even go get your daddy keys?
I could get 'em!
Get the fuck out of here. Go.
Hey, yo, your boy wilding, bro.
You not gonna let him in
for real, is you, brah?
Hell, nah.
Just fucking with
the white boy.
Pow pow!
50 points.
How's she doing?
She really needs
to get to a hospital.
What's your name?
Carley.
Carley, you know where we are?
Yeah.
You want to let us know how
to get out of here, Carley?
I don't know.
What do you mean
you don't know?
You're gonna tell us how to
get the fuck out of here.
Would you shut
the fuck up, Kevin?
Seriously, Carley, we
don't want to get this
any more fucked up than
it already is, do we?
Are you gonna take her
to a hospital?
I need you to tell me
where the highway is.
She really needs
to get to a doctor.
That wasn't my fucking
question, now, was it?
I don't think
that had anything to do
with what you were asking her.
Carley.
Just, um... Just go up here.
If you keep going straight,
the highway's on the left.
You'll see the sign
to the hospital.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What the fuck we listening
to this bitch for?
She don't know shit.
Why you acting like you know
when you don't know shit?
You know, don't you, Carley?
Yeah. It's... It's up here.
You best not be messing
with us, girl.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, Carley.
Yeah.
Dumb bitch.
Man, look for the signs.
Man, I ain't ever
seen any of this shit.
I don't know
where the fuck we are.
I'm supposed to be
at dad's right now.
" ...ball, motherf..."
" Test, motherf..."
" Club up, ah, yeah,
'bout to clown. "
" On the town. "
" Start off at the shot
that came down. "
" I got you up always. "
" I got you crunk always. "
" I got the dance club. "
" Club up all day... "
Man, why they gotta do that?
What?
Cut off the lyrics of the song.
It's the radio.
I know, but...
He chose that word to
express himself, you know.
They shouldn't be able
to do that, man.
They just trying to keep the
track from being heard.
Hey, Kevin, you know what?
Then buy the fucking cd,
and you get all the
self-expression you want.
I will, fool.
Seriously, turn this shit down.
Man, why?
'Cause I'm trying
to fucking think, okay?
You got me in this
fucking situation.
Turn this shit down.
I'm trying to think.
I don't know why I have to tell
you so many fucking times.
I turned it down, all right?
Come on.
I really just want to go home.
You've had the shittiest
day on record.
I'm not gonna let it
end this way.
You need a beer.
Can't believe I wrecked my car.
Oh, you should have
seen the tree.
Come on. Let's go.
He's gonna show up here at
some point with that girl.
Exactly.
This should be fun.
Rach, what are
you talking about?
We're gonna go bust
Mike's next date.
- No, we're not.
- Yes.
- Yes. It's payback time.
Please. Please, oh...
You know, I have such a
bad feeling about this.
Shit.
I should have walked.
Fuck this.
Dre, what the fuck you doing?
I'm taking her to the hospital.
You're gonna make us go to
prison for the rest of our lives
just so she can go
to the hospital?
I'm not letting her
die in here! You hear me?
She's gonna die anyway, Dre.
Not gonna let her die
in the fucking car!
Well, then let's
fucking dump her.
We'll ice her fucking friend, too.
My God.
Just let us out right here.
I swear to God you won't...
Shut up, bitch!
What the fuck...
What the fuck are you doing?
What the fuck did you do, girl?
What the fuck is this?
- Ah, shit.
- What?
Shit.
Man, what?
It's a cop, man.
Is it?
Oh, motherfucking bitch.
Shit!
Fuck! Oh, shit.
Okay. Shit.
Carley, you fucked up!
You fucked up!
You just gotta floor it, Dre.
Oh, yeah.
That's a fucking good idea,
have a fucking full-on
police chase right now.
You can't get pulled over, man.
Look, we're not being
pulled over right now.
They just behind us,
so calm down.
Don't do anything
else stupid, bitch.
- God.
- I trusted you!
Fuck! Fuck!
I swear to God. Oh, God.
Kevin, stop looking back there.
God.
Shit.
Stop looking back there.
What the fuck
is this cop doing?
He's just creeping on us, man.
Man, he's just
creeping there, Dre.
I'm gonna turn off up here.
Fuck, man.
Moment of truth.
Ah, fuck.
We can still go back.
How the fuck did we get here?
Ray!
Got food stacking up here.
Sorry. Sorry, man.
Ray!
Yeah?
You can go now.
Really?
Yeah.
Thanks, man.
Hey, hey, little man,
little man.
Uh...
So you like this girl, huh?
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
You gonna kiss her?
I don't know, Uncle Duane.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
I hope so.
You hope so?
Okay. Okay.
You be a gentleman now.
Don't kiss her so hard
you scare her.
Treat her with respect, and
she'll want to kiss you back.
Know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Yeah, I got it.
All right.
Little man Ray.
Sarah. Ha ha.
Guess I need to call
you big man now, huh?
Yeah.
Go on. Have fun.
Hey, mama.
Go easy on the cologne now.
Gotcha.
I believe he gonna get it.
What you think?
Man, he gonna do it, too.
Look at that white boy.
Hey, Rodger, grab me a beer.
What the fuck I look like,
Geoffrey from the Fresh
Prince or some shit?
Yeah, nigger.
Look, look, you really do.
Little bit, you do.
Get the fuck out.
Yo, what up, Dre?
How was school, dear?
Fuck you, Rodg.
Look. Oreo came to hang
with the niggers.
Why, 'cause I'm the only one
of y'all motherfuckers
getting an education?
Hey, we educating our
motherfucking self
around here, partner.
Oh, yeah, Rodg?
That's... that theory
working for y'all?
Yeah. It's
working out real good.
I got my niggers,
and I got respect.
Think your pussy ass
commanding respect
packing Dr. Seuss
in your book bag?
What, you think
that thing on your waistband
- gives you respect, J.J.?
- Yeah.
This piece gives me power,
and power gets me respect.
Fear and respect are two
different things, brother.
Let me learn you
something, nigger.
You may think you something
special, but you ain't shit.
In the eyes of the world,
there ain't no difference
between you and me.
So no matter what you do,
they ain't gonna
see you as nothin'
but a gangbanger,
homeboy. Believe that.
Hey, y'all got
some beers around here?
Somebody get this pussy-ass
schoolboy a beer.
Hey, where Kevin off to?
Where you got him going, J.J.?
Told him to go steal
his daddy's ride.
You know that's not
his daddy. Come on, man.
Whatever.
So, what? Y'all
letting him in now?
He's gotta do
his initiation, bro.
J.J., I thought
we talked about this.
He's too young.
Man, he's 16.
Yeah, but he's not like us.
Oh, now you and me
alike in some way.
- I just thought we had a deal man.
- Fuck your deal, man.
His big cousin wasn't
here to protect him.
He was off at nursery school,
and here we were.
Hey, let me tear up
that black, nigger.
Hey, didn't you
smoke a cigarette?
Walking cancer-ass nigger.
Fuck you.
Now will you get me a beer?
No, man.
You know, Dre,
I'm getting hungry.
What?
I'm hungry.
How the fuck are you thinking
about food right now?
I don't know. I'm just hungry.
Okay, man, I'm looking for a way for
us to get the fuck out of here.
I told you
to go left back there.
You know, Dre, seriously,
let's find a place.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
I'll get directions.
I'll be in and out real quick.
I'll just get me a
Slushee or something.
A Slushee?
Are you out of
your fucking mind?
That's so nasty.
All right, maybe a corn dog.
Craving a corn dog
I could actually understand.
At least it's got some
food value or something.
What we gotta find's
a place we know.
Yo, pull in up there.
We're not stopping, Kevin.
You don't know where
the fuck we are.
I'll get directions.
Okay, man, if I pull in there,
you gotta be in and out.
That's it,
and just get directions.
All right.
I'm fucking serious, Kevin.
I heard you.
All right.
Hey, yo, pull up closer so I
don't have to walk so far.
Go get directions,
okay, and hurry up.
Hey, you want something?
Just go. Go.
You okay?
You don't have to do this.
You can make this stop.
Nah, I can't.
Yes, you can.
You can. You can just...
just let me take her
to a hospital.
Please.
Look, it's a situation,
but I'm gonna handle it.
You guys are gonna
be okay. Just...
Take care of her, okay?
I can handle it. It'll be fine.
He looks up to you.
I swear to God
if you just let us go,
I won't say anything. You
won't get caught. I promise.
Yeah, why would you do that?
Because...
I think you got
caught in something
that you don't know
how to get out of,
and I think you're just
trying to save your friend.
And I'm just trying
to save mine.
Please don't let her die.
You have some I.D., son?
Well, you're gonna need some I.D.
To buy alcohol.
I'm 21.
Yeah, well,
I'm still gonna need
to see some I.D.
What are you laughing at?
Do you want the rest
of the items?
Son...
I'm not your son.
Just shut up.
Shut the... get out, son.
Son, I can't sell you
beer without proper I.D.
- I'm not your son.
- Do you want...
...some of this, son?
No! Get out!
Stop! Get off her!
What do you think
you're doing? Get... son!
Kevin, get out! You
piece of shit!
You want some of this?
Son, what did I just say?
Get out. This is
not your business.
I'll give you some of this.
Come on!
Put the shit in the bag.
O... okay, son. Just take it easy.
Put the shit in the bag!
Let's take it easy.
Let's take it easy, all right?
Okay. All right.
Look at me!
Kevin, get out. You
piece of shit!
Rodney, get the...
stay the fuck out of here.
Rodney... you, shut up!
Get back here!
Hurry up, old man!
Just leave, okay, son, please.
I'm not your fucking son!
Check your boy out.
He all geeked up,
like fixing to go wild.
He ain't about to do nothin'.
I need a gun.
What the fuck
you gonna do, nigger?
What's going on, Kevin?
I need a gun.
Why don't we
start you off with this.
It'll get the job done.
Kevin. Kevin! Kevin!
Shut the fucking door!
Shut the door! Come on!
Carley, you shut the door!
Get in the car!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
What happened?
I didn't feel like paying.
You didn't feel like it?
I mean, I was...
So I'm standing there
with all this shit,
and I realize,
fuck, I got a gun,
so I ain't gotta pay.
Did you shoot
the fucking clerk?
Nah.
I just scared him, though.
You want some of these?
No.
I got a 40 in here.
Hey, girl, you want
some of these?
So this guy's all "son"
this and "son" that,
and I ain't
no fucking son of yours.
Anyone else in there?
No.
You are a fucking fool.
Fucking fool! You know that?
I'm sitting there, trying
to pull damage control,
and you'll fuck up, and you
gonna pull some shit like this?
You should have brought us to
the fucking police station
and just fucking
throw cuffs on us.
Dre, it's just
some munchies, man.
You think this is a joke?
That clerk saw you.
He saw your face.
He heard your voice.
He got you on camera.
I bet you he saw
the fucking car.
Now he's gonna call
the fucking cops.
They're gonna be
looking for us.
Then what? You know
what happens then?
You know what happens
if we get caught?
Look behind you.
It's not a fucking joke.
I knew this was a bad idea.
I knew this was
a fucking bad idea.
I'm trying to have your back.
Why couldn't you
just go in there
like a regular
fucking customer,
in and out, that's it?
Just 'cause
you got a fucking gun
doesn't mean you
gotta fucking use it.
We're going away for the rest of our life.
You know that?
Dre, I didn't
kill him or nothing.
Well, you should have
fucking killed him.
You should have fucking
finished the job,
finished it like a man.
Dre, we cool. It's...
We're not fucking cool,
Kevin! Are you serious?!
We gotta ditch the car.
It's okay, man. I mean,
we'll tell J.J., a... and
he'll have to let me in,
and it's gonna be okay.
Shut the fuck up, okay.
I don't want to hear
another word out of you.
Dre, I'm sorry.
I'm done
hearing you talk, Kevin.
Potty training's over.
I'm not your fucking
friend right now.
- Hey, hold up.
- I'm not gonna take it anymore.
- What happened?
- I'm gonna fucking kill him.
Come on, man.
No, Dre, I'm gonna put a
bullet in his fucking head.
Hey! What?
It ain't worth it, man, okay?
What do you know?
I know you're gonna go to jail
for the rest
of your life, okay,
over some asshole your
mom brought home, okay?
Let's think about it
for a second.
Can you just
take a walk with me?
Kevin, take a walk with me.
You trust me, right?
Yeah, all right.
Let's do this.
I don't know about this whole
"winner buys the drinks" thing.
Well, it's the least
you two can do
after making me look
like a chump over there.
It's all in the wrist, baby.
- Is that right?
- Uh-huh.
Whoa. Tequila shots already?
Mm. I like to think of these
as little shots of courage.
Courage for what?
Nothing. We're
aborting the mission.
Oh, I think someone
needs another shot.
Um, Michael has
a date here tonight.
- What?
- I thought you two were still together.
- Yeah, me, too.
- What an asshole.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Speak of the devil.
Is that the girl?
Yeah.
He's such an ass.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Can we just go?
No. No, you have
to say something.
Seriously,
now's the time. Go on.
Taking the reins
of life, baby. I love it.
- So does that mean he's single now?
- Jill.
- I'm kidding.
- Yeah.
Seriously, I'm kidding.
Well, I'm gonna go see if
I can find some sucker
to try to take me on in darts.
I'll take that challenge.
Rach, I'm kind of ready to go.
Oh, you can't go.
The night's just
getting started.
Yeah, and... and I'm driving,
so if I'm staying,
you're staying.
My God. I wrecked my car.
Please just have some mercy.
You wrecked your car?
It's been a long day.
Well, I can take you home.
Really?
Yeah. No, I think I've squeezed
all the fun I can
out of this place.
- No. Stay.
- No...
No, I'm taking the reins, baby.
Touch.
All right,
well, go easy on him.
He's already had his ass
handed to him once tonight.
I'll see you at home?
Yeah. You have your keys?
Yes. I think.
Bye, guys.
Have a good night. Bye.
Oh, Jesus, help me, please.
It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
I want to go home.
Oh, God.
Gonna be all right.
Please, help me.
Please help me.
" Open up the shells. "
" Put your 5-o out. "
" No mercy, no pleas, "
" let my trigger finger
squeeze. "
" My money's on my mind, "
" and I'll pay
to make you bleed, "
" 'cause I sneak a... "
Shh. Shh.
Hey. Hey.
Shh.
Oh, God.
Are you okay?
Hey. Hey, wake up.
Hey. Hey.
Shh.
Shit.
What are you doing?
I gotta think.
Shit.
You want to have sex?
No.
Take your pants off.
No. No. No.
I'm not fucking around, girl!
Come on!
O... okay.
Please don't do this.
Now, bitch.
I cannot wait
for this day to be over.
I hear you.
Oh, shit, I forgot my credit
card back at the bar.
I'll wait here.
I'll be right back.
Where the fuck are we?
By the college.
What are we doing over here?
Come on, man. I'll show you.
It's a good place
right up here.
I'm hungry.
It'll be a'ight.
Hey.
Got it?
Yep. Let's get out of here.
Hey, thanks for
rescuing me back there.
No problem.
You sure you're okay?
Heh.
Yeah.
You been here before?
Yeah, man, a few times.
I mean, I know it's
for the best, so...
You deserve a lot better,
seriously.
I just can't believe
it took me so long.
- Hey, Dre...
- Hmm?
You ever kill someone?
Hell, no.
Come on, man. You know
better than that.
Can you believe we're
about to graduate?
God, I know.
You're going
to law school, right?
Yeah, that's the plan.
You don't sound
too stoked about that.
I was, but I don't know.
People tell you
your whole life you're gonna
be this certain thing,
and then somehow you just
one day end up becoming it.
J.J.'S killed lots of people.
Yeah, well, J.J.'S out of his damn mind.
You know that.
He's a real fucking gangster.
Yes, he is.
Hey, about J.J.
And those guys...
Yeah?
You joining, man?
J.J. Said if
I steal a car, I'm in.
It's about fucking time, too.
I don't know why they
didn't let me in before.
Kev, they didn't
let you in before
'cause I asked them not to.
What?
I didn't want to see you
get caught up
in something that you
have no idea about.
So you don't want
to be a lawyer?
I don't know.
In a way, I guess I've never
really thought about it before.
Why would you do
something like that?
I was just trying to
protect you. That's it.
You're not
my fucking daddy, Dre!
Yeah, I know that, but I'm
the closest thing you got
to family, okay?
Man, fuck you!
All I was trying to do
was protect you.
Yeah? Protect me from what?
From... from what? From all this.
From everything. From yourself.
Fuck this! This is bullshit!
Come on. Kevin! Kevin, hold on!
Well, what would you do?
I would just pack up
my car and just go.
Where would you go?
Anywhere.
Come on! Hurry up, girl.
Please don't do this.
What the fuck are you doing?
Give me the fucking gun.
Give me the gun!
A'ight!
Everybody out!
Everybody out.
What are you doing?
I know what I got to do now.
I'm finishing it.
Get out!
Dre, wait up!
Hold up!
This is you.
This is you, Kevin.
You next to her.
Dre, don't do this, please.
What'd you call me?
Shit.
Get down next to her!
Next to her on your knees!
What are you gonna do, Dre?
We're finishing it.
We're gonna finish
what you started.
Face the wall!
Put your face against the wall.
Face up against the wall.
Please don't do this.
Turn your face to the wall!
Okay.
Ah, jeez.
Can I do it?
What?
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
You think this is fun?
You think this
is some gangster shit?
You want to shoot somebody?
I should fucking shoot you!
Come on, Dre. Chill out.
"Chill out!" "Chill out!"
I worked my whole life...
My whole life
to not be like this,
for you not to get like this!
Look at us now,
exactly what
they thought we'd be!
Kevin, what do you think's
gonna happen after this?
Look at these girls!
Look at them. Look at us.
It's over.
It's all fucking over.
I got a gun in my hand 'cause I
don't see any other way out!
It's all right, man.
If we kill 'em, no
one'll know it was us.
Ah, Kevin...
We'll know.
I'm outta here.
I'm getting outta here.
Where the fuck are you going?
Just go. No.
Just go.
I can't leave you here.
Okay. Okay, just stay here.
I'll be right back.
Where the fuck you going?
You can't leave!
They'll go to the cops! Shit.
Hey, girl!
- This is bullshit!
- You're not hearing what I'm trying
- to say to you, okay?
- Just shut up!
Stop for a second.
Listen to me.
Get away from me!
You're not hearing what
I'm trying to say to you.
Stop. Listen to me
for a second.
Kevin, you don't understand
what I'm trying to tell you.
I... I was just trying to
protect you, that's it. Okay?
I'm gonna Jack
this car right here.
Kevin, what are you doing?
I'm gonna do
my initiation right now!
Kevin, come on.
Let's just get
out of here, okay?
Kevin, come on! Kevin!
Let's get out of here, okay?
- God.
- Kevin, stop!
Kevin, get off the car!
- You know there's an alarm on that car!
- Let's...
man, fuck that shit!
Oh, my God.
Give me the keys, bitch!
- Kevin, stop, okay?
- Give me the keys!
- Kevin, put the gun down!
- Shut up!
Let's just go, Kevin!
What are you doing?
- Shut up!
- Kevin!
Purse! Give me your purse!
Get in the fucking car!
Get in the car!
Kevin, what are you doing?
- Get in the fucking car!
- Kevin, put it down.
Get in the car!
Get in the fucking car!
- Take whatever you want. Please.
- Drive.
Take it. Take it.
Just don't hit me.
- Get in the car!
- Just don't do this.
Kevin! Please don't do this!
Come on.
Get in the fucking car.
Please, please don't do this.
Shut the fuck up!
- Take whatever you want.
- Shit.
Get in! Let's go! Come on.
Get in the car! Shut up!
- Please!
- Kevin, what are you doing?
- Now!
- Kevin, put the gun down!
Shut the fuck up!
- Kevin!
- Please don't... help!
- Kevin, stop!
- Get in the fucking car!
Help!
No!
What the fuck
did you do, Kevin?
What the fuck did you do?
Get in the car! Get in the car!
Oh, shit.
Shit.
Fuck.
Come on, man.
Dre...
You know I had to do it.
Let's just get out of here.
Let's go find J.J., man.
You hear me?
You have any idea
what's going on?
You don't tell J.J. Anything.
Nothing, you hear me?
This is really bad.
You know that?
Really fucking bad right now.
Kevin...
That place
I took you to today...
That's some place I go to...
I wanted to show you
that there's... there's...
There's... there's a place
you can escape.
Hey, listen, just don't say anything
to anybody about tonight, okay?
It's a different world.
Those girls aren't
from this world.
We're in a lot of trouble.
You know that?
Go home, Kevin.
Go home.
And don't say anything
to anyone. You hear me?
It's in God's hands now.
Help! Help me! Help me!
I need help!
Help!
Please, I need help! Please!
Oh, my God.
Hello. Help me.
Help me. Help me, please.
No! No! No!
No!
No, no.
No, no, no.
Oh, my God.
Please.
Please, somebody help me!
Please!
Oh, my God.
Help me! Please!
Somebody help me!
Holy shit.
W-what happened to you?
What happened?
Come on. Come on. Get... get in.
L.. let me help you.
Come on. Come on.
Get in, lady.
Come on, lady. Let me help you.
Come on. Let me help.
What happened?
They shot me.
What's your name, sweetie?
Where are you taking me?
There's a hospital nearby.
They'll take care of you.
W... what's your name?
Carley.
All right.
Oh, my God. Lena.
What happened? What happened?
Who's Lena?
They took her to the tunnel,
and then she's just...
She's waiting there.
We have to go back.
We have to go back!
No. We... we cannot go back!
When we get to
the hospital, we'll...
No, no, she...
No, we'll send someone
to go find her. You...
we got to get you taken
care of, all right?
Carley, can you hear me?
Carley?
She graduates in two weeks.
She's probably just waiting
there like I told her.
I promise we'll go back
to find her, all right?
We'll find your friend.
Look, h...hold this up
for me, sweetie.
Hold that... hold that up.
Okay. That's it.
Carley, stay with me.
Stay with me.
Look at me, Carley. Carley!
Somebody's been shot!
Help!
That's it. That's it now.
It's all right.
Okay, come on.
Somebody's been shot!
Hurry up!
Somebody come!
All right,
what have we got here?
- She was shot in the head.
- Lay your head down, ma'am.
- I don't know how many times.
- Who are you?
I found her in the streets.
She... she was
wandering the streets.
What's your name, honey?
Carley Mitchell.
She had a friend with her.
She's in the tunnel.
She said she was in a tunnel.
All right. You know what, sir?
We can take it from here.
- What?
- No, no, no, go with me.
- I'm... I...
- Please don't...
Carley. Don't leave me!
I'll be right here!
I'm sure the police
want to speak with you.
No! Carley!
I'll be right here!
I ain't going nowhere.
Where exactly was she
when you found her?
I saw her wandering on Jett
not far from the tracks.
She give you any details
about what happened?
Nah. Well, it seemed like,
uh, they were in her car,
and, um, she said
her friend was with her,
and they left her
in... in a tunnel.
She tell you anything
about who they were?
Nah.
You didn't ask?
Well, I was kind of focused on
getting her to the hospital.
She'd been shot in the head.
Where were you going when
you encountered the victim?
What?
This receipt has the girl
leaving a bar called the tavern
approximately 96 minutes
before she was admitted.
Were you anywhere
within that vicinity?
No. I told you I saw her
running in the street.
Where were you going?
I was headed home.
Where's that?
I live on Elizabeth Avenue.
Where were you coming from?
I have a restaurant.
I run a barbecue place
in the neighborhood.
I was coming from there.
Anybody see you there?
What kind
of a question is that?
- What you mean...
- Just answer the question, sir,
or we can do this
down at the station.
My customers. My
customers saw me there.
- You know any of their names?
- What, all of them?
Does anybody work with you?
My nephew,
but he left early, so I closed.
We're gonna need his name
and contact information.
Heh. Shit.
We'll be in touch.
Dr. Bradley, 2744.
Hey, little man.
Ray? Yeah, it's me.
Oh, uh...
I didn't mean to bother
you on your date.
It's almost curfew.
You know that, right?
Nah, nah.
I'm not home yet. Uh...
Just running a little late.
Nah. Uh, just, uh...
just helping a friend.
Yeah, okay, no.
I was just checking in.
You get home safe, okay?
Yeah, all right.
Ray?
Um...
You're my heart.
You know that, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, you...
you be safe, all right?
All right, yeah. Okay.
All right, bye. Yeah.
Dr. Gateau to the pharmacy.
Hi.
Hey.
I'm... I'm Duane.
I... I brought you here.
Where's Lena?
Um...
Hey, you... you might want to...
No, no. Lay back. Come on.
Is she okay?
Look, y... you got really lucky.
They say the bullets
shattered in your skull,
d.. didn't even
get to your brain, so...
Where's Lena?
They found her in the
tunnel, like you said.
She didn't make it.
I'm... I'm sorry.
No. No, she was... she was okay.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
I left her there!
- I left...
- A.. all right...
Oh, my God!
No! No!
I'm... I'm sorry.
Oh, no!
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
No! God!
All right.
All right, all right,
I... I got you. I got you.
I got you. I got you.
Let's go, Riggs.
Hands on the wall.
Okay.
Inmate name?
Um...
Who are you here to see, honey?
Andre Riggs.
Down the hall.
Through the doors.
Hi.
I heard about your cousin.
They sent me a letter
to tell me that he died.
Yeah, it happened
in the yard. He, um...
he got what was coming to him.
I'm leaving Georgia,
but they want me to
put a statement on file
for when you're up for parole.
So, um...
I have to do this to... to know
what I'm gonna tell them.
I've thought about this
moment a thousand times...
About what I'd say to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I've tried to forgive you.
Everybody says that you have
to try to forgive and move on,
but what people
don't understand
is that I can't move on.
I see you every time
I close my eyes.
I go to sleep at night.
You took something away
from me that night,
that I will never get back.
I hate you. I hate you.
I hate you for what you did.
I hate you for letting her die.
You could have stopped
it, and you didn't!
I saw you... Look at me!
Look at me!
I saw your eyes that night,
and you didn't have to let
it happen, and you did. Why?
I don't know.
Bullshit!
I was weak.
You're a monster.
Somewhere that night,
I got lost.
I let my fear take over.
I was...
I became everything
I vowed not to be.
I was weak.
And I'd do anything...
I mean anything...
Anything to take it back...
Well, you can't. I know.
You made your choice
that night...
And I can't change that,
but I'm gonna make my choice.
I'm gonna live my life.
I'm gonna show you
the same humanity
that I wish you
would have shown me.
You don't deserve to live in
the same world that I do...
But your life is
not mine to take...
Just like Lena's wasn't yours.
I pray to God you
don't get lost again.
I'm so sorry.
I am.
" How did I get here? "
Step in the cell.
" I can't feel your heart. "
" Ohh, ohh. "
" Holding "
" Feeling blue, "
" around you, hold on. "