Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
(Speaking In A Girlish, Dreamy Voice)
Someone is here.
Not closely.
Not willingly.
I feel a holding back.
What's the trouble, Henry?
(In Deep Male Voice)
Too many memories, too much pain.
Too... much... sorrow.
(In High Voice)
Whoever is there with you,
tell them to speak up, Henry.
Tell them to come closer.
(Woman 2) I think I know
who it is, Madame Blanche.
I think I know what's bothering her.
(In High Voice) Her, is it?
Never you mind, Miss Rainbird.
I won't have you doing
Henry's work for him.
(Moaning, Gasping)
Now, let's have it, my love.
That's why we're here tonight.
To help my friend be rid of her torment.
She has a right to rest her weary head
on a pillow each night
and sleep the peaceful
sleep of the angels.
H-How did you know
about my troubled sleep?
Who told you?
Her nights cannot
go on like this much longer.
L-I never told a soul
about my nightmares.
- How could you -
- Who is this person who arrives
in our presence tonight,
but does not dare to come close to us?
It's her. Its my sister, Harriet.
- It must be.
- (Henry's Voice) She stays her distance,
Julia Rainbird, for she does not feel
your love or your kindness yet.
There is selfishness where you are.
I've had all I can take from her.
Night after night, coming into my dreams.
Whining, complaining,
trying to make me feel guilty,
as though I need her
to tell me right from wrong.
Tell her I know what has to be done.
I've been wanting to do it for a year.
But it is I, Julia Rainbird,
who has made the decision.
(Sighing)
I don't need her to goad me on!
They're making me ill
with their ugly words in my ugly dreams.
Tell her to stop it,
to go away and leave me alone.
(Stammering) Oh, no. No, no.
Don't let her go!
- Don't let her go away.
- Harriet?
Harriet, stay with us, Harriet.
Your sister wants to speak to you now,
from the depths of her soul.
(Wailing, Howling)
- What's wrong? What is it?
- (Wailing Continues)
She says, "I've waited so long
to hear from you, Julia."
"I've been so unhappy without you."
It is you, Harriet.
Oh, I'm so sorry!
L-I should never have made you do it.
Oh, it's all past now.
But I'll do what I can to make up for it.
If he's still alive, I'll find your son.
And I'll take him
in my arms and love him
as if I were you, my poor Harriet.
And I'll - I'll make him one of us.
And give him everything. Everything!
(Whispering) Far away.
So far, far away.
Bu-But I need her. I need her help.
I can't do it alone.
You see, I need her memory.
It's over 40 years ago, and I don't know
where the child was taken
or who it was given to.
I don't know
where he is now or who he is.
(ln Henry's Voice)
The true measure of Julia Rainbird's love
lies in what she does now,
with your help, of course, and mine,
and that of the dear, departed one
who has drifted so far from us.
(In Normal Voice) We understand him.
Don't we, Miss Rainbird?
Oh, yes. Yes, I do.
I'm willing to do anything. Anything at all.
(In Henry's Voice)
In the end, there will be happiness.
From the tears of the past,
the desert of the heart will bloom.
Goodbye, Julia Rainbird!
Goodbye, Blanche.
(Gasps)
(Softly) Goodbye.
- (Moans)
- Madame Blanche! Are you alright?
Oh. It was - (Clears Throat, Noisily)
What in the world's been going on here?
I feel as though
I've been properly done over.
- Don't you remember what happened?
- Mm-mm.
Not the details, Miss Rainbird,
only the gist, if you know what I mean.
Suppose you give me the gist of it.
(Blows Nose)
Oh well, I wonder - (Gasps)
Could I trouble you
for a sip of something? Ju-Just -
Oh, of course. What would you like?
Oh, a double shot of anyth-
- A spot of that sherry might be nice.
- Oh, yes. Of course.
(Sniffles) Thank you.
(Clock Chiming Quarter-Hour)
Now, tell me
what you remember of the seance.
- In a nutshell?
- Please.
Well - (Clears Throat)
About 40 years ago,
you arranged to have
your sister Harriet's baby
given away without a trace.
And now your bad dreams
and troubled conscience tell you
to find the grown-up person,
take him into the family
and bestow your wealth on him.
- Excellent.
- Thank you.
And why did I force my sister
to give the child away?
I guess the kid was a -
illegitimate, Miss Rainbird.
I don't want you
to think me a puritan, Madame Blanche.
But 40 years ago, an unmarried mother
was not the commonplace
it is nowadays.
And in a family like ours,
a scandal had to be
covered up at all costs.
I understand.
And I'm still sufficiently old-fashioned,
and sufficiently protective
of the Rainbird name,
to want to seek the missing heir
in a private and secret fashion,
rather than go to detective agencies
and put notices in the newspapers.
A most wise decision, Miss Rainbird.
Well, now, suppose we get to the reason
for my sending for you.
I'm 78 years of age.
I would like to go to my grave
with a quiet conscience.
Particularly as I know
that my only heir is out there somewhere,
deprived by my acts
of his true Rainbird name.
Will you help me with your powers?
If in your heart you believe that I can,
then I owe it to both of us to try,
Miss Rainbird.
No, I'm too old for trying.
I've only time enough left for results!
Find him for me, Madame Blanche.
Use your spirit-control, your "Henry".
Get through to my sister.
Find her son,
whoever he is, wherever he is,
and I'll pay you $10,000.
Te-
(Sighs)
Only if you genuinely wish to,
Miss Rainbird.
But let's not think of this
as a payment to me.
There are many causes dear to my heart,
which need all the charity
the world can spare.
You've no idea how refreshing
it is for a woman of my wealth
to find someone
who has so little use for money.
Thank you.
(Sighs) Well, now, I regard
our arrangement as completed.
I - It's my bedtime.
I must take leave
of your delightful company.
This has been a most memorable
evening for me, Miss Rainbird.
See to it that you
make it a rewarding one.
At the risk of repeating myself,
I hope you will not forget
that nobody, absolutely no-one,
should know of our search.
The Rainbird name must be protected.
My jaw is locked.
On that note, I will say goodbye,
and thank you for coming.
(Engine Starts)
- So, how'd it go?
- Doing Henry is murder on my throat.
- Murder.
- Yeah, yeah. I know.
- So how did it go?
- She's hooked, waiting to be pulled in.
Another one of your $25 sardines?
No. This is a big one, George.
A great big whale.
Well, come on. Give.
Keep your eyes on the road.
Don't rush me.
(Sighs) OK, Blanchie.
Start way up at the top.
Well, it was as simple as A-B-C.
Henry came to me from
the Upper Brightness, whispered to me,
"This woman's
been having sleep problems."
From there on,
things followed naturally, logically.
A-ha! So I came through for you again,
didn't I, darlin'?
No. What are you talking about, George?
What do you mean,
what am I talking about?
You know damn well
what I'm talkin' about.
All that information that I dug up
by gabbin' to the local druggist
about how she was drivin' him crazy
tryin' to get sleeping pills
without a prescription!
That could have been
very, very useful to me.
Why didn't you tell me about that?
What do you mean, why didn't I tell you?
I told you.
You know damn well I told you.
No, you always think
you tell me things, and you forget to.
I have to go through heaven and hell,
the Great Beyond, with Henry.
Henry, my ass. It was me.
It's always me.
Without my research,
you're about as psychic as a dry salami.
(Sighs) Nasty. Nasty, nasty.
I'm sick and tired of having you
have me by the crystal balls.
Leave your crystal balls
out of this, George.
No, let's leave Henry out of this
and keep the bullshit for your customers.
You're jealous of him, aren't you?
Oh, please, Blanche.
I like your jealousy.
It's your driving that stinks.
Hey, look.
I happen to be an actor, not a cab driver.
I can play cab drivers, but I sure as hell
don't have to drive like one.
Well, until I can collect
from Julia Rainbird,
I'm afraid you're gonna have to
go on playing a cab driver.
Neither of us seems to be
very fond of starving to death.
Well, how are we supposed to collect?
How much is this Rainbird whale
gonna spout up?
Also, you're gonna have
to go on playing a private eye.
Christ, no!
I've had it playing private eyes.
Christ, yes! Now, George.
Stop blaspheming.
You wanna put the curse
on ten big ones?
Now, wait a minute, Blanche.
- Did you say ten big ones?
- Mm-hm.
- Ten thousand?
- Dollars?
- Dollars, George!
(Chuckles)
Now, Blanche, you got any idea
what you and I could do with ten grand?
Mm-hm. We could even get married.
What are you always a wet blanket for?
(Laughs) Oh, you flatter me so.
Well, what's the deal?
What do we have to do?
I'll tell you about it in bed, afterwards.
Aw, come on, Blanche. Give me a hint.
Just a little... (Chuckles) foreplay.
Alright. Find one man. That's all.
Well, we've had to do worse than that.
What's his name?
Hmm. Ah... nobody knows.
- Well, who is he?
- That's the problem. Nobody knows.
- (Laughs) Where is he?
- Nobody knows.
Well, for chrissake!
You mean, nobody knows, Blanche?
Nobody knows his name,
or where he is, or who he is?
Well, George, stop yelling.
There's a possibility
of one person who might have known.
- Well, who's that?
- Julia Rainbird didn't mention him to me.
Fortunately, her friend Ida Cookson did.
- Well, who is it?
- The Rainbird family chauffeur.
(Sighs) Well, now you're talkin'.
Now we're on our way.
Trouble is - Well,
he's been dead for 25 years.
Oh, for chrissake, Blanche -
Oh, no, no, no, no, no,
don't start to fret, George,
or our water bed will be
no fun at all tonight.
As an actor, you should know
fretting will ruin a performance.
You're not gonna have to worry
about my performance tonight.
As a matter of fact,
uh, on this very evening,
you're gonna see a standing ovation.
(Brakes Screeching)
She's here. No, not a man. It's a woman.
Right. Follow me.
As long as you've got
Victor Constantine, we can't touch you,
so you might as well put that thing away.
(Man 1) You've been calling yourself
"The Trader',
so we thought you were a man.
(Man 2) I think we deserve some
assurance that the victim is still alive.
(Man 1) All radios have been removed
from the helicopter, as you instructed.
"Mr Constantine will be unconscious
but in perfect condition when picked up."
"Just let him sleep the drug off."
Alright, Sergeant, turn on the lights.
- Don't try and be a hero.
- Yes, sir.
Well, we've done our part.
Where are we goin'?
(Helicopter Engine Starts)
(Rotor Speed Increases)
Not one goddamn mistake.
How far are we going?
It's lucky for you
they've still got the victim.
I'd like nothing better than to toss you
right out of this thing on your head.
You sure have this little trip
mapped out, don't you?
I bet that thing isn't even loaded.
(Wind Whistling)
Golf course, huh?
(Rotors Idling)
Brilliant. Absolutely perfect.
(Car Doors Slamming,
Engine Starting)
(Car Racing Away)
My feet are killing me.
These damn six-inch heels.
I happen to like tall women.
Everybody likes tall women.
In fact, everyone's
going to be looking for a tall woman.
Aside from complaining a lot,
what have you been
doing with yourself lately?
Oh, nothing much.
Picking up a ransom, that sort of thing.
Did you see anyone, uh, we know?
Two men who look like police
and a third who just had to be FBI.
You mix with the nicest people.
Beats housework.
- Did you say anything to them?
- Not a syllable.
Now, you see, honey?
I told you you could learn
to keep your mouth shut, if you tried.
Look who's here.
Mm. Has anyone seen
a tall, blonde woman around here lately?
Gone, poof! Who needs her?
I do. At least one more time.
Let me put that there, darlin'.
Mr Constantine has left us some wine.
I don't think he likes the imported stuff.
Uh - It was probably my veal parmesan.
- I'm afraid I overcooked it.
- He likes eating in a room with a view.
You know how fussy rich people are.
Don't forget to empty that out.
Don't you think
emptying a chemical toilet
is below the dignity
of a jewel collector?
- The wages of sin, Arthur.
- I'll do it tomorrow.
Never put off till tomorrow
- what you can empty out tonight.
- Bitch.
Arthur, what's Amsterdam like?
Oh, lots of canals.
Lots of wizened old men
with sharp eyes, sitting around
cutting big stones into little ones.
You'll see.
I don't know what's come over me
tonight. I'm tingling all over.
I told you about danger, didn't I?
First it makes you sick.
Then, when you get through it,
it makes you very,
very loving.
- Darling, is it -
- Hm?
It was all too easy. It's frightening.
(Sighs) Brilliant planning.
They don't have a single lead to follow.
What about the
ketamine we stuck him with?
If Doctor Vogel didn't miss it six months
ago when I had my wisdom tooth out,
he's not gonna miss it now.
Don't finish up in there. Let's go to bed.
- Tired?
- Mm-mm. Tingling all over.
How'd I ever let you get me into all this?
I thought I fell in love with you
because I needed some stability.
Well, I guess you're just
a bad judge of character.
- Where'd you put the diamond, dear?
- Where everyone can see it.
- You didn't.
- I did.
- Are you gonna tell me where?
- You'll have to torture me first.
Oh! (Giggling) I intend to.
In a few minutes.
Now, with all due respect to the FBI
and the Bureau of Inspectors,
I have no time to play games.
Now, lest we forget, gentlemen, I have
been away from this desk forcibly.
I've got a lot of work to catch up on.
Now, how many more times we gonna
go through this goddamn thing?
Until we come up with something,
Mr Constantine.
That's a hell of a way
to solve a kidnapping.
Mr Constantine, you're not
the first victim. There have been others.
Alright, alright. But from me,
you'll learn absolutely nothing.
- You never know.
- I know.
Alright. Floyd?
Now. The underground garage.
- Full of cars.
- Sounds?
- People, behind me.
- Was it a man, or was it a woman?
- I don't know.
- Man or woman?
- Man.
- Then what?
(Grunts) It was a prick in my shoulder.
I started to turn.
Eh - And I woke up in a room.
(Floyd) Yes, and what did you hear?
Inside or outside?
The room was soundproofed.
I never heard anything except
a disembodied voice of a loudspeaker.
- Describe it.
- But I've already done that.
Again!
It was the voice of a man, no accent.
Doctored up electronically.
Unrecognisable.
How many of them were there?
Two. A man and a woman.
Why do you say that?
Because the faintest light
filtered down from the hallway above.
But not enough to give me
a chance to see who they were.
- Yes, and who did the cooking?
- She did.
Why?
Because a man would not
bother to put the parsley
on the filet of sole, that's why.
- How old is she?
- Come on, now. Please.
- Twenty-five.
- Why?
Because if a man my age
is gonna get kidnapped by a woman,
he wants her to be 25, that's why.
- Describe your return.
- The return.
The disembodied voice
tells me to sit with my back to the door.
The light goes out,
the door opens, they both come in.
I feel a prick in my left arm.
The next thing I know,
I wake up in that hospital bed
with you sitting there,
thinking up questions!
Thank you, Mr Constantine.
You're doing great.
- That's what you think.
- Alright, let's start all over again.
Aw, shit!
(Piano Playing, Birds Singing)
(Blanche) Why, Henry, you have such
a beaming smile on your face.
(Blanche Playing Henry)
I smile because I'm happy, Blanche.
It comes through you, Blanche,
from your friend, Ida Cookson.
(ln Blanche's Voice)
I'm her guide, Henry.
Friendship can be claimed only
when it cannot be denied.
(In Henry's Voice)
Tell Ida Cookson we're all thankful here
for the warm tranquility in her heart.
It will grow even warmer
as she trusts in you,
and confides in you,
and holds back no secrets from you -
be they her own,
or those of her intimate friends.
(Blanche's Voice)
Did you hear that, Mrs Cookson?
(Mrs Cookson) Yes, Madame Blanche.
(Blanche) Henry,
I want you to seek Walter for us now.
Search through
to the Double Strand of Kindness, until
my friend Ida Cookson
is joined in loving communication
with her dear, departed husband.
(In Henry's Voice) I will try, Blanche.
But first, the mist must part a little,
and the veil must rise
to let in the light
that will show us the path.
(In Blanche's Voice)
Ah, I'm ready now, Henry.
Ready! Ready to follow you,
wherever you want me to go.
Where? Where are you taking me, Henry?
(Gasps) Yes, yes, yes! I see.
I see your hand beckoning to me.
(Laughing)
Oh, what a lovely garden, Henry.
My, my. Oh!
Is that - Is that a statue there?
Oh! Could this be Walter
standing beside the fountain?
- (Whispering) How can you do this?
- I need your car keys.
- I'm in a hurry.
- (Moaning) Oh!
Do you realise what damage you can do
my psyche, breaking in this way?
Just give me your keys. I need 'em.
(Shouting) Yes, Henry!
(Whispering) What for?
I've located the daughter
of the Rainbird chauffeur.
- And I'm not going as a cab driver.
- (Shouting) Oh!
- What will I do without my car?
- I don't care what you do.
- Take a taxi. Just give me the keys.
- The trees are swaying!
And the branches part!
But there's no-one there!
(Whispering) Here.
I see shadows falling!
The air is getting cold!
The brightness... dims. Good-bye, Henry!
Oh! (Chimes Tinkling)
(Gasps) Did you find Walter?
- Where?
- In the kitchen.
I did.
(Chattering)
I wonder if I could speak to you
for a couple minutes, Mrs Hannagan.
Why, sure. Do we know each other?
No, I'm Frank McBride, of the law firm
of Ferguson, Ferguson & McBride
and I just wondered if you would mind
answering a couple questions
about your background.
- My background?
- Mm-hm.
(Chuckles) Dull as dishwater.
I mean, what in the world
would you be wanting with that?
Well, let's just say that the, uh,
information that I'm interested in
could be worth a great deal of money.
- Oh, yeah? To whom?
- Mm-hm.
Well, we'll get around to that pleasant
subject in a minute, if you don't mind.
- OK.
- Oh, swell.
Now, why don't we just
start at the beginning?
- Your parents.
- Oh, they're both dead. God rest 'em.
- Your father was a chauffeur, right?
- How did you know that?
(Chuckles) He was a chauffeur
for the Rainbird family.
Right again! You'd be
a hell of a detective, Mr McBride.
(Chuckles)
I don't know about that, my dear.
Now, during this period of time, though,
can you remember anybody, uh,
being a close friend of your father's?
Uh, there was a man.
It was way back when I was in school.
Uh, there was this guy
that my father used to drink beer with
and shoot pool with down in the village.
This Harry Shoebridge
had a poultry shop with his wife, Sadie.
- (Chuckles)
- Shoebridge.
Yeah. His business was always lousy,
even when times were good.
And she used to have miscarriages
like other women have birthdays.
Well, they stopped trying,
and they moved away
to Barlow Creek,
and, uh, adopted a kid, I think.
- A boy?
- Yeah. An infant.
But, you know, I'm not so sure.
L-It's all kind of hazy, an-and, uh,
I keep connecting it with -
- (Bell Dinging)
- Well, I remember this night
with my dad driving over there
to the Shoebridge's all alone,
and then getting in
a big fight with ma because
he'd come home at 4:00am,
and he wouldn't tell her
what he was doing or something.
Now, after my dad passed away -
God rest his soul -
my ma was damn mad
at the Shoebridge's,
because they
never showed up at the funeral.
- Then she found out why.
- Why?
A year earlier,
they'd gone to their own funeral.
- Dead?
- Mm-hm.
- Their house burned down with them in.
- Well, what about the son?
(Woman) Mrs Hannagan!
Can't you see that there are customers?
- Oh, yes. Yes. I'll be right there.
- She'll be right there, ma'am.
Uh-Uh, look, um, Mr McBride,
- about all this being worth something -
- Mrs Hannagan!
- (Sighs) Yeah.
- Wait a second.
This Shoebridge son -
where do I look for him?
Well, try the Barlow Creek Cemetery.
- What do you mean, the cemetery?
- I'm not sure, but I think he's dead, too.
(Bell Dinging)
(Sighs)
(Shuts Off Engine)
Sorry!
(Sighs)
- (Shovel Scraping)
- Dead end, Blanche.
Dead and buried.
- Caretaker. Do somethin' for you?
- I'm a friend of the family.
None left. Bad business, that.
You mean the fire?
Never liked them multiple funerals.
Too much work involved, all at one time.
They died together, yet they're not
buried together in the same hole.
How come?
Search me.
Here. Look.
Died in 1950. Died 1950.
Both died the same date.
Old stone.
This is practically new stone.
- Smart fellow, ain't ya?
- Why? Have I stumbled on to something?
Well, nice meetin' ya.
Better get back to my work.
I got a job comin' in here tomorrow.
- (Rock Music)
- (Chiseling Stone)
Turn that damn thing down, Marcella.
- Can't even hear myself think.
- (Fades)
How do you expect me
to remember anything that far back?
I'd have to go through my old files
for that kind of information.
Well, Mr Wheeler, I hate to insist...
- (Chiseling, Music Continues)
- You know something, Mr McBride?
You lawyers are all alike.
Trouble, trouble, trouble.
Well, come on. I don't have all day.
What year did you say the family died?
Uh, 1950.
(Groans) What month?
Ah, I can't help you there.
- Shoebridge.
- Can I sit down?
Shoebri- Yeah, go ahead.
Shoebridge. Shoebridge.
Oh, here it is.
"Shoebridge: Harry and Sadie."
"Large marble. Model 28."
"Paid in full. Cheque number 93."
"First Church of Latter Day Saints,
Barlow Creek."
What about the son?
- Edward Shoebridge. He's their son.
- Edward?
- Yeah.
- OK. Nope.
- Nothing.
- What do you mean, nothing?
There's gotta be something.
Maybe it came later.
Wait a minute.
You're talking about Eddie Shoebridge.
- His headstone? That did come later.
- (Coughs)
I think in, uh, '65.
Sure, I remember that kid.
He wasn't too popular around here.
Some say he set that fire himself
to get rid of his family,
and then disappeared
to make it look like
he died in the fire, too.
- They never did find his body.
- There's no body in that grave?
Well, as I recollect,
that's why the local parson
wouldn't say any services for Eddie.
Well, (Coughs)
Wasn't there a death certificate?
I wouldn't know about that.
And I don't need to know.
I'm just a businessman, Mr McBride.
- (Sighs)
- Ah, here it is.
"Edward Shoebridge. Granite special."
"Ordered, November 12."
"Paid for, November 18, 1965."
"$395."
Now, that's funny. It's paid in cash.
- They don't usually do that.
- Who was it?
I don't know, Mr McBride.
I guess he didn't want his name known.
Well, what do you mean, "he"?
- You just said he.
- I did, didn't I?
Well, you know,
I seem to sort of remember
that it was a man.
Yeah. A young fella.
Slightly bald. I'd say in his late twenties.
And did you see him
again when you, uh...
(Scratches Paper) put in the headstone?
We didn't do that.
He came by and picked it up himself.
Yes, I remember now.
In one of those tow trucks.
- You know, the kind that garages use?
- Gotcha.
(Rustling Paper)
(Typing, Chattering)
No, there is no death certificate
here for Edward Shoebridge,
only Harry J Shoebridge
and Sadie L Shoebridge.
That's all you have?
Well, there is this.
It appears to be an application
for a death certificate
for one Edward Shoebridge,
dated November 4, 1965.
"Inasmuch as applicant could
furnish no proof of death
for party whose body
had never been found,
and who could supply
no medical death certificate,
and nothing from the coroner's office,
the application was denied."
"Applicant, when informed
he could file a petition for court action,
declined the suggestion."
Does it say who the applicant was?
Yes. "Request was made
by Joseph P Maloney,
426 Main Street, Barlow Creek."
- Attagirl. Thank you.
- Welcome.
(No Audible Dialogue)
(Starts Engine)
(Bell Dings)
- Fill 'er up?
- Please.
- You want a check under the bonnet?
- If you would, please.
(Petrol Pumping)
(Bell Dinging)
- Better be careful with those matches.
- Oh. Right.
Sorry.
- This your place? (Dinging)
- Yeah.
Then you must be, uh, "J Maloney."
Tell me,
does that stand for, uh, John or Jim?
- Joe.
- Right.
- (Pumping Stops)
- Everything's OK.
(Bonnet Slams)
Funny, uh,
you didn't hardly need any petrol.
Didn't need no oil - Guess you
didn't come here for the car, huh, mister?
Could you get my windscreen, please?
Don't worry.
You wouldn't happen to know a guy
named of Edward Shoebridge, would ya?
Used to live around here.
Name don't ring no bell with me.
What would you be wantin' with this,
uh, what's his name, uh, Shoebridge?
Yeah. Legal matter.
- You a lawyer?
- Yeah. (Coughs)
Name's McBride. Frank McBride.
First time I ever talked to a lawyer
didn't cost me money.
Actually, Mr Maloney, by talking to me
you could make yourself some money.
Yeah?
I'm prepared to pay
a reasonable sum of cash,
right now, for any information
that could lead me to Eddie Shoebridge.
Where I come from,
lawyers are usually bad news.
Oh, no. Not this time.
This time they're good news.
Matter of fact,
I think that Eddie Shoebridge
would be delighted
when he hears from me.
What are you gonna tell him?
Well, my client has asked me
to keep that confidential.
Who hired you to find this guy?
- That's confidential also.
- Sure like to help you, Mister -
Business ain't all that good around here.
- I think you can help me.
- Is that right?
See, people around here have been
telling me that Eddie Shoebridge is dead.
(Sighs) Well, if he's dead,
looks like he ain't gonna be hearin'
all that good news
you have to tell him, huh?
I think he's alive.
(Sighs)
Sure don't keep this car very clean.
You want to tell me why you put
a headstone on an empty grave, Maloney?
What headstone?
The one you paid $395 for back in 1965.
You owe me $2.47, mister.
Two weeks before that,
you went to the county courthouse
and asked for a certificate
of death for Edward Shoebridge,
and you were turned down.
- You wanna give me your credit card?
- No.
Credit cards are out.
Like you, I prefer to pay... in cash.
(Engine Starting)
- (Car Leaving)
- (Bell Dinging)
Now, this one happens to be
my personal favourite.
Isn't it exquisite?
(Woman) Probably too expensive for me.
- (Bell Dings)
- (Woman 2) Can I help you, sir?
Excuse me. I'll be right back.
Uh, Mrs Clay?
Would you take care
of Mrs Cunningham for a few moments?
(Woman 2) Certainly, Mr Adamson.
(Mrs Cunningham)
I'm afraid I rather like it.
(Joe) Hey, Eddie. You old son of a bitch.
If it's all the same to you,
I prefer Arthur Adamson.
Now what in the hell are you doing here?
Had to see you
about something kind of urgent.
Couldn't you have phoned me?
Some things
you don't put on no telephone.
Hey, uh, you got any booze around?
(Bottle Clinking, Top Unscrewing)
Alright, Joseph. What is it this time?
- (Pouring Drink)
- New freezer for your wife?
Mother needs another operation?
Bookies threatened to kill you? What?
Aw, come on, Eddie. You make me
sound like some kind of sponger.
Not that I ain't grateful
for all your favours.
- Did I ever have a choice?
- OK, OK. Here it is.
(Sniffs)
First off, I gotta ask you a question.
- Go ahead.
- I'm tellin' ya. No shit now, Eddie.
Can you think of any reason why anyone
would be sniffin' around in your life
after all these years?
I can't think of any reason at all. Why?
Well, there's this guy
comes around the garage today
tryin' to locate Eddie Shoebridge.
Claims he's a lawyer,
he's got good news for ya.
Won't say what, or who he's workin' for.
Calls himself McBride.
I know he's a phony the minute I see him.
- Police?
- No way. He's a real amateur.
I traced his license plates
with the bureau -
Doesn't even drive his own car.
"Blanche Tyler, 17 Castle Heights Road."
- What did he look like?
- (Coughs) He's tall, thin, about 35.
He's always got a pipe on.
Asking a lot of smart-ass questions.
- What'd you tell him?
- Nothin'. Not a goddamn thing.
I didn't have to. He knew everything -
fake headstone you had me put up,
how I tried to get you
officially declared dead.
The son of a bitch says
he thinks you're still alive.
He's lookin' for you, Eddie.
And any son of a bitch
who's lookin' for you,
is lookin' for me.
Well,
whatever he's up to, he won't find me.
You worry too much, Joseph.
Yeah, I worry too much.
Of course, you only planned the fire,
and locked your old man
and old lady in the bedroom.
- I poured the petrol. I lit the rags.
- And I thank you.
The happiest day
of my whole, inglorious childhood.
Alright, you want to kid about it,
it's alright with me.
- I'm gonna track this guy down.
- And then what?
This.
- You'll never change, will you?
- You got no cause to complain.
When you needed me,
I was always there, wasn' t I?
Look, put that thing away.
And listen to me.
I want you to go back to Barlow Creek.
Do nothing, say nothing.
Let me look into this matter
in my own, quiet way.
And if I need you for anything,
I'll contact you.
OK?
(Folding Knife)
You're the boss, Arthur.
Isn't it touching how... a perfect murder
has kept our friendship
alive all these years?
- You better believe it.
- (Knocking At Door)
- (Door Opens)
- I'm sorry to disturb you, Mr Adamson.
There are two gentlemen here
to see you, from the police department.
Tell them I'll be right out.
- (Door Closes)
- Jesus Christ, Eddie!
(Softly) Wait here.
Arthur Adamson.
What can I do for you gentlemen?
Sorry to bother you, Mr Adamson.
Andy Bush, Bureau of Inspectors,
and this is Lieutenant Peterson.
- Hi.
- My pleasure.
No doubt you've been reading, or hearing,
about the Constantine kidnapping.
I have a confession to make, Inspector.
When I heard of the size of that stone,
my mouth watered.
- Professionally speaking, of course.
- (Chuckles)
Well, just so you don't feel
discriminated against, Mr Adamson,
we're routinely covering every gem dealer
and jewellery store in the city.
Well, I'm flattered.
Have you, by chance, noticed anything
out of the ordinary, Mr Adamson?
Any unusual movement of large -
or small - stones
into the markets these last few days?
- Absolutely not.
- I see.
I take it that you're
going on the assumption
that this, uh, "ransom stone"
has been cut up into smaller gems?
- That's correct, sir.
- It makes a lot of sense.
We think so.
If I may presume to make a suggestion,
it seems to me you ought to be covering
the antique and
secondhand jewellery markets.
They buy from anyone,
whereas we jewellers buy exclusively
on the wholesale exchanges.
- That's already being done, Mr Adamson.
- Oh!
I think we've taken up
enough of Mr Adamson's time.
Well, I'm sorry I haven't been able
to be of more help to you.
However, if I do hear of any
unusual transactions in the marketplace,
I'll be sure and contact you.
- We'd appreciate that. Much obliged.
- Take care.
- Goodbye, sir.
- Good day. And good luck!
Mrs Clay, close up as soon as you wish.
I have some work to do in here.
I'll let myself out the back way.
- Good night.
Your friend,
Blanche Tyler, is a spiritualist.
A spiritualist?
That's what it says on her shingle.
Also, there's no-one home.
A spirit is never at home. Get in.
(Sighs) What do you think we should do?
We'll wait.
We still don't know who the man is yet.
- Must you?
- Mm-hm.
That must be her.
That must be the fellow
with the pipe who called on Maloney.
A cab driver.
Lumley. Lumley, what's this?
Where are ya goin'?
I'm going home to my own bed
where I can get some sleep.
No, you're not.
Blanche, is that all
you've ever got on your mind?
What are you saving it for, a rainy day?
Honey, you never know
when you're gonna need it.
You're not being friendly, Lumley.
Blanche, I'm too pooped to pop.
I'd be useless to you.
- You're always useless to me!
- (Dog Barking)
- You're always pooped when I need you!
- (Car Horn Honking)
(George)... so we can collect a huge sum
of money; you call that useless?
You know what I'm talking about.
Come on inside and stop being difficult.
Not tonight, Josephine. I'm outta here.
- You're a fink!
- If I'm a fink, you're an ungrateful bitch.
- What about tomorrow?
- What about it?
You've got important work to do.
I want you to be sure about Eddie Shoe-
- (Passing Car Obscures Dialogue)
- Talk to him!
How many times
are you going to tell me that?
How many times do I have to tell you
that tomorrow I have to work in my cab?
So it'll wait till Sunday.
(Engine Starting)
You better give me a quick synopsis.
I'm confused.
Simple. A cab driver is shacked up
with a sex-starved medium
named Blanche Tyler.
Don't ask me why,
but apparently they're on the trail
of some spook named Eddie Shoebridge.
Fortunately, not on the trail
of your favourite kidnapper and mine.
How can you be so sure?
You did hear him talk about
collecting a huge hunk of money.
Couldn't that be the reward
that's on our heads?
You got yourself a point there,
Frances, old girl.
Only time will tell whether it's any good.
One thing's certain.
We're not going to change our game plan.
Not now.
Buy me a drink, Arthur.
A shiny car. A... limousine?
Why does he drive so fast, Henry?
What's that? On the seat beside him?
I hear the sound of a baby crying.
Quick, Henry, before he disappears.
Ask - Yes, I know.
I... see him now.
The uniform. A chauffeur.
Words! Henry, I need words.
Who? The what?
(Panting) The Rainbird chauffeur?
Good heavens.
Old Michael O'Keefe, our chauffeur.
(Gasps) Where is Michael going?
Henry, ask him
where he's taking Harriet's baby.
Oh, more pictures are coming in too fast.
I can hardly make them out.
Henry, a graveyard, a headstone?
I don't like this, Henry.
A shoe. Bridge.
A shoe bridge?
Oh, don't do this to me, Henry.
- Speak to the chauffeur.
- Oh, God, something's burning.
The house.
Quick, Henry. The house is on fire.
Take me away from here.
I don't want to see this.
I can't bear the sound
of their awful screaming.
Go back to the chauffeur, Henry.
Get Michael into our presence.
Miss Rainbird remembers him.
Yes, I remember.
Madame Blanche, listen to me.
Can you hear me?
I've remembered something else
that could be terribly important.
Wait one minute, Henry. Before you go,
Miss Rainbird deserves some kind of
assurance about Harriet's child.
He's a man by now,
and we have to know,
is he happy, Henry?
Is he alive and well and happy?
If you can't, you can't.
I certainly can't force you.
Yes. Of course she'll understand.
Until next time, then. Goodbye.
Goodbye, my love.
- What happened?
- Don't you remember?
- Not a blessed thing.
- Oh, it doesn't matter now.
Listen, listen, Madame Blanche.
Your Henry jogged my memory
of something I'd completely forgotten.
When our poor old chauffeur,
Mike, realised he was dying,
he wrote to me and said
there was one person on earth
who had promised that
he'd make it his business
to know where Harriet's son was
as long as he lived.
It was the parson
who baptised the newborn baby.
And there's an additional thing
I can tell you.
Don't tell me. Let me guess.
Five hundred.
Not a penny.
Not even a hundred for expenses.
It's all or nothing, George,
until I can produce his name
and his present address.
Jesus, Blanche.
However, she gave me a marvellous clue.
- Here we go again.
- No, here you go again...
to the man who might tell you
if Shoebridge is dead or alive.
- Who's that?
- Bishop Wood at St Anselm's Cathedral.
- Holy Christ, Blanche.
- No, George, not him.
Bishop Wood at St Anselm's Cathedral.
He was a parson once
and he baptised the Shoebridge baby.
(Choir Singing, Indistinct)
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Do you know how I could, uh,
make a date to see Bishop Wood?
If you want to make
the appointment today,
you'll have to make it
through the chaplain.
Which one is the chaplain?
When the service is over,
I'll show you where to go.
(Singing Stops)
Oh, dear.
(Congregation Chattering)
- What's wrong with the Bishop?
- Don't know. You think he's sick?
You know he's moving.
You sure you gave him enough?
Just the usual dose.
He looks so harmless.
When I was a little kid
living in that village,
he always made me feel
like I was something evil.
- And look at me now.
- I feel years younger.
You know, one more like this one today,
and we'll be naturally grey.
It was an incredible job. I really think
it's worth more than a million.
I'm sorry, darling, but I'm not going back
and rewrite my ransom note
that I left in my prayer book.
You'll have to be a good sport
and settle for a million.
You were beautiful, Fran. Just beautiful.
- I was scared.
- I told you it'd be alright, didn't I?
People in church are inhibited.
They don't jump up and run around
and make a lot of noise.
They're all too religiously polite.
Shall we go on congratulating ourselves,
or would you like to talk about him now?
- Who?
- 'Who".
The man with the pipe.
- So you saw him there, huh?
- Larger than life.
Larger than death, you mean.
There's no doubt
about who he's after now.
What were you planning
to do about him, dear,
besides just not telling me?
I'm not planning to do anything about him.
Joe Maloney's been itching for that job.
He's got it.
I'll phone him as soon as we
put our guest in his quarters.
I was right about that silly cab driver.
For once in my life, I hate being right.
Well, how in the hell could he
have known we were going to be there
when you and I are the only
two people in the world who knew that?
(Sighs) I've got a thought.
- It's a dumb one.
- Say it.
Do you believe in ESP?
Extra sensory perception,
all that psychic phenomena?
What do you mean?
Madame What's-her-name?
Blanche Tyler.
Jesus.
You and I know that that's off the wall,
but, uh, can we afford to be wrong?
I'm afraid our two quarrelsome lovers are
going to have to share a fatal accident.
Oh, my God.
But Maloney wouldn't be
willing to do that, would he?
Of course he'd be willing. Gladly.
He'd believe he was protecting
himself and his old buddy.
I don't want to know about it. OK?
- Promise me, Arthur.
- Come on, now, dear.
That's what's so exciting
about all of this.
We move as one.
Everything together. Nothing held back.
It was gross negligence,
losing him that way. He was all we had.
I didn't lose him. He was kidnapped.
Why would anyone want
to do that to a bishop?
For the ransom, dummy.
It's a million dollars.
I can't get over it.
You know, I was right there.
Tsk. Oh, forget about the million.
What about our 10,000?
We've got nowhere to go now, Lumley.
What am I gonna tell Miss Rainbird?
I suppose Henry and I are going
to have to exhaust ourselves again
doing your work for you.
What d'ya mean, my work?
My work is driving a goddamn cab,
for Christ's sake.
- And startin' this minute, that's exact-
- (Phone Rings)
- Exact what?
- Answer the phone.
Hello? Who?
Mr Maloney?
Barlow Creek? Go ahead.
Hello.
Can you speak a little louder,
Mr Maloney?
"I said, I traced you
through the license plates."
"I figured if you was still lookin'
for some dope on Eddie Shoebridge,
- I might have somethin' for you."
- Oh.
How come you changed your mind,
Mr Maloney?
"I didn't say nothin' to your man
cos I felt it was none of his business,
but I been thinkin' about it
and how I could use the bread."
"So for a little consideration,
I'm willing to lead you to someone
who knows Eddie Shoebridge's wife."
- "lt'll cost you a grand."
- (Laughs)
Oh, don't be silly, Mr Maloney.
I have my lawyer right here beside me,
and he says he'll give you $100
provided it leads to something.
"Make it two."
Oh - alright. It's a deal.
- Where do we meet?
- "You and that lawyer friend of yours,
you drive up and meet me
at Abe and Mabel's in two hours."
- Abe and Mabel's?
- "It's a cafe up the road to Mt Sherman,
about five miles off Route 22."
- "You know where it is?"
- Yeah. Why so far away?
Can't we meet
somewhere more convenient?
"This party I'm gonna take you to
happens to be up in that area."
I see. Mr Maloney, are you admitting
Edward Shoebridge is still alive?
"I ain't sayin' a thing till I see
the colour of your money, in two hours."
(Dial Tone)
- What d'ya think?
- Smells fishy to me.
I know.
But even fish smells good
when you're starving to death.
What have we got to lose?
He's the only clue left.
You got $200 on you?
You know me better than that.
Of course not.
Fix me another one of these.
You don't need another one.
You already got one.
- I'll eat it in the car.
- Come on.
You're impossible.
A couple of beers, please.
He must be late.
- Thank you, dear.
(Car Approaching, Brakes Squeal)
(Doors Opening, Closing)
You kids sit over there.
- How was Sunday school today?
- Noisy.
- Five Cokes, please.
- We didn't make any noise.
That's right. That's why you're here.
(Boy Giggles)
(Car Approaching)
Don't blame me.
- Did I say anything?
- (Door Opens, Closes)
(Door Opening)
- Hello. I'm sorry I'm late.
- I'll get you a chair.
- That's alright. I'll sit over here.
- I'll join you.
Look at that. Nice arrangement.
Don't be obscene, George.
Oh.
Thank you, my dear.
(Truck Approaching, Receding)
Just see that you keep your head
screwed on straight, will you?
Ah! (Belches)
He's not coming.
(Engine Starts, Revs)
Well, that's the end of that.
(Tyres Screeching)
George, what's the big hurry?
Just slow down a little, will ya, please?
I told you not to drive so fast, George!
I don't know what's wrong.
The accelerator seems to be sticking.
George, for God's sake, slow up, will ya?
- (Tyres Screeching)
- I can't.
My hamburger's coming up.
The accelerator... is stuck.
Use the brakes!
- They don't work.
- What?
- The brakes don't work.
- What do you mean?
(Blanche Screams)
- George!
- Come on, woman. Don't grab me!
It's not me. It's the brakes don't work.
I'm getting violently ill, George.
You're chokin' me,
Blanche, for Christ's sake!
George! Do something!
(Horn Honking)
Get your foot down.
Grab the brake!
Reach down and pull the hand brake.
- Pull on it!
- I am pulling!
Get your hands off the steering wheel.
Pull on it!
- I am pulling.
- Pull it.
Come on.
Get your hand off the goddamn wheel!
(Screaming)
(Car Horns Honking)
Get your goddamn foot down!
- (Horns Honking)
- I gotta get off this road.
Blanche, just hang on.
Wasn't that fun?
- Damn you, George Lumley!
- What's the matter with you?
- It wasn't me. It's Maloney.
- He wasn't driving!
Of course, but he screwed up the car
and broke the brakes.
- Maloney?
- Yes.
You think it's a coincidence, Blanche?
Huh?
Your car... is gonna be
out of commission for a couple days.
So let's go find us
another way to get home.
George. Are you alright?
Mm-hm. I think so. How about you?
I'm OK. I'm sorry.
- Do you think Maloney wanted us dead?
- Mm-hm.
Why, in the name of God,
would anyone want to do that to us?
I don't know, but you can bet
it has something to do with your
mysterious friend, Eddie Shoebridge.
Maloney's probably got him
buried in his backyard.
Doesn't want us to find out.
That way.
(Vehicle Approaching)
Hi there. Sorry I'm late.
Congratulations on the nice job
you did on our car, Maloney.
What are you two doin'
standin' in the middle of the road?
You know perfectly well
what we're doing on the road, Maloney.
You must be Blanche Tyler.
Pleased to meet ya.
Where's your car?
Let's just say it ain't in runnin' order,
you know what I mean?
Hop in. I'll give ya a lift
to the nearest station.
No, thank you. We don't ride in hearses.
You think I came up here
for the fun of it?
You want me to take you to this party
that knows Eddie Shoebridge's wife?
Why don't you just go ahead, uh, by
yourself this time, Maloney. We'll skip it.
(Engine Starts, Revs)
He's all charm.
(Blanche) Who's that?
That's Maloney. He's after us.
Come on.
(Man)
Hey, guys, lets get the hell outta here.
(Explosion)
We better get the police.
And lose our $10,000?
(Bell Chimes)
May I be of some help to you, madam?
- I'd like to see some bracelets.
- Any particular kind?
Do you have anything with turquoise,
or perhaps pearls?
- Anything wrong with our houseguest?
- He's fine.
I gave him a very nice lunch
and a fresh bottle of wine.
- Maybe one of these will appeal to you?
- Are those seed pearls?
That's right.
- What are you doing here?
- These look like freshwater pearls.
The message has come through on KFAG.
They've located the stone we asked for.
In New York. Harry Winston.
Fifty-three carats.
These are very nice.
How much are they?
$315, including tax.
When do we make the pickup?
Tomorrow night, 9:30.
Good. Now go on home.
Would it be possible for you
to set these aside
so that I can bring in my husband
and he can look at them?
Of course, madam.
(Sighs) Now for the bad news.
Take a look at this.
Incompetent bastard. He blew it.
Now we'll have to
eliminate these two ourselves.
- Ourselves?
- That's right.
Tomorrow night,
right after we return our guest.
- I can't.
- You must.
Remember: Share and share alike.
You stop it! Stop it!
- Decided on this one?
- That'll be fine.
I'll have it wrapped.
(Man) But it was more than that,
much more than that
that you left behind
as your precious gift to life.
Yes, Joseph Maloney,
you were a generous man.
You gave of your heart and soul.
You gave the very best that was in you,
and no more than that can be asked
of mortal man on this earth.
You loved your wife dearly.
You bestowed upon
your dear mother and father
all the care, all the attention,
patience and comfort that they needed,
in the sunset of their lives.
And those of us who are left behind
to grieve for you, Joseph,
can only bow to the
divine judgement of our Lord,
who has chosen
to take you away from us
in this cruel accident.
Oh, how great the holiness of our God.
For He knoweth all things.
And there is not anything
save He knows it.
And He cometh into the world
that He may save all men if they
will harken unto His voice.
For behold,
He suffered that the pains of all men.
Yea, the pains of every living creature,
both men, women and children -
(Continues Indistinct)
Can't you leave me alone?
Isn't it enough that you killed him?
That's not so, Mrs Maloney.
It was the other way.
You. You started it all coming here
and messing in things
that were none of your business.
Now go away. Please!
- Mrs Maloney, I have to talk to you.
- He's dead and buried.
- There's nothing to talk about.
- Why didn't he want me
- looking for Eddie Shoebridge?
- I am not listening to you.
Get away from me!
Mrs Maloney, your husband tried to kill
me, and you were in on it, weren't you?
No.
Then why are you always
running away from me?
Do you realise that you are
an accessory to an attempted murder?
- I had nothing to do with that.
- Perhaps the police'd think that you did.
- You want me to go to the police?
- For God's sake.
- You wouldn't do that -
- Tell me where is Eddie Shoebridge?
I can't.
Mrs Maloney, where is he?
Please tell me.
There is no Eddie Shoebridge.
He went up in smoke 25 years ago
and came down in the city.
He calls himself Arthur Adamson.
Arthur Adamson?
If he finds out I told you, he'll kill me.
Now go away,
and don't ever come near me again.
Fake! Fake! (Sobbing)
Wait a second, now.
You're the one that's exaggerating.
No, I'll give you two or three days
maybe I missed, but never more than that.
- Tell him it's deeply important.
- Shh!
- Stand up.
- Why me?
What makes you think that
it's me that ran up all the extra mileage?
What about that little asshole, Herbie,
or, uh, Al, the one on the day shift?
I understand. I'll be there.
Yes, I promise I'll be there.
The answer's no.
He says I must work the shift,
and I must work it tonight.
And do me a favour, Blanche.
Please don't give me a hard time.
You didn't put up much of a fight.
Honey, look. After all the goofin' off
I've been doin' on your behalf,
I'm within a gnat's eyelash
of losin' my cab
and gettin' kicked right out
of the company.
Lumley, you're thick!
You won't have to drive a cab
if you can get this thing over
and done with and collect the money.
"Lf", darling. You're always givin' me ifs.
I can't eat ifs and neither can you,
while Julia Rainbird and you
are waltzin' around in the Great Beyond.
Come on, sweetheart. The least I can do
is show up for work every now and then.
After all,
didn't I give you the guy's name?
But the phone book
is full of Arthur Adamsons.
It's very simple. All you need
to do is find out the right one.
That's a snap.
The one that's close to 40 years old
and trembles a little bit
at the name Eddie Shoebridge.
- Easy. We do that tomorrow.
- Now would be much better.
- A bird in the hand, Lumley. Please.
- Oh, sweetheart.
The only bird
that's gonna be in my hand -
and I'm very sorry to say this -
is a steering wheel
from 4:00 to midnight.
Sure. Why should I get a kiss?
Just when I was beginning to think
you weren't impossible.
Maybe I'll do it without you.
The hell you will!
Come on, now. Please.
This Shoebridge fellow's
gone to a lot of trouble not to be found.
Now you got no idea
what kind of trouble you could get into.
Whatever it is, he'll forget about it
when he hears about
the millions he's coming into.
Oh, Blanche, come on.
Just sit down
on your pretty little... behind.
And I must say, it is quite an -
No, it is. Very attractive little behind.
Just wait for me, OK?
And tonight when I get home,
we will, uh -
Right. Very nice. Plot our strategy.
Know what I mean, darlin'?
Who needs him.
(Buzzer Buzzing)
You wouldn't be Arthur Adamson,
would you?
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Hello. Are you Arthur Adamson?
Hey, Art!
Yeah?
(Doorbell Ringing)
A A?
I'm sorry. We're just closing.
I understand.
I'm not shopping. Is Mr Adamson around?
I'm afraid not.
But if you come back tomorrow -
Alright.
But just to be sure
I have the right Mr Adamson,
- he is a gentleman of about 40, I trust?
- Yes, that's about right.
Oh, that's the first encouraging news
I've had all afternoon.
Isn't there someplace
I might reach him without delay?
- You mean tonight?
- Yes.
Well, he usually goes
directly home from here.
But tonight would be very bad
because I believe he's giving a party.
I know he left unusually early
for some such reason.
Isn't there something
I can tell him for you in the morning?
- This is personal. Rather personal.
- Oh, I see.
Perhaps you'd like to leave him a note.
- A note? Very good.
- Yes. Come this way.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Is anything the matter?
Uh, I was, uh, just thinking.
Instead of leaving this note here,
it might be better
if I sent Mr Adamson a telegram tonight.
- What's his address, please?
- Well, I don't -
It's alright. We're friends.
- 1001 Franklin Street.
- 1001 Franklin.
Thank you very much.
You've been very kind.
You're a Capricorn, aren't you?
No, I'm a Leo.
That's what I thought.
- Pete, hi.
- Hello, there, Blanche, baby.
Have you seen George?
He just left a few minutes ago,
but he'll be back.
Took a party of four out to River Valley.
- Oh, dear. That could take all night.
- Easily. What's up?
- Would you give him a message for me?
- Sure thing.
- Just tell him I found him.
- You found him?
- That's right. He lives at 1001 Franklin.
- 1001 Franklin.
That's where he lives,
and that's where I'm going now.
You found him, and that's where he lives,
and that's where you're going now.
- Thanks, Pete.
- Any time, Blanche.
You wanna go over
the new pickup spot once again?
I know it by heart.
Are you alright?
- I will be.
- You sure?
Have to be there at 9:30.
Let's get going.
Bishop Wood, it's time to go.
Have you your vestments on?
"Yes, but I haven't
finished the chicken."
I'm sorry, Your Excellency.
Here's what I want you to do.
Place the armchair
in the centre of the room
facing away from the door
and seat yourself in it.
You're going to be
comfortably put to sleep.
But it'll last only for a short while.
"Thank you very much.
You are most considerate."
Let me know when you're ready.
'By the way,
I haven't quite finished that book
you were kind enough to let me have."
"May I, uh, take it along?"
With our fingerprints on it? Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Nice try, Your Excellency.
"Thank you.
Don't bother, then. I'm ready."
Alright, I'll be turning your light off now.
(Grunts)
(Doorbell Ringing)
We mustn't be late.
See who it is, and be careful.
(Doorbell Ringing)
(Footsteps Approaching)
(Whispering)
It's her. That woman. Blanche Tyler.
(Whispering) This is incredible!
- Is that cab driver with her?
- She's alone.
If I didn't have to make
this pickup in 35 minutes -
What are we going to do?
Nothing!
Until later tonight.
- She's gone.
- Come on. Let's go.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- I thought you said -
- I know.
- Mr Adamson?
- Watch him.
Oh, Mr Adamson.
How lucky I am not to have missed you.
Apparently you didn't hear me
at the front door.
I am Madame Blanche Tyler,
the spiritualist.
Good evening, honey.
Madame Blanche,
I wonder if I might suggest to you
to remove your car from our driveway.
- We're terribly late for an appointment.
- Well, yes.
When you hear why I've come,
Mr Adamson - Or should I say Shoebridge?
- You won't mind being late at all.
- My dear lady,
- I know exactly why you've come here.
- How could you?
And exactly why you and your friend,
that cab driver,
have been sniffing along my trail like two
eager bloodhounds the past few weeks.
I had no idea, Mr Adamson.
- Alright, Madame Blanche, you found me.
- Music to my ears.
I'm perfectly willing to listen
to your demands,
whatever they may be, but not right now.
No demands, Mr Adamson. Oh, no, no, no!
Hardly that.
Julia Rainbird wants nothing from you
but the privilege of making you
heir to the entire Rainbird fortune.
The whole,
lovely millions and millions of it.
Now if she made any demands at all,
they were on me to find you.
Through psychic means, of course.
Let me get this straight.
Is that the only reason you have been
shall we say, investigating me?
Oh, yes. And don't think it's been easy.
Oh, Mr Adamson, you've given
George and me the devil's own time of it.
Tracing you from a foundling baby
to a young boy named Shoebridge
to a man named Adamson.
Oh, but, Mr Adamson, here you are;
here I am.
- It's a happy moment for us all, isn't it?
- (Fran Gasps)
(Blanche) It's the Bishop. (Gasps)
Does anyone know
that you've come here?
No one know -
Anyone kn-know?
No. Not a soul.
Not even George soul.
You have nothing to worry about,
Mr Adamson.
I promise.
I won't breathe a word... to anyone.
It looks like Miss Tyler needs some rest.
Will you do as I say?
No. No.
(Groaning)
Unlock the door.
Cheer up, Fran.
Let's go get the new diamond
for our chandelier.
Wow. It's gorgeous.
And now for Madame Blanche.
(Horn Honking)
(Doorbell Ringing)
Oh, my God.
Blanche?
(Garage Door Opening)
(Garage Door Closing)
(Car Doors Opening, Closing)
(Adamson) If I'm talking too much,
perhaps it's because you're not talking.
It's my stomach, Arthur.
Murder doesn't agree with it.
You think I'm looking forward to it?
(Adamson) If Joe Maloney had been more
efficient, they'd both be dead by now.
(Fran) You can have my share, Arthur.
You can keep both diamonds
all to yourself if you'll just end it.
(Adamson) I'll tell you what I'll do.
If you help me carry Sleeping Beauty
up out of the cellar, load her into our car,
and drive her out to some deserted road
where a suicide can take place,
I promise you we'll talk this thing over.
- OK?
- (Fran) What about the cab driver?
(Adamson) If she was able to find us,
I'm sure he can too.
- He'll walk right into our hands.
- (Fran) Your hands, not mine.
(Adamson) Don't you think we ought to
go down and take a look at her?
It's been a while
since we gave her that shot.
- (Fran) You do it.
- (Adamson) OK.
(Door Opening)
You'll be happy to know
she's still unconscious.
- (Whispers) Blanche.
- Shh!
I'll put this end into her exhaust pipe
and the other end in the window.
That way, it'll look like suicide.
Better go and get her now.
I'll take her in our car.
You follow in hers.
You take hold of her feet.
- Jesus, she's heavy.
- (Screaming)
George!
- (Panting, Coughing)
- Got 'em.
Blanche, you faked that one beautifully.
You are still the champ.
Thank you, George.
Do you realise how much
the reward is for those two?
(Chuckling) Yes.
But do you realise how much more
the reward would be...
if we could find the diamonds
and turn 'em in?
What's the matter with you?
I -
Blanche, what's the matter?
What is it?
Blanche, you did it!
You are psychic!
- What am I doing here on the stairs?
- You're not a fake.
You actually found one. Look.
I did?
I'll get the police on the phone
and give them our good news,
and call Miss Rainbird
and give her the bad.
Operator, can I have the police?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org