Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- You'll stay here untiI you learn!
- Let me out!
- Your father died in this room.
- His ghost is still there.
No!
- You'll stay there till morning.
- Aunt, I can t endure it.
You'll do as you re told.
The Reverend Mr. Brocklehurst.
John.
Good afternoon,
Mr. Brocklehurst.
Mrs. Reed.
Do come this way.
My chiIdren.
Enchanting.
- Tea?
- Perhaps just this once.
Pray, be seated.
John, dear,
would you go and find that
wretched girl?
Yes, mama.
This has been a very
difficult decision.
- Come on!
- She s going!
- Hooray! She'll never like it.
- I can t believe it.
Her mother...
was my late husband s sister.
She married a clergyman,
penniless.
Then both parents died
of typhus when she was
a fewmonths old.
Are you her only relative?
There is...
an uncle.
Her father's brother.
But he Iives abroad in...
Madeira,
I knownothing of him.
Go on.
I have done what I can
for the chiId,
but she has a
willful obstinate nature.
Ah, here she is.
This is Jane Eyre.
Jane, Mr. Brocklehurst
of Lowood School.
How do you do, sir?
I hear you re a wicked child,
Jane Eyre.
Let me examine you.
Knowwhere
the wicked go after death?
To Hell.
What is Hell?
Can you tell me that?
A pit full of fire.
And should you like to fall
into that pit and
and to burn there forever?
No, sir.
What must you do
to avoid it?
Keep well and not die.
It is as I said.
You must warn herteachers
to keep an eye on her,
and to guard
against her worst fault,
hertendency to deceit.
Deceit?
We do not tolerate that
at Lowood.
That's why I wrote to you.
I want her to be
brought up in a manner
befitting her prospects.
To be made useful,
to be kept humble.
And... As for the vacations...
I would prefer...
if she spent them...
with you.
Of course.
Come.
Deceit is a sin.
It is akin to falsehood.
And all liars shall
spend eternity in that lake,
burning with
brimstone and fire.
- I m not deceitful.
- I beg your pardon?
I'm not deceitful,
and I m not a liar.
If I were,
I should say I loved you.
I do not love you,
I dislike you worst of anybody
in the world...
except your son.
Your bags, Jane Eyre.
Did you see
what a wicked child she is?
Have no fear, Mrs. Reed,
at Lowood we shall
tame her unruly spirit.
The stool.
Place her upon it.
You see this...
this girl?
Her name isJane Eyre.
Be on your guard
against her.
Avoid her company.
Shut her out
of your conversations.
This girl,
take a good look at her,
this girl is a liar.
Let her stand there all day.
She shall have no food.
And let no one speak to her.
Alice.
Pay attention.
Back to your lessons.
Forgive me, Lord,
for Thy dear son,
the ill that I this day
have done.
That with the world,
myself
and Thee,
I, here I sleep,
at peace may be.
Let her sing.
O may my soul
on Thee repose,
and with sweet sleep
mine eyelids close.
Sleep that may me
more vigorous make
to serve my God
when I awake.
Jane.
What?
Some bread and cheese.
Thank you.
What s your name?
Helen Burns.
Thank you, Helen.
God bless you.
And you too, Jane.
Goodnight.
Hands...
Bonnet...
Shoes.
Hands.
Bonnet.
Bonnet, Jones!
Burns, you re on the side
your shoe.
Your toes out.
Your chin is poking out.
Your head up!
I will not have
you so slovenly.
Cover your mouth!
Dirty, disagreeable girl.
You haven t cleaned
your naiIs.
The water was frozen.
That is no excuse.
Fetch me the birch.
Obstinate girl.
Nothing will cure you
of your
slatternly habits.
Sorry, Miss Scatcherd.
Put it away.
Cleanliness...
is next to Godliness.
Time for your lessons.
- You destroyed our day now!
- No one likes you.
Go sit down,
I'll see you in a minute.
- Who taught you to draw?
- I taught myself.
I used to look at
my Aunt s books
and copy the pictures.
- You drawvery well.
- Not really.
You do. You have a gift.
You re lucky.
Helen.
- Can I drawa portrait of you?
- Me?
Yes.
Take off your bonnet,
you have pretty hair.
...seem fit to
burden us once more.
Who s that girl
with red hair?
Burns, sir. Helen Burns.
Burns, step forward.
Vanity.
You see this vanity?
Long curled hair,
masses of red curls.
In defiance of our principles.
You knowthat.
It was my fault, sir.
I told her to take it off.
It s not her bonnet.
It s her hair, her vanity.
It's not vanity, Mr. Brocklehurst.
Helen s
hair curls naturally.
And does she not sin
naturally as well?
I teach you discipline.
I am here to correct nature,
Miss Temple.
I'll arrange it so
it doesn t offend you.
Offending me is not the issue.
The chiId s
vanity must be suppressed.
Remove far from me
vanity and Iies.
Proverbs.
Chapter 30, verse8.
- Her hair shall be cut off.
- No!
Did someone speak?
You'd punish her for the way
God made her?
Fetch the scissors.
You, Jane Eyre.
Did you hear?
I will not ask you again.
Your hair will
grow again soon.
And if it is cut again,
it will grow again.
And it will be
more beautiful than before.
Come, into bed.
I'm sure you feel
sorry for yourselves.
I m sure you all
envy other girls who seem
to be blessed with happier lives.
But you...
have all been blessed
with intelligence.
Intelligence
and a proper education
will give you independence
of spirit,
the greatest blessing of all.
The only thing that matters
is to be in harmony
with God.
- What is this?
- Come, into bed.
Go to bed!
Lmmediately!
All of you!
Miss Temple!
I m worried about Helen Burns.
- Hercough is worse.
- Most of them have a cough.
We should call the doctor.
Only Mr. Brocklehurst
can do that.
Then I shall talk with him.
No, Miss Temple.
I will.
Helen?
Jane?
Is that you?
What are you doing here?
Lt's gone eleven.
I couldnt sleep
till I d seen you.
Your feet are bare.
Lie down.
Cover yourself
with my quilt.
Don t cry.
You mustn't cry.
Please dont leave me.
We'll be together again.
When?
Where?
In Heaven...
forever.
Will we?
- Don t you believe that?
- I dont know.
You must believe it, Jane.
You must believe...
God will take care of us.
Goodnight,
dearest Jane.
Mr. Brocklehurst.
I've found her, sir.
Burns.
I'll tend to it.
Dont grieve, Jane.
She s gone to a better place.
May God have mercy
on her soul.
Come, Jane.
Jane.
Hurry, the coach is here.
I hope you don t think
I m ungrateful.
Ungrateful,
what do you mean?
Since I've come to Lowood,
you ve been my one friend.
Apart from Helen.
- I feel I m abandoning you.
- No, no.
You mustn t think that.
No. It s good
and proper for you
to start a newlife.
I wish you could come.
Thank you.
But...
I believe it s God s will
I m here.
I cannot leave.
God bless you.
- Howmuch further?
- About 20 miles.
Oh, I see.
If Miss Eyre,
who advertised in the Yorkshire
Herald last Thursday,
is in a position to give
satisfactory references
as to character
and competency,
a situation can be
offered to her.
There is but one pupil,
a little girl
under ten years of age.
The salary is30 pounds
per annum.
Miss Eyre is requested
to send references, name,
address
and all particulars
to Mrs. Fairfax, Thornfield Hall.
It'll be nice
to get out and stretch.
- Goodbye, Miss.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye, young lass.
Come in, Miss.
Come in.
Leah!
It s the new Governess.
Would you follow me, Miss?
Mrs. Fairfax.
Miss Eyre.
How do you do, my dear?
It s a tedious journey.
You must be frozen.
Let me help you.
- Don t trouble yourself.
- No trouble.
Your hands must be numb with cold.
Come to the fire
and get warm.
There.
And I dare say
a hot drink would be
most welcome too.
- Sugar?
- No, thank you.
Leah, cut a sandwich ortwo.
- Do sit down.
- Thank you.
The key.
- What?
- The key, Mrs. Fairfax.
Here.
If Adele is still awake,
ask her to come down.
Yes, Mrs. Fairfax.
The chiId keeps
the most impossible hours.
Her mother
must have kept her up
the entire evening.
She isn t your daughter?
Oh, no, no.
No, her name is Varens...
Adele
Varens.
No, I have no family.
I am glad, I m so glad
you are come.
One can feel so isolated here,
especially in the winter.
It will be most pleasant for me
to have someone to converse with
on terms of equality.
Of course to be sure,
John and his wife Leah
are very decent people...
Here is yourcharge.
Come, Adele.
This lady will teach you
and make a clever woman
of you.
My governess?
That s right.
You may call me Miss Eyre.
You speak French!
May we speak in French?
Yes, Adele, but we re
with Mrs. Fairfax now,
it is more polite
if we speak in English.
You understand
when she runs on like that?
Oh yes.
Shall I sing?
My mama taught be to sing.
Where is your mama?
Gone. She flew away
to the Holy Virgin.
She taught me
to dance and sing.
Shall I sing for you?
In the morning, Adele.
It s late.
And it is time you were in bed.
Come along.
We shall come up
and hear your prayers.
This way, my dear.
Come on, Miss.
Thornfield is a fine old hall,
perhaps a little neglected,
but that could be remedied
if Mr. Rochester would come.
Who is Mr. Rochester?
Why, he is the Master
ofthis house.
But you won't see him.
He never stops here.
Of course he does,
sometimes.
He brought you here,
didnt he?
But it is true,
he s usually away.
Miss.
Will we be very happy?
We shall work hard
and be content.
- Goodnight, Adele. Say your prayers.
- Goodnight, Miss Eyre.
Goodnight, Mrs. Fairfax.
Goodnight, Adele.
I'll not keep you up all night.
I m sure you'll want
to retire early.
And your room is just along here
near to Adele.
It s small, but I thought
you d Iike it better
than the ones in front.
They re larger, but so solitary.
No one ever sleeps there.
One would almost say
if there was a ghost at Thornfield,
that would be its haunt.
Now, here is your room.
This is for me?
Why, is anything the matter?
Tomorrow I'll discover
this is a dream
from which I must awaken.
We are real,
and you are most welcome here,
most welcome.
- Goodnight. Sleep well.
- Thank you, Mrs. Fairfax.
Up here
is the main gallery.
What a handsome place.
I had the windows opened
to let in the air.
Everything gets
so damp in rooms
that are seldom entered.
Let me show you
the rest of the house.
Here are the Master s rooms.
Is that Mr. Rochester?
Oh, no.
His father.
Why Mr. Rochester keeps it
here despite everything,
I do not know.
One of his strange ways.
His father and his brother
were very unfair to him.
Some would say barbarous.
He was the youngest son,
you see.
And he was expected
to sacrifice everything
for the family.
He only inherited Thornfield
nine years ago.
When he was a chiId,
he was a gentle boy.
He s clearly not barbarous
if he s taking care of Adele.
Oh, no.
No, Mr. Rochester does accept
his responsibiIities.
Hes a just and liberal
landlord to his tenants.
He s well travelled
and very intelligent.
But when he talks to you,
you can t be sure
whether he is in jest
or in earnest.
Whether he is pleased
or the contrary.
He is not a happy man.
Oh my goodness, those flowers!
I keep telling Leah that all the
rooms must be kept in readiness.
Mr. Rochester s visits
may be rare,
but we re never warned.
What was that?
One of the servants most Iikely,
Grace Poole.
Did you hear it?
Oh, yes.
I often hear it.
She does sewing in
one of these rooms.
Grace!
Too much noise!
Remember instructions.
We can go back this way.
Your arithmetic
is not very good, Adele.
It s dull.
I don t care for it.
- Cant we do something else?
- I m here to give you an education.
Arithmetic is
an important part of that.
Mama said it was important
to sing and dance.
That wasn t dull.
If you re good,
I'll teach you the piano.
Will you?
- When?
- Perhaps tomorrow.
- Why not now?
- Arithmetic today, piano tomorrow.
I m going for a walk,
and when I come back,
I want to see how many
of those sums
you ve got right.
- But they re so difficult.
- You can do it, I know you can.
Are you injured?
Can I do anything?
You can stand to one side.
If you re hurt,
I'll fetch help.
Thank you.
I have no broken bones.
Go on then.
I cannot leave you here until
you re able to mount your horse.
You should be at home.
Where do you come from?
There.
That house
with the battlements?
Yes, sir.
Whose house is it?
Mr. Rochester s.
Do you know Mr. Rochester?
I ve never seen him.
What is your position?
I mthe Governess.
The Governess.
I believe I must ask
your help after all.
Would you get hold
of my horse s bridle
and lead him to me?
You re not afraid?
No, sir.
The mountain will
never come to Mahomet,
so help Mahomet
go to the mountain.
Would you come here?
Excuse me.
Necessity compels me
to make use of you.
Thank you.
Would you hand me my hat?
And crop.
Thank you for your help.
Now...
make haste home as fast
as you can.
Whose dog is this?
He came with the Master.
- With whom?
- The Master.
Mr. Rochester.
He just arrived.
Here is Miss Eyre, sir.
Is the leg more comfortable?
Doctorwill be here
in the morning.
Let Miss Eyre be seated.
Look what Mr. Rochester
has brought me.
Have you brought
Mademoiselle a present?
Did you expect a present?
Are you...
fond of presents?
I hardly know, sir.
I have little experience
ofthem.
They are thought pleasant.
Generally thought so,
but what do you think?
Apresent has many faces,
has it not?
How long have you been
in my house?
Four months.
And you came from?
Lowood School, Lancashire.
Lowood!
How long were you there?
Ten years.
Eight as a pupiI,
two as a teacher.
You must be tenacious to have
survived that place so long.
You have
the look of another world.
When I saw you, I thought
of fairy tales and almost asked
if you d bewitched my horse.
I m not sure yet
it is she who is
responsible for my sprain.
There was ice on the road.
It caused your horse
to slip.
Perhaps.
I m not sure yet.
Very well, Miss Eyre.
I bid you goodnight.
Adele.
Watch and Iisten.
You mean Iike this?
I ve examined Adele.
You ve taken great
pains with her.
She s not bright,
she s no particular talent,
yet she s made
much improvement.
- Shes worked hard.
- You re teaching her piano?
- Yes, sir.
- Are you fond of music?
Do you play well?
I'm very fond of it.
I play a Iittle.
Like any other
English schoolgirl.
Perhaps better than some,
but not...
well.
Adele showed me some sketches.
She said they were yours.
I don t knowif they
were of your doing...
Perhaps a master helped you?
No one helped me, sir.
That wounds your pride.
These pictures must have taken
much time.
When did you do them?
My last two vacations.
Did you copy them?
They came out of my head.
That head I see now
on your shoulders?
Yes, sir.
Has it other furniture
of the same kind within?
I think it may have.
Better, I hope.
Were you happy
when you painted them?
I couldnt paint what was
in my imagination.
I always wanted to achieve more.
You may have
insufficient technique...
but the thoughts are magical.
Ah, nine o clock.
- Is Adele in bed?
- Not yet, sir.
She should be in bed.
I don't approve ofthese late hours.
See to it, Miss Eyre.
I would do the edges darker.
His leg is better.
He will be going away soon.
Perhaps.
It will break my heart.
It s this one here.
Could you draw me his picture?
To always have him with me.
You examined me,
Miss Eyre.
You think me handsome?
No, sir.
There is something singular
about you. The air of a nun,
quaint, quiet, grave and simple.
But when asked a question
you are obliged to answer,
you rap out a reply
which is at least brusque.
What do you mean?
I was too plain.
I beg your pardon.
I should have replied
that tastes differ.
That beauty is of Iittle
consequence. Something Iike that.
You will endure my surliness
without being hurt.
Few masters would trouble
themselves to enquire
if their employees
were offended.
You never laugh, Miss Eyre?
Never mind.
Let me see what my employee
has been drawing.
May I?
You have me utterly.
No, no, it's mine.
Come, Miss Eyre.
Adele, continue with your work.
And remember...
shadows are as important
as Iight.
- Do you believe that?
- What, sir?
That shadows are as
important as Iight?
I believe none of us is perfect,
without some fault to hide.
You are not naturally austere
nor I naturally vicious.
I once had a heart
full of tender feelings.
But fortune has knocked
me about.
Now I m as hard and tough
as an India rubber ball.
Is there any hope for me?
Hope for what, sir?
My being transformed from rubber
back to flesh and blood.
Come on, Pilot.
Is all well, my dear?
What a strange man!
So changeful and abrupt.
I suppose I ve grown
accustomed to it.
- And one has to make allowances.
- Why?
Partly because it s his nature,
and none of us
can help our nature.
Partly...
family troubles.
He has no family.
There are painful memories
which are perhaps
best forgotten.
Well done, Adele.
Is that how mama
danced for you?
Precisely.
Exactly.
Now...
Off to bed.
Fairfax, take her.
Let me stay a while longer.
- Let me dance again.
- You heard me.
Please!
Don t argue.
Do as you re told.
Come, Adele.
Come.
Well?
Treat me as you will,
but dont treat a chiId thus.
I will treat her
however I see fit.
When I look at Adele,
I see a miniature
of her mother.
The same...
beauty,
the same merciless charm.
She was an opera dancer.
I wasn t the first
to love her,
but she told me that I...
was Adele s father.
At the time I wanted
to believe that.
But one night, I found her in
the arms of a brainless viscount.
I left a bullet
in his feeble wing,
gave her my purse
and ordered heraway.
So...
perhaps you'll think
differently of the child.
You'll tell me I should
look fora new Governess.
She s not responsible
for her mother s faults.
- Or yours.
- Or mine?
What have I done but play
the village idiot?
You've made Adele
feel unloved.
Why didnt you
leave her in Paris?
Because
her mother abandoned her.
When I looked around
I was all she had left.
And I do honor
my obligations.
However they were incurred.
No one can deny me that.
Goodnight, Miss Eyre.
Mr. Rochester!
Mr. Rochester, wake up!
Wake up, sir, please!
Is there a flood?
Come on, sir.
More water!
What happened?
I dont know.
I heard a strange laugh.
Grace.
Where are you going?
Stay here, don't move.
Wrap yourself in my cloak.
You re soaked.
Grace!
Open the door, Grace.
It was as I thought.
- Grace Poole, sir?
- Quiet so.
You should send her away.
Say nothing ofthis business.
I will answer for
all this.
You can go to your room,
There s nothing more to fear.
Goodnight, sir.
What?
Are you leaving me?
You told me to go.
Not in that brief, dry fashion.
Not without...
taking leave.
At least,
shake hands.
The roses had thorns.
You have saved my life.
I am in your debt.
There is no debt,
no obligation.
I knew you d do me good
at some time.
I saw it in your eyes
when I first beheld you.
I'm glad I happened
to be awake.
What s the matter?
You re shivering.
I'm cold.
Cold?
You re cold?
Yes, sir.
Go then, Jane.
Go back to bed.
You call that clean?
You and I are going
to have words downstairs.
Good morning, Miss Eyre.
What happened?
The Master was reading
last night.
He feel asleep with a candle lit
and the curtains got on fire.
Luckily he woke up in time
to put the flames out.
Here you are.
Hang them.
Did nobody hear anything?
Did nobody wake up?
Perhaps
you heard something?
Yes, Grace... I did.
I heard someone laughing.
If I were you, Miss,
I d get in the habit
of bolting my doorat night.
Leah, that s one, and two...
Good morning.
Oh, Miss Eyre!
You ve heard about the accident?
It s a mercy he wasn t burnt
in his bed. Leah!
- Is he all right?
- Well enough...
to be gone before breakfast.
Gone? Gone where?
Lord Ingram s,
the other side of Millcote.
There s quite a party
assembled there. PiIlows.
Do you expect himtonight?
No, no.
Nor tomorrow night either.
When these fashionable people get
together, they re in no hurry.
They may go to London
or the Continent.
Mr. Rochester may not be back
for a year.
Hes a favourite
with the ladies.
Miss Blanche
has been at him for years.
Miss Blanche?
Lord Ingram s daughter.
Prettiest girl in the county.
She is, Miss.
Does the Master like her?
Oh, yes!
He s different
when he s with her.
So merry and lively
you wouldn t know him.
Ah, Leah.
You re a fool.
I'll help you with this sheet.
Hurry.
They'll be coming soon.
James, hurry.
Take them to the dining room.
My cornerto your corner.
Have you something
we can keep a frog in?
- Awhat?
- Afrog.
My dear,
I have no time for frogs.
Mr. Rochester
may be here any minute
and all of Lord Ingrams friends
with him.
Hes neverdone this before.
They'll bring their maids
and theirvalets.
In the past he couldn t wait
to leave Thornfield,
now he s filling
the house with guests.
- They re coming!
- What?
Mademoiselle,
the beautiful ladies are coming!
Lady Ingram.
And Lady Eshton.
Yes, and Lady Lynn.
And that, of course,
is Miss Blanche.
- This way.
- Thank you.
Is Mr. Rochester in love
with Miss Ingram?
Don t ask such a question.
Why not?
It s none of our affair.
It would be
ifthey got married.
Adele, stop this conversation.
Go back to your work.
I hope he doesnt marry her.
A maid told Leah she s only
interested in his money.
She said he brought back bundles
- fromJamaica.
- Adele!
Miss Eyre!
Mr. Rochester wants you
to bring Adele to the party,
and he wants you to stay
untiI it is her bedtime.
He doesn t want me to stay?
Oh, yes.
'If she objects, tell her
it is my particular wish.
Those were his very words.
Good evening.
What a Iittle puppet!
That must be Mr. Rochester s ward.
The Iittle French girl.
- What s your name, chiId?
- Adele.
So pretty, how charming.
Adele, come here.
Edward, I thought
you weren t fond of children.
Nor am I.
What persuaded you
to take charge of her?
Where did you pick her up?
I did not pick her up.
She was left on my hands.
You should send her
to school.
I couldnt afford it,
schools are expensive.
You look after her?
We have a Governess.
AGoverness.
Yes, I thought I saw someone
with her just now.
You can tell a Governess
at first glance.
They re plain,
is a very special way.
Arent they, Mama?
Aren t who what?
Governesses.
Dont talk to me
about Governesses.
The very word makes me
tremble with rage.
I have suffered a martyrdom
in their incompetence.
What?
Nothing.
I said something wrong?
She s sitting just
behind you.
Who is?
The Governess.
Never mind.
It may do her
good to hear the truth.
Come along...
time for dancing.
I ve been idle too long.
Bianca, will you do me
the great honour?
I didn t know you danced.
He only dances
- with me.
- Who else would I dance with?
Mrs. Bennet, will you play?
You look pale.
Was my dancing
- so clumsy?
- No, sir.
Come back,
it s too early to go to bed.
I'm tired, sir.
And depressed.
What about?
- Nothing, sir. I m not depressed.
- But you are.
Afew more words would bring
tears to your eyes.
- I see them there now.
- Excuse me, sir.
- I m very tired.
- Very well.
I'll excuse you tonight,
but while my visitors stay,
I d like you to appear
in the drawing room every
evening.
It is my wish, Jane,
don t ignore it.
May I help you, sir?
I...
I d Iike to see Mr. Rochester.
We have guests.
Mr. Rochester and I are old...
old friends,
and I am very tired.
I ve come a long way to see him.
FromJamaica.
May I have your name, sir?
Mason...
Richard Mason.
Peter.
Take this gentleman
to the tapestry bedroom.
Damn your luck, Dent!
Anything else, sir?
No, thank you.
I need your help.
What is it?
Come with me.
You don t turn sick
at the sight of blood?
I don t think so.
Give me your hand.
It wont do to risk
your fainting.
Here, Jane.
There's a sponge
on the washstand.
Try to stop the bleeding.
I'll fetch the doctor.
I won t be long.
Sir...
I'll give you half an hour
to dress his wound
and get him out.
Why did you come,
why on earth?
I thought
I could do some good.
You thought.
You thought!
She said shed
drain my heart.
Keep him at your house untiI hes
well. I'll come in a day or two.
Have pity on her.
Let her be treated tenderly.
- Let her be...
- Yes.
I do my best.
And will continue to do so.
- It s not her fault.
- I knowthat.
If anyones to blame,
it s you.
Go.
Ace of spades.
You have the devil's own luck.
You knowwhat they say.
Lucky in cards, unlucky in love.
Penny, off you go
with the other guests.
I m bored with this game.
Why dont we play
something else?
What would you Iike to play?
Lord Brancaster has a billiard
table. Buy one, I adore
billiards.
They re rather expensive.
I m not sure
I could afford one.
Does that person want you?
Is something wrong?
May I speak to you?
7 card whist?
What is it?
I received a letter
this morning.
I want leave of absence.
Why?
- An old lady who s sick.
- What old lady?
Her name is Mrs. Reed.
She s my aunt.
- I thought you had no relatives.
- None that would own me.
She cast me off
when I was a child.
- Then why go offto see her?
- Shes dying.
I cant ignore her dying wish.
You wont be
persuaded to stay?
No, sir.
I will return to Thornfield.
So we must say goodbye.
Yes, sir.
How does one perform that ceremony?
Teach me.
They say farewell.
Or any form they prefer.
Farewell, Miss Eyre.
For the present.
Is that all?
Yes, sir.
Why don t we shake hands?
Remember your promise.
Mr. Rivers?
Miss Eyre is here.
Miss Eyre.
St. John Rivers, Rectorof
Gateshead. How do you do?
Please come in.
Your aunt is most anxious
to see you.
He family is in trouble.
John Reed, your cousin,
died last month in London.
He died. How?
He ruined his health
with bad company.
That brought on
your aunt s illness.
My sister, Mary.
I mtaking her to see her aunt.
I'll be back presently.
You are Iike...
Why, you are like...
Jane Eyre.
I am Jane Eyre.
I am very ill.
My mind is much troubled
by two wrongs
I have done you.
One...
was breaking my promise
to my husband...
to bring you up as
one of my own.
The other...
Go to my writing case.
Take out the letter
you find there.
Read the letter.
Will you have the goodness
to send the address of my niece,
Jane Eyre,
and to tell me how she is.
It is my intention to ask her
to come to me at Madeira.
As I am unmarried
and childless...
I wish to adopt her
during my Iife...
and bequeath her at my death...
whatever I may
have to leave.
This is dated 3 years ago.
Why did he never write?
I wrote to him...
I said I knew
nothing about you.
Now, act as you please.
Write to him...
tell him I Iied.
You were born to be
my torment.
I am not vindictive.
Let us be friends.
Love me or hate me as you will.
You have my full
and free forgiveness.
Mademoiselle!
- I thought you d left for good.
- I said I d come back.
You said a week.
It s almost a month.
Forgive me, Adele.
Mr. Rochester
is sending me to school.
I was afraid I d be gone
- and never see you again.
- To school?
To Paris.
Aschool for young ladies.
Adele.
Tell cook
Miss Eyre has returned.
Another place at dinner.
I'll ask her
to make a cake.
You came back after all?
As I promised.
As you promised.
You re very quiet
this evening.
What s on your mind?
Many things, sir.
My aunt s death.
Being back at Thornfield.
And?
Adele says you re sending
her to school.
Yes.
It s a good idea, dont you think?
Paris is her home.
May I ask why, sir?
I thought you might
have guessed.
Perhaps...
because you re
going to be married.
Exactly.
Precisely.
With your usual acuteness,
you ve hit the nail on the head.
I amto be married.
Which means Adele
will go to school.
You'll need another situation.
- I will advertise directly...
- No, you will not.
I ve heard of a position
that suits you.
Governess to 5 daughters
of a family in Ireland.
It s a long way off.
Agirl of your sense
won t object to the voyage.
But the distance...
And the sea is a barrier.
From what, Jane?
From England, sir.
And from Thornfield.
And...
Sometimes I have the strangest
feeling about you...
Especially when you re near,
Iike now.
It s as though I had a string
tied here, under my rib,
where my heart is.
Tightly knotted to you...
in a similar fashion.
When you go to Ireland,
with all that distance
between us,
I m afraid this cord
will be snapped...
and I shall bleed inwardly.
But you are sensible.
- You'll forget.
- I'll never forget!
I wish I d never been born.
I wish I d never come
- to Thornfield.
- There are other houses.
How can you be so stupid?
How can you be so cruel?
I may be poor and plain,
but I m not without feelings.
It's not the house,
but the life here.
I was not trampled on.
I was not excluded.
I was treated as an equal.
And so you are, Jane.
And so...
Yes, so, sir...
And yet not so,
for you re a married man.
Or as good as married.
- Let me go.
- Be still.
Don t struggle. You re like
a bird clawing at its cage.
I m no caged bird. I m
a free human being, independent,
with a will of my own.
Then stay.
Stay and marry me.
- How dare you make fun of me?
- I mean it.
Stay at Thornfield.
Be my wife.
What of Miss Ingram?
I don t love her,
nor does she love me.
Jane, you strange,
almost unearthly thing,
I love you
as my own flesh.
I beg of you to marry me.
Say Edward, give me my name.
Say Edward, I will marry you.
Yes.
Yes, Edward.
I hardly knowwhat to say.
I m so astonished,
I feel I must have been dreaming.
I thought Mr. Rochester
came in here
and said...
that in a month s time
you were to be his wife.
He said the same to me.
You know how much I like you,
Jane, but...
you re so young...
and little acquainted with men.
I have noticed
Mr. Rochester s growing
fondness for you...
And I have wanted
so many times...
for your sake,
to put you on your guard.
Why?
There is an old saying...
all is not gold
that glitters'.
And in this case I fear...
something different...
may be found...
from what you or I expect.
Is it impossible
that Mr. Rochester
should have a sincere
affection for me?
Oh, no, no.
It is not that,
my dear, it s...
He is a proud man.
All the Rochesters
were proud.
And gentlemen in his station
are not accustomed to marrying
their governesses.
Now, then...
Let s try the cape on,
shall we?
There... Turn around.
Turn around, dear.
Oh, you look beautiful.
- Have you been to the chapel?
- The parson s arrived.
- The carriage?
- The horses have been harnessed.
- We'll leave the moment it s over.
- Yes, sir.
- Jane!
- Yes, I'm here.
Any regrets?
Adele is away. Shed have
loved to see me in this dress.
I will have a portrait painted
and sent to her.
Like this,
with the morning Iight.
We are gathered together
in the sight of God...
to join together
this man and this woman
in Holy Matrimony.
,... so many as are coupled together
but as God's word
both allow,
are not joined by God...
The marriage cannot go on.
I declare an impediment.
- Continue, sir.
- I cannot.
What is the nature
of this impediment?
Mr. Rochester
is a married man.
- Who are you?
- My name is Briggs.
I'm a lawyer.
I am looking after
the interests
of your wife.
There is no wife!
'I affirm and can prove that
on the 20th day of October 1829,
Edward Fairfax Rochester of
Thornfield Hall, was married
to my sister,
Bertha Antoinetta.
Acopy of the wedding
certificate is now
in my possession.
Signed, Richard Mason.
That proves I ve been married,
not that she is still Iiving.
She was three months ago.
I have a witness.
Produce him, damn you!
Do not forget you are in
a sacred place.
Have the goodness
to step forward, sir.
Mason!
Close your book.
There'll be no wedding.
What these men say is true.
I have been married...
and the woman lives still.
Come to the house,
all of you...
and meet Grace Pooles patient...
My wife!
Stay out ofthe way, Grace.
Be careful, sir.
She s a bit snappish.
She s seen you, sir,
you d better not stay.
- We'd better leave.
- You stay here!
This is my wife.
Your sister, Mason.
Look at her. She is mad.
So was her mother.
So was her grandmother.
Three generations
of violent lunacy.
I wasnt told
about that,
was I, Mason?
All I was told about
was that my father had made a
suitable match to prop up
his dwindling fortune
and give your family
the Rochester name.
I did what I was told!
And Bertha
was kept away from me
untiI the wedding.
It was cleverly done.
Everyone got what they wanted
except me.
Even
she is betteroff here
than in an asylum...
but I have spent
the last 15 years in torment.
And this is what I...
what I wish to have.
This young girl stands
so grave and quiet at the mouth
of Hell.
- Bertha!
- No, Ma am.
Hold her down!
- Keep calm, lass, calm.
- Hold her, Grace.
Take care.
Calm, calm, lass.
I love you.
Say you love me.
I love you more than ever.
But this is the last time
I shall ever say it.
I must leave you.
Don t leave me, Jane!
The horse!
Mr. Rochester!
The house, sir!
- Trust me, Bertha, trust me.
- Leah...
John, wheres Mr. Rochester?
Mr. Rochester, help me!
Help me, somebody!
Bertha.
Bertha, come close to me,
don't be afraid.
Come to me.
Give me your hand.
Bertha, come to me.
I would never harm you.
Dont be afraid.
Come to me.
Please.
Come, come on.
Oh, here we are.
- This is for York.
- Thank you.
- And this is for you.
Good day to you.
Miss Eyre, isnt it?
Remember me? I m Mary Rivers,
the rector's sister.
Are you ill?
- How is she?
- She s had a good sleep.
Now may be a good time
to talk to her.
- How are you feeling?
- You look better.
The doctor is pleased.
You'll be well enough
to come down soon.
I ve been here almost a month.
I can t stay here any longer.
I must find work
and somewhere to Iive.
Hush, be still.
Stay as long as you wish.
Don t make her talk any more.
Tell her.
Miss Eyre.
I did not want to excite you,
but I have some surprising news.
Agentleman has been here
looking for you.
A lawyer.
I took it upon myself
to act on your behalf.
A lawyer.
What did he want?
It seems your uncle in Madeira,
John Eyre, has died
and left you his estate.
He always believed you were alive
and that you would be found.
You re his only
surviving relative.
You have become a wealthy woman.
These are the papers relating
to your uncle,
and the fortune
you will inherit.
This is your uncle, John Eyre.
And your father...
the father you never knew.
How young he looks.
And how kind.
He was kind.
Amongst the papers
is the letter he wrote
to your uncle announcing
your birth.
You were deeply loved.
Please forgive me.
There is nothing to forgive.
I know you have suffered greatly.
But the past can no longer
harm you.
You are safe now.
Jane, you strange,
almost unearthly thing,
I love you as my own flesh.
I love you.
Say you love me.
Mrs. Fairfax?
Pilot.
Hello, Pilot.
Pilot!
No more noise.
Miss Eyre!
Mrs. Fairfax,
bring me a glass of water.
Who s there?
Who is it?
Pilot knows me.
My brain will burst.
What delusion is this?
What sweet madness!
Her fingers.
Her very fingers.
Jane Eyre.
So many times I ve dreamed
ofthis moment.
Then the dream vanishes
and flies away.
Gentle dream.
Kiss me before you go.
I shall never leave you.
You will stay with me?
How?
I will be your friend,
your nurse, your companion.
You will not be alone
for so long as I Iive.
I m no better than a ruined tree.
I m Iightning struck
and decayed.
You re no ruin, sir.
You re vigorous
and full of Iife.
Plants will grow
and wind around you,
because your strength offers them
so safe a hold.
And so...
And so I married him.
Slowly but surely,
Edward began
to recover his sight.
When our first born
was put into his arms,
he could see the boy
had inherited his eyes
as they once were,
large and briIliant
and shining with Iife.
We sent for Adele,
she now Iives with us,
as beloved as if
she was our own daughter.
We are truly devoted,
my Edward and I.
Our hearts beat as one.
Our happiness is complete.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org