Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Can you tell me
what time the show starts?
- Course I am.
- I wanna know when the show starts.
Hold on for a second. What?
What time does the show start?
The show started a half an hour ago.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- You're very good at this job.
- I know this.
Some punk-ass nigger.
Yeah, hi. What time did
Flight 97 from Toronto get in?
Three hours ago? OK, was there
a Jacqueline Broyer on the plane?
You can't give that information?
This is Flight Information, right?
Then why do you call it Flight...?
Forget it. Forget it. Thank you.
Can you see if there've been any
accidents between JFK and midtown?
Well, what the hell is 911 for?
Well, I wanna talk to a supervi...
- Hello.
- You finally decide to show up.
I had some meetings that ran over,
so I had to take a later flight.
And you can't pick up a telephone
and call somebody, right?
I would've called, but they didn't
have a phone on the plane.
I wasted $200 on tickets. Just wasted.
And it's all your fault, OK?
I'm sorry. Why don't I give you
the money for the tickets?
It has nothing to do with the money.
You're bein' inconsiderate.
I was callin' all over New York. You
could've been on a road somewhere.
That's very sweet.
That's very, very sweet.
One of my tricks, OK?
I know the flower thing.
Listen, I'm upset with you. What you did
was inconsiderate, and I'm upset.
Well, maybe I should just go.
Yeah.
I'll go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Listen...
Look, I had a long day.
You had a long day.
I'm trippin', I'm buggin' out,
and maybe I'm goin' a little overboard.
You dry off. Let's put this whole thing
behind us and just squash this thing.
So, does this mean
that you forgive me?
This means I'm being a bit emotional,
and I acknowledge that,
and we should just squash it.
Well, I think it means you forgive me.
- You have no clothes on underneath.
- No.
You're too much.
You knew you was wrong, that's why
you came over in your drawers.
Cos you knew that it wasn't right.
- It's Jacqueline's.
- Say it.
Jacqueline.
- Whose is it, huh? Whose is it?
- It's yours. It's yours.
Wait, wait, wait,
I don't wanna come yet.
No, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
No, wait, wait, don't do nothin'.
No... Don't you say nothin'.
Don't say nothin'. No, don't touch me.
Don't touch me. Don't move.
Don't do nothin'. Just hold still. Hold...
No, no. Don't, don't. Oh, no. Shit.
You knew I was coming.
You knew I was. You knew I was.
I have to call my mother.
Where you goin'?
Home. I have to give a speech
in the morning to the board of directors.
But thank you. You were great.
God, Marcus, I was so tense when I got
off the plane, but you really relaxed me.
So, Mr Graham, thank you.
You really have to go?
But I'll call you
sometime tomorrow, OK?
Get some sleep.
Call me.
- Would anyone care for some dessert?
- Yeah, I'll have the tiramisu.
- I just want some coffee.
- And for the lady?
I am on a diet.
- v ery good.
- Diet? Diet, schmiet.
Are you crazy? You look great. I can't
wait to get you down to the Caribbean.
I'm not sure I'm going anywhere.
You've gotta go. Marcus has planned
a wonderful trip. We're gonna have fun.
Yeah. I'm gonna make a phone call.
- Go make a phone call.
- Excuse me. Yeah.
I know you were concerned about
how the layout was gonna be,
but I'm picturin' you
and beautiful white beaches,
and powder-blue skies,
crystal beautiful water.
You stand in the middle of it,
lookin' breathtakin'.
So, when are we gonna fuck?
- What?
- According to Jacqueline,
you are really great in bed.
Jacqueline told you
I was really good in bed?
Well, according to Jacqueline,
you really know how to
move your ass, you know?
She told you I know how to
move my ass in bed? OK.
OK, well, I don't know what Miss...
what Jacqueline has told you,
but it's not that kinda party,
and I'd appreciate it if... Stop that.
Stop. Stop it. Will you stop it?
Merde, alors. Man, I don't believe this.
You are going to turn down
a pussy like this?
Staring you smack in your face?
No man can turn down this pussy.
- Will you stop it?
- I don't know any man that can refuse.
Stop saying pussy, people are eating.
Pussy. Pussy.
Pussy. Puss, puss, pussy.
Tryin' to find our cat. Where is that cat?
- What's the matter with you?
- You don't like women?
Yes, that's it.
I don't like women. I mean, I'm gay.
You're not gay. You're not gay,
you just don't wanna fuck me.
I know a gay man. I know what
a gay guy looks like. My brother is gay.
And you. You. He's gay.
And he is gay.
- OK, what did you say to her?
- What did I say?
I heard this woman
screaming from the bathroom.
How dare you discuss what I do with
you in bed sexually with that woman?
As soon as you leave,
she starts sayin' she wants to fuck me.
- How could you talk about what I do?
- She said that?
- You said it...
- She's a little off.
She starts talkin' about
how my ass moves. I know you said it.
Don't expect me
to sleep with people for business.
- You did with Lady Eloise.
- Excuse me, that is a rumour.
We do not know if I slept with
Lady Eloise. I had a chitchat with her.
- Please, Marcus.
- Please, my ass.
Don't discuss what I do with you
with other people.
I'll handle this.
OK, Strangé, what's the problem?
- I'm not going.
- Now, listen.
You're gonna
have yourself on the plane,
or I will not only take back
the million-two I am paying you,
I will sue you for every goddamn dime
you've got. Do you understand that?
What an absolutely
exhausting evening, huh?
To tell you the truth, Marcus,
I don't feel very well.
Don't touch me. Don't touch me.
You've made me feel dirty.
I don't believe this is happenin' to me.
Look at you. God, Marcus,
you're gettin' yourself all upset
and worked up over nothing.
Nothin'? That's what sex is to you.
Whatever happened to
caring and commitment?
Some people still think
things like that are important.
You've made it painfully obvious
that you're not one of them people.
Well, why don't I give you a second
to think about it, hm?
Really?
Yeah. I think you should, you know,
do your own thing.
OK, Marcus.
It's over.
Good night.
Marcus. Marcus. I don't believe the way
you let her dog you out like that.
You're walkin' around
with your head down, mopin'.
Where's your pride?
Where's your dignity?
You think Malcolm X died so you could
walk around lookin' like a chump?
Bony, not today, OK?
Sad, man.
First the Fat Boys break up, now this.
There's nothin' to believe in.
Good morning, Marcus.
Morning.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
Good morning, Marcus Graham.
Morning.
Marcus? Excuse me.
I need the storyboards for the Strangé
spots. I'm shooting next week.
- Shoot whatever you wanna shoot.
- Whatever I want to shoot?
It's your show.
- I have complete autonomy?
- You the man.
Thank you. Bless you. Bye.
Excuse me. Jacqueline,
can I talk to you for just a second?
- Yeah, sure.
- I know it's none of my business,
what's going on with you and Marcus,
but can you try to take it easy on him?
Please?
Excuse me?
Well, whatever it is you're doing to him,
it's starting to affect his work.
What I am doing to him?
Yeah.
Well, it seems like whatever it is
I'm doing to him,
you are taking rather personally.
- Am I mistaken? Huh?
- No, Jackie.
I'm just saying, it's just
affecting his work, that's all.
Well, we don't wanna do that.
Thanks, Jack.
We have something exciting coming up.
After months of hard work by our
creative team, you are about to see
the commercial that will launch
our $18 million push
for the new Strangé fragrance.
Lights, please.
- How is it?
- I haven't seen it. I let Nelson do it.
This is my vision. It is fabulous.
Fabulous.
Strangé.
It stinks so good.
That is ridiculous.
Well, the board
wanted me to let you go.
I convinced them
to give you another chance.
Well, as an employee, I thank you
for saving my job, and as your lover,
- I thank you for ruining my life.
- Come on, I didn't ruin your life.
You ruined your life.
I said this was gonna happen.
I was just hoping
it didn't happen with you.
The only thing that I can suggest is...
perhaps you should
take a few weeks off.
OK.
There's this one kid that you are gonna
love. He is so cute. It'll really lift you up.
Marcus. I am not gonna let you sit and
mope all day long. Now snap out of it.
Have you been listenin' to me?
Cupid has his foot in my ass.
I have the cure for Cupid, all right?
Now, when I have problems with my
relationships, which is most of the time,
I find out that it's better to take the
focus off myself and put it to others.
I don't wanna be around no kids.
I wanna go home and sit in my house
and look at the wall and listen to Sade.
- And that's fun?
- No, but that's where my head is at.
That's where I need to be. I don't wanna
paint. You can't paint my misery away.
- Hi.
- Hi, Angela.
Thank you.
Everybody, this is Mr Graham.
Who did that?
These are kids I teach art to whose
schools can't afford an art programme.
- That's so nice.
- Now, remember last week we saw...
- I'm gonna whup somebody's ass.
- Sit down, Marcus.
Remember last week we looked at
collages from Romare Bearden?
- Yes.
- And what were you supposed to do?
Bring your own collages.
OK, who wants to show me theirs first?
Oh, boy. Kenny.
Assalam alaikum, my brother.
- Greetings, my Nubian princess.
- My king.
This is the sun,
and these are the sunrays,
and this is a big, giant,
huge hole in the ozone layer,
and this is what'll happen to people if
we don't fix up the ozone layer quickly.
That's very Afrocentric.
I like this, Khanya.
- What a lively little thing you are.
- OK, tell us about this.
This is my house. This is the sun.
This is a spear, and this is a shield.
Then we have...
That, right here,
is my fish bowl, and this is blood.
Then these are my clothes,
and these are the fish.
Yeah, why...?
This is the fish bowl up here, right?
And these are the fish, and this is the
floor. Why aren't the fish in the bowl?
- Because I don't want them there.
- But they can't live on the floor.
Art can be very abstract. It doesn't have
to make sense. Only in the artist's mind.
- Thank you, Khanya.
- Thank you for your interpretation.
OK, who's gonna be next?
You cannot tell me you did not
have fun in there with those kids.
I ain't sayin' it wasn't fun,
I just wasn't in the right mind-set.
Mind-set? You didn't think about
Jacqueline once in there.
True.
I bet you didn't think about
the Strangé commercial either. Right?
Yeah, you're right. The kids are a little
more inspirational than I've been lately.
Thank you.
- I got an idea.
- What?
I got an idea for the Strangé ad.
OK. Slow it down.
Right there.
OK. What do you think?
Well, I like it.
Hold it. Is that a nipple?
- That's not a nipple. That's a shadow.
- That's a nipple.
- Excuse me, that is a shadow.
- I think it's a shadow of a nipple.
Come on. Stop playing. That's a nipple.
- It's a shadow.
- I'll blow it up.
It's a nipple, cos I'm droolin'.
You a little nervous
about meeting Gerard's parents?
No, I'm not. I just don't want them
to think we're a couple, you know.
Don't even trip. Gerard ain't even
that close to his father, first of all.
You know, I knew it.
Gerard is really a fun guy, isn't he?
- He's very much fun.
- It's his father and his mother
that are the square ones.
- Right?
- I got it.
Happy Thanksgiving.
- Hey, what's up?
- Angela's over there.
How you doin', Mr Jackson?
Happy Thanksgiving.
- You look great.
- Thank you. So do you.
Thanks. My parents are here.
- You look just like your dad.
- Thanks.
- I brought you some chitterlings.
- Gerard's mother...
Angela, Gerard's mother brought us
a whole trough of chitterlings.
- I'll take the chitterlings.
- I want a bowl.
This the little girl you been
talkin' about? Agatha?
Angela. Angela Lewis.
- That's what I said.
- Nice to meet you.
Isn't she pretty?
She looks like one of Marcus' girls.
Agatha, go in the kitchen and help
Mrs Jackson with these chitterlings.
Cutie pie.
I have to talk to Mr Jackson.
Mr Jackson, come here.
So good to see you.
Every year, you do something new.
- Where'd you get the mushroom shirt?
- I'm trying to impress you.
I know. Now, where'd you get the shirt?
The secret is you got to coordinate.
Most people don't coordinate.
- See, you got to coordinate.
- That's what you did.
- Interesting.
- See? I told you they don't stink
- when you pull the membrane out.
- Momma.
- You saw me, saw the mushroom shirt.
- I said "mushroom shirt".
See, you can't stop
with the mushroom shirt.
- I would've stopped.
- You gotta keep goin'.
- Now, let me show you somethin'.
- You got on a mushroom belt.
Gerard, did you know your pops
had a mushroom belt on?
- Yes.
- But you don't stop there, see?
- You gotta keep goin'.
- What you got, a mushroom ring?
That's a good idea. Look what I got.
Gerard.
Did you know on the inside
was special mushrooms?
Yes.
Simply delicious, Marcus.
I tell Yvonne she should take cookin'
lessons from you. All she cook is pork.
I'll bet we've eaten everything
on the pig from the rooter to the tooter.
- The whole pig, huh?
- You didn't marry me for my cookin'.
You got that right, baby.
That's why we got junior.
Daddy, please.
Must you embarrass me in front
of my friends on every occasion?
Now, see? That's your son. Private
school got him all saddity like that.
Yeah, man, chill. That's your father.
Mr Jackson, Angela made this meal.
I can't take credit for it. It was Angela.
- v ery good.
- Good pick, junior.
- Daddy.
I told you that Angela and I
are just friends.
- Just friends, huh?
- Yes.
- Just friends.
- Leave it alone, hon.
They told you that 500 times.
Just let it go.
Fine. We'll change the subject.
Now, Marcus, I hear a girl
at the office got you pussy-whipped.
Why don't you reverse it?
Don't be pussy-whipped.
Whip that pussy. Look.
Daddy, please.
If you really insist on standin' around,
I don't dig the long face.
Man, my parents been in that bathroom
damn near an hour, man.
- So what?
- Well, they been in there hittin' it.
- Your parents are smokin' a joint?
- No, they been in there fuckin'.
Damn. Goodness.
What's for dessert? Wow.
I'm all right, man.
Let's go. Let's go eat, man.
- You don't want me to go with you?
- No, I'd better run them home
- before they embarrass me any further.
- OK.
I had a great time. I'll call you tomorrow.
Mrs Jackson. I cannot tell y'all
how much fun it is to be with y'all.
- So good.
- A piece of coat, I think.
Oh, boy. The rabbit is gettin' old, baby.
Look at that.
We could tear another piece off
and make some earrings. Coordinate.
- Yo, yo. Yo, got a hook-up for tonight.
- Who?
Remember that little girl I met in
Emergency? Baby got her stitches out.
- Well, whatever. I'll rap to you.
- All right. I gotta go.
- OK, bye, Tyler. Take care of yourself.
- See y'all later, all right?
- Later.
- Bye.
- You don't want me to help?
- I got it. Go on home.
OK.
Where's my coat?
Angela.
Yes?
I'm gonna have to
take you up on that offer.
- I thought so.
- Yes.
Chitterling juice everywhere,
and I don't know if I can handle it alone.
I'm so tired. I don't care if I never see
another cup or plate again in my life.
- My feet. Can I take my shoes off?
- Yeah, you can.
You'll have the whole house
smellin' like funky corn chips.
- Please, my feet do not stink.
- Star Trek's comin' on.
- I love Star Trek.
- Do you really?
- Yeah, I'm a Trekkie.
- Get outta here. I'm a Trekkie.
Ain't Captain Kirk the coolest
white man on the planet?
You can always tell who's gonna get
killed. Now, look who's beamin' down.
You see Kirk, McCoy, Spock,
and Yeoman Johnson.
Doesn't Yeoman Johnson know
he's gonna get killed?
If I was Yeoman Johnson, I'd say "I'm
not goin'. I know what's gonna happen".
It's amazing how you've just broken
down this whole Star Trek thing.
I'm a Trekkie, that's why. I broke it
down to the barest essence of the Trek.
I'm a Trekkie.
I know everything about Star Trek.
- What's Captain Kirk's first name?
- Captain.
No, it's not Captain.
His name is James T Kirk.
What's Mr Spock's last name?
You didn't even know that.
Name is Spock Jenkins.
One of the Jenkins boys from vulcan.
We'll talk about it later.
What are we doin'?
We're kissing.
We ain't supposed to be kissing.
- Why?
- Cos we're friends.
So?
Friends can kiss.
Do something
CRAZY
It's good. It's very good.
- Congratulations, Marcus.
- Congratulate Angela.
It was mostly her idea.
Nice going, Angela.
Thanks.
Hey, you.
Yo, man. It's racial.
- Well, expand.
- All right, check it out.
The white ball dominates everything.
Knocks the shit out of the yellow ball,
the red ball, right? And the game's over
when the white ball drives
the black ball completely off the table.
Now why is that?
I don't know, but I'm sure
you'll tell me, my brother.
Sure you right. Look...
It's because of the white man's fear
of the sexual potency of black balls.
Now, that one was kinda interesting.
I see where you're goin'.
- The pool table is earth, so it's green.
- See, your shit is comin' out now.
And the world,
they used to think it was flat.
School him.
When you do Oprah,
I wanna be front row.
It's not about jokes.
Me and him are here.
That one was kinda deep. You went to
the bottom of the ocean on that one.
- Losers get the beer.
- I'm gonna get the beer...
- But see how our thing is here?
- We are on the same wavelength.
- We're the same cat.
- Get him, then.
- I'll get him. I'm gonna work on him.
- Fine.
Yo, man, he's gettin' worse.
We got to find him a woman, quick.
He's gonna be all right.
Hey, how are things
with you and Angela?
We're cool, man. You know.
We went out a couple times,
and she was gettin' so involved.
And I said "Look,
I'm just gonna pull back."
Cool.
Yeah. You know, I told her
"Look here, girl, do your thing."
"See other men, cos I'm gonna
see other women, you know."
I just didn't wanna break her heart
right off. You know, I just pull out easy.
Good. You don't mind if
she goes out with other guys?
Hell, no.
You thinkin' of
hookin' her up with Tyler?
- No, nothin' like that.
- Why you askin', man?
I was just curious.
I don't believe this shit.
Why you askin', man?
You can't even look me in my eye,
can you, Marcus?
Did you sleep with Angela?
Yeah, I did.
Why do you always have
to have all the girls, Marcus?
You said you didn't care
who she went out with.
Now you're flippin'.
You're bein' a hypocrite.
I don't wanna hear that bullshit, man.
This is different. Angela is a nice girl.
- So I can't be with a nice girl?
- No.
Cos all you gonna do is dog her out,
like you do every woman in your life.
OK, tell me this, man. Why Angela?
What, she has nice feet?
It has nothin' to do with her feet.
I care about this girl.
Man, you don't care about
nobody but yourself, man.
So, when we can rise as a people,
we runnin' things, you know?
- What'd you do, man?
- Guess.
Marcus. Come quick.
I got somethin' I wanna show you.
- What?
- I wanna show you something.
- Get outta here. I'm in the shower.
- Marcus.
Stop.
Come on, I'm soakin' wet. You
gonna make me catch a cold out here.
No, I won't. Look.
Well? What do you think?
- Blue people. Yeah, that's nice.
- What do you think?
- Do you like it?
- Yes, very much.
OK, OK, OK. Look at it and
tell me how it makes you feel.
- Honestly, it's makin' me kinda horny.
- No. Feel.
- I'd like to think I was the inspiration.
- No. Look.
- I think you should be blue.
- No. You'll get paint all over me.
- The phone's ringing.
- I'll get paint on you.
Take your clothes off.
Take 'em off. Off. Clothes...
No. Hello?
Jacqueline. Hi.
How you doin'?
He's right here, actually.
No. No, we weren't busy at all.
Here he is. OK.
Hey. Yeah.
No, that was Angela.
She just stopped by for a second.
Really? That's...
Your spot tested through the roof.
Yeah. Yeah, she's happy.
Yes, absolutely. Absolutely.
That's perfect. Great.
Yeah. Peace.
They're showin' the spot
to the board of directors on Friday,
and Jacqueline wants me to be there.
Great.
Wait. You don't have
a problem with that?
- No.
- I will call her and tell her that...
You sure?
Cool. That's bad.
Blue people.
Peace. Chill.
You are brilliant. God, Marcus,
they loved it. They loved it.
Did you hear him
screamin' "magnifique"
with a bead of sweat runnin' down his
face, man? I knew I had that cat.
Marcus, you are incredibly talented.
Well, I thank you.
Lady Eloise thanks you.
Tell her I said hey.
I'm sure Strangé would like
to thank you personally.
Yeah, she'd like
to thank the hell outta me.
I have to say, it's very nice
to have the old Marcus back.
- I was kinda worried about you.
- Really?
You seemed...
You seemed so... I don't know.
- Can I be honest?
- Please.
Well, you seemed desperate,
and unsure of yourself.
- Pathetic?
- Kind of.
But look at you now. You're...
You're relaxed.
You're more confident.
Just like the man
I met in that elevator.
- I got it goin' on again?
- Yeah. I like it.
I find it very attractive.
How'd it go last night?
It went OK.
Just OK?
Must've gone pretty well. You didn't
get home until the middle of the night.
I went for a walk so I could sort
some things out that was in my head.
I was trippin' on it.
Like the fact that
you still love Jacqueline?
Angela, I saw the woman,
and a bunch of stuff in me
I didn't know was still there came out.
Things happened and... There's certain
things you just have no control over.
Really? Like what?
Like love.
Love?
You know,
what do you know about love?
What do you possibly think
you know about love?
I'm sick and tired of men using love
like it's a kind of disease you just catch.
Love should have brought
your ass home last night.
- Didn't you hear me say I was sorry?
- I heard you.
You're sorry and you're tired.
You don't love me or Jacqueline.
You only love your damn self.
How could you say
I never cared about you?
Jacqueline says that I'm a better person
now, and I owe that all to you.
I'm outta here.
I'll get the rest of my things later.
Let me just tell you one more thing.
I might not be all glamorous,
and I don't have hair down my back, but
let me tell you one great thing about me.
I've got a heart. You know the bad
thing about having a heart, Marcus?
It's that it gets broken
when you deal with people like you.
Now stay the fuck outta my life.
She left you, huh?
Yeah. She did.
I guess I should feel happy, but I don't.
I hate to see another person in pain.
Thank you very much. That's very nice
of you, Yvonne. Good night.
So, would you like to come over
for a cup of coffee?
Not even if Jesus was pourin' it.
Some motherfuckers can't see
a good thing when it's starin' at them.
Why don't you just leap your black ass
off the ledge, then? Fuck you.
- I can't do this.
- I have condoms.
No, it's not that. I gotta go.
What?
I'm in love with somebody.
Angela, right?
So now you think
you're in love with Angela.
No. No, no.
I know - just at this moment,
I know I'm in love with that woman.
Marcus, if you are in love with Angela,
why are you here with me?
Exactly.
Oh, shit. Dammit.
Hold up.
- Yo, whassup?
- Whassup?
Come on in.
- Welcome to the penthouse.
- It's kinda smoky in here, chief.
No, no. Wait. That ain't smoke, all right?
That's aroma.
Yo, can you get that for me?
Think that might be a little surprise.
Whassup, man? Where you goin'?
Yo, man. Talk.
Whassup, man?
Hey, how you doin'?
So have you seen Angela lately?
No, I hear she's over
at Barton and Dobbs now.
Yeah, I heard she got
promoted to creative director.
Really? Where'd you hear that?
Bony T told me.
Look, man.
- You don't have to say anything.
- I do. I'm really sorry, Gerard.
I've known you all my life, man. You're
like my brother, you know, and I...
I love you and I...
I don't wanna go through this, man.
Listen, it happened,
and I'm sorry, and I feel bad.
How long you gonna have me beg?
You know what I'm tryin' to say.
You gonna
milk all the apologies outta me.
It's cool.
- All right, man.
- My man.
Yo, man! Whassup? Y'all gonna let a
girl come between us, man? What's up?
We supposed to be here, man.
We boys, man.
We don't hang out no more or nothin',
man. Man, this shit hurt, man.
- Y'all make up now, man.
- We just, you know, made up, man.
Well, then, hug.
We hugged just now, and gave
each other a pat and we boys again.
- All right. Give it to me.
- We hugged already.
No, man. I want
a big motherfuckin' hug, man.
Damn, man. I love y'all, man.
- Y'all ready to eat?
- Yeah.
All right.
Yo, is that my shit?
Damn, not the penthouse.
No. It's all wrong.
You know that memo I showed you?
Refer to it and show me
a new mock-up in the morning.
This is way off, Tye. We are not
gonna shoot this until it's right.
- Angela.
- Come on.
- Hi. We're lookin' for Angela...
- We are not.
What?
Excuse me for a second, please.
- What are you two doing here?
- Angela.
- I haven't seen you in so long.
- Four months, two weeks, to be exact.
- Thank you.
- We miss you. Where have you been?
I miss you, too, and I've been working.
I got a new job. It's very demanding.
It requires me to work long hours,
and I haven't had the time
to teach the class. I'm sorry.
You always had time for us.
I know. Let me tell you somethin', OK?
You know what I had to do? I had
to rearrange my priorities in life.
Angela had to start
lookin' out for Angela.
- How'd you get here, anyway?
- Our new teacher brought us.
- Your new teacher? Where is she?
- He.
Well, where is he?
I think we best get goin' now.
Goodbye, my queen.
- OK.
- Peace.
My brother.
It's pretty low using the kids, Marcus.
What else could I do? I been sendin'
you letters and I know you got 'em.
I'm just not real big
on words on paper these days.
OK. I know I fucked up.
You're damn right you fucked up.
You hurt me.
I miss you.
No. I really, really miss you.
I've never missed anybody in my life
and I miss you. I'm in love with you.
It isn't about your love. It's the fact that
you can't love me the way I deserve.
That's what this is about.
You think I'd bother you unless I was
ready to be everything you wanted?
I wanna be straight up about
everything. I want monogamy.
You are my best friend. I'm miserable.
- I even quit my job because of you.
- Did I ask you to quit your job?
- Why are you doin' this?
- Doing what?
Bein' all stiff and cold,
and hidin' behind your work.
I'm taking care of my business,
and I suggest you take care of yours.
Listen.
I know havin' a great job is cool
and all of that but...
you used to have a good time.
You used to be with these kids
and we used to have fun.
We had a great life. You had everything.
Give me one reason
why I should take you back. One.
I didn't think you could.
Do you still love me?
Because I love you so much.
I miss you.
I'm scared.
And I'm miserable.
I can't breathe without you.
I can't breathe.
We should go get your things
and go to my place.
No. I'm not moving into your house
this time. I'm staying in my place.
I want 24-7.
- No.
- That's how committed I am.
No. No. I'm not doin' it.
If you turn and look at her
I will break your fuckin' neck.
I was lookin' at this woman, thinkin'
about the future. That's you in 15 years.
- You better still love me.
- She's by herself. I'm playin'. It's you.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org