Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Don't give up.
Oh, I never do.
May I?
Your work with your hands, don't you?
- Hey, Red.
- Luther.
Your life would be a lot simpler
if you could learn to operate a VCR.
True.
Truer words were never spoken.
Let's see.
Here we go.
That's nice.
It's okay, he's not here.
Anyway, I told him that...
...I was sick...
...so you can relax.
Cheers.
I'll be right back.
You like that, huh?
Oh, yeah.
So, you want to play, huh?
You okay?
How'd you like that?
- You slap me?
- Don't slap me.
Little bitch.
Alan, what are you doing?
Alan!
Stop it.
Alan, you're hurting me.
I'll hurt you good.
You're hurting me.
Goddamn you!
You want to be hurt?
I'll hurt you.
- Let go!
- Do you?
You like that?
God damn you.
- Get away.
- Fucking bitch.
- Get back here.
Get back here!
Stop it!
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Bitch.
You bitch.
Want to play? I'll show you how.
You fucking bastard.
You bastard.
You like that?
Come back here.
Let go of me!
You bitch, you cut me...
...Goddamn it.
Fucking asshole.
- I'll kill you.
- Bitch.
Help!
Did you kill her?
No choice in the matter, sir.
What am I going to do?
Jesus, Tim, what did we do?
No choice in the matter.
What the hell was that?
Oh, shit.
My God.
Oh, my God.
Jesus.
Do you realize what
a shit storm we're in?
Come on, tell me.
Nothing to tell. He screamed for help.
You heard no sounds
of violence till then?
Nothing we haven't heard before.
- Maybe I should call the police now.
- Jesus.
What?
Bill?
Why don't you think about that.
Just take a second...
...and think about that.
Think real...
...fucking...
...hard.
It's...
...probably not a good idea.
Here's what happened.
Poor Christy...
...came home alone...
...and interrupted a burglary.
Sound logical?
Sure.
We'll have to sanitize this place.
Did you have sex with her?
I don't know.
You'll have to examine her.
- I'm no gynecologist.
- I just made you one.
Christ.
- I'll take that.
- Both their fingerprints are on it.
Thanks for sharing.
Gloria?
- Did I kill her?
- Everything'll be fine. Come on...
...just don't worry about it.
- Oh, God.
- Now be careful.
Just don't get blood on you.
I'll take care of everything, okay?
Just like I always do.
- Shit!
- What?
Madame's purse.
Miss Russell. Let me get him.
Thank you.
- I got him.
- Fine.
Nice and easy, sir.
My God!
No knife!
- What?
- Where's the knife?
In the bedroom.
- Come on.
- Get up there.
Shit.
Go!
Excuse me.
I got the number.
Gee, guys, maybe it was the bogey man.
Don't forget to check under the bed.
You may have buried us.
I got his license, remember?
You think he'll sit around
waiting for us, asshole?
Take it easy, Miss Russell.
Everybody shut up, all right?
What have you got?
Oh, boy.
Okay, Tim.
Two-way mirror.
We better get cracking
on that license number.
That's all we've got.
He's got the letter opener.
Blood.
Fingerprints.
Jesus...
...think what he can do.
The man's a thief.
A thief who witnessed a murder.
It looks like he stole
a bunch of money.
I'll tell you what he'll do.
He'll run like hell.
They beat us by seven.
By seven.
Who'd have thought that.
Kate.
It'd be a little late for me,
wouldn't it?
The jogging, I mean.
Kind of dumb way to start, isn't it?
But I did...
...want to talk to you.
About?
About the weather, actually.
Getting kind of cool in the evenings.
That happens this time of year.
I was thinking of...
...moving to a kinder,
more gentle climate.
I thought I'd talk it over with you...
...since you're my only family.
Luther, you don't have me.
I was the only kid at show-and-tell
who got to talk about visiting day.
This move, it would be a...
...permanent one, you understand?
We never see each other anyway.
I haven't seen you since Mom died.
That's a year.
Look...
...you had a right to choose your life.
You were never around.
Fine.
I have no plans to be around for you.
Wait a minute. Wait.
You're lying, aren't you?
Are you active again?
Is that why you're here now?
I don't believe you.
Oh, Christ.
Father, what have you done?
Christy Sullivan?
Wife of Walter. Most likely came home
and stumbled onto a burglary.
Some burglary.
I wish my carpets were this clean.
I couldn't find one decent fingerprint.
- Are you serious, Laura?
- It's like Mary Poppins was here.
Where's Mr. Sullivan?
Sorry, Seth.
The entire Sullivan household
went to Barbados two days ago.
Thanks for your support.
No, wait. It gets worse.
The shots came from here.
If she stumbled on a burglary...
...she'd have been here. But she
was killed exactly where she is.
The blood patterns indicate that.
What's she doing here?
Looks like someone sat here,
but I couldn't find any prints.
Think old man Sullivan hid in this
chair and watched his wife perform?
Oh, God, I hope not.
For his sake. He's such a great man.
Be careful, now, digging that out.
Seems he tried to strangle her.
Then he went to the door
to shoot her from behind?
He also inspected her vagina.
He did what?
Why?
Maybe he didn't remember he did her.
A strong burglar with a weak mind.
Obviously, it's another
open-and-shut case.
Tomorrow's temperatures should climb
into the 70's, with lows around 50.
Mr. Sullivan?
Sorry to bother you.
Seth Frank, senior homicide detective
for Middleton County.
My client's in no mood
for conversation, sir.
That's all right, Sandy.
You're in charge of the case,
Mr. Frank?
Yes, sir.
I must ask you a few questions.
What is it you want?
Positive identification?
That was my wife.
Anything else?
You were in Barbados for two days?
I took the staff.
Always do this time of year.
Your wife didn't come with you?
Well, she was.
Had it all planned...
...but you know women.
She changed her mind.
I had been married to my Rebecca
for 47 years.
When she died...
...I decided I never wanted
that pain again.
One thing I knew about Christy:
She was going to outlive me.
I think that's enough for today.
Sir, I have to ask you about the vault.
You mean the contents
of the vault, of course.
- Sandy, you go on.
- Walter?
No, really, I'm all right.
You go on to the reception.
Obviously I can't make it.
I'm sure everyone will understand.
You don't mean the contents.
You mean the chair.
You must ask about the chair.
Yes, sir, I do.
Why? Are they connected?
Someone may have been sitting in it
and have been involved in the murder.
You're a great man. I've the deepest
respect for you. I'm sorry to do this.
I promise you none of this
will make my highlight reel.
Well, I hoped I could satisfy her...
...but you know, she...
...had needs and she...
...didn't want to go behind my back.
She suggested the chair.
She hoped I might get
to like sitting there.
I didn't.
For 80 years I've tried to live...
...a decent life.
I've given a billion dollars
to charity.
If this comes to trial...
...none of that will be remembered.
I'll just go out...
...the joke of the world.
I understand, sir.
I'll do what I can.
Will you listen to me whine?
I apologize...
...Mr. Frank.
Just do your job, huh?
- And I'll try to do mine.
- Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, sir.
General.
Ladies and gentlemen...
The President.
Sandy.
Mister President.
- Take a walk with me.
- Certainly, sir.
Tell me about Walter. How is he?
Well, he's 80 and alone, Mr. President.
He understands that, officially,
my hands are tied.
But he's very moved
by your concern, sir.
- Any news of the killer?
- No.
Why isn't there? Who's in charge?
Top man.
He spent eight years,
homicide work in New York.
I understand how you feel.
It's hard to be patient.
No one understands how I feel.
I'm supposed to have all this power...
...and I can't even help
my oldest friend.
You and I know,
more than any man alive...
...Walter Sullivan put me here.
And now when he needs me most...
...well, he must feel abandoned.
I'll have a press conference.
I'll have Walter come.
I'll embrace him in front of the world.
He'll treasure that, Mr. President.
What a generous gesture.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
Tennis elbow.
This thing is getting worse, Gloria.
I need to see a doctor.
The country would have
to be informed, Mr. President.
What happened to my rights to privacy?
I think she nicked a tendon.
Burton says it's a flesh wound.
Since when did you become
an expert, Bill?
You ever been wounded?
Yes, sir. A few times.
Are you serious about
this press conference?
Of course I am.
Walter's like a father to me.
Shall I bring Mrs. Richmond
home for it?
I don't think Mrs. Richmond's
mission...
...to help the poor in Asia
needs to be interrupted.
What do we know so far?
We've checked his license plates.
He stole the car from
a police impoundment lot.
We're not dealing with
a fool here, are we?
Has he initiated contact?
Burton doesn't think he will.
I agree.
I apologize. This won't happen again.
Consider it a blip...
...on the screen.
That's all he is, too.
He could be a little more than that.
He saw.
He saw nothing but a drunk woman
who liked rough sex too much.
He's a burglar.
Who'll believe him?
It's not as if he has
any evidence or anything.
He's a burglar. Who'll believe him?
It's not as if he has
any evidence or anything.
Boy, you always did
disappear good, Luther.
You're trying to say
I have a weak face, right?
I'm just saying you're lucky.
Some of my customers, no matter
what I do, still stand out.
How many passports you want?
Four should do the trick.
Different looks, matching
international driver's licenses.
Since it's you I'll throw in
some dummy credit cards.
How are the rugs I made you holding up?
Good. The mustaches
and the beards also.
We try to give quality for our money.
You leaving the country for permanent?
That could be, yeah.
Does it matter where you've been?
I hate doing...
...those Asian passport stamps.
Make it European and the Caribbean
in the winter and...
How long will all this take?
It usually takes some time.
For you I'll rush it.
You were always very dependable.
Listen, Luther.
I don't want to know what you're into.
I do, but I won't ask.
But leaving the country forever...
What is it?
I just never figured you for a runner.
Luther, 30% of my runners,
they kill themselves within five years.
Right now, five years
doesn't sound too bad.
Take care.
See you.
Okay, see if this makes any sense.
I am Christy Sullivan...
...I come in a bedroom
and I surprise a burglar.
Now, you're the burglar
coming out of the vault.
Gold star. I draw my gun. Boom.
Why bother to strangle her
when you could shoot?
Why do I bother to strip her and
then put her clothes back on?
There I can help you out.
Before you were a burglar
you were a dry cleaner...
...and you love beautiful clothes.
Thanks a lot.
And you dress her because...
She was a good customer and you didn't
want her to be embarrassed.
She had a 0.21 blood alcohol level,
not that that makes any difference.
She didn't drive.
The chauffeurs, they keep
exact mileage on these cars.
They haven't been driven
since the clan left town.
I checked every cab and limo service.
No one knows a thing.
Somebody drove her home. Who?
- Why haven't they come forward?
- Maybe...
...because whoever drove her home
killed her.
Maybe.
I love this case.
Lieutenant?
The problems you had with the phones?
- Just took care of them.
- Thank you.
Just part of the job.
I hate people who say that.
It is your fucking job.
Remember the bullet hole in the wall?
Guess what?
No slug.
Why take a slug out of the wall
when there's one stuck in her head?
Different from the one in her body?
Two different guns means two burglars.
Two guys broke in? They both
went out the window? That's bullshit.
By the way...
...why he or they go out the window
in the first place, when he or they...
...got in by breaking
a zillion-dollar security system?
A Bill Burton from Secret Service
is in the parking lot.
Thanks. What's Secret Service
doing in the parking lot?
Bill Burton. Hi.
Seth Frank.
To what do I owe the honor?
I know you must be going crazy, but the
boss is interested about your progress.
We could help each other out.
What do you have in mind?
You know how close he and Sullivan are.
Right.
Well.
The minute anything breaks...
...call me and I'll tell the president.
He'd be the first to alert Mr. Sullivan.
It'd mean a lot to him.
And any red tape you want cut, done.
Here's my numbers.
Any leads?
We're still trying to figure it out.
- I loved playing Sherlock Holmes.
- Secret Service guys do that?
I was a state trooper before
the government got me.
Wait. You're that Bill Burton?
I was younger and dumber then.
I was younger.
I think I'm dumber now.
Keep in touch.
My chef makes them especially for me.
I promise you, they're sinful.
You're a salesman, Mr. Sullivan.
This is a new arena for me...
...but from what I'm told, you...
...have a flawless reputation...
...which is why I need
to employ you, Mr. McCarty.
Understood.
I don't know who it is I'm after yet.
Until I do...
...you'll have to wait in Washington
for instructions.
I'm afraid that's out of the question.
My work is not very creative...
...and I do it because I enjoy living
beyond my means.
I can't afford to just sit around.
My father died when
I was ten years old.
He was a miner.
He died of lung disease.
I became rich at 25.
The first thing I did was buy
that mine, close it down...
...and give every miner
$50,000 to retire on.
You will wait in Washington,
Mr. McCarty...
...and I will put...
...one million dollars expenses...
...in a Swiss bank of your choosing...
...and...
...when the time comes...
...two million dollars a bullet.
You are a salesman, sir.
Selling sin is easy.
- Who is he?
- That's Luther Whitney...
...one of the world's great thieves.
I'm going nuts with this.
I was up all night.
I remembered your notion about
how maybe it was two burglars.
Around dawn I thought:
What if it's not two burglars
but what if it's one guy...
...trying to throw us off
by making it look like two?
I called the FBI.
They keep track of this stuff.
There's maybe six guys who
could have done the Sullivan job.
I've traced all six...
...only Whitney lives in Washington.
Why's it I never heard of him?
'Cause he hasn't been arrested
in 30 years.
What's this? His graduation picture
from Harvard?
That's ancient history.
He was part of a gang.
Three-time loser.
Since he got out the last time...
...no one's touched him.
Anytime something big comes up
they question him, but it never sticks.
We can make this stick.
I bet this is our guy. He's local.
You can't ask for anything more.
Well, we got a problem.
What?
He hasn't killed anyone in 45 years.
Korea.
So what, he's a veteran.
He's not just a veteran.
He's a wounded veteran.
I got his war record here.
Battles, commendations...
...decorations up the kazoo.
He lives alone on his disability.
That's what he says anyway. But...
I don't see this guy as a killer.
He's just a great thief.
Besides, I don't do war heroes.
Well, you must be smart.
Pardon me?
Usually it takes you guys
a week to get to me.
I recognize your picture...
...from the newspaper.
Nice to meet you.
Would you like a signed confession now,
or would you like to have coffee first?
Before I send you away for life,
I should check out your alibi.
I was watching football...
...with a friend, Red Bransford.
He owns a saloon here in town.
You can ask me about the game
if you like. I could be lying.
You've been following the case?
I have.
I love true crime.
FBI says only a few guys could handle
the Sullivan job. I got a list.
You're on it.
How I wish it were true.
This person, they...
...they go in the front door, then out
a window and down a rope at night?
If I could do something like that I'd
be the star of my A.A.R.P. Meetings.
What, the American...?
Association of Retired Persons.
Luther, why was this so difficult?
You want me to help you
solve your case?
Just looking for insight.
How would you...
Scratch that.
How would one go about it?
What kind of person should I look for?
Except for the rope trick,
an older person. Like me.
Because?
Well, you need patience.
The secret is research.
At least I've read that.
What kind of research?
From what I saw on the tube,
this is a rather large home.
There must be an architectural office.
You'd have to go to the library,
go through public records...
...find out where that office is
and then you break in.
You xerox the plans and
get them back by morning.
Why not just steal them?
Anyone can break in, but breaking in...
...without people knowing it,
that's the trick.
Then there's the general contractor...
...and there's the security company.
Do you realize the skill in breaking
the security of a security company?
I don't know how those guys do it.
Why go to all that trouble?
It's a large vault. There must be
a secret way into it.
There was, that's what I don't get.
How do you mean?
This guy had obviously done
the research you're talking about.
So why take a crowbar
to open this vault...
...when there's a clicker right there?
Clicker?
Gizmo. Like a VCR remote.
Sounds amazing to me.
Must have been a lot of valuables
in that vault.
Close to five million, total value.
Is that funny?
Are you trying to surprise me?
I was trying to surprise you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
There you go again.
Would the burglar use a disguise?
He might.
Get with the program,
if you want to catch this guy.
It is a guy, we think?
Some sort of a loner? Weirdo, yeah?
Maybe like you.
I'd be the perfect prototype, actually.
But you see a person long enough,
you start putting things together.
That's why these top guys
have disguises.
Some of them, I understand,
become make-up experts.
Hire wigmakers and things like that.
Why don't you go on
about the wigmakers?
Well, I would...
I must go have my pacemaker checked.
It's been so exciting talking to you.
A: You don't have a pacemaker.
And B: I'll be back tomorrow.
Tomorrow is promised to no one.
Good-bye.
Pacemaker, my ass.
Oh, Katie.
You must start eating
better than this, darling.
I'm having this
press conference here...
...because it is at this courthouse...
...that Christine Sullivan's killer
will be tried for his crime.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org