- Don't touch me.
- I'm chatting to you.
- Shut up.
- Where you going? Where you going?
There better be something
in your fucking eye, blood.
- Who the fuck are you?
- Balance, man.
Hey! That car's shabby, blood.
- Who's my man looking at, though?
- Fucking kids.
Why is he showing what he's got,
like he's a big man?
- He's an idiot, man.
A man like that ain't nothing around here.
You know what? Fuck it, let's jack
this bre, man. Are you man on it?
Course. That man there
should be sharing the wealth, man.
Yeah, I'm on it still.
- Me and you, Dabs, yeah?
- What?
Yeah. All right.
Yous two wait here.
Come on... Nah, man. Am I a dickhead?
Why am I waiting here for?
This happens all the time.
Am I a dickhead, though?
I'll take the passenger side.
Come on. For fuck's sake.
Come on.
- Fuck! What are you doing, you fuckers?
- Let go of me, blood!
You fuckers! What are you doing?
You fuckers!
It's a fucking gun!
Argh!
Argh! Argh!
- What you get?
- Watch. What'd you get?
- Nothing.
Fuckers!
Hey, keep your chin up.
Stay out of trouble.
Say my name!
It's Jay, on a hot thing!
What, my man?
I told you,
I'll blow your man later, innit.
- Jay, get off the phone.
- Hold on, man.
I'm banging at that Polly gash.
No, not that one, blood,
the one from...
- Yeah, yeah...
- Jay! I'm gonna be late for uni.
Can't you see I'm busy, like?
I'm a business, babe. Like a doctor.
I gotta be on call. You get me?
Hey, blood.
I beg you bell me back, yeah?
Safe.
What did you want to tell me
that's so important it can't wait?
Can you at least pay attention to me
when we're fucking?
Hey, listen, shut your mouth, man.
I do pay you attention, babe.
Didn't we shave my name into your pussy...
hair the other night,
huh? That's attention.
We'll finish off, yeah?
Aw! Has he gone to sleep?
Oh, shut up, man!
This ain't happened to me before.
Oh... maybe once.
Now, you better swallow.
Go away, man!
First day out, man.
So what you gonna do?
Dunno, blood.
See my mum.
Just wanna have a peaceful day.
You're simple, cuz, man.
I'm gonna get me a couple of girls,
get fucked all day, man.
Sweet boy like you must have a ting
you used to bang, man.
Babe.
- Do you wanna get some breakfast?
- Yeah.
- See you soon then, mate.
- Fuck out, man.
Sam.
You need something... anything...
just give me a bell
and I'll sort it, yeah?
Yeah. Bless, Big Man.
Hey, Chinatown!
You still owe me that fuck,
you know.
Now, your cousin said
if she couldn't pay, you would.
So tomorrow,
my money, my drugs, or you.
I gotta go work.
- What?
- You gonna take that from her?
I remember that one chick.
- I went back to her house, bruv.
- What happened?
Her dad came home, innit,
so man had to jump out the window.
I was running down the street in my
boxers and my socks. I was pissed.
Oh, shit, you'd feel pissed...
- Sorry, would you like to sit down?
- Thanks.
You cool, blood?
Yeah, I'm bless, man. You?
Yeah, man.
I'm good.
I'm Jahvon, blood.
Do I know you, cuz?
No, bro.
Can't a man chat?
Yeah, man, safe.
Talk, innit.
It's not safe, though.
What you move for? We're having a little
chat - I chat to you, you chat to me.
What you getting nervous for?
Just come out of jail, man.
That shouldn't make you feel nervous.
That should make you feel good.
What'd you go in for?
What'd you go in for, blood? !
I don't wanna chat about it.
Bet I guess what you went in for.
Don't tell me, let me guess.
I think you hurt someone.
I'm thinking someone died.
Like you killed them or something.
You're a clever one,
ain't you, blood?
I don't think you stabbed no one, though.
You don't look like the type.
If you was gonna do something to a bre,
I think you'd use a baseball bat.
- Low it, man. Low it!
- My fucking cousin, blood!
What's this about, blood?
What's it about?
You ain't gonna survive this day.
I guarantee it!
Man's coming for you.
Your mum, your family, everything!
Who's coming?
Who's gonna hurt my mum?
Who, blood? Who?
Mum! Roy!
Come from yout offenders?
What you in for?
Killed one yout.
Don't feel you're big in here
just cos you killed someone.
Enough man in here done that.
Some of them man ain't even affected.
You get me?
You are.
I can see it in your eyes.
Who gave you that black eye?
Listen, blood, watch them man.
See my man there?
They don't get on.
Trust me, don't let any of them see
you're weak, blood.
You want something?
You keep watching me.
Whenever you and your boyfriend
are ready, you can see what go on.
What's your dad's name, blood?
Dunno. I ain't got one. Why?
Cos, like, my mum tried to introduce me
to some broke-down yellow-teeth
waste man, yeah, called Cedric.
And hear this - he's coming into my house
telling me about how he's my dad.
But I'm like,
"You're not my fucking dad."
He had that ting Michael Jackson
said he's got. He looked like a panda.
I said, "Move from my house
with your polka-dot skin..."
Why's he taking so long, man?
Yeah!
I swear my maths teacher
lives somewhere round here.
And she's buff, blood.
I wanna fuck that.
I could quote algebra
while I'm in the pussy.
Q=Z means "Yeah!"
Get me? Why do you think
she's always giving me As?
You don't get As, blood.
- Who don't?
- Fool.
Don't get it twisted.
Just cos I'm with you,
don't think I'm stupid. I got plans.
Although I might have to bang
my English teacher as well.
Who? Mr Randall? You batty...
No, man. Shut up.
It's a woman, man. You know that.
- Yo, blood, it's broad daylight, man!
- If you're shook, leave, innit.
Yes, Ike.
What you man got?
That ain't fake, man.
I got it last night.
I'll give you six for both tings.
What?
Six, blood.
You know what? I'll throw in a piece
of yay each. You'll have to wait, though.
I gotta go, bruv.
I got a mark-up booked, innit.
Safe, man. We'll wait here.
All right, later, you man.
You man wait here.
I gonna deal with a little ting.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, come we play this.
- Hey, pass the controller.
- Tss!
- What? !
- You deaf, blood?
He said pass the controller.
You fool.
Hey, I'm Arsenal, blood.
Who was it?
Omen and Dabs and them man.
So you understand
what I was saying to you before?
Yeah.
Even my man had to
learn the hard way, you know.
See this?
Some fucker done that to me.
You're all right.
I'm not into face-cutting.
Something about the face
makes people too angry.
But he was right to do what he did.
I took the fucking piss like you are.
You know what, blood?
I don't even know this Curtis brother. Hm?
But he was trying to do his ting.
You understand?
And Andreas here, he fucked up.
And now us man,
we're trying to do our little ting.
And you are fucking up.
You understand?
- Yeah, bruv, but I was...
- Uh.
Listen, we like you, blood.
I like you.
But I can't have you
making money off of my shit.
- It's mine.
- I... I...
Now you're gonna have to learn, blood.
Argh!
Oh, fuck! Argh!
Safe.
Where'd you park?
About three roads away.
Come on, we'll have a walk.
I've got to meet Jon and Vern at the shop.
You're one lazy cow,
do you know that?
I'll go and get it and them,
then I'll come back and get you, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Giz a kiss.
Unbelievable. Unbelievable.
Hayden!
Shh!
Claire. Claire. Shh!
I'm not gonna hurt you, I swear.
I just wanna speak to you.
Hayden!
Promise me you're not gonna scream.
Promise?
- Mm-hm.
- Yeah?
What do you want?
Some bre attacked me when I come out.
Said people are gonna hurt me, my family.
I don't want that.
I done my fucking time.
- What'd you come to me for?
- Have you seen my mum anywhere?
That was six years ago.
I haven't seen any of them.
I haven't seen your mum in, like, a year.
- What about my brother? You seen him?
- No!
Claire, you must know something.
Just tell me anything, please.
Moony goes Central University.
That's all I know.
Now just fuck off and leave me alone.
I don't wanna get involved in any of this.
- D'you want something?
- Mind your business.
What?
Who the fucking hell are you?
- Do you know him? Is he bothering you?
- Yeah.
All right, jog on, bruv, yeah?
Do yourself a favour and fuck off.
Hey, blood, don't fucking touch me!
What part of me
looks like your fucking blood?
Sam, just fuck off.
Sam? Fucking Sam?
Fucking Sam, yeah?
She still has nightmares because of you.
She flinches if I move too quickly.
- You fucking wrong 'un!
- I'm just talking to her. I've finished.
- Leave it.
- I'm all right, mate. I'm all right.
Like you said, you're finished, so do
yourself a favour and fuck off. Yeah?
Go and get in the car, babe.
You've had a squeeze.
Hey, babe.
Robert, you know we've got basic ethics
and understanding of law on Monday?
I could really use some help
getting my head around it.
Yeah, of course. Anything I can do. Give
me your number and I'll give you a call.
- Thank you.
- I'll see you later?
Bye.
- Don't think you're calling her.
- Of course not, babe. You're my girl, man.
- So, how was your class?
- It was all right...
Moony.
- How the fuck did you find me, blood?
- I saw Claire.
She said you went to that uni
and I just asked a few people.
- A guy try bore me up today.
- So?
He's telling me mans is gonna hurt my
family because of what happened to Trife.
Don't mention his name.
You have no right to say his name.
If it's you, if you're
involved in this, I just...
wanna tell you that I'm not on it, blood.
I'm not on dem tings no more.
We was all young.
I'm just about my studies,
money and my girl.
If you're not on it, you know how I feel.
Do you know where I can find them lot?
Just so I can tell them
I'm not into this beef ting.
Saw Becky a couple of months ago.
She works in that salon ting in Grove.
Don't know where Alisa is, and Jay...
You don't wanna see Jay. He ain't planned
nothing but he ain't forgotten you.
Yeah? Why don't you give me his number
so I can tell him that I want this over?
- Are you dumb, blood?
- Come on, man.
What d'you mean, "Come on, man"?
Don't talk like we're fucking friends!
You're any bre to me, understand? I ain't
forgiven you and I'm giving you nothing.
Can you two leave,
or I'll call the police.
Know why I'm studying law, blood? So...
mans like you don't get
out after six years!
- Tell Jay I want to see him.
- Are you sure you want that?
If I told Jay you're out,
you wouldn't need to look for him.
He'll find you,
and he will want arms.
Dickhead!
It's a ball, but I suppose you can come.
You'd have to dress up a bit, mind you -
I've had the best week.
I don't want your fucking life story.
I told my friends you've got the best shit
on the street, cos that's what Giles does.
Put your fucking hand down, blood.
You're baiting me up, man.
I'm not being funny,
but I've got a barbecue to go to.
Oh, shit!
Just relax, man.
- Give me my shit before they come back.
- I told you to put your hand down.
- Blood, if I had to run, yeah...
- Jason, don't be such a drama queen...
What the fuck do you think...
You ain't getting shit, bruv.
Oi! You! Stand by that pole! Now!
Furthermore, yeah, take all your
fucking shit and put it in my bag, blood.
What have you got on you, man?
What the fuck you got on you?
Give me your fucking ring.
Please! That's her engagement ring.
It's French 17th century.
Shut the fuck up, man! Hurry up, blood.
Put the watch in the bag as well.
Blood, hurry the fuck up
or I will shank you, man.
Jay, just let us go. I'm a good customer.
I'll give you anything.
You, blood? I don't need
your lickle business, man.
You're anything to me, blood.
The amount of white man I get.
What?
What, you think you're big, Giles?
Show your yuppie girl you know where
to score to impress her? You're a pussy.
Let me show you
what a little pussy you are, blood, yeah?
Show me your titties.
Before I murk your man.
For goodness' sake,
just show him the titties!
Run! Tammy, come on!
Are you mad, bruv?
The fuck you doing, bruv?
The fuck you doing, man? !
Hold on, yeah?
Hello? Jahvon.
What you saying, man?
What?
Sam? What, at the cemetery?
Where's he now?
Fuck him, blood!
He's a dead man!
He's dead tonight.
Nah. No, you go home, blood.
I'll get Moony and handle it.
You better thank God
something else has come up.
- Well, thank him, then!
- Thank you, God! Oh, thank you, God.
Get out of here, man.
Arsehole!
Tammy!
Max? Can I just...
please nip out for a?
Make sure you wash your hands
when you get back in.
Come outside.
One second.
Hey, cokehead!
Where's your fucking cousin?
- Think I don't know what she tried to do?
- Fuck off. Is this a joke?
It ain't no joke. My man showed me that...
she tried to move to
him at the drinks ting.
And you were there skinning your teeth.
You thought because I was on holiday
I'd forget about it?
Listen, your man
pushed himself up on us, yeah.
If your tings ain't tight enough
to keep his dick pointed at you...
She ain't even fucking worth it.
Where is she?
I don't fucking know where she is.
I don't care where she is.
Forget this. Find your fucking cousin and
both you get back to whoring yourselves.
What? You think I don't know about you?
Listen.
We all know about you.
Shiners for a fiver.
And you're fucking for a score.
- I never did any of that.
- So what about for a bit of coke?
Is that why I've heard
you've had all them dicks inside you?
- You fuck... Ow!
- What you saying?
Come off me, man.
- What the fuck is going on?
- She flipped out and attacked me.
Anna, Lisa, go to lunch. Now! Go. OK!
Yeah, that's...
Now, look, Lexi, I know
you've been a bit...
stressed. I want you to
take a few days off.
Please don't fire me! I need this job.
I can barely afford to pay my rent...
I'm not going to fire you.
Come in on Tuesday. All right?
Today I want you to go in there,
get your stuff, and go home.
Sorry, ladies,
that will not happen again.
Can I speak to Becky, please?
What do you want her for?
Who are you?
Jay.
I don't wanna get involved, man.
I'm not scared.
But I'm about positivity,
like that black Jedi guy from Star Wars.
All right, I'll see you later. I'll see you
at Hammersmith later. I'll be there, man!
- Robert, what is going on?
- Low it, babe, yeah?
You don't remember me, do you?
Alex. Lexi, innit? Becky's cousin.
There's no reason you should. I was
two years younger and you was a cunt.
I left in year 11
while you was still in sixth form.
Picking on boys
and trying to fuck girls in year 10...
- So what d'you wanna see her for?
- I thought she might know who's after me.
Yeah, she might, but I ain't seen her.
No one has. She's fucked off, innit.
Look, yeah, I didn't know Trife well,
but... it's fucked-up he's dead.
- So do you know anything?
- Why the fuck would I know anything?
I know some of them lot from school
and through her,
but not well enough to know
who's after you.
Or to give a fuck for that matter.
Well, that's it, innit?
What else do you want me to say?
You've gone jail, come out - what?
I ain't got nothing
against you, but I don't...
think we got anything more to chat about.
Ask that girl you was banging,
they was mates.
Claire? I asked that chick already.
She don't know nothing.
That girl was grimy.
Always losing her knickers. After lunch
she'd not know where she'd left 'em.
I remember you now.
You was always on your own, innit?
Yeah. My boyfriend went to a different
school, so I didn't chat with boys.
Girls didn't like me, so...
I got to the point where I did more things
to piss 'em off. You get me?
Fuck it. If they ain't gonna love you,
make 'em hate.
I beg you a browns, Lex?
Who's your friend?
No. He ain't a friend.
Cool.
Yout!
- Safe for what you did, blood.
- I didn't do nothing, man.
Listen, I ain't trying to be
spars with you, you know.
You don't have to affiliate yourself
with me. I'm just saying safe, that's all.
Don't worry about it, boys.
It gets better.
I'm getting out tomorrow. Can't wait
to see my kids. You got any kids?
Know anyone that's got any kids?
Suit yourself.
Oi, Lex! What about Alisa?
You know some of them lot.
Can you get her to speak to me?
I've not spoken to her but I could get her
number. You know she had a daughter?
- Yeah. Can I have it?
- Her daughter? Oh, her number? No.
I'll get to her, see if she wants
to chat to you, but I doubt it.
I'm not high on the list of people
she wants to chat to either.
Here what. I got my mum's mobes,
I'll give you the digits.
I beg you bell mans
if she wants to speak or anything.
Yeah, safe for doing this, yeah?
Hey, can you get any gear and that?
Like, cheap?
Nah, man.
Oi, what's it like
knowing you've killed someone?
Blood, I need that ting off you now.
I don't give a fuck.
I want him dead.
I want him dead today.
Kill my boy. Now he's back in the ends
like he's big and I'm not gonna do nothing!
Just cool down, man.
- I'll give you seven for everyting.
- Cool, man.
- You gonna help me with this or what?
- Jay, man just got out of jail today.
If something happens to him,
friends are gonna come for you.
I don't care, blood. I'll go jail.
You know what, I'm gonna give you
the piece, cos me and you are boys.
Just don't bring no fucking drama
to my door, you hear me?
Course not.
You just gotta understand,
do you get me?
This boy... killed my tight bredren, man.
Listen, why don't you buy
a couple of the boys we got?
They'll do anything for a bit of cash.
Why don't you get 'em to do the job
for you, save you the trouble?
- And if they get caught, who gives a fuck?
- Who?
Don't put no pussyholes on it
who'll take my money and not do nothing.
This lot won't fuck about,
they're a tight little crew.
- Omen, Dabs, and some others.
- Omen?
Yeah. You know him?
Nah, not really.
Why? Is he here?
Dabs is still here.
- Go on, go through with Andre.
- Come on, then.
Cuz, you're not on my level
on this game, man.
Cuz, why do you think they call me
King Henry, bruv? Check out the header.
Look-look-look! Bang!
Check out the replay.
- Mine's stuck.
- Nah! Check out the replay.
Hey, Dabs. Come through, mate.
Now, man. Come on.
Let me have that.
Mum?
How you doing, mum?
Everything OK, like?
Came out today.
Did you do that to the front door?
Yeah. I'm s... I'm sorry.
I just needed... I needed to get in.
No one was home.
I mean, I'll pay for it.
Gonna go try get a job.
I'll go Jobcentre or something.
You know, cos we get taught stuff
in there. You can still get jobs and that.
I missed you, mum.
Some toast?
Let me get this straight. You want me
to get Omen, find this yout and murk him?
Yeah.
- You sure you want him dead?
- Yes, man, are you deaf? Dead.
- Why's he getting excited?
- Who the fuck you talking to?
Look, let's just calm the fuck down.
Can you do it or what?
What's in it for me, like?
Listen, I like the way
you been going on recently, blood.
So what say you come flex
with me and Andre for a bit?
Step up a bit, get a little piece
of what we're going on with.
You better watch yourself.
All right, man.
I'm sorry, man.
Sorry, Ike, man.
But come the fuck on. Kill a bre for just
that? You must think I'm any road yout.
- I ain't doing that.
- Listen!
I'll give you three grand now.
And then three more when it's done.
I ain't chatting shit to you, all right?
Take the money and go find him.
- You know what? Seckle the fuck down.
- Blood, you need to watch your mouth!
- Who is it?
- Name's Sam Peel.
Sam Peel?
- You do know that...
- Don't worry about what I know.
- Yeah, but...
- You still gonna do it, blood?
- Know what? Rag on.
- Good.
And don't let the others know
who he is, blood.
No, I mean it, blood. Don't even
let them mans see his face too tough.
Just go get Omen and do your fucking job.
You see him, you kill him.
- You do know what he looks like, yeah?
- Course, blood.
He robbed me when I was nine.
Yo, Henry!
- We're gone, blood!
- Tss!
Don't forget I've got the title, blood.
I beat you eight times.
That's Henry the Eighth.
What's wrong with these kids nowadays? !
They ain't got no respect, blood.
Always on a hype ting.
I didn't chat to my elders like that.
Here you go.
So what's going on?
- They want us to kill someone.
- What? ! Who?
- I ain't supposed to tell you, blood.
Come on, blood, I ain't gonna tell no one.
- Sam Peel.
- Who's that?
- You don't know?
- No.
But you know what, cuz, it don't even
matter. I ain't into all that stupidness.
You told them it's all nonsense, yeah?
You're thinking about it, innit?
Blood, don't be stupid, man!
When I tell Omen and Blammy
they're gonna laugh in your face.
Tss!
Ike and them must think we're dickheads.
If you're thinking of
doing it, you're stupid.
Who the fuck you calling stupid?
Blood, you're a dunce
if you kill someone for them fools.
Next man would do it twice
for that kind of Ps.
Get off me, man.
I don't even care!
I'm up for a little arms and robbing, man.
But you gone psycho, blood.
You shot man last night and now this.
I'm not going jail for you.
I'm not going jail for no one to call me
Abigail, call me some next man's chick.
Burn that, man.
You can go, man. Fuck you.
- Who the fuck are you talking to, blood?
- Get off me, cuz, yeah?
Calm down. What's wrong with you? I'm
supposed to be your friend. Calm down!
I'll catch up with you on Monday.
- Hey, baby.
- Hey, Mum.
- How was school today?
- All right.
Mummy's just got to see someone for a
bit, but then we're gonna go straight back.
OK, come on. Over here.
- You all right?
- What do you want?
Can I give you a lift home?
- OK, I'm gonna be in in a minute, OK?
- OK.
- Where'd you get my number from?
- She left her phone when she fucked off.
- So what you up to these days?
- Being a mum.
Safe.
I'm just working in a salon, innit.
I wanna get into...
What the fuck d'you want, Alex?
It's Lexi.
All right. Lexi.
You bell me, say you want to
talk about something important,
and now you're sitting having a chitchat?
I don't mean to be rude,
but one of the last...
people I wanna have a social with is you.
Fine. Whatever.
That guy Sam's out. Someone's after him.
He wants to know if you know anything.
Well, I don't.
Now tell me,
why the fuck should I even care?
He deserves everything he gets.
Come on, Alisa. He's done his time,
he doesn't want any trouble.
So? I don't give a fuck about him
and I don't even know why I met you.
Actually, do you know what, I do.
I thought you were gonna tell me Becky
was hurt or homeless or something.
I wanted to see if I felt sad.
And now you tell me she's missing.
And do you know what?
I don't even fucking care.
I don't care about her, you, or him.
I don't even give a fuck either.
I just thought since he took time out
to find me and... and to see Moony...
and Claire, that at
least I would pass on...
- He saw Moony and Claire?
- Yeah.
He just said his piece and left.
What harm can it do?
All right. Call him.
But if he so much as raises his voice
to me, I'm calling the police.
You never came to see me.
Even when I was in hospital. Why?
You...
make me feel so shame.
I couldn't bear it.
More than one woman
lost their son that night.
- Lord God. What did I do wrong?
- You did nothing wrong.
I try to raise you on my own. I work every
hour God send me to provide for you.
- And what do I get? You, a murderer.
- It's different from murder.
And your brother.
He's gonna be worse than you are.
Maybe if I'd gone to church more.
I never meant to let you down, Mum.
You never meant to.
But you did.
I borrowed your phone.
Whenever you're ready, pussy.
Yout.
Wha' gwan, blood?
What you got?
Bre! I ain't had them crisp in time,
you know! Let me have your crisp.
- Tss!
- What? You say something?
Did you say something, blood?
Give me the fucking chocolate too.
My man got 'nuff batteries.
What you need them for?
- My shaver and...
- Nah, cuz! You don't need them.
Give me your batteries.
- I'm not giving you the batteries.
- What? You a bad man now?
You kill someone big? What was his
name? Tell me. See if I get shook of you.
- His name was Trife.
- What?
- His name was Trife. Don't know him.
And you know what?
I'm taking your fucking batteries.
You?
Hello?
- That Sam?
- Yeah.
- It's Lexi.
- Yeah, what's going on?
- Alisa said she'll see you.
- Where?
Go Latimer Station, do a left
through the alley then bell me.
Safe.
What you doing, blood?
That's my chair.
- I'm next.
- Did I say that's my chair?
- Shut the fuck up! I heard you first time.
Oi! Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi!
Come out the fucking shop.
You trying to fuck a man's business?
I'm coming back for him, you know.
Yo, Omen.
Wha' gwan, man?
What's going on, man?
What happened to your lip?
You know I'd do anything for you.
We like blood.
Yeah, yeah, man. Course.
Tell me, man.
Ike and Andre asked me to get you man
and kill some bre for six Gs.
- What? What for?
- I dunno.
Me and Henry said,
"Nah, we ain't on it,"
then we saw the bre and thought, "Fuck it.
May as well rush him." He bricked Henry.
I tried to fight my man but he got away.
- So where's Henry? Hospital?
- I had to kick out before the feds came.
- You left Henry, blood?
- He was out cold.
I chased the bre, called an ambulance,
got Blammy, came here.
I was banging my yat. When Dabs called,
I just left her - legs
up, gash out, everyting.
Let me call Henry, man.
Fuck this. Who's the bre?
I'll fucking do it. He's dead.
Dunno. But I'll recognise him, though.
I'll fucking recognise him.
- They said it's big tings for us, blood.
- You know what? Fuck their tings!
If this bre hurt Henry,
he's fucking done.
It's done. That's what I said.
Well, you on it or what?
You done know. Come.
Oi, Moons.
I swear I'm leave, like.
I just thought I seen my man
walking like he's big.
Nah. Nah, I'm coming to get you now.
- What did she say, like?
- Alisa?
Nothing. She just said bring him
and I said I'd sort it.
Why are you helping me?
- I saw Jay.
- What? When? What did he say?
Nothing. Well, I thought it was him -
he was on the train, I wasn't.
You all right?
- Is her kid here?
- Yeah.
- What do you want? Find God in jail?
- I understand how much you hate me...
You'll never understand
how much I hate you.
I didn't plan this. I
didn't know what I was...
gonna do today, I just wanted to get out.
But this guy attacked me and he's saying
people are gonna hurt my family.
I wanna tell you that if you know who's
involved, I don't want any more trouble.
- So this is about what you want?
- Come on, the guy's trying...
Shut up, Alex.
What about all the people you've hurt?
What about what they want?
What about all the lives you've ruined?
- I didn't mean to kill him.
- You didn't mean it?
Wait here.
It's not going the way you planned, is it?
What? !
Fucking prick!
OK. Go play with your toys,
sweetheart.
What about what she wants?
Like a dad? Which she doesn't have
because of you.
You think... I have time to sit around
and organise how to get you back?
D'you know what?
Mum?
Don't you ever... come near me
or my daughter again.
You either.
What you doing now?
I dunno.
I know it sounds dumb,
but it was good seeing you today.
It's good that you come out of jail,
and you're, like, all right.
Bell me sometime, yeah,
if you're bored or whatever.
Or if you're not doing nothing now, you
could just... go back to mine and just...
just whatever...
for a bit.
- Any of these bres?
- Nah, man.
- You heard this?
- Put it away, man.
Fucking hell, man.
Everywhere I go... Why the biggest guy
in the world always stand in front of me?
Yo, blood!
You get paid to follow me around
or something?
What?
You wanna say something to me?
You better chat slow, yeah, blood.
I don't speak Big Foot.
- Hey, that's him. That's the fucking bre.
- Come we get him, then.
Fuck round him and knock him out.
Hey, man! Hey, pussyhole!
- Get the fuck up.
- Fuck up!
Get the fuck up! Stand up!
- I wanna see him.
- Fucking do it, man.
Fuck!
- That's not him, man.
- What?
It's not fucking him.
- Fuck!
- Might as well jack him.
- Fucking come here.
- Come on!
Shut up!
Shut up. What? Shut up. Sing.
- You deaf, pussyhole?
- Fucking sing.
- # Let me go
- Fucking dickhead. Get out of here, man.
I thought you knew
what the bre looks like.
I do, man.
I just made a mistake, innit.
It's Henry.
Hello?
What, blood?
That was his mum.
- He's not dead, he's just unconscious.
- So are we still gonna do this, or what?
Yeah, come.
Come in. We can have a fat spliff,
just cotch for a bit.
It's small. Hope it don't
remind you of jail too much.
- You want a drink?
- Yeah. What you got?
Um... water.
M-might have some Um Bongo
in the cupboard.
What's that?
Exzoryapan. It's, like, a...
It's an antidepressant... thing.
I get...
So what you doing tomorrow, like?
Why? That your way
of asking me to do something?
No, man. I was just...
No. I was just asking.
I never do nothing no more.
Get up, go to work, come home.
I spent six and half years
wishing I could do something
and you don't know
what you're doing tomorrow.
So what you doing?
- Something, man. Anything.
- Exactly. You don't know.
Well, what do you like doing?
I draw designs sometimes...
It doesn't matter. It's stupid.
You know what? You're the first bre
that asked me what I like to do in years.
- So where exactly is Becky, then?
- I don't know. She just up and left.
Got home four weeks ago - gone.
I ain't seen or heard from her since.
- You don't seem that bothered.
- No, I'm not.
- I've missed this, man.
- What?
Just cotching at a girl's yard, like. Just
little things, like going cinema and that.
- Shit... Oh, sorry.
- Oh, fuck!
Nah, it's all right.
Come here.
Oi, Moons!
- What you saying, fam? You cool?
- No, I'm not cool. I'm vexed.
I thought I see him on the train, innit?
I swear I'm going mad, blood.
I wanted to spark him,
then I thought, "Let me calm down."
Let me come get you and let's do this
together, blood, like it should be done.
I got some little youts
looking for him as well.
- Which way we going, man? It's that way.
- Relax. Come in for a chat.
We ain't got time for no chat!
We need to go get him now.
- Hey!
- Shut up, you waste man!
You're all butters anyway!
Bitch!
Relax, Jay, man.
Hey, blood.
What you wearing, man?
You look like a fucking batty man, blood.
This better be for some uni project.
Jay... this is my girl Kayla.
Rah, blood!
So I don't see you in a couple of months,
yeah, and you got yourself a girl, blood?
Babe, check they didn't
put no onions in it.
You know how you get.
- Are we gonna go get him or what?
- What exactly is going on?
- Robert ain't really filled me in.
- "Robert"?
All right. Basically, yeah.
This guy...
that killed our best friend...
just come out of jail, innit?
- And I want us to go get him back.
- And do what?
Blood, what's this girl on?
What you think?
- I'm not on it, bruv.
- What you talking about?
- I'm talking about Sam.
- He said he's not interested.
You speak for him now? Go suck out.
Who's talking to you anyway?
I don't know who you think you're talking
to, but you don't speak to me like that.
- Seckle yourself. Moony, tell your girl.
- Tell me what?
Listen, this ain't a dictatorship, "blood",
this is a relationship.
I'm a 22-year-old woman
who's studying law.
He does not tell me nothing.
We discuss things together, yeah.
Maybe if you was a man instead of a yout
in a man's body you would know that.
Hey, blood, I will spark your girl...
- Jay, don't chat...
- Don't speak for me.
Listen. On Earth, where I'm from, men are
supposed to treat women with respect.
If you ain't gonna chat to me with respect,
have your conversation away from me.
Move!
- What you looking at?
- You!
- Don't look at me, man.
- Come on, man! Just jam, man.
Jay, what's your problem, man?
- Fuck... Get off me!
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
- You know what? Fuck this.
Wait, wait. I will, I
swear. Please. Fuck...
Just... Sam, give me a minute.
You all right, like?
Yeah. I'm fine.
So what you act like tings
is gonna run for then back out?
It's just...
It's been a while. You get me?
It has!
Why you let it get so far, then?
It's been time for me as well, innit?
It's weird.
When I was, like, 15,
all I wanted to do was get older.
And now I am.
I can do anything I want.
I can drink...
vote...
fuck... drive...
I'm legally an adult.
But I've realised two things.
One...
I would do anything
to go get them years back.
Two...
I never felt more alone.
I've never felt more like a kid
in my whole life.
D'you get me?
Yeah.
How you let her chat to me like that, man?
What? Are you some kind of pussy?
- The only pussy is you.
- Fucking...
- Relax, Jay, man.
- I'll take you on, bruv.
Listen, Jay, I don't think
this is a good idea, you know.
Come on, blood.
Have you forgotten what my man did?
What he took from us, blood?
He killed Trife! He took everything!
- What happened to your arm?
- Nothing.
- Why you fight them girls earlier?
- It was something about one of their men.
It was nothing to do with me,
it was to do with Becky, but...
when you hang around with a girl
that's notorious for fucking everyone...
That's why you're here, innit?
Cos you thought,
"I'm gonna fuck the white girl."
"And she'll be easy too,
like her cousin."
He made our lives hell, blood!
For fucking years!
Then he came to that party, blood,
with a bat, and he killed our boy!
If you'd have jumped in,
it wouldn't have happened, would it?
So you have to help me!
And yeah, you know what, I had a few
when I was younger, but so what?
Trouble is, once everyone's fucked you,
your bargaining tools is used up.
You ain't got nothing left to offer.
Cos if you'd done something
when you had the chance,
Trife would have still been here today!
- Come we kick, fam.
- Robert!
Yeah, come we go, blood.
You know what?
I ain't got nothing.
I got no man.
No mates.
I got no loyalties to no one.
No one's got none for me.
- Lock that girl off, man!
- D'you know where he is, fam?
Yeah. I know exactly where he is.
So what happened to you?
What? Why does something
have to have happened?
It takes something fucked-up to happen to
us for us to realise how big we fucked up.
All right.
Fine.
You wanna know? Cool.
A year and a half ago.
Seven men.
Three hours.
They took turns.
They fucking put things in me.
They raped me.
And they got away with it.
Cos we'd gone there,
to the gym, after hours,
to meet this instructor and his mate.
She didn't tell me
there was gonna be seven mates.
She went off with her one,
left me with the rest.
My dad had to sit in court and hear all the
shit they managed to dredge up about me.
They had money.
Said I was a fucking whore.
I never sold myself,
but cos I was with her,
they never believed me.
We didn't speak after it happened,
lived here for ages just not talking.
When she was here, that is.
I had nowhere else to go.
That's why I don't give a fuck
where she is, or if she ever comes back.
No one deserves that.
- Who you keep texting?
- No one.
- Who you fucking texting?
- No one. What the fuck are you doing?
Sorry.
What's all that on your back?
Oh, fuck...
What you want, man?
What do I want?
Do you believe in karma?
Hm?
Trife, the yout you killed...
was my nephew.
Aaargh!
Shut up.
Make one more fucking noise and I will
kill you even slower than I planned to.
You pussy!
- Hey!
- Noooo!
- Don't fucking touch me!
- Sorry. Sorry. Fuck.
- Sam, it's locked.
- Open the fucking door.
- Open the fucking door!
- All right. Listen.
I know. You try and block it out and
you can't, so you shut everyone else out.
- Fuck you, man!
I'll tell you what I get told all the time.
What you just told me. Sam.
Whatever happened to you,
whatever it was, you didn't deserve it.
You did fucking deserve it,
you fucking sket!
Don't you ever fucking say that about me!
Come we fuck him up, man.
See, I knew you'd be on it, blood.
We're gonna finish this tonight. Show him
he should never've fucked with us.
Leave that girl as well. Come roll together
again. Jay and Moony running tings...
- My name's Robert.
- All right.
Robert, then, innit?
Bob and Jay running tings.
Prove to people you ain't a pussy no
more. Show Sam we're better than him.
- I can't do this, blood.
- You're gonna back out of this now?
- Why you a pussy? We gotta show him...
- I am showing him!
By what? By being a pussy and letting him
get away with it? By studying your shit?
Yeah! I'm not doing this. I don't want
nothing to do with this. What'll it prove?
Well, fuck you then, innit.
Fucking prick!
That's what it's about now, yeah? You're
gonna forget about a man over a girl.
You fucking pussy.
That's what you are, what you've
always been. A fucking pussyhole.
What? You think you're
a big man now? What?
Maybe I'm the smart one, yeah?
He killed Trife, blood!
Hey, you, man.
That's him.
That's him. Come.
Do this shit!
- Turn him over.
- What the fuck for, man? He hurt Henry.
Give me the fucking blade.
I'll do it.
Now turn the pussyhole over.
I want him to see me.
- So he knows who he fucked with.
- Shit...
Sam?
- What's going on?
- What you doing?
That's my brother, blood.
You man mad?
Who knew who we was looking for?
- You knew.
- What you talking about?
You knew. That's why you
didn't want to let me look at him.
I didn't know nothing about this.
All right, look...
Ike and Andre and them man.
They had some next bre there, offering
bare Ps, blood. We'll split it, me and you.
- But that's my brother.
- Fuck him! You don't even like him.
You always gunning him,
telling me you hate him.
Fucker's been in jail since you was ten.
- You didn't even know he came out today.
- It's still my brother, blood.
So what happened to Henry?
Did my brother hurt Henry?
- What can I say, man, he weren't on it.
- You done him.
You fucking pussyhole.
If not for this prick,
I wouldn't have had to.
- You're wrong, Dabs.
- No, you're wrong.
Yous are all fucking wrong.
Wrong in your fucking brains!
- I'm talking about six Gs here.
- Who gave you the money, blood?
Tss!
Sam, shall I bore this bre?
No one's around, man.
Come I just jook him and we dust, man.
Just like he was gonna do to you.
- Don't be silly...
- Shut your fucking mouth.
Shall I do it, blood?
Just tell me, Sam.
Just say the word.
Nah, man.
What a punch, blood!
Seriously, man...
Thung!
You all right, bruv?
Yeah, man. Come we kick.
Whoa!
Oyster card too, man.
I'll go check your girl tonight, man.
Safe, blood.
You dickhead, man. Fucking dickhead.
- Where is he?
- He's left. He won't be far.
I told you to keep him.
- Have you got the gear?
- Why should I give you anything?
Come on, Jay. Please. Come on. You
took too long. I tried to keep him here.
Jay, please. Please.
Just give me a little bit, all right?
- Remember when we let you stay here...
- Where's he gone?
- He doesn't want any trouble, Jay...
- Where's he gone? !
I don't know.
Come on, Lex.
What've I gotta do
to get information from you, huh?
- Bring my boys round?
- Fuck you.
Take your fucking drugs.
- What the fuck...
It was me. What the fuck is all this shit?
- You can't tell me nothing.
- I'm not trying to tell you nothing...
You know what,
just give me your heater.
I know you got one.
Just give it to me.
We got to make the best
out of bad situations.
I get treated certain ways
everywhere we go,
even when I'm not doing nothing,
mans watching me.
Judging me.
For something you done.
Right, that... that's making the best
of a bad situation.
There's nothing for man to do round here.
You know what I learnt when I went
big man jail, blood? Fuck all.
I packed them little breakfast trays,
did a bit of laundry.
I never learnt how to not go back in.
You get on that path...
I'm not stupid like you, though, Sam!
- If I do something I'm not getting caught.
- It's not about getting caught.
It's about spending your days looking over
your shoulder. I don't want that for you.
- Where's this Ike bre's place?
- 40 Compromise Avenue.
It's a basement flat, innit.
- I'm coming.
- Stay here.
- I'm coming...
- I said stay here!
I want you to stay here.
Look, man.
Just do me one favour.
Stay here and look after Mum. The bre
that's after me I think might come here.
If you love her, if you ever loved me,
just stay here tonight.
OK?
OK.
You fuck with them, they'll kill you.
Badder men than them have tried.
I love you, Mum.
Royston does too.
- Take your hands out your pockets.
- What the fuck you want?
- Just do what I asked you, please, sir.
- Sam?
- It's Desmond.
- Buds?
- It's what they used to call me.
It's all right. I know him.
Have a little walk, let me chat to him.
Yeah, walk on, man.
What's going on, blood?
When you come out?
Come out today, blood.
Policeman?
Community support, bruv.
I can't arrest no one.
I'm on 22 grand, bruv.
Look, I'm... I'm sorry I never come check
you inside, man. You know what it's like.
Yeah.
Listen, man, I... I better dust
before my man gets annoyed, yeah?
Listen, man, how long armed-response
unit take to come round here?
There was a shooting here yesterday,
so there's a couple of cars around.
- Say about 15 minutes.
- Safe, man.
- Why? What's going on?
- Nothing, man. I'm just curious.
You sure?
Yeah.
Stay out of trouble, blood.
It's OK.
Desmond, or Buds,
or whatever you wanna call yourself,
I'm not gonna be made to look a fool
in front of these people.
Yeah.
Hello, Big?
It's Sam. I wanna ask you for that favour.
No, I ain't got it, but...
it won't take me long to get it.
Filo.
Yep.
How you gonna get him there?
I know how to get him there.
All right, man, it's... your funeral.
15 minutes.
I've got a proposition for you.
Call it a peace offering.
But if I give this to you...
me and you, our problems are done.
When you get there, ask for Big Man.
Give me your bag! Give me the bag, man.
I'm sorry. Just give me the bag.
Hello, police? I've just been robbed
by a man with a gun.
He's going into number 40, Compromise
Avenue. I need help right now.
You're not one of our regular boys.
You must be the geezer
Omen said was coming.
Yeah, yeah.
My name's Big Man.
I'm here to check Ike and Andre.
About what?
Nice.
OK.
- Get the fuck over here!
- What the fuck is wrong with you, man?
You got the time, blood?
You in a rush, blood?
Nah, man. I'm just asking.
All right, come.
Wait there, yeah?
What you saying, blood?
- So you're Big Man, yeah?
- Yeah, man.
So what you want from us?
Talk then, man.
Me and my business partner heard of you.
We thought it might be beneficial
for all of us if we come work with you.
- So where's your partner?
- He's coming.
Why do you keep looking at the clock,
blood? There somewhere you need to be?
- Nah, I'm just...
- Come on, then. Tell us.
Yeah. You tell us what you can do for us
that we can't do for ourselves.
Didn't Omen and Dabs tell you?
You need to speak to them...
Really? And honestly,
I don't never see us working together.
Think I'd have a fucking monkey like you
on my level?
Don't look to me for support,
you know, blood. His sister's my girl.
And you know what? I don't really
work with man like you, you know.
See what Dabs has to say about this.
- Who are you?
- Where's Big Man?
Nah. It's answering machine.
Listen, I don't give a fuck...
What the fuck do you want, man?
I haven't done...
Shut your fucking mouth.
Put your hands on the table.
Now, you're gonna keep quiet.
And you're gonna stay in here.
Or man is gonna go on different with you,
you understand me, blood?
Fuck!
What the fuck is going on? !
Back up! You stay there.
You stay on the fucking floor!
- You set me up.
- I didn't, Curtis, I swear.
What the fuck is going?
All of you, shut the fuck up.
- You!
- Nah, man.
You. You.
Never fuck with a guy
who ain't got nothing to lose.
And you two, you were gonna send
my own brother to come try kill me?
Are you dizzy, blood?
- All of you is fucking dead, man.
- Yeah?
Blood, can dead men do this?
Open it! Police!
Fuck!
Down! Get down!
Fuck.
Hi. Sam... Um, you said
you had your mum's phone.
Take him.
I got problems.
But I'm sorting 'em.
Open this!
Listen, Jay's after you,
so just be careful.
Um...
I know you said you missed,
like, going cinema and that,
so I've booked a couple of tickets.
Thought we could just go tomorrow night,
just as mates?
Please.
Call me when you get this.
If you want.
Out! Police!
Police! Get down!
You think I forgot you, blood?
Is that what you think?
We don't need to do this, Jay.
I'll kill you, blood.
I'm gonna kill you, blood!
You think that's faster than this, blood?
- Trife wouldn't want
this. That's what he...
Shut your fucking mouth!
Remember that night, blood?
- Yeah.
- And what? You think you're a big man?
No, man. Look, I...
I never wanted him to die, blood.
What?
You think this is just about him?
This is about me!
Why you think I'm here, huh?
Like this?
You did this.
You made this happen.
I fucking hate you for it.
I'm here not just for you,
I'm here because of you!
- Then I beg you, let's stop.
- That's right, blood, beg!
I wanna hear you.
I wanna hear you beg like Trife did.
If that's what you want, blood.
I'm begging, man, don't do this. Please.
I'm still gonna kill you, blood.
I'm gonna take your fucking life,
like you took Trife's.
Like you took mine!
Just fucking do it, man,
and get it over with.
Six and a half years
and that's what you still want.
You think you're a bad man, Jay?
I thought I was a fucking bad man,
remember that?
I thought I was fucking bad,
and they put me in a big-man jail,
and look what happened to me.
You see this?
This is from where I tried to kill myself
because I couldn't cope in there.
You see these?
Look at them. Look at them!
I cut my arms so I wouldn't give them the
satisfaction of dealing out the most pain.
You know why they did it to me? Because
I thought I was fucking bad, and I wasn't.
Now you wanna be bad. You think
you're big, Jay. You wanna be a big man.
You wanna be what I thought I was.
You wanna be me!
Then you fucking do it, blood.
You see what happens to you.
Is this what you want?
- See, you're just like me, man.
- No, I'm nothing like you.
You ain't a killer, blood.
You're like me.
You're nothing.
I never meant to kill Trife, blood.
And I'm so sorry.
This ain't over, blood.
You really think this is over, blood?
This ain't fucking over, blood!
Where the fuck you going, blood?
You ain't got nowhere to go.
You ain't got no friends.
You ain't got no one.
This ain't over!
Yeah, it is.
Thought we could just go
tomorrow night, just as mates? Please.
Call me when you get this.
Subtitles by LeapinLar