Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
No. No no!
No, Trevor!
Trevor, baby, no.
Hello?
Is someone there?
Is someone in there?
Is there someone
alive in there?
Hey.
Are you okay?
I'm gonna get you
out of there.
Hold on!
What does it mean
to be happy?
To be content
in the world around you?
Mom used to say
it was family--
That family is the heart
of everything, even existence.
Without it, there's nothing.
She would always have
these simple answers
that somehow would sound
so brilliant.
And then she died.
My father died
along with her.
Shortly after that, my brother David
had to sell the farm
where we grew up.
Now we're just trying to be
an ordinary family,
trying to figure out
where we fit in in the world.
And for me,
I'm trying to figure out
where I belong,
right now
in this exact moment.
I don't know, Dad.
What do you think about the black hair?
Come on, it's different.
- It's different than normal.
- It's pretty, don't you think?
Oh, yes.
Yes yes, definitely--
right there, right there.
Look at the baby,
he's part of the family.
- Hey, there we go.
- Okay, Dad.
I don't wanna hear that,
Darlene.
The social worker
will be here tomorrow.
We can't have the place
looking like this.
- Whatever you say, Dad.
- That's not funny, Darlene.
Okay, I'm trying to do
the best I can here.
Oh, Jesus. You know, I'm not
a little girl anymore
and you don't have to be
a dick about this!
Just-- can you just please
clean your room
and maybe not wear that mess
on your eyes tomorrow?
Fuck you, David!
Francis, turn it off now!
Oh, come on, David,
it's a school project.
- Just not our personal stuff, okay?
- It's about our family.
- I need this kind of stuff.
- Turn it off now!
You just get the heck
out of my face for a second.
My brother David
is the oldest.
He picked up all the responsibilities
after Mom and Dad died.
We used to be real close,
but after he sold our farm
something changed in him.
He became like one of those life-sized
cardboard cutouts you see in the stores,
trying to sell the idea
that everything is perfect,
but really nothing
is the same anymore.
We just keep moving
from town to town
running from the truth,
waiting for it to one day
catch up with us.
This is our sixth house
in two years.
Oh, yeah,
every single one of them.
Wow, that's cool.
Okay, guys,
I'm gonna go pee.
- No, wait.
- I gotta go. No, come on.
- Sam, stay.
- I'm gonna go. I'll be right back.
- Don't take too long.
- I won't.
Sam, get your ass in here
and smoke a joint.
It's beautiful. Come on,
do the rain dance.
Hell, no! Get in the car
right now, girl.
Come on. No!
- Yeah! Ow! Get in here.
- Come on!
Back in.
So, did you guys have fun?
- Yeah.
- You are glowing.
No, I'm not.
So, Wendell,
what do you do?
I work for my brother--
fetch stuff for him,
things like that.
- Nothing too exciting though.
- Sounds cool.
So where are you guys off
to next, huh?
Seattle, I think.
We're just gonna keep traveling
city to city
till we run all out of money.
- Can't beat that kind of freedom.
- No, we just picked up and left!
No one even knows
where we're at.
- What?
- Hush.
We don't have to worry
about Wendell, our hero.
Wendell is Superman.
Wow, look at that.
Look at all
those pretty stars.
- Where?
- I think you mean raindrops.
You can at least pretend
to like it, okay?
Hey, I'm sorry for yelling
at you yesterday.
I didn't mean to.
We're good?
Yeah, we're good. But, David,
I'm really not feeling too hot today.
- You're going to school, okay?
- I just don't think--
I don't wanna hear it.
You're going to school.
Good morning, sleepyhead.
You want some breakfast?
Why do you even bother?
Because that's what families do.
They have breakfast together.
Cute, David. Anyway, Kitty's
spending the night tomorrow.
- Who's uh--
- I am telling you in advance,
- just like you asked.
- Who the heck is Kitty?
I don't know,
some chick from Ohio.
All right. Remember, social worker
is coming tonight at 5:00 for dinner.
You should really try
giving up cooking, David.
I'm off,
and you go to school.
I really don't fit in there.
Look,
I know it's hard for you,
but can you please
at least try?
Why? It's not my fault
we're always moving.
You're right, Francis.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry, guys.
I know I have a bad temper.
What do you want me to do?
Some maybe say I'm bipolar.
Good morning, Francis.
How are you doing there, bud, huh?
What are you reading?
"Gay sperm donors needed
for lesbian couple."
- Knock it off.
- You're calling that today.
- Have you fed Lenny?
- Don't look at me. Look at Franny.
Oh, come on, I just did it
two days ago.
Okay, I gotta go to work.
- Will you just please do it?
- I'll do it before I go to school.
Where're you going? Oh, yeah, you gotta
go do your thing. Forgot, sorry.
Have fun.
Have a good day.
The twins-- they've always
been distant from the family.
Wendell is the main reason
why we move a lot.
He just got out of jail for biting
some guy's ear off
at a Cheesy Chuck's Pizza parlor
up north.
Darlene is just as mean,
but more refined.
Like when we were kids,
she used to lock me in the closet
just to hear me scream.
Then, hours later,
she would let me out pretending
she was the one who saved me.
And I always fell for it.
Let me out of here!
Help, please!
Please.
Somebody please help us!
Oh, heck no, we've had a lot
of social workers come here,
but you're the first
for dinner.
So, Francis, what's up
with you tonight, huh?
- Nothing.
- Anything you wanna talk about?
Anything at all? School maybe?
I don't know...
Well, you know, if there is,
you just jump on in, all right?
Yeah, he told me he wasn't
feeling too well this morning.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, thank you, Darlene.
That's, uh... quite a creative look
you've got going there,
young lady.
- What do you call that, huh?
- Death.
Ah, death. That's cute.
So tell me, David,
are you and Wendell
still working over there
at Del Rancho?
I don't know if I could work
at a slaughterhouse, huh?
Yeah, well, my father
owned a farm
when we were younger
and he did the same thing,
so I guess it just
came naturally.
Well...
so, like, what do they have you
doing over there?
I mean...
you don't have to kill the animals
and all that stuff, do you, David?
Heavens, no.
No no, I'm a carver.
I take out the organs,
prep them, stuff like that.
Yes, David has a real knack
for gutting the life out of things.
Thank you, Darlene.
So... too bad there's not--
not a demand
on the black market for cow parts.
You would be a rich man
by now.
Not at the table,
please, Francis.
I apologize. Paul, he's been
following us around with that thing
for the past few days--
some sort of school project
- or something or other.
- No, that's fine with me.
I think it's kind of cool.
Francis, tell me about the project.
Well, it's uh--
I'm supposed to write
a report about my family--
our family--
and I just asked if I could
shoot a video instead.
Good. Now, that's a good idea.
That is a great idea.
- I hated doing papers. I hated it.
- Me too.
I really did.
- Hey, gang.
- Hey, Wendell.
- Hey.
- How are you?
- Good, Paul. How are you?
- Good, thanks.
Am I late?
What do you think,
Wendell?
David,
may I please be excused?
- We're not finished eating.
- No no no, let the boy go.
- Mm-hmm.
- He's probably bored out of his mind.
- Where are you going, Francis?
- I used to have two younger brothers,
so I understand these things.
They are a handful.
That was great, you guys.
Thanks a lot.
I know I'm not much
of a cook, but I do try.
Not to worry. You probably never
tasted my wife's cooking, huh?
Well, I'll be in the kitchen
cleaning.
Did you hear that?
Oh, it's probably cats...
fucking.
Yep, that's cats
fucking, all right--
getting after it.
What do you think, David?
Who'd have thought?
- Listen, that was a great dinner.
- Thank you.
- I'll talk to you soon.
- Thanks. Yeah.
- Thanks, David.
- Good night, Paul.
Good night.
Need more padding on that south wall.
You can hear 'em upstairs.
All right, so you're sure
that they're good?
Positive. On a road trip,
it's gonna be two, three weeks
before anyone notices.
- Healthy?
- Oh, yeah.
- I even took one for a test drive.
- Quit acting up, okay?
I don't want their faces showing up
on the 10:00 news like last time.
- This could sustain us for awhile.
- Trust me.
All right.
Let's get to work.
- Help.
- Room service.
How are we holding up, girls?
Good?
Well, you're
looking good. Hi.
I hope this doesn't change
anything between us.
Wendell, what did I tell you?
Come on, sweetheart.
- Stop it!
- Come on.
Get up.
Oh, yeah!
Don't worry, Sam.
I still got something
right here, okay?
All right, let's
get you up, huh?
You're a live one,
aren't you?
Let's tie you down here.
Let's get you down here.
Is that too tight, sweetie?
- Sounds like he's changing.
- Hey. Hey, Lenny.
Poor guy's
probably hungry.
We'll feed him later.
Just go keep watch.
I'm gonna tuck you in
later, okay?
I got you.
Get in. I'll give you
a ride to school.
I saw some stuff
I want to shoot, Wendell.
Just get the fuck in.
God damn.
You gotta pop your cherry,
baby brother.
Huh?
So you can quit moping around,
playing with that camera.
Hey! Hey.
What, are you too good
to talk to me now?
- Fuck you, Wendell!
- What?!
- What the-- hey! Hey!
- Fuck you!
- Keep it up, Francis!
- No!
Keep it up! We take care
of your sorry ass, all right?
We feed you, we put fucking clothes
on your back,
and you do nothing in return
but complain.
Let go of me!
Dude, l-- look,
I know it fucking seems
fucked up, all right?
But we do what we do
to survive.
All right?
You do anything to fuck up
our family-- most importantly me--
I'll fucking kill you, okay?
Hey! Okay?
Get the fuck out of my truck.
Shut the fuck up
before I gut you myself!
Bye, Lenny.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Yes, hello.
This is David Hamilton.
I'm calling on behalf
of Francis Hamilton.
Yes yes. Yeah,
he's not feeling too well,
got a case of the flu
or something.
Yeah, right right.
Oh, thank you,
I appreciate it.
Have a great day. Bye.
Please don't hurt her
anymore.
I'm not like them.
Then can you help us,
please?
I'm sorry, but I can't.
- Please.
- I don't even have a key.
Do something, please.
I can give you
something to drink.
Do you want
something to drink?
She needs some, please.
I don't have a key.
She just needs water.
She's dying.
I have to go.
Someone will be here soon.
Please.
The top drawer, eh?
You need a fake ID?
Where did you get all those?
I know a guy in the city.
You want one?
I won't charge you.
Yeah.
Let's see.
>>DRIVER LICENSE<<
Here we go-- Dani Cummings.
Oh, look she's an organ donor.
How sweet!
Seems about your height...
- Blonde hair.
- That's okay.
What are you little girls doing?
We are just getting comfortable
and throwing in a flick.
You wanna watch?
I'd love to watch.
Where were you, Francis?
I was just down by the river
filming some stuff.
Pretty late, huh?
Yeah, I guess.
Well, I'm going out
for a little bit.
So if you need anything...
All right.
All right. I'll see you later.
Turn it off, turn it off!
It's just a movie, sweetheart.
I thought you liked
this kind of stuff.
Well, I do.
It's just these movies
are too real sometimes.
Kitty, if monsters were real,
they'd be a lot different
than they are on TV.
Well, I just can't stand
being scared.
Well, what do you
wanna do now?
Let's play a game.
What kind of game?
Let's play truth or dare.
What?
Around here we only play
dare or double dare,
if you can handle it.
- What about truth?
- No truth.
Dares just keep doubling
until someone gets hurt.
- Play nice, Wendell.
- I am.
Okay, Kitty,
you can even go first.
All right.
- Dare or double dare?
- Me?
If you can handle it.
Dare.
I dare you...
to finish your beer
in one drink.
Okay, my turn.
Kitty,
dare or double dare?
Double dare.
Double dare?
I double dare you...
to...
make out with Darlene.
You think I won't?
Well, if you don't,
you lose.
I mean, we could play Scrabble
or something, if you want.
Not bad.
- You surprise me.
- I'm full of them.
Aren't we all?
Okay, Kitty.
It's your turn again.
All right, Darlene...
- dare or double dare?
- Triple dare.
- Triple dare? Come on--
Okay...
I triple dare you and Wendell
to make out.
Huh?
Make out with her?
You are a--
just a kinky little thing,
aren't you?
I win.
I don't think so.
Come on in.
- Nice house.
- Thank you.
- And the flowers--
- Yeah.
This is the sort
of fall foliage...
Oh, yeah.
This is the wood--
woodland room.
This is nice.
I like that frame right there.
- Thank you, thank you.
- Very nice work.
Thank you.
I picked it out myself.
Very nicely hung.
We really shouldn't be here.
- Why is that?
- Just--
get in trouble.
We could go to your room
and be quiet.
I don't know, it's kind of--
Come on.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Okay. Just, we gotta be
really quiet, okay?
Okay.
No. No!
No!
Help!
So, sure you
don't want some?
I'm buying.
Pretty good!
No, I'm fine,
thank you.
So...
what did you want
to talk about?
It uh-- you know, something
at school? Something?
My fucking family, just--
I'm sorry?
Yeah, Paul, it's school and stuff,
you know?
- Yeah.
- Teachers and stuff, you know?
You know, I don't know if I ever
told you about this, but--
my dad, when he was
an army captain and--
we moved from base to base,
it seemed like--
Christ, every--
every year or so.
So I know what
it's like to be--
Francis.
Hey, I'm over here, pal.
Yo, Francis, I'm over here.
Francis.
I'm gonna go, Paul.
I have homework and stuff,
you know?
- Just--
- All right.
Well, I'Il--
I'll stop by in a couple of days
and I'Il--
I'll check up on you, all right?
Here. There you go.
- Thanks.
- You're all right?
Yeah.
- Okay.
- Thanks for the soda.
Sure.
You take care, pal.
Wendell, what the fuck
are you doing?
Oh, hey, Francis.
I didn't know you had
a girlfriend.
Seems really nice, huh?
I saw your little movie too--
creepy.
This is a lot of fun,
a lot of fun.
You don't mind sharing
with the family, do you?
You know, I gotta hand it
to you, brother,
you're a lot more like us
than I thought, aren't you?
She's pretty good-Iooking too.
You know, I had
this good idea though.
I was thinking that we--
oh, yeah, look at that.
Look at that.
We could make our own porn movies
down here if we want.
Bitch, huh?
How do you like that?
Huh, Francis?
Huh? Come on, brother,
let's see what you got.
Let's see what you got--
oh, yeah! You fuck!
Come on, bud. Come on, big guy.
Is that all you got?
That's what I thought, bitch.
Hey, Sam, how about your little hero
now, huh? Huh?
- Fuck!
- No!
- Get over here! Come on.
- Wendell.
You fucking bitch! Huh? You wanna
show off for that fucking bitch?
Huh? I'll let you.
Come on, Lenny, come and get it!
Come on, Lenny.
Check it out.
You like that feeling, bitch?
Come on.
Hey. Hey, Sam, keep it up.
You keep putting shit in his head,
I'm gonna skin you both
alive, all right?
- Please.
- What was that?
Excuse me?
I'm sorry, I don't think
I heard you right.
What was that? Huh?
What was that?
Okay, I'll tell you what,
why don't you hang out here
for awhile?
I'll come back down and we'll finish
what we started, okay?
You can scream
all you want, Sam.
Just know one thing:
I am going to kill you.
All right?
What are you doing
here, Francis?
- We need to talk.
- What happened to your hand?
Wendell.
I'm working here, Francis.
You know, you can't come running to me
- every time you two have a fight.
- Yeah, but--
I'm getting awfully tired
of your hullabaloo, okay?
Wendell, school...
I can't be with you
24 hours a day, bud.
I have no one else
to talk to, David.
I'm working a double shift
here, okay?
Don't you think it's time you started
trying to handle your own problems?
What would you do, huh?
What do you want me to say?
God.
Man,
I just wish Mom and Dad
were still--
They're dead, Francis, okay?
When are you gonna--
when are you gonna
understand that?
Just go home, okay?
We'll talk about this later.
No. You know what?
Fuck you, David!
Fuck you!
I don't need your help.
Don't even fucking worry
about it.
Hey, Wendell.
Is Darlene home?
She's in her room.
So, what are you doing tonight?
You know I'm spending
the night again.
Darlene?
Hey.
- Is she here?
- No.
I meant, she's coming back
in a bit.
No one's here,
it's just you and me.
Okay, well, I'll just
come back later then.
Why not stay
and wait here, huh?
I should probably
just come back.
Really?
Yeah.
What's the rush?
Anyone ever tell you
you smell absolutely delicious?
Huh?
I bet you taste even better.
- Hey.
- Hi, guys.
I guess you're spending
the night, Kitty?
Yeah.
Come on.
What was that?
He's so weird.
You keep telling yourself
that things will change...
that it's all a bad dream
and one day you'll wake up.
I just wish they would catch us
and then it would be all over.
Stay away from me.
I'm not going to hurt you.
You killed my friend.
I brought you some food.
It's all I could afford.
Is that a joke?
Just go away.
Don't worry.
It's just Lenny.
What's Lenny?
You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
You kill people and you feed it
to something you call Lenny?
We're not like you, okay?
We're sick. We have
a fucking disease.
Yeah, you're sick.
You are.
I should go.
Wait.
Can I have some
of that food, please?
It's just--
they'd kill me if they knew
I was here.
- This is looking good.
- Which color are you using?
- This one in here.
- I like it.
Yeah. Okay.
Okay, get you doing this.
I'm just not good at it.
No, just need
a little practice.
Thank you.
What's your name?
Francis.
Can I ask you
something, Francis?
Why did you
bring me food?
Because...
I'm not one of them.
They're gonna
kill me, Francis.
I know.
All you have to do
is call the police.
Please.
My family has money.
They'll give you
anything you need.
You don't understand.
I can't.
Yes, you can.
Yes, you can!
Francis, I have people
who love me, who need me.
I just want to go home.
I want to see my family.
And what about my family?
They're all I have.
They're killers, Francis.
They're not a family.
I can't survive--
can't survive
without them.
Shit.
Hello?
Wendell, are you
messing with me?
Oh my God, you scared
the shit out of me!
Really? What happened?
Let me see.
- Oh my God.
- Can I kiss it and make it better?
I'll just clean it off
in the bathroom.
- Oh, that's a lot of blood.
- Yeah..
- Let me help you.
- Darlene, come on.
Hey, Wendell.
Hey. That's a nasty cut.
Yeah. Wendell, was that you
fucking with me out in the hall?
- Not me. Must've been Darlene.
- Oh, tell the truth, Wendell.
- Truth or dare?
- Ooh, you up for another game, Kitty?
- Can I go first?
- Be my guest.
- Okay. Darlene, dare or double dare?
- Yeah? I don't know,
I'm feeling a little frisky tonight.
How about a double dare to start?
- I double dare you--
- What the hell--?
--to give Kitty a little
seductive dance.
Darlene?
You guys, stop.
Darlene, why are you
doing this?
Stop!
Darlene, stop!
Double dare
or triple dare, Kitty?
I triple dare you to let Wendell
kiss you on the lips.
Here, Kitty Kitty.
Come on, pussycat.
Where are you going, babe?
Where are you going, pussy?
Here, Kitty, Kitty,
Kitty, Kitty.
I don't want
to talk to you in there.
We're not done
with our game yet.
How long have I been out?
Not long--
hour or two.
Somebody will be here soon.
I should go.
Francis...
Thank you for talking to me.
I'm sorry, but...
l--
I can help you out there.
I can help you
without your family.
You don't need them,
Francis.
I'll take care of you.
Please, don't kill me.
You're leaving me here
to die.
I know.
Hey, Dad, over here.
Did you know your redwood
is in violation
of the neighborhood safety
growth code?
- No.
- Uh-huh.
That's a good job, son.
Hi, I'm Larry Davies.
I'm-- I'm Katherine--
Kitty's uncle.
- Kitty is a friend of Darlene's.
- Yeah, sure.
Yeah. This is my son, Allen.
Lieutenant Commander Daniels,
private sector.
David Hamilton.
Just for your information,
Kitty's gonna be staying with us
this college semester.
So if you see her around, that's why.
Is everything all right?
Yeah. Look, I'm sure
it's nothing.
We're just a little worried, that's all.
We haven't heard from her all day
and she isn't answering
her cell phone.
Is she here, by chance?
Unfortunately, no one's here.
Darlene doesn't have
a cell phone--
brain tumors.
That's strange, you know?
It's just not like her.
She said she was gonna be spending
the night here last night with Darlene,
and she knew we had plans
for this morning.
I put a couple of calls in
to some friends of mine
down at the local sheriff's office,
just in case.
But if you hear from her,
please call that number.
Of course, of course.
Hey, look, l--
I know we are bothering you
and all that,
but we didn't have
your number.
So we just thought
we'd pop by and check.
So, if something turns up--
Just let me know
if there's anything I can do.
Take care.
What did you do?
Why, nothing, David.
She left here this morning.
We really haven't seen her since.
I can't believe
you two did this!
Oh, and what
about the dozen homos
you have buried
under the house?
Yeah, Mr. Perfect,
how do you explain that?
Are you that blind in your
make-believe world,
you don't think we know?
I use my head!
I pick transients
and drifters,
not some neighborhood girl
whose cousin or--
or brother or whatever
is the police!
You know why you hate us
so much, David?
It's because
we represent everything
you wish you could have,
but are just too afraid
to face.
You two always--
fuck it up!
Are you trying
to scare us, David,
like when we were kids?
We're not little kids anymore.
So what are you
gonna do, David?
When are you gonna realize
this isn't the first time
and certainly not the last time
it's gonna happen?
Pull it together.
Hey!
- Mom and Dad--
- Mom and Dad were the exception.
None of us have the kind
of self-control to have what they did.
The only difference
between you and us, David,
is we don't look at ourselves
in the mirror and lie.
We accept who we are.
We don't deny it.
We have to move again.
All right, pack up
what we need--
- Hi, this is Paul.
- Hey, Paul--
Please leave your message
at the sound of the tone.
Don't forget to leave
your phone number. Bye.
Paul, it's Francis.
There's something really important
we gotta talk about
about my family
and um...
I can't-- I can't do it
over the phone.
If you could meet me in person,
that'd be great.
l-l-I just--
fuck!
I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
I know, Lenny.
I know.
It's coming.
It's coming, Lenny!
Please sit still.
Actually, it's--
it's kind of funny.
My father taught me
how to do this.
It's kooky, I know,
I know.
He just wanted to make sure
if something were to happen to him,
we'd still survive.
Now you gotta get it
just right, so no air gets in.
It has a longer shelf life
that way.
It's kind of like...
frozen food.
You have something
on your face there.
Oh, I apologize,
I don't mean to make you
self-conscious or anything.
"David," he said,
"David--
David, one day
you might have to be
the man of this family.
David...
David," he said--
he said, "David,
you might have to be
the one that takes care
of your brothers
and your sister."
And I do, I do,
but they don't care.
Do you think they appreciate
what I do for them?
No no no no.
Look, missy,
I don't mean to be a rude cunt,
but it sort of seems to me
that you're not listening
to me.
I just want
what's best for them.
I just want what's
best for them.
I just want
what's best for them.
Goodbye, Lenny.
Francis?
Hey, Francis,
I got your message.
Francis?
David, are you here?
Francis, is that you?
Francis, you out here?
Hello?
David? David?
Da--
David?
Hello?
David, are you all right?
Hey, I'll try to get you out.
Here, listen, I'm gonna--
shit.
You hiding there, huh?
Are you all right?
Hi. Everything's going to be okay.
Stop it, stop--
What are you doing?
What are you doing?!
- Ah, no!
- No, Lenny!
No! Stop!
No no!
Ooh, what happened?
- He's still alive. We can drain him.
- Not him.
Aren't you the one who said
they're just cattle to us
and nothing else?
- Just do what you want.
- Look at this.
So, I guess he took her
with him?
Fuck!
I didn't know the little fucker
had it in him.
I'm actually
kind of proud of the kid.
Yeah, well, he's gonna
get himself in trouble.
He's right on the verge.
We've gotta find him.
Maybe you should
go get him.
He looks up to you.
Will you still help me
out there?
Francis,
where are we?
We're hiding.
Are you okay?
We should get some help.
Francis,
I need your help.
I can't come near you.
Francis, I can't hear you.
What?
What did you say,
Francis?
You're bleeding.
Francis, you're scaring me.
There's something
I need to tell you.
Please-- please,
just help me get up.
We need to get help.
We're born, not made.
- Not like everybody thinks.
- I don't understand.
Oh Christ,
let me go.
Please, please--
Not like the fucking movies.
Francis, please stop.
You have to go.
Francis, please
don't do this.
Franny.
I know.
We all gotta go
through it our first time.
It's just the way
it is, okay?
- I wish Mom and Dad were here.
- It just hurts so bad, David.
I know, I know.
It's just part
of growing up, okay?
It's what we are.
What does it mean
to be happy?
To be content
in the world around you?
Is family the heart
of everything--
even existence?
So what do we do now?
We have to move again.
The twins are packing up
the house.
We're gonna leave
in a few hours.
What about Lenny?
We're gonna have to bring him
out of the box early.
Will he be okay?
You were brought
out of the box early.
I was?
Yeah. See how
you turned out?
- Dave?
- Yeah?
I'm sorry.
So am I, Francis.
- Are you ready?
- Okay.
You guys, I really
hate keeping him like this.
You know it's the way
it's always been.
He would've
killed everything in sight.
- Kind of like us. You ready, David?
- Let me do this.
We're gonna open the door.
We don't have time for this.
- This is Lenny!
- Darlene, come on.
- David, let's go!
- He is-- he is our family!
I can do this.
Okay.
Are you sure?
Fine.
Lenny?
Hey, baby.
Excited?
You see?
We live with a disease.
Mom used to say it was
the one thing that kept us close.
I always thought that it was the one
thing that would keep us apart.
But I was wrong,
and everything you thought
you knew about us is wrong.
We live in the houses
next to you,
we work in the stores
you shop at.
Our kids play with your kids.
We're just trying to be
an ordinary family,
trying to figure out
where we fit in in the world.
But we do need blood,
and we need a lot of it...
...preferably fresh
and not frozen.
Howdy.
We're the Thompsons.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org