Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
No questions about the layout, right?
No questions.
Let's go over this shit again.
They got a small dinger on the door.
l'll get 'em to open it.
Then me and Levine go in. Giolito
and Pederson, block this door.
OK? Rondell and Leppert,
hit the back door.
No problem. lt's a piece of cake.
McKee and Cline, you're outside
in case we get some jump-outs...
- Foley.
- Excuse me a sec.
Where in the hell is SWAT?
- Boss, l cancelled the SWAT team.
- You what?
l wouldn't raid
a church bingo game without SWAT.
These guys are carjackers.
They're mechanics.
We don't need SWAT
blowing holes in my evidence.
Besides, they might shoot somebody.
Let's do this.
This is your operation. l'm just
an observer, but l'll be watching.
Just observe how l don't have
to use SWAT, and trust me.
Everybody's ready?
Nobody need to take a nervous piss?
Let's mount up.
This is Dick Burton.
We've got 55 degrees this morning.
Here's Diana Ross and the Supremes,
Come See About Me.
What are you doing?
Bobby, they're here.
Any trouble with the hijack?
- Right where you said.
- Piece of cake.
- Anybody hurt?
- No.
Good. l don't like to see
people unnecessarily injured.
Nobody got hurt, boss.
- Keys?
- Ain't yours till we see money.
l just want to look in the back.
- Where's our money?
- Pay him.
You think we should have used SWAT?
- Fuck SWAT.
- That's what l say. Fuck SWAT.
- Some guy. What should l do?
- Kill him.
How you doing? ls this the illegal
chop shop where they chop up cars?
l got my wife's Buick. l want it
chopped, the bitch ain't been right.
Go, go, go!
Go!
They got fucking machineguns.
- You said they had no guns!
- They must have changed their view.
Get the 12-gauge.
We should've called SWAT.
Police! Hands in the air!
Move it! Go! Go!
What the...?
Daniel, come on!
Cover me. l'm going in with Todd.
Axel, you on a coffee break?
Go get that son of a bitch.
Boss. Hey, man! Shit!
We got a tail.
Wax that clown.
God damn it!
Help me, man.
Police officer!
Trying to catch a killer. Move it!
- Get out of my way! l'm a cop!
- Take it easy.
Get the fuck out of here,
all right?
Thank you. My name's Steve Fulbright.
Could l see some lD, please?
l am a Detroit police officer.
My name is Axel... Where's my shit?
l'm a police officer chasing
a killer who's getting away now.
- We know.
- You know what?
We know.
What's happened is you're in the
middle of a federal investigation.
What, income tax? The fucking guy
just shot a police officer!
lt's very important
he not be apprehended at this time.
We want to know where he's going
and who he's selling it to.
- lt's drugs?
- We're not DEA.
We appreciate
your co-operation on this.
l checked with Washington,
Fulbright's kosher.
He's working
on something classified.
lf they want these guys loose
we should close the investigation.
Fuck them. l want the man
that killed Todd. What you got?
Not a hell of a lot.
The dead mechanics were executed.
Only one was strapped,
he was still holstered.
The bodies of the shooters
had 30,000 cash.
- High-price heat.
- San Diego drivers' licenses.
San Diego PD's sheet says enforcers
for hire for Tijuana drug dealers.
lt's about drugs?
An attaché case had a towel from
the Wonder World Hotel, California.
Wonder World? Did you check out
that car they shot Todd from?
Rental from the airport.
The renter's a Dr Oliver Hirsch.
- A stolen lD?
- Yeah.
Doctor said it was lifted
while in an amusement park.
- l hope the park was Wonder World.
- Yeah.
- Excuse me.
- Wonder World.
l understand
that you were with him at the end.
Yeah. His last words were about you.
That does not sound
like my Douglas, Axel. Try again.
Actually, his last words were,
''Axel, are you on a coffee break?
Go and get that son of a bitch.''
Those were his last words.
- That sounds like my Douglas.
- lt sounds like a good idea, too.
Hello, l'm looking
for Billy Rosewood.
Welcome to Beverly Hills Police.
To continue this message
in English, press one.
For Spanish, press two.
For Farsi, press three.
lf you have homeless people
on your lawn, press 15.
lf you need
the riot rumour hotline, press 17.
Which button for Billy Rosewood?
Monsieur Rosewood? ln the house?
Le Rosewood. Moi le Rosewood.
''Monsieur était beau.
Le crayon. La table.''
Come in.
lt's open.
- Axel Foley!
- Billy, how you doing?
- l don't believe it.
- Look at your office! Look at this!
You got three windows,
venetian blinds, and a ficus.
One of them big, healthy
ficus in your office.
Not just the ficus. Look.
You got a refrigerator
in your office?
J Edgar Hoover
didn't have a refrigerator.
Just some hair curlers or something.
- Did they promote you to captain?
- l'm DDO-JSlOC.
The JG-Joe-Joe-C? What is that?
Deputy Director of Operations
for Joint Systems lnterdepartmental
Operational Command.
Here we are. Los Angeles. one of the
greatest cities in the world, Axel,
divided by its unique geography.
- Geography?
- LA is a vast metropolis
with social and economic imbalances
spread over an enormous distance.
A criminal hits Beverly Hills,
then West Hollywood, then downtown.
Whose responsibility is it?
Everybody's?
lmpossible. So it comes here. Every
crime that crosses the green line.
- The green line?
- Green lines of jurisdiction.
Beverly Hills,
West Hollywood, Santa Monica.
Officers respect these green lines,
but the criminal doesn't.
Whenever a criminal crosses green
lines, the DDO-JSlOC goes to work.
Very impressive, Billy.
l control the green lines,
and Axel...
whoever controls the green lines
controls Southern California.
You wanted to see me, Billy?
The sheriff's department nabbed
two guys pulling a stall-and-hook.
lt's the same MO
as those jobs on Melrose.
l'll run out there and talk to them.
They're in Van Nuys.
l'll tell them you're coming.
Jon, l want you
to meet a friend of mine.
Axel Foley. Axel, Jon Flint.
How are you? l've heard about you.
You're from Detroit, right?
- Taggart talked about you.
- Taggart! Where is he?
Taggart's retired to Phoenix.
Spends his days lost in the woods
looking for his golf balls.
That's a dream
l'm not too far from myself.
What brings you to California?
Vacation?
- l'm looking for a killer.
- ln Beverly Hills?
- No. Wonder World.
- Wonder World?
You mean Rufus Rabbit
has gone berserko?
No. My boss got gunned down.
The killer escaped
in a cream-coloured Ford truck.
- l think it's here.
- Plates?
Plates were phoney. Some evidence
points to Wonder World.
l want to go to Wonder World
and ask some questions.
- Would y'all know somebody there?
- Ellis DeWald, head of security.
Biggest private
security force in America.
- Can you introduce me to him?
- Soon as l get back from Van Nuys.
You go on out. l'll call DeWald,
tell him you're coming.
- He's a pal of mine. l'll meet you.
- Great. Thanks.
You'll love Wonder World,
it's a great place.
Axel, don't forget,
we play by the rules around here.
l've heard Taggart's stories.
Which one of those green lines
is Wonder World behind?
Welcome to Wonder World. Can l help?
Yes, l'd like to talk to a park
executive, a Mr Ellis DeWald.
- Do you have an appointment?
- l'm supposed to. Axel Foley.
l'm sorry, sir.
l don't have you on the list.
Maybe they haven't called yet.
A Detective Flint was supposed
to call and get me squared away.
lf you don't have an appointment
you'll need a ticket.
- How much is a ticket?
- $35.
That allows you access
to all rides and attractions.
Wait a minute.
l don't want to go on any rides.
All l wanna do
is talk to the director of security.
Excuse me, sir,
would you step out of line?
- What line?
- Just step over here, please, sir.
Thank you.
- ls there a problem, sir?
- $35, that's the problem.
lf the admission seems high,
try Fantasy Park.
You might find
their ticket price to your liking.
l'm here to see Ellis DeWald.
ls he your boss?
Yes. Mr DeWald
is head of guest relations.
- Do you have an appointment?
- l'm supposed to.
Supposed to is not having,
is it, sir?
Excuse me.
- One, please.
- There you go. Thank you.
Thank you.
You should have your tailor
cut the jacket a little wider.
That way your gun
won't bulge in the back.
Thank you.
Uncle Dave.
What's going on?
''Alien Attack''?
Can l help you?
l was just curious
what Alien Attack is.
Watch.
Attention! This is a red alert.
Aliens are invading the city.
Board the subway trains
for immediate evacuation.
This is wild.
Yes. lt's one of
our more popular attractions.
Excuse me,
but what are you doing in here?
You're right. l gotta go. l have
a meeting, but thanks for the show.
Tunnel nine. Take a look.
- What should we do?
- l'll send Cooper. Get him.
Excuse me.
- That's not fair.
- Maintenance. Gotta grease a chain.
- Hear how dry it sounds?
- Sorry.
Come on. Let's go.
- Hi, Mom!
- Up here!
- Hi, Mommy! Up here!
- We're here!
- Bring that man down.
- l can't until it goes all...
- Bring it down, damn it.
- Don't...
Don't. Don't! Jesus!
- What the hell?
- Oh, my God!
Code red on The Spider.
Wonder World? Axel!
Help!
Help! Please!
Shit!
My God. Look!
- Are you all right?
- l'm OK, just don't let go.
All units near Wonder World,
proceed to assist
in emergency rescue.
You see this rope? We're gonna
slide down it to the ground.
- We are?
- We're gonna try.
Come up and hold on to my neck.
Come on. lt's OK.
You gonna grab onto my neck really
tight. Come on. Hold on really tight.
Not too tight!
Give me your hand.
Come on. None of that.
Give me your hand. Come on. lt's OK.
Come on.
Hang on tight!
Come on. Come on up.
Our head of security confirmed your
identity with the Detroit police.
But neither they nor l...
..understand what
you're doing at Wonder World.
l'm investigating a crime.
l've been here 10 minutes
and l've already been shot at.
Yes. Some of our
guest relations people, you said.
Miss Perkins is here
with the surveillance tapes.
Send her right in.
This starts in The Spider
maintenance tunnel.
There l am,
coming down the tunnel.
- What is that?
- Tracking. The monitors are looped.
- l don't see any gunmen, Mr Foley.
- So who was l shooting at?
You better think about a lawyer.
The tapes don't show your gunman.
They don't show something else,
Mr Foley's courage when the ride
malfunctioned. He risked his life.
They don't show that.
That would be very impressive,
if you didn't cause the malfunction.
- Mr DeWald.
- Send him in.
Mr Foley, Mr DeWald.
You fuck! Motherfucker...
That's him!
That's the fucking guy
l'm looking for!
What's going on here?
He shot a Detroit police officer
last weekend!
Last weekend? l was at my
beach house in Laguna last weekend.
Your beach home in Laguna?
Wait. l think l got the wrong guy.
l'm sorry.
This is a big misunderstanding.
You were at your beach...
Fuck! Beach house in Laguna!
You motherfucker!
- Miss Bruce, call the police.
- They just walked in.
- That guy! That's the killer!
- Ellis DeWald?
We really appreciate this, Ellis.
Your friend is lucky Mr Sanderson
doesn't want any publicity.
You just keep him and his delusions
out of my face and out of my park.
No problem. You got it. By the way,
are we still on for Sunday?
Bring your money, sucker.
All right. When you have
some time, l'd like to...
Not right now. Later, perhaps.
Thanks.
Here we go.
Thank you.
And the usual for you, Billy.
- Thanks a lot.
- lsn't it possible you're mistaken?
That Ellis DeWald
just resembles Todd's killer?
l made the guy in Detroit.
lt was DeWald.
He's the head of the largest private
police department in California.
He works with us, with the governor's
office. Everybody loves him.
He's getting an award from the
Association of Security Agencies.
lt's understandable
that you're distraught
and looking for justice,
not to mention revenge.
But isn't it just possible
that you want it so much
that you saw your killer in a man
who bore a slight resemblance?
We run into this
all the time in police work.
- Where's he getting that award?
- Don't!
Flint, your friend DeWald is foul.
l know he's foul,
and l'm going to this awards show
to put some pressure on him.
Maybe panic him
into doing something stupid.
Axel, if you go
to that dinner tonight...
- l'm going with you.
- Pick me up at the Sunset Motel.
Freeze, motherfucker!
- Detective Foley?
- You're Uncle Dave!
Oh, my God. l almost shot Uncle Dave!
l'm so embarrassed. l'm sorry.
Nice to meet you! Uncle Dave!
The front desk let us in.
l hope that's OK.
No, it's fine. lt's Uncle Dave!
Uncle Dave! Have a seat.
- Thank you.
- l was such a fan of yours.
- Thank you, son.
- Uncle Dave...
You're very kind. Detective Foley,
what's going on at my park?
- There's something going on?
- l have no doubts.
- What?
- l have no doubts,
nor do l have any ideas.
Exactly two weeks ago,
Detective Foley,
Roger Fry, the park's
chief operating officer...
and my friend, disappeared.
Roger Fry designed the park, from the
landscaping to the concession stands.
- What do you mean, disappeared?
- Show him the note.
l received this interoffice
the day Roger disappeared.
''This is important,
life and death. Roger''
- What was so important?
- l don't know.
What was he doing
the day he disappeared?
He was probably doing
one of his usual inspections.
- This guy designed the whole park?
- Yes.
- And he knew the place cold?
- Of course.
So what are you thinking?
He must've found something
someone didn't want him to find.
At Wonder World?
What on earth could that be?
lt's a place
of childhood innocence and fun.
And life and death.
You met Uncle Dave? Uncle Dave.
l don't believe it. l'd give
anything to have been with you.
- Did he do the Oki-Doki Shuffle?
- No.
Outstanding.
- William Rosewood, DDO-JSlOC.
- l beg your pardon?
This is me. Thank you.
What you gonna do with this shit?
No way.
l don't believe this! Ackwell!
Ackwell Folee! Ackwell Folee, you
crazy thing. What you doing here?
- ''Surge.''
- Serge.
Look at your head!
l love it short!
- Yeah, Serge.
- Turn around. Turn around.
You look perfect! And finally
you have black ''Hush Poopies'',
which are totally retro.
You put a good package together.
- You remember Billy Rosewood.
- Billy, l remember you.
- Do you remember?
- Of course.
l made you an espresso at
the art gallery with a lemon twist?
lt was the last one l ever made.
lt's terrible, espresso.
You know why?
lt stain your teeth. l won't
show you mine. Show me your teeth.
They're so pretty.
Can l see your teeth?
And you got healthy gums.
- Do you do colonics?
- Excuse me?
- No. Never...
- lt's my new favourite!
- You dig colonics?
- They stick a hose up inside you...
- l know...
No, you've got to understand.
Out comes a candy bar
from when you were five!
- What happened to your art gallery?
- lt is completely bankrupt,
in the toilet. Why?
Because we had an owner who was
obstinate and stupid and ignorant.
- You shot him, remember?
- Yes. l shot him.
- What are you doing now?
- l'm doing guns. Come!
This is my booth.
The Survival Boutique.
We are doing weapons and protective
devices and products for survival
in the helter-skelter world of today.
One thing's very important.
At the Survival Boutique,
it's my philosophy that everything
must conform to the three P's.
Which is protection,
prestige and pretty.
Why should you look ugly
if you're just trying to survive?
You should maintain your style
and be safe. Guess what this is.
ls look like a key chain,
but it's so much more.
lt's called a stunner.
lt is designed by an ex-Navy SEAL.
Very serious individual,
l never see him smile.
Also l never see him
in pants that fit.
Someone comes up to you
who is a carjacker.
Do you want to die for your Camry?
l don't think so.
So you say -
a little bit of deception -
''l want to separate
my house and car keys.
''l'll just push this button, OK?''
And he says, ''OK.''
And then you push this button,
and out it comes from the mechanism,
the brightest, blinding light
ever that you seeing.
He cannot see. He's like this.
Everyone is come running
to help you.
And once again,
you have survived with style.
That's cool.
Billy, l want to give you one
for a present.
Thank you.
And, Ackwell, l want to give you one
because l worry about you.
- l want you to be safe.
- Thanks.
Now l'll show you something that
is going to blow your rocks off.
lt's absolutely orgasmic
and my most thing that l'm proud of.
lt's the most up-to-date, the
ultimate survival tool for today.
A new generation of luxury personal
weaponry, the Annihilator 2000
is America's premier survival,
home and travel security unit.
The Annihilator 2000
is a high-performance weapon
that meets the demands
of upper income urban survivalists.
The Annihilator 2000
has the conveniences
of a cellphone,
fax and microwave oven.
Night-vision goggles,
microprocessor,
verbal alarm systems,
compact disc player, digital radio,
video camera and playback functions
are just a few features
of the extraordinary
Annihilator 2000.
You think those are real?
Stopping power
is a matter of convenience.
That's Dodi, my personal trainer.
She can bench-press 200lbs.
She's working on reducing
my body fat, but it's difficult
because l keep sneaking goat cheese.
l don't care. l wear suits.
The Annihilator 2000
is constructed of aluminium alloy
combined with polymer technology,
totally resistant to corrosion.
A new generation in luxury personal
weaponry, the Annihilator 2000
is America's premier survival,
home and travel security unit.
Who's gonna buy that shit?
Are you joking? This is LA.
l'm selling hundreds of these.
- Get the fuck outta here!
- No, because l am telling you,
l sell 10 of these
to Jackie Stallone.
- Get the fuck outta here.
- Sly bought 1 4.
Zsa Zsa Gabor has one...
- We gotta go, Surge.
- Thanks.
Ackwell, try to say Serge.
lt's not so difficult.
''Surge'' sounds like a detergent.
What are you gonna do?
Nothing.
l just wanna hear the man speak.
To keep a park like Wonder World
a safe, wholesome, family environment
in difficult times like these
is an enormous challenge.
But my friend Ellis DeWald
has done just that.
Couple that with Ellis' work
with underprivileged kids,
some of whom are seated at the
head table right now with Ellis...
..and you can understand
why he's our award winner.
So let's bring him up here.
Head of security at Wonder World
and private law enforcement's
Man of the Year award winner,
my dear friend, Ellis DeWald.
- Congratulations. You deserve it.
- Thank you, Orrin.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks, Mike.
You're not gonna do nothing.
You never do nothing.
Thank you very much.
You know, a lot of nice things happen
when you work at a nice place
like Wonder World,
especially when your bosses
are people like Orrin Sanderson
and Uncle Dave Thornton. l don't
think that Uncle Dave would mind
if l said that this is
the nicest thing yet.
Thank you very much.
Please don't do this, Axel.
Please don't do it. Don't do it.
- Bravo! Bravo!
- Don't do it.
Bravo, Ellis DeWald! Ellis DeWald!
Ellis DeWald, ladies and gentlemen!
Ellis DeWald! Y'all keep it going!
Keep it going for Ellis DeWald!
Come on, it's Ellis!
You're not clapping loud enough!
This is Ellis DeWald!
Ladies and gentlemen,
l've travelled from Detroit
to be with this man tonight,
to honour this man tonight.
My name is Axel Foley.
l'm a Detroit police officer.
lt is a tremendous surprise
for Mr DeWald to have me next to him.
l can feel his body tingling!
But, ladies and gentlemen,
there's not a night that goes by
that l don't think about
what l owe Ellis DeWald.
And there's not a night that passes
that l don't think about
what the people of Detroit
owe Ellis DeWald.
And l'd like to say,
when l see y'all give him this...
What's this? That's beautiful...
''With gratitude
for community service.''
And l'm going to do
the community a service
because l'm going
to pay back Ellis DeWald
everything we owe him with interest!
Go on, smile.
Get them last few smiles in.
What's the matter? You mad at me
for shooting your boyfriend?
l got him! l got him! l got him!
You and Billy
disturbing the peace? No!
Just make your phone call
and get us out of here.
Sure. Who do l know
down there? Let's see.
Don't fuck with me right now.
Keep your shirt on.
l'll get you out.
lncidentally,
we found that truck you wanted.
- Where?
- By the Santa Monica pier.
l'm headed there now.
l'll pick you up on the way.
ln the meantime,
don't take any showers.
l'm all washed-up. Dead in the water.
Stop worrying.
Flint's going to get us out.
l really liked that office.
- Foley! You're out of here.
- That was quick.
Not him, just you.
Come in.
Thank you, officer.
l ran a check on you, Foley.
You're a hell of a detective,
but something of a maverick.
l know what you're doing.
l know the drill.
You hassle DeWald, you get him
to panic, make a rash move...
But God damn it, Foley,
we do not want to panic this man.
We want him doing business as fucking
usual. Do you copy me, Foley?
Ticket to Detroit, first class,
courtesy of the Federal Government.
Also, my card.
Should you have any more thoughts
about DeWald, let us handle it.
l give you my word as a gentleman
l'll be on that plane.
Truck was spotted
by an LAPD traffic officer.
lt's a different colour
but the same make and model.
Read you. Out. Beach leader, over?
Negatory, SWAT,
hold for our arrival.
ETA...1 1 minutes. Out.
Billy, who were you talking to?
Truck was inside
the county green line,
so l co-ordinated
with the SMPD, BHPD,
LAPD, sheriff of Los Angeles County,
Parks and Recreation,
Highway Patrol, district attorney's
office and US Naval Shore Patrol.
Beach leader to team one. Proceed.
All teams standing ready...
Go! Go! Go!
Area secured.
Lab says these are the same
fibres as the truck upholstery.
No help there. Some sand, probably
blew in after it was abandoned.
l just had a very unpleasant
conversation with my superiors.
- About being busted?
- No.
There was some objection to my use
of manpower on Operation Truck Siege.
- What is it?
- You got a $50 bill?
l'm married with kids.
l haven't seen a 50 in 1 2 years.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org