Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
You ever think about dying?
Yeah. You?
Yeah. Some.
You think there's a heaven?
Yeah. Don't you?
I don't know.
Yeah, maybe.
Can you believe there's a heaven
if you don't believe in hell?
I guess you can believe
what you want to.
This ranch has been in my family
as long as anyone can remember.
My granddaddy used to tell me
this was heaven on earth.
Just like his granddaddy
used to tell him.
Everything's changed now
since he died.
Appreciate you lighting them candles.
It wasn't me. It was the lady.
My mother?
She was here?
She's left already?
All I ever wanted was to live
out there like him...
...and work my own spread.
Can't imagine no better life.
I've come to find out Mama
aims to sell it.
Says the oil company would pay
three times what it's worth.
Mama lives in San Antonio now
with her new husband.
She wants to be in the live theatre.
As your granddaddy's only child...
...your mother inherits outright.
It's her property.
She can do whatever she wants.
I don't have any say-so?
What about my father?
They're divorced.
You could talk to her.
You're a lawyer.
Well, I have talked to her.
It's a sorry piece of business,
but, son...
...not everybody thinks life
on a cattle ranch in Texas...
...is the second-best thing
to going to heaven.
She don't want to live
out there, that's all.
If it was a paying proposition,
that'd be one thing, but it ain't.
It could be.
I could run it.
It's his own damn fault.
Your father signed every
paper she set in front of him.
Never lifted a hand to save himself.
I begged him to get a lawyer.
Well...
I'm sorry to have no better news...
...but some things in this world
can't be helped.
I believe this is probably
one of them.
She went back to San Antonio.
Don't call her "she. "
Mama.
I thought the world of that old man.
Yeah.
Don't go crying on me now.
I ain't.
- Well, don't.
- I ain't.
- What do you think I should do?
- I don't think there's much to do.
- Will you talk to her?
- I can't.
You could talk to her.
Last conversation I had with her...
...was in San Diego, California,
in 1942.
It ain't her fault.
I ain't the same as I once was.
Like to think I am...
...but I ain't.
You are inside.
Inside you are.
It's hard to watch people you came
from waste away before your eyes.
When the land is gone too...
...there's nothing to stand on
or stand for either.
When do y'all have to be out?
Closing is the first of June.
You could wait till then.
What for?
Down in Mexico...
...they got ranches so big...
...you can't ride from one end
to the other in a week.
It ain't all fenced in
and sold off and played out.
Not down there.
You think they can't use
two more top hands?
ReaI cowboys, huh?
Just like the old-time waddies.
If I don't go, will you go anyways?
I'm already gone.
- Thank you for everything.
- Goodbye.
May God go with you.
Be carefuI.
Is that you, bud?
I hope so.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
- They suspect anything?
- No.
- Let's go.
- Hang on. Got to pile all this stuff.
- Yonder goes the light.
- Damn.
- Late for your own funeraI.
- He could be getting milk.
He could just be loading a shotgun.
Shut up. Lacey, there's been
somebody following us.
- Somebody on horseback?
- Yeah.
Come on.
Some kid.
That's a hell of a horse.
Ain't it, though?
You hunting us?
- I ain't hunting you.
- Why you following us?
I ain't. I'm going to Langtry.
I don't even know you.
- Where'd you get that horse?
- It's mine.
- How old are you?
- Sixteen.
- Lying sack of shit!
- You don't know.
I know you ain't no goddamn 16.
- What'd you do, run off?
- What if I did?
We could sell his horse in Mexico.
- You want to?
- I ain't digging no grave this time.
Your idea. I was the one that said
just leave him for the buzzards.
Call it.
Heads.
Damn.
Let me have your rifle.
It ain't fair.
You shot the last three.
You go on, then. You can owe me.
Hold his horse.
It might not be gun-broke.
Y'all ain't never shot nobody.
You could be a good somebody
to start with.
Y'all just funning.
I knowed it all along.
Who's hunting you?
Nobody.
They're hunting that horse,
though, right?
You ain't riding with us.
Get us in the jailhouse.
He belongs to me.
Son, I don't give a shit
who he belongs to.
But he damn sure don't belong to you.
Now, let's go, bud.
I thought he'd put up more
of a argument.
We ain't seen the last
of his skinny ass.
That's her, ain't it?
That's the goddamn Rio Grande.
Just think. Over yonder's Old Mexico.
You reckon you want to cross now?
Yeah. You?
Yeah.
Maybe we'd better rest
these horses up first.
All right.
Shit.
I got a uneasy feeling
about that son of a bitch.
I do too.
He ain't as green as he looks,
neither.
There won't nobody
be hunting me in Mexico.
That all depends on what you done.
- What's your name?
- Jimmy Blevins.
You got any grub?
No.
You got any money?
You're just a deadhead.
Just tell me one thing.
What the hell would we want you
with us for?
Because I'm a American.
When did you eat last?
Other day.
Your name ain't Blivit, is it?
It's Blevins.
You know what a blivit is?
No. What?
Ten pounds of shit
in a five-pound sack.
Y'all ain't said y'all's names was.
I'm John Grady Cole.
This here's Lacey Rawlins.
We're from San Angelo.
Where you from?
Uvalde County.
Near the SabinaI River.
What made you light out for Mexico?
Same reason as you.
What reason is that?
Because they'd go bowlegged
and blind finding your ass down here.
Nobody's hunting me.
I told that son of a bitch
he wasn't whupping me again.
- Your daddy?
- No.
He never came back from the war.
Your stepdaddy.
I know what it's like
to get a beating.
You didn't shoot him?
I would've. And he knowed it too.
Suppose we trade that horse off
for one less likely get us shot.
- I ain't trading horses.
- We ain't no wet nurses.
- I can take care of myself.
- Sure.
Hell, you're a regular
old desperado, ain't you?
I reckon you got your own gun and all.
Yeah, I got a gun.
What kind of a gun?
-32-20 Colt.
- Bullshit.
That's a rifle cartridge.
Let's see it.
Where'd you get a gun like this?
At the getting place.
- You ever shot it?
- Yeah, I shot it.
- You hit anything?
- Anything you want.
Bullshit.
All right, let's go, outlaw. Come on.
You ready, Annie Oakley?
Waiting on you.
Goddamn.
Let me see it.
- Let me see it.
- We'd better get going.
- Come on, give it to me.
- You know what my wallet looks like.
Look at this shit.
She got anything to drink?
What is that?
- Cider.
- All right.
Let's have three of them.
How much is it?
It's like three cents.
Oh, let your old dad buy it.
He about dead-centred
your pocketbook, didn't he?
I want you to look at my
goddamn driver's license.
And my pooI hall card.
You won't need them down here.
Look at this shit.
Shot Betty Ward between the eyes.
What's she doing in there?
I didn't know you liked her.
What is this? Cactus juice?
I don't know.
- Got a little kick to it, though.
- I think it does.
Pretty doggone good.
Say it again. Say my name again.
Golly!
What am I doing leaving
my hat on the bed? It's not much.
You can't have no more cider.
Shit.
I'm drunker than shit.
Can you ride or not?
Hell, yeah, I can ride.
I was riding when I fell off.
I'm a regular buckaroo.
Certified damn bronc peeler.
Just leave him lay there.
Get on and quit assing around.
It's fixing to come a good one.
Come on.
I can't be out in this.
- Where do you think you'll go?
- Why can't you?
On account of the lightning.
Damn if you don't look
sober all of a sudden.
- Are you afraid of lightning?
- It runs in the family.
My grandpa, he was killed
in West Virginia in a mine bucket.
It run all the way down the hole
to get him, 180 feet.
A great-uncle on my mother's side...
...was killed off a horse. Horse's
hair wasn't singed, but it killed him.
I got a cousin not
four year older than me.
He was struck by lightning
coming back from his barn.
Melted the fillings in his teeth
and soldered his jaw shut.
He's gone completely dipshit.
I done been struck twice myself.
How come me be deaf in this one ear?
I'm born to death by fire, man.
You'd better get away from all metaI.
You don't know what it'd get you.
Your boot spurs, shirt buttons...
What do you intend to do?
Outride it.
You can't outride a thunderstorm.
What the hell is wrong with you?
It's the only chance I got.
I knowed it from the first time that
son of a bitch had a loose nut.
What the hell are you doing?!
Just sitting here.
If this rain hits hard, there'll be
a river come down like a train.
You thought about that?
You've never been struck by lightning.
You don't know what it's like.
You'll drown sitting there.
That's all right. I ain't never
been drowned before.
Well...
...I'll say no more.
Your horse is gone.
Yeah, I know. I done been on foot
looking around this morning.
Where'd you find that boot?
On the ground.
Well, what do you aim to do?
I don't know.
Let's get your ass up out of there.
Got a spare shirt in my saddlebag.
You put that on.
Appreciate it.
Rawlins will pitch a pure hissy
when he sees you.
I don't give a shit.
There's my damn pistoI.
- Shit.
- Hold on.
Keep riding. Good God almighty.
I ain't leaving untiI I get my stuff.
- My gun too.
- Listen at that.
Get us all shot for horse-stealing
don't mean a thing.
- It ain't stealing. It's mine.
- Shit-for-brains!
Hush. Both of you.
Get over here and sit down.
We're going to stick here...
...till about a hour before daylight.
Now, you got to play this
exactly like we say.
If that don't satisfy,
you tell us right now.
Yeah. Okay.
All right.
You go on and get some sleep.
And no fire tonight.
Every dumb thing I ever done
in my life...
...there was a decision I made
before that got me into it.
It was never the dumb thing.
It was always some choice I'd
made before. You understand?
Yeah, I think so.
Meaning what?
Meaning this is it.
This is our last chance. Won't be
no other time, I guarantee it.
- Meaning just leave him?
- Yes, sir.
What if it was you?
I wouldn't leave you, or you me.
You realize the fix he's in?
I realize it. It's the fix
he's put himself in.
I can't do it.
Well, if you can't, you can't.
I guess I knew what you'd say anyways.
Oh, no. Damn it.
That little son of a bitch.
Hold up, hold up. Let's listen.
You little son of a bitch.
- Boys, they're coming.
- Cars or horses?
Horses. And there ain't no way
y'all can keep up.
I'll take the road. They'll follow
the dust, since they're hunting me.
Get in the woods.
I'll see y'all down the road.
Let's get off this damn road.
You think they caught him?
I don't know.
I'll say one thing for him anyways.
What's that?
Son of a bitch wouldn't stand still
for nobody hijacking his horse.
You got your boots on?
- Yeah.
- All right.
You reckon they're friendly?
Shoot, I hope so.
Where are you going?
We're just passing through.
We're looking for work.
Oh, yeah?
We might have some work for you.
He said maybe.
Can we come with you?
Yes, of course.
Good.
Go that way.
Over there?
Did you see that little darling?
Watch it. Bring him over here.
Get in there.
How long you reckon
you'd like to stay here?
About a hundred years.
Now go to sleep.
There's Don Hector Rocha y VillareaI.
Owns this whole shebang.
One of the last great ranches
in Mexico.
27,000 acres.
Flies his own plane
to Mexico City every week.
ManueI said this ranch been
in this family 170 years.
You reckon that was his daughter?
Yeah, I guess it was.
Let me go get my boots on.
Looks like there's
about 12 or 13 of them.
I make it 16.
Armando said the old man's got
like 400 mustangs up on that mesa.
Damn.
You think you and me can break
all 16 of them in four days?
- Why four days?
- You think we could do it?
You'd be about a wore-out sumbuck,
I'll tell you that.
I'll have a look at them.
Go talk to Armando.
How you doing?
I'm all right.
If we mess this up, bud, it's gonna be
a long ride back to Texas.
Give it some slack.
That's it. That's it. Whoa, boy.
I'll put a saddle on you right now.
Your jackets.
You tired?
The horse is arriving, get ready.
Don't delay!
Hector de la Rocha y VillareaI.
John Grady Cole.
Glad to meet you.
Alfonsa, you look like
an Impressionist painting.
Armando says you know
a lot about horses.
I've been around them some.
Do you know what a criollo is?
Yes, sir. It's a Argentine horse.
You're from Texas?
Yes, sir.
San Angelo.
Why are you here?
I just wanted to see the country,
I reckon. Or we did.
- You and your friend.
- Yes, sir.
But you are the leader.
We don't have no leaders.
No, we're just buddies.
Of course.
I recently purchased a thoroughbred
stallion of excellent blood.
- You gonna raise racehorses?
- No. Quarter horses.
I'm thinking of breeding my stallion
with my mesteno mares.
What's your opinion on that?
Well, I've known it done.
There's been good cow horses
sired out of thoroughbreds.
Of what importance is the mare?
Same as the sire. In my opinion.
Most breeders place more confidence
in the stallion.
Yes, sir, they do.
But I agree with you.
And you rode all the way here
from Texas?
Yes, sir.
- You and your friend?
- Yes, sir.
Just the two of you.
Yes, sir.
Just me and him.
Well, Mr. Cole, would you like
to see some horses?
Yes, sir.
- It ain't like you was going away.
- No. We'd still be working together.
It's a good opportunity for you.
Hell, I'd do it.
They told me to come bunk in here.
I was going to put my horse
in one of these stalls.
Can I put my horse in this stall?
Well, I guess we can talk later.
That's your mare.
Look at the eye on her.
Bring this one here.
She's not as big as the other one,
but that's your mare.
Do you like this one?
She's a beauty.
Looks like some of them
got their hats on, bud.
I figure you just must be ready to cry
yourself to sleep every night.
She's probably used to dating guys got
their own airplanes, let alone cars.
You're probably right.
I'm glad to hear you say it.
It don't change nothing though.
My name's John Grady Cole.
My name is Alejandra.
I know.
I hoped that you would come.
I come because I thought
you'd be here.
I know.
My granddaddy lived
his whole life on that ranch.
Seventy-four years.
Seem there could hardly be one
without the other.
I guess...
...the country lasts forever,
and people ain't but for a while.
And how will you live now?
Where will your home be?
What's wrong?
I dreamed about you last night.
What did you dream about?
Someday I may tell you.
But not tonight.
Do I have something in my nose?
No. I have something in my nose.
Do you like him?
A hell of a horse.
I want to ride him.
What?
When?
Now.
- I want to now.
- He don't have a saddle.
I know.
I don't think the patron would want me
to give him to you without a saddle.
Your father.
Get down.
- Are you sure about this?
- Yes!
Hurry.
Well, what do you aim to do
with your horse?
I want you to take him
back to the barn.
Somebody's gonna see me.
Fixing to get me in trouble.
You are in trouble.
I am Senorita Alfonsa.
I'm John Grady Cole.
I'm happy that you have come.
Alejandra will be in Mexico City
with her mother for two weeks.
Then she'll be here for the summer.
Alejandra and I disagree strongly.
In fact, I...
She's so much like me
at that age that I-
I seem, at times, to be struggling
with my own past self.
So you see, I cannot help but be
sympathetic to Alejandra.
But I won't have her unhappy.
I won't have her spoken ill of...
...or gossiped about.
I know what that is.
It is not proper for you to be seen
riding in campo together...
...without supervision.
I considered whether to speak
to my niece about it, but I...
I've decided not.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to be considerate
of a young girI's reputation.
I never meant not to be.
I believe you.
But you see...
...this is another country.
Here, a woman's reputation
is all she has.
There's no forgiveness...
...for women.
A man may lose his honour and regain
it again, but a woman cannot.
I guess I'd have to say
that don't seem right.
It's not a matter of right.
It's a matter of who must say.
And in this matter, I get to say.
What is it?
You're going to wake Esteban.
Then invite me in.
What did she say to you? My aunt?
You want to sit down?
Go on.
What did she say to you?
- Didn't she tell you what she said?
- Of course she did.
What did she say?
She said she didn't want me
being seen with you in the campo.
And you agreed?
- You are afraid of her.
- No.
Just like everyone else.
It ain't like that.
I hate the way she treats me.
I thought you were my friend.
You tell me what you want me to do.
I'll do anything you say.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org