Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
We're back!
Let's go!
Nuts.
Give me the Black Beauty.
Alvin! Alvin! Alvin!
Alvin, take it easy out there.
You gotta share the spotlight.
You got it, Dave.
Dave?
I'm serious, Alvin.
This is a charity benefit.
It's not all about you.
Sorry, Dave, I can't hear you over the
thousands of fans screaming my name.
I'm back, Paris!
Yeah! A little help, boys.
Yeah!
Yeah, man!
Alvin, will you please get down
from there?
I can't hear you!
- Alvin, I'm not kidding!
- What?
Dave, look out!
Alvin!
Dave!
Dave?
This should help with the pain.
I wanna talk to my boys.
I just gave you a sedative that will
take effect in about one minute, so...
Well, let them in quickly.
- Dave!
- Dave, you're alive!
- Hey, guys!
- It was an accident, I swear.
- Are you okay?
- I'm really sorry, Dave.
I'll be fine. I'm just gonna be
stuck here for a while.
And until I get out,
I've made arrangements
for my Aunt Jackie
to come stay with you.
- Who's Aunt Jackie?
- The one who sends us
those metal buckets of yummy popcorn
for Christmas.
Oh, Popcorn Jackie.
You don't have much time,
monsieur Seville.
Listen, I want you guys to go home
and live a normal childhood.
I've even made arrangements
for you to go to school.
- School?
- Yes, school.
Simon, I'm putting you in charge.
- You are?
- I'm counting on you.
Dave, wait a minute. Why is he in charge?
He's counting on me.
Dave, please don't die.
He's just sleeping. He's had a sedative.
A sedative.
Excuse me.
I'm here to escort the Chipmunks home.
We're not leaving Dave.
I'm putting my paw down on this one.
You come here!
I got it. I'll fix it. Nope, made it worse.
- Please. Please go.
- Oh, this must be it.
The more stress you put
on monsieur Seville,
the longer it will take him to recover!
You are too slow for me, nurse.
- No! Don't...
- You'll never take me!
I'm not going anywhere without...
I hope for your sake he stays asleep
for the entire flight.
Maybe we should give him another shot,
just to be sure.
Any ideas on how we find Aunt Jackie?
Got it! Follow me.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Excuse me. Coming through.
Look! Aunt Jackie!
- Oh, yeah! Aunt Jackie!
- Popcorn Jackie!
- Oh, hello, dears!
- Cool wheelchair.
- Yay, we found you!
- Popcorn! Where's Simon and Theodore's?
There's plenty for everyone.
But let's have a hug first.
Get over here, you old teddy bear!
I'm not really much of a hugger.
Boys, I want you to meet someone.
This is my grandson Toby.
- Toby?
- Hi! I'm Theodore.
- Toby.
- What? What happened? What?
- The boys.
- Hey.
- Hi!
- Hey! How are you?
- I'm Toby. Nice to meet you.
- Toby's living with me
till he figures out
what he wants to do with his life.
So far, that means going
"pyu, pyu- pyu- pyu- pyu"
- with his thumbs all day.
- Well, for the record,
going "pyu- pyu- pyu- pyu- pyu"
with my thumbs right now
is keeping me in first place.
So that's important.
- Toby, get the bags.
- What bags?
- The luggage. Get the luggage.
- The... The... Right.
Yeah, let me get those. Sorry.
- Toby?
- Hit the brakes! Hit the brakes!
Abandon wheelchair!
Toby!
I'm fine. Don't worry.
I'm so sorry, Aunt Jackie. I'm so sorry!
Is she gonna be okay?
Don't worry about me.
I'll be home in no time.
- In you go.
- I wouldn't be so sure.
What? It was an accident. I swear.
Been there, done that. Several times.
I guess you'll be taking care of us now.
I'll take "Frightening Thoughts"
for $500, please, Alex.
Not a problem. I can totally do this.
I took care of my cat,
until he ran away. Well, "ran away"
is kind of strong wording.
I think he just wanted his space.
I still see him around
the neighborhood, you know.
He, like, hisses and claws at me,
but I think that's just his way
of saying we're still tight. You know.
You guys have nothing to worry
about, seriously,
'cause I'm not gonna be like Dave.
You know, Dave's gone.
Gone?
Not gone. Not gone, guys. He's...
He's not dead. He's very much alive.
He's completely coming back.
I'm just gonna be in his room,
keeping his bed warm.
I'm gonna be doing my thing,
you'll be doing your thing.
You're not even gonna know I'm there.
We're supposed to know you're there.
That's... That's the whole idea.
Yeah. Yeah! Oh, yeah. Absolutely.
Yeah, you'll know that I'm there.
I'm just saying, I'm not gonna be,
like, "I know everything"
and, "You do this, and you do that,"
like my dad.
All right! Let's do this.
Oh, boy.
Theodore, we're gonna be just fine.
The important thing is
we're all still alive.
Maybe my get well card
will help Dave get home faster.
It needs just a touch more glitter.
Yep, that should do it. Who's hungry?
- Me! Me! Me!
- Let's eat.
Simon?
It's a food ghost town in here. Alvin?
Holla! The Cheese Balls
are in the hizzouse!
* Well you can tell
by the way I use my walk
* I'm a Cheese Balls man
No time to talk
* Whether you're a brother
or whether you're a mother
* You gotta love Cheese Balls
Gotta love Cheese Balls
* Get in my belly
Cheese Balls, get in there
* Stayin' alive
Bingo! Dinner, she's a- served.
- Yay! All right!
- Hey! What're you doing in here?
- Cheese Ball?
- Dude, let's go! Come on!
Tom- bo, hey, hey,
give me a second, real quick.
Alvin, I really, really need
to focus right now
because I am one knockout away
from a heavyweight title.
Can we play as well?
You know,
I don't wanna hurt your feelings,
but I also don't wanna see
anybody get hurt,
and there are gonna be
fists of fury a- flying.
We can play Monopoly.
We play Monopoly with Dave all the time.
Do you? That sounds fun,
and we should do that sometime,
but right now I gotta get back
to floating like a butterfly
and stinging like a bee. So...
Hey, Tom- bo, you still there, buddy?
Who needs Toby, Theodore? You got us!
Yeah, who needs Toby?
Boys, right this way.
I'm gonna puke!
Do you know what Dave would say
if he were here right now?
- Alvin!
Not bad. But I think it needs to come
more from the belly.
- Alvin!
Phone. Get it together.
Be cool.
- Hello?
- Yes?
- Boys, it's me.
- Dave!
Dave? As in, "Dave"?
Well, I guess
since you answered the phone,
- you haven't burned down the house yet.
- Have a little faith, Dave.
Yeah. Mayday!
- What was that?
- Don't stress him out.
That was Aunt Jackie. Yeah.
She's making us a zesty 5- course meal.
Really? Well, can I talk to her?
- She's practicing her pole dancing.
- Pole dancing?
What happened to making dinner?
Guys, what's going on?
- Gotta go, Dave.
- Alvin, I'm not kidding.
- Feel better.
- Alvin!
Yep. Nobody does that better than him.
Toby? Toby, wake up.
Sorry.
No, that's... That's okay. What is it?
I had a nightmare.
The nightmares.
I hate the nightmares. What was it?
I dreamt we didn't have a family anymore.
Theodore.
Theodore, that couldn't happen.
No, you guys are tight.
Nothing could ever separate you.
Unless, like, an eagle swooped down
from the sky and was like, caw- caw!
- What?
- And grabbed you and...
Which... Which couldn't happen, ever.
So why would you...
Why would you ever think that
that would ever happen?
You know, 'cause the Eagles
are in Philadelphia.
No! No!
Sweet dreams.
- Toby! Toby, make it stop!
- What are you doing?
There's something wrong with the clock!
It won't shut up! I can't sleep!
That's the point. It's an alarm clock.
It helps you wake up early in the morning.
- Why would anyone wanna wake up early?
- Well, for school.
- You gotta be there by 8:00.
- In the morning?
Look, I don't like getting up this early
any more than you do.
But we are in this together, Alvin.
Sooner you get to school, sooner I get
to come home and get back to sleep.
You mean,
you don't stay with us at school?
No, no... No, I've done my time,
thank you very much.
But school is fun, right?
Fun? Well, I guess maybe it's fun- ish.
Hey, it's my cat!
Hey, remember I was telling you? Hey!
Hey! Hey, kitty. It's me. Remember?
I treated you good.
Okay, here we go.
Enjoy your first day at school.
See you around 3:00- ish.
Okay.
We got this. This'll be a walk in the park.
A chaotic and frightening
walk in the park!
Hi, I'm Theodore. Hi, I'm Theodore.
Hi, I'm Theodore.
- Watch out!
- Look out!
Hi, I'm...
Guys? Guys?
Oh, boy!
- Eagle!
- Go, Eagles!
Eagle!
That wasn't very fun- ish.
You must be our new students.
I'm Dr. Rubin, the principal.
And we're the Chipmunks.
Yes, well, that would explain
the fur and the bushy tails.
Follow me, gentlemen.
Gentlemen? Oh, us. Right.
There was a minute left and
we were down by 2. And I'm like,
"Coach, I don't care if my leg's broken.
Put me in. I can win this."
- I never get tired of this story.
- So I hobble out, barely able to stand.
Did I mention my leg was broken?
- Miss Ortega.
- Yes?
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
- Hello, guys. Welcome to homeroom.
- Good to be here.
- I hope.
- So this is a classroom.
I love the smell of zit cream
in the morning.
Hello, ladies.
- Is that the Chipmunks?
- The Chipmunks!
We love you, Alvin!
Hi, I'm Theodore. Hi, I'm Theodore.
Yes, he's Theodore, in case you missed it.
And I am Simon.
The name's Seville. Alvin Seville.
Somebody's gonna have to
knock those guys down to size.
Well, that should be pretty easy.
I mean, they're only 8 inches tall.
I had 15 cars.
I mean, that's, like, 5 more cars
than anybody really needs.
I had 7 maids.
I had courtside seats to the Lakers.
Even my maids had
courtside seats to the Lakers.
And now look at me. Look at me!
- Alvin and the Chipmunks!
- I lost everything.
Except for my dignity.
They can't take that away from me.
And it's all because of them.
Hey. Breakfast.
Now I run around hoping and praying
that I can find other animals
that can sing or dance. I mean...
Wait a second. You don't sing, do you?
Hey! Hey! That's my muffin!
Give me my muffin, you dirty rat!
I will get you, Chipmunks.
Girls, we gotta get out of here.
- I can't see.
- Not on my nose!
- That's my tail!
- Sorry.
- Move your butt!
- Okay.
Who's squishing me?
We made it. Jett Records.
Oh, my gosh. That's him. Ian Hawke.
Mr. Hawke?
That voice. I can't get it out of my head.
Hello? Mr. Hawke!
That's not in my head.
That's really happening.
- What do you want?
- We want to introduce ourselves.
That's right. I'm Brittany,
and this is my sister Eleanor.
Hello, sir. Such a pleasure to meet you.
And I'm their sister Jeanette.
Although I feel more like an Olivia,
or sometimes a...
Anyway, we're the Chipettes.
And, well, we would just be so honored
to have you represent us.
You made Alvin and the Chipmunks stars.
We wanna be stars, too.
- Yeah.
- And hang out with the Chipmunks.
Okay, now, listen, before we get
all girlie and giggly about this,
just tell me one thing.
You can sing, right?
No, no, wait. Hang on. Not here.
Why don't we take this meeting upstairs
in my penthouse office?
Sure! This is so exciting.
We're really on our way now.
Oh, my gosh. Guys, can you believe it?
My first penthouse office!
- Wow!
- Oh, boy!
Oh, my. The Hollywood sign.
Thought you might like the view.
So, ladies, tell me a little something
about yourselves.
Well, we grew up in a small town,
population 300, and...
Yeah? Really? That's fascinating. Great.
All right, impress me.
1, 2, 3.
Girls, girls, girls, girls.
Guess who just became the number one
Chipette fan in the whole dang world?
Ian Hawke, that's who.
- Yay! Nice!
- Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh!
So when can we meet the Chipmunks?
That's an excellent question.
And the excellent answer is,
I don't really represent
Alvin and the Chipmunks anymore.
- Oh, no!
- What happened?
Classic tale. Sweet and innocent
when I met them, and they had nothing.
And then I work my butt off
to make them rock stars,
and they changed.
Turned on me like bad cheese.
- No!
- That's terrible.
I know! I mean, I treated Alvin
like he was my own son, you know?
And then he just goes and spits on me.
Literally. He filled his chipmunk cheeks
with saliva and just had at it.
And don't even get me started
about Simon.
But not Theodore, right?
It's the cuddly ones
you have to watch out for.
But what are we talking about them for?
Come on! They're over.
Tired. Novelty act.
Chipmunks who can sing.
But girl chipmunks who can sing?
Fasten your seatbelts!
So, I'm on Jay- Z's yacht, right?
And I say, "Jay, where's Beyoncé?"
And he says, "She's holding a plate
full of Cheese Balls. Turn around."
And guess what? She was!
P.S., Dave left me in charge.
Staying up till 10:00 every night.
Oh, yeah!
Hey, girls, look what I can do.
You are Theodore- able.
- Thank you.
- You're so cute.
I am so sorry.
- It's cool. No harm done.
- Not yet.
Girls? Please? Private conference.
Thank you.
Listen up, rock stars.
If you talk to those girls again,
you're dead.
If you look at those girls again,
If you even think about those girls...
Are you thinking about them?
Well, I am now!
That's it. You're dead!
- Run!
- Xander! Come on!
- Back here, you dirty rats!
- Hang ten, bros!
Scatter!
Go, go! That way! Over there!
Ryan!
Hey, slowpokes! Catch me if you can!
- You're dead, fur ball.
- Not!
- It's wedgie time!
- My butt!
Oh, boy. Eagle.
- Eagle! Eagle!
- Get them!
- Bully! Bully!
- This way! This way!
Gotcha!
- Guys, wait, wait. Time out!
- It's swirlie time!
Come on, come on, guys. This is so 1980s.
Please! Please!
Oh, man! Come on.
- That's a good look for you.
- Thank you.
Can't swim. Help!
Grab on, Simon.
Thanks.
You okay?
Well, considering that you just
saved me from drowning in a toilet,
I'm pretty good.
I'll be right back.
Alvin! Alvin! We're not going
to solve anything with violence.
- It's the fatty- ratty!
- Cut it out!
This rat has serious junk in the trunk.
- Yeah, little fatty!
- Stop it!
He jiggles when I poke him.
Mommy!
Simon, does this make my butt
look smaller?
Theodore, your butt looks fine.
Those guys are just jerks.
Gentlemen.
You threatened to climb inside of him
and build a nest.
That was out of line.
I'm not even sure
that's physically possible.
I should suspend all 3 of you.
Please do.
Instead, I have a better idea.
Due to budget cutbacks,
we are in jeopardy of losing
our beloved music program.
- That's awful.
- I know.
But there is one small ray of hope.
Every year the district sponsors
a music competition.
And the winner's school receives $25,000.
If we win, we can save our program.
And you want us to perform?
'Cause I didn't think you were a fan.
Why don't you sleep on it?
Wait a minute! What is that? That's us!
- Wait.
- I look skinny.
Promise me that you won't say anything.
A principal has a certain image to uphold,
and if the faculty ever found out
about this, I could...
I just cannot believe that you're
actually sitting in my office.
I have all of your CDs.
I even went to see you last year in Denver.
That's where I got this.
It was my birthday.
And I was like, "The Chipmunks! "
So what do you say?
Will you represent our school?
Honestly, suspension still sounds
pretty good to me.
Come on, Alvin. What do you say?
1 for all and 3 for 1!
Well put, Theodore. Very well put.
Count us in.
Go, Eagles!
Eagles? Where?
The penthouse level.
Isn't that that Chihuahua?
You know, from the movie?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, it...
I mean, yeah, of course it is.
A lot of big names live here.
- I must have his autograph.
- Hey, hey, Brittany.
You wanna be a star? Act like a star.
All right?
You don't get autographs, you give them.
Right.
Hey, look, over there!
There're a couple of the Jonas Brothers.
- Where?
- I don't see them.
Here we are! Okay!
Let's scoot in to my...
What? Did I... Darn it! Darn it to heck!
- What's wrong?
- Girls, I apologize,
but I seem to have left my keys
back in my office.
What if one of you were
to shoot through that mail slot
and open it up from the inside, huh?
I'll do it.
I'm stuck!
All right, I got you. I got you.
Not so hard!
Might want to lay off the nuts.
All right, how about you, Glasses?
You're in better shape. Wanna go?
I'm not that great at things like this.
I got it!
Yes!
- Impressive!
- Nice!
- Gee willikers! Stripes!
- Snazzy!
- Circles!
- This is the best tree house ever!
- A red piano!
- Brit.
Is this a dream? Somebody pinch me.
This is way better than a tree.
I just adore a penthouse view.
Nice one, Hawke.
- Yeah? You like it?
- Do I?
- I live here.
- It's so beautiful!
Yeah.
Last time we visited Meerkat Manor,
a rival group called the Commandos
was making large inroads
into the Whiskers' territory.
Toby! I thought Alvin was messy.
This is literally disgusting.
I feel like I'm living in a dumpster.
Simon, it's Meerkat Manor.
Watch with me.
You know, you're right. You're right.
I just need to relax.
Maybe that'll ease my nerves a little.
What is this? What...
You've got to be joking.
A taco? In a blanket? Toby!
Ladies and gentlemen,
going for his turkey, it's the Tobester.
Come on, baby!
Yes!
No problem. Watch and learn, my friends.
Well, it looks like it's time
to play my second favorite game.
Hide the Broken TV from Dave.
You wanna play?
- No!
- Go easy on him, taco boy.
This day's been bad enough already.
I think I see what's going on.
You guys have been having
some problems at school?
No. Not really. Unless you consider
getting your head dumped
into a public toilet a problem.
Swirlies are the worst.
At least that's what I've heard.
Because there's no way that I could
possibly know that on a personal level.
Toby, what was school like for you?
Toby? Toby?
- Toby? Toby!
- What?
What was school like for me?
In a word, awesome.
But, you know, that's 'cause
I was, like, extremely popular.
Is that why you still live
with your grandma?
And refer to yourself as "the Tobester"?
And go "pyu- pyu- pyu" all day?
Bedtime!
Alvin?
Alvin, wake up and turn off the alarm!
Alvin! Alvin, I'm not kidding!
I'm not kidding, buddy. Turn it off!
Guys! Guys...
Boys, this isn't funny.
Hello. Humane Society? Yes. I need help.
A man is after us.
He wants to take us to a terrible place.
- School!
- Out!
- Have a heart, huh?
- Have a heart?
Dave wants you to go to school,
so you're going.
Yeah, well, don't worry about
picking us up at 3:00, Toby.
We'll get a ride. In a hearse!
Guys, guys, come on. Look, trust me.
The second day
is never as bad as the first.
Glasses! Glasses! You wouldn't hit
a guy with glasses, would you?
You're out, man!
Right in the pancreas.
- Call the nurse.
- Out! Out! You're out.
Come on, Alvin!
Remember your 5 D's!
Dodge, duck, dip, dive and dodge!
- Move!
- You're next, fur ball.
You talking to me? You talking to me?
I'm the only one here,
so you must be talking to me.
- Yeah! Got him!
- Did you see that?
Unbelievable. He caught it.
You're out, man.
And the fat lady, she's a- singing.
- Dude's got hands.
- I think they're paws, actually.
Whatever. We can definitely use him
on the team.
Hey, fur ball! How would you like
a spot on the football team?
Football?
I gotta say, you're good. I'm gonna
let you hang out with us at lunch.
- That is, if you wanna be on the team.
- Interesting proposition.
- Alvin?
- Let me get back to you on that.
This is a one- time offer.
Don't take too long to think it over.
Right! Like I would ditch my brothers
just to become the first chipmunk ever
to play on an actual varsity football team.
Fat chance!
The stadium is pandemonium!
It's 4th and goal. It's up! It's up!
And he catches it! The crowd goes crazy!
Hey!
- Me?
- Alvin! Alvin! Alvin!
Alvin, I think the super- cool jock table
is paging you.
Why would I go over there? Like I really
need to worry about being popular.
Hello? Talking chipmunk? Huh?
World- famous rock star?
Guy with his own plush doll?
Guys, I'm on pajamas!
Not to toot my own horn, but...
Come on. It's laughable.
- Just go, Alvin.
- Really? You mean it?
- Yeah.
- Thanks! I'll be right back!
- What up, dudes?
- What's up, little man?
- Welcome to the cool table.
- Yeah! Bring it.
- Yeah!
- Pound the paw.
I want it! I got it! I got it! I...
Don't got it.
- I think he's cute.
- Me, too.
Toss. And he's up!
- Thank you.
- Hey, Alvin.
Call me.
Bernie, I'm telling you,
the Chipmunks are old news.
I got the next big thing.
Singing female chipmunks.
Hello? Bernie? Hello?
God! What part of "singing female
chipmunks" don't these people...
Girls, we're going to school.
And he's up and he scores!
Hey! What up, S?
Don't hate on the high- five.
Yeah. High- five.
Look, Alvin,
I know you guys have been busy
with your sporting endeavors
and whatnot,
but I can really use your help at home.
No can do.
Ry- dawg is gonna teach me how to get
pretty girls to do my homework.
Alvin, you promised Theodore
we'd hang out.
We are watching Meerkat Manor tonight.
No pretty girls.
- Dude, I can't swing it today, bro.
- That's what you say every day, Alvin.
Need I remind you
it's your day to do the laundry?
You better listen to your daddy, Alvin.
You don't wanna get grounded.
Are you going to pick that up?
Are you going to make me?
I'm just going to elegantly show you
how it's done.
Simon...
Off the glass.
And you call yourself a jock.
My brother, he's a real jokester.
Always kidding.
Anyhoo, see you guys in class.
- Hey, that's my pudding.
- It's my pudding.
Why are you trying to embarrass me
in front of my friends?
Are you kidding me? They're the ones
you should be embarrassed by.
- Good luck with the show, guys.
- Front row seats. Can't wait.
So? What song are we gonna sing?
No pressure,
but the whole school is counting on us.
Relax. It's like Ryan says,
who's gonna beat singing chipmunks?
That Simon is dreamy!
I think Theodore was looking at me.
Yeah, I know.
But, guys, remember what Ian said?
We can't trust them.
- Wow.
- What happened?
I never thought I'd say this,
but pink is my new favorite color.
Her glasses were quite fetching.
She's like a beautiful green gumdrop.
Okay, well, if you guys wanna do this,
you have to pay attention.
Maybe this is a good time
for us to take a break.
Good call. Take 5.
- She's right. We need to focus, fellas.
- Right.
This is for my screensaver.
Cheese Balls!
Hey, you guys! Hey.
You guys ready to go?
'Cause I got a lot of important stuff
to do at home.
You must be their guardian.
That I... That I am. Yes, I am.
Hi, how are you? How are you, Dr. Rubin?
I know that because
I went to school here a few years ago.
I don't know if you remember me.
Toby Seville? Probably not.
Toby?
No way! Hi! Hey, no braces.
- Your teeth look great.
- You... I... Thank you. I appreciate...
I did. I did. I did get my braces off
'cause they were just...
Okay.
That... You know what,
I know a guy who actually...
Who works on drum heads.
So that's very good.
I'll be in the car, guys. So...
Somebody's in love.
That aside, we're going to replace
everything. Chipmunk's honor.
Yes, the old false- modesty
suck- up routine.
- Ian Hawke?
- I thought I smelled a rat.
May I help you, Mr. Hawke?
Well, I was wondering if I could help you.
I just heard about
your musical competition,
and I just skedaddled down here as quick
as I could to volunteer my girls.
Well, that's very thoughtful of you,
but I've already made up my mind.
Well, perhaps this will
change your mind. Girls?
They're with Ian?
Curtains!
1, 2...
Wow! They're good!
Good? They're astounding!
My good people of West Eastman,
you have just witnessed
the debut of the Chipettes.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you.
So?
They were splendid, but as I said before,
I have made my decision.
- Brit?
- No!
I see. You've made your decision.
I don't mean
to speak out of school, Doctor,
but in the true spirit of democracy,
which our great, wonderful country
was founded upon,
I say let the people vote.
Let them choose!
One person, one vote. I say, let us vote!
Let us vote! Let us vote!
Please, don't be a fascist granny.
Let freedom ring, Doctor.
- Let us vote!
You make a persuasive case, Mr. Hawke.
All right, here's what I'm going to do.
This Friday, each group will perform
one song in front of the student body.
- Yes!
- All right!
Whoever gets the most applause
will represent the school.
What?
- Thank you!
- Yes!
We did it!
In your face!
It is on like Donkey Kong.
The meerkats huddle together
at the end of a traumatic day
to reaffirm their family bond.
The Whiskers are gonna have to rely
on each other more than ever.
Guys, I am so happy that Ms. Ortega can
rehearse with us every day after school.
Every day?
- But Ryan and I have...
- Alvin, stop right there, okay?
We're a team. We need you.
Would you relax? We're not gonna lose.
We'll talk about this in the morning.
Not much to talk about.
I will see you at rehearsal.
- Stop hogging.
- I'm not hogging.
You might as well be rooting out
truffles in the French countryside,
because you are, in fact, hogging!
- I'm not!
- Are so!
- Not! Am not! Not! Not!
- So! So! So! So!
Forget it! I think
I'll sleep in my own bed tonight.
- Ditto for me.
- I'm so glad I'm not a meerkat!
- Really? Why is that?
- Because as cold as I am,
- I would never huddle with you!
- Good!
- You hear me? I won't huddle!
- Fine!
Toby?
Can I sleep with you?
- What?
- Dave lets me.
My brothers are fighting.
Well... I'm... Okay.
Oh, man! Dutch oven!
Not the Dutch oven!
Anything but the Dutch oven!
Must find fresh air before it's too late!
It's too late! It burns.
Mama, it burns!
Let's see. What else am I in the mood for?
How about a side order of friendly advice?
Courtesy of me.
No, thanks.
Grapes, please.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah, well,
I just wanted to warn you about Ian.
What? You should be grateful to Ian.
He did everything for you, Alvin,
and you broke his heart.
Really? How do I put this gently?
He's the devil. He doesn't have a heart.
And one of the things he did for us
was put us in a cage.
Alvin, he would never do that.
Yeah, 'cause you were there. I forgot.
- Brittany, you'd better watch out.
- I don't need advice from you.
- But...
- But nothing, Alvin.
Ian's taking us straight to the top!
Got it. Straight to the top.
- Ironic.
- Yeah, funny.
We are so going
to destroy those Chipmunks.
- I don't wanna destroy them.
- Me, neither.
I just wanna hang out with them.
All right, all right, all right. Hold...
All right, look.
You know, if you feel that way,
maybe we should just
withdraw from the contest.
- What?
- Then I'll put you in a FedEx package
and mail you back to whatever tree
you came from. Sound good?
- No.
- Okay, then.
Take it from the top. Let's go!
All right. Wait. Stop!
Short one in the green dress.
- What's your name again?
- Eleanor.
Yeah, look,
I'm losing you there, you know.
- Have you always been that short?
- I... I guess.
Well, you got to work on that. Okay?
All right, let me try something here.
Brittany. Here, come up here.
No, you two stay back.
Little further.
Oh, yeah. Now, that I like.
And it's not just because Brittany's
more of a mega, ultra superstar
than you guys.
Good, good. Okay, you know what?
Let's get a little more separation.
Brittany, stay there. Let's get a little
more separation from you guys.
Yeah, let's give her some room.
Give her some room, guys. Back.
Okay. All right, watch me now.
1, 2, 3!
Now, watch me. Watch me now.
Hello.
Toby?
What are you doing at the house?
Where's Aunt Jackie?
Dave! Hey! Hey, Dave, what's happening?
Aunt Jackie is in the hospital.
I'm a little worried.
Who's watching the boys?
I am.
So, Dave, how is Paris?
- Wait, are the boys behaving?
- Absolutely. They've been just peachy.
Toby, what's going on?
Nothing. Nothing. No, don't even...
Don't even worry about it.
You know, I know that you're
not supposed to be stressed out,
so I'm going to go right now.
But it's all good here.
Come home soon! Bye!
Toby?
Toby!
Nurse! Nurse! Get me out of here!
Help!
I don't mean to interrupt your game,
but I saw you stand up to Ryan
- when he littered. That took guts.
- Really?
And that's the type of guy
that we're looking for.
Jeremy Smith, student body president.
- How do you do? I'm...
- International recording star
- and litter monitor Simon Seville.
- Litter monitor?
Litter monitor.
It's a new position that we've created
to help raise awareness
of a pressing problem in our society.
I agree 99% plus 1. You do the math.
Well, Simon, I know this is a lot to ask,
but we're looking for a take- charge guy
to take charge
of this very rewarding position.
What do you say?
Excuse me, everybody.
Quick announcement.
I'm Simon. I'm the litter monitor.
Put your trash in the garbage can.
Peace out.
Hello, ladies! You probably weren't aware
that you dropped a wrapper
on the ground,
so we're just gonna call this one
a warning.
Carry on.
- What up, dudes?
- What up, Al?
Hey, everybody! Check it out!
The newest member of the football team.
Suiting up for our first away game.
- Ry, don't mess with me.
- I talked to coach. You're in.
Dude! That's great! Awesome!
So check it out, A- man.
We're watching the new litter monitor.
I wasn't aware
the school even had a litter monitor.
We don't. But don't tell him that.
- Are you going to pick that up?
- No.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
I guess I'm going to have to give you
a citation.
- Oh, no! I got a citation for littering!
- Oh, no!
You wanna play that game, do you?
Well, guess what?
I can play that game all day long.
- Simon!
- It's a joke, dude.
Litter is no joking matter.
No. You're the joke.
We're messing with you.
There's no such thing as a litter monitor.
- What?
- Good one, huh?
You knew about this, Alvin?
Does the word "brother" mean
anything to you?
Yes. Of course.
Yeah, well, he has some new brothers
now that he's on the football team.
You still haven't picked up that litter.
- You want me to get rid of litter?
- Yeah.
- Let's start with you.
- Hey, let... Let go. Let go!
No!
Downtown!
I'll catch up with you guys in a second.
Simon! Simon!
Simon!
Okay, I am a total jerk, I admit it.
So are we cool now?
Okay. Alvin, I am going to put this
behind us for Theodore's sake.
I know. That's why I'm giving you
the Alvin guarantee
that I will be at that
sing- off Friday night.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Why wouldn't you be there?
Because I have a...
- What?
- A...
- You have a what?
- A football game!
There! I said it! A football game!
Simon? Alvin? Is everything all right?
Theodore! Yeah, we're fine.
Just a little dumpster wrestling.
Crazy in here.
Right.
Don't worry, Theo!
Everything is going to be fine.
Alvin, do not miss that sing- off.
Don't worry, Simon. I'll be there.
I can do both.
Hey, guys, thanks so much
for helping out today.
Toys for Tots is a really cool organization.
So, everybody's getting cool points today.
- What's going on with Theodore?
- I have no idea.
Hey, Eleanor, why don't you see
if Theodore needs some help?
Well, okay.
They don't look very comfortable.
My shoes? They're not.
But Ian says
that I need to work on being taller.
Well, I think you look great
just the way you are.
You do?
Hi, you've reached Dave Seville.
Please leave a message.
Hi. Toby? This is Julie Ortega.
We talked yesterday.
Well, we kind of, sort of did.
Anyway, the reason I'm calling
is that I'm worried about Theodore.
He's been acting a little down lately.
I hope you're going to the sing- off Friday.
You know, with his dad gone, Theodore
needs all the support he can get.
So, I'll see you there.
I hope we get a chance to talk. Bye.
Okay, folks. Time to
get behind your undefeated Warriors.
The visiting Eagles are down by 5
with about 30 seconds left in the game.
- Time is running out for the Eagles.
- Go, Eagles!
Quarterback Ryan Edwards
really needs to make a move here
or this game is over.
I know they're gonna put me in.
They've gotta put me in!
Time out! Time out!
Time out, Eagles. 4th and 15
with 9 seconds remaining in the game.
Substitution, Eagles.
All right, boys. It's time for the big A.
I'm gonna crush them.
I'm bringing the pain!
- The Alvinator is in the house!
- Are you sure about this?
4th and 10, Xan.
We need to go with the secret weapon.
Trips right, Alpha left, motion on me.
Time to make history, boys.
- Ready!
- Break!
Defense!
- This ain't no dance, baby!
- I'm taking you down, Jennifer!
You're the one going down, rat face.
I'm gonna crack you like an acorn
and eat you for dinner,
with some fava beans and a nice Chianti.
Is he talking about my father?
A- 42! A- 42!
Hut!
Incoming!
- Yeah!
- Touchdown, Eagles!
Oh, yeah. Come on!
That's what I'm talking about.
Don't hate the player, hate the game.
And I love how awesome I am.
Final score, Eagles 15, Warriors 14.
What do you think about that,
suckers? Oh, yeah!
In your faces!
That's what I'm talking about.
You're like the Randy Moss of chipmunks.
Yeah! Give me an "A". Give me an "L".
Give me a "V". Give me an "I".
Give me an "N".
- What does that spell? Awesome!
- Way to go, Alvin!
- I'm the king of the world!
- Party with the MVP!
- Oh, yeah!
- Party with Alvin!
- You got that right.
- Everybody to the beach house!
Let's do it!
Alvin! Alvin!
Chipmunks! Chipmunks!
Chipettes! Chipettes!
So, look, guys, I just want you to know
that I'm here for you.
There's plenty of time.
I'm gonna go find Alvin,
everything's gonna work out.
Thanks, Toby.
Ladies and gentlemen, Dr. Rubin.
Thank you, students. Thank you.
Welcome to our exciting
sing- off competition
between the Chipmunks and the Chipettes.
Now, remember, students,
there are no winners or losers.
Yeah, remind me to tell the Chipmunks
that when we blow them off the stage.
The group that we choose today will give
our school a chance to win $25,000
to save our music department.
So, without further ado,
I give you the Chipettes!
This is it, girls. Can you believe it?
Brittany, your time to shine, baby.
Go out there and knock them dead.
Yes, sir! I can do it!
You two, I just want to let you know
not to get in Brittany's way.
Okay.
Like what you see? Call Ian Hawke.
310- 555- 5309.
Don't worry, Simon. Alvin will walk
through that door any minute now.
Alvin!
I am back!
- Girls, that's for us.
- Thank you so much.
Thank you. Thank you.
Well done, ladies. And now,
let's hear it for a group
that will rock you like a hurricane.
At least that's what
many of you students have told me.
Here they are, the Chipmunks!
Hey, you know they say there's no "I"
in the word "team," and they're right.
But you know what there is an "I" in?
"Alvin."
Sucks to be you. Girls!
Sadly, he's correct.
- Did you find him?
- Guys.
Sorry, I searched the whole perimeter.
And I don't know why,
but the team's not back yet.
Well, what should we do?
I would...
I would ask someone who's not me.
I know what we should do.
Chipmunks! Chipmunks!
Hi, everyone.
Our brother Alvin couldn't be here today.
The thing is,
we've never performed without Alvin.
And we're not starting now.
You can't have only 2 little pigs.
You can't have only 2 musketeers.
So, you know you can't
have only 2 Chipmunks.
Thank you.
I'll take you home.
Hear that, girls?
That is the sound of success.
I realize how devastated
you Chipmunk fans must be.
So, I guess that means that the Chipettes
- will be representing West Eastman...
- Come on, girls.
Let's take a victory lap.
Hey, come on, guys. Let's go.
- Brit, we have to.
- Let's go.
Yeah! Let them know!
Thank you. Thanks.
Life is good.
Especially when you're not a loser.
Hey, guys! I'm here!
Guys?
Great.
They're gone, Alvin.
They're never gonna forgive me.
You know, Alvin, Ian was right.
You don't care about anyone but yourself.
And by the way,
I never wanted to win this way.
Simon? Theodore?
Simon, are you awake?
Theo?
Theo!
Theodore? Theodore?
Theodore, I don't blame you
for being mad...
"I ran away from home.
"Don't look for me at the zoo,
'cause I'm not there."
Oh, no, Theodore.
Hello? Meerkat family?
Oh, brother.
Is anyone home?
My name is Theodore.
I'd like to be in your family.
Maybe they're hiding.
Don't be afraid!
You are not a meerkat.
Toby, you take the lions,
the tigers and the bears.
Simon and I will take the butterfly room.
Nice eagle.
- Theo!
- Don't move, Theodore!
No problem there.
Hang in there! Hang in there, little guy!
We're gonna get you out of there!
Okay, okay, we need a plan.
We need a carefully executed plan.
Or you could just run in there
like a maniac.
- Theo, watch out!
- Hi, I'm Theodore.
Hey, birdie! Over here! Are you hungry?
'Cause this "A" stands for "appetizer"!
Let's all just relax
and we'll talk this out. Okay?
Look, I get why you want Theodore. I do.
But, I'm sorry, I can't let that happen.
He's my brother. Not that he'd know that,
because I've been such a big jerk lately.
If anyone deserves to be eaten, it's me.
Not literally!
I got you, Alvin!
Move it!
- Theo.
- Help!
Guys, it's a wedge- tail eagle.
Their only mortal enemy
is the pygmy elephant.
Luckily, I speak a little pachyderm.
I think it's working!
Or not!
Guys, that was huge.
He's right.
So, are we back to 1 for all
and 3 for 1?
Come on, Simon. Hug it out.
You know I'm sorry, Si.
Si? Don't make me have to kiss you!
Because I'll do it. I don't care.
Here come the lips.
Make- out train is leaving the station.
- Think I'll take that hug.
- Guys.
Interested? Call Ian Hawke.
310- 555- 5309.
Deloris, get me that
Ian Hawke on the phone.
- There you are...
- Hi.
my sweet little moneymakers.
Do you remember when I told you
that I would make you all big stars?
- Yeah.
- Well,
guess who's opening up for Britney
Spears at the Staples Center tonight?
- Yeah!
- Pinch me. Am I dreaming? Oh, my gosh.
Wait, tonight?
We'll miss the school contest.
That is correct.
You will miss the school contest.
You're so smart.
I can never get anything past you.
It was never about
that stupid school contest.
It was always about
making Brittany a star.
That's what you wanted, right?
- Well, yeah.
- Well, tonight's your big chance.
It's all about you, Brittany.
What about Jeanette and Eleanor?
Yeah, well, they can sing backup.
I got them some stuff, too.
Hey!
But we're her sisters.
And the 3 of us sing together
or not at all.
Okay, fine. All I really need is the B- girl.
Ian, I won't do it without them.
Okay. Fine, fine. Let's move on to plan B.
- Okay! Who likes barbecue?
- Barbecue?
Because I know this awesome little
barbecue restaurant in the Valley
that makes the best roasted chipmunk.
Real tasty.
Unless, of course, you wanna sing.
Welcome to West Eastman, and thank you
for supporting music in our schools.
Now, remember,
the group you pick tonight
will win $25,000 for their school!
Now, we've got a lot of acts,
and we have to turn the heat off at 9:30,
so without any further ado,
representing Orange Grove,
put your hands together for Li'l Rosero!
So, we meet again.
What? You want a piece of this, eagle?
- Ian Hawke?
- I'll take that.
I didn't realize
I pocket- dialed 1- 800- LOWLIFE.
- Alvin?
- Brittany?
Yeah, could you guys fill in for us?
We're not gonna be able
to perform tonight.
What about the music department?
The whole school is counting on you.
I know. I know.
I should have listened to you about Ian.
- Don't tell me!
- Yep. He locked us in a cage.
What? This is the biggest you have?
I had my assistant call
and ask for the biggest limo.
This is not the biggest limo you have.
I'll go break the news to Dr. Rubin.
- Brittany?
- Alvin, don't move!
You got it!
Brittany, I'm coming to get you.
Simon, tell Jeanette how to pick the lock.
Roger that!
Oh, man. I need to get to the girls, fast!
I know how!
Jeanette, focus. The 3rd number is
notoriously the hardest to crack.
I'm assuming it's a prime number,
but we can't assume...
Simon! The first 2 numbers were ones.
I got to go with one.
- It opened!
- All right, girls.
Ian's coming.
Put the phone back. Hurry!
- Get ready to be fabulous.
- We're ready.
Yeah, you better be.
Because tonight's performance is
going to put me back on top.
Next up, please welcome Charice!
Driver- man, take me to the arena.
VIP entrance.
How about a little moon roof action?
Moon roofs are go!
Rooves? Moon roof.
Roofs? Rooves?
Champagne. Don't mind if I do.
You know why I don't mind if I do?
Because tonight, we've got to toast
to a very special someone
named me.
They said I couldn't do it.
They said I'd never bounce back.
Guess what? Time to kiss my sweet...
Oh, yeah.
A toast to the ladies who're gonna make
the world forget about the Chip...
- What...
- See you!
No. No, no, no! No!
What are you doing? Alvin!
Hi, Ian! Good to see you!
You never write!
- No! Brittany... No!
- Come on, girls!
I signed a contract!
- Jump, Jeanette!
- Wait!
- I'm not really good at...
- I got you.
I'm dead if you don't perform!
- Punch it, Alvin!
- You got it!
- No! Don't!
- Hey, Ian!
In the words of the Donald,
"You're fired! "
Alvin!
Hey! Hey. Hey, guys.
Any sign of Alvin yet? Huh?
No. No Alvin, and no Chipettes.
Just Dr. Rubin and, you know,
the entire school counting on us.
Well... Yeah, you know, don't worry.
Everything will work out- ish.
- Faster, Alvin!
- Don't worry.
I'm gonna get a little help
from my friend Digger!
- Roger that, Alvin!
- Look out!
Feels like I'm back at the race track.
- Hey! Careful!
- Keep going! What are you doing?
Yeah.
Wait till I tell everybody back home
I saved Alvin Seville.
I guess I owe you an apology about Ian.
Stick with me, Brit.
I'll never steer you wrong.
Oh, yeah. I'll never doubt you again.
I gotta say, he is definitely persistent.
- We have got to lose him.
- Hang on!
I've got a plan.
Jump on the count of 3.
3!
That's it.
I'm not really good with heights.
Just hang on tight, Jeanette.
Bring my girls right to me.
- We need the remote.
- Guys, I know what to do.
It's hats off to Ian.
The remote!
I can't reach it!
I'm going for it. Grab my ankles.
I got it!
I got it.
- Way to go, Jen!
- Nice work, Jeanette!
Good going, Jen! Hey, Ian,
you were wrong. I don't need these!
- My bad!
- Adiós, Ian!
And now for our final act of the night.
Now, listen, we've had
a last- second change to the line- up,
but we don't think
you're gonna be too disappointed.
Representing West Eastman,
it's the Chipmunks!
We may have to go out there, Theodore.
Chipmunks! Chipmunks!
Chipmunks!
Well, if there are no Chipmunks,
we're gonna have to move on. So now...
I don't wanna be booed again.
I'm sorry. We're gonna have to move on.
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! I...
I'm not a Chipmunk, as you can see.
Play some music, you loser!
- Play some music!
- Yeah!
- More music!
- Play some music!
Okay, okay.
Okay, okay, I got a song.
I got a song, I got a song.
* Ever since I met you
* I wanted to be your guy
* But as you've probably noticed
* I'm pathologically shy
* And standing on this stage right now
I think I'd rather die
* So I'm just gonna start by saying
Hi
Hi.
Now, that was huge.
Thank you. Thank you.
No, really. Thank you.
- What the...
- The Chipettes are in the building!
- It's the Chipettes!
- Alvin!
- Theo!
- Hello, West Eastman!
I'm putting her down! Hang on!
- Alvin!
- Double high- five, brother.
High- five!
Ladies and gentlemen,
representing West Eastman,
it is my great pleasure...
This is such an honor.
For you or for us?
- For us.
Jinx! Double- jinx! Triple- jinx!
Quadruple- jinx! Infinity- jinx!
Guys! We get it.
- Huddle up, gang.
- Okay, here's the plan.
I give you the Chipettes
and the Chipmunks!
- Dave!
- Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Hey, everybody. It's clear
that we have a winner of the $25,000!
And it's West Eastman High!
West Eastman High!
- Guys, we did it!
- Yeah!
- Wow!
- Can you believe it?
A little something
for the music department.
All right!
Right back at you, Dr. Rubes!
Oh, yeah!
- Chipettes! Chipettes!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Staples Center is proud
to welcome the Chipettes!
Hi, everyone.
I'm Jeanette. And I'm Eleanor.
And I'm Brittany!
And we're the Chipettes!
- What?
- What is that?
1, 2, 3.
That's not the Chipettes!
- Come on, lady.
- I know, I know. All right, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I know, I'm sorry!
I'm going!
- Dave! You're dancing!
- You're moving good, Dave!
- Yeah!
- Welcome home.
So, did you miss us?
- Of course I missed you. You're my boys.
- Cool!
And, Dave, just think how much
you'd miss us if there were 6 of us.
Alvin, what did you say?
Well, the Chipettes needed
a place to crash, right?
So, I said that you said
they could stay with us
for as long as they needed to.
- Alvin!
- Okay! This one's for Dave.
Everybody,
shake what your mamma gave you!
Subtitles: Arigon
Look at you. All ready for bed.
Looks like the Chipettes
are a good influence.
- Thanks, Dave.
Thanks, Dave.
Okay, guys. Now lights out.
Good night, everybody.
- Good night, Jeanette.
- Good night, Simon.
Good night, Dave. Good night, Alvin.
- Alvin?
- I'm not tired.
Sorry, but you've got school tomorrow.
Not tired.
Alvin, come on. It's time for bed.
- Not tired.
- Alvin?
Still not tired. More awake. Tired.
- Just kidding. Much more awake.
- Alvin, that's it.
- Don't make me come over there.
- Okay.
Boy! I suddenly got really, really tired.
Night, Dave.
Alvin!
Good start, gentlemen. Only 10 more
rows of bleachers to go. Let's do it.
All right, guys.
All right. All right.
All right, I'm out. I'm out.
Is this necessary?
Come on. Is that necessary?
Is that...
At least let me go back and get my purse.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org