Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
[MAN LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
SHELBY:
God.
How long have I been out?
About an hour.
Where are we?
ROB:
We just crossed the state line.
- Really?
- Mm-hm.
Already?
Mm. Why do I smell food?
ROB: There should be a girlie toy
in there for you.
SHELBY: Thanks, sweetie.
- Yeah.
Jesus, Rob, slow down.
You're driving over a hundred.
- I've got a really good convoy going here.
- No.
Just slow down. Now.
Thank you.
Look...
...okay, I know we had a shitty weekend.
I wanna get home too.
But let's just do it safely, okay?
No more bad luck.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Oh, I got the spot.
"I love you too, Shelby."
I love you too.
I do.
I'm wide awake so get some sleep.
- Okay. Thank you, sweetie.
ROB: Mm-hm.
[TRUCK HORN BLARING]
Ah. Bingo.
- Hey, you knocked out another hour.
- Ugh.
I only feel more tired.
Are you tired yet?
Nope.
I cannot believe you started another one.
I didn't.
- This one found me.
- Oh, whatever.
Look at the speedometer.
It's like 12 miles over the speed limit.
The other one, you were right.
It was too fast and unsafe.
- This one isn't.
- Oh, please.
Seriously, there's like an art
to a good convoy, babe.
It's like a conversation between us
and the cars as we drive. We communicate.
No, did you see that? That's him warning
me that there's some slow cars up ahead...
...so we're gonna have to pass them.
Oh, that's pretty considerate.
Oh, see, now this is what I like to call
a brake pumper.
You think speeding's dangerous,
try driving behind this guy.
Okay.
At this speed, I'm fine with it.
Just don't go faster.
ROB:
Oh, right on.
I was wondering
when they were gonna need to fuel up next.
Well, what do we do?
Are we supposed to introduce ourselves,
say hi?
I don't know.
I mean, I've never actually met anyone
I've been in a convoy with.
[TRUCK ENGINE DOWNSHIFTING]
[TRUCK BRAKES HISS]
BERT: Sure am glad we all had to stop.
Hey, I'm Bert.
- Rob.
- Hi.
- Oh, nice.
You a Robert?
Or a Roberto? Ha, ha.
No, I'm just kidding. Ha.
[SIGHS]
- Hello. So where you headed there, Rob?
ROB: Uh, Cincinnati.
BERT:
Oh, you're kidding.
It'll be nice
to have some steady company.
- Yeah, you bet. Yeah.
BERT: Yeah.
[CHUCKLES]
Okay. Uh, well...
...see you inside.
- Sure. Yeah.
- Kids want their chocolates.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
All right.
[CHUCKLES]
[CASH REGISTER DINGS]
Uh-oh. Looks like someone
got the munchies.
Ha, ha, ha. Yeah.
No, I'm just messing with you. Anyway,
uh, I was talking to this trucker inside.
Not very chatty guy.
Anyway, he said he got on
his, uh, radio-thingy.
Said the interstate up ahead's
pretty wall-to-wall.
ROB: Mm. Really?
- Hey?
Trucker on my CB says
it ain't moving worth a damn out there.
Told me a way around it, though, so...
...you're more than welcome
to swing on in behind me.
Come on. I could use the company.
Road's a Ionely place
when you're traveling solo.
Yeah, you got it, man. Hey, thanks.
No problem.
[SIGN BUZZING]
[TRUCK BEEPING]
What'd you talk about?
Oh, the interstate's jammed up ahead
so we're gonna go around.
- Yeah, and Mr. Lonesome up front there...
SHELBY: Uh, he's not alone.
Yeah, he is. That's what he said.
Rob, he's not alone.
There's a girl with him. I saw her.
Misunderstanding then.
It's no big deal.
You sure we should be doing this?
Would you rather turn around
and crawl up the interstate?
It's like a parking lot.
SHELBY:
No.
Guess we're fine.
Great.
It's the sticks, Shelby.
People hunt out in the sticks.
There, see? Did you see that?
- What?
- In the window. Get closer.
There is someone in there.
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
SHELBY:
Hello? Hello?
- Can you hear me?
- What the hell?
You get his plates.
You get his license plates.
- Shelby, come on.
- No, just go! Get his plates now! Go!
- Just hurry up!
- Okay.
SHELBY:
Okay.
BERT: Is she okay? Is she alive?
SHELBY: Yeah.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[LOOSE GRAVEL RUSTLING]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[WOMAN COUGHING]
- Get her up.
- There she is. There she is.
Okay, she's back with us.
SHELBY: Lift her up.
- You keep her coherent. I'll be right back.
WOMAN: Keep him away from me.
- Oh, I will. It's okay.
He threw you from the truck,
but he took off. You'll be fine.
No, I jumped.
What?
[CRASHING]
[CAR ENGINE HISSING]
[GRUNTING]
Shelby!
Are you okay?
What happened?
He... He...
He came back.
I know. I know.
Where's my girlfriend?
He took them.
He took both of them.
Both that lady and your girl.
What?
BERT:
He took off over there.
Lift me up.
- Help me up.
ROB: Yeah. Okay. Okay, come on.
[PARKING BRAKE ENGAGES]
BERT:
Wait, wait. Yeah, okay, all right.
- You let me go.
- You're hurt. I'll go.
Shhh. Just please promise me...
...you take care of my family
if something happens, okay?
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
[CAR DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
TRYTON:
I don't know where I am.
No, no, I was taking her to rehab.
Don't know. Accident.
Maybe she jumped.
I don't know
because the bitch was crazy.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
[WOMAN WHIMPERING]
[GRUNTING]
[WHIMPERS]
BERT:
Sorry.
[CHUCKLES MANIACALLY]
[MUFFLED]
Rob. Rob!
Hold on, Shelby.
[BERT LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
[SHELBY SCREAMING]
[SHELBY BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DOOR HANDLE CLACKING]
[SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY]
[LAUGHS MANICALLY]
You picked the wrong convoy, buddy.
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
TABITHA:
Hello?
[INDISTINCT TV CHATTER]
- Hi, Tabby.
- Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
DANNY:
Huh.
TABITHA: Hello?
- Smoking.
[TABITHA GRUNTING]
- Hey, Maxie.
- Hi.
Danny, where's the babysitter?
- She left already.
- Yeah, she lefted.
What?
Are you sure?
[BANGING]
TABITHA:
Hello?
I'm here.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
[SOFA CUSHIONS SQUEAKING]
Hello, it's Tabitha, the Carmines' niece.
[MANIACAL CHUCKLING]
[SIGHS]
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[HANDS SLAP LEGS]
[SIGHS]
[DOOR CREAKS SHUT]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Okay.
[SIGHS]
What's next?
"Quiet time."
[BANGING UPSTAIRS]
Boys, you're supposed to be quiet.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
Hello?
MAN:
Yes, hi. I'm here for June.
June? There's no June here.
MAN: Oh, well, no, she's been sitting
over here today.
I dropped her off earlier.
She missed cheerleading practice,
I'm getting worried.
I'm her boyfriend, Owen.
I'm the Carmines' niece
and when I got here, she had already left.
OWEN:
Just left the children alone?
OWEN: You haven't heard from her since?
- I haven't heard from her.
I didn't even see her.
OWEN: Oh, it's... It's just not...
It's not like her to not call me.
Maybe she just went to a friend's house.
With the storm and all.
OWEN: Yeah, l... I guess so.
I just...
Be sure...
...to tell her that I stopped by
if you see her.
I will.
[THUNDER CRASHING]
[DISHES CLINKING]
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
[LOCKS CLICKING]
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
[THUNDER CRACKS]
And what are his special powers?
Um...
Um, he can... He flies.
Swoosh, swoosh.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And shoots fire from his hands.
[TO Y REVS]
[FARTING]
[BO YS GIGGLING]
I tooted.
[ALL GIGGLING]
Excuse me.
[INDISTINCT NOISES OUTSIDE ROOM]
[BO YS MIMIC SHOOTING SOUNDS]
[BO YS CHUCKLE]
Okay, men, time to hit the hay.
DANNY:
Aww.
Okay, good night, love bug.
Sleep tight.
- Good night.
MAX: Night, Tabby.
No, no, no, leave it cracked.
TABITHA:
Okay. Shhh.
Just go to sleep.
[SIGHS]
[BANGING]
[CREAKING]
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[UNBUCKLES BELT]
[BANGS]
[TV STATIC]
You've gotta be kidding me.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
[EXHALES]
[SIGHS]
[PHONE RINGING]
- Hello?
GRACE: Tabitha? It's Aunt Grace.
- Sorry to be calling so late, but you know.
- Yeah, no, no. It's okay.
GRACE:
Oh, I didn't wake you?
No. No.
GRACE: I just wanted to check
on the little ones. How are they?
TABITHA: They're fine. Perfect angels.
They went to bed no problem.
GRACE:
Okay, good.
[TABITHA EXHALES SHARPLY]
TABITHA:
Listen, um...
...I love your new house
but the clown in my room...
No offense, but I hate it.
GRACE:
Oh, God, which one now?
The big one.
GRACE:
Which one?
You know, the really big one.
GRACE:
I'm not sure which one you mean.
TABITHA: The one that sits in the chair.
You know, it's life-size.
The really, really big one.
You have him propped up
in that rocking chair.
GRACE:
Tabby, what...? What are you talking about?
TABITHA: In the guest bedroom,
with all the other clowns.
The one bigger than me.
GRACE:
We... We don't own anything like that.
TABITHA:
Yeah, you do.
I'm looking right at it.
GRACE:
Tabitha.
Tabitha, are you there?
Tabitha!
[ROCKING]
[DOOR KNOB RATTLING]
[BREATHING SHARPLY]
TABITHA:
Boys.
Wake up.
Boys?
Where are you?
[BANGING]
[TABITHA BREATHING SHARPLY]
What's wrong, Tabby?
Don't be scared.
TABITHA:
Boys, listen to me, we have to hide.
There's a bad man,
a very bad man in the house.
He just wants to play.
Like earlier at the door.
That was him?
[CHUCKLES]
Owen.
TABITHA:
No, don't!
But, Tabby, he said he just wanted
to have some fun.
[SCREAMING]
BO YS:
Help!
[CLOWN LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
TABITHA:
Get going.
Come on.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[BANGING]
Hurry up, hurry up.
[WHIMPERS]
[GRUNTING]
[TABITHA BREATHING SHARPLY]
TABITHA:
Boys, run. Get help.
Run.
[CLOWN GRO ANING]
TABITHA:
Ah... No!
[CLOWN GRUNTING]
TABITHA:
No!
[COUGHING]
[BREATHING SHARPLY]
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
[TABITHA GASPING]
[GRUNTS]
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
[PANTING]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[CRASHING]
[TABITHA SCREAMING]
[CLOWN LAUGHING MANICALLY]
[SCREAMING]
COP: Miss Wright, do you know anybody
who would want to hurt you?
This whole thing is gonna work out
a lot smoother...
...if you just cooperate with us, okay?
Do you remember anything about the man
who attacked you?
[DOOR BUZZES]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[MANIACAL LAUGHTER]
[CHILDREN CHUCKLING]
CHILD TABITHA [VOICE-O VER]:
Let me see, let me see.
CHILD LAUGH:
Let me look at yours first.
CHILD TABITHA:
Okay, here.
[CHILDREN CHATTERING]
CHILD LAUGH:
Tabitha, this is boring.
CHILD TABITHA:
No, it's not. Yours is boring.
CHILD LAUGH:
Mine is better than this.
You'll see.
CHILD TABITHA:
Now let me look in yours.
Not till I see all of yours first.
CHILD LAUGH [VOICE-O VER]:
Um, Shelby.
CHILD LAUGH:
Shelby, yours is worse than Tabitha's.
CHILD SHELBY:
No, it isn't.
CHILD LAUGH:
Lisa.
CHILD LAUGH: Now, what's that?
CHILD LISA: It's a sleepover.
CHILD TABITHA:
Now let us see yours.
CHILD LAUGH:
Okay. One at a time and I have to hold it.
[CHILDREN CHUCKLING]
[CHILD LAUGH CHUCKLES]
It's funny, right?
No.
It isn't.
[CHILD LAUGH CHUCKLING]
CHILD LISA [VOICE-O VER]:
Shelby.
Let's go. Hurry.
[CHILD LAUGH CHUCKLING]
[SHRIEKS]
[MANIACAL LAUGHTER]
[DOOR BUZZES]
Hello, Tabitha.
I'm an on-site trauma counselor
for the state...
...and I'd just like to ask you
a few questions.
All right?
I realize you're in a serious
state of shock...
...so we'll just go at your own pace,
okay?
Do you know a Lisa Swan?
[CHATTERING]
LISA: I'm telling you, dude.
CAT: Stop it.
Don't make me laugh when I'm applying.
You're drunk, Miss Swan.
And you're celibate. Take off
the chastity belt and go home with him.
No.
It's Roommate Night.
Besides, he just moved into town
and he's staying at the Pere's Pension.
- That dump by the park?
- Yeah. But it's temporary.
Be nice.
[CHATTERING]
Mm.
At least let him drive you home.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
You're right.
- So I'll see you at home in 30, okay?
- Mm-hm.
[LISA EXHALES SHARPLY]
Okay. Okay, stop.
You know I want to
but it's Roommate Night.
And she lives for this shit.
You had to live
with the consummate good girl.
- I know. I'll make it up to you. I promise.
- Yeah.
Bye.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hey, Cat.
Let's get this night going.
Cat?
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
LISA:
Mm.
DAN [ON PHONE]: Hey.
- Hey, baby, it's me.
You can turn back around.
DAN: You're kidding me.
It's Roommate Night.
No, she's not here.
I guess she got lucky.
DAN: Good for Cat.
It had to happen sometime, right?
- I'll see you soon.
DAN: I'll be there.
Bye.
[PHONE CLICKS]
[BED SQUEAKS]
LISA:
It's after 4:00.
She never does this.
She never goes home with a guy
unless she's dated him for a month at least.
Maybe she did.
No.
I mean, we're talking about Cat.
Come on, you know her.
LISA: No, I'm just gonna run over there
real quick.
- Over where?
- The Pere's Pension.
DAN:
Oh, come on, Lise.
You're overreacting.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[GATE CREAKS]
[BELL CLANGS]
LISA: Hi, I was wondering if I could...
MAN: Sorry. All the beds are full.
LISA:
But...
[PEEPHOLE CREAKS OPEN]
Now, don't you find it strange
that for a full hotel...
...we haven't seen one person come or go
in over two hours?
Yeah. But, I mean, we're not even sure
that Cat went anywhere near that place.
She's my best friend.
She doesn't do anything without telling me.
And the last person that saw her
is staying there.
I mean, come on, Dan, she hasn't called
all day. That never happens.
Can't you just use your badge?
Lise, I work for the Health Department,
okay? Not the police.
My badge is useless.
Look at that place.
I mean, can't you make something up
just to get in there and see?
Just to see if she's in there.
[BELL CLANGS]
DAN:
Hi there.
MAN:
I'm sorry, I can't help you.
All of our beds are full tonight.
DAN: That's all right, sir. I'm actually...
I'm from the Health Department.
Just need a moment.
[KEYS RATTLING]
[EXHALES]
[DOOR LOCKING]
[DOOR SQUEAKS]
MAN:
How may I help you?
Well, the neighbors were complaining.
Uh, seems they're getting
some vermin from here.
We just wanted to let you know
before a formal complaint was made.
- The neighbors, huh?
- Yeah.
That's interesting.
Hm.
Like I said, it's nothing serious as of yet.
Sir, will you pardon me for a moment?
- Yeah.
- You can go ahead...
...and wait in the gaming room.
[DAN EXHALES SHARPLY]
MAN:
It's a metal scope Victrola.
Oh.
It's very old.
And priceless.
What's it do?
What does it do?
Well, it plays a song.
And at the end, you get a surprise.
[DAN EXHALES SHARPLY]
Well, go on. Try it.
Oh, no, no. That's okay.
Try it.
Okay.
[CREEPY MUSIC PLAYING]
Where did you find this thing?
Well, I come from a long line...
...of entertainers and performers.
You know, lovers of the laugh.
[GRUNTS]
[CRASHING]
[MAN LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
[OWL HOOTING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[CELL PHONE DIALING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
DAN [ON VOICEMAIL RECORDING]:
Hey, this is Dan. Leave me a message.
[VOICEMAIL BEEPS]
Dan, why aren't you answering?
It's me again.
Please call me back.
I'm panicking here, okay?
Where are you?
[CELL PHONE CLICKS SHUT]
[BOTTLE CLATTERS]
[LISA BREATHES SHARPLY]
[DOOR OPENS]
[LISA INHALES SHARPLY]
[BROKEN GLASS CLATTERS]
[BROKEN GLASS CRUNCHES]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[PANTING]
LISA:
Excuse me.
Can you help me?
[LISA BREATHES SHARPLY]
Please...
Um...
[MAN MUTTERING]
L... l... I need to find someone.
He came in here a while ago.
[WHIMPERING]
Please, uh...
Oh, um...
[GIBBERING]
Um, I need to find someone in here.
GUEST:
I'm sorry.
I need read lips.
Okay, good. Good.
Um...
I need...
...to find someone.
- Okay.
Um, a man. My friend...
...uh, came here hours ago.
Did you see anyone?
No one come in here.
[SIGHS]
Okay. Um...
Another friend...
...a girl, came here last night.
Did you see a girl?
I mean, where is everyone?
[GIBBERING]
[DISTANT SCREAMING]
Um, okay, there's a man, an angry man.
He don't let us leave.
LISA:
Um...
[LISA BREATHING HEAVILY]
GUEST:
No. No, no.
You hide. You hide.
- What?
- Hide in here.
- Where do l...? Hide?
- He come very soon.
- You mean hide?
- Hide. He come very soon.
He come very soon.
[GUEST WHIMPERING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[PHONE BEEPS]
[LISA BREATHES SHARPLY]
[SCREAMING]
[MUFFLED WHIMPERING]
CAT [MUFFLED]:
Lisa.
[CAT SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[CRYING]
[LISA SCREAMS]
[WHIMPERING]
Please help me.
Please, my friend. My friend.
She's alive in here.
CAT [MUFFLED]:
No. No.
CAT: No!
LISA: Cat!
LISA: Oh, God, Cat.
CAT: No, no...
LISA: Cat, it'll be okay!
CAT: He's not...
LISA: Please, help me get her out. Please.
[CAT CRYING]
[MUFFLED]
He's not... He's...
He's...
[GUEST HUMMING GIBBERISH]
[CAT SCREAMING AND CRYING MUFFLED]
CAT [MUFFLED AND CRYING]:
He's...
[CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[SCREAMING]
[LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
PSYCHIATRIST:
So you did know Lisa Swan.
But you don't know Rob Ellerbe?
Maybe you know his girlfriend...
...Shelby Leds.
Shelby?
What's Shelby got to do with this?
You tell me.
Shelby and Lisa and I,
we were inseparable.
But I haven't seen them in years.
Not since we were kids in Briar Hills.
Briar Hills.
That's a subdivision of Columbus,
isn't it?
How did you know?
Um...
[CELL PHONE CLICKS OPEN]
[SIGHS]
[CELL PHONE CLICKS SHUT]
Miss, you need to stay here.
How did you know about Briar Hills?
I had a patient.
A boy.
Years ago.
One of my first asylum cases.
He was from Briar Hills.
I've never met anyone who...
He had the most distinctive laugh.
TABITHA:
Where...? Where are you going?
I just need to find a phone that works.
Don't worry, I'll be back for you
and your friends.
[DOOR BUZZES]
They're here?
Shelby and Lisa?
Yeah.
The three of you were found
in separate cells in this building.
[PSYCHIATRIST INHALES SHARPLY]
A call went out for a trauma couns...
Oh, God!
No, no, don't leave me here.
Don't leave me here!
[DOOR CLOSES]
[DOOR BUZZES]
[DOOR SQUEAKS OPEN]
[DOOR CREAKS]
Shelby?
Lisa?
[WATER DRIPPING]
[LIGHT BUZZES]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Thank God.
Here!
I'm over here.
[MAN CHUCKLING]
[LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
TABITHA:
No!
[TABITHA CRYING]
TABITHA:
No!
[GRUNTS]
[TABITHA WHIMPERS]
[DOOR SLAMS AND LOCKS]
[TABITHA SCREAMS]
[LAUGHS MANICALLY]
[TABITHA CRYING]
Na, ha.
[TABITHA WHIMPERS]
[GRUNTS]
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[DOOR LOCKS]
[TABITHA CRIES]
[MAN LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[DOORS SLAM SHUT]
[TABITHA CRIES]
[TABITHA EXHALES SHARPLY]
[CREEPY MUSIC PLAYING]
[METAL CREAKING]
[CRIES]
[WHIMPERS]
[GRUNTS]
[CRYING]
No!
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[EXHALES]
[SIGHS]
TABITHA:
Shelby?
What's he done to you?
Lisa?
[BREATHING SHARPLY]
Let me out of here!
Let me out!
[DOOR OPENS]
[METAL CLANKING]
[MUFFLED WHIMPERING]
[METAL CLINKING]
[WHIMPERING]
[DOOR OPENS]
No, not...
No. Don't touch me.
[CRANKING]
[WHIMPERS]
[CRYING]
Get away from her.
It's funny, right?
TABITHA:
No! No!
[WHIMPERS]
Mm.
[CHUCKLING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
[TABITHA EXHALES SHARPLY]
[CHUCKLES]
[TABITHA SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
[LISA GRUNTING]
[LISA CRYING]
It's okay. We're gonna get you out.
It's okay. Hurry!
Close your eyes.
LISA: Please get me...
Please get me out. Please.
- It's okay.
SHELBY: It's okay. It's okay.
LISA: Hurry, please.
SHELBY: We got you. Just stay still.
SHELBY:
Stay still, we'll be here, okay?
[LISA WHIMPERING]
SHELBY:
Now, get them off.
You got it. You got it. Okay, you're free.
LISA:
Okay, we have to go!
[GRUNTING]
[LISA SCREAMS]
[LISA MO ANS]
SHELBY:
Come on!
Go! Come on!
Climb! Fast!
Go!
[GRUNTING]
SHELBY:
Tabitha! Go!
[THE LAUGH GRUNTING]
He's coming!
Tabitha, help me!
[GRUNTING]
Oh, no! No!
No!
[SHELBY SCREAMING]
[BOD Y THUMPS]
[EXHALES]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[GRUNTS]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[PANTING]
[CRYING]
[MACHINE TURNS ON]
[TABITHA INHALES SHARPLY]
[TABITHA CRIES]
[WINDOW CAGE RATTLES]
[TABITHA SCREAMING]
[TABITHA PANTING]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[BANGING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
No!
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[TRUCK ENGINE STARTS]
[THE LAUGH LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[TABITHA WHIMPERS]
[BANGING]
TABITHA:
Let me out!
Let me out of here!
[TABITHA PANTING]
[TRUCK ENGINE REVVING]
TABITHA:
Please let me out!
[TRUCK ENGINE BACKFIRES]
[TRUCK ENGINE STALLS]
[TRUCK ENGINE TURNS O VER]
[TRUCK CABIN DOOR OPENS]
[BANGING]
[TABITHA INHALES SHARPLY]
[TRUCK ENGINE TURNS O VER]
[ENGINE STALLS]
[ENGINE TURNS O VER]
[ENGINE SPUTTERS AND STARTS]
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[GRUNTS]
Now, that was funny.
[CHOKING]
[THUMPS]
TABITHA: For Shelby, Lisa and I,
he was a joke that crossed the line.
We made fun of him.
And after he was sent away...
... we forgot him.
But he never forgot us.
Even though I was the one to survive...
... my life will never be the same.
I can't bring Lisa or Shelby back...
... and I can't get his laughter
out of my head.
[THE LAUGH LAUGHS MANIACALLY
IN VOICE-O VER]
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org