Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
1957 was a big year.
The Russians put that Sputnik
into outer space.
The Dodgers played their last game
at Ebbets Field...
...and said goodbye to Brooklyn.
That guy, he shot Frank Costello
in the head and missed.
The Gallo brothers whacked
Albert Anastasia in that barbershop.
It was total chaos.
With Anastasia out, Vito Genovese
figures he's the big boss.
But Carlo Gambino...
...and Joe Bananas had other ideas.
So they called a meeting.
A big meeting.
It was the first time the whole
Commission would meet face to face.
Bosses and wiseguys were coming
from all over the country...
...and all the
New York families too.
Maybe 50 bosses,
the whole wiseguy world...
...all coming to this
little town upstate.
My father went with Dom Manetta
and Tommy D. Fat Tommy.
He was running the family then.
Some asshole thought it would be
a good idea to have this meeting...
...at Joe Barbara 's farm,
up in the country, nice and quiet.
Get away from the car.
Want to be a fucking rib eye?
Get away from the car!
Turns out the cops were
watching Joe Barbara like a hawk...
...and some deputy sheriff notices
all the traffic and calls the feds.
The meeting never even
got started.
The feds moved in...
...and bingo, the bosses,
they moved out.
My father and Dominic, they hid out
in the field with some hay or corn.
Along comes a farmer.
Dominic bullshits him
while my father holds out...
... this .44 cannon he used to carry,
and hijacked the tractor.
The story is they drove it
to Bensonhurst...
...but my father told me they
only got as far as Poughkeepsie.
Anyway, Carlo Gambino came out of it...
. . .capo di tutti capi,
"boss of all bosses"...
...and that was the last time the
Commission tried to meet, until now.
I don't like it.
What do we gotta meet for?
Let everybody else worry about
their own business.
The '57 meeting was about how we were
gonna divide this country.
This meeting is how we're
gonna survive.
You got made guys
informing for the feds.
Bosses are going to jail.
People are getting whacked
without permission.
And on top of everything else. . .
. . .you got these Chinese. . .
. . .and these crazy Russians
to deal with.
Everything's changing.
We gotta change with the times.
We gonna get a fucking Website?
When your papa died. . .
. . .I made him a promise
that I'd always look out for you.
I want you to come to
that meeting with me.
Capisci?
Listen. This guy, Primo Sindone,
you watch out for him.
He's a scumbag.
Keep your eye on him, okay?
Let me get a toothpick.
I'll be back.
Ijust kept telling him
that I needed room...
. . .to grow. . .
. . .and to find myself as a person.
You know?
Not just as a woman. . .
. . .but as an independent entity.
Then I told him I needed to get
in touch with my uniqueness. . .
. . .but he could not handle that.
He said that I was
driving him away.
He said I was driving him away.
Do you think I was
driving him away, Dr. Sobel?
Caroline, things end.
It's part of life. It's how we deal
with the ending that's important.
I just cannot believe. . .
. . .that it's over between
me and Steve, you know?
I mean, maybe there's still hope.
He took a restraining
order against you.
To be honest,
that's usually not a good sign.
But what should I do?
The first thing that I think
you should do. . .
. . .is to stop whining about this
pathetic loser, for chrissakes!
You are a tragedy queen!
Steve doesn't like me.
Steve doesn't respect me.
Who gives a shit?
Get a fucking life!
Dr. Sobel?
I was reflecting on your situation.
It's interesting what
you were saying.
I want you to think about it.
And I'm going to think about it.
We'll both think about it. . .
. . .and continue next week
when I get back from vacation.
Caroline, what are you feeling?
You're just like Steve.
You just want to--
You just want to. . .
. . .get rid of me
and throw me out.
You know that's not true.
Yes, it's true.
I'll see you next week. . .
. . .whereas Steve never wants
to see you again.
Please, Mr. Vitti.
I don't know nothing.
They don't believe me. . .
. . .because once I said Joe
hit Dukey and he didn't.
I didn't know because Little Joe
looked like--
Shut the fuck up!
You know me, right?
You're Mr. Vitti.
You know what I'll
do to you if you lie?
You'll crack me on the head
with that pipe.
It's a rhetorical question,
you idiot.
I'll ask you only once:
Who killed Dominic?
-Who killed Dominic?
-I don't know!
I swear to God--
Don't fucking lie!
You little motherfucker!
Who killed Dom?
He don't know nothing.
Forget it.
That was relatively painless.
Shut the fuck up!
That hurt.
We're not going anywhere.
We've sat here for 1 0 minutes.
I hate being late.
I hate walking into
that house late.
Dad, relax.
You're like this because you're
mad we have to go to Grandpa's.
Please don't analyze me.
I can't be analyzed by somebody who,
until recently, believed in Santa.
There is one Dr. Sobel
in this family. Just one.
But there's two.
There's you and there's Grandpa.
You know what?
Let's talk about something else.
You gonna read
Grandpa's new book?
Mom says you won't
because you're jealous.
Does your mother talk about anything
else, or is it just me, 24 hours a day?
Shit!
This is your mother's fault.
She knows where I am every second.
Get in!
If I point to you,
make believe your neck hurts.
What are you, a moron?
I'm sorry.
This was my fault.
Did you see anything?
-I was talking to my son.
-Bullshit!
That's all right, sir.
It's our fault for
being in front of you.
No, really.
Listen to me.
I'm responsible.
Here's my insurance information.
It's okay.
Forget it.
Forget--?
Your rear end's screwed up.
No, it was like that before.
Let's call the police
and file a report.
Fuck the police.
Hear me?
Okay.
Fuck them.
You're right.
Especially those mounted cops
who leave big piles all over. . .
. . .and you just step in it
up to your shins.
Let me give you my card. . .
. . .in case you look at it
and change your mind.
You a doctor?
I'm a psychiatrist.
A shrink.
I talked to a shrink one time.
When I got sent upstate on a. . .
. . .fishing trip.
Jelly!
Let's go! Come on.
I gotta go.
I'll see you.
Pings and knocks.
Cheap gas.
What are you gonna do?
-Right.
-Take it easy, Doc!
Neurotics only!
Oh, you must have been
a beautiful baby
'Cause baby, look at you now
Thank God for Prozac
Baby, look at you now
You're not coming?
This is my wedding!
We understand it's
a special day for you, Benny. . .
. . .but we can't just
pick up and leave town. . .
. . .every time you decide
to get married.
Every time?
This is a once in a lifetime--
Twice in a lifetime thing, Mom.
Dad, you're not coming
to my wedding?
We want to, but I have
three book signings next weekend.
I can't piss off
these big bookstores.
If I cancel, they stick me on the
bottom shelves. That's how they are.
That's the word on the street.
Barnes is okay, but Noble is
a vindictive prick.
Ben.
The language.
I'm sorry, but listen.
I have been alone for eight years.
I finally found somebody that
I want to spend my life with.
At least meet her
before we get married.
You are gonna be her family.
I think she should
know that up front.
You're being very hostile.
I was joking.
I'm going to see the mayor.
The mayor is here?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Everything's fine.
How's your practice?
Excellent.
I have interesting patients.
Very interesting.
Fascinating, actually.
Dad has a patient who
dreams he shits trout.
Thanks, Mike.
The Manetta family is bound
to ask questions.
They think we put
the hit out on Dominic.
Forget Dominic.
They were after Paul.
It's a miracle you survived.
I just thank God.
Yeah, thank God, all right.
If it wasn't because I had to
go back for that toothpick. . .
. . .I'd be lying dead with Dominic,
God forbid.
May he rest in peace.
This is about the big meeting.
Primo Sindone wants to
run the whole show.
Primo knows the rules.
He couldn't come after them unless
he had permission from the families.
If they did, we're headed for
one big war, I can tell you that.
Find out what you can.
We got two weeks.
God forbid the other
New York bosses are against us.
I want to know that
before I go into that meeting.
Sure.
You all right?
You don't look too good.
What's the matter?
I'm a little choked up.
I'm going to get some air.
-Easy.
-Take some air.
You all right?
What?
I feel like shit.
This whole thing is like
one big fucking headache.
You having one of them "mindgraines"?
-Let's go.
-What's the matter?
-Just drive.
-What happened?
Good news, Mr. Evans.
Your heart is just fine.
"Just fine"?
But I had eight heart attacks
in the last three weeks.
Based on everything,
I'd say you had an anxiety attack.
A what?
An anxiety attack.
A panic attack.
I'll give you Xanax.
Anxiety?
What are you saying?
It's a common thing.
Hey, look at me.
Do I look like a guy who panics?
-Do I look like a guy who panics?
-It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Where'd you go to medical school?
I got a fucking heart attack.
Not according to your EKG.
Jelly, I need you to do
something for me as a friend.
Yeah, anything.
-Find me a doctor.
-We just come from the doctor.
Not that kind of doctor.
Like a head doctor.
You gonna change your face,
like Sonny Black?
Don't get his nose.
He looks like a pig.
Not a plastic surgeon.
I gotta spell everything out for you?
It saves time.
I mean, like a head doctor.
Like a psychiatrist.
This is like one of them psychic,
ESPN. . .
. . .ESPN things, you know?
I just ran into a psychiatrist.
Actually, he ran into me.
Was he any good?
He seemed like a smart guy.
He had a business card.
A business card?
That's a real fucking achievement.
What do you need a shrink for?
It's not for me.
It's for my friend.
I'm gonna ask the shrink
some questions. . .
. . .and get some answers
for my friend.
Nobody can know. God forbid somebody
hears I been talking to a shrink.
It could be interpreted wrong.
Know what I mean?
No one will ever know.
-Could I just ask one question?
-Go ahead.
This friend. . .
. . .is it me?
Yeah, it's you.
Carl, I'm detecting a pattern.
You settle too easily for things.
You're right.
I do.
See, you just did it again.
I suggested something,
and you immediately agreed.
You're right.
I did.
Why do you do this?
I don't know.
I think it's your fear
of rejection or disapproval.
You don't have to
worry about that.
Be your own man.
Stand your ground.
You don't have to
let people roll over you.
Dr. Sobel?
We're in session.
Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry.
You're the guy I hit last night.
Bingo.
Get out of here.
Upsy-daisy.
Got a coat, nutbar?
-What--?
-He's leaving.
He's not going till
he's done with his session.
-I'll give you $1 00 to leave.
-Don't take it.
-Make it 1 50.
-Listen.
300.
He ain't that fucking crazy.
You were right.
I stood my ground.
-This was the wrong time.
-I got him up from 1 50.
-I'm proud.
-I feel like a new man.
I'm so happy.
I know you're upset about the car,
but you can't come in here.
This is a patient's private session.
You know me?
-Yes.
-No, you don't.
You seen my picture
in the paper?
-Yes.
-No, you didn't.
I don't even get the paper.
Jelly, wait outside.
Sit down.
You ain't got no bugs in here?
Bugs?
Bugs.
Recording equipment.
No, I don't record.
I take notes.
I tried to give him the insurance
information several times.
Several times.
He wouldn't take it.
Please don't kill me.
I was just gonna ask
if you like Tony Bennett.
I'm a big Tony Bennett fan.
Me too.
I like all ltalian singers.
Mr. Vitti,
I know it's not your fault. . .
. . .but shouldn't we take this up
with our insurance companies?
That ain't it.
I don't care about the car.
I got a friend of mine. . . .
He's got problems, and he'll
have to probably see a shrink.
So I'll ask you
a couple of questions.
Go ahead, then.
What do we do?
What, we sit?
Whatever makes you comfortable.
I'll sit over here.
-I'll sit here.
-That's your--
If you're comfortable,
it's fine.
So who starts?
Tell me why you think
you need therapy.
I don't need therapy.
I told you that. It's for my friend.
-I'm sorry.
-You didn't hear me?
I'm sorry.
You're supposed to be good at listening.
You can't remember what I said?
So sorry.
I ain't thrilled with the
level of service up to this point.
That was my fault.
I apologize.
Why don't we start over?
Why don't you just tell me
about your friend?
This friend, you know,
he's a very powerful guy.
Never had trouble
with nothing.
All of a sudden,
he's falling apart. . .
. . .he cries for no reason,
he can't sleep. . .
. . .he can't be with his friends.
All of a sudden,
he gets nervous around them.
He wants to get away from them.
And these are guys he knows
his whole life, you know?
And then he has these attacks.
He can't breathe,
he gets dizzy. . .
. . .chest pains, you know. . . .
He thinks he's going to
die or something.
Panic attacks.
What's with you guys
and panic attacks?
Who said "panic"?
Not panic.
Dizzy, chest-breathing,
constricting. . .
. . .attacks.
This guy, he just wants to know
what he can do to make it stop.
I'm gonna go out on a limb here.
I think your friend. . .
. . .is you.
You got a gift, my friend.
You got a gift.
You saw that there was something
I was trying to do. . .
. . .and figured it out.
That's why you are who you are.
God bless you.
You got a fucking gift.
-No, I don't.
-Yes, you do.
Go on.
-What?
-Go on.
I think. . .
. . .medication could help.
Drugs?
Can't do drugs.
I don't do drugs.
If you want to get to
the root of the problem. . .
. . .you'll want to get
some form of therapy.
Like what?
With you or something?
Me?
No, I don't think you want--
My roster of patients is full.
I'm full right now.
Plus, I'm leaving on a short vacation.
Where you going?
-I don't share that with patients.
-Where?
Sheraton Bal Harbour Hotel
in Miami Beach.
That wasn't so hard, was it?
No, it wasn't.
You know, it's a funny
kind of a thing. . .
. . .but I feel better after
I got all that off my chest.
I feel like a load. . . .
A load is off my shoulders.
You're good.
Doc, thank you.
-I didn't do anything.
-You did.
-I did nothing.
-You did too.
The load, gone.
Where is it?
Don't know.
You're good.
You're good, Doc.
I'll be getting in touch with you.
-Don't, please.
-One more thing.
If I talk to you, and you turn me
into a fag, I'll kill you. Understand?
Could we define "fag"?
Because some feelings--
-I go fag, you die. Got it?
-Got it.
Simple.
You're good, Doc.
You're good.
See you, Doc.
We take on Manetta,
what does Vitti do? Nothing.
-Why doesn't he move?
-Fuck him.
You say "fuck him,"
but he's planning something big.
The shit's coming down.
Then let it come down.
Let me tell you,
Vitti's a tough guy. . .
. . .but a lot of tough guys get fed to
the crabs off Red Hook.
Vitti. That name has been
haunting me since I was a kid.
Growing up, he was the smart guy.
I was the dope.
My father was a nickel-and-dime
shitheel. His had it all.
Vito Genovese blew it at Apalachin. . .
. . .because he forgot to kill
Gambino before the meeting.
I won't make that same mistake.
I want Paul Vitti dead!
You hear me? I want him dead.
Not breathing now. Dead!
Like the pants?
They look great.
He's some tailor.
I'll tell you. Look good.
I like them.
Don't leave any food in your room.
I won't come home to a science fair.
I didn't.
Dad, one thing, though.
-"I go fag, you die. "
-That's it!
I'm sealing the vent
in your room.
You cannot listen to my sessions!
It's so cool.
Was that really Paul Vitti?
I didn't ask to see his
Mafia decoder ring, but yes.
-Are you going to treat him?
-Of course not. Are you crazy?
You cannot tell anybody
that he was here. Understand?
Should I take it off the lnternet?
I'm kidding.
Despite the heat and the popularity of
more exotic Caribbean destinations...
...Florida 's hospitality industry
reports booming business...
...from Orlando to the Keys.
Judging from the mob...
...around the pool here...
... there's nothing "off" about the
off-season in Miami Beach this summer.
On a personal note,
this is my last report for WVBF.
I'm marrying a wonderful man
and moving to New York.
Thanks for everything, Miami.
For the last time, this is
Laura MacNamara for WVBF.
Catch!
We're clear!
Nice, Laura.
Everybody! This is him!
This is the guy!
-I missed you so much.
-I missed you too.
-Michael, say hi.
-Hi, Laura.
Hi, Michael.
How are you?
You want to go
look at the camera?
Why would I want to go
-Is it okay?
-Yeah, go ahead.
Don't worry if you break anything.
I'm out of here.
-You think he likes me?
-He's crazy about you. No, he is.
I love you.
I'm so glad to be with you.
Do you really?
And do you really love me?
Of course.
What's the matter?
-I'm nervous.
-Why?
Because I'm going to be
a stepmom to a grown kid. . .
. . .and we're getting married.
So what are you worried about?
What if you get tired of me?
A lot of couples are very happy,
and then they marry. . .
. . .and completely lose interest
in each other.
That won't happen to us.
Is everything okay, Paul?
Will you stop talking?
I'm trying to do this here.
-You seem distracted.
-I am. I got things on my mind.
-Would you stop talking?
-I'm sorry.
Lie down.
Thinking about your wife?
I wasn't thinking about my wife.
What are you talking about?
Now I am thinking about my wife.
Sheila, why can't you
keep your mouth shut?
Sorry.
Dr. Sobel.
Mom?
It's me.
Mr. Vitti wants to see you.
I got your robe.
I got news for you, you two-bit prick,
son-of-a-bitch rat bastard. . .
. . .you did nothing for me!
Whatever you did, it didn't take.
I'm still fucked up.
You did nothing for me!
I did nothing for you?
I saw you for five minutes.
What do you expect?
I can't work miracles.
Let me tell you something else.
I don't like it when someone
breaks in. . .
. . .and kidnaps me
in the middle of the night!
I have a family.
I have a life.
And I have a serious practice.
And I don't have time
for your bullshit!
That got away from me
at the end there.
I couldn't get it up last night.
Do you mean sexually?
No, for the big
Michigan State game.
Of course, sexually!
What's the matter with you?
Can I get this straight?
You flew 1 ,500 miles,
you dragged me out of bed. . .
. . .because you couldn't get
an erection?
Don't that prove I'm motivated?
You can take a pill for that.
That's a cheat.
You start with the pills,
next it's hydraulics.
A hard-on should be gotten
legitimately or not at all.
I think Mark Twain said that.
Are you gonna help me or not?
I don't believe this.
All right.
Has this happened before?
The dead-dick thing?
Never.
Well, one time. Last night.
One more time.
So twice.
Do the math.
Two times.
Then another time, but after
a big meal, so that don't count.
Being unable to perform
three or four times is not--
Eight times.
Eight times is not catastrophic.
Maybe not to you.
Look at you.
But if I can't get it up,
that makes me less of a man.
In my world,
I deal with animals.
They may seem dumb to
an educated guy like you. . .
. . .but animals are very cunning,
and they sense weakness.
I got less than two weeks. . .
. . .to get strong, or they'll kill me.
What happens then?
I can't tell you.
You don't want to know.
You can't tell me and I don't
want to know. That's a big help.
You're supposed to tell me.
I want to know.
That's how this works.
This is impossible.
I can't do anything in two weeks,
and even if I could. . .
. . .what is my goal? To make you
a happy, well-adjusted gangster?
The other day I was watching
a TV commercial. . .
. . .some kid playing with puppies.
I cried for 45 minutes.
Slap a pair of tits on me, I'm a woman.
I can't help you.
You're turning me down?
When I got into family therapy,
this wasn't the family I had in mind.
You with your schmucky little office
and house, you're turning me down?
So you can listen to
housewives piss and moan. . .
. . .about nobody fucks them
right anymore?
I'm leaving now.
You see this?
This is what I'm talking about.
I'm a dead man.
You call yourself a doctor.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
A real doctor could never turn his back
on a person who's suffering!
You couldn't treat a fucking
two-celled amoeba, you fucking phony.
Mother of God, give me
the strength to get through this.
This fucking rat bastard. . .
. . .won't help me.
I cry all the time. . . .
Don't know what it is.
All right, here.
Sit down.
What happened with
your wife last night?
I wasn't with my wife.
I was with my girlfriend.
Are you having marriage problems?
Why do you have a girlfriend?
You're moralizing with me now?
No, I'm curious.
Why do you have a girlfriend?
I do things with her
I can't do with my wife.
Why can't you?
That's the mouth she kisses
my kids with. Are you crazy?
Have you been under stress lately?
-Like seeing your best friend murdered?
-That would qualify.
I got a lot of stress.
Based upon what you told me before
about the attacks. . .
. . .I'd say that was probably it.
-Just stress?
-"Just stress"?
Stress is a very powerful force.
I doubt there's anything
physically wrong with you.
-That's it?
-That's it.
That's it?
I think so.
You're very good, you.
You are very good.
-There's more to it--
-You're very good.
-There are underlying--
-Understand me?
You're right on the money.
I feel the juices rush back
to my balls as we speak.
I never thought I'd hear
a man say that to me.
That settles it.
You are my shrink.
No, I couldn't.
You're not ready to open up.
You're not a good candidate--
Listen to you.
The fucking honesty.
That's it.
You don't understand.
Nobody, nobody talks
to me like that.
You understand?
-Yes, I do.
-That's it.
Let's do it.
I'm ready.
You don't hear the word "no"
very often.
I hear it all the time,
only it's more, "No, please, no, no. "
I'm here for two more days.
When I get back to New York,
I'll treat you exclusively.
For two weeks.
I just don't know what
to tell my patients.
You want me to clear
your schedule?
It would be my honor to do that.
My pleasure.
Not Jimmy.
I will do this myself.
-You sure?
-Positive.
I will see you in New York.
Okay.
Want one of them?
-No, thanks.
-Sure?
That's very kind of you, but l. . . .
Want to give a little sta minch ?
You sure?
The pause that refreshes.
I don't--
No, I really. . . .
You're on vacation.
I'm also about to get married. . .
. . .so I'd like to go back
to my hotel and. . . .
Good night.
I'll see you in New York.
You.
Hey, Doc. You.
I'm gonna see a lot of you.
Where were you?
My God, I woke up
and you were gone!
There was no note or anything!
I was out of my mind!
I walked all over the hotel
looking for you.
I even ate a Rice Krispy Treat.
I almost called the police.
No, don't call the police.
I'll tell you the truth.
I had a patient emergency.
You have patients in Florida?
One. He followed me from New York.
I had to go, trust me.
My God.
Who is this patient?
Paul Vitti.
Mafia Paul Vitti?
Oh, my God.
It's not like
he's a regular patient.
He's got problems.
He thinks that I'm treating him.
It's crazy.
So you're not treating him?
Tell me you're not.
I'm not treating him.
It's scary. You don't want
someone like that in your life.
I've covered the mob down here.
I've seen what they do.
He and I spoke about it.
He understood. It's over.
-You're sure?
-Absolutely.
I was so worried.
I thought maybe you
got scared or. . .
. . .saw an ex-girlfriend
or something.
Well, I don't know.
-I love you.
I'm sorry, but everything's
going to be okay.
Give her a big hand!
Let's hear it!
How about that?
That was great!
Come on, get into it.
I don't understand.
They splash in the water.
They eat fish.
This is not a big stretch
for a whale.
Stop it.
We're having fun, right?
I'm not having as much fun
as it looks like I am.
I'm pretending, because we
have to bond and all.
A little snack for her
might be 50 pounds of mackerel.
There she goes!
I'm going to get a hot dog.
Anybody want anything?
-I'll go with you.
-It's fine.
You're pretending to have a good time.
I don't want to spoil that.
I'll be right back.
You think those whales
piss in that water?
I think they use the men's room
next door to the Burger King.
Dummy.
-What's going on?
-Mr. Vitti wants to see you.
Is this a joke?
You're employed
by Mr Vitti. . .
. . .which means you're on call
24 hours a day. . .
. . .just like the rest of us.
I'm sorry.
He and I discussed--
We discussed this, and I agreed
to see him in New York.
That's it.
Doctor, listen to me.
It is what it is.
If he wants you sooner, you go sooner.
That's it.
No.
I am not going.
And if either one of you
bother me again. . .
. . .I won't treat him at all.
Do you understand that?
Capisci?
It's over!
End of story.
Look at the size of this one.
Jesus Christ!
It's feeding time.
They threw me in
the shark tank, Paul.
They wanted to make a point.
That you're scary?
Believe me, I get it.
You're in a mood.
I get that way when
a shark tries to chew on my ass.
-We had an agreement.
-We did, but I had an episode.
I didn't have a panic attack,
but I started panicking. . .
. . .thinking I might get one.
Is that weird?
I am redefining "weird"
on an hourly basis.
-What's he doing?
-I don't know.
-He's talking with some guy.
-Can you hit him?
He's got fat Jelly and his
partner Jimmy Boots with him.
I could do it with a rifle,
but I don't have that with me.
Just get him.
You told me to take care of him,
I will.
What were you thinking
when you got anxious?
Let's get out of here.
We're being watched.
Don't look.
There's feds up there watching us.
How do you know that?
I'm a criminal.
It's my job.
Who's the new face?
Maybe he's Vitti's new consigliere.
Whoever this guy is,
he must be important to the family.
Put his picture on the wire.
See what you come up with.
Normally, a patient wouldn't have
a vat of scotch during a session.
That's interesting. I'll have to
remember it if I'm ever on Jeopardy.
Tell me about your father.
My father.
Well, my father. . . .
Let's sit here.
My father.
A big man in the neighborhood.
Everybody loved him.
Very well-respected,
God rest his soul.
He passed away?
I just like saying "God rest his soul. "
Of course he passed away!
I was about 1 2 at the time.
How did he die?
It was a sudden thing.
A heart attack.
How was the relationship?
Were you close?
We were pretty close.
We weren't getting along great
right then.
Why is that?
I was hanging out in the neighborhood.
I had a borgata.
What is that?
A kid gang, nothing big.
But he didn't like that.
He didn't approve.
He slapped me around
a couple of times.
And what?
And then he died.
How'd that make you feel?
It felt great, wonderful.
How'd it make me feel?
Think about it.
Were you angry?
Were you afraid? Sad?
Maybe all those things.
Any feelings of guilt?
About what?
I didn't kill him.
I know that.
I'm just speculating. . .
. . .that maybe in some way
you may have wanted him to die.
Why would I want him to die?
You said you were fighting.
He slapped you around. . .
. . .because you rebelled
against his authority.
Maybe some unresolved
Oedipal conflict.
English, English.
Oedipus was a Greek king who killed
his father and married his mother.
Fucking Greeks.
It's an instinctual
developmental drive.
The young boy wants to
replace his father. . .
. . .so that he can
totally possess his mother.
Are you saying
I wanted to fuck my mother?
It's a primal fantasy.
Have you ever seen my mother?
-Are you out of your mind?
-It's Freud!
Freud's a sick fuck, and you are
too for bringing it up.
Can I be honest?
I don 't think I can call you Dad.
So what do I call you?
Do I call you Scott?
My friends call me Captain.
Captain?
Want another drink?
I'm definitely having eight or nine.
I'd like a morphine and soda.
I'm shaking.
Shall we go to our table?
Come on, Michael.
Seor Sobel.
How you doing?
It's the Vittis.
My God.
Everybody's happy.
Everybody's smiling. This is nice.
You're Paul Vitti,
the mobster.
Now, is that polite?
Is that being nice?
I'm trying to be nice.
Do I walk up to you and say
you're so-and-so, the hard-on?
This is Laura's father,
the Captain.
I'm very, very sorry.
Excuse us.
I heard about the wedding.
Here you go.
A little something for the
bride and groom. God bless.
We can't accept this.
-Yes, you can.
-Thank you.
I'm just gonna borrow this guy.
I'll bring him right back.
And then you'll leave us alone.
I'll leave you alone.
I got to talk to you.
Two minutes.
Wait over there.
Don't listen to what we say.
My ears are sealed.
I had a weird dream
last night.
I feel like I'm having one now.
Why'd you interrupt my party?
You're really very rigid
about certain things.
Did you know that?
All right,
tell me about your dream.
I'm asleep.
I hear a baby crying.
I go to the refrigerator.
I get him a bottle of milk.
I bring the bottle of milk to him. . .
. . .I see the milk is black.
That's fucking weird!
Get out of here.
-Get out of here.
-Sorry.
What does that mean?
And no more filth about my mother.
I don't know.
What does it mean to you?
This is why I pay you? I say
something, you say it back to me?
I could get Jelly to
do that for nothing.
Get Jelly.
I'm going back to my party.
All right.
I'm letting it go this time.
Because you're getting married,
I'm gonna let it go.
Why don't you look over that way
before I bust your head open?
I'm gonna grab a bite to eat.
You want a sandwich?
What kind of sandwich
ain't too fattening?
A half a sandwich.
I'll be back in a few minutes.
Now, nod your head and smile.
Do it.
Now, you listen to me, goombah.
I know what your game is,
and you'd better call it quits.
If you and your paisans
do anything to hurt my little girl. . .
. . .I don't care who
you are. . .
. . .I'll hunt you down like
the dog you are, and I'll kill you.
Understand?
Now, nod and smile.
Congratulations.
What was that about?
Just guy stuff between
me and the Captain.
Shit!
In sickness and in health,
from this day forth. . .
. . .as long as you both shall live?
Bring Marie and
the kids right to the airport.
Pull the car in the
back of the hotel and wait for us.
You got it, boss.
That's it. That is it!
I've had it with you.
-What happened?
I just saw a man fall seven stories
into a platter of poached salmon!
-Did he break anything?
-Everything!
They're still pulling capers
out of him.
People get depressed, they jump.
It's a tragedy, but it ain't my fault.
You're telling me
it was a suicide?
I think he left a note.
Jelly, did they find it?
No, but they will in a minute.
Let me guess what it says.
"Life is bullshit.
I can't take it no more.
Signed, The Dead Guy. "
That's good, Doc.
Enough talk.
We gotta get out of here.
There's feds all over.
I'm going back to New York. . .
. . .and I would suggest that
you do the same thing.
Because they're probably
onto you too.
Onto me?
What are you talking about?
Being an accessory to a murder
wasn't part of our understanding.
I didn't kill nobody.
I can't speak for
other people here.
He tried to kill me.
God forbid he did that
to somebody in my family.
It would've been
a double or a triple tragedy.
Trust me, in this case,
we're the good guys.
Where is he?
-Where are you going?
-Don't touch me.
How could you do that?
Another country heard from.
Wait downstairs.
Why? Are they going to throw me
off the balcony too?
You're upset, and
you're upsetting me.
Of course I'm upset!
My wedding is ruined
because you've got problems!
I got problems?
Honey, please.
I'm going to pack,
and then I'm going to New York.
And I am getting married with you
or without you!
With! With!
I'm sorry, honey.
It'll all work out.
I promise.
Please?
No, I hate you!
Are you happy?
You know what you did?
You ruined my life!
Happy?
What are you talking about?
You think I wanted this?
I'm a victim here.
I can't believe this guy.
He tries to kill me,
then whacks one of my guys.
On top of that, he fucks up your
wedding. You know how upset I am?
I'm so enraged, I don't know
what to do with myself!
Plus, I'm trying to
get out of this hotel and--
Are you listening to yourself?
Listen to yourself!
This has been a disaster from the
moment you stepped foot in my office.
That is it. Over!
I'm no longer your doctor.
Just because of this?
Because of this little double homicide?
Yes, because of this!
You don't have a shred
of human decency. Not a shred.
I actually thought
I could help you.
There's no helping you.
You're a common thug!
Nobody in the world
could help you!
All right!
What do you want me to do?
Let me speak to Primo.
Hold on.
Paul Vitti's on the phone.
-Who is this?
-It's me.
-Me who?
-Me who-- Me, me.
-Me? Me who?
-Me, me. You know me. Me.
Yeah, how's it going?
Not good.
Whoever did that thing to
you-know-who, my good friend. . .
. . .is trying to do that to me.
And I'm having a lot
of feelings about that.
And I'm trying to get some. . . .
-Closure.
-Closure on that.
What kind of feelings?
I'm very angry.
I'm feeling very angry about that.
I'm enraged.
I'm feeling very,
very mad about that.
Why are you telling me?
Why am I telling you?
Like you don't know
nothing about it?
You don't know nothing?
What?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
-I'm trying to. . . .
-Tell you how I feel.
Tell you about my feelings
and that. . . .
-I'm angry.
And anger is a. . . .
-A blocked wish.
And I'm looking forward to seeing
you next week at that thing.
Then I can unblock
that angered wish. . .
. . .and then hopefully. . . .
You make one more move on me,
you motherfucker. . .
. . .I'll fucking cut
your fucking balls off!
I'll shove them up your fucking ass!
I'll fucking bury you!
I'll put ice picks in your eyes!
I'll chop your eyeballs!
I'll send them to your family
to eat for dessert!
You understand me?
-What?
-Fuck you.
You motherfucker!
You get a dictionary and find out
what this "closure" is.
If that's what he's going to hit us
with, I want to know what it is.
How was that?
It was going great until. . .
. . .the cutting off of the balls
and shoving it up. . .
. . .his ass.
You know what I do when I'm mad?
I hit a pillow.
Just hit the pillow.
See how you feel.
There's your fucking pillow.
Feel better?
Yeah, I do.
Good.
Call the Vatican.
See if something is missing.
So cool!
I need to talk to your dad
in private, okay?
Would you unload the car, please?
It's almost as tall as the house.
What is going on?
What is this?
Why?
It's a wedding gift.
He felt bad for the--
Well, we're not married,
so we can just send it back.
It was not my fault.
Everybody was there.
You didn't want to
go ahead with the ceremony.
What did you expect? That's not what
I want for an anniversary memory.
Look at our wedding video.
There are your parents, and mine.
There's the guy that
plunged to his death.
I just want to marry you.
I'm thinking it'll never happen.
It's happening next Saturday
at the Waldorf.
And who'll be there?
We three, the clergyman. . .
. . .and any of your family who
are done with their crisis counseling.
No guests without necks.
Everybody has to have a neck.
We will do a neck check
at the door.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org