Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Alexei Alexandrovitch,
leave me Seriozha.
You know l can´t live
without him.
lf you´ll conduct yourself
so that neither society
nor the servants can find
anything to say against you,
you can enjoy all the privileges
of a respectable wife
without fulfilling
the duties of one.
and you may
keep your son.
Late as usuaI.O
-You have a Iot of peopIe here.
-Who´s here?
Is Kitty here?e
I never did quite beIieve that there
was anything wrong with my Iungs,
but the secIusion and quiet
of karIsbad were aII heIpfuI to me.
I Iearned how to heIp care
for the other patients,a
those with serious aiIments,a
and the work suited me.v
I Iearned that there are
so many more important...
I saw you Iast summer.m
Oh, you didn´t see me,
but I saw you.a
Where?ã
You were driving to Yergushovo.
My estate´s on the way.
It was very earIy in the morning.
You were probabIy onIy just awake.
You had a spIendid team
of horses with beIIs.
YoufIashed by
in a second.i
I saw you through the window.
Your head was Iike this.
And you were pIaying
with the ribbons of your cap,a
thinking about
something very deepIy.
I wish I knew what
you were thinking then.
ReaIIy?s
I don´t remember.e
Don't go.
I´ve a question I´ve been wanting
to ask youfor a Iong time.
What is it?
Here.é
That´s the first Ietters
of the words.
What is that word?a
-Never.
-Is it something I once said?a
I know what it is.
´´When you toId me it couId not be...
...did that mean never...e
...or then?´´i
I don´t know.a
´´Then I couId not answer
differentIy.´´
OnIy then?a
He wiII have reached the church
any moment now.
Word wiII come.g
Oh! This is impossibIe!a
Don´t worry. You´II just
have to wear mine.
Yes, weII, if I was going to do that,
I shouId´ve done it a Iong time ago!
Everything wiII
turn out just fine.
Don´t you worry.t
I went out to buy a new shirt.
AII the shops were shut...
I was beginning to think that you had
made up your mind to run away.
What happened to me was
so siIIy, I was...
I´m ashamed
to teII you.l
Kitty shouId have
stepped on the mat first.
Whoever does
runs the househoId.i
I did.i
What about you, DoIIy?
I don´t remember.x
Why on earth not?P
I was so in Iove.a
Sir, Madame Karenin
miscarried Iast night.
My God, how is she?l
Very bad. The doctor
is with her now.
Who is here?m
Is... is she...d
She has
a very high fever.q
Ana Arkadyevna,
he has come.c
Has Seriozha had his dinner?
l Know they will allforget.
I am entireIy
in your hands.i
He must be moved
into the corner room...e
Maria told
to sleep with him.
I´m not afraid of you.e
I know I´m dying now.
You ask him.e
I feeI it aIready.v
I want onIy one thing...P
for you to forgive me.m
Forgive me compIeteIy..
There is some hope..
I must stay.e
She may ask for me..
I´ve Iong wanted to be
revenged on you and her.d
When I got the teIegram.
I came here with the same sentiments.
But I saw her...
and forgave her.a
And the happiness of
forgiving her reveaIed to me
my duty.o
I wiII not
forsake her,a
and I wiII never utter a word
of reproach to you.
ShouId she want to see you,
I wiII Iet you know.
Now I think
you´d better Ieave.d
Idiot!
You had the misfortune to faII in Iove
with man who´s not your husband.
This is a misfortune,
but this is a fact.
Your husband
has forgiven you.
AIso a fact.f
The question is,o
can you go on Iiving
with your husband?
Do you want to?
And what does he want?
I don´t know.
I don´t know at aII.e
I feeI I´m fIying headIong
over a precipice.
We´II catch you,o
and we won´t
Iet youfaII.a
There is
nothing Ieft for me,
except for it
to be aII over.
Look at you.a
I hardIy know you
with this short hair.
You´ve grown so pretty,
but how paIe you are.
I´m stiII very weak.o
We´II go to ItaIy.p
You´II soon get weII.c
We´II Iive together
as husband and wife.
You´II be ruined.
I resigned
my commission.ê
Now aII I want
is you.
My dear friend,u
you must not give way
to your grief.
You wiIIfind support,
but seek it not in me,c
though I beg youa
to beIieve in
our friendship.m
I wiII set to work..
I wiII be your housekeeper.
Don´t thank me.
I do it not of myself.
How can I heIp
thanking you?
You mustr
thank Him,
and ask for His heIp.d
In Him aIone
can we find peace.
My dear, dear boy.a
How unhappy you must be.o
I´m quite weII,
countess.
Your poor father is...n
to distraughte
to teII you himself,.
so he´s Ieft it to me.o
He is...
a saint,
you know?s
Your mother...
is dead.s
Letters have arrived from town,
Constantine Dmitrich.o
You see, your Iady´s settIed me here,
toId me to sit a IittIe with her.
Here.e
I opened
your Ietter, too.
I think it´s from that woman,
your brother´s,
and this is a Ietter
from home.
DoIIy took Grisha and Tanya to a
chiIdren´s party at the Sarmatskys´.
Tanya went
as a French marquise..
What´s...
what´s the matter?
My... my brother
NikoIai is dying.a
I... I must go to him
I´II Ieave tomorrow.
Let´s go.
Why didn´t you
Iet me know sooner?
What is so awfuI
for me...
is that I can´t heIp...s
remembering him as he was
when he was young.
you can´t imagine
what a charming boy he was.
But I didn´t
understand him then.a
In infinite time...o
in infinite matter...
in infinite space...
an organic ceII
stands out,o
wiII hoId together
awhiIe...
and then bursts.i
And that ceII is me.
I cannot Iive without
knowing.
what I am and why I am here,
and that I cannot know.
So, therefore, I
have no reason to Iive.
What?
I´m pregnant.n
WeII, don´t spare
me now.D
It´s going
to be perfection.
-I´m not going to finish it.
-Why?Why ever not?
Because its defects wiII become
more and more obvious.
I can´t fooI myself
that I am an artist.a
I am going
to give it up.
I confess I hardIy miss
Seriozha at aII.
But you do.u
Yes.p
Let´s go back to Russia.
Karenin wiII
grant us a divorce.
We´II get married,
and we´II be together.
Oh, I was afraid you´d say that.
I´m so unpardonabIe happy here,
away from aII of them,
aII of that.
I thought you were, too.b
Being with youc
is the reaIization of
aII my deepest desires,s
but there is nothing
I can do here.
I need a purpose.e
That´s what I Iike so much,
having you aII to myself.
Seriozha
needs his mother.r
Dear Lydia lvanovna,v
Forgive me for
reminding you of myself.r
Count VronsKy and l are
returning to St. Petersburg.
l am unhappy at
being parted from my son.
l beg to be allowed
to see him.i
Will you send Seriozha to me, or should
l come to the house at some fixed hour?
You cannot conceive
the yearning l have to see him
and so can not conceive the gratitude
your help will arouse in me.
Anna.a
I don´t think
I can refuse her.
My dear friend,
You never see eviI in anybody..
Her Iove for her son
exacts...
But is it Iove?
My friend,
is it sincere?n
Have we the right to toy with the
feeIings of that IittIe angeI?
He thinks she´s dead,r
and he prays for hern
and besieges God
have mercy on her sins,n
and it is...e
better.p
Madame,D
to remind
your son of yous
Might lead to questions on his part
which it would be impossible to answer.
l beg you to interpret
your husband's refusal
in the spirit
of Christian love.s
I am here to teII you that I Iook upon my
union with Madame Karenina as marriage.
If you wish to be on good terms with me
then you must be on good terms with her.
Our intimate friendsc
can and must Iook at it
in the proper Iight.
I for one am so gIad
you are back.b
I can imagine how horribIe our
Petersburg must seem to you
after your
deIightfuI traveIs.
-How about the divorce? Is that aII settIed?
-I´m onIy waiting for Karenin.
PeopIe wiII throw
stones at me, I know,s
but I shaII come
and see Anna.
I wiII ignore
the conventions,
but other starchy peopIe
wiII give you the coId shouIder
untiI you are married,.
and that´s
so simpIe nowadays.
Of course, I cannot invite her to my
home. I have daughters growing up.
How can you
say that..
When everyone knows you were
Tushkevich´s mistress?
How dare you
make comparisons?c
AIiosha, darIing,s
You hardIy have
the moraI high ground.
The doctor.
It´s time.ç
Are you aII right?h
Get out of here,
Kostya! Go!a
Lord have mercy on us
and heIp us.
A boy too!E
You may ease your mind.
AII is weII.r
Show him to his Papa!e
That´s how they are
when they come out.
This one is a beauty.o
Seriozha...b
my darIing.
They toId me
you were dead.m
You didn´t beIieve it,
my precious.
I never beIieved it!
Oh no, you´d never
have Iet her in!
Ten year´s service and nothing but
kindness from her,
and you´d have got up
and shown her the door.n
He´II get up presentIy and
you wiII be out on the streets.
Don´t go. He won´t
come just yet.r
Seriozha, my darIing,
you must Iove him.ã
He´s better than I am,
and I have been wicked to him.
When you´re grown up,
you wiII understand.h
Don´t go.
Mama!l
Get out! Our door
is closed to you!
You're not welcome here!
You deserted your son!
The laudanum prescribed for Ana
after the loss of her child
Now became the opiate used to
deaden the pain of Seriozha's loss.
Why shouIdn´t I go?s
You are going.a
Oh, of course, there´s
no reason whatever.e
That´s exactIy
what I say.c
Anna, for heaven´s sake,
what has come over you?
I don´t understand
what you mean.
You know you can´t go
into the opera.
Why not?e
I´m not going aIone.o
I´m... I´m going
with princess Varvara.
Princess Varvara...o
Is IittIe more
than a courtesan.
She´s no worse
than the others.
Besides, I am not ashamed
of what I have done.
I´m not ashamed
of my Iove for you.q
And whom
are you accompanying?
You´ve been out
with your mother quite a bit IateIy.
Anna, she is my mother.v
I hear your mother has taken on
princess Sorokina as a companion.
Why don´t you make your mother
happy and marry her?i
Anna, I have not
the sIightest interest
in princess Sorokina.r
How do you think
that makes me feeI?n
What?u
How am I
supposed to feeI?.
You spend your evenings
with a pretty young girI.
What do I know?
OnIy what you teII me.a
Oh, you don´t trust me?
Why can´t I go out?s
I Iove you, and nothing
eIse matters to me..
So Iong as you
haven´t changed....
As Iong
as you stiII Iove me.
Oh, Iook at me.p
AII we need
is the divorce.m
I know how difficuIt your
situation must be untiI then,
but, pIease, don´t make matters worse.
PIease, pIease, don´t go.
Oh, I´II stay,
as you wish..
Princess Sorokina.n
Your mama
is asking for you.f
Good evening, mama.a
I´m sorry to be Iate.m
WeII, you´re here now,
and that´s aII that matters.
You're not worthy of him.
You've lost your child! You're a whore.
You're a whore!f
You deserted him!.
Excuse me. You seem to be putting me
in the position of defendant. I was given
to understand that Anna decIines a
divorce if I insist on keeping the boy.
I repIied to her in that sense
and considered the matter cIosed.
AIexei AIexandrovich,
you are a good man.
Put yourself in
her position for a moment.
She´s moved to Moscow.r
She´s been there 6 months now,
each day expecting your decision.
I´m a beIiever now. I can´t go against the
teachings of Christianity in such a matter.
Why, divorce is sanctioned,
even by the church.c
I must think it over.d
I must seek guidance.s
What do I see?n
Ah, Yes. That´s right.o
We must go away.
I Iong to be in the country,
and there´s nothing
to keep you here, is there?
-My one wish is to get away.
-You know, it came over me Iike an
absoIute inspiration. Why shouId we
go on waiting here for the divorce?
I´ve made up my mind that it
shan´t infIuence my Iife anymore.
-Do you agree?
-Oh, yes..
WeII, how was
your dinner party?l
Oh, the dinner
was first-rate
and the boat race
and aII that quite enjoyabIe.
WeII, when are we off?i
The sooner the better.a
We can´t get off
tomorrow, I´m afraid,
but we couId be ready
the day after.
Oh, no. Wait a moment.a
The day after tomorrow is Sunday,
and I have to see mama.
-You couId go there tomorrow.
- No, I´m going there on business
to do with the power of attorney,
and the money won´t be ready tomorrow.
In that case, then,
we won´t go at aII.
I won´t go any Iater!
Monday or not at aII!n
Why? There´s
no sense in that..
You see no sense in it because...
because you care
nothing for me.s
You seem unabIe
to see my position.
How do you think I feeI
cooped up in these rooms?
But you are free.
Yes, you are free,
and if you don´t Iove me anymore, that
wouId be better and more honest to say so.
Oh, reaIIy! This
is becoming unbearabIe!e
Why do you try my patience?
It has its Iimits.
What do you mean
by that?f
I mean...e
I mean, weII,
what do you want of me?g
What I want is that you shouId not desert
me as you are thinking of doing.
No. I don´t want that.
what I want is your Iove,
but it has gone,
so it is aII over.e
Wait. Wait. Wait!
What is this aII about?
I said that me must put off our departure
for a matter of 3 days,
and you, Anna, sit by accusing me of
Iying and being dishonorabIe.
It is a matter of compIete indifference to me
what your mother thinks and whom she
wants to marry you to.t
But we´re not taIking
about that.
PreciseIy about that!n
I know aII about that
IittIe princess Sorokina,
and Iet me teII you,
a heartIess woman..
Be she oId or not oId, your mother or
anyone eIse is of no consequence to me,
and I do not want to have
anything to do with her.
I wiII not have you speak
disrespectfuIIy of my mother.
There´s a Iimit
to my endurance.a
Why didn´t I die?í
Mashka is going
to eat your banana!n
Who is that teIegram from?
-It´s from Stiva.
-Can I see it?e
It is addressed to me.m
What secrets
can Stiva have from me?
I don´t want you to see it because
Stiva has a passion for wiring.
Why teIegraph
when nothing is settIed?
He wires:.
could get nothing out of him.
Promises definite answer soon.
Read it yourself.e
Little hope, and l'll do everything
possible and impossible.
I don´t care about
the divorce anymore,
And there was not the sIightest
necessity to hide this from me.
I just want things
to be definite.l
I am sure your irritabiIity is due to
the uncertainty of your position.
And why did princess Sorokina
deIiver this teIegram?!
She did not.t
This arrived earIier
whiIe you were sIeeping.a
Princess Sorokina came with the money
and the documents from my mother.
I couIdn´t get them
yesterday.c
I didn´t want anything
to deIay our departure.?
By the way,r
we are definiteIy
going tomorrow, aren´t we?
You are...
but not me.
Ana, we can´t
go on Iike this.a
You are, but not I!
This is intoIerabIe!ã
You wiII be sorry
for this.
God,
forgive me everything.
I have here...n
the Iatest dispatch...
from the front!
The infideI musIims
have been driven back!
We russians...r
have flown to helpr
our Serbian Slavonic brothers,
our fellow Christians!a
Count Vronsky.ç
Perhaps you´d rather not have seen me.
If so, pIease don´t hesitate to say.
I can aIways find
another compartment.
No. PIease.o
The Serbian war
is a blessing for me.
As a man I have the merit that my
Iife is of no vaIue to me.
I´m gIad there´s something for which I may
Iay down the Iife which isn´t simpIy useIess,
but Ioathsome to me.o
Anyone is weIcome to it.g
I know the dreadfuI
thing you have suffered,
But I beg you not to continue
on this course you are foIIowing.
I am doing my duty
as a Russian...a
and a Christian.a
PIease, hear me out.
I saw your Iady onIy once.s
l wish l'd spoKen up then,
but l did not.
which is why l cannot
remain silent now.
Ever since the death
of my brother,ã
aII I have been searching for are
answers to questions Iike,
´´what am I?´´ , ´´why am I here?´´
"What am l living for?"a
When, suddenly,
it all became clear to me.
l'd been living on spiritual truths
that l'd drunK in with my mother's milK,
but l'd never
acKnowledged them.c
I know what is right and wrong.
I wasn´t taught this..
It was given to me, as it is to everyone.
I discovered nothing.
I mereIy opened my eyes
to what I knew.t
For me it is too Iate.i
As a man, I am finished. As a weapon,
I may be of some use.
Don´t think iII of me.
I have Iost too much.d
AII I ask is to be abIe
to remember Anna as she once was...
when I first met her.e
I try to bring back
those moments, but I cannot.r
l cannot
see her face.m
l can only see her
laid oute
in the railway shed
where they tooK her.
She was...a
This newfeeling
has not changed me.m
lt has not made me happy
and enlightened all of a sudden
as l dreamed it would.p
just liKe the way it was with
my feeling for my son.
-Come to the nursery at once.
-Is something wrong with Mitya?
There was no surprise
about this, either.
-What´s going on?
-Mitya wants to see you.
But be it faith or not.
l don't Know what it is.
Through suffering, this feeling has crept
just as imperceptibly into my heart.
He knows me.
and has lodged
itself firmly there.n
l shall still be unable to understand
with my reason why l pray,
and l shall
still go on praying.l
But my llfe now...n
my whole llfe... independent of
anything that can happen to me,
every minute of it is no longer
meaningless as it was before,
but has a positive meaning
of goodnesst
with which l have
the power to invest it.e
Lev ToIstoy.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org