Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Listen to me.
What are we talkin' about, really?
Getting high? No.
We're talking about a journey, man.
A subconscious safari. A mental
expedition, okay? A mind trek.
This planet has been raped,
pillaged and fucked, all right?
And the mind is-is the only
uncharted territory.
And this shit is the ship. It's the Nina,
the Pinta and the Santa Maria,
and you are fuckin' Magellan.
Oh, fuck! I spilled some!
So what do you say,
my Serbian motherfuckin' friend?
Do you wanna take a trip,
or do you wanna sit on your ass?
Okay, Napoleon,
let's see what you got.
Robi.
That dog is really creeping me out.
It's a big fuckin' dog. It makes my girl
very uneasy. I don't really like dogs.
The pooch was not invited.
You don't talk about my fuckin' dog,
okay? I'll handle it.
Can you tie it up or something?
He'll do what I say.
Once I show him who's boss
with a few treats and some smacks.
Good boy. Here's treat.
He knows who's boss, yes?
Shit, man!
Hey, hey, I got a dog too.
Yo, Tony.! I love this guy.
He works his ass off for piss.
All right, once I show him who's boss
with some few smacks and some treatsies.
- You got that? You got a smoke?
- No, no. I'm fuckin' out. I told you.
- Are you giving me some static?
- No.
Huh? You giving me the hairy eyeball?
You Irish fucking pig!
Fuck, man! See? Whoo!
I got my dog too.
Here you go, dog.
- Are you guys in? Are you in?
- Fuck you!
- What's your fucking lackey saying?
- He say that he knows your dog.
- My dog?
- He say that your dog testify at his brother's trial three years ago.
- Oh, shit.
- He also say that your dog is not even a fucking dog.
He's a dirty, fucking pig!
And I believe him.
God!
- Fuck! Call for backup! Call for backup!
- Unit 17 requesting backup.
- Fuck!
- Fourth floor, one suspect.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm all right. Come on!
Good dog. Good dog.
Shit! Shit!
All right, Coral, take that
back stairwell there. Got it.
Tony, come on. Come on.
Oh, shit. Okay.
You take this hallway on the right.
All right.
I'll take the left.
Gotcha.
Can you believe
that cocksucker shot me?
Shit.! Shit.!
Tony! Tony?
Ah, shit! Ah!
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Officer down!
I repeat: Officer down!
Suspect on north stairway!
I'm going after him!
And where the fuck is my backup!
Freeze! Shit!
Shit. Shit. Shit. Help me!
I'm a police officer! Help me!
Call an ambulance!
Shit! Shit! Call an ambulance!
Shit!
Hello? Yeah. Shit, yeah.
No. No, no, I'm up. I'm up.
I'll be right there. All right. Bye.
Mornin', buddy.
Come here, shithead.
Come here.
Good morning.
Ohh!
It's cold, people. Detroit's
gonna have a white New Year's this year,
because we're getting hit with
yet another storm. No shit!
Sports comin' up.
#In the lane, snow is glistening #
#A beautiful sight
We're happy tonight #
This kind of sex
is evolutionary instinct, gentlemen.
Example: Tiger Stadium.
Bleachers empty, except me and a friend.
We always get it on
whenever and wherever we can.
No one saw us
except for the left fielder.
Let's just say he enjoyed the show,
and I didn't mind the audience.
Impulsive sex is in our genes, boys.
Don't deny yourselves.
I gotta go jump in the snow
to cool my shit off.
- Have a good New Year, I.
- You too, babe.
That animal was your type, Iris.
Probably an ex-con.
- You two should hook up.
- Fuck off, Carlyle.
We were just talking about acting
on impulses with no guilt.
Don't get angry, I. You only bed
criminals. Everyone knows that.
Which is unfortunate for me,
because I am in love with you.
I don't bed criminals.
I fuck bad boys. Big difference.
I just hope I don't have to become
a fuckin' ax murderer to prove I'm worthy.
What the hell is this? Fun and games?
- Buzzkill.
- Does anybody work around here anymore?
Hey, Sarge. You're late.
Happy New Year.
Hey, you're pissing me off. Get outta here
before I give you something to do.
You boys don't wanna get stuck
with us here tonight. Bye, boys.
I'll see you guys at the new precinct.
Happy New Year, Iris.
Later, Iris. Stuck.
That's not very nice, boss.
You're right. I apologize.
You're lovely and amazing,
and it's my honor
to spend New Year's Eve with you.
You're a sarcastic prick, aren't you? We
are going to have a good time tonight, boss.
We officially shut down at midnight,
but all calls are being diverted,
so we might as well be closed now.
We could start gettin' fucked up
real early!
All right, but not too early, all right?
We still gotta pack this shit up.
Not much. All the computers
are gone. Most of the gear.
Now, come on, Sarge.
It's my favorite holiday.
I even put on my very special,
sexy holiday boots.
Even though we're here,
I wanna do it right.
How could you possibly
do it wrong?
# We will conspire #
#As we dream by the fire #
# To face unafraid #
# The plans that we made #
# Walkin' in a winter wonderland ##
Never take for
granted the greatest power of all...
the power to choose.
Consider the choices
you have made in the past.
And when they led you astray,
faith in times of opposition...
will lead to your salvation,
or often the easy way
will lead only to temptation.
Think of consequences...
and cherish your power
to choose the righteous path.
You figure I'd be more liable
to tell the truth with God watchin'.
If you believe in God, Mr. Portnow.
You don't? I never met a brother
who didn't have faith.
I've stood in front of dozens of men...
who were all staring death in the face.
Every single one of them
begged for God's help.
After seeing all those pleas
go unanswered,
I... lost my faith.
So what's the what?
My answer... is this.
No.
I guess we're done here.
What'd you think? I was gonna let you walk outta
here with the crowd for protection? Get the fuck up.
Walk in front of me.
#Amazing grace #
#How sweet the sound #
#That saved a wretch #
# Like me #
Police.!
Hold it right there!
Freeze, Bishop! Drop your weapon!
Drop it now, motherfucker!
We're here at the new Precinct 21,
where one of the city's most powerful
crime figures, Marion Bishop,
is being held in the alleged murder
of an undercover police officer.
Move back! Bishop, notorious
for his brutal execution methods,
earns untold millions
from his various criminal operations...
in the Detroit area.
Bishop's crew.
Yeah?
Now is not the time.
I'm Lieutenant Holloway.
Marcus Duvall, Organized Crime
and Racketeering squad.
This is my team.
I know who you are.
Sorry about your man.
Where is this son of a bitch?
I don't spend one night,
not one night, inside,
and we both know why.
You do whatever you have to do
to get me out of here.
Do you understand?
That guy's a cop killer.
Judge hands down bail,
I swear to Christ I'll...
No arraignment 'cause of the holiday.
Bishop spends two days inside
until he has a chance to make bail.
Don't worry, Cap. We got him.
We ain't gonna fuckin' let him go.
Happy New Year!
Come on, man.
There's only three of us here.
Yeah, well, one of us is Irish.
My God, look at this thing.
It's gotta be older than me.
You'll never take me alive, G-man!
Look at this room.
Boy, there's gotta be evidence in here
from some of my first busts back in the day.
Uh, they got rid of all
the Civil War stuff. Oh, ho!
Hey, that's so funny.
Don't quit the day job, all right?
Sarge?
Yeah?
Friday appointment's here.
Are you kiddin' me?
Any feelings of anxiety lately?
Yeah. Two words. The Lions.
They give me a lot of anxiety.
Please stop avoiding
my questions, Sergeant.
Are you still taking
the painkillers?
Come on, Doc.
I mean, even you have got to be getting
a little bored of these conversations.
Why don't we talk
about the real reason...
that you would come down here
on New Year's Eve...
in the middle of this storm.
Okay. Uh, let's see.
We had an appointment.
I think the real reason...
is you're in love with me.
Huh. Interesting.
I can see it in your eyes.
That's why you come
wearing these fancy clothes.
It's very flattering,
but I think you should stop
denying it, you know?
I hear... No, I hear you.
You're right. You're right.
You're right.
My face obviously betrays me.
I didn't get dressed up like this because I'm
going to a New Year's Eve party later tonight.
Oh, no. No, Sergeant.
This was all for you.
A form of seduction.
Is it working?
Wonderfully.
I'm glad.
Okay, well, we'll have to finish
this conversation another time.
What is this thing
here? Hey, hey, hey, hey!
That's mine. All right, relax.
I don't care about the file.
So, uh, you got a desk job
at Precinct 21, I see.
You don't quit, do you?
How do you feel about it?
How do I feel about it?
It's no big change.
So I guess the new year's
not bringing anything different for you.
How's your leg, by the way?
I noticed you weren't limping anymore.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It's just an observation.
Five years of undercover work,
and now this. Wow!
Good-bye.
You must be itching to get back on
the streets. Good-bye. Happy New Year.
Happy New Year to you. I'll see you at the
new precinct. God, you know, I cannot wait.
I'd walk you out, you know,
but I just have so much...
I know the way. Thank you.
So much to do.
Jake, you should see this.
And now Lieutenant Marcus Duvall...
that's Officer Ray Portnow's superior...
is coming out of...
Hey, that's Duvall.
Good cop. Good man.
Crime
kingpin Marion Bishop in custody.
That man is in hell right now.
...responsible for the slaying,
the fifth in Motor City this year alone.
Hey, you okay, Jake?
Everybody in the bus.
You know what a bus looks like.
New Year's Eve in a house
of a thousand doors. How about that?
Huh? You'll be sittin'
in that cell of yours.
You're gonna want some "cham-pag-ne,"
and you're not gonna get any. No.
No "Dick Clark's
Happy Rockin' New Year's Eve. "
Losers.
I ain't no loser, baby, a'ight.
I'm just tryin' to exist 'cause my people lack the
power to consume what the media emphasizes in society.
So I'm forced to take shit that
ain't mine. Beck, your eyes are red.
You been snortin'? You been drinkin'? Your
eyes look glazed. You been eatin' doughnuts?
That's funny. Think
that's funny, motherfucker?
What'd you read that in? A comic
book?
Get in the fuckin' back.
Round 'em up!
# You're nobody
till somebody loves you #
Well, we won't need that anymore.
All right, boys and girls.
We must raise our glasses in a toast.
A toast to this old shit-hole
before they tear it down.
I got a terrible feeling
I'm gonna miss this place.
Not as much as I'm gonna miss you
two. What are you talkin' about?
I have news, boys and girls.
Old school here is retiring.
You're kidding.
I'm packin' it in.
- Just like this place.
- Congratulations, Jasper. Why didn't you tell us?
I just got the word officially.
Anyway, here's to this old shit-hole.
Here's to me,
and here's to my new life.
Huh?
Cheers.
And now, little lady,
may I have this dance?
To celebrate
my retirement, huh?
Come on. Oh.
Don't go away.
Maybe you'll learn something.
#The world still is the same #
# You'll never change it #
#As sure as the stars #
#Shine above #
# You're nobody #
# Till somebody loves you #
One more. There you go.
#So find yourself someone... ##
We never should've left in this shit.
Ah, shit. You mean their captain
didn't want these scumbags in there?
Wanted to give his men
more time off for the holiday.
Marion Bishop. Marion Bishop.
Chief, head cheddar
and whatnot, baby.
You know, I heard... I heard about you
getting shot five times, man.
Five fuckin' times! What was it... your left shoulder,
your stomach, upper back, lower back, right hip?
Ain't that a bitch?
You didn't wanna die, though, right?
'Cause you're a persistent motherfucker.
You're like the black Rasputin and whatnot.
Serious, man.
Um, let me introduce myself.
My-My name is Beck.
I'm an entrepreneurial motherfucker
like yourself, slash lawyer, slash...
Got any openings, man?
Throw me a bone or somethin'?
Yo, pump the brakes! Don't slam 'em!
- Shut the fuck up!
- Hey, Ray Charles! Slow this motherfucker down, man!
Officer Balls and Officer Cock.
Psst. Psst. Eye contact, man.
Eye contact. Let
me tell you somethin'.
The Constitution requires
that the state provide secure...
- Sit down. - Incarceration. I'm-I'm just
sayin' that I'm feelin' pretty fuckin' unsafe.
- Shut the fuck up.
- Transport 1121, this is Dispatch.
Transport 1121, Dispatch. Go.
We're gonna have to reroute
you to Precinct 13 until the storm breaks.
No problem.
What's goin' on, Dispatch?
There was an injury accident
on the Parkway 101.
We're gettin' everyone off the road.
You'll stay at 13 until further orders.
They've already been advised.
Copy.
Thirteen. What a piece of shit.
I don't care.
I'll be glad to get out of this.
Well, how about
this for a New Year's present?
That scumbag Bishop
is hand-delivered to us!
- I'm gonna get some righteous payback from that skel for Ray Portnow.
- What are you doin' here?
What? I've heard so much about this
Bishop guy over the years. I wanna see him.
I thought you gave up bad boys.
Get back inside.
It's not the new year yet, Sarge.
You must be Roenick. No offense, Officer,
but I'm pretty fuckin' perturbed about this.
We're closing down.
We're short-staffed.
Central said we park here overnight
until the road's clear.
You got a problem with that, call in.
I tried. I'll give it another shot.
Jake, come on. You're not gonna send these
guys back out in that weather. Nah. Now, look.
We'll lock 'em up,
and we'll let 'em be. No problem.
All right, fine.
But they're your responsibility.
I don't wanna hear jack shit
about them or from them.
- Let's go inside.
- Bring 'em in.! Come on. Bring 'em in.!
Interesting cast.
Yeah, we got a female gangbanger...
who swears she never
committed a crime in her life.
This guy here specializes
in counterfeit merchandise.
Need a fake Rolex, he's your man.
Some junkie who robbed a deli.
- Allegedly.
He's still ridin' on a high right now.
And the star of the show.
He needs no intro.
You know his credits.
Sarge, when it rains, it snows.
Got another freakin' guest.
How's your car?
Won't move. Must've walked
two miles in this damn weather.
I'm soaking. Look at me.
Well, thank God you're not hurt.
So how did you enjoy your file?
Oh, yeah, yeah. You dropped this.
Oh, really? I dropped it? That's strange,
because I was sure that you took it.
Definitely dropped it.
That's disappointing.
If you had stolen it,
it would've been the first time...
you were taking a proactive
interest in your therapy.
- You know it's a bunch of bullshit.
- So you read it.
Yeah, I fuckin' read it.
Did you steal it?
You know I stole it, all right?
And stop being so goddamn happy
about it, Dr. Sabian.
It makes me sick.
"I think he's hiding behind his injury.
He's not really hurt.
Jake Roenick no longer
considers himself a cop. "
What kind of bullshit is that? Huh?
You think I'm scared?
That's what it is, right?
If you'd read further on,
you would see that's not what I think.
All right, well, then tell me what it is
that you think, Dr. Mrs. Mind-Fuck.
What is it that
you think I'm hiding from?
I'm not gonna explain myself to you if
you're gonna act like a child. Excuse me.
Run away. We both know you can't handle
this shit, 'cause you want to fuck me.
Sergeant, if I wanted to fuck you,
it would've happened already.
Gotta learn to control yourself, Doc. It's
affecting your work. It's very unprofessional.
Don't try to discredit me
because you're afraid I may be right.
Right?
Yes.
About what? Come on. Tell me
what it is you think I'm hiding from,
and then I'll tell you
whether I think you're right.
Okay! I believe that the prospect
of responsibility has rendered you impotent!
Impotent?
Yes!
And that's why you're working
at this old precinct behind a desk.
I'm injured, all right?
That's why I'm here. Bullshit!
You feel responsible for the death of your team
eight months ago, and that's why you're here.
I didn't do anything wrong.
A board of inquiry cleared me.
That's right.
You didn't do anything wrong.
But it was your decision that sent them
down the left hallway...
and not the right,
out the front door and not the back.
And you don't want to make
decisions like that again.
Yeah. So? Maybe you're right.
What? You want a medal?
So now you're hiding
behind that desk.
And behind that liquor
in your drawer...
and those... pills
in that stupid little matchbox.
But there's still one life you're
responsible for, no matter where you go.
- Oh, let me guess. My own?
- Yeah, your own.
And if you don't start taking care of yourself,
you're never gonna be the cop you used to be.
Bish.
Bish. Bishop.
Bish, Bish, Bish, Bish,
Bish, Bish, Bish, Bish!
Hi.
Yo, Bish, Bish. Just check it out.
Check it out, man.
Puerto Rican guy and a black guy
in a car. Who's drivin'?
The cops.
You're killin'
me, man. You're killin' me.
That was... That was...
We had somethin'.
Did you feel that?
All right.
This jail shit ain't for Smiley.
This is definitely
out of Smiley's essence.
Who the fuck is Smiley?
I'm Smiley. Me. I'm Smiley.
Look, I'm facing a lot of jail time here.
I didn't do shit
to be up in this bitch.
They lookin' for my sister,
and they picked me up.
I ain't never committed a crime
in my motherfuckin' life!
#Nothin' but the best
is good enough for me #
#I like to eat lobster #
#Directly from Maine #
## Are you
still waiting for that tow truck?
- #In sunny old Spain #
- It's not gonna come.
Oh, shit. It's almost time, people.
#Bish, Bish, bo-Bish
Banana-fanna-fo-fish #
#Fee-fi-mo-mi-ish #
# Bish, Bish ##
How you get in the life, man?
For me it was I wanted this bicycle.
I was always prayin' for it, right?
And God, in all his wisdom,
decided not to give it to me,
so I stole it, and then I asked him
to forgive me after that.
But that was the beginning, man.
I could never stop after that shit.
That was... It was over for me.
Right.
Okay. Twenty, 19,
18, 17, 16, 15,
14, 13, 12, 11,
10, nine, eight, seven, Listen
to them trying to demoralize us.
Six, five, four,
three, two, one.! Happy New Year!
You gonna do it?
I'm doin' it. I'm doin' it.
#Should auld acquaintance be forgot #
#And never brought to mind #
Look at him.
All jacked up and shit,
sweatin' out his fuckin' ass.
Lookin' like fuckin' Mike Tyson
in a spellin' bee.
Hey, you slanderin' me?
You slanderin' me?
I'll give you some free advice. Don't.
Yo, why don't you leave her alone, you
fuckin' junkie! Leave her the fuck alone!
- Who's talkin' to you, man?
- Yeah, but I'm talkin' to you. So what's the problem?
What was that?
You heard me.
Who the fuck you pushin', man?
I'll slap the smack outta you!
Happy New Year.
That's it, you bitch-ass punk!
I'll fuck you up.!
Hey! Hey, you fuckin' animals!
What the hell!
- What the fuck?
- Oh, shit.! What's that?
- Shit!
- You monkeys keep it down, for Christ's sake.
Hey, stop yelling; you fuckin' animals.!
It's only New Year's...
Who the fuck are you?
What's goin’ on down there?
- Rosy!
- I'm all right.
Are you all right?
Stay with him. Stay with him.
Open this! Get us outta here!
Get us outta here!
- Let us out of here, man.!
- Iris, get in here! Get in here!
What the fuck is goin' on!
Son of a bitch!
Just keep breathing!
What the hell is going on!
Shit.
Ow! Man!
Come on!
Come on.!
Hang on.! Goddamn it.!
Rosy, yeah, that's right.
Love... Talk to me,
goddamn it! Talk to me!
Keep breathing, goddamn it! Rosy!
Iris.! Iris.!
- How is he? Is he all right?
- "Is he all right?" He's dead, for Christ's sake!
That's how all right he is!
Goddamn it! Fucking Bishop!
They're tryin' to bust him outta here.!
You son of a bitch.!
Get us outta here.! Come on.!
All right, relax! Relax!
The threat is over!
Look, get us outta here!
Get us outta here!
Shit! Calm down!
The threat is over!
You fuckin' kidding me, Sergeant?
I know. I know. Shh.
How's he doin; Iris?
I'm sorry about your partner.
We just moved him to an office.
Oh, shit.
He needs a doctor fast.
Why wasn't there an alarm
on your back door?
That alarm hasn't worked in months.
They're still out there.
Some kind of a truck out there
in the forest. It's not moving.
Are you kidding me? They must
have assumed we'd call for backup.
I'm having a little problem here.
The phones aren't working.
Sure, they cut the wires. The
storm could've taken the phones out.
Bullshit! Those are Bishop's guys
out there. They cut the wires.
Just try the radios! Forget
it. Frequencies are blocked.
The frequencies are blocked?
That's not easy to do.
Well, they must've got professional help,
because all the frequencies are blocked.
They probably screwed up
your cell phones too.
I'm not getting a signal.
Neither am I.
What the hell is this!
I told you!
They're Bishop's guys out there!
They're gonna break him outta here
one way or another.
Maybe somebody heard the gunshots
and will come check it out.
There's nothing out there but factories.
No, no. I don't buy any of that.
They, whoever they are, are gone.
They're gonna think they're fireworks.
They don't give a shit about me, and I'm going! Thank you.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What the hell is happening here? This is a fucking
police precinct, for God's sake! Jesus Christ!
Sarge, if you're all right,
you better take a look at this.
They're surrounding the place.
It's a goddamn siege.
I am not supposed to be here.
- Shit!
- Cease fire! Cease fire! Cease fire!
- It wasn't gunshots.
- Bishop.!
I told you. Those are
Bishop's troops out there.
They're taking him outta here
tonight, no matter what.!
This doesn't make any sense.
This is a police precinct!
Shut the fuck up, Doc.
You said that already.
All right, look.
Everybody just listen up.
Maybe they're trying
to give us a way out of this.
Let's just give them what they want.
Let 'em have Bishop, and it's all over.
- Nobody else gets hurt.!
- Not a bad fuckin' idea.
No, we can't let that scumbag gangster,
a cop killer, walk out of our precinct!
It's not an option! I'm
trying to defuse this situation.
- You got a wounded cop over there!
- I already said no!
What in God's name
are we supposed to do then, Sergeant?
- They're gettin' ready to storm the fort.
- I don't think so, all right?
I think they're just tryin'
to scare us into giving up Bishop.
They're doin' a damn good job.
See, this blackout, this is the kind of shit
that deflates human smugness...
about government's
so-called miraculous technologies.
Doesn't it? Shove it up their
lyin' corporate fuckin' asses.
This ain't no blackout, junkie.
Something suspect is goin' on.
I wanna know what the funk it is.
I know it hurts, but we
gotta get you away from these windows.
Jasper, you got those flashlights?
I don't know where the fuck the are.!
Everything's been packed.! Roenick!
Get down! Get down!
Jasper, get the blinds!
All right. All right.
Yeah, we're perfectly safe now.
These are just scare tactics, all right?
They don't know how much firepower
we have or don't have.
They're not gonna come in here again.
It's too risky.
What about us
gettin' out there, Sergeant?
L-I need help real bad.
I need it.
Let's barricade up
these doors and windows,
and I'll figure out
how to get some help in here.
What are you doing this for, Jake? Nobody
gives a shit anymore about anything.
We can end this right now. I can't
let a murderer walk out of here.
I can't do that.
I'll get us out of this, Jasper.
I will. I promise.
You got almost no chance
out there, buddy.
That cop in there dies if I don't try.
You keep the place locked down
until I get some help.
All right.
I'd better cover from the front windows.
I can see the truck better from there.
Keep your head down.
Schmuck.
Oh, shit!
Oh, shit.!
I found this on our friend out there.
Fuck it. Fact or fiction? You pulled
a guy's spine out once, didn't you?
Are you a surgeon?
I heard that bullet you took in your belly
is still lodged in there, rattling around.
I bet you it's causing you a lot of
intestinal issues. Right? Right, man?
Bishop, I need to talk to you.
So I just killed a man.
His name was Danny Barbero.
A cop.
A cop who works for Ray Portnow.
The man you killed.
So tell me why cops are risking
their lives to get to you, Bishop.
Why should I answer that question?
Because I'm thinking about sending you out to
the wolves and saving my own ass if you don't.
I assume you know
who I am, Sergeant.
You're a scumbag gangster.
And one of my scumbag partners in crime
is your fellow officer, Marcus Duvall.
Marcus Duvall and his entire team.
We used to split things 50-50.
Marcus got greedy. He wanted more.
- So you killed Ray Portnow.
- After he tried to kill me.
Mm. Right.
They're here to execute me,
because if I make it to court,
every single one of them goes to jail
for the rest of their days.
How many cops
are involved in this?
I can't say exactly, but the blood money
runs through your entire department.
I bet they're all here now, and they can't
allow me to leave this precinct alive.
They can't allow any of us
to leave here alive.
Now that we all know
it's them out there.
Sarge.
Poor guy, he never had a chance.
Anyone know if he had any family?
Someone's coming.!
Shit, someone's coming.!
- Someone's coming.
- Hit squad, Sergeant.
They're here for all of us.
Me?
All of us. You especially.
Fuck you, dealer.
This is all your fault.
Those are your brethren
out there, old man, not mine.
Don't compare me with your scumbag friends out there.
If it was up to me, I'd kick your ass out the door.
- I'd like to see you come try.
- Yeah, sure. You'd love to kill another cop today, wouldn't you?
Only you.
They'll be coming on strong now.
Why? Why are cops
coming to kill us?
They need to kill him
before he fingers them in court.
They need to kill us too,
now that we know it's them.
So... here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna take positions
all around the precinct,
and we're gonna hold 'em off
until dawn.
Iris, Alex, you know
how to use a firearm?
No. No.
Why don't you give me
one of them guns, Sergeant.
I'll help you fend off the black hats.
Oh. Oh, shit. Men are here.
Good.
What a fuckin' mess this is.
I know.
I'm lookin' at this as a matter
of simple mathematics.
If we walk
and those eight people survive,
then 33 lives are destroyed.
The lives of my men
and their families.
People I'm responsible for.
People I...
People I love.
I don't see any other way, Marcus.
The blood trail leads right back to us.
We have no choice.
If we go through this,
we are gonna have to live with this
for the rest of our lives.
But you know something, Mike?
I could live with that
more than I could live with a cell mate.
Once we step outside,
those people are no longer
civilians or cops.
We gotta put 'em all down.
Without pause, without regard.
1,024. 2,048.
Um, 4,096.
Obsessive-compulsive disorder.
The complex problems
force me to concentrate,
neutralizing any feelings of fear
I have at a given moment.
I hide behind its structure.
You're gonna be all right, Doc.
We don't know that.
Don't know that. You're so calm.
Thank you so much. Thanks.
You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do. I do.
If I'm gonna die,
at least I should die gracefully.
How are you keeping it together?
I just think about living.
I want to live,
as opposed to
I don't want to die.
That, and I keep telling myself
everybody's gonna make it this time.
We both know what
could happen here, Sergeant.
Safety off.
Yeah. Right.
All right! Wake up!
Wake up! Wake up!
- All right, already.
- Come on. Get up.
Oh, come on.
Look, uh, here's the deal.
Those men that came in here...
they're still outside.
And... I have no idea
how many there are...
or what they're prepared to do.
Don't sweat it. There's nothin' you
can do. You can't stop Bishop's people.
Go ahead, Sergeant. Tell them.
They're not Bishop's people.
They are police officers.
What! "Po-po" popping each other?
This is the fuckingest shit I ever seen.
This ain't Smiley's fight, man.
Let Smiley go. Let me go.
I totally figured it out.
Assassination politics, right?
By the government-sanctioned thugs
abusing their authority again, man.
Who's gonna save us from your
corrupt brethren, Sarge? You?
You?
I'm gonna do my best to protect you.
All right? All of you.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
I feel real safe, man.
Fuck!
What the fuck is goin' on now?
Get down!
Fuck!
- Fuck!
- They blew out the fuckin' window!
Cover the front.
I'll be right back.
- The window, Sergeant! The window!
- Look out.! Look out.!
- Shoot him again.! Shoot him again.!
- Shoot him.! He's not dead.!
Man down. Denied entry.
You gotta get us outta here, man. Smiley feels very
fuckin' unsafe. It's scary. I'm scared to death.
You can't use us as fuckin' live bait.
Come on. Think about it. We're hostages.
I know. They're gonna come
for us. Come on, man. Come on.
- You can't do that. Think about it.
- Please. Come on, man.
- You can't leave us here as fuckin' animals to fuckin' die.!
- Smiley's scared shitless, man.
Please. We're sittin' ducks here.
Come on. Don't leave us like this, man.
All right, choose a weapon.
Anything you see.
Tell me again why we should help
your little skinny white ass?
'Cause if you don't, you'll die.
No resistance. Advancing
to the front door. We're going in.
Spread out across the
precinct. Stop anything that approaches.
- We might make it through this night.
- Christ Almighty. What are you doin'?
- You can't trust these people.
- What the hell are you doin'? You're supposed to be coverin' the front. Goddamn it!
Come on.
430.
13,760.
All right. Just hold the front.
And don't move this time!
508.
You fucker!
You make me your defendant, you
son of a bitch! Make me set bail!
- You all right?
- I feel better. I'm better.
I got mine, baby.
Oh, yeah.
Come on, you motherfuckers!
Come on! Run!
Come on.
Come on. Yeah.
There you go, secretary.
Jesus Christ.
All right!
They're pullin' back!
You all right?
He saved me.
There's nobody out there in the front.
Them motherfuckers runnin' scared.
All right. All right. I drove
'em back, baby. I drove 'em back.
We're gonna have a red-raw revolution
on our hands, man. All right. Good job.
Good job. Good job.
Maybe they'll leave for fucking good
now. They're not going anywhere.
- Put that goddamn weapon down.
- J...
Old man, you do not
wanna point that weapon at me.
That is not a bright thing to do.
Put that goddamn weapon down slowly, then back away from it, all of ya.!
Jake, get their weapons.
Take their weapons.
Ain't this a bitch. We saved your
asses. Now you wanna turn on us?
Yeah, well, thank you for that, sweet
cheeks. Now, put your weapon down.
The problem is outside, not inside.
Put the gun down, Jasper.
No, no. You know what the problem is?
That we criminals got rights, baby.
That's right. We got rights to be protected
against assault under any circumstances.
- If you can't provide that, well, fuck you... we will.
- You're a fuckin' psycho.
Jesus Christ, Jake! What? Are
you gonna trust these freaks?
Huh? The first chance they get to blow our
brains out, they'll try to make a break for it.
They need us as much
as we need them.
We all gotta start trusting each other right
now if we're gonna make it through this night.
Put the gun down,
Jasper.
Put the goddamn gun down!
What?
- Shit.
- All right. All right.
Now, let's all introduce ourselves to each other.
It's New Year's Eve. Let's turn over a new leaf.
All right. Let's not
all fuckin' speak at once.
The name's Smiley.
I'm a Libra, and...
I'll handle these jokers.
You handle your people,
maybe we get out of here tonight.
He armed his prisoners.
It's a smart play.
Must be at least eight guns
in there now.
Just a couple hours till the sun's up.
If we can't breach, what do we do?
Get the A.V. -5 here.
Are you sure about that?
Yep. I'm not takin'
any more chances.
It's gonna take
a while in this weather.
Marcus? What the fuck do we do
if it doesn't arrive in time?
We'll have to think of some
other way of ending this.
You either flirting with me or clocking
my game 'cause you don't trust me.
I don't like your beady little eyes all
over my goodies, so turn the fuck away.
You're manipulative, weak knees
and that sexy copper complexion.
You're definitely an Aries,
baby. You're pretty good.
Smiley thanks you.
We got something in common,
you know that?
You comin' down
off some shit, ain't ya?
Don't be ashamed, man.
Don't be ashamed.
What's your poison?
Seconal to bring me down.
Adderall to bring me back up.
You gotta get up to get down.
Oh, yeah, baby. Oh, yeah.
All right. That's enough.
Come on. Let's pay attention.
I want a cigarette so bad.
Stupid New Year's resolutions.
Hey, gangster,
you make any resolutions? Hmm?
What do you think,
secretary?
Oh, my God. I can't stop
thinking about sex.
I mean, I usually think
about sex a lot, but this is crazy.
Sex and death
are very closely related.
The Greeks called it Eros
and Thanatos... love and death.
Or sex as a way
of nullifying thoughts of dying.
What's your deal, gangster?
You actually been shot five times?
Six.
You really
pull a man's spine out?
It was an Adam's apple.
If you ever get
into tussles, secretary,
you grab a man
by his throat, hmm?
Dig it?
And then you squeeze.
I guarantee you he will drop. He
will not get up for quite some time.
Oh, God. It's really quiet
out there now.
Yeah.
That's what worries me.
We're not gonna make
it till morning. Marcus Duvall will not allow it.
We've got eight people covering six entry
points. If we work together, we will make it.
Look at it this way. That's me out there. You
think I'd let you survive until the morning?
- We don't have a lot of options here.
- Well, we got to figure something,
'cause I'm not gonna stay here all night
waitin' to get killed.
If you use the situation to try
and escape, it's about me and you,
'cause when this is over,
you're goin' back to jail.
- Relax, Sergeant.
- "Relax. "
This ain't about me and you.
Not yet.
- Our shit's on pause, huh?
- Yeah. Our shit's on pause.
You saved my ass back there.
Why?
Everyone in here
is my responsibility.
It's my job.
That's noble.
Unfortunately,
I don't share the sentiment.
I see a cop in jeopardy,
he's on his own,
unless it benefits me
to jump in for the save.
Listen. I don't try
to be anything I'm not.
That ain't gonna change;
I don't care what day it is.
You remember that,
Sergeant.
Hey.! Someone's comin;
Oh, God.
It's Capra, Sarge!
You know this guy?
He's a cop. He works here.
They'll execute him.
- Capra!
- Shh!
Yeah. Drive. Drive!
Oh, my God. He's gonna make it.
He still has to get by the sniper.
Come on, Capra.!
He's still moving.
They didn't get him yet.
Where are you going?
Come on. Come on.
Come on, Capra.! Come on.!
Come on!
What the fuck is goin' on?
Who's fuckin' shootin' at
us, Sarge?
Who the fuck
are all these people?
What are you doin' here, Capra?
What are you doin’ here?
It's New Year's Eve.
I knew you'd be here alone.
- I came to have a drink with Iris.
- You picked the wrong night to make your move, baby, believe me.
You know, that's really sweet.
That's really sweet, but, unfortunately,
I don't believe a fuckin' word of it.
Put that goddamn weapon down,
you psycho! He works here!
I don't care that he fuckin' works
here, man. He could be a plant.
No, Jasper. Put the gun down, all right?
Let's not start that again, all right?
He comes here in the guise of courting
that lady. It's a fuckin' ingenious plan.
They get one of their boys in here and then
take us out one by one by one. Come on. Tell 'em.
They shot at him. All right? They
shot at him. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, but they conveniently fuckin' missed,
didn't they? The act is a fuckin' charade!
Come on. Tell 'em.
He's fuckin' right, Anna.
Isn't it a fucking
charade? Do I have a gun?
Do I have a fucking gun?
I can't hurt you.
It's not fuckin' good enough, rat-bitch. Come on.
Just lock him up, man, so he doesn't do any damage.
Come on. Come on, Roenick. Listen to
me, man. We're not lockin' this man up.
Not in my precinct, all right?
I vouch for him.
Okay. Okay, I'm fuckin' sorry, but your
authority has been super-fuckin'-seded.
You understand?
You're not in charge anymore.
Right, Bish? Bish, tell 'em.
He could be one of them, man,
so fuckin' easily.
You don't think we see right through
you? Fuckin' believe that shit?
Comes in here playing that game,
playing stupid. You don't think we know?
Right, man?
Let's do the math.
Let's put him away, man,
just play it safe, you know?
Put it down. No, no, no. Come
on. Come on, man. Come on.
Just do the math. Come on. Motherfucker
comes in like that, playing...
Come here. Sergeant Roenick
is in charge. Understand?
"Yes. "
Let's go.
Only because I respect you. But I still say this
shit is fuckin' illogical bullshit, all right?
He may not be who he says he is. Just mull that
shit over. Think it over. Think it over, man.
Iris, look after Capra,
fill him in on what's goin' on.
All right, Capra? Just be cool
so no one else here gets spooked.
Everybody else,
back to your positions.
Thank you. Don't. That
was self-preservation.
The more men we have,
the better chance we stand.
Are you sure you vouch
for this man? I do.
Come with me.
You know, I hate to admit it, but Smiley
agrees with what you said back there.
Smiley want a fuckin' medal?
Hear me out, man.
Look, we're out of our shackles for what?
The last time in the next 15, 20 years?
All right, man. Get to the point.
What do you want?
Listen to me, man. Look out that
window. That's freedom, baby.
Get what I'm sayin'?
Look, maybe this New Year's can bring
something different for us after all.
Beck like Smiley now.
Eight months ago he loses
his team when a deal goes sour.
Problem with drugs and alcohol
since the incident.
Burned-out cop. Only a matter of
time before he drops his guard.
Watch the truck.
They'll eye it as a way out.
- What's the word on the A.V.?
- Storm's starting to let up, so it shouldn't be long now.
Good.
Someone gets inside,
takes off, goes for help.
It's too obvious.
We'd need a distraction.
We also need the keys. Your cop
said he dropped 'em in the snow.
- I could hot-wire a car. - I thought
you never committed a crime in your life?
- I haven't.
- Yeah.
Just picked up some shit
along the way. Whoa. Hold on.
How do we know she's not just gonna drive out of here and leave us
all here to die? Who the fuck are you, Miss Fuckin' Little Skirt?
Shake that skinny ass
in somebody else's face.
Okay, Anna. No offense, but I'll
feel better if somebody goes with you.
Maybe I should go. I promise I'll
make her get help. Scout's Honor.
It's either me or Jasper.
Can't be.
We need your guns.
It's gotta be...
Me.
- Me.
- You?
- Shoot.
- Hey, I'll go. I'll do it.
- What? It's the only thing that makes sense, right?
- Whatever.
Whatever the fuck ever.
Let's just do this. Come on.
Me and... me and the doc.
Fine. Okay.
What? It's the right move,
Sergeant. I know that.
All right. All right.
I'm the doctor, right?
Right. You can handle that? Yes.
You can?
I don't know. I don't know.
But I have to try, okay?
No. No.
Please. I have to go.
I have to do it.
Shit!
Hey! Those two skels are buggin' out,
just like I told you they would.
They torched the bus
for a diversion, I guess.
Come on!
- Aw, Jesus. They're gonna get themselves killed.
- They're dead already.
We can use this.
Very smart.
They knew we'd expect them
to make for the car.
Free life, baby! We
did it. Yeah. I told ya.
Happy New Year. Now, how are we
gonna get the fuck out of here?
Visual on two men. No shot.
Moving to a better vantage.
Hey. You sure
you wanna do this?
Yeah.
All right.
Aw, shit!
- They're fucking shooting!
- Where'd they hit you, man?
My shoulder.
Let's go! Come on! Let's
haul ass now! Okay, okay.
Go. Go.
You go.
All right. Come on.
Come on, baby. Come on.
This was not the plan, man!
This was your idea.
Come on. We're so fucking close.
Come on. I think I can still make it.
Come on, man. You can do it.
I'm on target.
Thirty-six, 45, 54, 63,
72, 81, 90, 99...
Come on, man. What am I gonna
do? What am I gonna do, man?
- Don't make me go at this alone!
- Target two blocked.
- No shot.
- Have position but no shot.
What the fuck's
up with that multiplication table shit?
Fuck you!
It's freakin' me out.
You couldn't hot-wire my
ass! You're a liar! Liar?
I will bite your little white head
right the fuck off! Forty-five, 54,
63, 72, 81, 90, 9, 18, 27, 36, 45...
What is taking so long?
I'm gonna make it for you, man!
I'm gonna do this for you!
- - Seventy-two,
81, 90, 99... - Damn, motherfucker!
What did I tell y'all?
What'd I tell you? You and your
sergeant boyfriend didn't believe me.
- What?
- Sergeant boy. That's your boyfriend, right?
- No.
- Yeah.
They made it.
They're clear!
We made it.! We made it.!
Whoo!
The skels are dead.
We don't have a goddamn chance,
do we?
Sarge. Sarge. God-fucking-damn it,
the five of us can't hold them back.
They're gonna take out each and every one
of us. What are we supposed to do, Sarge?
What are we supposed to do?
What the fuck
are we supposed to do?
I don't know.
What do you wanna
do, Marcus?
How many inside?
Uh...
A hundred.
Answer the question.
You're a brave woman.
What do you want to do
with the body, Marcus?
Bishop's men were responsible
for all this, remember?
Let's get this thing done.
Time's up, Sergeant.
Last stand.
Your gun would be appreciated.
Why did I let her go?
I know a lot about dying,
Sergeant.
There are two ways
you can handle it:
With the self-pity or without it.
Fuck you.
Get out of my office.
I see you've made your decision.
Sun's almost up.
Whatever Duvall's gonna do, he's gonna do
now. We need to get ready, or we'll be trapped.
Now, who the fuck asked you?
You know, I've had all the shit
I'm gonna take from you, old man.
- Hey, fuck you, dealer.
- No.
Fuck with me.
- I should've fucked with you...
- Enough!
Bishop's right.
Jasper, you just watch the front here.
Iris, the cell block.
Capra, you're on.
Take the back stairs.
Bishop and I'll roam,
coverin' all the other entrances.
Hey.
What were you doing by the back door? What were
you doing? What the fuck are you talking about?
I saw you. What did you tell 'em?
Why didn't you let 'em inside?
Hmm? What's the plan? Aah!
- What's goin' on?
- You were wrong. He's workin' for Duvall.
He removed the handcuffs
from the back door.
What's the plan? Answer me.!
Fuck.! I'm a fuckin' police officer.!
I don't have to fuckin' answer you.!
What's the plan, Officer?
Oh, so it's about you and me now,
huh, Sergeant?
It's not about me and
you. Not yet.
What were you doin' by the back
door, Capra? It wasn't me, Jake.
- What's the plan?
- I wasn't there.
We let 'im live once.
He almost got us killed.
We let him live twice,
we deserve to die.
You and I are friends, Jake. You gonna do this to me?
- What is the plan?
- There is no fucking plan!
- Don't make me fucking kill you!
- What the fuck are you doin' to him? Listen! They're coming!
A. V. -5, getting
into position. Ten seconds to target.
- What the fuck are they doin' up there?
- What do you think?
Save your ammo.
We don't know where they are.
We need to make a move
outside.
- That's what they'd want us to do.
- Yeah. They'll pick us off, one by one.
Jake, I found a way out!
Down in the basement.
All right, Iris, Capra.
All right. Go.
Bishop, I need you.
Come on. Come on.
- It's an old sewer tunnel.
- Why didn't you mention it before?
I didn't think of it.
We've been a little bit busy.
I don't even know where it goes.
Of course, we can always stay here.
It doesn't
matter. Good job, Jasper.
Okay. We need to move.
Fire department'll be here soon.
Here it is.
All right. It's all clear.
Everybody up.
Come on, Jasper.
Thanks.
- Son of a bitch! Jake!
- All right. Now.
Me and the secretary are going bye-bye.
You don't follow, she don't get hurt.
You lower your weapons, gentlemen,
we can end this on a happy note.
My apologies, secretary.
Apology not fuckin' accepted.
Hold it right there.! Drop
your fuckin' weapons right now.!
Down, motherfucker! Down! Goddamn it.!
Get down!
How the hell did they find us?
Oh, my God. It was Jasper at the back
door. You set us up, you motherfucker!
You just killed us, Jasper.
Fuck you, Jake!
Goddamn it. I told you, "Just let 'em have
the son of a bitch. Nobody else gets hurt. "
'Cause I ain't dyin'
for that piece of shit!
- Or for you either, Jake.
- I thought you were a cop.
Go in the truck, Jas.
You don't need to see this.
Bishop, you should've
taken that deal.
These men aren't cops, Sergeant.
They're criminals.
They're killers, just like me.
Ain't that right, old man?
Yeah, that's right. That's right.
You're goddamn right, you son of a bitch!
Not with your weapon.
Give me a clean piece. Goddamn
it! Give me a clean piece!
Close your eyes.
Let him finish it.
Oh!
Shit.! Get down.!
The truck.! The truck.! The truck.!
Go!
Get them!
You
breathin'? Good. Okay.
Oh, fuck. Fuck.
Just act like you're dead, okay?
Motherfucker!
Fuck you!
You fuckin' bitch!
Hello, Sergeant.
What the
hell are you still doin' here?
Marcus Duvall still lives.
For me, this is unacceptable.
So our shit's back on pause.
Is that it?
Yeah.
We have a problem.
Duvall and his men can see us.
We can't see them.
I'll draw their fire. Their muzzle
flashes will give away their position.
Don't miss, Bishop.
Run fast, Sergeant.
Call Roenick.
Who's Roenick?
Hurts like a bitch, doesn't it?
Call Roenick.
Tell him I'm dead.
You know me, Marcus.
I cannot tell a lie.
Look at you.
When I first approached you 10 years
ago, you couldn't look me in the eye.
One of them nervous,
God-fearin' types.
Now you put a bullet in me,
no hesitation.
You're quite the changed man
this New Year's, Marcus.
Now, for the last fucking
time, call him.
He doesn't have to.
Drop your weapon.!
- What are you waitin' for?
- Shut up!
- Put the gun down, Duvall.
- What are you gonna do? Shoot me?
- Arrest me? You gonna kill a cop?
- There's only one cop here.
Now put the goddamn gun down.
You're caught.
How many more people are you gonna
kill tonight? As many as it takes.
You make me fuckin' sick.
Aw! Aw, fuck!
Aw, fuck!
Ow.!
Uh-uh.
So it's about that time, huh?
Looks that way, don't it?
Well, thanks.
- For what?
- You didn't call my name.
That was self-preservation,
Sergeant, and it worked.
I told ya.
I'm not gonna change.
You try to follow me,
you'll find out just how true that is.
You're not gonna
get very far.
I'll manage.
Well, you take care
of yourself, Sergeant.
I will find you.
No other cop. Just me.
Jesus.
Sarge?
Sarge! Sergeant!
Yeah, Iris.
Oh, Christ. Look at you.
Shh. Shh. It's okay. I told these
firemen. They're not leavin' us alone.
Not for a second. Okay?
All right. Help me up.
Ow! Ow.
We have some questions for you, Sergeant.
I'd like to get this wound looked at first.
Anybody else out there?
No, man. There's nobody else.
Just me and... and them.
- Let me get you on a stretcher.
- No. No, man. It's all right.
I'm walkin' out of here.
Oh, geez. Do you think we have to
show up at the new precinct tomorrow?
Shit. This is fucking tempting.
No. Don't
break your resolution, huh?
Give me one.
I didn't make that promise.
You know, Sarge, I didn't
even recognize you tonight.
You were like a whole different
bad-ass motherfucker back there, huh?
Mm. You think so?
Yeah.
Well, get used to it.
Happy New Year, Sarge.
#KRS-One 'bout
to wreck the joint #
# Our scene opens up
at the edge of Detroit #
# Where the cops
go beyond the laws #
# Where enemies work together
by puttin' their shit on pause #
#So what does it mean
Assault on Precinct 13 #
# You about to see
just what the dirt brings #
#It's working
that force I have been searching #
#Laurence Fishburne
when it's time to hurt things #
#Ethan Hawke, man
He faced all that #
#I hold my mike
like Ja held the baseball bat #
#I stay ahead
like a baseball cap #
# The ways of the world
Chris don't chase all that #
# We gettin' up outta here #
# That's the stuff, that's the stuff #
# Watch me back up the truck
You livin' with a lot of fear #
# That's the stuff, yes they are # #
You're crooked cops you backin' me up #
# We gettin’ up outta here #
# That's the stuff, that's the stuff #
# Watch me back up the truck #
# You livin’ with a lot of fear #
# That's the stuff, yes they are #
#Crooked cops, you backin’ me up #
#As I walk through the street my spirit will
speak to those I meet and greet from week to week #
#I am not on my hands and feet I command to
speak as the observer inside the physique #
#Many rappers tried to compete
of course #
#But they got smashed and trashed
in the streets and tossed #
#Sometimes I think we all just lost
We just flashin' across in a disastrous course #
# We don't even know the oneness
of the only force #
#Instead of a golden calf
we got a platinum horse #
# What did Moses do
with the golden calf #
# Threw the Lord at it
and it ended in a blast #
#Master, you wanna quit
we'll run faster #
#In the background, you burnin'
'cause it's nothin' but laughter #
#I tag shirts like the shirt king
Turn up the track for Assault on Precinct 13 #
# We gettin’ up outta here #
# That's the stuff, that's the stuff #
# Watch me back up the truck
You livin’ with a lot of fear #
# That's the stuff, yes they are #
# Two crooked cops You backin’ me up #
# We gettin’ up outta here #
# That's the stuff, that's the stuff #
# Watch me back up the truck You livin’ with a
lot of fear # # That's the stuff, yes they are #
# Two crooked cops
you backin’ me up #
Cour shit's
on pause. Precinct 13.
That was self-preservation.
Thirteen.
Relax, Sergeant. Our shit's
on pause. Precinct 13.
Relax, Sergeant. Our shit's on pause.
# Wow, what an
ending what a conclusion #
# They thought they was winnin'
but they really was losin'#
#He thought he was sinnin'
but he really was provin'#
# That leadership keeps it moving
steady cruising #
# Guns up, fun's up from sunup to
sunup to sunup # #But-But-But, yo, Doc #
# We wound up
two down, one up #
#And get butterflies in they stomach #
#Brothers can't speak
they just shut up #
#KRS on the come up liftin' big
pun up Let me sum up #
#Brace the drummer or breath for
breath I'll rip your lung up #
# On my trophy wall
I'm there with your tongue off #
#KRS-One, you know what it means
turn up the track for Assault on Precinct 13 #
# We gettin’ up outta here #
# That's the stuff, that's the stuff #
# Watch me back up the truck You livin’ with a
lot of fear # # That's the stuff, yes they are #
# Two crooked cops, you backin’ me up
We gettin’ up outta here #
# That's the stuff, that's the stuff #
# Watch me back up the truck #
# You livin’ with a lot of fear #
# That's the stuff, yes they are #
# Two crooked cops
you backin’ me up #
# We gotta start trustin' each other
if we gonna make it through this night #
#From criminal mind into spiritual mind
and even beyond and behind #
# They better be your friend or fight
or be the lazy type #
#Me, I'm the crazy type
I give them thugs some crazy hype #
#I've thrown the classics on
with them ladies, right #
#And years later
rocked with they babies like #
#I blazed a light They may be eight million
ways to die but they's 16 million ways to fight #
#So wherever you are in your crib
or your car or your tank too #
#Jean François would like
to thank you right #
# That's why, can I wrestle the mike
wishin' you peace for the rest of the night #
# 'Cause at the end of the film
you'll see what it mean #
# Turn up the track for
Assault on Precinct 13 ##
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org