Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
You okay?
Yeah.
[Breathing heavily]
What time do you think it is?
That was far.
Here.
Animal tracks.
Follow these to water.
Animals have to know
where the water is out here.
Then we follow them
to the water,
and we just drink our faces up.
Or else they go to the mating
grounds, you know, and...
And then they mate,
and they get thirsty,
and they come back.
All right, but, I mean, I...
Yeah.
We don't know how far
the water is, though.
And I don't think we should
abandon the higher-ground idea,
'cause it was a good idea.
And that was a rolling hills
scout-about.
And if we go on a mountain,
like, crow's-nesting,
like that mountain over there...
Yeah, but...
We know where the water is now.
We could just go there,
and then get water
and then go on our mountain,
the mountaintop scout-about,
after we've gotten water.
I think the mountain's
a better idea
because what if we go
to the mating grounds
and they see us
and they get self-conscious,
and then they don't mate?
Then we'll just...
And then
they won't get thirsty...
Whichever way it is,
if we go there,
and it's the mating grounds,
then we'll just watch them
from a brush.
They won't know we're there,
they won't have any body shame,
and they'll mate,
and get thirsty,
and then they'll come back,
and lead us to the water.
All right.
- [Both breathing heavily]
- Fuck this.
I can't even
see the tracks anymore.
Fuck 'em.
[Grunts]
[Breathing heavily]
Do you think we should
just go over to that mountain?
Just stop crying, man.
Where you going?!
[Voice breaking]
I don't know!
You wanna help?!
Fuck you.
[Exhales deeply]
We're walking north-northwest...
for...
a couple hours... a ways...
But that's been the way we've
been walking the whole time.
I mean, it's been
30 hours of walking.
North-northwest.
- Okay?
- Uh-huh.
We've gotta be fucking close
to the highway.
Yeah.
But we got lost.
I mean, we were going...
We walked our ways,
and maybe it was north.
And then...
We came,
we turned around, and...
We got off...
We started going straight back
down the way we were going.
No, we didn't.
No, no, no, no.
Before we turned around, we
started going down the same way.
But we had turned before...
No, we didn't go
the same fuckin' way.
We have not seen any
of the stuff that we've seen.
We haven't passed
anything that looks familiar.
Whatever our direction is,
it's not south,
and it has not been south.
We veered off
at a different point,
and when
we started to come back,
to go back, we started
back the exact same way.
But we didn't see anything
that looked the same.
We could have just
bailed early, you know.
There were so many gerrys
along the way.
We took a...
[Inhales sharply]
I mean, we started
going back the same way,
and then we stopped
and said it didn't look right,
and then we went to the right
for a little while.
So we were going east, all
right, which is a total gerry
because that's fucking
a million miles to a road.
That's because we came up
over the thing,
and we saw that whole layout.
There was nothing there.
We didn't see anything.
And then in the morning...
In the morning, we walked north.
In the morning, we...
[Sighs]
In the morning,
we definitely walked north.
And then we gerried off
to the animal tracks,
which was east...
which was west,
but it doesn't matter...
When we hit the tracks,
we took a left,
which was going...
...which was going west.
But more importantly, when I
got up, when we split up,
and I was walking up
on my scout-about,
I was looking into the sun,
which means that it was east.
Um...
So, and then,
when I was on the rock,
and I was looking at you,
the sun was...
When we came down,
we went in that direction.
That means we were going east,
and we walked for a long time.
And our scout-about was east,
so we gerried the scout-about.
We went up
the wrong fuckin' mountain.
Okay?
So our direction's
been north-northeast,
but if we spin the fucker
and just go north,
balls-out north,
we're gonna hit
the fuckin' highway
because we can't go south.
South is a fucking
disaster for us.
It would take too fucking long
to get there.
All right, then let's go north.
[Exhales deeply]
Come on, let's go.
We may as well just sit here.
You know why
I think we should go?
Why?
Because I've got water.
Come on, don't fuckin' joke.
I'm not joking.
I found water.
I know exactly where the car is.
[Sobbing]
How?
Just figured it out.
It was another fuckin' mirage.
It was a mirage.
What are you doing?
I really wanted to...
walk up to you and say I had
two bottles of water,
and that I knew
where the car was.
Come on, we gotta go.
- Come on.
- [Groans]
How do you think
the hike's going so far?
[Chuckles]
Pretty good.
[Laughing]
I'm leaving.
[Choking]
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org