Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Please take notes.
No wounds on the body to indicate
foul play from a weapon of any sort.
The contents of the safe are intact,
thus ruling out robbery as a motive.
The science of fingerprinting
has determined...
... there are no prints but the victim's
on the doorknob and frame...
... to indicate anyone else
entered or left.
The window is latched shut
from the inside.
So no one entered or left by that route...
... thus ruling out homicide
as a cause of death.
There's no indication of whiskey in
the glass or on the breath of the deceased.
No carpet fibers
on the soles of her shoes.
So she never set foot on the carpet.
There is a scuff on her right shoe tip...
... where polish was removed.
There is traces of the same polish
on this upturned bit of carpet.
There are traces of flower pollen
on the edges of the nostril.
I therefore conclude
from the evidence gathered...
... that the deceased entered the room
with a bunch of flowers.
She placed the flowers
in the vase by the door.
She took the vase in one hand, along
with the whiskey tumbler in the other...
... went across the room
to the decanter of whiskey...
... let the flowers get too close
to her nose.
She sneezed, her left foot
involuntarily slipped forward...
... caught the tip of her shoe
on this carpet...
...tripped, hit her head on the floor,
died from shock of the brain.
In other words, it was not foul play
that killed this poor woman...
...but an accident
caused by a simple sneeze.
And, in fact, it is not a woman at all...
...but a man wearing a horse-haired wig.
Oh, Quentin, I'm so proud.
- You know what this means, Clarissa?
- Yes, that we can get married.
It means science has a place
in police work.
I proved it. I convinced
each and every one of them.
Now there's only one more person
you have to convince.
I'm convinced.
But you must remember, Mr. Jackson...
...if we don't own the land
within 90 days...
...the railroad will go to other banks
to finance their expansion.
No worries, Mr. Ashe.
In 90 days, we'll be laying track
right through the middle of Mexico City.
Go.
That's a good one.
You do better.
How could you sell the mortgage
on my farm to the gringos?
Pedro, we have no choice.
The big American banks
control the cash flow.
And through the cash flow,
they control us.
Don Diego's doing all he can.
I'm sure Don Diego is.
But I've worked my whole life
to leave something to my poor daughter.
All she knows is the farm life.
What will become of her?
You cheated. I wasn't concentrating.
Best of three.
- Let me talk to Bernardo.
- Bernardo just follows orders.
So, what are we supposed to do, Papa,
stand by and let them steal our land?
Unless some higher authority
intercedes...
Maria, where are you going?
To see the higher authority.
Up. Up.
The spitting image of her mother,
God rest her soul.
My condolences, Don Diego.
Twenty years she's gone now.
Well, she left you
a very beautiful daughter.
Who I haven't seen in most of the 10 years
she's been away at school in Europe.
- Left a girl, came home a woman.
- Indeed.
My only problem now
is trying to convince her to stay.
She's been home for a week,
and already she wants to go back.
- I want to see Don Diego.
- He can't be disturbed.
Neither can I. And I am.
Very disturbed.
He is meeting
with a very important person.
Don Diego has always said,
"Every client is a very important person."
This is not a client, Maria.
This is a gentleman
from The Bank of New York.
I knew it.
Gotta pay the toll.
May I present Mr. Jackson from
the Capital Bank and Trust of Nueva York.
How do you do, Mr. Jackson?
Infinitely better in your presence
than I do out of it, Señorita Sandoval.
Afternoon tea. How civilized.
Are you surprised to find
that we are civilized, Mr. Jackson?
No, not at all.
No, I find it charming.
Charming?
I presume if you are using
such a word...
...that you've never experienced
the pleasure of an afternoon tea.
Mr. Jackson's bank has agreed
to provide us...
...with the capital we need
to continue with what we are doing.
We were just going over the papers.
A big New York bank taking an interest
in our small Mexican bank?
Why is that, Mr. Jackson?
Well, if you can't help friends
in a time of need, who can you help?
Pardon me, but in Europe
we have a different perspective...
...on the American definition
of friendship.
Forgive my ignorance, señorita,
but I'm a little uninformed...
...on the European perspective.
But I'm always willing to learn.
In fact, I'd be delighted...
...if you would enlighten me
on that subject, perhaps over dinner?
Perhaps some other time.
I need to get up early.
I have a long ride tomorrow.
Checkmate.
Goodbye, Mr. Jackson.
Men. All they have is one thing
on their minds.
And, by the way, that includes you.
Please. I've seen how you look
at that little filly of Señor Gomez.
A little more.
Stay here.
Don't talk to anybody.
Excuse me.
What was that?
Is there a problem?
For me? No.
For the horse
that gets poked in the side...
...with metal every time
you want him to do something...
...for him, I'm sure it's a problem.
Of course, he's probably
too polite to say anything.
Well, certainly more polite than you.
But, anyway, thank you for your opinion,
misinformed as it is.
Perhaps you can tell me
what you're doing in my house.
Oh, so you are the daughter.
- Yes, I am the daughter. And you are?
- Maria Alvarez.
- Do you work for us, Maria Alvarez?
- No, I do not work for you.
- Then what are you doing here?
- I have business with your father.
- And what sort of business, may I ask?
- Private business.
Hey.
Hey, stop. Hey.
Maria.
I knew it.
You help the gringos steal our land.
You betray your own people.
How dare you accuse me.
Get her out of here.
Have her arrested.
Traitor. Thief.
You're gonna pay for this.
I'm sorry.
They are stealing our land.
Don Diego is a traitor.
- The future.
- To the future.
Are you lost?
Mr. Alvarez, Pedro...
...you're delinquent
in your loan payments.
How can I pay when the interest
is more than I earn?
Says in this agreement
that if you're in arrears...
...we have the right to foreclose
and purchase this property for one peso.
Over my dead body.
No problem.
There's your receipt, Mr. Alvarez, Pedro.
Burn it.
You should have locked them up,
not me.
- They did not break into someone's house.
- No, they are doing worse.
You want my advice, Maria?
You should stop trying to change the world.
You want my advice, Gustavo?
You should start trying to change the world.
Eat.
The poultice that will help
your horse's hoof.
Thank you.
Now who's gonna be outside?
Keep an eye on her.
- What are you doing here?
- Hey, old man, read this.
- What's this?
- This is for you.
You haven't been making
your payments to the bank.
We have a right to foreclose.
I've given you everything you're gonna
get from me. Now get out.
Papa? Papa?
Papa.
Maria.
Papa. Papa?
Papa?
Somebody, please go get a doctor.
- What did you do to him?
- I didn't do anything.
- We were finishing the arrangements...
- You killed him.
You killed my father.
Señorita,
he's evidently had a heart attack.
No.
He was...
He was healthy.
You did something to him.
I know you did.
I know this is a terrible shock for you,
but you need to try and remain calm.
In fact, I think you need to sit down.
Grief is intense, I understand that.
But if you can,
let's review the situation calmly.
Your father's dead. Everything that
belonged to him is now mine.
In your mistaken belief
that I had something to do with it...
...you've attacked me.
You're trying to kill me.
My natural reaction is self-defense.
Before we can stop this,
I'll shoot you dead.
But it doesn't have to end that way.
Look at that, darling.
It's choosing time.
That's it.
Well, I guess we've got a deal.
If you don't mind,
I need to go to my room.
I must lie down.
This is all too much for me at once.
You understand?
Yes.
Absolutely.
I understand.
You take all the time you need.
Don't worry about a thing.
I'll make all the arrangements.
Oh, darling?
Would you like your afternoon tea...
...sent up to your room?
That would be very nice. Thank you.
- Hey. Hey.
- Get back here.
Come back here, you bitch.
- Come back.
- Hey. Come here.
I got you now.
Goddamn it.
- Padre.
- Maria?
They shot him.
I know, my child. I know.
What do you want from me, huh?
I have nothing to give you. Nothing.
You should have eaten
while you had the chance.
Get out of here. Shoo.
Hands up.
No one...
Move.
What are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
I'm taking this bank.
- With an unloaded gun?
- How do you know?
When a gun doesn't have any bullets...
Doesn't matter.
This bank is taken. Find another one.
This is the only bank in town.
Besides, it's my father's.
And take that raggedy mask off.
It doesn't even match.
Everyone knows who you are.
Your mask isn't silly?
People won't recognize that voice?
- "This is my father's bank."
- It is my father's.
Get out of my way.
I need to finish my job.
- Señoritas?
- I would hardly call stealing a job.
Señoritas?
I am not stealing.
I am taking it back from the bastards
who murdered my father.
- They killed Don Diego?
- Señoritas.
What?
The first order of business
is that we're gonna secure...
...and then remove all the deposits.
And then we're gonna instill
some renewed confidence in it.
I'd like to see the Stars and Stripes
flying over this place...
...so things start to look
a little more American down here.
Señor Manager?
This establishment is now
a wholly-owned subsidiary...
...of the Capital Bank and Trust
of New York.
What do you say we open the vault?
Take a look, and see what kind of cash
is on hand in the liquid-assets department.
Excuse me. Where is the vault?
In Don Diego's office.
Well, I guess that would be Señor Jackson's
office now, wouldn't it?
We did it. We did it.
- We did it.
- And what is it that you think you did?
Look. We're gonna help a lot of people.
To really help...
...you'd have to reverse the massive theft
of property that has taken place.
Listen, do you know how many
kilos of rice we can buy with this?
We can feed 500 people.
Why were you robbing the bank?
Revenge.
Not to help the people?
No.
What?
Stop looking at me that way,
both of you.
My life is not here.
- What are you doing?
- What does it look like?
Taking the money.
I'm going back to Europe.
You're joking.
All right, you can take half. I don't care.
You can even keep the dog as a bonus.
If you want to go, go.
But the money stays. All of it.
- No, it doesn't.
- Yes, it does.
No, it doesn't.
We were just debating
the basic economic theories...
...of wealth distribution.
Yes. Yes, we were.
That's good.
But before you reach
any hasty conclusions...
...let me show you something.
What?
Rice and beans
are not good enough for you?
I just can't eat when I see
what has been done to these people.
At least tonight they can eat.
We have to find a way
to get them back on their land.
We must come up with a plan.
Something that will benefit the people...
...and destroy these murderers.
I think we should rob more banks.
Yeah.
Let's go.
- Let's go where?
- Let's go rob more banks.
We can't just go right now
and rob a bank.
Fine. Finish brushing.
That's not it. We're not ready.
- Yes, we are. We just did it.
- We were lucky.
We cannot rely on luck.
We need to think first.
We need to consider the implications,
the consequences.
- Why are you so complicated?
- Why are you so unrealistic?
This is a noble cause
you seek to undertake, señoritas.
But if you keep fighting like cats and dogs,
you won't make it to sunrise.
My daughters, you know...
...when Columbus proposed his journey
to discover the New World...
...everybody said that was...
...unrealistic.
But he succeeded.
Because he had the king and queen
of Spain to help him.
Who do we have to help us?
I think I might know someone
who can help you.
Can I help you?
We're looking for these two.
What's a pair of señoritas like that
gonna be doing way out here?
We found this snagged on a cactus
half mile down the road.
Well, you find any more of that,
you can make yourself a nice little hankie.
Now, do you mind getting your foot
out of my door?
- And if I don't?
- Lf you don't, I'll kill you.
Now get your sorry ass off this porch.
You too.
Come on.
Hey, does this belong to you?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Mr...
- Where are you going?
- Far from here.
Toughs like that tend to come back
with reinforcements.
- But you said you would help us.
- I just did, missy.
No, no. Padre Pablo said
you could teach us to rob banks.
Well, where did he get that idea?
He said that's what you used to do.
That you robbed 37 banks in Texas
and never got caught.
Thirty-seven.
Last time I go to confession.
Listen, high-minded ideals is one thing,
robbing banks is another.
And to tell you the truth,
neither one of you pass the muster.
- We're well aware of that. At least I am.
- That's why we came to you.
To learn.
Well, to learn, you gotta have resources.
So far the only thing you've shown me...
...is a talent for bringing trouble
to my front door.
Buena suerte, ladies.
Mr. Buck.
You're not going anywhere...
...until you tell us
everything we need to know.
First, if you pull the trigger
on that gun...
...the way you're pointed,
you might cause it to rain.
- Well, haven't you fired a pistol before?
- I have.
But you didn't kill anybody.
There's always a first time.
That's true. But this ain't it.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Come on. Go on.
What the heck? Go on.
Git.
Go, git.
Come on.
Hey, what have you done to this horse?
- Please, Mr. Buck, they killed my father.
- And they almost killed mine.
You're breaking my heart.
All right, look, no whining, no complaining,
no fighting, or I'm adiós.
I never whine.
- Oh, please.
- "Oh, please." Well, I don't.
- Don't. Don't hit.
- Don't hit me. Stop.
- Don't hit me.
Ladies. Hey.
What's it gonna be?
- Deal.
All right, you first.
That's pretty good.
- How many you got left?
- I don't know.
You need to know.
Many a man's been left to die
for want of an extra bullet.
She's not very good with numbers.
Your turn.
I can't do this.
When I get nervous, I get the hiccups.
Guns make you nervous?
What the hell are you gonna use
to rob banks?
My education.
- "My education."
- What's so funny?
- To rob banks. Rob a bank.
- "My education."
You wish you had one,
you ignorant crack-shot showoff.
Fort Granger, Oklahoma, U.S. Cavalry.
That's my education.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
No one moves.
Get on the floor.
How are they gonna get on the floor?
I told them not to move.
Right.
So get on the floor and no one move.
Sara. Sara.
- I have to tell you something.
- Hold on.
Why are we doing this?
This has nothing to do with robbing banks.
Robbing banks is easy.
It's getting away
that's the hard part.
- Sara.
- How long do we have to stay like this?
- As long as it takes.
- Sara.
What?
I don't think I can hold any longer.
So drop off and swim to the shore.
I can't swim.
Sara.
Hold on to the rock.
Thank you.
- For what?
- For saving my life.
You noticed this time.
Good.
- Sara.
- What?
I guess...
I guess this makes us friends now.
I don't know about friends.
But partners...
Definitely partners.
Single file.
You gotta aim. Aim the gun.
Aim it.
Go on, higher. Higher. Higher.
Stinky, I'm sorry.
Come on, go. Faster, faster.
Before you kill your dog,
we need to try something.
Just take that.
See what you can do with those.
See, I knew she had talent.
Two hundred and forty-four, 245, 246...
...247, 248, 24...
That's the expert?
Mr. Cooke...
...welcome to Mexico.
Well, clearly, they're a pair of amateurs.
Robbing a bank in less than a minute
with no casualties.
I'd say they could pass as professionals.
That's odd.
These land transfers they left behind.
Who would sell a farm for one peso?
Mr. Cooke...
...the claim is that you're an expert
in criminal science, correct?
- Yes.
- Down here, I'm the expert in land finance.
So why don't we both just focus on
our respective areas of expertise, okay?
Time's slipping away here.
All right, what's the first rule
of robbing a bank?
- No one gets killed.
- The second?
Don't take more than you can carry
in one hand.
- And the third?
- Getting away is the first rule.
Perfect.
So do you think we're ready?
Well, you really only needed
to know one thing all along...
...and you learned that back in the river.
Trust your partner with your life.
Why did you make us go through
everything else if we were ready?
Well...
...I kind of liked having you two around.
Now go rob me some banks.
Everybody, hands up.
Are you sure the room
has been left undisturbed...
...since the death?
- Yes.
- You've worked here for a long time?
- Almost 20 years.
Do you know if he took any medication
for his heart condition?
Don Diego was healthy as a horse.
He was never sick a day in his life.
Thank you.
If you'll excuse me.
This should cover the mortgage
on the five farms north of the river.
I was thinking, you know,
we already have a lot of money.
Maybe we should stop
before the regulators...
Padre, they took 10 banks,
we take 10 banks.
- Right. We still have five to go.
- Four.
That's what I said. Four.
But one of my parishioners
told me about a specialist...
...they brought in.
- A specialist?
- For us?
- I'm afraid yes.
A detective from New York.
Let him come.
Are you Padre Pablo?
Yes.
- May I come in?
- No.
I thought the house of God was open
to all people at all times.
It is. But God is not at home right now.
He is down the road at the orphanage...
...where I was just going.
I'm Quentin Cooke.
I know who you are, Mr. Cooke.
Oh, you do?
It's my job to know
what concerns my flock.
Okay. Well, then maybe you can help me.
This girl.
- I was wondering if you could tell me...
- No.
I didn't finish the question.
You want to know if I have seen her.
No, I'm sure you haven't seen her.
I was wondering if you could tell me
if she had any problems...
...with her father.
- I loved my father.
Why does he ask such a question?
She loved her father.
Why do you ask such a question?
Just the way he died.
Anyway...
I'm staying at the hotel...
...in Santa Rita
if you have any information.
What did he mean
about the way my father died?
You heard what I heard.
If you want to know any more,
you will have to ask him.
Come on. Come.
We can take him right here.
- What?
- Wonderful.
- And how do we get the information?
- We ask him.
Our picture's all over the town.
So what? We wear bandannas.
I have a better plan.
Hello, mister. Do you want company?
- What are you doing?
- Saving time.
Yes?
Wrong room.
No. We're compliments
of the management.
- She's new.
- I don't mean to offend you, ladies...
...but I have a fiancée.
- And we have some questions.
- Hands up.
- Down.
- Up.
- Excuse us for a minute.
- What? You've never seen one before?
- Yes, but in the dark.
Up.
- My wallet's over there.
- This is not a robbery.
Oh, my God.
- You're them.
- Yes, it's us.
Well, you're not getting any answers
out of me.
I will not dishonor my profession.
Hey.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- We'll ask the questions.
Is this the fiancée?
Not bad.
- What are you doing?
- Puts me in the mood.
- Ready?
- Smile.
Beautiful.
Unless you tell us everything
we want to know...
...these pictures will show up in every
newspaper from here to New York.
With a special set going to your fiancée.
Then you won't have to worry
about dishonoring your profession.
Because you won't have one.
Now tell me about my father.
I won't tell you anything.
- This is a waste of time.
- Hey, hey.
Excuse my partner.
She's a bit impetuous.
Mr. Cooke, I am asking you
as a daughter who lost her father.
- Did your father drink wine?
- His passion.
I don't think he died of a heart attack.
I think he was poisoned.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org