Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
(drumroll)
(rousing orchestral
fanfare playing)
(fanfare ends)
(birds chirping)
(insects buzzing)
(ball hits ground)
Safe!
In the beginning,
when we moved to Naomi,
it was just the preacher
and me.
Only sometimes...
most of the time, really...
it seemed like it was me alone.
And then, one morning,
the preacher sent me
to the store for a box
of macaroni and cheese,
some white rice
and two tomatoes.
And after that,
everything changed.
But I'm getting ahead
of myself.
It's a good story.
Let me tell it right.
(singing)
(church bell tolling)
I appreciate you comin'.
I really do.
Thank you very much.
(chuckling):
All right, have a seat in there.
- Oh, is that a...
- Good morning.
Is that for me, I hope?
- Yes, it sure is.
- Yeah.
(singing continues)
I feel blessed
to be brought here to Naomi
to do God's work
in His new church.
I have to admit,
I'm-I'm still trying
to get used to the idea
of His house being
in a convenience store.
(chuckles)
Nothing wrong with making church
more convenient.
(coughs)
(singing continues)
(singing ends)
(sighs)
I have preached in some pretty
strange places in my time.
Not that... not that this is
a strange place.
I didn't mean that.
I ju... Ah!
Opal.
Come on in.
Come on.
Sit down.
Please.
(whispering):
Glad you finally made it.
This is my daughter, India Opal.
Forgive us.
We're new here.
Still trying to find
our way around.
(chuckling)
Maybe, uh, one of you two boys
could teach Opal
a better shortcut
to church, hmm?
(scoffs)
PREACHER:
No?
(chuckles)
Oh, well, let-let us pray.
(sighs)
Our Father,
who art in Heaven...
OPAL:
It's me, God.
If it's not too much trouble,
I'd like some friends.
I don't know that many kids.
Only the ones from church...
and there aren't
that many here.
There's ol'Amanda Wilkinson,
whose face is always pinched up
like she's smellin'somethin'
real bad.
And Sweetie Pie Thomas,
who's only five years old,
still mostly a baby, and is
always suckin' on her knuckle.
And there's Dunlap
and Stevie Dewberry.
And I know they can't help it
that they're bald, God.
Their mama shaved their heads,
on account of Dunlap got fleas
in his hair
from their cat, Sadie.
(grunting)
But even the bald Dewberry boys
don't want to be
my friend, anyway.
And one more thing, God.
I miss my mama.
Please, God, I'd really like
to see my mama again.
Amen.
CONGREGATION:
ANNOUNCER (over television):
Unless it's good supervision.
PREACHER:
Opal, come on.!
No TV until you put
some of that stuff away.
ANNOUNCER (over television):
Brett Parker
in that hitting streak...
(ball strikes ground)
I'll bet they already have
a new pitcher.
We're not moving back to Watley.
I know it's hard
movin' all the time,
but that's part of my job.
OPAL:
Up and at 'em, Daddy!
I made orange juice!
Daddy, I made orange juice!
Daddy!
(song on radio)
(song fades)
(bicycle rattling)
WOMAN (over P.A.): Well, folks,
we've got some wonderful specials today
I want to tell you about
in Aisle 3.
Uh, in the meat department,
you'll notice
the pork chops are...
(rustling)
FEMALE EMPLOYEE:
Did you see it?
MALE EMPLOYEE:
Come on. Come on.
We can get him
over here. Come on.
MALE EMPLOYEE #2:
There he goes, that way!
FEMALE EMPLOYEE:
Oh! Get over here!
I'll get him!
Comin'-comin'
through!
WOMAN (over P.A. System):
Boyd?
Boyd Lee,
could you please approach
the produce section?
(screaming)
(giggles)
What... what in the Sam Hill
is goin' on?
What is goin' on?
WOMAN (over P.A. System):
Please report
to the produce section, Boyd.
BOYD:
I'm in the produce section.
What? What is it?
WOMAN (over P.A. System):
It's a dog, Boyd.
BOYD:
We can't have no dog
in the Winn-Dixie.
Well, don't let him get
by the eggs!
(all exclaiming)
MALE EMPLOYEE:
He's gone left! We're goin' left!
Look, there he goes!
Stop him! Stop him!
Hey! He's goin' around!
Go get him!
MALE EMPLOYEE:
I got him! I got him!
BOYD:
Tracy, go 'round that way!
Get the do...!
(sighs):
Cut him off!
MALE EMPLOYEE:
He's goin' that way!
BOYD (shouting):
No!
Get that dog!
MALE EMPLOYEE:
He's under the table!
FEMALE EMPLOYEE:
I think he's trapped now, y'all.
(giggles)
Will somebody grab
that dog, please?!
Somebody, grab that dog!
(barks)
Somebody, grab that d...
(groaning):
Oh!
(barking)
Get him off of me!
I don't like dogs.
Somebody, get him
off of me.
OPAL:
It's okay, sir.
All that dog wants to do
is get face-to-face with you
and thank you for the good time
he's havin'.
(sobbing)
Call the pound!
Mike, go call the pound.
OPAL:
Wait!
Don't call the pound!
That's my dog!
And then I knew
I had done somethin' big.
Maybe stupid, too.
But I couldn't help it.
I couldn't let them take
that dog to the pound.
Here, boy!
Come on, boy!
Here, Winn-Dixie!
BOYD:
Who named the dog "Winn-Dixie"?
Me. It's his name, honest.
(sniffles)
Don't you know better
than to bring a dog
in the grocery store?
OPAL:
Sorry, sir.
It won't happen again.
I promise.
Come on, Winn-Dixie.
Well, what are
all y'all lookin' at?
That dog almost ate my face off.
(blubbering)
Sit.
Stay here.
I'll be right back.
(barks)
Sometimes the preacher looked
just like a turtle
hidin' inside its shell:
In there,
thinkin' about things,
and not ever stickin' his head
out into the world.
Daddy?
Yes, what is... what is it?
Wh-What is it, Opal?
I found a dog,
and I want to keep him.
You... A dog?
Now, we have been
through this before.
You do not need a dog.
I know it.
I know I don't need a dog,
but this dog needs me.
Oh, he doesn't neither need you.
He does, too!
Oh, for goodness' sakes, it don't...
Yes, it does!
Winn-Dixie!
Here, boy!
The last thing in the
world that we need
- is a... Uh!
- (barks)
Ow.
(grunts):
This isn't a dog. It's a horse.
And he's homeless, too.
Yeah, and he's got
a stink to him, too.
I know it.
Well, he needs all the help
he can get, right?
I could be doing my duty.
(sighs):
Yeah, well...
(barks)
(barking)
(sighs)
OPAL:
Look, he's smilin' at you.
Don't you love a dog
with a sense of humor?
Oh, would you run
and get the tweezers?
I think he's got
something stuck in his paw.
(sighs)
Here.
Yeah.
He's a nice dog, isn't he?
(sighs)
(Winn-Dixie whimpers)
He's a great dog, isn't he?
(whimpers)
You can't keep this dog, Opal.
Oh, please, Daddy, look at him!
He's skinny!
He's needs to be fed well.
- And bathed, too!
- No.
- Oh, please...
- No, no, no.
- Please!
- No! No! I said no.
(whispering):
Please?
(whimpers)
All right, he can stay here
while you're trying
to find him a home
or you figure out
where he belongs.
- He can stay?!
- Temporarily.
(whispering):
Yes!
You're not
keepin' him, Opal.
This is temporary, so don't
go getting your hopes up.
- (barks)
- I know it, sir.
We're not gettin'
our hopes up,
are we, Winn-Dixie?
- Good.
- No, no, no.
Why don't you go
make some signs
so folks'll know
that, you know,
you found a dog
who needs a home.
Come on, Winn-Dixie!
And a bath and a shower.
(song on radio)
Hey, hey, come back here,
Winn-Dixie!
(song ends)
(grunts)
Little miss...
you think you're using up
enough water?
Uh, we still got to rinse.
Opal, where'd you get that hose?
I didn't think you'd mind
if I borrowed it.
Well, I do mind!
Oh!
I'm sorry, Mr. Alfred!
- I'm sorry!
- Whoa!
(barking)
MR. ALFRED:
Come back here, you stupid dog, you!
(barks)
If I catch you,
so help me, you won't...
Oh!
(groans)
MR. ALFRED:
I made an exception for the kid.
But there is no exception
for that mongrel.
You see that sign
on the front of my trailer?
Does anybody
read my signs?
We're-we're
not keeping him.
We're trying to
find him a good home.
Well, hurry it up,
or I'm calling the pound.
(low growl)
We... (sighs)
Daddy?
Dry that dog off, Opal.
And dry yourself off, too.
You know, Winn-Dixie,
if my mom were around,
I bet she'd let me keep you.
Ever since we moved here,
I've been thinking
about my mama extra hard.
Opal, I hope that dog's
not in your bed.
OPAL:
Yes, sir.
L-I mean, no, sir, he's not.
(whines softly)
I really don't
know where she is.
She left
when I was only three years old.
I can't hardly remember her.
(whines softly)
PREACHER: And make sure
you got your window shut tight.
Don't want that rain gettin' in.
OPAL:
Okay.
(whines softly)
The preacher?
It's no use.
He won't talk to me at all
about her.
I bet you don't remember
your mama much, either.
So we're really alike,
you and me.
Think I should
make the preacher
tell me about her?
Mm, I'll think about it.
You're supposed to be in bed.
Daddy,
can you tell me about Mama?
Uh, I know you don't
like to talk about her,
but I don't even remember
what she looked like.
What did she look like?
I don't need to know a lot.
Just a few things.
She'd tell you
not to stay up so late.
(kisses Opal)
(grunts)
PREACHER:
Opal.
You ready to head out
and put up those signs?
Yes, sir.
Hold on.
- (sneezes)
- (groans)
No, leave him here.
- Stay here.
- (whines)
Stay.
(singing)
What the...?
(singing continues)
God... bless it.
(Winn-Dixie barks)
(mournful howling)
Opal, would you bring
that dog inside, please?
(howling)
(whining)
Come on, Winn-Dixie.
That night,
I wrote down in my journal
that what the preacher
couldn't see
is that Winn-Dixie wasn't lost.
And I didn't find him.
He found me.
He was a dog
who knew how to be a friend.
(singing continues)
Hey, boy.
Where are we goin'?
(singing ends)
You like that?
I bet with a collar like that
you'd feel like
you belonged to somebody.
Well, maybe we
could afford it.
(coins jingling)
- (bell dinging)
- Winn-Dixie.
(birds chittering softly)
Hello?
BI RD (mimicking):
(goose squawks)
Hello.
BI RD:
(goose squawking loudly)
Hello.
(squawks)
(quietly):
Hello?
(clears throat)
L-l-I'm sorry.
Do you work here?
Yeah, but we're closed.
(Winn-Dixie sniffs)
Hey. Hey.
Don't mind him.
That's just how he says hello.
Um, that's Winn-Dixie
and I'm Opal.
I'm, uh, Otis.
BI RD:
Otis. (squawks)
Well, Otis,
my dog sure likes
this red collar,
but I don't get
a big enough allowance
to afford somethin' this fancy.
Well, look, Miss.
I'm mostly just here
to take care of the animals.
BI RD:
Otis. (squawks)
Shut up, idiot.
I was thinking
maybe we could set up
an installment plan.
Well, I don't think
I can do that.
Well, I could work for you.
I could come in and
sweep the floors
and straighten
up the shelves
and take out the trash.
I could do that.
Well, that's what I do.
Oh.
Well, you sure need some help.
BI RD:
Otis. Hello.
I'm real trustworthy.
But the only thing is,
Winn-Dixie, my dog,
he'd have to come inside with me
while I work.
He doesn't like
to be left alone.
Well, Gertrude doesn't like dogs.
She owns a pet shop
and she don't like dogs?
Yeah.
No, I mean, that Gertrude.
The parrot.
Gertrude. (squawks)
It's named
after the owner.
Doesn't like dogs.
Well, she might like Winn-Dixie.
Almost everybody does.
If the two of'em get along,
then could I have the job?
Mm, I don't know.
GERTRUDE:
Dog. Dog. Dog!
I know it's a dog.
Gertrude's a pretty bird.
Hello.
Hello, dog.
(Winn-Dixie grunts)
See? She likes him.
That's pretty amazing,
don't you think?
OTIS:
I'll be damned.
Then we're all set, then. Thanks.
No, wait, Miss.
I can't-I can't
just give you a job.
- I can't just give you a...
- Thank you.
You won't be sorry.
I'm a real hard worker.
That's nice.
Thank you for listening.
Have a nice day, ma'am.
Have a nice day.
Little ten-year-old kid
walk in here,
make me look like a idiot.
GERTRUDE:
Shut up, idiot.
(strained breathing)
(grunts angrily)
(chuckles):
Yeah?
Need some help?
Get rid of that dog.
Oh, Lord.
What did he, uh,
what'd he do now?
Nothin'.
He don't have
to do nothin'.
I make the rules here,
and it's plain: No pets.
Well, you know,
Opal's been very responsible
with the dog, Mr. Alfred.
She's still lookin'
for a home.
Uh, well, get me a photo.
I'll post it on eBay.
I'll get you competing
bids within an hour.
Okay, thank you,
but I don't think
that's necessary.
You just stay here rent-free
because I can write it off
as a charitable donation
to the church.
But my charity stops
with that animal.
You know how much
we appreciate
the accommodation here, sir.
Call the pound.
(sighs)
Mr. Alfred, please.
I'm sure
we can work somethin' out.
I mean, just give us
a little bit more time.
You want a home or a dog?
Call the pound.
(crickets chirping)
Well, yeah, I just-I just figure
you got such a nice, big place
over there, you know.
And, uh, and he's, and
I'm sure he'd be fine
with-with your other dogs.
Uh-huh.
(Opal grunts)
- Uh-huh.
- Don't let him see you.
Uh-huh, yeah, look,
he's very playful.
Yeah, he's great with kids.
Opal thinks
the world of him.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Well, listen,
if you think of somebody,
you be sure to give me a call,
all right?
(growls softly)
- Okay.
- Come back here, Winn-Dixie.
I hope to see you
in church on Sunday.
- (Winn-Dixie groans)
- Come on.
Okay, all right.
Bye, now.
(song on radio)
(vehicle approaching)
(song ends)
(Winn-Dixie barking)
No.
OPAL:
Winn-Dixie.
Dixie.
Dixie. No!
- Opal. Opal. Opal.
- (Winn-Dixie barking)
Come on. Come on.
I know, I know.
- No!
- Sir, I need you to sign
- this release form, please.
- It's not right, Daddy.
- You know it isn't!
- Opal.
(sobbing):
No!
Stop that right now.
- Please, Daddy.
- (Winn-Dixie barking)
He's the only friend I have!
(sobbing):
Don't take him away.
Please.
- Please.
- (Winn-Dixie whining)
(Opal crying)
Please?
(Winn-Dixie whining)
Wait.
Don't take him.
What, this isn't the dog?
Uh, there's
been a mistake.
That isn't the dog.
(van door opening)
(Winn-Dixie barks, whines)
(van doors closing)
(engine starting)
(sighs):
Come on. Get him inside.
Let's go.
OPAL:
The preacher took a loan out from church
and paid off our rent,
but he had to promise Mr. Alfred
that he would find Winn-Dixie a home
before the end of summer.
I would have promised
anybody anything.
I was just so happy
to have Winn-Dixie with me.
And I was happy to have a job
at Gertrude's Pets.
(Winn-Dixie panting)
(Winn-Dixie whines)
This is our town.
See?
Kinda lonely, isn't it?
What?
(Winn-Dixie whines)
(barks)
Hey, Winn-Dixie.
Wait... wait for me, boy.
(barks)
Hey, Winn-Dixie.
Winn-Dixie, come back here.
That's the library.
(barks)
Winn-Dixie,
you can't go in there.
It says so on the sign.
(whispers):
Wow, look at all those books.
(classical music playing
quietly in background)
(snoring softly)
(music continues playing)
(woman screams)
(gasps):
Oh, my goodness.
(woman panting)
Are you all right?
(panting):
It's a bear.
A bear?
He's come back.
- He has?
- Yes. Yes.
Where is he?
(panting):
He's right out there.
That's no bear.
That's just a dog.
It's my dog, Winn-Dixie.
A dog?
Oh. I...
It's your dog?
Oh. You sure?
Yes, ma'am, I'm positive.
I'd know him anywhere.
- All right.
- Let me help you up.
- Oh.
- Come on.
(woman panting)
- (sighs)
- It's okay.
Mm.
(panting)
Wh-Who are you?
- I'm India Opal.
- Oh.
But you can just call me Opal.
Well, I'm Miss Franny.
You must think
I'm a silly ol' thing
mistaking a dog for a bear.
Are you sure that is a dog?
Yes, ma'am.
- I'm sure.
- Hmm.
He just don't like to
be left alone is all.
Mm-hmm.
Sorry to bother you,
Miss Franny.
Well, l-I had a bad experience
with a bear
coming into Herman W. Block
Memorial Library,
and I've never quite
gotten over it.
A bear came into the library?
Oh, yes.
It's quite a story.
Sure would like to hear it.
But Winn-Dixie
gets lonely without me.
(sighs):
Well...
maybe we could
make an exception.
Now, one hot Thursday,
way back then,
I was sittin' here
in the library,
and all the doors and windows
were wide open.
And I had my nose in a book
until I noticed
a very peculiar smell.
A very strong smell.
And I raised
my eyes up slowly
and standing
right in front of me was a bear.
- (roaring)
- A very large bear.
How large was it?
At least four times
the size of your dog.
That big?
Wow.
Then what happened?
I very slowly
and very carefully raised up
the book I was reading.
What book was that?
War and Peace.
And I carefully aimed it,
and I threw it
right at him!
- Be gone!
- (Winn-Dixie barks)
(laughs)
Good dog.
Thank you.
(barks happily)
And do you know what?
No, ma'am. What?
This is why I will never forget.
He took the book with him.
Nuh-uh.
Yes, ma'am,
he snatched it up
and ran off.
(bear snorts)
Did he ever come back?
No.
I never saw him again.
Well, the men in town,
they used to tease me about it.
They used to say, "Miss Franny,
"we saw that bear of yours
out in the woods today.
"He was reading
War and Peace
"and said it sure was good,
and he'd like
to check it out again. '
(bear snorts)
(chuckles)
Ah, I imagine I'm the only one
who even recalls that bear.
(whines)
You don't have a husband
or children?
Mm, I never married.
Why not?
I didn't have the need.
But you don't have anyone.
I have these books.
Now, look at that.
That dog is smilin' at me.
(Miss Franny chuckles)
Would you like to be friends?
You and me and Winn-Dixie?
Would you wanna
be friends?
Why, that would be fine.
That would be grand.
Just grand.
OPAL:
Winn-Dixie was better
at makin'friends
than anyone I had ever known.
I talked to him
about everything.
And he was
a real good listener.
(whines)
Just about everything good
that happened that summer
happened because of Winn-Dixie.
(Opal kisses Winn-Dixie)
(Winn-Dixie grunts)
(bell dinging)
(birds chirping softly)
(acoustic guitar plays
slow melody)
(bird chitters softly)
(guitar continues playing)
[Music] Oh... [music]
[Music] Hey... [music]
(Winn-Dixie whines)
(vocalizing)
(oinks)
(bleats)
(vocalizing continues)
Uh-oh.
[Music] Hey... [music]
GERTRUDE:
Dog.
- Dog!
- (Winn-Dixie barks)
- (Winn-Dixie barking)
- Otis, the animals.
(animals squawking)
(squealing)
(shouts):
Help me here.
Oh, God.
- (barking)
- Stop it, Winn-Dixie.
- Ah. Ooh.
- (Winn-Dixie barking)
OTIS:
Help me get 'em back in the...
- Ooh.
...cages.
I'll get the rabbits.
(piglet squealing)
OTIS:
You idiot.
(animals squawking)
(Winn-Dixie barking)
(goat bleats, hamster squeaks)
- Sarah...
- (animals squawking)
Sarah, come here, sweetie.
- Come on, come on.
- (piglet squeals)
(Winn-Dixie barking)
(Otis grunts)
Son of a...
(animals squawking
frantically)
OPAL:
Play some more music.
What?
What I said was,
play some more music, Otis.
(animals squawking
frantically)
(Winn-Dixie barking)
(playing gentle melody)
(animals quiet down)
Far out.
Do it again.
(guitar continues playing)
(birds chirping softly)
(animals chitter contentedly)
Well, it seems
to be working.
(bell dinging)
I'm gonna go tell my ma
about what I seen.
That man's magic.
He's a magic man.
Bye, Magic Man.
- (bell dinging)
- Bye, Opal.
(guitar continues playing)
Are you really a magic man?
I was just playin'
for the animals.
Uh...
(whimpers)
They seem to...
they seem to like it.
Yes, sir.
Did they escape
from their cages?
No, I left the cages open.
You just let 'em roam around?
I don't know.
It's... it's no good
bein' locked up, though.
GERTRUDE:
Locked up.
Shut up.
Shut up, idiot.
Shouldn't you be sweepin' up?
(clears throat)
Why don't you sweep up?
With your guitar?
Just sweep up the place and...
clean it up a little bit,
this mess.
[Music] Hey... [music]
(guitar music continues)
(Otis vocalizing)
(snoring softly)
(guitar music fades)
(snoring continues)
(door squeaks)
He doesn't want to
be left alone is all.
Can't we bring him?
Can't bring a dog
to church, Opal.
Come on. We're
gonna be late.
It's a big day for me.
He's scared we'll
leave him for good
and never come back.
(whines)
That mutt ain't got
a home yet?
Uh, no, not yet, but
we're workin' on it.
I had a dog like that once, myself.
A real howler.
I got him to shut up.
You did? How?
I shot him.
Well, you can't shoot
a church-goin' dog.
It'd be a sin.
(barking)
CHOI R:
[Music] Amazing Grace [music]
[Music] How sweet the sound [music]
[Music] That saved a wretch like me [music]
(Winn-Dixie howling)
[Music] I once was lost [music]
[Music] But now am found [music]
(howling)
[Music] Was blind... [music]
(chuckles and laughter)
[Music]... but now I see [music]
[Music] 'Twas grace that taught [music]
(barking and whining)
[Music] My heart to fear [music]
[Music] And grace my fears relieved [music]
(howling)
(laughter)
(laughing)
[Music] How precious did... [music]
All right, all right!
That's enough. That's enough.
Please, stop.
Everyone just stop, please.
- Please.
- (music trails off)
Thank you.
Opal.
He doesn't know
the words is all.
But he sure is moved
by the spirit.
(congregation chuckles)
Get that dog, now.
Yes, sir.
Oh, my stars!
(congregation chuckles
and murmurs)
It's a face
only a mother could love.
Are dogs allowed in church?
(whispers):
Sit. Sit.
We, uh, we recently celebrated
the hundredth anniversary
of man learning to fly.
Now, that's the sort of miracle
that we tend to take
for granted nowadays.
But for hundreds of years,
man was taking that same kind
of leap of faith...
and falling right on his butt.
(chuckling)
Yep, folks, they was
tyin' themselves to kites
and homemade wings and hurlin'
themselves off of barns
and crashin' off of cliffs.
So how did
the Wright brothers do it?
When everybody else was
nose-divin' for centuries?
They saw...
(whispering):
Don't even think about it.
...the unique value in all
the inventors around 'em.
Did you know that part
of their wing design
was actually the same design
as a railroad bridge?
- Yeah.
- No.
Isn't that a genius leap?
Usin' a bridge to fly?
(barking)
- (congregation murmurs)
- Keep on preaching!
I got him!
And more importantly,
they had each other...
(screaming and yelling)
...working as brothers,
as a team.
It's the same reason we have...
(congregation exclaiming)
Whoa! Look at him go!
Working together,
we can lift this town up!
(barking)
More than just taking a leap
of faith, we can learn to fly!
Sorry!
(women screaming)
Opal, stop that dog!
(barking)
(disgusted murmuring)
WOMAN:
Mm, mm, mm.
(all gasp)
Never in my life.
A dog catchin' a mouse.
(murmuring)
(sighs)
Let us pray...
for this mouse.
(laughter)
OPAL:
That sure was somethin'.
I bet Mama would have gotten
a big kick out of it.
Opal, the dog cannot
go back to church.
Everybody was talkin'.
They said they
hadn't had
that much fun in church
in a long while.
Opal.
Doesn't it look better?
(barks)
Now where you takin' me,
Winn-Dixie?
DUNLAP:
That dog looks like a dirty carpet.!
(boys giggle)
Yeah.
I can hear you.
I can hear you guys behind me.
You better watch out!
That dog's headed right
for the witch's house.
Winn-Dixie, come back here!
Winn-Dixie!
You better go get
your dog out of there.
Get lost,
you bald-headed babies!
Hey, that witch is gonna
eat that dog for dinner
and you for dessert!
I wouldn't go in there,
Baloney Breath.
Baloney Breath?
You're just a couple
of skinny-armed chickens.
We'll tell the preacher
what happened to you.
(whispering):
Winn-Dixie?
Winn-Dixie, where are you?
WOMAN:
Give me this, I said.
Let it go. Let it go!
Give it! Give it to me!
(grunts softly)
Let it go, I said.
- Stop it!
- Oh!
(grunts, then gasps)
Who's there?
(shuddering):
Um, please don't eat me.
D-D...
Don't eat me!
I don't taste good!
Please, help!
Eat you?
You silly child.
How can I eat you?
(laughs)
Where's my dog?
Did you eat my dog?
Hardly.
But he darn near bit my hand off
stealing my sandwich!
Where is he?
Where is the dog?
Where's the dog?
Where is the d...
Oh, I hear him.
I hear him.
He's smackin' his lip.
He sure love peanut butter.
Listen at him.
(laughs)
I'm sorry I got
on your property.
Hmm.
My name's Opal.
My name is... Gloria.
Gloria Dump.
Isn't that
a terrible last name?
Dump?
Well, my last name's Buloni.
Sometimes the kids at school,
they call me Lunch Meat.
"Lunch Meat."
(chuckling):
Oh, my.
Well, I'm pleased
to meet you, Lunch Meat.
What you call
your friend here?
- Oh, that's Winn-Dixie.
- Winn-Dixie?
You mean like the grocery store?
Now, that takes the
strange-name prize, don't it?
Woo-wee!
(laughs)
(whines)
Oh, no. Hmm-mm.
This one's mine.
I'm gon' eat this one.
You know, baby girl...
these eyes of mine,
they don't see
too good no more.
You can't see?
Well... you know, I can...
I can see only
the general shape
of things.
So I rely on my heart.
Why don't you go ahead and tell
me everything about yourself,
so I can see you with my heart?
Well, the first thing you should
know about me is that...
my dad's the preacher,
which was why
we moved to Naomi.
OPAL:
I had been waiting for so long
to tell a person
everything about me,
I couldn't stop.
I told Gloria Dump everything.
And the whole time
I was talkin',
Gloria Dump was listening.
I see, I see.
But the most important thing
you should know about me...
is that I don't have a mama.
You don't have a mama.
Somethin' happened to her
that made her go away,
and I don't know
what it was.
Well, then the Dewberry boys...
OPAL: I could feel her listening
with all her heart.
And it felt good.
(rain pattering)
(whining)
(thunder rumbling)
(barking and whining)
Winn-Dixie?
(whispering):
What's wrong, boy?
Quiet!
You'll wake the preacher.
(thunder rumbling)
Winn-Dixie.
(whispering):
Winn-Dixie, come back here!
- (whining)
- (startled yell)
Opal!
(thunder cracks, whining)
What's going on with that dog?
- (glass shattering)
- I don't know!
Come on, Winn-Dixie.
Come on, come on!
Come...
(yells):
Winn-Dixie!
Daddy, I'm sorry.
I don't know
what's gotten into him.
It's just thunder.
It's okay.
(thunder cracks)
Daddy, what if he hurts himself?
What if he tries
to get away?!
Daddy, what's happening?!
Let's get out of the way.
Oh...
Do you know what
a pathological fear is?
No, sir.
It is a fear that goes way
beyond normal fears.
It's a fear that you
can't be talked out of,
you can't be reasoned out of.
And I think Winn-Dixie
has a pathological fear
of thunderstorms.
(thunder cracks)
(sighs)
(whimpering, clattering)
(racing footfalls)
(whining)
We get an awful lot of
thunderstorms in the summer.
Well, I'm gonna have
to make sure
he doesn't get out
during a storm.
Might run away.
We'll have to make sure
we keep him safe.
Yes, sir.
(chuckles softly)
I've been talkin'
to Winn-Dixie.
Oh, is that right?
He thinks,
since I'm ten years old,
you should tell me ten things
about my mama.
Why don't you just
go back to bed, Opal?
Just ten things, that's all.
One thing for each year
I've been alive.
He made it sound like
a reasonable request.
I should've known
you'd be more trouble.
(barks)
You remind me
so much of your mama.
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
But that doesn't count
as the first thing, okay?
Okay, all right.
Ten things... and then
it's off to bed, all right?
Okay, let's see.
One: She was funny.
She could make
just about anybody laugh.
Two: She had fair hair
and big eyes.
Just like me.
Exactly like you.
I kinda remember that.
Do ya?
Mm? Good.
Three: She liked
to plant things.
She had a talent for it.
She could stick a tire
in the ground and grow a car.
Four: She could run.
Oh, was she fast!
You couldn't ever
race her, you know.
I mean, if you did,
y-you couldn't let her
get a head start.
Otherwise, she'd
beat you for sure.
What's number five?
She couldn't cook.
Burned everything, even water.
(chuckles)
Six: Your mama
loved a good story.
She could sit and listen
to anybody tell a story.
She especially liked
funny ones, mm-hmm.
'Cause she loved to laugh.
What's number seven?
She knew all the constellations.
Every planet
in the nighttime sky.
And she could name 'em,
you know?
Point 'em out.
She never got tired
of looking up at 'em.
Number eight...
She hated being
a preacher's wife.
She said she couldn't stand
havin' all those ladies
at church judgin' her
on how she sang and what she was
wearing and what she cooked.
She said it made her feel
like a bug under a microscope.
What's the ninth thing?
Number nine... is...
your mama loved you.
She loved you very much.
But she left me.
She left us.
Why'd she leave us?
She just...
packed her bags and left us.
Just... yeah.
Didn't leave one thing behind.
She didn't leave anything?
Nope.
Nothin'.
What's number ten, Daddy?
I think that's enough for now.
But that's only nine things.
It's late.
You'll think of number ten
for me, won't you?
Good night, Opal.
(woman laughing)
PREACHER: She could stick a tire
in the ground and grow a car.
(engine running)
(laughing)
Burned everything.
Even water.
She knew
all the constellations.
She hated bein'
a preacher's wife.
It made her feel like a bug
under a microscope.
(screen door creaking)
OPAL: That night,
I went over and over in my head
the nine things
that the preacher had told me.
Then I wrote them down
just the way he had
said them to me.
That way, I would
never forget them.
(birds cawing)
Oh...
(singing)
He shouldn't be away
from his mom too long
when they're this small.
(singing continues)
What kind of tree is this?
It's a wait-and-see tree.
What's that mean?
It means you got to
wait till it grows up
before you can
see what it is.
Tight?
Well?
(singing continues)
(singing ends)
MAN:
So you just drifted
on into town.
OTIS:
I told you everything.
Mornin', Otis.
Well, well, well.
How long you known
Mr. Otis, here?
(growls)
Not so long, I guess.
So I reckon you
know Gertrude, too?
Yes, I do.
Winn-Dixie!
(barks)
Yet somehow you don't
know Miss Gertrude.
Hmm?
Nor why she'd
leave her shop
in the hands of a drifter.
Look, I told you
that we're cousins.
POLICEMAN:
You ain't no cousin
I know about, there, smiley.
I told you her mama's sick,
and I told you she asked me
to look after this store.
Well, aren't you
a big steamin'
pile of pancakes?
OTIS: Don't you have
anyone else's day you can ruin?
Why'd you come
in here, man?
Just leave me alone. God.
Well, well, well.
Somebody's all fired
up on budgie food.
Now, you.
We're gonna go outside
and have a little talk,
me and you.
Leave the girl alone.
Someone better shut
their gob-hole.
Come on, little one.
Get you out of the presence
of... Mr. Ravioli over here.
Come on.
Come on, now.
Now, you don't
know so much
about that fellow
in there, do you?
I know he can sing
near anything.
Oh, yeah, he can
sing, all right,
like a bird in a cage.
He tell you he
was locked up
in jail for a while?
I don't know anything
about that.
POLICEMAN: Mm-hmm.
The preacher know you're working here?
(growls)
I didn't think so.
You just better
watch out.
Hey! Hey! Whoa!
Get away from there!
You are in violation
of Ordinance 29-02:
The ramming of
a horny head
into a police-issued vehicle!
- (quacking)
- Ow!
Don't you sass me,
you naughty goose!
- (shouts)
- (laughs)
Hey, Elvis! You stupid...
Ow!
Just, oh, get out here
and help me!
Get away, you freak!
(barks)
(screaming)
Get away from me,
you hairy barnyard freaks!
(groans)
(shouting)
Crazy wild goose on me!
Oh! 10-59!
(siren chirps)
Ah, I went through a stop sign!
- There's a goose! Help!
- (barks)
(giggling)
STEVI E:
You're such a goody-goody.
Shouldn't the
preacher's daughter
be at home
studying the Bible?
I saw you with
the police.
You're so busted.
That pet shop man
is a retarded criminal.
You don't know anything.
I know Preacher...
wouldn't like you hanging
around... with criminals.
Lay off her, Stevie.
I don't care what you guys say.
- (growls)
- Go pick your lice,
you booger-eaters!
Dang, Opal.
GLORIA:
Baby girl, how 'bout telling me a story?
OPAL: Once upon a time,
I hated the Dewberry boys.
The end.
Oh, stop that nonsense.
I do hate 'em.
They're ignorant.
They think you're a witch.
Oh, they're just trying
to get your attention.
I'll bet they like you.
(laughs)
Gloria, you know Otis?
No, I don't know Otis,
but I do know
what you told me about him.
You know he's a criminal?
He's been in jail.
Baby girl, come on.
I want to show
you somethin'.
See this tree?
- Yeah.
- Hmm?
OPAL:
Why are all those bottles on it?
GLORIA:
To keep the ghosts away.
What ghosts?
Ghosts of all the things
I've done wrong.
You did
that many things wrong?
(chuckles)
More than that, baby girl.
But you're not
a bad person.
Doesn't mean
I haven't done bad things.
But there's whiskey
bottles on there,
a-and beer bottles.
That's right.
I know that.
I'm the one what drank
what was in 'em,
and I'm the one
what put 'em up there.
Oh, baby girl.
You know, a lot
of folks have problems...
with liquor and beer.
Get to start drinkin'
and can't get stopped.
Are you one of those people?
Yes, I am...
but you know somethin'?
These days, I don't drink
nothin' stronger
than coffee.
Did the whiskey
and beer and wine...
did they make you do all those
bad things that are ghosts now?
Some of'em.
Some of'em
I would've done anyway,
with or without the liquor
and the beer...
till I learned.
Learned what?
Till I learned what was
the most important thing.
What's that?
Oh... it's different
for everyone.
Got to learn
it on your own.
But, you know,
we should judge Otis
by the pretty music
that he makes
and how kind he is
to all them animals,
'cause that's all we know
about him now... right?
Yes, ma'am.
(sighs)
(whispering):
All right, then.
(bottles clanking)
Miss Franny, I've got this
friend named Gloria Dump...
- Mm.
...and she really loves to read,
only her eyes are bad,
so she can't read anymore.
- Ooh.
- So I was thinkin'
maybe I could read her
a story.
- Mm.
- Do you have any suggestions?
Of course I have
suggestions.
Hmm. What about...
Gone with the Wind?
What's that about?
Oh, it's a wonderful,
exciting story
about the Civil War.
The Civil War?
Now, Opal,
don't tell me
you have never heard
of the Civil War.
It was the war
between the North
and the South
over slavery.
MISS FRANNY:
That's right, Opal.
My great-grandfather,
Littmus W. Block,
fought in that war.
I'm ready for another book.
Well, Amanda, maybe you
wouldn't mind waitin'.
I was just telling
India Opal a story
about my great-grandfather.
I sure would like
to hear a story
about your great-grandfather.
MISS FRANNY:
Now, Littmus, only a boy of 14,
went off to be a hero,
but he soon found out
the truth.
What truth?
That war is hell.
Pure hell.
"Hell" is a cuss word.
MISS FRANNY:
Well, "war" is a cuss word, too.
I mean, nei-neither
of you can imagine...
Littmus was hungry
all the time.
He was covered
with all manner of vermin.
Fleas and lice.
And he was constantly
being shot at.
He suffered in a way that no boy
should ever have to suffer,
and it changed him.
(grunting)
(whispering):
Shoot, I can't see nothin'.
(grunting)
There probably
ain't nothin' to see.
Come on, Dunlap.
You got to think
like a secret agent.
like a spy.
He walked back home
when the war was over.
I mean, he walked from Virginia
all the way to Georgia,
but when he got there,
his parents, his sisters,
everything
and everyone was gone.
AMANDA: But, Miss Franny,
what about his sisters?
- What happened to them?
- Dead.
Dead from typhoid fever.
And his mama?
Dead, too.
And his father?
(sighs)
He died on the battlefield.
People are dying
all over the place.
This guy's whole family's dead!
STEVI E:
Come on, I wanna hear.
So, Littmus was
an orphan?
Yes. Poor Littmus was
all alone in the world.
(whimpers)
(clears throat)
Well...
when he finished crying, he...
had the s-strangest sensation.
He wanted something sweet.
He wanted
a piece of candy.
Yes, ma'am.
Littmus W. Block figured
that the world
was a sorry affair
and had enough ugly things in it.
And what he was going to do
was put something sweet in it.
STEVI E:
Let me see.
(gasping)
(grunting)
- Quiet!
- (Stevie groans)
Would you care
for a Littmus lozenge?
- Yes, Miss...
- Yes, please.
Thank you.
Now, they're
not made anymore.
The world, it seems,
lost its appetite
for Littmus lozenges.
Fortunately,
I had the foresight
to save a few.
Do you like it?
OPAL:
Yes, ma'am.
What about you, Amanda?
Yes, ma'am, but it
makes me feel sad.
There is a secret
ingredient in there.
What is it?
(whispers):
Sorrow.
Not everybody can taste it.
I taste it.
Me, too.
Well, then...
you've probably both had
your share of sadness.
The world has changed so much.
People in Naomi, they-they used
to know each other's sadnesses.
They used to rely on each other.
This town just isn't the same
without the candy factory.
But how do you get sadness
into a piece of candy?
Yeah, how'd you get
that taste in there?
That is the mystery.
That's how Littmus made
his fortune.
By manufacturing a candy
that tasted sweet and sad
at the same time.
Man, we missed out
on the candy.
Now they're just
sitting around,
talking about
how they feel.
(mutters):
Come on.
I had to move away
from Watley...
and leave all
my friends behind.
That's one sadness
I've known.
And my mama.
I don't know my mama.
(sniffles)
I only know a few
things about her.
And there's something the
preacher won't tell me.
(voice breaking):
It makes me think of Carson.
(sniffles)
STEVI E:
Hey, guys.
Bookworms!
Where's your apples?
I have to go.
(sighs)
STEVI E:
What's with her?
Who's Carson?
Carson was
Amanda's brother.
Was?
He drowned last year.
I saw the whole thing.
Come on, Dunlap.
(grunts)
OPAL: Gloria said that Naomi
was like one big mistake tree.
And every person
was its own bottle,
hanging in the wind,
all empty and alone.
Miss Franny thought
it had been that way
ever since the candy factory
closed years ago.
People lost more
than their jobs.
They lost each other.
(crunching)
Tastes like music.
(smacks lips)
It reminds me of, uh...
being in jail.
Otis, what were you in jail for?
(grunts)
(plucks guitar note)
You don't have to tell me.
I was just wondering.
(strums guitar chord)
I never hurt anybody.
(picking gentle melody)
Never meant to.
But I've been locked up.
And I remember the day
very well.
I was sitting
in the park,
playing a little music.
And there were people
walking their dogs,
and children
were laughing.
It was a perfect day, so I...
felt like playing music.
(strumming chords)
I put my...
I put my hat out there,
but I wasn't really playing
for money.
I just thought that maybe
if someone was enjoying it,
they might throw
a little change in there.
(strumming steadily)
Or not. I just...
Well, music is better
if somebody's listening.
Anyway, this...
(steady strumming)
...this policeman
came up to me.
He said I was disturbing
the peace.
And then he tried to take
my guitar away from me.
And I guess I got
real angry at him.
(strumming resumes)
But I'm not a bad man.
I'm just...
[music] Not a lucky man [music]
(strumming steadily)
Anyway, they told me that I
broke that policeman's nose.
(strumming continues)
And they charged me with
assault on a police officer.
And no matter what I said,
they wouldn't listen.
No matter what I said,
they wouldn't...
They gave me
three years.
I said I'm...
not a bad man; I'm just...
(strumming continues)
[Music] Not a lucky man... [music]
But you. When I...
when I look at you...
(strumming continues)
[Music] You are like a butterfly [music]
[Music] A caterpillar's dream to fly [music]
[Music] To bust out
of this old cocoon [music]
[Music] And dry your wings off [music]
[Music] Butterfly [music]
[Music] Go ahead and fly... [music]
(guitar strumming continues)
OPAL:
I swept the floor real slow that day.
I wanted to keep Otis company.
I didn't want him to be lonely.
Sometimes it seemed to me
like everybody
in the whole world was lonely.
Yuck.
That tastes bad.
That tastes like
not having a dog.
OPAL:
I wondered if my mama...
wherever she was...
was lonely for me.
Thinking about her was the same
as the hole you keep on feeling
with your tongue
after you lose a tooth.
Time after time, my mind kept
on going to that empty spot.
The spot where I felt
like she should be.
Ooh, here, here!
(grunting)
BOY:
Get back in your spots.
BOY 2:
Okay.
STEVI E:
Strike one.
What do you think?
Shall we give some
to the boys?
(whines)
(sighs)
Yeah, but they haven't been
very nice.
They never want to play with us.
Try this one, Dunlap.
(boys shouting)
(barks)
Winn-Dixie!
I got it! I got it!
I got it!
Whoa!
There he is! Get him!
(boys shouting)
BOY:
Just get him!
Get the ball!
(growling)
Help me! Help me, Dunlap!
BOY:
Here comes the sheriff.
What in the name of corn on
the cob is goin' on around here?
Have we got
a situation here, fellas?
No, sir.
They're just all playin'.
(boys laughing)
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Keep away from me!
(barks)
(shouts)
Oh!
Get off of me!
- Off!
- (fabric tearing)
Get off of me, you hairy,
heavy-metal hound dog!
Ow! Give me my pants back!
Oh! That's a wedgie!
(shouts)
(screams)
This whole town's
gone mad!
(boys laughing)
Look, he has chicken legs!
I suppose you think
this is funny?
(laughter)
(shrieks)
Don't look at that!
(laughs):
He wasn't trying to hurt you.
He just wanted
to give you a candy.
(laughing)
You little sea-monkeys.
But I'm gonna see you
in sea-monkey jail.
(engine revving)
I better put it in drive.
(shouts)
(barks)
(sighs)
(song on radio)
(whining)
What's wrong?
You all right?
(whimpering)
(whispering):
Oh, Winn-Dixie!
How many did you eat of these?
(belches)
(whispering):
Oh! Oh, that's gross!
(belching loudly)
Oh, Winn-Dixie, ew!
PREACHER:
Opal, I hope you don't have
that dog in your bed.
(song continues)
(song ends)
Daddy?
Opal...
it's 2:00 in the morning.
What are you doing up?
Daddy, are you hungry?
You lookin'
for somethin' to eat?
Yeah, that's it.
I'm hungry.
(sniffles)
(sighs)
Try this.
What's this?
A Littmus lozenge.
Do you like it?
(scoffs)
Candy tastes melancholy.
What's melancholy?
Sad.
It's supposed to taste sad.
Makes me think
of your mother.
Do you think
about her a lot?
I do, Opal.
Daddy...
did she drink?
Opal, there's some things
you're just too
young to understand.
L-I understand a lot of things.
I know about people
with drinkin' problems.
(sighs)
Gloria Dump had
a drinking problem.
(whispering):
I want to understand.
Yeah, I don't
even understand
what happened
with your mama.
We were happy,
I know that,
for a long time.
Well, it seemed like a
long time, we were happy.
But then she
started drinkin'.
She started drinkin'...
and that's the tenth thing?
But it's more
complicated than that.
Did she drink
because I was bad?
Was it my fault
that she left?
No. No! No!
It's not your fault.
Don't... don't ever
say it's your fault.
(whispering):
Don't ever say that.
Do you hear me?
Yes, sir.
OPAL: I thought about how life
was like a Littmus lozenge,
how the sweet and the sad
were all mixed up together...
and how hard it was
to separate them out.
(whines)
He was so angry.
Well...
He was hurtin',
that's why.
Everybody's hurtin'.
Makes me feel sad.
I want to help 'em, but I
just don't know what to do.
Well... don't dwell
on it, child.
Why don't we see what Miss
Scarlett's doin', hmm?
I believe she's gettin'
ready for that party.
That's what we need to do!
"We" who?
We... me and you!
We should have a party!
Don't you think we should have
a party, Winn-Dixie?
(groans)
We can invite
Miss Franny Block...
- No, Opal!
...and the preacher and Otis.
Opal, don't go
in there!
Come on, we need
to start plannin'.
GLORIA:
No!
Wow, it's dark in here.
GLORIA:
Hold on, now, hon...
Opal?
Opal, wh-where are you?
Do you see?
- Don't, don't...
- That's a lot better.
Close those cur...
(sighs)
- Come on.
- Stop it!
You cannot have
any party here!
I haven't had folks
in here for years.
Just make sandwiches.
And Otis can bring
his guitar.
I said no, and that's
the end of it.
(whines)
Miss Franny said the problem
with people here
is that they forgot
how to share their sadness,
but what I think is that people
forgot how to share their joy.
Oh, Winn-Dixie, oh...
Gloria, we need this party.
(whines and barks)
(whispering):
Please?
Oh, Lord.
(sighs):
This child.
Well, if we're
gonna have a party...
this house needs
a big pick up
if we gonna have folks over.
Whee! We're having a party!
We're gonna have a party,
and don't you forget to
invite them Dewberry boys.
(singing)
Thank you, Opal!
Thanks.
You're welcome.
(singing continues)
GLORIA:
Fruit.
Oh!
(laughs)
Winn-Dixie!
(growls)
(singing ends)
You're gonna come, right?
Yeah, l-I'll be there.
Should be done with
prayer group by then.
We're havin' a party,
and you're invited.
You don't have to thank me.
It was Winn-Dixie's idea.
Come on, Winn-Dixie.
Come on.
MR. ALFRED:
Little miss?
He don't howl so much anymore.
He's not so lonely anymore.
Come on.
Mr. Alfred, you're one
of the first people here.
Well, there's no sense in
dilly-dallying, you know?
Hello, Opal.
Hi, Miss Franny.
Mr. Alfred,
do you know Miss Franny?
No.
Miss Franny. Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I brung dog pictures
for the theme of the party.
Oh! That's great,
Sweetie Pie.
Let me show you.
Come on, Winn-Dixie.
Oh, wow,
they're beautiful!
AMANDA:
Hey, Opal.
Oh, hey, Amanda!
I'm so glad you could come.
Thank you for
inviting me.
Oh, thanks for comin'.
- Hey, Winn-Dixie.
- Hold on.
Okay.
Gloria!
Gloria! Gloria.
GLORIA:
I'm comin', I'm comin'.
I'm comin', baby girl.
Don't rush me.
Please don't rush me.
I'm so nervous.
I haven't done this
in such a long time.
It's okay.
You look beautiful.
Well, thank you for my
hair and my fingernails.
And you look pretty, too.
You wearin' that
necklace I gave you?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, everything is
so beautiful, Opal.
I can see it.
I can just see it.
Hi, Gloria.
Who's that?
Oh, Gloria, I'd like you
to meet my new friend, Amanda.
Amanda.
What a beautiful name.
- I'm glad you came.
- Thank you.
- Come on.
- Me, too.
Come on. And this is
Miss Franny Block.
Hello, Gloria.
I've heard all about you.
I hope you're enjoying
Gone with the Wind.
(gasps):
Oh... thank you.
- You're welcome.
- And that's Mr. Alfred.
Miss Gloria,
I'm delighted to meet you.
GERTRUDE:
Gertrude's a pretty bird.
MR. ALFRED:
I had no idea all this was back here.
- Hello.
- Hey, Otis!
Otis. Uh-oh.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
It's all right.
It's just a few people.
Hardly any people at all.
I brought pickles.
Pickles.
Have a pickle.
Oh! That's just exactly
what we needed.
They'll go perfectly
with the egg salad sandwiches.
Oh, Gertrude's a
pretty bird!
(squawks)
- Oh.
- (sighs)
Miss Franny, this is Otis.
Oh! Oh!
What happened?
The-the pickles fell.
It's a pleasure
to shake your hand, Otis.
Thank you.
I brought pickles.
Yes, I see. It's nice.
Oh, and this
is Gloria Dump.
I brought pickles
for the party.
I'm glad you did.
I mean, wouldn't have been
no party without pickles.
Now, I've been
to several parties with no pickles.
(chuckles)
A-And not one of
'em was any fun.
Otis, you can put
the pickles down right over here.
Thank you, ma'am.
(whispering):
Baby girl, what happened
with the Dewberry boys?
And where's the preacher?
Uh, I don't know.
Well, I told 'em what
time we're startin'.
GERTRUDE:
Uh-oh.
Look at that dog
and look at that bird!
- (laughing)
- Oh, no! Winn-Dixie!
No, Winn-Dixie!
Get down! Get down!
Winn-Dixie, come on.
Well, if we don't eat soon,
there won't be any food left.
I think you're right.
Let's just hold hands and...
give thanks for this.
Opal, give me your hand.
Winn-Dixie, sit.
Dear Lord
and Heavenly Father,
we have egg salad sandwiches,
we got Dump's punch,
we got pickles,
we got doggy pictures,
and we have
Littmus lozenges,
but, more importantly,
Dear Lord, we have good friends.
Dear Lord, we got
good friends to share
this warm summer night with us,
and, for that,
we're grateful.
Teach us, dear Lord,
to love one another.
This we ask in Your name.
Amen.
ALL:
SWEETI E PI E:
Are we fixin' to eat now?
I think we might
want to eat inside.
(thunder rumbles)
It's not supposed to rain.
MISS FRANNY:
Oh! Oh, my God.
(shouting)
Nobody said rain.
It didn't pred...
Get the sandwiches!
Get the punch!
I got the plates!
Somebody get the punch!
Get the sandwiches!
Pickle?
(shouting)
Oh, yes, I'm cleaned up
real good, now.
Did you get
the sandwiches?
Somebody get
Yeah. They're
all wet, Gloria.
- And the punch?
- Yeah.
GERTRUDE:
Get the sandwiches?
(squawks)
Uh-oh.
Pickles. Pickles. Pickles.
Comin' down.
- Can I talk to you, please?
- Oh, sure.
GERTRUDE:
Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
Opal, you worked real hard. I...
I brought this for you.
I figured you'd earned it.
Oh! Thanks, Otis.
(squawking):
Dog! Dog! Dog!
Don't worry.
I got them dog pictures.
I got 'em right here.
Winn-Dixie!
Oh, no!
(gasps):
Winn-Dixie!
He's scared of thunder!
Winn... Winn-Dixie.
No, Winn-Dixie, no!
Opal, no, no, no.
- No, no!
- Look, he's probably outside
under the chair.
We'll take the
flashlight and go look.
No, no!
- I forgot to hold onto him!
- Opal! Opal!
Opal, take the flashlight.
Opal!
Opal! Uh...
Winn-Dixie!
GLORIA:
You can't see!
Come back!
Opal! Opa...
Dewberry boys.
You got all wet. Opal!
No, Winn-Dixie!
Opal, your guests are here!
Opa...
Opal, your guests
are here.
I don't care!
Now, you come up here
right this minute!
Come right up here!
Now, let me
tell you somethin'!
This is your party,
and I want you
to tell these boys
how glad you are
that they came.
Thank you for comin'
to my party.
It's just I got to find
Winn-Dixie.
You want me to help?
Listen...
Opal...
you cannot hold onto anything
that wants to go.
Do you understand
what I'm sayin'?
You just got to love it
while you got it,
and that's that.
(panting)
I just got to find him!
Opal, wait
till the rain stops!
Opal!
Opal...
Winn-Dixie!
(grunts)
(pants):
Is he here?!
Who?
Winn-Dixie! He's gone!
He ran away
because of the storm,
and I can't find him!
Come on in out
of the rain, Opal.
Come on!
We were at the party,
and you were supposed
to be there!
(panting)
And you weren't,
and now he's gone!
Opal.
Op...!
Opal!
Come back here!
Here, take your raincoat.
We'll look for him together.
Winn-Dixie!
Winn-Dixie?
I'll write a list
of ten things about him.
That way, people'll know him
if they see him.
We'll find him, Opal.
One: He has a pathological fear
of thunderstorms.
Two: He likes to smile
at everyone he meets.
Three:
He likes going to church.
Four: He snores.
Five: He can catch mice
without squishing 'em to death.
Number six.
Number six is he likes
to meet people.
Number seven: He sure does like
peanut butter.
Number eight: He can't stand
to be left alone.
Nine: He likes to sit on
couches and sleep in beds.
Number ten is... he was a dog
who knew how to be a friend.
I kept on goin'over and over
that list in my head,
the same way I did
with the list
of ten things about my mama.
Winn-Dixie!
I memorized it
so if I didn't find him,
I'd at least have
some part of him to hold onto.
Winn-Dixie!
(sighs)
It's gettin' late, Opal.
You're gettin' tired.
We need to head back.
But, Daddy,
he's out there.
We can't leave him.
Well, there's only
so much lookin' we can do.
(sighs)
You're gonna give up.
Opal...
You give up on everything.
That's not true.
It is true.
All you do is give up.
Just pull your head
back inside your stupid
turtle shell and give up.
You won't talk.
You won't go
to parties.
(sighs)
And I bet you didn't
even go out lookin'
for my mama when she left.
(sighs)
I bet you just let her
run off, too.
I couldn't stop her.
I tried.
I... No, loo... I tried.
You don't think
I wanted her to stay, too?
She was everything to me.
- You didn't try.
- Yes, I did.
She wasn't everything to you.
Yes, she was.
Opal, she was everything.
Everything. I f...
I failed her, all right?
I failed her.
I failed her, Opal.
I tried and I t...
- You didn't try!
- I tried and I tr...
- I know you didn't.
- I tried.
I did. I tried
and I tried and I tried
with everything I am.
It's my fault.
Opal... it's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
(whispering):
Daddy...
I ju...
And don't... don't believe
losing Winn-Dixie
isn't gonna upset me
as much as it does you.
I love that dog.
I love him, too.
(sighs)
(whispering):
I love you, Daddy.
(sighs)
I love you, too.
Daddy...
do you think Mama
will ever come back?
No. No, I don't, Opal.
I've hoped and prayed and
dreamed about her comin' back.
I don't think
it's gonna happen.
Gloria told me that you can't
hold onto anybody...
that you can only love what
you got while you've got it.
Gloria Dump is a wise person.
But I'm not ready
to let Winn-Dixie go.
Well, we'll keep on lookin'.
Opal...
do you remember
when I told you
that your mama took everything
with her when she left?
Yes, sir.
Well, there's one
very important thing
she left behind.
What?
You.
(laughs)
Thank God your mama left me you.
Did you find him?
No.
Not yet. We haven't
found him yet.
We went looking, too.
We drove all over.
MISS FRANNY:
I'm sorry, Opal.
We just drove
all over town.
I had a dog once that wandered
all over the place.
And?
And... when he got
through wanderin'...
he came home.
Don't worry, Opal.
He'll come back.
He's got to.
Preacher?
PREACHER:
Mm-hmm.
You're blessed
with this one.
(sighs)
(whispering):
Is she prayin'?
DUNLAP:
Are you prayin'?
No, I'm not prayin'.
I'm just thinkin'.
What about?
OPAL:
A lot of different things.
L-I'm sorry I called you guys
bald-headed babies.
You want to come
back inside?
I guess so.
(crickets chirping)
I'll race you to the angel
by the porch.
DUNLAP:
Go!
PREACHER:
Otis, you know any hymns?
OTIS:
Yeah, I know some.
Yeah?
You hum it, Daddy.
I know he can play it.
Oh, all right. Um...
(humming "Glory, Glory')
(singing):
[Music] Hallelujah [music]
[Music] Since I lay
my burden down [music]
Yeah.
ALL (singing):
[Music] Glory, glory [music]
- [Music] Hallelujah... [music]
- (dog howling)
(dog barking)
OPAL:
Winn-Dixie!
(whining)
AMANDA:
Oh, Winn-Dixie, hi!
SWEETI E PI E:
Winn-Dixie, Winn-Dixie!
Where have you been,
you dumb dog?
We looked all over,
Winn-Dixie!
(indistinct voices)
Well?
Are we havin' a party,
or are we havin'
a paaaarrrrrttty?!
We're havin' a party,
and the theme is this dog.
GLORIA:
All right!
MISS FRANNY:
It is lovely.
It is beautiful.
(singing):
[Music] I feel better... [music]
GLORIA:
Good, feel better.
ALL (singing):
[Music] So much better [music]
[Music] Since I lay my burden down [music]
[Music] I feel better [music]
[Music] So much better [music]
[Music] Since I lay my burden down [music]
[Music] Feel like shouting... [music]
Feel like shoutin'!
- [Music] "Hallelujah!" [music]
- (howls)
[Music] Since I lay my burden down [music]
- Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
- [Music] Feel like shouting [music]
ALL:
[Music] "Hallelujah!" [music]
[Music] Since I lay my burden down [music]
I am climbing Jacob's ladder...
ALL:
[Music] I am climbing [music]
OTIS:
ALL:
[Music]Jacob's Ladder [music]
[Music] Since I lay my burden down [music]
[Music] I am climbing Jacob's ladder [music]
[Music] Every round goes... [music]
GLORIA:
Higher, higher!
ALL:
[Music] Higher, higher [music]
[Music] Since I lay
my burden down... [music]
OPAL:
My heart doesn't feel so empty anymore.
It's full... all the way up.
I've got Winn-Dixie.
I've got Gloria Dump,
and Miss Franny Block,
and Otis,
and even the Dewberry boys.
And I also have
the preacher back as my daddy.
It was a good story, right?
And it's all because of...
well, you know.
ALL:
[Music] Since I lay my burden down. [music]
Glory! Hallelujah!
Hallelujah!
All right!
(percussive music plays)
CHOIR: (singing)
(singing ends)
(slow pop song playing)
(vocalizing)
(singing continues)
(singing ends)
5@y3
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org