Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
O God,
bless, we pray You,
our great army
and its supreme commander
on the eve ofa holy war
undertaken for Your sake,
and grant,
in the name of your Prophet,
our great Lawgiver,
that we, Your chosen servants,
created and born
in Your divine image,
may aspire the more perfectly
to that spiritual Godliness
and bodily beauty
which You, in Your infinite mercy,
have thought fit to deny
to our brutish enemies!
So be it.
There they go,
Dr. Zaius trotting
along beside them.
Don't be too hard
on the old boy, Zira.
His motives are honest.
He has only one motive..
to keep things
exactly as
they have always been.
I say that it's
time for a change.
We chimpanzees are too few.
How can we take initiative
when they're in control?
Love, yes! War, no!
No more lies!
No more crying!
No more guns!
No more blood! Stop!
Stop!
Stop the war!
Freedom! Freedom!
Whoa!
Freedom! Peace!
Peace and freedom!
Get off the road, young people.
Freedom! Peace!
Get them out of the way.
Wait.
We don't want martyrs,
do we?
We want peace!
We want freedom!
Major, do it quietly.
We want peace!
We want freedom!
Peace!
Freedom! Peace!
Freedom!
Peace and freedom!
Battalion.
Are you what we were
before we learned to talk
and made a mess of everything?
Did any good ever
come from all that talk
around all those tables?
I wonder where
the hell they are?
the hell we are?
I think we're near
the Forbidden Zone.
That's where the army's headed.
They'll roll right over us.
Why can't we go
back to our outfits?
Because the sarge
says to keep looking
until we find them.
Nova.
Nova, Nova, wake up.
We've got to go. Come on.
That hum...
You hear it, too?
All right, come on,
we're going to follow it.
Well, whoever or whatever...
something's guiding us.
Whatever they are,
they breathe air.
Well, there's an intelligence
working in this place.
That sound, good or bad,
it's either a warning
or a directional device.
It doesn't matter.
They know we're here.
Put my hands...
around her throat.
Off!.
Hold her throat!
She...
dies!
Get out!
Get out of my head!
I reveal my inmost self
unto my God.
What did you say?
What do you mean there's no point?
Will they hurt her?
No, maybe not
physically, but here.
Here, you can hurt here. I know.
Your lips...
don't move.
But I can hear.
No, I mean...
I know what you're thinking.
Nothing. I...
I saw nothing.
Who are you?
It's Brent.
Oh, I see.
The only reality in the universe.
That's nice to know.
I got here by accident.
How did you get here?
You got it all wrong.
Why would I want to spy on you?
I'm not even sure you exist.
Ofcourse I know who I am!
I'm an astronaut!
I was sent here
on a rescue mission
to find a fellow
astronaut, Taylor.
We're from this planet,
but from another time,
2,000 years ago.
I know l...
I know I sound insane.
And it's my insanity.
No, I don't know how to get back.
We came through a defect,
a slippage in time.
That's what must have
happened to Taylor.
I'm sure he tried to get back.
Yes, my Skipper is dead.
I'm..I'm alone.
Who?
Nova? What's that?
Some star? A galaxy? What's Nova?
All right, all right, yes!
I know her. I know her.
No, no. She's harmless.
Let her alone.
Tell me what you want to know.
Tell me.
She helped me
to break out ofape city.
No! Wait a minute!
Stop it!
I can't understand you.
You're all screaming at me
at the same time.
I can't separate it!
He's right.
He has only limited intelligence.
We should speak aloud,
and one at a time.
You were in the city of the apes?
Yes, two days ago.
What sights did you see?
You're talking.
Certainly we can talk.
We use speech when we must.
When we pray.
When we sing to our God.
You mean that..
that thing out there,
an atomic bomb, your god?
You don't understand.
The Bomb is a holy
weapon of peace.
Holy weapon of peace!
Peace.
Mr. Brent, we're a patient people,
but we are determined
to know what the apes want..
war or peace.
Try to understand.
The only weapons we have
are purely illusion.
You just imagined that he hurt you.
Traumatic hypnosis
is a weapon of peace.
Like the visual deterrent..
or the sonic deterrent..
Let me make a last appeal
to your reason
before we inflict more of this on you.
These are weapons of peace, Mr. Brent.
Like all our weapons.
Mere illusions.
Mere illusions? Damn your hypocrisy!
Is that bomb out there,
is that an illusion?
It's operational, isn't it?
The firing mechanism..
it's intact, isn't it?
We very much need
your help, Mr. Brent.
Why?
We are the keepers
of the Divine Bomb.
It is our only reason for survival.
And yet, as you see,
we are defenseless,
defenseless against
the slaughtering,
monstrous, materialistic apes.
I'll help nobody.
So go ahead. Annihilate each other.
I forgive you your language.
Sometimes your sanity
is about to give way.
I hope that does not happen.
I hope you can tell us..
Exactly what the apes are planning.
We've caught some of their scouts.
They're hideous creatures.
We've had them here,
standing precisely where you are now.
Either their skulls were too thick,
or they really
knew nothing at all.
Neither do l.
Can't you understand that?
I don't know anything!
You make us very sad, Mr. Brent.
She can't help you.
She can't even talk.
Don't harm her.
We never harm anyone, Mr. Brent.
You're going to harm her.
The apes sent me out to you.
You're lying.
How do you know?
How do you always know?
Nova.
Now..
Tell us of the apes.
The apes...
are marching on your city.
Bugler,
sound the advance.
Ursus!
Ursus, I warned you.
Look what we're faced with!
I told you you should wait!
Brutal butchery!
I swear, those responsible
shall pay with
torture and with death.
If you have any pity,
give orders to shoot
our poor people.
I can't order them to do
what the Lawgiver has forbidden.
Ape shall not kill ape.
Hold your positions!
He bleeds.
The Lawgiver bleeds!
The spirit of the Lawgiver lives!
We are still God's chosen!
This is a vision!
And it is a lie!
The vision was false!
Bugler,
sound the advance.
Advance!
Stupid animals.
They don't have the brain
to hold our illusions.
We have no defense.
Except our Bomb.
Call our people to the high sanctuary.
Do you know the range
of their city?
Yes.
Set in the mechanism and wait for me.
I want a public thought projection
at adult and infant level.
Adults to the cathedral,
infants indoors.
Is nowandevershallbe
World without end
Amen
The heavens declare
the glory of the Bomb,
and the firmament
showeth His handiwork.
His sun has gone out
unto all the land.
And gives light
unto the end of the world.
He descendeth from the
outermost part of heaven,
and there is nothing
hid from the heat thereof.
There is neither
speech nor language,
yet His voice is heard among them.
Praise Him.
My strength and my redeemer.
Glory be to the Bomb
and to the holy fallout
as it was in
the beginning, is now,
and ever shall be,
world without end.
Amen.
Amen
Almighty and everlasting Bomb,
who came down among us
to make heaven under Earth,
Iighten our darkness.
I nstrument ofGod,
grant us Thy peace.
AlmightyBomb
Who destroyedallheavens
Andcreatedangels
BeholdHis glory
Behold the truth that abides in us.
Reveal that truth unto that Maker.
I reveal my inmost self unto my God.
Unto my God.
Unto my God
All things brightandbeautiful
All creatures greatandsmall
All things wise and wonderful
The good Bomb made us all
He gave us eyes to see with
And lips that we might tell
How great the Bomb Almighty
Who made all things well
Let everyone go
to his private shelter.
Empty the streets.
They're to find
the city of the dead.
May the blessing
of the Bomb Almighty
and the fellowship
of the Holy Fallout
descend on us this day
and forevermore.
Amen
I trust this simple ceremony
convinced you of
our peaceable intentions,
and I'd like to thankyou
foryour cooperation.
When may we hope
to be set free?
You may hope whenever
you please, Mr. Brent.
How could we
hope to let you go
on the eve ofwar, Mr. Brent?
You know too many ofour secrets,
Iike your friend.
Taylor!
You're Brent.
My God, Taylor!
Brent! How in the hell
did you get here?
Spaceship, ape city, subway..
Byyourself?
No, Nova found me.
Nova? ls she with you? Where?
I don't know. They separated us.
They tried to make me kill her.
Mr. Taylor, Mr. Brent,
we're peaceful people.
We don't kill our enemies.
We get our enemies
to kill each other.
I'm fighting it.
I'm fighting it off.
Taylor.
Taylor!
Unto God...
I reveal my inmost self.
This isn't exactly sterile.
We'll do the best we can.
Taylor.
Taylor, they've got a bomb..
Atomic bomb.
It's operational.
They intend to use it.
What type is it?
I don't know.
I don't know what type.
I've never seen it before.
Didn't you see a series number?
No numbers, just some
letters on one of the fins,
Greek letters.
Alpha...
And omega.
What?
The doomsday bomb.
My God.
Another lovely souvenir
from the 20th Century.
They weren't satisfied with a bomb
that could knock out a city.
They finally built one
with a cobalt casing,
all in the sweet name of peace.
Those bloody fools.
They don't know what they've got.
They pray to the damn thing.
If they shoot it off,
it could set off a chain reaction
in the whole atmosphere.
Burn the planet to a cinder.
How's that for
your ultimate weapon?
This must be what
your scout reported,
a subterranean passage.
I think it's worth exploring.
What will you do, Holiness?
Everything necessary.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
I'm thinking just that.
Nova.
Ah, God!
Should let them all die..
the gorillas, every damn...
When it comes time.
It's time it was finished.
Finished.
Taylor.
Come on, come on.
The bomb.
Yeah.
Why not?
They're obscene!
Follow me!
Sergeant!
Arrest that creature.
This is the instrument of my God.
He can speak.
Your God, eh?
Sergeant.
Your God didn't
save you, did he, huh?
Ursus!
That weapon is built by man.
You can't shoot it
down with bullets.
If we can't shoot it down,
we'll pull it down.
Rope! Block and tackle!
You don't know what you're doing.
It will kill us all!
I'll find a way to stop it.
Men, over there!
Ursus, someone at the pillar!
Zaius.
Taylor!
It's dooms day.
The end of the world.
Help me.
You ask me to help you!
Man is evil,
capable of nothing
but destruction!
You...
bloody bastard.
In one of the countless billions
of galaxies in the universe
Iies a medium-sized star.
And one of its satellites,
a green
and insignificant planet,
now is dead.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org