Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Grendel
Pappie!
Yahhhhh!!! Yahhhhhh!
Ahhhh! Owwee.
Aohhhhheeweee!
Yoeyeo!
Yahhhheeoooooooooweewaaaa!
Let this great horn tell the world
no man stands above the Danes.
All we look up on is ours.
Hrothgar much loved king of the Danes.
Under Odirs eye I blood you lucky
on all parts that leave this hall.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhh!
Blahhhhhhhhhehhhhhhahhhhh!
Ahhhhhh! Blehhahhhhh!
May all those who cross
these steps find a happy heart.
Yay!
Olaf!
Olaf! Pal!
Where were you when all this happened?
Asleep.
I'd had some beers.
What fucking thing would dare...
G'day
G'Day.
I'd love much to know man, whereabouts?
Fish beach.
Likely I'm the only one
who names it that.
Where I get fish.
I'm Beowulf
Beowulf?
Yea Beowulf the what?
Heh? The eel meal?
You've never had another?
Wash up like myself?
In the name of Breca? Ahhh.
We were out hunting walrus
a couple of days ago...
when a storm came up and ate our boat.
So this is just you coming in now?
Yeah
You've ever swum in the open sea?
I leave that to my boat.
Ahh. I'd like to think you'd botter me.
I can't see much life in that.
Do you do this a lot?
I take what comes.
Good then you'll have no qualms
if supper tastes like you.
Eat, be yourself.
So, what's it like being a hero?
Qualling things with axes and,
and that sword of yours. And what.
Kinda bloody madness. Heh
In truth I don't get all that mad.
So, ahhh hahh-hhhah,
A hero ahhh, A hero for supper.
Don't my shit shine.
Hah, hahhhh, hahhh
I'm in your debt
I'm in the fishes.
All these days have come for theirs.
The winds were kind.
No storm waylaid Sawthwood
from his hard walk home.
None in Geatland held so strong the love
of kin as Beowulf.
But coming home he heard the tale.
Friends to the west
slept with slaughter.
...from death upon the Danes.
Great Beowulf alone had best it bares
thought fearless in their mood
for men but now he brought a half score
or more Geat swords
to swing against this thing.
Let's hear the names
Breca the loud.
HahhhAhhhh
Right from the seas.
Lost no son in hoisting sword.
Hoisting swords?
He couldn't hoist his own sail.
The huncho. Queller of puffins
Hahhh.
...and beer.
Shook his shields to shake the world.
No. Just on that scum troll's head.
Beowulf.
Well as we've done these last few years
this sail holds grim bliss for me.
A thing that takes two hundred
in arms is no small thing.
But I will see Valhalla
or that thing's head on a pole.
Aye, aye, aye
So that Danes might say Geats don't
wield words where swords speak truer.
Ayyye. Yea.
Great as our own shield king Is,
there is another nearest kin to me.
None bleed for a better king
than Hrothgar I'd die happy.
Loved as he.
But we live happy even now.
So, Beowulf goes at dawn to the Danes
all you who go along, keep us proud.
Yeahhh!
And if you can find Hondscioh
a wife our sheep have had enough.
Troll!!!!!!!!!
Trollllllllll!
Trollll!!!!!! I call you out!!!!
Trolll!!!!
Trollllllllllllllll!!!!!!!
Meet me the like if you dare!
Or fight me in hell. You hairy creep.
Creep. Creep!
Ahhhmmm.
Ahhhhhhhh!!!!!!!!!!
Are you wounded?
The thing wouldn't fight.
It spared me to witness this.
Then get up off your arse
with your Thanes insight.
This is no ground for a game.
Ahh, you're wrong where a king
who has had his balls hauled up
his guts it is the ground.
All the broken bone wretches
I've flung to death.
And to Valhalla.
I don't know.
Is that the look of
a man going happily up to the feast?
Or down to the worms?
You talk like a mad man.
No!
Just like the Danish king of daylight
Get up now or do we bury you here?
Is that your wish?
With your thanes in sight?
Whose wife would you have me be?
A burly sword of Christ to cleave you
thus, and thus and thus!
That's one shiny sword.
I'm told you're the Dane's king.
Connaught wishes you well
Celt, you're a ways from home
I am but safe with the sword of Christ.
Father Brendan.
Christ. I heard of him.
You ever have much luck with trolls?
I'm of the thought
they've never crossed paths,
but if you're willing to bow
before Christ you shall feel
the blessing of his great strength.
My gods don't ask me to bow.
And nor should they dare
if they won't protect ye.
To fear god's fools is an honor.
I've come to drive this evil out.
With your stick?
With the fire of heaven!
Well if your heavers on fire
you'd better look to that.
You leave me
on a dish for the troll then.
Leave me.
And if I don't see mars stone.
I shall see god's! I shall see god!
Ahhh!
Selma, should I fear for my husband?
You've got nothing better to do?
Sweet don't play the bitch with me.
I don't ask much and I don't ask often.
No one dares dirty your name around me.
Nor yours around me.
Hrothgar dies happy, in his sleep.
That's a lift.
Selma, I could find
a place for you inside.
We chose our beds along time back.
Men!
Hold there!
As you wish.
Is this land Dane?
It is and you're not.
So unless you're ready for a shower
of arrows you tell who you are!
Two blows from this
and fifty men will be on this beach
before your next breath.
Fifty birds maybe.
Is that then your word?
I'm Beowulf.
Beowulf the Geat?
Ahh, here we go.
We come as friends for Hrothgar.
Well we welcome friends.
Bring what you need.
I'll have men look to your ship.
Welcome to Daneland
By Thor they have the spark of cows.
Who's that?
Selma, a witch.
The happy would keep
a boat length from her
Happiness isn't everything.
She sees people's deaths.
That is one beer hall.
If you like to drink with the ghosts.
Beowulf!
Oh my little Beowulf,
nobody tells me anything.
I somehow think of you as smaller
I was eight when I left.
Ahh you've grown. Ahh.
I'm sorry we didn't mean to wake you.
Wake me.
I'm a grief crippled king half drunk
in the middle of the afternoon,
what's there to wake?
By the gods it's good to see you.
Hahh, hahh!
Hah! Hah!
You think you need a beer?
-Ah, ya.
-Aye.
If Geat were seeking a wife,
this room would hold better
up than most.
So many.
Widows.
Widows far too early.
Ho, ho.
Ah...
With my King I welcome you all.
We can never forget this gift.
Hahh. Nannnnannnannnannnnanaaaan
From this night on
the only working flesh
this troll feasts on will be it's own.
Yae!
With the morning,
your curse will be less than a shadow.
Yas!
Well maybe not less,
but I mean to hold in my hand
the head that by my sword
no more steers a dead troll body.
Yas!
We'll hoist the shield now
Drive that hunger back down it's mouth.
Await, can chew on it's tongue.
It can chew on it's own stinking stone
of a heart,
...but no more Danes.
We mean to put an end to this fiend.
Yas!
As other's vowed
Unferth!
By you will dear Queen.
We're wiser in knowing the hearts of
those who tangled with that thing.
Those are dead.
I don't brag of wrestling with it.
Nor of Being able to kill it.
The troll broke down these doors with
twenty Danish warriors sleeping inside.
What gives thirteen Geats better hope?
We won't be sleeping.
Unferth!
Sit!
Or see your guts in a dish.
Now before the dark will sharpen us -
play, drink.
No.
Since it began we'll have Swedes,
Saxons even Sloths even coming
to see how weak we were.
Ya I know, I look like walrus shit.
Comes from fighting things you can't.
All bad dreams end.
We'll see you in the morning
for herring and egg.
Herring and egg?
Now, if there's anything
you need to tell me about it,
now would be the time.
I'll stay here. Amongst you.
We'll bring you the head -
throw it in with the herring and egg.
MMMMMMMMmmmm
Ahhhh, hahhahahhhaa
Ahhhhhhhhhhh!!!!!!
Priest.
Where did you spend the night?
Why was such a dark wretch spared?
That's not what he asked.
Wise king.
You must know of the name of Clovis
The Frank?
The Frank, yes, yes, the Frank.
The Christian Sword over land ten times
what the Danes hold dear.
He's dead.
Yes, ten years now.
...but not before he saw God's grace.
The Visigoths of Aquitaine, the Romans
and the Syagrius, Burgundians,
Alamans all fell before him
and all because he had God's ear.
As I recall yours had a thousand swords.
Neighbors offered wine and pork
and no eyes at his ribs.
And no fucking trolls!
My skinny hand can only bless,
but trust me.
This thing shall meet it's end
in striking me or those of mine.
Madness has it's wonders.
The Celt sat straight in
the path of the thing.
It was not touched.
The Celt held no sword.
Perhaps the thing hates weapons.
The old men were armed, true.
Others here in arms have been spared.
I have been waiting for Odin
to bring me my death.
He hasn't.
In his wisdom?
This is where the blood trails led.
I tell you,
this troll must be one tough prick.
Do this climb every night after supper?
Why don't you blow your horn now,
I wouldn't mind
those fifty bows bragged of.
I could bring the bows.
But the men are gone.
Thorfinn!
Are you alright?
-I'm fine.
-Good
A little high up for driftwood.
What are we fighting here?
A Thing beyond our ken.
Could spread out...
meet back here in a year?
We're out of our world.
Padre, santi...
Go in peace my son, go in peace.
Next!
I was off in a dream.
Wish I could bring a better one.
Baptism they call it.
Unferth feels that he's fallen
from the grace of the gods.
It's not every mars wish
to sit in blood.
If this Christ can stiffen
Unferth's heart, what's the harm?
They swim only out of fear.
But still... they swim.
Dusk soon, eh.
You a herd dog?
I've been called worse.
I'm Beowulf...
Yes. The much-told hero from Geatland.
So who are your people?
None. I came here in my teens.
A whore to Unferth's uncle,
Alvis Three-Legs.
So you're not then Dane?
Oh I am.
My family was killed by Wulfing raiders.
Ah, my father too...
not killed, but...
I mean, but a feud
with the Wulfings brought us here.
I guess you werert made a whore.
I'm told you know of things to come.
Hmm, that's a wide sea.
Of deaths of things.
Seeing that everything living dies
you still give me the sight of gods.
Speak clean. You wonder of yourself.
More of the troll.
Not of yourself?
In some things I'd rather be blind.
You're worse than Loki
with your sheepshit twining.
The death of the troll will cost dear
both the Geats and the Danes...
as it bloody well should.
Why as it should?
The Danes have done their doom on him.
And you come here to kill.
Day's going down.
If we want to be ready...
Careful with what you don't understand.
Has this thing,
this troll killed any children...
-No.
-women?
Old men?
What are you saying?
It fights with a clean heart?
It kills the strongest first.
It shows us and kills the strongest.
Who cares if he spares the children?
They'll die anyways
without their fathers.
My wits still war
with how this all began
It came for the mead hall...
I can only guess.
The night we finished it,
before creep came,
we hadrt seen a troll in
fifteen twenty years.
So nothing was done to the troll itself?
Oh Beowulf!
It's a fucking troll!
Maybe someone looked at it
the wrong way!
Some Dane?
Who hands you this? Selma?
Come on.
She's been out in the wilds too long.
Her head is full of spiders,
her lap is full of moss.
It's said she sees things.
Well the crazy do see things.
I never begged anyone to come here
and take on our fight.
I don't hold you here...
I know you don't.
Then don't saddle my heart
with the talk of
why a fucking troll does
what fucking troll does.
Ahhhhh!!!!!
Ahhhhhhhhh!!!!
Watch the sides!
Cone on crab slime,
show me these teeth.
O'er the night, the warriors waited,
sword and shield in ring wrapped grasp.
Then the fiend of bog and brine reached
those doors of ten mers weight,
...bade it creak by breath alone.
But then smelt God amongst the men.
Hardly had they hoisted steel,
this thing's rank guts gave out.
Great Beowulf, God's awful arm...
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org