Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
How'd that happen?
lf l can ask.
Oh.
Before time,
l was sick, bad lung, TB.
At this time no doctor
where l live.
Khmer Rouge kill our doctor.
So, l walk to border
for medicine,
but l must cross
the mine field first.
You never forget that sound.
The first thing you hear
is click.
lt's your foot priming
the land mine.
Soon as you hear it,
it's over.
But your mind go crazy,
you know?
You thinking, maybe if l jump,
maybe if l find a rock
to match my weight...
But it's nothing you can do.
You hear the click
and big bye-bye.
But,
l was lucky.
Just lose my leg.
Any problems?
None.
You're not wearing perfume.
So, are you going to tell me
where we're going?
A place near Pailin,
by the border.
And the boat's
the best way to travel?
You don't like my boat?
l think it's very you.
lt's safer.
Avoids the road blocks,
the Viet troops,
plus other assorted madness.
You know, heart of darkness.
The horror.
Actually it is.
Horrible.
And now you're going
to tell me why.
Well, Elliott's no good, is he?
All he gives you is
the Buddhist version,
all fucking temples
and gentle people,
which is bollocks.
The Khmer Rouge--
rouge being very much
the appropriate color--
used Pailin as a hideout.
Everyone lives
in absolute terror.
They use the women
as baby-making factories,
the kids as mine sweepers,
and just in case
we actually help anybody,
they come and steal everything
that we don't hide.
So why do they let you
stay at all?
They've got no doctors.
l should be singing
''Old Man River.''
Please don't.
Colonel Tao,
how are you doing?
lt's good to see you again.
The boxes, they for who?
Well, you know who they're for.
l give you my word.
This goes only
to the women and children.
Wait, easy, that's medicine,
for Christ's sake!
l don't understand,
what's the problem?
lt's a laptop.
Every NGO has got one.
That's the way
we do business here.
Don't throw those away.
People's lives depend on that,
for fuck's sake!
-Colonel...
-Sarah...
l'm with UNHCR, United Nations.
This cargo is protected.
lf this shipment is harmed
in any way,
your name will surface
in the follow-up investigation.
l don't...
l promise you,
l know nothing about this.
Somebody must have...
Colonel Tao, you know me.
l swear to God,
l don't...
Son of a bitch!
What was that?
You explain it to me.
l can't explain it to you.
We were set up.
l knew nothing about that book,
what was in the box,
the equipment...
Did you know about the guns?
Answer me!
Did you know...?
Yes, l knew about them.
l came here
to help these people,
and the only way
l can do that
-is if l transport guns.
-You don't have
to transport guns
to help people.
You do here.
Right. So fuck the next person
that tries to bring
a shipment full of medicine
in for people.
Fuck them.
As long as you get
what you need today,
fuck everybody else!
No one else comes here,
so what do you want me to do?
You want me to watch
thousands of kids die of measles
'cause l wouldn't
bend the rules?
ls that a price worth paying?
Or am l actually killing
more than l save?
You seriously believe that
l don't worry about that?
That l don't think about that
every minute of every day?
What's worse?
You tell me.
You tell me what l should do.
What happened?
Never compromise
another organization
for your own ever again.
l won't.
Sarah, you made it.
Oh, good to see you.
So, l believe congratulations
are in order?
l know, can you believe it?
Oh...
What the hell happened?
No guns--
confiscated by Tao.
He found
these intelligence files.
They freaked him out.
What intelligence files?
Well, how do l know?
He was tipped off.
He was waiting for us.
He found these documents.
He went fucking crazy.
Well, if we don't have anything
for the Khmer Rouge,
we're in deep shit.
We leave in the morning.
Take everyone with us.
No, we need to leave
sooner than that.
We've got all this vaccine.
l'm not wasting it.
We don't have time.
We need to go now.
Not until we vaccinate.
This is not worth risking
our lives for.
You do whatever you got to do.
l'm staying.
Joss, remember to pack
the iodine.
And the emergency kits--
how many we got?
Joss?
No, no. They...
He says that we're thieves,
that we stole his files
and his guns,
and he wants them back.
Tell him the truth.
And tell him that we're trying
to save his bloody people.
He doesn't give a shit
about the people.
He just want the file.
So tell him whatever he wants.
Just try and buy us
some time.
He wants us to...
He wants us to what?
He wants us to make amends now.
He wants us to go to Pailin.
You know what that means.
He say now.
Okay.
Tell him that Sarah
is from the UN.
And that the UN is very
important to Big God Ankha,
and if anything happens to her
or to us,
the UN will crucify him.
He say you are a ClA agent
working for Vietnam.
One of you must die.
English doctor, you say
all you care about is my people.
Life mean nothing.
We serve only Ankha.
Now you will see.
For God's sake,
he's just a baby.
Tell them to drop their guns.
Tell them to drop
their fucking weapons now!
No!
Tell them to back off.
Back off!
Look, as long
as we hold due west,
we hit the river.
That's about two miles.
And the camp's up there.
About another three miles north,
just over the Thai border.
Oh, Jesus.
Shit. That's Khmer Rouge.
They've reached the village.
At this rate,
they're going to catch up.
Keep them moving.
Keep them moving!
Tell them we're nearly there.
Sierra Tango 619.
This is Outpost Grade Seven.
Sierra Tango, come in.
Me father.
Look! Look! Helicopter!
Helicopter!
Looks Vietnamese, mate.
Good, that will keep them busy.
Nick?
lt wasn't your fault.
Yes, it was.
lf l'd have listened to him,
none of this
would have happened.
l couldn't even
bury him properly.
l didn't even give him
a decent fucking burial.
Elliott wanted to dedicate
his life
to helping other people.
And in the end,
he died for them.
Be proud of him.
Miss him...
but be proud of him.
l don't know what
l'm going to do without him.
l can't stop;
l've got to keep going.
-There's so much...
-l'm worried about you, here.
l'm worried that something
is going to happen to you.
Every day for four years,
every morning,
l wake up and l wonder
if you're okay,
if you're still alive,
where you are.
Shall l ring down
for some room service?
Chocolate cake...
and some air-conditioning.
That'd be lovely.
How did you meet Henry?
l was staring at a Roscoe.
What's that,
some sort of dishwasher?
lt was a painting.
l used to work
at an art gallery.
And one day, Henry came in.
How old were you?
Too young.
But you stayed together?
Yeah.
We've both known that
the marriage has been over
for a long time.
But we stayed together
for Jimmy.
You love him very much,
don't you?
He's amazing.
l'm going to have
to start making plans
to go to New York.
See Elliott's parents,
tell them what happened.
How long will you be gone?
l don't know, no idea.
What is this?
What are you doing?
l'm absolutely crazy about you.
l can't stop thinking about you.
You're always in my mind;
you're in my heart;
you're in every fucking bit
of me.
But l can't go there with you.
l can't do it.
Look at what happens
to people around me.
lt's not good.
-l'm not good for you.
-That's not true.
Listen, believe me,
if l could live this life again,
l would never leave you
for a second.
But you belong with your family,
and l belong here,
and there's nothing
we can do about it.
Because whichever way
you look at it,
somebody gets hurt.
One, two, three.
-Oh.
-Oops.
Oh!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday
to you
Happy birthday, dear Sarah
Happy birthday to you.
Thank you.
Thank you, baby.
Oh, that was lovely.
Lovely playing, lovely cake.
My playing
was lovelier than his cake.
Mom.
They were both exactly
as lovely as each other.
l think you better
blow the candles out
before the cake catches fire.
Wait until they do you
a candle for each decade, dear.
Then you'll know
you're past it.
Didn't forget to make a wish.
Got it.
Oh!
Mom, when are we going
to open the presents?
Now.
Many of you know her
from her work
with the Elliott Hauser
Foundation
for the lnternational Promotion
of Human Rights.
ln more recent years however,
she has become an active
lobbyist at Whitehall
on issues of asylum
and refugee protection.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it gives me great pleasure
to introduce
our new spokesperson
for the UNHCR
in the United Kingdom,
Mrs. Sarah Bauford.
Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
l feel very nervous to be
standing in front of you today.
l also feel very honored.
ln particular, because
UNHCR was the organization
to which l was first introduced
by my friend Elliott Hauser.
l know that my being
offered this post
would have given him
enormous pleasure.
Over 50 million people
are refugees or displaced
persons in the world today.
And because of closed minds
and funding shortfalls,
we are only able to reach
half of those in need.
So we rely on our partners,
the network of aid groups
blazing a trail across crises,
like El Salvador, Angola,
Chechnya, Sri Lanka...
those NGO's, the non-
governmental groups from OXFAM
right down
to the smallest outfits
run by people like Elliott
and...
...and l pray for those
who survive him--
who continue his work--
without certainty or security--
wherever they may be
in this world.
Excuse me.
Hey.
Thanks for coming.
Listen, l travel
thousands of miles
to hear my sister
give a speech,
l got a backache and jet lag.
What's a taxi ride to the park?
Sorry.
Are they angry?
No. They don't care, Sarah.
l think they actually
kind of enjoyed it.
''She's nuts'' makes
for much better conversation
than ''Nice speech.''
l got a letter from Nick,
and l think he's in trouble.
Why? What did he say?
Nothing, really.
Just little things.
Well, where is he?
He's in Chechnya.
He's running
some sort of camp.
l'm really not sure.
l need to find him.
So, you have contacts.
You can find out where he is.
So, please?
Sarah, sweetheart,
you know as well as l do
that Chechnya is
a very dangerous place.
Yes, l can angle
a story there, l'm sure.
lf l find out anything,
l will let you know. Okay?
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Thank you.
Perhaps we are all refugees
from something,
but l see now
there is nothing to fear;
that the world we hold on to,
the lives we cherish,
are a part of something greater
--something more.
When l look at my children,
l see it so clearly--
that hope--
that chance of life--
and l know
it's worth fighting for.
''The wedding was
a splendid affair.
''Everyone attended--
''the dwarves, and the
animals of the forest--
''and there were tears of joy
''and songs of happiness,
''and the prince
and the princess
lived happily ever after.''
How does it really end, Mummy?
What do you mean?
What do you think happens,
honey?
She wakes up,
looks at the prince,
and goes, ''Eww! Boys. Yucky!''
Hello.
Hi, Henry. lt's Charlotte.
ls Sarah there?
Charlotte, hi.
Uh... well, she's upstairs
with the kids right now.
Can l take a message?
Oh. Okay. Um...
Then could you just, uh...
Just let her know that
l will call her later, okay?
Well, l can take a message.
Um... well, then, just tell her
that l've got some news, uh...
and that l will... l will fax it
to her office in the morning.
Okay?
Right. Okay.
Um... l'll pass that on.
Okay. Thanks, Henry. Bye, now.
Bye.
That was Charlotte.
She said, um...
she has some news.
She'll fax you at the office.
So this is it, is it?
You kiss the children good-bye,
scribble a quick note, and then
sneak off into the night.
Have you any idea
how fucking cruel that is?
l'm not sneaking off.
l'm not leaving the children.
You could have talked to me.
l mean, writing a note--
it's, uh...
l just thought
it would be easier.
Than what?
Than having
this conversation again.
God, this is so...
l should be back by Friday.
Dinners are in the freezer.
Their swimsuits
are in the dryer.
They have swimming
tomorrow at 4:00.
lt's all in the note.
l want this to be as easy
as possible for them.
And we'll talk about this.
We'll talk about everything
when l get home.
Sniper!
Oh, God...
This is total carnage,
and not a single western leader
has said a thing
about what's going on here.
There's no threats,
no criticism,
no fucking comment.
This place might
as well not exist.
And now that
we're all they have,
they want us to save face
for them.
Well, fuck that. They should
get off their fucking asses
and get the fuck out here. Shit.
Sorry. l'm still swearing.
Freeze it there.
Can we cut?
Okay.
Roll tape.
Basically, nothing has changed.
People keep saying that
everything has changed.
Not from where l'm standing.
Chechnya, Somalia, Cambodia,
Ethiopia--
it's the same shit every time,
and it's just going to go on
and on until we stop pretending
that our loyalty ends
with the asshole...
You okay?
What do you know?
An English news crew
filmed it six days ago.
The sound man is dead,
the cameraman is in a coma,
and Nick has disappeared.
We think it's bandits--
Chechens looking for money--
but there's been
no ransom demand.
Sarah, l want you
to meet Bob Strauss.
He's with the lCRC here.
He's been helping us.
Hi.
No, sit. Sit, please.
So, the, um...
net result right now
is we don't know who took Nick.
We don't know if he pissed off
the Russians or the Chechens.
We're pretty sure
there was a motive.
What was he doing?
l think you know
he wasn't just
a doctor anymore.
He, uh...
l'd have to say--
and this is well known--
Nick's activities
went quite a way
beyond what you'd call
famine relief.
How do we find him?
Well, nobody l've spoken to
has any leads yet.
Can we offer a reward?
Can... can...
can we do something?
The best thing for you
to do is to stay
in the hotel for
a couple of days. Be patient.
No. No.
No.
Sarah.
Sarah, listen to me.
This place,
they will take journalists,
Red Cross, anybody.
Don't think for one second
that you are immune.
l don't.
Just listen
to what Strauss said.
l don't care what Strauss said.
Sarah, l love you.
l want you to be safe. Go home.
l swear to God, l will let you
know if we hear anything.
Say it.
What?
People disappear here;
they don't come back.
l'm not leaving
until l find him.
Okay.
Charley?
Who is it?
Mrs. Bauford?
My name is Jan Steiger.
l'm a friend of Nick's.
May l?
We work together.
On and off.
You should move your bed.
lt's too near the window.
Were you working together here?
Yes, in a manner of speaking.
How'd you know where l was?
My sister?
Oh, no, l'm not a journalist,
Mrs. Bauford.
l'm more import/export.
Cambodia, we nearly met.
Actually,
Nick mentioned you a few times.
l most certainly would have.
What do you want?
What do you want, Mrs. Bauford?
l want to know where Nick is.
Last l heard,
he was being held
in the mountains--
a rebel position,
about five, six miles
northeast of here.
Whole area's under heavy
Russian shelling now,
but l managed
to make radio contact.
They were negotiating,
they knew who he was.
But that was yesterday,
been nothing since.
Chances are that he's dead.
So why are you telling me this?
l'm curious.
l mean, you come
to this shit-hole in hell,
and you think you can find him?
What is it?
ls this... love?
ls that what it is?
Okay, whatever.
You're here.
Now...
if l get him back alive.
l'll lose one less operative.
lf he's dead, he's dead.
Of course l'm not stupid enough
to risk my own ass
for some fucked-up big mouth.
But you, you're willing
to risk your life for love.
l'll trade with anything,
Mrs. Bauford.
Anything at all.
Fine.
What do l do?
l have a friend, a local.
He can get you
into the mountains,
but after that,
l'm just a spectator.
Love.
l'm looking for Nick Callahan,
the English doctor.
Come.
Five minutes.
Nick?
Nick, it's Sarah.
l'm going to get you
out of here.
We're going to get
out of here right now.
There's a Red Cross camp
on the border.
lt's about
four miles west of here.
We can walk it.
Damn it!
Come on, get up.
Get up!
Nick, get up!
Nick? Remember?
Remember l wrote to you?
And l told you
you have a daughter.
Anna.
You remember?
You're a dad.
And she needs you.
She needs you to get up
and walk out of here.
So get up.
Get up, Nick.
That was close.
What?
We need a lot
of money to do...
lt won't be hard to track us.
-l can't make it-- go!
-You can...
Go, you've got to go.
Listen to me.
They're not going to kill me.
They need me alive.
l'm worth money to them.
lf they get you,
they will rape you,
they will kill you.
Y-You've got to go
and get help.
Okay. Okay.
Sarah!
Sarah, go!
Go! You can make it.
Go!
What are you...
What are you doing?!
For God's...
Sarah, please!
Stay. Stay.
Go!
l hope when
you're reading this letter,
that l'm sitting there
next to you
and you're telling me
that l'm stupid for writing it,
and crazy
for trying to find you.
But how could l not?
lt's you.
All this time,
so many years apart...
l've missed you,
but l have never been
without you.
l've woken up with you
every morning
and gone to sleep with you
every night.
You have always been with me.
Your courage, your smile...
your damn stubbornness.
There has never been
any distance between us,
and there never will be.
l love you, Nick.
l love you.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org