Grandma.
Your eggs.
It's Billy.
Come on.
Fuck.
- You been playing my records, you twat?
- I never played naught.
Knobhead.
If Dad knew you smoked that stuff,
he'd go mental.
Fuck off, will ya!
Little twat.
Here we go, Dad. Come on, man.
Dad!
Hurry up, Dad, man. We'll be late.
I'm telling you, the whole world
will be on that picket line this morning.
Have you tidied our room? Dad!
There's not much coal left.
That's fine.
We'll be digging it up again next month.
Don't kid yourself.
I'm not waiting for you.
Tony!
See you down the picket line, Dad.
Leave it, Billy.
Mom would have let us.
Your 50 pence is on the fridge.
Scab, scab, scab!
- Are you sure you're not going to come?
- Am I fuck.
- It's a right load of old bollocks.
- It's not.
It's a load of shite, kicking people in.
I don't know why you bother.
- I'm good at it.
- Are you shite.
- Look at them gloves. They're outdated.
- They're me dad's, these.
Exactly.
Right, lads. Listen up here.
Hold it. Right.
Here.
Now, because they're using downstairs...
...as a soup kitchen
for the striking miners...
...I'm gonna let Mrs. Wilkinson...
...use the bottom end of the boxing hall
for her ballet lessons.
So, no hanky-panky, understood?
Yes.
Elliot, you're late.
Get changed and get in here.
Right then, lads.
Give it all you got. Round one.
Don't just stand there, Elliot.
Not again. This is man-to-man combat,
not a bloody tea dance.
What are you doing, man? Hit him!
He's just pissing about.
Get stuck in and give him a belt.
He's like a fanny in a fit.
Billy, hit him!
Jesus Christ, Billy Elliot!
You're a disgrace to them gloves...
...your father,
and the traditions of this boxing hall.
You owe us 50 pence.
Ho! Liberace!
Will you give it a rest?
Billy, punch bag.
You're not going until you do it properly.
Shit.
Give these to Mrs. Wilkinson and her class
when you're done. I'll see you next week.
Okay, girls. Left hand on the bar.
Thank you, Mr. Braithwaite.
Pretty arms.
Bottoms in.
Where are you looking, Susan?
Lift. Feel the music. Feel it.
In time, Debbie, please.
And one, and two, and three, and four...
...and five, six, seven, eight.
...five.
And hold.
Hold it.
Support yourselves.
Don't look at me. Look ahead.
Where's your confidence? Come on.
And down.
Connie.
Oh, God.
And Debbie, eyes front.
And five, and six, and seven, and stop.
For God's sake.
Thank you, Mr. Braithwaite.
Right, into the center, girls, please.
Miss?
- Miss, the keys.
- Not now.
Right, Mr. Braithwaite.
The Sun Will Come Out Tomorrow.
Fat chance.
Ready, and...
"Port de bras" forward...
...and up.
Why don't you join in?
"Port de bras" forward...
...and up...
...and hold.
And three, and four,
and Debbie, straight leg...
...seven and eight.
And one, and two, and three, and four...
...and five... Boots off!
Seven and eight. What size are you?
- Miss, what about the keys?
- Into the center.
Go on, I dare you.
Prepare.
And one, and two, and three, and four...
...and five, and six, and...
And eight, and hold.
Hold it.
What have we got here, then?
Heel out.
Drop your hip.
Nice...
...straight leg.
Good arch.
Turn that leg out.
Right. Class dismissed.
Hometime.
Debbie, get the 50 pences.
- You owe me 50 pence.
- No, I don't!
You do.
Why don't you bring it along next week?
I can't. I'm going to boxing.
- But you're crap at boxing.
- No, I'm not!
Shut up.
I thought you enjoyed it.
Please yourself, darling.
"Dancing in my tails"
He was your mom's favorite,
was Fred Astaire.
We used to watch him
at the Palace Picture House...
...and then dance around the front room
like lunatics.
Marvelous!
Mind, they used to say
I could have been a professional.
Come on, Grandma. Not now.
Grandma!
It's this one here!
It's over here!
Tony?
- Do you ever think about death?
- Fuck off!
Night-night, then.
Plenty of boys do ballet, you know.
Do they now? What boys do ballet?
Nobody around here, but plenty of men do.
Poofs.
Not necessarily poofs.
Who, like?
What about that Wayne Sleep?
He's not a poof.
He's as fit as an athlete.
- Bet he couldn't beat Daley Thompson.
- Maybe not in a race, but in stamina.
- Come tomorrow. You can just watch.
- I can't.
Gotta go to boxing, haven't I?
Please yourself, then.
See you around.
Aye. See ya.
Right, lads. Look sharp. Everybody out.
Turn, turn and stop.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
Arms are in fifth.
One, two, three.
Turn, turn and stop.
One, two, three. Where are those arms?
- I don't know what to do.
- Follow the others.
Shut up, Debbie. One, two, three.
Nice pretty arms. And stop.
See? I told you it takes loads of practice.
- Debbie.
- What, Mom?
- What do you call me?
- Miss.
Shove off!
So, do we get the pleasure
of your company next week?
It's just...
...I feel like a right sissy.
Well, don't act like one.
Fifty pence, please.
If you're not coming again,
give us your shoes.
- You're all right.
- Right.
What are you doing,
going around like creeping Jesus?
Naught.
They found your nanna in the Spar stores.
Where have you been?
Boxing. Where do you think?
What are you doing?
- I forgot me gloves.
- They were my dad's gloves.
You better take better care of them, okay?
Copy down that diagram.
You only have five minutes left.
Hurry. This way.
You're going to ballet every week?
- Yeah, but don't tell.
- Why do you need to take lessons?
Why do you think?
To get better, you divvy.
- Do you get to wear a tutu?
- Fuck off!
They're only meant for lasses.
I wear me shorts.
- You want to ask for a tutu.
- What for?
- To dance in.
- I'd look a right dickhead.
I think you'd look wicked.
Come on.
I don't know why you're looking at that.
You can't take that out on a junior ticket.
Come on!
See you, then.
Okay, Billy Elliot, he's the center.
Right, I want you to watch carefully, girls.
First, arabesque.
Drop your shoulders.
Look forward, beyond your fingertips.
There.
Right. Spin it, Mr. Braithwaite. Spin it.
Come on! Spin it!
Now, focus.
Look at yourselves! Look in the mirror!
Christ almighty! What was that?
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
Prepare one, and two. Strong position.
Weight on both legs.
Pirouette, and down.
Up you get.
Find a place on that bloody wall...
...and focus on that spot.
Then whip your head round
and come back to that spot.
Prepare!
- One, and two, and...
- Fuck it.
Have you got the spot?
Prepare.
- Prepare!
- Prepare.
Go!
Go, Billy!
What have I told you about that arm?
Right. Back to the bar.
You look like a right wanker to me, son.
Listen, it was just 50 pence a session,
you know.
I can do without it.
I don't do it for the money.
- What are you talking about?
- The boxing.
I haven't seen
hide nor hair of Billy for months.
I was gonna say something,
but I thought it might be embarrassing.
First, I knew about it.
He's never got the gloves off.
Send him round to my house.
I'll knock some sense into him.
Scab! Scab!
Step, open and "balancé".
Balancé.
Scab, scab, scab!
Right. Let's do it again.
Open and lift your chest.
Let's do it again.
Thank you, Mr. Braithwaite. Step...
Open your arms. Do it.
Pay attention.
Arms like this. All right?
Thank you, Mr. Braithwaite. Step really...
...open.
Powerful! Proud.
You're not concentrating.
- Yes, I am concentrating.
- You're not even trying.
Can we have a go at it, Miss?
Let's do it again.
Listen, have you noticed anything weird
about Billy lately?
What are you after, like, a list?
Got enough food there, scab?
What are you doing?
- Scabs eat well, eh?
- You're me best mate.
First rule of a union, Gary,
you never cross a picket line.
- We're all fucked if you forget that!
- We're fucked anyway.
In a speech to Tory MPs yesterday...
...Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher
referred to members...
...of the striking National Union
of Mine Workers...
...as the "enemy within".
The speech comes following
several months of violent clashes...
...between police officers
and striking miners.
- See you, then.
- Wait. Your breakfast...
What the hell's he up to?
One, two, three, "pas de bourrée".
And one, two, three, and a turn.
And one, two, three, "pas de bourrée".
You, out!
Now!
I beg your pardon?
Please, Miss.
Don't.
All right, which way are we facing?
Come on.
And one...
...two, three, "pas de bourrée".
Ballet?
What's wrong with ballet?
What's "wrong" with ballet?
It's perfectly normal.
"Perfectly normal"?
I used to go to ballet.
See?
Aye, for your nanna.
For girls, not for lads, Billy.
Lads do football, or...
...boxing, or...
...wrestling.
Not frigging ballet.
What lads do wrestling?
Don't start.
I don't see what's wrong with it.
You know exactly what's wrong with it.
- No, I don't.
- Yes, you do.
- Yes, you bloody well do.
Who do you think I am?
You know quite nicely.
What?
What are you trying to say, Dad?
- You're asking for a hiding, son.
- I'm not, honest.
You are, Billy.
It's not just poofs, Dad.
Some ballet dancers are as fit as athletes.
What about that Wayne Sleep?
He was a ballet dancer.
- Wayne Sleep?
- Aye.
Listen, son, from now on
you can forget about the fucking ballet.
You can forget about the fucking boxing,
as well.
I'm busting my ass for those 50 pences,
and you're...
No, from now on you stay here,
you look after your nanna.
Got it?
Good.
They used to say I could've been
a professional dancer, with some training.
Will you shut up?
I hate you!
You're a bastard!
Get off!
Billy!
Hello.
My dad'll kill me if he knows I'm here.
He's stopped you coming to classes.
It's not his fault, Miss.
That's all right with you, is it?
I suppose so.
You should stand up to him.
You don't know what he's like.
Well, that blows it.
- Blows what, Miss?
- Debbie.
I've heard a lot about you.
Durham's little Gene Kelly, eh?
Your dad worked down the pit, then?
Yeah.
Must be hard for the family,
being on strike.
He is out on strike, isn't he?
Of course.
I shouldn't worry. They won't last long.
Tom, don't.
If they voted, they'd be back tomorrow.
It's just a few commies, stirring things up.
Let's face it,
they haven't got a leg to stand on.
Who doesn't?
The miners.
It stands to reason.
Some pits are just uneconomical.
If it costs more to pay everybody
to dig the coal out...
...than you get for it when you sell it,
what does that say?
I don't know.
You wanna think about that,
don't you, son?
Tom.
If it was up to me,
I'd shut them all down tomorrow.
For God's sake.
What do you do, Mr. Wilkinson?
He's been made redundant.
- I thought he was gonna hit me.
- Don't be silly.
He's just under a lot of pressure.
That's what Mom says.
I think it's because he drinks too much.
Does he drink too much?
He's always pissed.
Once he pissed himself.
Your dad?
'Cause he's unhappy and that.
'Cause they sleep in separate beds.
- Why do they sleep in separate beds?
- So they can't have sex.
Do they not have sex?
Dad did it with this woman from work,
but they don't think I know.
Do you miss your mom, then?
I don't really miss her as such.
It's more like just feeling sad.
Especially when I remember her
all of a sudden.
When I'd forgot that she was dead
and that.
What about your mom?
Does she not have sex?
No, she's unfulfilled.
That's why she does dancing.
She does dancing instead of sex?
- Your family's weird.
- No, they're not.
They are though. They're mental.
Get off!
See? You're a nutter, you.
Debbie, it's time for Billy to go home.
Come on, Billy.
I'll drop you off at the corner.
I'll see you, Debbie.
Okay, then.
Miss...
...what have I blown?
This'll sound strange, Billy...
...but, for some time now,
I've thought of the Royal Ballet School.
Aren't you a bit old?
No, not me. You.
I'm the bloody teacher.
They hold auditions in Newcastle.
I'd never be good enough.
I hardly know aught.
They're not interested
in how much you know.
They'll teach you.
That's why they're a ballet school.
It's how you move,
how you express yourself that's important.
Express what?
I think you're good enough to go for it.
It would mean an awful lot of hard work.
But I'm banned.
- Maybe I should have a word with him.
- No, Miss!
- I could teach you on your own.
- We couldn't afford it.
- I'm not doing it for the money.
- What about Dad?
- He doesn't need to know.
- What about boxing?
Listen, if you wanna piss about
with your mates, that's fine with me.
All right, don't lose your blob.
"Blob"?
So, we could do it private like?
Just you and me.
Miss, you don't fancy me, do you?
No, Billy. Funnily enough, I don't.
Now, piss off.
Piss off yourself.
See you Monday, then.
You coming in or what?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing. Just dressing up.
- Whose dress is that?
- Come on.
- It's me sister's.
- Did she give you it?
- She doesn't know.
Do you wanna try?
You can have one of me mom's.
No. You all right?
- What are you doing that for?
- I'm just trying it on.
Christ.
Come here.
Stay still.
There.
- Won't we get in trouble?
- Don't be stupid.
Me dad does it all the time.
He dresses up in your mom's clothes?
Only when he thinks everybody's out.
Have you got a tutu yet?
Do you think being a ballet dancer
would be better than being a miner?
I don't know.
It's just, I've got this audition
in Newcastle, in a couple of weeks.
- What for?
- To go to ballet school.
Ballet school? Is that in Newcastle?
London.
You'd have to move
with your Tony and everybody?
- No, by myself.
- That's a bit steep.
- Can't you be a ballet dancer here?
- Don't be stupid.
- When are you going there?
- I don't know.
I haven't even got in yet.
What does your dad say?
- He doesn't know.
- Fucking hell.
- Are you not going to tell him?
- Not yet, anyway.
He might be pleased about it.
He could rent your room.
He couldn't. What about our Tony?
What do you reckon?
I think you shouldn't bother.
Why not?
I'd miss ya.
Fucking hell.
Brought your things?
I don't know if they're right, Miss.
If they're special to you, they're right.
What are they for?
To give us some ideas for a dance.
Come on, then. Let's see them.
What's that?
It's a letter.
I can see it's a letter.
It's me mom's.
She wrote it, for when I was 18...
...but I opened it.
Here.
"To my son, Billy. "
"Dear Billy:
I know I must seem
like a distant memory to you...
...which is probably a good thing. "
"It will have been a long time...
...and I will have missed seeing you grow. "
"Missed you crying, laughing...
...and shouting. "
"I will have missed telling you off. "
"But please know that I was always there. "
"With you through everything. "
"I always will be. "
"And I am proud to have known you. "
"And I'm proud that you were mine. "
"Always be yourself. "
"I'll love you forever. "
"Mom. "
She must have been a very special woman,
your mother.
No, she was just me mom.
I brought a tape and all.
- What is it?
- I Love to Boogie.
It's one of our Tony's.
Spin it!
Go on!
Tap, tap.
Go!
Grandma, teatime.
Where are you going?
Go back to sleep.
It's 4:00.
You weren't thinking of taking it with you?
If you just wanna stand around...
...getting the shit kicked out of you,
that's fine.
- Some of us are ready to fight back.
- They're already after you.
You're no good to us in jail.
I don't plan on getting caught.
- What's going on?
- Get back to bed.
Both of you!
Fuck you.
Put it down.
- You gonna stop me?
- I'm warning you.
You haven't got it in you. You're finished!
Since Mom died, you're a useless twat.
What are you gonna do about it?
Stop it!
What the fuck are you looking at?
You haven't been practicing.
Prepare.
One, two, and one, and two.
Get up.
Miss, I can't do it.
That's because you're not concentrating.
I am concentrating.
- You're not even trying.
- I am, Miss.
- Do it again.
- I can't.
You do it again.
No!
Shit.
I'm sorry.
It's all right for you.
It's not you who has to do it.
- I know.
- You don't know anything!
What do you know in your posh house,
with your husband that pisses himself?
You're the same as everybody else.
All you want is to tell me what to do!
Now, wait a minute.
I don't want to do your stupid,
fucking audition.
You only want me to do it
for your own benefit!
Look, Billy...
- Because you're a failure!
- Don't you dare talk to me like that.
You don't even have
a proper dancing school.
You're stuck in some crummy boxing hall!
Don't pick on me
because you fucked up your own life!
Can I put a tape on, Miss?
All right, if you must.
It's cush, isn't it?
So, is there a story, then, Miss?
Of course.
It's about a woman
who's captured by an evil magician.
Sounds crap.
And this woman, this beautiful woman...
...is forced to be a swan...
...except for a few hours every night...
...when she becomes alive.
When she becomes real again.
And then, one night...
...she meets this young prince...
...and he falls in love with her.
And she realizes...
...this is the one thing that will allow her...
...to become a real woman once more.
So then what happens?
He promises to marry her
and goes off with someone else, of course.
So she has to be a swan for good?
She dies.
'Cause the prince didn't love her?
Come on. It's time to go.
It's only a ghost story.
Come on.
It's me.
It's Billy.
Oh, little one.
Oh, little one...
...what have I told you
about drinking out of the bottle?
Sorry, Mom.
Well, put it back.
One.
Lift...
...and reach.
Down, and one.
Breathe and stretch.
And one.
Lift and stretch.
Lift...
...and lengthen that foot.
And it's one.
Extend.
Reach out.
Lift and breathe.
And one.
Lift.
Out and close.
And one.
Lift.
When's the audition, then?
Tomorrow morning.
I'll miss you if you go away.
Who do you think is better,
Fred Astaire or Ginger Rogers?
Billy, do you not fancy us, like?
Don't know. Never really thought about it.
If you want, I'll show you me fanny.
No. You're all right.
- Get inside.
- Come on.
That's the union leader. Get him!
Get down!
Thanks, pet.
Wanker!
Keep away from there, son.
Shit.
Here they come!
Fuck!
Tony!
Tony, come back!
Take him away. Off you go, mate.