Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Man:
Hold him there. Hold him there!
Man: Hey!
Henry, we've got a bolter!
Henry, Tucker,
go get him!
Get down, hold him!
Hold him! Hold him!
Good boy, get down.
Get down!
Hold him. That's it.
Good on ya, boy.
Tucker:
Come on, Henry!
Henry had
a little lamb,
its fleece
was white as snow,
and everywhere that
Dudley went,
Henry was sure to go.
Mrs. Mac? They're coming
down for lunch soon.
Coming down,
Henry!
Dudley?
Dudley,
where are you, boy?
Dudley?
Come out of there,
Dudley.
Ahh! Ah!
Boys!
Angus, pull
your head in!
Henry?
Boys.
It's your father.
There's been
an accident.
City boy, eh?
- No, I grew up on a farm.
- Oh, me too.
- Oh.
- You all right, my friend?
- Need some fresh air?
- Close it. Close it!
Woman:
Dr. Carey's office.
It's Henry Oldfield.
I need to speak with her.
She's in a session right now.
Can I have her call you?
Please, please.
Driver:
Nothing like it, eh?
God's green earth.
"All creatures great and small. "
There we go.
- Okay.
- This way.
This isn't gonna be like
the salmon farm, is it, Grant?
Hey, those fish
died free.
- Come on, possum.
- Shh shh.
What's that?
Angus fucking Oldfield.
You'll wait
for me, right?
It's your money.
Hello?
Mrs. Mac: Unless you fancy nostrils
in the back of your head,
I'd not be moving
if I were you.
Mrs. Mac.
Bugger me days!
Henry!
Oh! Oh.
Oh don't worry.
I haven't shot anyone since Christmas.
Oh, just wait until
your brother sees you.
Yeah.
The Merino,
the Romney, the Drysdale...
these names are
whispered in the winds
that caress
the rugged hills.
These names are shared
in corners of
the farmyard,
and these are the names the
young men of the land recite
as they take themselves
off at night.
But in the future,
they will whisper
just one name...
the Oldfield.
Now you take it down
and lead it round in
front of the guests. That's it.
Stop so they
can touch it,
slap a flank,
feel the wool.
I'll take the other microphone,
give it to anyone else who...
has a question.
Get a prospectus
on every seat,
then go up the hill
and get the animal.
What are you doing here?
Lawyers have this
under control, don't they?
What am I doing here?
Our family's been here
for over 100 years.
Our father
was born here.
Our mother died giving
birth to me here.
This is where I spent
the first 10 years of my life.
And my therapist
said I should come.
Therapy.
- So you're still funny about the sheep.
- It's not about the sheep.
It's about other issues
I need to resolve.
Okay.
Angus.
Go inside.
I'll cut you a check.
Girl:
That must be the laboratory.
Woman:
Careful.
There you go.
- Okay.
- Astrid Rush.
Girl: Who'd hire her after
the thing with the leeches?
- You're end?
- Come and give a hand here.
Rush:
Careful!
Grant!
- Up, up more...
- Shit.
Yeah, baby, yeah!
Go after him!
Oi!
- Whooo!
- Hey wait!
They'll never catch us.
They're meat eaters.
Okay.
- What was one, Grant?
- What?
Um, get in
unobserved.
Right.
And what was two?
- Collect visual evidence.
- Right.
Three?
- Get out unobserved?
- Yeah.
And four?
Blow this whole
fucking game wide open;
Take the bastard under
and go down in history
as the two people with
enough balls to save this country
from genetically-
engineered devastation!
No, Grant.
Four was a have a meeting
about what to do next.
This is evidence, okay?
It's evidence.
Actually, that's probably
highly-toxic genetic material.
Fuckin' A!
Fuckin' A. And it's mine.
Or, it's ours.
You and me, baby,
all the way.
Yeah, Grant.
About the you
and me bit...
Now I wonder if
our relationship hasn't kind of got...
Shh!
They're in
here somewhere.
- Go!
- Grant, wait.
Man:
There he goes!
Oi!
Whoa!
Over there!
Where is he?
- Bugger!
- Grant: Oh fuck.
Right.
That's for me.
And that's for you.
It'll buy you
a lot of therapy.
Well, there's not
much around here
in the way of your
cappuccino culture,
but I'm sure Mrs. Mac
will do you a cup of tea
and an Anzac biscuit
for the road.
That's it, then.
You got rid of
all Dad's things.
Living in the past...
that's what's wrong with
these bloody farmers.
You're now the owner
of the biggest farm in the district.
What does that make you?
Up here's where the smart farming's
done these days, Henry.
Is that what all that
outside's in aid of?
People are interested in
what I'm doing here, Henry.
It's a whole new
approach to farming.
It's better for the animals,
better for the farmers,
better for the consumer.
It's an exciting time to
be in agricultural sciences.
And a profitable one.
More tea, Henry?
I think three's enough.
I should get going.
That's a pity.
You'll miss my rabbit pie.
I'm making watercress
for the Japanese.
Look, chopsticks.
He's quite the lord
of the manor now, isn't he?
Uh...
Angus was throwing
this away.
I know your father would
have wanted you to have it.
The Golden Shears.
Best shearer in the country
three years running.
Your father said you
were a natural too.
L... I really can't
see it on my coffee table.
You got what
you came for then?
Angus has
got his deal.
Guess I'm done here.
I'm having the farm manager take you
for a run up to the top.
But I haven't been
up there since the accident.
I know.
That's why you're going.
Oh, here he is now.
- Kia ora, Auntie.
- Henry: Tucker.
Flash threads, bro.
So you a model now or something?
I'm doing I.T.
Internet stuff.
Oh. Nude modeling.
And you're manager now?
Well, your brother's hardly young
farmer of the year, is he?
Angus seems to think he's
got a handle on things.
The only thing he's
got a handle on is his...
Okay, farm boy,
let's see your stuff.
Sure.
Okay.
Come on.
Yah!
What happened to you,
darling?
Give us a hand, bro!
L... I just need
to make a phone call.
Jesus, man.
Just gonna shove her
back over the fence.
Hey!
- Tucker: Hands up?
- Hands up!
It's okay.
I'll protect you.
Girl:
Grant!
Grant?
Is this gonna take long?
Because I've got a taxi waiting.
If you fascists
have hurt him,
I will organize the biggest
sit-in this farm has ever seen.
Look, we don't know
where your friend is, okay?
- Maybe my brother could help?
- Brother?
Angus Oldfield.
I should have known
you were an Oldfield.
I can see it
in your aura.
I think that was just something
he stepped in back there, eh?
- No, you have a very selfish aura.
- What?
How would you like a taste
of what you're dishing out?
Safety's on.
- What?
- The safety's on.
Just...
yeah, on the other side.
Back a bit.
And down.
Back and down.
Up.
Here here, here.
Yeah.
There we go, here.
Yeah, right.
...they were like,
looking around at us and...
What about me?
Can we give you
a ride somewhere?
Maybe to the car
so I can, um...
Tucker:
Organize your sit-in?
Wait for my...
for Grant.
I'm Henry, this is Tucker.
What's your name?
- Experience.
- Has been so far.
So why were you
going to shoot me, Experience?
Because this farm subjects
innocent animals
to cruel and sadistic
torture. Because...
Smoke.
- You coming?
- Um...
Mike?
Mike!
Oh my God.
What?
The feng shui
in this room is terrible.
Anyone there?
Mike?
Oh God.
Jesus, man,
it's not gonna bite.
- What's it doing?
- What is wrong with you?
- Ovinophobia, my therapist calls it.
- What's that?
Just a completely
unfounded and irrational fear
that one day
this is gonna happen!
Well, this happens when
you run the most reckless
genetic engineering program
in the southern hemisphere.
- Who engineered that?
- Your brother.
Mike.
Come on then,
muttonchops!
Bugger me.
Shoot it again!
That'll give you something
to talk to your therapist about.
Experience:
Oh, I'm going to be sick!
Oh shit.
Kia ora.
Kia ora, kia ora.
Rattle your dags,
Henry!
There we go.
Good girls.
They're fine.
Tucker:
You get Henry. I'll start the car.
God, your chi
is in shambles.
Huh?
Take a deep breath.
You need
to ground yourself.
You're a tree.
Come on.
A tree.
Your taproot extends
down into the earth.
My... my what?
That's your base
chakra.
Feel the energy drawing
out of the soil.
Can you feel it?
Yeah.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Come on, Henry.
The energy flows up
into your navel chakra,
your solar plexus
chakra,
into your heart chakra.
It spreads
to your branches,
your twigs, your leaves.
You are a mighty kauri
commanding the forest.
Look with
your third eye.
Totally relaxed.
Get on the fucking truck!
Nearly there, nearly there.
Go!
Go go go!
Watch out for the sheep!
Shoot!
Sorry.
What the hell's he doing?
Chainsaw.
Is it turned on?
- Prime it, prime it!
- What?
The pump thing.
Fuck!
Oi, Henry!
- Are you okay?
- If it weren't for my gumboot...
Who's driving?
- Jump!
- Both: What?
Jump off, now!
Jump off! Ah!
Oh, shit.
Experience:
Wow, what a beautiful view.
- This is, uh, where...
- I know.
This is what?
Ooh, long way down.
I wouldn't want
to fall off there.
This is where my father
fell to his death.
Oh.
Sorry...
to hear that.
Oh, a sheep!
Is that a good one
or a bad one?
Oh, definitely bad.
That's not funny.
Animal flatulence is responsible
for almost half the world's
greenhouse gas emissions.
It's pure methane.
The Kyoto Protocol...
Kyahhh!
What do we do?
Well, reducing carbon
emission from industries...
No, what do we do about
raising the alarm?
My phone...
is in the truck.
Tucker,
what do you think?
Hoof it for the house.
Tell his lordship what's going on.
Is it far?
It's rough terrain,
open paddocks, hot day, no cover.
Yeah, I'd say
it's pretty far.
With about 50,000 sheep
in between.
Then what?
Then I get as far
away from here as I can.
You're still leaving?
I'm especially leaving.
Experience: Oh, what if the sheep
get down there before us?
Then Angus is gonna have
some unexpected visitors.
Henry.
Well?
No sign of him.
The others have gone
out into the paddocks.
You cannot make a cup
of tea in this country
without some do-gooder starting
a petition to have you do it their way.
You help me in the lab.
And you,
get rid of that stuff.
Bloody animals.
You and your...
your bloody 4-wheel drives.
Think you own the road!
I do, actually.
Angus Oldfield.
What hole
did you crawl out of?
WEKA. The Whole Earth
Kollective Aotearoa.
I know all about
your Frankensheep!
Mother Nature spent millions
of years making sheep.
She doesn't need your help!
Don't talk to me
about nature.
Man made sheep
what they are today,
and I'm making them
what they'll be tomorrow.
If I was a sheep, I wouldn't
be anywhere near you!
If you were a sheep, I'd have you ground
up for dog food, you little worm.
Now get the fuck off my land.
Ahh!
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org