Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
That company guy, Matusek,
cleared me this morning.
This will do everything
but cook breakfast.
H23.
The house is here. She's there!
How did the computer know she's there?
The people clear it with their
security patrol and they zap it to us.
Oh! Let the good times roll!
No.! No, not yet.! Not yet.
No.! I'm not ready.!
Stupid putz.!
Sounds like old double-dork
is missing a step or two.
We recorded this?
It's all on tape.
It's locked in the memory bank.
Listen, I think double-dork
is entitled to a quickie, don't you?
Absolutely.
- You can erase that tape, can't you?
- The memory bank's locked.
- But I can get in there.
- Good.
This mother hears through walls.
Fires 4,000 rounds a minute.
- Peeks down dresses at 1 ,000 feet.
- There's more than that.
This terminal is hooked
into every data bank there is.
A dozen of these copters,
and you could run the country.
Watch this. I feed it my name, right?
They've got your whole life in here.
Hit mine.
Murphy, Frankie.
''File under repair''?
Did you break your file?
That's weird.
Special base to Blue Thunder.
Come in.
Blue Thunder.
- It's a wrap tonight. Come on home.
- Ten-four.
I better get going.
You better go, too, Mr. Fletcher.
I'll come along when he's in.
Yeah, right.
Blue Thunder, wind 2 70 degrees at 1 2.
Blue Thunder to base. Final approach.
Altimeter 2995.
Cleared to land.
Does your buddy Cochrane
drive a gray Corvette?
Yeah. Why?
Check 9:00.
He's in some kind of hurry.
Oh, yeah.
- Check Cochrane out.
- On the computer?
Yeah. I'm gonna tag along.
Blue Thunder, this is Tower.
Do you copy? Is there a problem?
That's Cochrane, F.E., U.S. Army.
What's the F.E. stand for?
- Fuck everybody.
- Marvy.
We're almost there.
Blue Thunder, this is Tower.
Do you copy?
- Coming in garbled. Can't read you.
- I got Washington.
Go for it!
Cannot read you, Special Base.
Still garbled.
Blue Thunder, come in.
Do you read me?
Breaking up, Special Base.
Can't read you.
Still garbled.
Here it comes.
''Sole survivor.'' Is he kidding?
''Project Thor''? Wait a minute.
- I know what that is.
- Request information.
Thor Project.
I got it.
Here it comes.
''Tactical Helicopter Offensive Response.''
''Defensive Response''?
What does that mean?
Washington's jerking us around.
They've got bigger plans for this turkey.
Blue Thunder, you will acknowledge.
Shit!
Blue Thunder to Special Base.
Oh, shit!
- Oh, he's going in there.
- Yeah.
- Where are we?
- Federal Building.
You wanna find out
what's going on in there?
I certainly do.
Here goes the whisper mode.
Get anything?
I had a good shot of a couple guys
emptying trash.
Can't use it.
Murphy, what's going on out there?
Captain Braddock, I hold you personally
responsible for that man's behavior.
Dr. Haycock strongly recommended
that he be grounded.
For your information, Mr. Icelan...
there are no paranoid schizophrenics
on active duty here.
He checks his sanity
with his wristwatch.
What do you check yours with,
a dipstick?
I don't have to take crap
from you, Braddock.
He's finished as of now.
If there's one scratch on that aircraft,
so are you.
- Try the thermograph.
- Yeah.
- I told you it was cool.
- Lovely, lovely.
Can you park it here?
- I'll bring it around.
- I got something.
- It locked!
- Yeah. Hold it.
I still fail to understand,
Mr. Holmes, Mr. Hornsby.
The Astro Division was autonomous.
The man was assigned to us.
- The McNeely business complicated it.
- That's Fletcher.
McNeely,yes. I can't say you people
covered yourself with glory so far.
If she hadn't started shouting...
it wouldn't have been necessary
to rough her up.
''Rough her up.''
Is that the latest euphemism
for assassination?
She had street informants,
and she'd already made the connection...
between our project
and the trouble on the streets.
-She was going public, on the record.
- Who are these other guys?
- They can't hear me.
- Shut up anyway.
- This pilot-
- Frank Murphy.
Is it under control? I want no premature
attention coming in the program.
Blue Thunder might be perceived
as a threat.
- Drop the hammer on him.
- What do you think, Colonel?
I think, Mr. Holmes,
that I should take him out.
You mean kill him? When?
As soon as possible.
Jesus Christ!
Boy's crazy about me, isn't he?
You got all this on tape?
- I got every word of it.
- Good.
Give him all the help he needs.
This conversation never took place.
If it gets back to me, I'll deny it.
Oh, shit!
Hold your nose. We're in deep shit.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Blue Thunder to Tower.
Wind 330 degrees at 1 5.
Altimeter 03002.
Clear to land?
Ten-twelve traffic, 1:00,
two miles northeast bound.
It's a Cessna 1 82 at 5,000 VFR.
Blue Thunder down at 2 1 30.
Captain Braddock wants to see you
in the office right away.
I'm gonna get the key card
for the tape.
Be careful.
Yes, sir, I will.
Well, sir, he's not that-
Very well, sir. I will.
All right, sir, I will.
Yes, thank you.
- Did you have a nice flight?
- I enjoyed it. Wish you could've come.
I hope so, because it will be
your last one for a while.
- Listen,Jack-
- No, you listen, Frank.
It's the way it's got to be. Me captain,
you cop. Me talk, you listen.
If you notice I don't have an ass
when I get up...
it's because the old man
just chewed it off just like that.
You're beautiful when you're angry,
but I'd like a more private conversation.
We don't have any secrets
from Mr. Icelan.
You're off the program, Frank.
You and your buddy Lymangood.
I'll be lucky if I'm not out in Pacoima
tomorrow driving a black-and-white.
Captain Braddock speaking.
Yes, sir, he's here, Colonel.
Guys, don't forget to check
under the hood.
Just gonna get my cuff links.
Who do you think you're conning
with that phony radio bullshit?
That went out the window three days
after Marconi invented the fucking thing.
Captain Braddock speaking.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir, it's taken care of.
- Who unlocked the memory bank?
- It was that tall cop.
- You got it.
- Son of a bitch!
Get his gun.
Take it easy. Pay attention.
Pay attention!
We don't want to hurt you.
We want the tape.
Let's be reasonable. You'll tell us
what we want to know sooner or later.
I think you'd really rather
it be sooner.
'Cause first I'm gonna break
your fingers.
Then your arm.
Then maybe your knees.
I know you don't believe me,
so I'm gonna show you.
Now, can it be sooner?
The tape. Is it in your car?
Check the car.
You wanna tell us where it is.
Yeah.
You wanna write it down.
Attaboy!
All units for information.
Detain and hold for questioning...
Officer Frank Murphy in connection
with the death of Officer Lymangood.
Possibly driving a black '79 Trans Am.
California license 909 King-Edward-Boy.
I wanna get a confirmation on that.
This is Air 1 2 to Central.
Can we get a confirmation
on that last dispatch, please?
Black '79 Trans Am,
California license 909 King-Edward-Boy.
Officer Frank Murphy.
Detain and hold for questioning...
in connection with the death
of Officer Richard Lymangood.
So far so good.
Check out Big Brother's tape
in Blue Thunder if you want to know more.
I just heard about Lymangood.
I'm really sorry.
Call me if you want to talk.
- Here's your tea, Colonel.
- Thank you.
Why don't we just blank the tape?
That's what it's designed for, right?
They tell me Lymangood
changed the code numbers.
To go through every possible combination
would take forever.
Trouble is, we don't have forever.
Hiya, boss. How's it goin'?
Listen. I got the tape.
But I can't take it home.
It doesn't feel safe to take it home.
So I'm gonna take it-
There's this drive-in I go to
on Riverside and Victory, on the corner.
They've got a Dumpster in the back
behind the concession stand.
I'm pretty sure they don't empty it
till Monday, I think.
That's where I'm gonna stash
the tape, okay?
This is gettin'fun, huh?
Cops and robbers for real.
Well, good luck if you should decide
to accept this mission.
This is Lymangood.
Yeah, I forgot to tell you.
I found out whatJAFO is.
''Just Another Fucking Observer, ''huh?
Get outta there. You're not supposed
to be there. Get the fuck outta there!
You talking to me, asshole?
Damn it! Murphy!
This is Special Base.
Commander, come in.
Shit!
Los Angeles Mobile.
Mobile, get me KBLA-TV.
That number is listed
in your directory, sir.
Don't give me any static. This is
a police emergency. Get me KBLA-TV now.
Good afternoon. KBLA-TV.
I want to speak to Mario Machado
or Alf Hewitt.
They're not here. They're in the field.
Want to leave a message?
Tell them this is Officer Frank Murphy,
Astro Division.
I've got a package coming their way.
Do you read me?
- That's Frank Astro?
- No. Frank Murphy, Astro Division.
Police emergency.
You got it, sweetheart?
- Yeah, I got it.
- Okay. Mobile?
- Los Angeles Mobile.
- Listen, I need another number.
- Hello.
- Kate, it's Frank.
Where are you?
I've been worried sick about you.
I'm okay, baby.
I want you to pick up a package.
It's in a drive-in at the corner
of Victory and Riverside.
It's near the concession stand.
- It's in a Dumpster.
- Then what?
Take it to KBLA-TV,
to Mario Machado or Alf Hewitt.
- Don't stop for anything or anybody.
- Got it.
Okay. Thank you, baby.
- Where is he now?
- Over the freeway interchange.
Get the mayor's office on the phone
and the city emergency center.
We're gonna get the air force now.
We're gonna get 'em now.
He made two phone calls. The first to
channel 8, the second to his girlfriend.
Forget about the police. Get our cars
over to her place and that TV station.
It looks like the bastard
wants to go public.
- We'll stop that.
- We'd better.
Come on, move out!
Move, move!
- Damn it! I can't see nothin'!
- There she goes.
Air 7 to Special 1.
Air 7 to Special 1 .
No shit, pendejo.
You gotta set that thing down.
We got two choppers full of SWAT guys.
Oh-ho, it's getting cozy up here.
Return to base,
or we'll open fire.
Come on, will ya, Murphy?
All right, knock him down.
Okay, amigo. How's your
auto-rotation technique?
Son of a bitch!
Hang on!
Sorry about that, my friend.
Not again!
All right, chaps.
How'd you like to follow my leader?
Pull up! Pull up!
Okay, lady, pull over.
- Is there a problem, Officer?
- Yeah. A den mother in a Vega, right?
Play it very cool.
I need your license and registration.
Sure.
- Maybe I-
- Why don't you get out of the car?
For those who have tuned in late,
channel 8 brings you live coverage...
of a helicopter hijacking.
Stay inside your homes. There is
a sniper over the city of Los Angeles.
We've already lost one police car
and two helicopters.
Well, what now, gentlemen?
I don't plan on losing
any more of my helicopters.
May I introduce Colonel Coe
of the air force?
Colonel.
We've got a couple of F-1 6s
standing by at March Field.
- F-1 6s?
- We can take him out now. Say the word.
If I may say so,
the F-1 6 is armed with rockets.
Potential destruction of innocent
human beings is unimaginable.
The F-1 6 is armed
with heat-seeking missiles.
We can surgically remove him
from the air like a tumor.
We're not talking about a tumor.
You gotta make a right there.
''One Way''
You're ridin' with the angels,
sweetheart.
Atta girl! Good work.
Got Ray Icelan at Astro Control.
He says they've just scrambled
two F-1 6s out of March.
- What about the tape?
- No sign of it.
But he did make that call to KBLA.
Fletcher's standing by to intercept.
If you people would be calm,
I'll take care of you one at a time.
We're gonna have more help.
Just keep calm.
Sir, I've got to get this tape
to Mr. Machado or ''Abe'' Hewitt.
-They're very busy.
- It's important. It's from Frank Murphy.
There's a crazy man in a helicopter.
If you'll sit down,
I'll tell somebody you're here.
The most dangerous thing in the world
is a man afraid for his job.
I'm Dick Fisher.
I'll get that to Mario if you like.
- No, I have to give this to Mr. Mosher-
- Machado.
I'm his producer.
I'd be delighted to bring it to him.
I don't think so.
Can't we simply erase it?
Isn't that what the bug's for?
We don't know the code number.
Then erase them all.
Why don't you give it to me?
I'll take it upstairs.
Because Frank told me to give it
to Mr. Hewitt-
Hi. I'm Alf Hewitt. You're the lady
with the tape from Frank Murphy, right?
- Your producer said that Mr. Machado-
- Who?
I never saw this guy before in my life.
Come on, let's go.
Not so fast. That's government property!
Give me that!
- Get your hands off me!
- Stop it! No!
Bill, get this bastard off of me!
You son of a bitch,
I'll blow your heads off!
Go, go, go! I've got the tape.
''Property Of U.S. Government''
March Control,
this is Little Brother One.
We have your target.
Bearing 1 21 at 1 3 miles.
Request clearance to engage.
Roger, Little Brother.
This is March Control. Affirmative.
Engage and destroy.
I repeat.
There he is.
He's all yours, cookie.
Holy shit!
What?
Well, I'll be damned.
Colonel, one of your missiles just took
out a barbecue shack in Little Tokyo.
- Frances, isn't that Ray's district?
- Yes, it is.
- Do you have his number?
- Right here.
Give him a call, because they'll be
calling him, and he'll be calling us.
I'm on my way.
There he is right there.
- This is an emergency.
- Clear the area.
All right, clear the area.
Clear the area.
Well, what do you know?
He froze.
Okay, he's all mine now, Cookie.
Oh, my God!
I'm hit, Cookie! I'm hit!
He blew my wing off!.
Mayday.! Mayday.! This is
Little Brother One. I'm ejecting.
Just lost an F-1 6 and the top
of the Arco Tower. What do we do now?
That's it. Call it off.
May I remind you there's a crazy man up
there with a six 20-millimeter cannon?
Call it off.
Request permission for takeoff.
Colonel, hold your position.
Operation cancelled.
Repeat. Hold your position.
Do not take off.
Thank you.
Back to base.
''Rough her up. ''Is that the latest
euphemism for assassination?
She had street informants,
and she'd already made the connection...
between our project
and the trouble in the streets.
Jesus Christ!
You ought to hear this stuff.
These guys sound like cops and feds.
They're stirring up trouble in the
barrio to prove what the chopper can do.
It's all right here.
You better tell Mario to go easy
on that ''Mad Sniper'' stuff.
That cop might be the hottest ticket
since Horatio set the bridge.
All right, let's try this.
Where are you?
Damn it!
All right, Murphy. It's about time
you put your money where your mouth is.
One. Two. Three!
Come on, you tub of shit!
That's impossible.
Catch you later.
Okay. And now it's your turn.
The $5 million prototype
was utterly destroyed...
when Officer Murphy,
his gasoline supply exhausted...
set the helicopter down in the tracks
in front of a southbound freight train.
That was the end of the special
helicopter, but not of this story.
On the strength of the tape Murphy
delivered to this reporter today...
the mayor has reopened
the investigation into the death...
of Councilwoman Diana McNeely...
which might also be connected with
the death of Officer Richard Lymangood...
of the Astro Division.
Half a dozen members
of the local police department...
and several government officials ofboth
the State and Justice Departments...
have been detained for questioning.
Coming up, the weather and a sneak
preview of a Japanese bullet train...
soon to be seen
in the Southland, maybe.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org