Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- What are you talking about?
- The psychologists are convinced...
that Eva imagined
the second killer.
I don't care what the doctors say.
I was there. I saw it.
She comes from an Indian culture.
Her people...
often don't distinguish real things
from the things they imagine.
- Are you saying she's crazy?
- No! She's not crazy.
She believes what she says.
But this doesn't mean that it's true.
I saw the look on that man's face.
- He recognized her.
- No, please.
- That is the man...
- Don't!
Don't. This is my house and this
stops here. I can't deal with this.
- You wanted this story, too.
- No!
Your story is destroying her.
And, God, Lauren.
You can be killed too.
You understand that? They tried it
before and they will kill you.
I cannot do this anymore.
Please, just leave.
- I'm sorry. Did we wake you up?
- Are they photos of the bus drivers?
- It's not important right now.
- It is important.
- Eva. Please. You need to heal.
- No, Teresa.
The only thing
that will heal me...
the only thing that will
give me back my life...
is to find my attackers.
Lauren is helping me.
And we are gonna find them
together. Right?
This is the road
where Eva was raped.
This is where I want you to be.
You and the police.
Eva identified the bus driver.
His name is Domingo Esparza.
They drive the victims out here
and then meet the other attacker.
I'll go undercover into the factory
he worked for and pose as a worker.
If we know who this Esparza is,
just have him arrested.
If we have him arrested, we have
no chance of catching the second guy.
He's already seen Eva.
He'll come after her.
I'm going into the factory as bait.
It's our only chance to catch both.
You can't. We have to warn too many
people. The police'll never allow it.
That's why you'll only tell them
after I'm in there already.
They're not gonna risk having
an American journalist killed.
There must be people
on the police that you trust.
- People who care about the truth.
- Yeah, I know people.
I think I can trust them.
But you never really know.
People get bribed. I'm not going
to gamble with your life.
I'm not gonna gamble with Eva's life.
It's now or never. Don't you see?
No, I don't see.
This is out of the question.
- Diaz, listen to me.
- I won't listen to you.
I won't let you. If anything happened
to you, I'll never forgive myself!
I can't do this.
All right.
You are not going into the factory.
And we will find another way
to hunt around this. Get in the car.
It's not your choice to make.
I promised Eva that I'd help her
find these men.
And I pray that you'll help me.
But even if you don't, I'm going
into that factory tomorrow.
Eva! You've come home.
Come in, come in.
How do I look?
- With just this.
- Okay.
- Like that?
- Something like that.
You look pretty.
For good luck.
Now you look like me.
I want to give you something.
- No, it's okay.
- Yes. Yes. No.
She protect me that night.
Now she's gonna protect you.
Let me.
Okay.
You are safe now.
Daughter, Cecilia is here.
- Hi. Lauren.
- Eva.
This is dangerous.
You shouldn't be doing this.
It's too dangerous.
I'll be fine.
Good luck, Lauren.
- This is my cousin, Silvia Rojas.
- Yes, we've been expecting her.
We've received her paperwork
from the front office.
This is where you'll work.
This is your supervisor.
Lines 1 and 3 are falling
behind their quotas.
Accelerate production.
The shift has ended.
Please leave quickly.
The next shift starts
in 10 minutes.
Please leave quickly.
The next shift starts
in 10 minutes.
Do you mind if I stop for gas?
Attention all units.
There's still no sign of the bus.
Don't be afraid.
I won't hurt you.
We've received a call
from lauren.
She's in a junkyard.
You all right?
A mass grave.
It was a mass grave.
We didn't find the other attacker.
There was nobody there.
Well, he was there.
He's out there.
I'm telling you, he was here.
He can see us.
I can feel it.
This isn't over until I find him.
When I was on that bus...
everything was just as Eva told it.
It made me feel like
I was living her story.
"The screams of the women
of Juarez are silent...
because no one will listen...
not the corporations who make
their profits from their labor.
Not the governments of Mexico
and the United States...
who benefit
from the free trade agreements.
No one will listen.
All the evidence points to the fact
that there are many killers.
A whole culture of murder
that just gets worse and worse...
the more it's denied
and covered up.
Covering it up is less expensive
than protecting these women.
Money is
about the bottom line.
And so the death toll mounts.
Eva Jimenez, 16 years old.
She works in a factory
assembling televisions.
She makes five dollars a day."
- I finished your story.
- Yeah? You finished my story.
Tomorrow it'll be printed
and everybody will know about it.
Don't forget that in five days
you're gonna have to go to court.
- I know.
- You'll have to talk to a judge...
and you'll have
to tell him everything.
- Can you do this?
- I think I can.
The man we saw at the party,
we didn't catch him.
- What?
- I know. It's gonna be okay.
No, you don't.
He is the Devil. The Devil.
He'll take me to Hell.
He don't want me to go to the judge.
Eva, please.
You'll be safe.
You have to believe me.
I will not let anything
happen to you.
And I will find this man.
You're gonna be okay.
I know how to find him.
- Just leave the glass there?
- Just leave the glass there.
- Here comes the magic.
- All right.
- You gonna show me something?
- Now it's gonna disappear.
It took me two semesters at Harvard
to learn that trick.
I learned that first week
at St. Mary's High.
- I was always a poor student.
- Don't worry. I give tutorials.
- Oh, you do?
- Yeah.
What was it like being a Mexican at
Harvard? They had two of you there?
But I'm an American citizen.
It's convenient. I can be Mexican
whenever I want to or American.
- So, deep down you're just a gringo.
- Well, of course.
It's the best thing to be.
The whole world wants to be gringo.
Come to think of it, there were a lot
of gringos at your party that night.
- I even saw Senator...
- Rawlings.
- Right.
- You know...
my family owns most of the land.
So, he's given us a great
opportunity with NAFTA.
There was somebody else there, too.
So he was tall. He was kind
of dark eyes. Gold teeth?
- Why do you wanna know?
- No reason. It was just...
something that Teresa had said.
He had a scar right here.
Aris. Aris Rodriguez.
His family's involved
with the NAFTA factories.
A very old family, too.
Who's calling me?
George!
Hey can you give a minute?
Hold on. I'm in a restaurant.
So, did you read the piece?
What'd you think?
Best think you've ever done.
It's got something I've never seen.
Some incredible humanity.
And this portrait of Eva?
Quite beautiful.
I don't know what to say.
You're my inspiration, George.
It means the world to me
that you liked it.
Frankly, I couldn't have done
a better job myself.
Congratulations.
Diaz, I just got off the phone
with Chicago. They loved the story.
You want my husband.
- Alfonso, telephone.
- In a minute.
Daddy! Kick me the ball.
- Hey, George.
- No. This is Frank.
I'm not supposed to tell you this,
but George didn't print the story.
He got a visit from some political
types, including Senator Rawlings.
After that, it was a no go.
They're not printing it at all?
You don't understand. Rawlings is
pushing a bill through Congress...
to expand the Free Trade agreements
to include Central America...
and they don't want
any bad press right now.
- You dug too deep.
- Okay.
- Your story is too fuckin' hot.
- Do me a favor.
- Put me on the phone with George.
- He's not gonna talk to you.
They're gonna say it's temporary
and for you to stay put.
But that's just a smoke screen
to kill it.
If you want the story printed,
you've gotta get back here.
- Why are you doing this?
- 'Cause it's a great story.
It needs to be printed.
It's now or never.
So, Eva, I have something
to tell you. Your story...
I have to fight for it.
What do you mean?
They don't want my story?
No, they will want it.
But, because of that...
- I have to go.
- You can't go.
I have to talk to the judge
in three days.
- I know.
- The murderer'll be there.
- I'm very afraid. You can't go.
- Don't worry.
I will return.
They will not publish my story.
And you will not return.
People promise many things,
but that never happens.
I will get your story printed
and I won't stop...
until both of your attackers
are punished.
And I will be back.
Eva, look at me.
I will return.
I promise.
Teresa!
Teresa! Teresa!
What happened?
- Calm down.
- He's in there.
Search her room.
Search outside!
What's the matter?
- The Devil is here.
- Who?
The Devil!
It's all right. It's all right.
Tell me.
- Nobody is there.
- Nobody, right?
See? No one is there.
It was just a nightmare.
Look at me.
He's not real.
It was just a nightmare.
Everything is all right.
Miss, you can...
Lauren, is that you? Wait a minute!
- Could you just...
- Lauren, come in.
Lauren Adrian,
this is Samuel Denton...
the C.E.O. of the publishing
syndicate that owns the Sentinel.
- This is Senator...
- Rawlings, I know.
Saw you in Juarez last week
at the Salamanca house.
- What were you doing there?
- Hi. I'm Denise McKenzie.
I'm head
of all syndicate operations.
Congratulations. You're gonna make
an exceptional foreign correspondent.
We are all very excited.
We're gonna have to let you go, or
else we're not gonna make our lunch.
- I'll talk to you later.
- All the best.
- Good to see you.
- Yeah.
- Foreign correspondent?
- How about that?
- It's unbelievable.
- Your first assignment.
- This is a bribe, isn't it?
- What do you care?
You'd do anything for this job.
Consider it a freebie.
This can't be you.
You can't bow to those people!
- I'm not bowing to anyone.
- Then print my story.
We cannot print your story.
In three days,
a 16-year-old girl...
is going into court to face
the man who tried to kill her!
All because we said
that we would print her story.
This story could save her life and
the lives of many women in Juarez.
This is a fucking important story!
I understand that.
But you are blaming...
- the Mexican and American governments.
- You're god damned right I am.
- And the Free Trade Agreement.
- It isn't free trade!
It's slave trade. It's a scam.
Everybody is making too much money...
- to give a shit about these women.
- Listen to me.
These are very serious accusations,
they're damn near criminal.
And this newspaper is not
prepared to make 'em...
- and you can't substantiate them.
- And they're true!
This is now a matter
of corporate responsibility.
Since when do you put corporate
responsibility above the truth?
Get off your soapbox. I liked you
better as a cutthroat reporter.
I like you better as an editor who
couldn't be bought or intimidated!
- A man I admire.
- The days of investigative reporting...
are over, Lauren.
The news isn't news anymore. It's
as dead as the typewriter I used!
Corporate America
is running the show now.
And their news agenda is free trade,
globalization and entertainment.
That's our glorious future!
You know what would happen to me
if I published your story on my own.
If you don't have the balls
to print my story...
- I will find someone who will.
- It's not that easy, kid.
Read your contract.
The Sentinel owns your story.
Hell, it owns you.
Nobody owns me!
That's the difference
between me and you.
Lauren!
Take the job, Lauren.
You got a damn fine career
in front of yourself...
and you're throwing it all away
and for what?
Your story about these women
is just not worth it.
Not worth it?
I forgot. They're just Mexican women
so they're not worth it.
I didn't mean it that way.
Do you see this?
And this?
And this? And this? And this?
All of it is assembled in Juarez
and it's all covered with blood.
Would you calm down?
If you walk out of here today...
you could never get back in here,
and you know it.
- For God's sakes, let this thing go!
- I can't.
- You think this is your big story.
- My parents are from Mexico.
- You identify with it.
- I'm one of them. Can't you see?
My parents came here
as migrant farm workers.
They were killed...
so I was adopted.
I only have vague
memories of them.
I remember a field
filled with workers...
My mother.
My father.
I was there when he was killed.
I saw him die.
- I'm sorry.
- When I met Eva, I saw myself.
I've been running away
from who I am my whole life.
Because you don't wanna be Mexican,
not in this country.
You see?
I could be one of the women
in those factories.
It could be me
in one of those graves.
I can't let this go.
Alfonso, hurry.
What are you doing?
Just a minute, my love.
Alfonso!
Call an ambulance!
Out of the way!
Get up. Let's go.
Come on. Quickly!
Get in before the Border Patrol
finds us!
Watch your head.
Can I speak to Diaz?
What?
He's coming back. Let's go!
- Who did this?
- I don't know. Nobody does.
Diaz is gone.
And tomorrow the bus driver's
gonna be a free man.
No! With Eva's testimony,
he will go to jail.
- Eva's gone.
- What?
She ran away. Nobody knows
where she is, not even her mother.
Her mother. To move away
from Colonia Anapra.
She want to be there for her,
waiting for her at their home...
but she doesn't feel safe
there anymore.
How could she? Tomorrow...
Domingo Esparza
is gonna be a free man.
- This isn't happening.
- It is happening.
It's all over.
Kids, get up.
Oh, jeez. Poor people.
- Lauren.
- Who are you?
Would you gentlemen please
excuse us for a moment?
Do you believe in anything?
Are you, Mexican? American?
What are you?
These are limiting terms. They don't
mean much now in a modern world.
Alfonso Diaz was my friend.
Now he's dead.
I wanna know what happened to him.
He was reporting things
people didn't want reported.
What did you think
was going to happen to him?
- Who did it?
- Do you think I know that?
Do you think I even concern myself
with such things?
- It gets taken care of.
- Is Aris involved?
How many more women is he gonna kill?
Why don't you tell somebody about it?
And who am I gonna tell?
These people know more than me.
- Lf they arrest him, nothing'll change.
- He's a murderer.
- He's protected by the authorities.
- You have to be realistic.
There are two sets of laws
in any country, okay?
The laws for rich and powerful people
and the laws for everybody else.
And don't think it's any different
in the United States...
because I buy politicians on both
sides of the border all the time.
What do you think built this?
Now...
when can we get together again?
I can free my schedule anytime.
What do you say?
I wish people like you didn't exist.
And on top of everything else...
you're a lousy god damned fuck.
The first shift has ended.
Please leave quickly.
The second shift
will start in 10 minutes.
Please leave quickly.
The first shift has ended.
Vamanos. Let's go.
They're shipping you back
to Juarez.
Hurry up, Nacho.
We need the electricity.
Hold on. I'm doing it.
Eva?
It's morning and the court
will be in session soon.
They're gonna be waiting for you.
We're both pretty beat up.
Maybe if we help each other...
well then we can make it.
Eva testified against her attacker,
Domingo Esparza.
He is awaiting trial.
Eva was reunited with her mother.
They are being protected
by a human rights organization.
Aris' body was found.
It was never claimed.
No one was arrested
for the murder of Alfonso Diaz.
I took over Diaz's paper.
I continue to write to tell
the truth about Juarez.
Congress passed the bill expanding
the free trade agreements...
to Central America.
There are still no provisions
protecting the workers.
Last week another body
was found in the desert.
A girl. About seventeen.
She was still dressed
in her blue factory smock.
The murder of woman
in Juarez continues.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org