Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
"So won't you just come on, come on
"Take it
"Take another little piece
of my heart now, baby
"Break it
"Break another little piece
of my heart now, darling
"Have another little piece
of my heart now, honey
"You know you got it, child
"If it makes you feel good
"Oh, yes indeed"
Thank you.
I'm Jane Deluca.
This is Johnny Figgis and our band.
- I got to go take a leak, baby.
- Fine.
Did you see that bitch?
Fuck her.
I'm going to fuck her.
Girl, that man is so fine.
Actually, he is.
Is this your first date?
Do you need to clear or something?
Go ahead and take everything.
Just leave the glasses, thanks.
No, no, I was the singer up there.
You didn't see me? I was signalling
and going like this to you.
- What are you talking about?
- You don't know? Oh, baby!
You had the biggest, greenest thing
hanging out of your nose.
- I kept going like this.
- You could see it from up there?
It looked like Gumby doing Tarzan.
- Oh, my God!
- It was huge. You know?
You ruined my rep, man.
I invite an important A&R guy down
and you fucked me.
You know what? You're out of here.
You're cancelled. Forget it.
- Wait!
- For what? Till you learn to sing?
What's up with him?
You want to know what's up with him?
Son of a bitch just fucked us.
This town is dead for me anyway.
We got that gig in LA.
We'll just leave a little early.
Maybe this is trying to tell us something.
It's telling us we're fucking fired.
No, not just this. Maybe LA is not
the answer to our problems.
What does that mean?
Tommy hooked me
with some studio work in the city.
It's good money. It's in the city.
I got to think of Debbie, you know.
Debbie? The little girl in Queens
who sets her hair every day?
This is suddenly a factor?
Get the fuck out of the way!
You get the fuck out of my way,
understand?
Go back to Pakistan!
Look, I got to be realistic here, all right?
I got to look ahead.
How long you been doing this fuckin' shit?
For what, 17 years?
- Look...
- Look, what?
Look, what?
- I don't want that to happen to me.
- You should be so lucky.
I got priorities here, you know?
You know, she's holding you back, man.
Everybody says it.
She's like Yoko with bangs.
They don't say she's holding me back.
All I'm saying is, don't go to LA,
all right?
Even if you don't got shit going on here,
you've still got...
Let me tell you something: You stay here.
You stay here. You play Daddy, okay?
I'm gone.
I was supposed to be the new Aretha,
but the old Aretha was the new Aretha...
...and I wasn't neither one.
I was something
nobody'd ever seen before.
So I'm getting the fuck out.
Can I get some French fries, please?
You know, head down to LA, get some
gigs going, get that heat happening.
That's great, because I can drop you there
and then head to San Diego on my own.
Great.
- I used to sing too.
- Really?
Nothing professional.
Mostly amateur talent competitions.
- Like Star Search?
- Sort of.
Only I never made it that far.
I played the piano and sang.
What did you sing?
"Way Over Yonder." Carole King.
"Close to you." Carpenters.
- It was the '70s.
- "Close to You? "
You know, "Why do birds suddenly appear
every time you are near?
"Just like me
"They long to be... "
No, no, I know. I know.
Why San Diego?
Well, why not?
Here you go.
I'm in real estate.
And right now the market is
just unbelievably bad.
And I think sometimes
you have to make a change.
You have to take control and say:
"Things are going to be different.
"I can make them different
if I believe it in my heart."
Fuck Star Search.
You should have been Miss America.
Bring it on up.
I hope you don't mind my mentioning this:
No smoking in the car.
- What do you mean, "no smoking"?
- No smoking in the car.
Whatsoever?
I'm going uptown. Can I give you a lift?
Taxi!
No, I have a car...
What do you think? I think it could work.
I'll let you know in a couple days.
Because I really need to leave
as soon as possible...
...and I just don't want to do it alone.
I don't think that'd be safe.
You were the first person
that answered the ad.
I think that's a sign of something.
And I think you'd be fine.
I mean, I think our personalities
would mesh.
Look...
...Robin, right?
You're a nice lady and...
...I’m sure there's a lot of things
about yourself that you just can't help.
But I don't fucking think we mesh at all.
I'm sure somebody's out there
wanting to go cross-country...
...with the whitest woman on earth...
...singing Carpenter songs
and reliving childhood memories.
But it ain't me.
That's my car, man!
That's my...
Hey, that's my car!
That's going to cost at least $200
to get your car back.
Okay, Jane. Good luck in LA.
Earthquake. Fire. Riots.
They got some real crazy bastards
in California.
I don't know why you want
to go out there anyway.
Careful! Easy with that piano!
Good morning!
I have a friend in Pittsburgh.
Do you mind if we stop
and take her to lunch?
No, absolutely. No problem. It's a deal.
Smile.
My brother threw up right here.
Near Exit 7. I remember. We pulled over.
How come he's not making
this trek with you down memory lane?
Or does he have a life?
He doesn't, as a matter of fact.
He died of cancer when he was 6.
Oh, man, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Damn.
Would you mind if I used your headphones?
Go ahead.
Thank you.
Hi. You've reached Nick and Holly's.
Leave a message.
There's a sick lady in the bathroom.
Is she with somebody here?
She's outside!
Is that your friend in the bathroom?
Yeah.
Girl, you better get in there.
She's in there throwing up.
Thanks.
Are you all right?
That stupid woman. I told her I was fine.
You look like shit.
Thank you.
Allergies. I have allergies.
They come and go.
Sometimes I think it's all in my head.
Do you ever knock?
Not in a public toilet, no.
I'm really sorry. It's probably
'cause I brought your brother up.
No, it's not that. I'm fine.
I'll be fine if we just keep moving.
It's nothing.
You smell like an ashtray.
So I'm just going to go down to LA
and see what I can find.
We're going to pass... What?
Are you getting HBO? Because we're
supposed to and it's not on mine.
- I don't know. I'm on the phone here.
- I'm sorry.
No, come in and check.
Come in.
I'm on my way to LA.
I thought I'd stop by and see you.
No, no, I said Tuesday or Wednesday.
Are you okay?
All right. I'll wait.
The Way We Were is on.
Robert Redford. Barbara Streisand.
The Way We Were.
I don't get out much.
It was 20 years ago.
Oh, great, you got it.
Do you mind?
No, please, please.
No, I'm here.
I figured we'd come by
tomorrow around noon.
Are you okay?
Is it Nick?
No, fine, fine. All right.
I'll see you then. Goodbye.
Goddamn.
Is that your friend in Pittsburgh?
Yeah. If she is still my friend.
It's nice.
I don't really have any girl friends.
My mom always felt, you know,
you can't trust women.
I don't know about that.
Oh, come on.
Men know all about PMS.
Somebody talked.
Your girl is lovely.
Why don't you bring her for a drink?
I can't.
I know.
That kills me. The way she like...
...brushes his hair off his forehead.
Really...
...gets me.
Which one of them were you?
The one who loved too much
or the one who loved too little?
Neither.
I'm the one who spent three years
at happy hour...
...and never went home with anybody
except the bartender.
Well, the bartender's somebody.
He was somebody, all right.
I don't know.
I don't know about...
...men.
I just don't get it.
Maybe you're not into them.
You mean...?
No.
What do you mean, "Ew, no? "
I think I scare them away
because I know what I want.
Tell me, what do you want?
It's not very liberated, I know.
I want a husband with a decent job.
You know?
And I want two kids...
...a boy and a girl.
In that order.
And a...
...saltbox colonial with three bedrooms...
...a sun porch, a stairway
with a white banister...
...and a convertible den.
You could have been Donna Reed
in another life.
Anyway, I didn't get it.
It's all right. There's always time.
Yeah.
Is that why you left New York?
'Cause that bartender did you wrong?
Something like that.
8:00 tomorrow, okay?
If you want to get to Pittsburgh by 12:00.
Good night.
Thanks for the movie.
I looked around. Got into real estate.
That's where the performing really paid off.
Sizing up situations, handling people...
...getting what you want from them
without them really knowing.
You know, control.
Don't worry, you don't have to come in.
I hate this belt.
- It's for your own protection.
- Yes, I know.
I'll wait here.
You look good.
Thanks.
Thanks. You too.
What's the matter?
Something's come up. Nick's in a mood.
Can we do this another time?
We're on the road here.
Fuck, I'll handle it. I'll fix it.
Let me talk to him.
Jesus Christ!
Holly!
- He thinks he's lost something.
- I thought you said he was clean.
He is. He has nine months in N.A.
He's just dealing.
But then, you know,
he has a drink and he gets...
...confused.
Holly, if you clean this fucking place up
maybe I'll fucking be able to find my shit.
- What the fuck are you doing here?
- Hello, Nick. I'm just passing through.
We'll catch you later.
You think you're going somewhere?
Nick! Nick! Don't be a prick.
Stick to what you know, Jane.
That's something about you girls
I could never figure out:
What is sex like without a dick?
I don't know, man. You tell me.
- Fuck you.
- You wish. Come on.
You ain't going nowhere.
Help!
Hey, man! Hey, man!
Dyke!
Asshole!
Stop that!
Don't hurt her!
Fucking bitch!
You fuck!
Bullshit!
Are you all right?
Who the fuck are you?
Hi. How are you?
Are we going?
Nobody's going anywhere
until I get my coke.
This bitch, she stole it.
She ain't seeing daylight
until she gives it up.
You don't remember shit
when you're drinking, you asshole.
You sold it Tuesday night.
Remember the last time
I caught you in a lie?
Is that how you want to play this?
Guys, guys.
My hunch is our two positions
might be a lot closer than we think.
Who do you believe he sold it to?
Frank, this guy uptown. A friend.
Jane, let me close this.
Where's his number?
It's on the wall.
I'm Robin, by the way.
You must be Holly.
- It's really nice to meet you.
- You too.
I really like your hair.
Thanks, the humidity really messed with it.
- You know how it is.
- I understand.
Is Frank there?
Frank.
You score one-eighth off me
Tuesday night?
How much?
That's what I thought.
Holly's saying you didn't.
All right.
Later.
So I sold it to him.
Fine, let's go.
Where's the fucking money?
Give us a fucking break.
- Where's the money?
- He hides it.
He always does. The same three
or four places and I'm not telling.
Tell me where.
I tell you to write it down
but you never do. So forget it.
You stole it.
- See what I mean?
- Jane, you know her.
She's a liar and a thief.
It's not her fault, it's her fucking nature.
Get the fuck away from me.
Fuck you too.
No fucking trust here!
Get the fuck up!
That's what fucking hurts!
Jesus fuck!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Are you crazy?
- Did I hurt him?
- What do you mean?
You hit him with a bat!
I'm going to call the cops.
Fuck.
He's alive!
Give me the bat. Give it to me right now.
I'm going to kill you, Holly.
I'm going to fucking...
- Don't!
- Time out!
Nobody move.
Jane, give me the bat, please.
Thank you.
Holly, don't tease him.
And Nick...
...you've got some real likeability issues.
Who has tape?
I do not feel good about this.
What would you like to do?
Call the police?
They'll arrest them both.
There's drugs everywhere.
What're you doing?
Nothing.
Fuck you, Jane.
Fuck!
What are you doing?
Just the cash. I'm clean.
No, we're not taking drug money
on the road with us. Put it back.
Well, it's not like you can tell
by looking at it.
Okay, you have a point.
We'll just take half. All right?
And we're not taking drugs
on the road with us either.
So give them back.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
We'll take the gag off when we leave.
Then there'll be four hours of loud music.
After which point, you can scream for help.
Meanwhile, work on the tape.
Phone's in the kitchen. Water?
Thanks, hon.
Everyone go potty!
We don't want to have to stop!
I went.
- Look what she's doing!
- Don't tease the animal.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
I'm going to kill you, Holly!
I'm going to kill you!
I should drive.
I feel really strongly about it.
Buckle up.
Close the door.
I'm not going over a cliff for you two.
So just forget it.
Fuck.
I've got some friends in St. Louis.
You remember Linda. I can stay with her.
Where are you guys going?
Los Angeles, then San Diego.
Yeah, and you're not coming.
Bummer.
Why did you stay with this guy so long?
A lot of that back there was drugs.
They really fuck him up.
But he's really a nice guy underneath?
Well, I wouldn't go that far.
It's the sex. Let's be frank, okay?
He was great in bed, am I right?
Sometimes.
I don't know. I think that
there's something beyond sex.
Yeah, me.
I don't know, but I certainly
didn't like his attitude.
I'm gonna think long and hard
before I take him back.
You go, girl.
Hi, you've reached Nick and Holly's.
Leave a message at the sound of the beep
and we'll get back to you.
My fucking head.
Jesus.
Thank you. Really?
Oh, my God, are you kidding?
Dance Fever was my favorite.
I thought Deney Terrio was
the coolest guy on earth.
Will you look at her?
It's pathological, man.
- She's young.
- I guess.
How you doing?
I'm fine. A little tired.
You were great back there.
You must have sold a ton of condos.
It was kind of fun.
Adrenaline.
You were very frightening.
I was very proud of you.
It was really nice meeting you.
Is Robin asleep already?
Yeah, she gets tired real easy.
You know, she doesn't look so good.
She's got all those allergies, man.
They come and go.
Did you call Linda yet?
Yeah. I was just thinking, you guys can
go ahead and leave tomorrow.
I'll just grab a bus.
Why? We're going right through St. Louis.
It's no big...
You're going back, aren't you?
Might as well.
What do you mean, "might as well"?
This is a guy who kicks your ass
all the time. This is not love, honey.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
Look, the man is going to kill you.
We humiliated him. We tied him up.
Come on.
I mean...
...I can't always do
what you think I should do.
- We've been there, Jane.
- Fine.
I just don't understand why you keep
setting yourself up to get hurt, that's all.
You should talk.
What does that mean?
You guys have been really great,
and I really like Robin.
I just hope that you know she's not gay.
So what?
So that's what I meant by saying
you should talk.
Shit!
Bus to Pittsburgh is now arriving.
Passengers with tickets,
please go directly to the boarding area.
Those passengers still needing tickets...
...please purchase them
at the ticket window.
Please take all luggage
to the baggage loading area.
Here we are.
Take care of yourself.
You too.
Get some sunshine, okay?
Promise?
Take care of yourself.
She'll get over it.
Thank you.
It's her life, you know.
She gives us all a bad name with that
"I'm addicted to a bad guy" stuff.
I hope everything was satisfactory.
Actually...
...the green on No. 8 is a little rough.
Really? We'll check it out
as soon as we can.
Is there anything else?
Screaming like that!
What?
Oh, shit.
Move closer.
Just a little bit closer.
There she is. There.
Holly!
Nick's...
...dead!
Sounds like "head."
Wait a minute. I have an idea.
What are you going to do?
What are you writing?
Morte.
She's not going...
It's French for "dead."
I can't because...
Who's Morte?
Wait!
Dead!
Who is he?
Get off the bus!
I can't believe this. I mean,
he was alive when we left.
I have a photo.
Do you think it would help?
Poor Nick.
He was such a nice guy, once in a while.
Stop with the nice guy stuff.
- They have to believe this was self-defence.
- Who's "they"?
"Who's they? " The cops in Pittsburgh.
You want me to go back there?
- Yeah.
- Now?
- I couldn't.
- Why not?
The memories.
- What fucking memories?
- Why does she have to go back?
Why don't we pretend we never saw it?
- Please tell me you're kidding.
- No.
When we left, he was alive.
How do we know what she did killed him?
Exactly! He could have tripped and hit
his head on the bat. It could happen.
You're going back. This is not a game.
I can't go to jail. Not with a baby.
What baby, honey?
I'm eight weeks pregnant.
You were going to bring a baby
into that house?
Like what were my options?
- How about abortion?
- I couldn't do that.
- I'd feel like a murderer.
- Honey...
...you are a murderer.
Oh, God!
To think it's possible
I killed my baby's daddy.
"To think it's possible? "
You hit him in the head
with a baseball bat. He's dead.
No, I mean, it's possible
that Nick is the daddy.
We never saw the newspaper.
She hit him in self-defence.
She's never going to see him again.
I'll call my lawyer in New York.
He'll tell us what to do.
If we have to go back, we'll say
we came as soon as we found out.
That's fine with me.
I suggest we keep driving.
We sleep in shifts. The farther away
from that body I get, the happier I'll be.
Try this. It's good.
In celebration of my uterus.
I'm wet.
No. Hold it.
Stop the car. Back up.
Fine.
I'll go get it.
Don't go around leaving messes.
All right! I don't know what you're
bitching about. It's all biodegradable.
It's plastic!
Nick had this house
with this drummer that Jane knew...
...and we'd all hang out together.
But then Nick pissed some people off,
so we had to move to Pittsburgh.
Can I have a bite of that?
It's been a long couple of days.
Tell me about it.
Jane's been so great to me.
I mean, at first I thought she just liked me
because of the whole...
...gay thing.
Jane's gay?
Like, hello?
You didn't know?
I don't know.
Don't look, don't look.
My God!
It's okay.
Anyway, she just got dumped.
So, you know, rebound time.
I know. Gross.
Don't worry, she won't try anything,
especially not after me.
I told her it was a real self-hating thing
to get crushes on straight girls.
But this person who dumped her,
she was gay, right?
Yeah, but even with gay girls
there are no guarantees.
They're very emotional.
That's about all I know.
They love uniforms
and don't break their hearts.
Uniforms?
Oh, yeah, all kinds. Especially UPS.
Will that be all?
Yeah.
- I'll get the check.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
Not that I'm an expert. I mean,
she's the only one I've ever seen.
Except for the girls in the porno tapes
Nick used to rent.
I'm sorry.
It's just that every time
I think of his little ways...
"Shame, shame, shame
"Shame on you, if you can't dance too
"Shame, shame, shame, shame, shame
"Shame, shame, shame on you"
Try to look a little more Western.
That's good.
Take the picture.
You sort of need to do something.
That's cute.
Who're you calling?
- Who're you calling?
- I was calling a friend.
You can't call that friend. He's dead.
And you're not supposed
to know he's dead.
I want my friends.
I want Nick.
Will you come talk to Holly, please?
Don't come in!
What's the matter?
Ms. Deluca?
Susan Newbauer.
She asked me to talk to you.
It's pneumonia.
We have to keep her for a couple of days.
- Can we see her?
- Tomorrow, after 11:00.
Just go on up to the eighth floor.
It's typical in this kind
of AIDS-related pneumonia.
AIDS?
You're telling me she's got AIDS?
Yes.
I'm sorry. I thought you knew.
No, I didn't.
She's okay. She'll be out
in less than a week.
Get this filled right away, please.
How you doing?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
For what? It's not like you knew
this was going to happen.
No.
I thought...
...if I could just...
...go somewhere else...
...I could make it...
...not happen.
I shouldn't have lied to you.
It wasn't a lie exactly.
It was more like a sinful omission.
Can I sit down?
Sure.
So I guess now we're even.
How so?
Holly told me you didn't know I was gay.
But I don't want you to worry
about anything because...
...I’m not after you.
I'm not worried.
Why?
Luck of the draw, I guess.
No, I mean...
...why aren't you after me?
You're not my type.
Is this a black-white thing?
No.
It's more like...
...a blonde-Carpenter thing.
You're safe with me.
Is there somebody I should call
or something? Like family?
My mother.
We don't...
...communicate much, not anymore.
What about you? You've got to get to LA.
Would you get me some ice?
Sure.
What's the matter? What is it?
What is it, goddamn it?
Wait, wait, wait!
What is it?
Are you in pain?
I don't know where to go.
I don't have any place...
...to go.
I don't know any place, Jane.
Sometimes if you don't have
any place to go...
...it's probably a good idea
to stay where you are.
Yeah?
Here...
...put your arm up.
Oh, Jesus.
This may be the wrong time
to bring this up, but...
...where the fuck are we?
Really, where are we?
Tucson.
As in Arizona?
Are you serious?
You know what this means?
I'm going to have to get some
cowboy boots. What about a horse?
Good.
No, I'm going to go straight from work.
I'm leaving now, Holly.
If you're coming, get off the phone.
- He's coming.
- Great.
I've got to go.
Get a move on.
We still have to pick up the cake.
Think she's gonna be surprised?
That's the idea. Hurry up.
I'll pick up the cake because I have
to drop by the hospital for a blood test.
Okay, and I told Abe
to meet us there around...
Are you okay?
Kicking all morning long.
Anyway, I told him to meet us there
around 10:00. I really think you'll like him.
Listen, I like any man who dates
a pregnant woman.
I wonder about him, but I like him.
Are you ready?
Two hands. In this bar...
...we wash the glasses with two hands.
That's the difference between clean...
...and fucking disgusting.
Watch your language.
Hi, Mom. Hi, Alex.
- What's up, Alex?
- Get in the kitchen and stay there.
- She sees you, she'll know.
- Give me a beer.
No, there isn't time.
Is there no mercy? I can't believe it.
A body like that on a 12-year-old.
That's enough candles.
Enough! Enough! No more!
We all know she's not 12.
It's not polite.
I thought I'd never get here.
Am I late? Great.
You ready?
The light.
Blow out the candles!
Come on, girl. You've got a cute little ass.
Can I have a light?
Give me that.
You're such a slut.
"In Georgia
"Nights are softer than a whisper
"Beneath a quilt
Somebody's mother made by hand"
It's like gay people are the only people
getting laid anymore.
Maybe you ought to try it.
I like being straight. I think
heterosexuality's gonna make a comeback.
Not if you have anything to do with it.
Go dance.
Would you like to dance?
Oh, Jesus.
My dream evening. Lesbians and cops.
What's next, Republicans?
Cop. Cop.
What?
Cop.
Evening, ladies.
Sir.
I'm looking for a Holly Pulchik.
Who?
Holly Pulchik.
She's got blonde hair,
green eyes, about 5'4".
Gee...
- You made it!
- There she is.
I was afraid some crime
would keep you away.
No, it couldn't.
It happens to be a slow night.
But Friday is the 1st.
And when they get their checks...
It's time to go. Good night, everyone.
We're gonna clean up.
Nice to meet you, Officer Lincoln.
No, no, please.
Call me Abe.
Abe?
As in Abe Lincoln?
Is this some kind of joke?
It's his name.
Isn't that a coincidence?
Just like the president.
I wonder why his parents thought Abraham
and Lincoln sounded good together?
Let me guess. You must be Robin.
Nice to meet you.
And this is Jane.
Hello.
Hi, Jane. Happy birthday.
Thank you. Peppers.
Yes, they're from my garden.
Isn't he sweet?
Hold on, babe.
I'm still in uniform.
Isn't that cute?
He takes it so serious.
Come on, honey. Let's go get a drink.
What will you have, babe?
Is it me, or is she working her way down
some list of guys who call women "babe"?
I hope she keeps her mouth shut.
Right.
- Where are you and Anna going again?
- She's taking me to see some psychic.
Here's your buddy.
Robin, do you need a ride home?
I have a car.
Didn't I tell you?
Holly came up to me inside
and said she needed the car.
It's on my way.
Could you take these...
...for me?
- Good night.
- Thanks.
I don't want to be late for this woman.
She scares the shit out of me.
Let's go.
She is really good. You have
to be prepared when you get there.
Here we go.
There's a long trip here. Travelling.
This is nice. You're in love.
This is very nice.
And...
What?
This is a friend, I feel...
This is not good at all.
There's a sickness here.
There's a curse. Yes.
This is a curse.
I can feel it.
- Can you do anything to remove the curse?
- Anna!
She can do that.
Last year...
Sit down.
Let me talk to my guides.
You're going to talk to these rocks?
These rocks are gonna
say something to you?
Uncross your legs, dear.
You want some?
Yeah, thanks.
How was the psychic?
Don't ask.
How was Alex?
He leave fingerprints all over you?
What is it with me and bartenders?
I don't know.
He's coming with us Saturday night
to the street fair.
Good, there's safety in numbers.
Just don't let him get you by yourself.
I cannot believe it's a cop.
He's cute though.
For a cop.
He does have a nice heinie.
Heinie?
What, is he two years old?
He has a nice "heinie."
Don't laugh.
And don't think that I didn't see you
checking out that man's basket.
What do you mean, "ew"?
What do you call it?
I don't call it anything.
I just wasn't brought up
to talk about a person's anatomy.
That's probably 'cause
you don't have a word for it.
That's just ridiculous. I do too.
It just doesn't often come up.
Okay. What is this below the bellybutton?
I'm not going to say it,
if that's what you're after. I hate that.
What do you call it?
"Down there."
Come on, "down there."
"Vagina" seems so formal.
You make it sound like a basement.
Honestly? Fine.
"Hoo-hoo" or "cissy."
You're kidding. A "hoo-hoo" or "cissy"?
- What is that?
- That's what my mother called it.
I had a "hoo-hoo" or a "cissy," and
my brother had a "noodle" or a "dingle."
And that's what you still call it?
It's better than "pussy."
Or...
..."beaver." What's that about?
I never got that.
Or worse...
Worse?
Did you say, "worse"?
Now what could be worse?
I have to hear you say it.
You know, I'm not going to say it.
C-U-N-T. Come on, please.
- I don't think so.
- Please. It'll free you. Try it.
- There's a policeman who can hear me.
- Give him a thrill.
- I don't think so.
- I'll wait.
No, you're such a baby.
- Come on.
- All right.
Cunt.
- What?
- I said it.
You breathed it. I want to hear you say it.
All right.
C-U-N-T. Cunt.
- Cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt.
- Free! Free!
Cunt!
Cunt! Cunt!
Cunt.
Dirty mouth.
You're right. I feel...
...I don't know, different.
That's because you're free, Miss Scarlett.
You're free!
Let's go get everybody and tell them!
Cunt, cunt, cunt!
Cunt! Cunt!
That can't be good for the baby.
They'll probably take a break
in the delivery room.
Maybe.
Do you miss it?
What?
Sex.
Yeah, I do.
You know what's weird?
You never know the last time you sleep
with somebody, it's the last time.
You're thinking:
"We've got problems,
we've got work to do," but...
...you never think...
Then you break up and a month later
you look back and go:
"That was it."
That Tuesday, or Friday, or whatever.
And you wish you'd paid attention.
Because it was the last time.
You know?
Oh, well.
Listen, thanks for my birthday present.
A girl can never have
too many ThighMasters.
I know, I'm sorry.
No, no. I love it.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
Your mail's in the living room.
Good night. I drank too much.
Good night.
"Long ago
"And so far away
"I fell in love with you
"Before the second show
"Your guitar
"Just sounds so sweet and clear
"But you're not really here
"It's just the radio
"Don't you remember
You told me you loved me, baby
"Said you'd be coming back
This way again, baby
"You call me baby
"I love you"
- What's the deal? Do you like her or what?
- Yeah, I do.
I've been trying, but she's got that...
..."back off" thing going on.
So I just assumed she was one of the girls.
No, she's not that.
She's definitely not one of the girls.
- No kidding?
- No kidding.
She's shy, you know.
I hear you're going with us on Saturday?
I am now.
We should have a little talk.
I'll give you a beer.
Come on.
You ready?
All right. One.
Two.
Three.
You're right there.
Higher.
You want a drink?
You okay?
Just tired.
She's having a good time.
Yeah.
That's good, no?
It's what you wanted.
Yeah.
Hey, babe.
Is something the matter?
No.
Smells like marijuana out here.
Clove cigarettes.
You know that's not good for the baby.
Having him come out that tiny hole's
not good for me either. So...
...we're even.
What is wrong?
I got things on my mind.
It's that guy, right?
Nick?
Who told you about him?
It had to be someone.
And besides, you keep calling out "Nick,"
in bed.
I do?
Maybe it's something
that sounds like "Nick."
Does he know about the baby?
You know...
...I’m only here temporarily.
I might go back.
I know that.
And I will not stand in your way.
But if he loves you so much...
...why doesn't he call?
Maybe he can't get to a phone.
Come on back to the party.
I want to get one dance before we go.
All right.
No, stop.
- Why?
- I don't know.
- You don't like it?
- No, I do.
I do like it.
So do I.
Oh, God.
Feel me too. Put your hands on me.
- Feel.
- It's been a long time.
Me too.
Go slow. Slow.
Real slow.
Wait.
What's the matter?
I'm a little drunk.
Where's the couch?
You are so beautiful.
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
You are so fucking beautiful.
You taste so good.
Talk to me.
- Tell me what you like.
- Listen...
- I want to make you come so hard.
- I have to tell you something.
I know.
You need to know something.
It's okay. I know.
I'm gonna use something.
What?
I'm gonna use something. We'll be safe.
Don't worry about it.
About what?
It's okay.
No, you don't understand.
I'm...
...positive. I tested positive.
I know. I just don't want to talk about it
'cause I already know.
Jesus.
What? What's the matter?
Who told you?
Nobody told me.
Jesus. You knew. She told you.
Yeah, she told me.
Why?
It was no big deal.
She said you were shy and had a bad time
with some guy. And I guessed...
...and she didn't deny it.
It came out real casual,
like it's just a part of your history.
Like, "Hey, she's on the rebound."
"Be careful," you know.
Come on, it's just a detail.
What does that make you?
A big hero...
...bringing sex to the unfuckable?
You must feel really good about yourself.
God.
That's not it.
I just want things the way they used to be.
You know?
I want to meet someone. Someone I like.
Get drunk, have a good time
and fuck my brains out.
Why can't we do that anymore?
Because you can't.
That's all, you just can't.
I think you should go home.
No, please don't make me beg. Just go.
Good morning!
- How's it going?
- Great.
How was last night?
It was good.
Good.
- Is Alex still here?
- No, he's gone.
So you had a good time though?
Real good, till I found out
you told him I've got HIV.
I didn't exactly tell him, you know.
No, I know. He guessed.
"She looks like the kind of girl
that tested positive for the AIDS virus.
"I don't know.
She's got that kind of glow."
It slipped out.
What did you think you were doing?
I thought I was doing a good thing.
I know you like him.
- He likes you.
- Yeah, great.
Maybe he'll ask me to go steady.
Maybe he'll take me to the prom.
Come on.
What do you think I am, stupid?
No. I don't think that at all.
You think you can just put a man
in my bed and I'll forget?
All it does, if you want to know,
is remind me.
Alex, and you, and Holly and her baby.
Every living thing I see reminds me.
So what are you going to do?
You gonna hide in the house?
Lock yourself away?
Come on!
You don't know anything about it.
It's none of your business.
You're the one that's in love
with somebody you can never have.
Do me a favour, okay. I'll stay out
of your love life and you stay out of mine.
Not just my love life, my life.
Stay out of my life.
Meaning what?
That means maybe this isn't working.
Maybe you should move.
Okay.
Take the fucking piano.
If you don't, I'll leave it out in the rain.
I swear to God I will.
All right.
All the way back across the room.
Against the wall.
- How are you?
- Good.
Will you teach me to play piano?
- Is this gonna be good?
- That's fine.
Hey, babe?
Marry me.
Get serious.
I am serious.
Get out of town.
Look.
- Freeze, sucker.
- I got you!
I got you.
- Stop! Stop!
- Marry me.
Marry me tomorrow.
I can't marry you, Abe.
You're not over him yet, are you?
We're all over him.
Like six feet over him.
Mom?
But it was an accident. Or...
...self-defence. I would never kill anybody
on purpose, or like in cold blood.
Did you ever see that movie?
Let's get some rest, okay?
You don't want to marry me now, do you?
We're together now.
We're together.
And that's not changing.
She looks so thin.
Look at you, honey.
They gave us a terrible map at Hertz.
I have been driving around
for an hour and a half.
Is this your house?
Isn't it quaint?
I need to use the little girls' room, darling.
- Sure, Mom.
- This heat!
And the A/C is NG, right Jer?
You know me.
I like it so you need a sweater.
It's two days. It'll be fine.
- I'm Jerry.
- I'm sorry, Jerry.
- My daughter, Robin.
- Pleased to meet you.
I told her I could've picked you up.
You know me, I'm so damned independent.
Riding in other people's cars, forget it.
Well, isn't this nice?
Look, Jer, a cactus flower.
They bloom once every 100 years.
Quick, show me the potty, darling.
I'm about to burst.
Anyway, Jane called me at work.
Wants to know how you are.
I'm fine.
- Who's Jane?
- Jane lived here up until a few days ago.
You stay out of this, Holly.
It's between me and Jane.
She asked for my advice.
So I told her she's anti-lesbian.
- I am not.
- Who's a lesbian?
Jane is.
- And she was living here?
- Yes, ma'am.
I am not anti-lesbian.
Not you, her.
- Who?
- Jane.
This is her old problem.
She creates a situation where she gets this
rejection that everyone else sees coming.
She wasn't being honest.
I think it's a black thing too.
Jane is black?
Yes, ma'am. She sure is.
You can't live a lie, you just can't.
Well, there's lying
and there's just not telling.
Big diff.
She's a black lesbian?
Yes, ma'am, that is right.
And she was living here?
With you?
No, she was just living here.
They weren't like fucking or anything.
Were you?
I'll get the coffee.
I have to get going, babe.
Why? Your shift doesn't start until 10:30.
Don't you want to go upstairs for a while?
No, not tonight.
- It was nice meeting you, ma'am.
- You going already?
- We have dessert.
- Maybe next time. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Good night.
Maybe I'm just too fat now.
Don't worry, dear. It's a natural thing.
Will they live here after they get married?
Who?
Holly and that nice young man.
What is his name?
I'm not sure she wants to marry him.
A pregnant girl?
Is she crazy? She should grab him.
It's not really his baby.
So what?
She still should grab him.
Believe me, I know what she's gonna
have to go through.
You know, I'm a feminist too.
I was a single mother after your father left.
Do you think that was easy?
I even voted for Carter twice.
But you can't fight nature.
God knows, you girls keep trying.
Treating your men like side dishes.
You stick a fork in when needed,
just like men used to treat us.
Mother, who am I treating?
Do you see a man here anywhere?
No, I don't.
And I think it's a problem.
I don't understand
why you don't come home.
I like it here, Mom.
It's so strange.
You're not exactly bubbling over
with happiness.
It's a life, Mom, not a hayride.
Honey, what is this?
My gosh!
The police are here.
Yes, I see the police, Mother.
What the fuck is going on?
Hold it.
Jane, what are you doing here?
I called her.
- I thought that she should know.
- Know what?
He's arresting me.
What for?
You know what for, Robin. Pittsburgh.
- You told him?
- Yes, she told me.
I take this name seriously.
I cannot tell a lie.
That was Washington, schmuck!
Whatever.
Anyway, I'm going to stand by Holly
100 percent.
But I am sworn to uphold the law.
And I don't believe I would be any use
to her whatsoever if I broke my oath.
Now would I?
He really loves me.
Yeah, I can tell by the manacles
on your wrists.
Right this way, miss.
Don't say a word. Not to him,
not to anybody. We'll get you a lawyer.
I'll miss you guys.
I promise you that they're going
to treat her right.
They know that she is going to be
my future wife.
Son of a bitch!
Honey, what in the world is going on?
I feel like I've just seen
America's Most Wanted in person.
This has got to be the mother.
Jane, please.
Yes, I am. And who are you?
I'm the lesbo. I used to live here
till your daughter threw me out.
Well, I'm sorry.
Me too. I think this makes her
real happy...
...'cause now she's got the house
all to herself.
Cut it out. You're just being mean.
Jane, stop.
You know, she's gonna need our help.
No, not "our" help.
I'll take care of this myself.
Okay.
Fine, fine, fine!
- They do that now, don't they?
- What?
Call themselves "lesbos."
She makes it sound like a compliment.
She wants to confess.
She says she doesn't want to bring
her child into a world of lies.
You have nothing to worry about.
Holly has promised me
that she'll keep her mouth shut...
...as long as she does not have
to lie out loud.
We wouldn't be here if it wasn't for you,
you brown-nosing putz!
I took an oath.
You took a fucking oath.
Now we're stuck in Pittsburgh.
Holly's on trial 'cause of your oath.
- So what exactly do they have?
- Nothing.
- Except Abe's testimony, which is hearsay.
- That is the truth.
Shut up! Nobody wants to hear the truth.
Aside from that, what do they have?
They have the Polaroid.
The Polaroid?
Yes.
I mentioned that I had seen a snapshot.
It's on the list of exhibits, but come on.
What the hell can they do with that?
Cold-blooded?
Cruel?
Inhuman?
What words would you use to describe
the woman who posed...
...and took this photograph?
This is a photograph...
...of a man, who in a few short hours,
will be dead...
...from wounds inflicted by this woman
that you see before you.
Not surprisingly, everything that you say
tends to exonerate your friend.
Sorry. It's the truth.
Perhaps, not coincidentally,
it exonerates you.
- There are no charges against me.
- Yet.
Come on, Your Honor...
...is he allowed to just intimidate me
like this?
- Mr. Massarelli, please.
- I apologize. It was unintentional.
What is the nature of your friendship
with Holly Pulchik?
- Excuse me?
- I'm sorry. Let me...
...rephrase the question. How would
you characterize your friendship?
I would call her my friend.
- What is this "friendship" stuff?
- That's what I'm trying to find out.
Let me put this delicately to avoid
offending the court. Is there a...
...romantic character to your friendship?
- Objection!
- Overruled. You may proceed.
To repeat, Ms. Deluca:
Is there a romantic character
to your friendship with the defendant?
- No, Mr. Mazzaratti, there is not.
- Massarelli.
Sorry. Unintentional.
You are one of these gay women
that we read about...
...or do you prefer "lesbian"?
- Do I prefer them to you?
- Are you gay?
Do I look it?
- Your Honor...
- Please answer the question.
Are you gay?
Yes, I am.
And I'm sure you hear that
from women all the time.
But in my case, it happens to be true.
She's scared shitless,
just like I would be after today.
No, I don't want you to do that, Anna.
Okay? I don't want you to do that.
I'll call you tonight.
Schmuck.
You did your best.
Yeah, I did. Which is more
than I can say for you.
Justice is hard.
Justice?
You call this justice?
This girl protects herself
against some marauding asshole...
...who uses her as a punching bag
and she's going to jail. That's justice?
Is that what you want?
I want Holly to be my wife.
I want us to be a family.
Where, in the joint?
I don't know that.
But I do know there's no kind of family
without the law.
None whatsoever.
'Cause the law that governs this society is
the same law...
...that holds the family together.
Where'd you read that?
On the side of a Cheerios box?
You think I love her less now.
But I don't.
I love her more.
That is why I had to do this.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
- And they lived happily ever after.
- Did I wake you?
I was just looking for a drink.
There's beer.
I had some bourbon from the plane
but I seem to have finished it.
What are you doing?
I thought somehow if I made this trip
again, we'd all be here at the end.
Oh, honey.
Nobody was happy in these pictures.
Except maybe you.
Tommy was already so frail.
And your father...
Well, you loved him, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
With all my heart.
But I lost him.
And Tommy too. And that's that.
You just have to let it go, Robin.
Just let it go.
I can't.
You have to, darling.
Because it's never going
to come out any differently...
...no matter how many times
you make this trip.
I know that.
When we lost Tommy...
...your father just couldn't live with that.
I don't blame him.
It's not right, losing your children.
Children are supposed to live after you.
Oh, honey.
Are you crying?
Oh, my gosh.
Do you know,
I don't ever remember you crying.
Even when you were a baby.
Isn't that funny?
I'm sorry.
I know you're not well, darling.
I don't know what it is
and I don't want to know. But...
...I know you'll get better.
You were always the strong one.
I can't lose you.
I can't just lose everybody.
I do the best I can, honey.
I know it's not enough.
And I'm sorry.
But that's what you get in life. You know?
You get whoever you end up with.
Whoever is willing to stick by you
and fight for you...
...when everyone else is gone.
And it ain't always who you expect.
But you just have to make do.
I'm not complaining, Mom.
"Never complain. Never explain."
Katherine Hepburn.
She said that in Redbook last month.
It's a good motto, isn't it?
The best I can do is pretend
like you never testified.
- Just go on like it never happened.
- Go on to what?
Honestly?
I don't know.
All right, this is the situation:
I am still angry.
I do not forgive you for anything.
And I don't want to talk about it.
Anna filled me in. She told me...
...everything I needed to know
about the trial so far. I know I can help.
Even if I can't,
I couldn't make it any worse.
Holly is as much my responsibility
as anyone else's.
And so are you. Because you are
my family and I love you.
I feel fine.
My T-cells are over 100
and I'm raring to go. So...
...unless you want to waste time
being stubborn...
...I suggest we get me on the stand
as soon as possible.
You expect us to believe
that the defendant...
...pregnant with this man's child,
would leave him and never look back?
It was over. He beat her and abused her.
I saw. I saw how he treated her.
But not to call? Not to leave an address,
so he could forward her mail?
Practical reasons aside,
let's just say she did strike a blow...
...for self-defence. Let's just assume.
And she decides to let him...
...stew in his own juices for a while.
But a couple of hours, a few days later,
she realizes, "Hey...
"...he's my little baby's daddy.
"And you know what? He's not so bad.
"Maybe he's got a temper."
But all she knows is she needs him.
She needs to call him.
But it was over between them.
I know you think a girl like her, the most
important thing in her life is a man.
But she didn't need him. She had us.
I hardly think that you're
a replacement for a father.
I don't know what it is, but...
...there's something
that goes on between women.
You men know that because...
...it's the same for you.
I'm not saying one sex is
better than the other. I'm...
...just saying...
..."like speaks to like."
Love, or whatever,
doesn't always keep. So...
...you find out what does. If you're lucky.
Thank you for that very illuminating view
of the war between the sexes.
Are you a lesbian too?
No, sir.
But at times I understand the inclination.
Suppose there is this bond between
women. Suppose men are disposable.
- I didn't say that.
- If so, why should we believe you?
Wouldn't you say anything,
do anything to keep your "sister"...
...keep your bosom buddy, so to speak,
out of jail?
I'm under oath. I wouldn't perjure myself.
I'm glad I don't have to remind you of that.
And just for the record...
...you didn't know...
...until the police told you...
...that this man was dead of his wounds?
If I'm lying...
...may I be struck down
with some terrible disease.
All right, good news.
Got an offer.
Involuntary manslaughter,
extenuating circumstances.
One to two years.
Parole after six months.
I got you minimum security in Arizona.
Two hours from home, good medical care.
I'd hate to have my baby in jail.
What are the chances for an acquittal?
He's dead as a result of her actions.
Juries want to make someone pay.
She didn't testify in her own defence and
I don't know how much good you did her.
I mean...
...my baby will have a mother
who's a convicted felon.
I don't know, what do you think?
- Under the circumstances...
- I'd have her...
I mean, Abe.
What do you think about that, babe?
I think that you should take it.
I will keep the baby until you get out.
Yeah, but...
- That's what I'll do then.
- Fine.
I'll tell them we take it.
I love you.
- I got to get in there with you.
- Do you?
I want you so much, babe.
Can we have a minute?
We'll see you later.
Honey.
How's my baby?
Baby...
...I missed you so much.
Well, so much for the bonds
between women.
I love you.
You can't fight that.
I love you so much.
You were pretty good in there.
What ever happened to
"Honesty's the best policy? "
You don't want to go overboard.
I've been thinking and thinking about this.
I want to say it.
I am really, really sorry.
I truly am.
Yeah, me too. I get so angry, so fast.
It's just...
It's lonely.
Between me and everybody else
there's all this...
...space all the time. And it gets...
...bigger and bigger.
I'm on one side and...
...I’m screaming, and they're...
...waving.
And the...
...one person I think I'm holding is...
...waving too.
I'm holding you.
There won't be any more lies...
...between us. Not even for my own good.
No, ma'am.
Good.
I'm going to go call Anna.
- I feel...
- What's the matter?
What's wrong?
Listen, I'm sorry to wake you,
but we're back in Tucson and...
...she's in the hospital.
What curse, honey? Who?
The one on my friend.
Remember when I came to see you? You
said there was a curse on a friend of mine.
It's my friend, Robin. She's...
You know I don't believe in this stuff.
You know that.
I just thought it couldn't hurt
to come and see you.
Oh, Robin.
That's the girl with AIDS.
Anna's friend.
She's my friend.
I see.
So can you do it?
Do what?
Take the curse off of her.
You said you could...
It's AIDS, honey.
I know that, but right now
it's just a lung infection, see?
I don't want a miracle.
I just want to give her a 51-49 shot.
I brought money. I can pay you right now.
Pay when it works.
I can't promise anything.
Don't wake her up.
Just doing my job.
Is that a cold?
Because she can't afford an infection.
I'll have to mask you.
Are you blind?
Can't you see she's been crying?
It's her mother.
People think they're being nice,
but they come in here with colds.
It's not a goddamn cold.
Don't be such a hoo-hoo.
What's a "hoo-hoo"?
It's a cunt, dear.
Now, why don't you leave us alone?
Tommy?
It's just me.
I know.
Okay.
Where's Mom?
She had to go back to the house.
Will you call her?
Sure.
She's asking for you.
Do you want me to get a doctor?
No.
I had a crush on a woman once.
I was ten.
That's when I had crushes on boys.
She was a strawberry blonde.
That's what my mom called her.
She was the babysitter...
...at a hotel we stayed at...
...right before my dad went to Vietnam.
She was beautiful.
Strawberry blonde.
I used to be a strawberry blonde too.
It was me you loved, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Still.
I loved you too.
I won't...
...want a funeral, but...
...Mom will.
But it's got to be here.
Don't let her take me back to San Diego.
Okay.
And afterwards...
...you could have a big party
at the house, okay?
Okay.
Big party.
You can do it. Push right into it.
Push. You can do it.
Nice deep breath and push.
No screaming.
Perfect. Come on, you can do it.
Give us a real good push now.
Hold it. The baby's coming.
I wanted to be here for it, you know,
to help her with the breathing.
Next time. You ever seen
one of these things?
They're really ugly.
- Where are they?
- Let's go.
Wait a minute. Come on, man.
"Fristad."
"Mitchell."
"Pulchik."
Don't look at me.
I can't wait to see the baby.
We made it. We're back home.
You look great.
Thank you.
Isn't she beautiful!
Hi, little one.
Welcome, Mary Todd.
What, what, what?
Push it out of there. Push it out.
"They call me mellow yellow
"I'm just mad about fourteen
"Fourteen's mad about me"
It was rough going there.
But she managed to pull herself through.
And the next day
the Pentamidine kicked in, so...
What are her T-cells now?
They're about 35.
They were under 20 before.
She doesn't look good.
She looks great.
We want to welcome Holly home
with her new baby and her new husband.
We're all glad to be here with our friends.
And I want you right now,
ladies and gentlemen...
...to put your hands together
and give a round of warm applause...
...to 1983's fourth runner-up...
...in the Star Search talent competition.
No, no, Jane.
It was third runner-up, not fourth.
I told her.
Fourth was this terrible
little boy tap-dancer with pimples.
He only got that far because he cheated.
I mean, that is the only reason...
What?
Shut up.
"Every time I look into...
"...your lovely eyes
"I see a love
"That money just can't buy
"One look from you
"I drift away
"I pray that you...
"...are here...
"...to stay
"Anything you want
"You got it
"Anything you need
"Anything at all
"You got it
"Baby
"Every time I hold you
"I begin to understand
"Everything about you
"Tells me I'm your best friend
"So I live my life
"To be with you
"Because no one...
"...can do
"The things you do
"Anything you want
"You got it
"Anything you need
"Anything at all
"You got it
"Anything you need"
Ready to go?
You better be back for Christmas
'cause Mary Todd's expecting you.
I will.
Make sure you call me
as soon as you get to LA.
- I want to know how the audition went.
- Okay, Mom.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org