Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Jesus!
Asshole!
Did you see that?
He pulled right out in front of me!
I took my eyes off the road
for a second, but come on!
Maybe it's time we take a break.
I'll pull over the next chance we get.
Nice car.
Thanks.
You got your air, CD...
...leather.
You sprung for the whole nine yards.
I guess so. But I suppose that rig of
yours is what you really need out here.
Why would you want that piece of shit
when you got a ride like this?
- What you need out here is a CB radio.
- Yeah, is that right?
If you use a CB, you need a handle.
Yours could be "Shit-for-Brains."
Do you even care
that you damn near killed us?
I didn't see you.
You pulled out in front of me.
- Like hell I did! I saw what happened!
- Let's just forget this, okay?
I'm sorry it ever happened.
I don't want any trouble.
No, I bet you don't.
Howdy, ma'am. Ought to be
more careful who you ride with.
- What was that all about?
- Nothing. The guy in the truck.
He thinks I tried to hit him.
Come on, let's go.
- Do you want me to drive?
- Later. Just get in.
- I promise not to sideswipe anyone.
- Just get in.
I'm kidding.
You getting ready
for the Grand Prix?
What did you get?
Junk food fiesta. Let's see...
Sno Balls...
...Yoo-hoo and MoonPies.
- Can you believe they still make this?
- It's gourmet cuisine around here.
This is crazy. Look at this.
It says, "If you win
this mail-in contest...
...you can choose between $90,000
or 90,000 donuts."
What would you do
with 90,000 donuts?
I don't know. Sell them for
30 cents each and pay off this car.
No kidding.
Ninety thousand dollars.
That'd solve some problems.
What the hell?
- What did you do?
- Nothing. I...
Hang on. I can't steer.
Unbelievable.
- Perfect.
- Out of range?
So much for taking the scenic route.
- The baffle gasket's burned out.
- What?
- It's connected to the connecting rod.
- Oh, God, shut up!
Oh, man! Can you believe this?
- This could be our worst decision ever.
- What are you doing?
No, just listen.
We're changing jobs, right?
Our finances are pretty well fucked.
And we're in the middle of nowhere.
Yeah, this is our worst decision.
Get out of here! You're bugging me.
Okay, good luck,
because I'm going to California.
No problem.
Just leave me the MoonPies.
- And the donuts!
- No, there's a car.
Christ, not these guys.
Assholes.
Jeff?
What the hell's..?
- What's he doing?
- I don't know.
This isn't good.
- Hi. You folks all right?
- Fine. Our car broke down.
I saw that.
I'll help you push it off the road.
Thanks for the help.
Honey, you want to steer?
Massachusetts plates.
You folks on vacation?
No, we're moving.
- Oh, yeah? Whereabouts?
- San Diego.
Do you think we can use your CB
to radio a tow truck?
I blew a fuse on it this morning.
I'll fix it at the truck stop at l-40.
- How far is that?
- About 60 miles.
I was just driving along
and she quit on me.
Belts, battery's working.
It used to be, you'd kick it and it
would start. Now they got computers.
- It is a new car.
- You know, that could be it.
You been riding it pretty hard?
They tend to overheat when they're new.
Well, yeah, a little, but not...
Tell you what. I can give you a ride
to Belle's, a diner five miles down.
They've got a pay phone.
You can call a tow truck.
That's nice of you,
but I think you got it.
We'll just let her cool off a bit.
Thanks. We really appreciate it.
- I wish you luck getting it started.
- Thanks a lot.
- Honey.
- He's right. It's just overheated.
What if it's not?
We'd be stuck out here.
No, but just give it some time,
let it cool off. We'll be all right.
It's getting pretty toasty out here.
Are you sure you wanna blow this ride?
No, but...
I don't want to leave the car alone.
What if I take the ride, call the tow
truck and order a nice, cold iced tea?
- And I stay with a nice, hot car?
- Right.
Right.
- Sure you're all right?
- I'll be fine.
Excuse me.
- Can I take you up on that ride?
- Sure, step on up.
- Your husband doesn't want to come?
- No, he's gonna stay with the car.
What the hell?
Tow truck, my ass.
Excuse me. I was supposed
to meet my wife here.
She's dark-haired, about 5'5",
wearing a white Benetton sweater.
- White what?
- Benetton sweater.
Hank, your order's up! I'm pretty
busy here. People come and go.
This was within the last half-hour.
She may have been with a trucker.
A guy wearing a baseball cap,
driving a big 18-wheeler.
Doesn't ring a bell.
You sure?
This man's looking for his wife.
Dark hair, white button-on sweater...
...traveling with a guy wearing a cap.
Has anybody seen them?
Looks like she got away
from you, cowboy.
You think maybe she left a message
with one of your other employees?
Don't see how that's possible.
I'm the only one that works here.
- Is there another Belle's Diner?
- No sirree! Definitely not.
She and I must have gotten our signals
crossed. How far is the next town?
About 20 miles.
Can you do me a favor?
If my wife, Amy, comes in...
...tell her I was here
and to stay put till I get back.
- Could you do that, please?
- Yeah, okay.
Thanks.
Pull over!
I don't believe it.
Jesus!
Christ!
Hey, man.
- What are you doing?
- Trying to stop you. Didn't you see me?
- Yeah.
- Well?
Never mind. I'm looking for my wife.
Where is she?
How should I know where your wife is?
I'm the guy with the Jeep.
You gave her a ride to Belle's Diner.
Not me. Sorry.
Sorry? This was like a half-hour ago.
You don't remember?
Look, I've never seen you before
in my life.
What are you doing?
Amy?
Amy, are you in there?
Look, I don't know what you want...
I want my wife back!
Now what have you done..?
- Officer, I need your help.
- What's the problem?
- He's done something with my wife.
- Calm down, sir. What's going on?
I don't know. Last I saw her,
she was with this guy, in his truck.
- Now he says he never saw her!
- I don't know what he's talking about.
- Don't lie, you son of a bitch!
- Calm down!
- Now tell me exactly what happened.
- Okay, all right.
Our car broke down.
He stopped, offered to help...
...and took my wife to a pay phone.
But she never showed up!
- What do you have to say about this?
- Officer, I don't know.
He runs me off the road
and starts hollering about his wife.
I swear, I've never seen him before.
- You didn't give his wife a ride?
- No.
He's lying!
- Sir, may I search your truck?
- Hell yes. Go ahead.
My name's Red Barr. All my permits
are current. You can see them.
That's not necessary. Stand back
behind the line, both of you.
I need to see your license
and registration, please.
- Are those yours?
- Yeah.
My personal stuff.
You want to take a look?
No.
I think we're done here.
You're free to go.
Wait, that's it?
You won't question him anymore?
I've searched the truck. There's
no evidence of suspicious activity.
Maybe you confused my truck
with another.
- Go to hell! Let me see that!
- Hold on a second!
You want to get arrested?
The man's got a point here.
This is a plain-looking truck.
Looks like a lot of trucks.
Maybe you did get them mixed up.
You stay put.
Mr. Taylor?
Come on.
It was him. It was this truck.
I can see that.
Did you get a license plate number?
What? No!
- How about the information on the door?
- I wasn't paying attention. Come on!
Mr. Taylor, did you have a beef
with your wife today?
What's that got to do with anything?
Is there a possibility
she could have left you?
I don't believe this.
My wife did not leave me!
You put two people in a car
long enough, they'll go at it.
I've seen men dump their women
on the roadside and vice versa.
Officer, I'd really like to stay and
help, but I got a long haul to Fresno.
Go ahead.
I appreciate your cooperation.
This is insane. Officer, please.
I've got his information. If I need to
find him later, I know where to look.
Sir.
Much obliged.
No hard feelings. I really do hope
you find your wife. Thanks.
Mr. Taylor, you want to come with me?
I believe you that she's missing.
Maybe you got confused about
which truck. I'm trying to help.
The town of Brackett is 31 miles away.
My deputy's name is Len Carver.
He'll help you if you want
to report your wife missing.
Sheriff, Mrs. Gilbert's locked out
of her trailer. Can you help her?
- 10-4. Tell her I'm on my way.
- Will do.
Mr. Taylor, do yourself a favor...
...go see my deputy.
- Is this a recent picture?
- Yes, a couple months old.
Her hair's the same?
Yeah.
Well, we'll certainly
do our best, Mr. Taylor.
Over 100,000 people go missing
in this country every year.
Runaways, deadbeat dads, dropouts,
folks hiding from the IRS...
...all vanishing without a trace. We get
these kinds of pictures all the time.
I'm not saying your wife
is one of them. I hope not.
Unless there's a ransom demand
or evidence of forced abduction...
...the FBI won't even look at
your case until it's been 24 hours.
Nevertheless, we'll certainly
keep our eyes peeled.
Mr. Taylor...
...why don't you go to Belle's? Get
a cup of coffee, wait for your wife.
If anything comes up,
I'll contact you. How's that sound?
Yeah.
- Did my wife come in?
- Didn't see her.
You didn't see her
or she didn't come in?
Like I said last time,
maybe she was in, maybe she wasn't.
All I'm saying is
that I didn't see her.
It ain't none of my business, but if
I was you, I'd check the ladies' room.
Amy?
Amy!
I'll be right with you, cowboy.
- I want to see your order slips.
- What?
You write down the names.
Let me see.
Are you nuts?
I don't have to show you jackshit!
If my wife came in here,
then her name's in that pile.
You calling me a liar?
Let me see these fucking slips!
Mister, I've had
just about enough of you.
- Operator.
- Sheriff's office.
- One moment, please.
- Come on!
My name's Billy.
You the fella looking for his wife?
Yes!
Yeah, how'd you know?
Did you see her?
Have you seen her? Please,
if you know something, tell me.
- I seen her, maybe.
- Where? When?
Inside, a little while ago.
- She came in on a truck.
- Right.
- A big semi.
- Then what?
Well, then she left on another truck.
With who?
With some men.
They think I'm a dummy, but I ain't.
I'll get my trucker's license.
This is very important.
Did you see where they took my wife?
- Route 7, north. Up by the river.
- By the river? Where?
They don't tell me that kind of thing.
Who doesn't? The bartender?
The men in the truck?
I ain't talking to you no more.
Come with me to the police. If you tell
them what you saw, they can help me.
- Well, now you the dummy.
- What's that supposed to mean?
Don't you get it?
Police is the ones in on it.
Work, goddamn it.
Hello! Steve, this is Jeffrey Taylor,
you remember? Right.
Don't put me on hold, please!
Listen, I need a favor.
I gotta talk to that friend of yours
at the FBI.
Right. It's about Amy.
Something's happened to...
I think she's been...
She's missing! I think she's...
Hello? Fuck!
Hello! Steve? Yeah.
No, don't call me back!
Steve! Steve! Shit!
What..?
- Get out of the car now!
- Oh, shit!
Son of a bitch!
What do you want?!
He's getting away!
- What the hell's going on?
- He got away, went down the river.
Yeah, we're pulling it out now.
- Careful. It's gonna come loose.
- I got it.
This is what happens
when you get one without the other.
- How do we explain this to Warren?
- I ain't gonna.
Hey, you all right?
According to your wife, you got a pile
of cash in your bank account.
Is that true?
- There's some, yeah.
- Well, "some" just don't cut it.
She gave us an exact dollar amount.
I want that same figure from you.
There are different accounts.
The balance fluctuates. I don't...
Fluctuates, my ass.
If some hotshot like you ain't
watching his bottom line...
...it'd be the first time in history.
What do you think, Earl?
I think we've been lied to.
He ain't no goddamn donut king.
The slut lied to save her ass.
Piece of shit. I'm gonna do him.
Ninety thousand.
Ninety thousand dollars.
Now you crawl your ass out of there.
You're a tough man
to get ahold of, Jeffrey.
What do you want?
It's not what I want,
it's what you want.
How bad do you want it?
It is gonna cost you.
I can't show it to you now...
...but it's about 5'5", 115 pounds,
three or four of that just pure tit.
Nice, curly, brown hair
upstairs and down.
Interested?
Why?
What does this..? Why us?
Bring him up here.
The town of Brackett, Jeff.
It's a two-bit shithole
in the middle of nowhere.
See the bank down there?
You're gonna tell the manager
to express-wire...
...$90,000 from your bank account
in Boston. Cash.
How do I know she's still alive?
Shut up!
Come on, Jeff.
I need you to pay attention.
You see that building with
the flagpole coming out the top?
- Yeah.
- That's the sheriff's station.
There are two cops. One has desk duty,
the other is patrolling the foothills.
A minute ago, Billy here...
...called in an accident
on the l-40 connector.
See? There he goes.
It will take him 20 minutes
to get there...
...10 to see there's no accident,
and 20 to get back. That's 50 minutes.
That is exactly the amount of time
you have to get my money.
Before you get any ideas
about calling in the cavalry...
...remember, we'll be watching you.
We're gonna be listening
on those scanners.
And if we see anything unusual...
...an unmarked car, a plane, one human
being who even smells like a cop...
...you can just keep
your fucking money, Jeff...
...and I'll send you pieces of her
from time to time.
Billy.
Give him the jacket.
Go on. Put it on, Jeff.
You can't go into a bank looking
like that, now, can you?
We don't have to do this, because
I can get you the money, I swear.
I promise you.
Just let my wife go, please.
Forty-nine minutes, Jeff.
Time to get the show on the road.
Here's my driver's license
and credit card, if you need it.
The account number from my bank
in Boston. How long will this take?
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
I only have $5000 in that account.
How much can you advance me
on my credit card?
My card has a $6000 limit,
can you advance me that?
No, I'm sorry, I can't. The limit
for non-customers is $500 a day.
Sir, are you sure you're all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just transfer the money, okay?
I'm gonna tell you something.
What I'm about to tell you...
You can't call anyone,
do you understand?
Yes.
Whatever happens,
just keep writing on that pad.
Please, now, just keep writing.
They're probably watching now.
They have police scanners.
The whole town's under surveillance.
If I don't walk out of here with...
Excuse me. You the manager?
- Yes, I am.
- I was told to see you about a loan.
Certainly.
If you would just take a seat.
Yes?
Just forget it.
I had a car accident, a minor one.
I'm just kind of...
How long is this gonna take?
It will... Well, it's going
to take a few minutes.
Yeah, I'm calling
regarding account number...
...9- 8-2-5-8-1-0-3.
Jeffrey Taylor.
Shit.
It's me.
No shit. I can see that.
How much you got?
The whole thing. Ninety thousand.
That's good.
Start walking toward the main road
and get in the first car that stops.
When do I see my wife?
Soon enough, Jeff.
Just start walking.
Just throw the money
right up here on the seat.
No. First you tell me where she is.
Wrong, asshole.
First you give me the money...
...unless you want me to shoot your
ass dead right here on the highway.
Turn around.
Do it!
Put your hands behind you.
Step toward the truck.
Get up in the truck. On your knees.
Get in here, goddamn it!
I gave you the money, now let her go.
What the hell..?
Yeah, it's a done deal.
I'm heading in. Yeah, I got you.
You gotta be the dumbest
motherfucker yet.
Think we picked you
out of the clear blue?
Shiny, new car.
Massachusetts plates.
It'll probably be a week
before anybody misses you.
You should have a bumper
sticker that goes with that car:
"Rich Assholes Looking for Trouble."
I wish I had been there to see
your face when your car seized up.
Maybe you'll learn not to leave your
hood open when you go in the store.
What the hell is that?
These ain't nothing but goddamn
singles! You lying son of a...
Shit!
Hey! What are you doing in there?
Where is she?
- Fuck you.
- No, fuck you!
You like that? How about this?
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
The fuck you don't know!
Stop. Stop.
What's that?
You really want me to stop?
Because I'll bet this baby stops
on a fucking dime!
What the hell?
- Where is she?!
- With Billy.
- Where?
- Driving around.
Bullshit!
I'm in pursuit of a black Ford pickup
truck. Contact the state police.
We're headed northbound, Highway 31.
I need backup.
- Where were you taking the money?
- The truck stop.
- Where exactly?
- On the main highway. The Texaco.
Son of a bitch!
Help me. My wife's been kidnapped.
- Drop the gun!
- You got it.
- Get down!
- I know where she is.
Get on the ground! Do it!
I'm down. Listen to me. He's in on it.
They kidnapped my wife.
There's four of them.
- They have her at a Texaco truck stop.
- Shut up!
- You in the pickup, you all right?
- You have to believe me.
- Yes, I'm okay.
- Can you get out?
Yes. Please don't shoot me.
There's a bag with money in there!
Face down, spread eagle and shut up!
Get out, damn it!
Goddamn it, listen to me!
Shut the fuck up!
Hey, shit-for-brains.
Shots fired.
Officer down.
Suspect identified.
This is state police dispatch.
What is your 20?
- Get an ambulance. He's been shot.
- Who is this?
- Sheriff, can you respond?
- They're coming.
Sheriff, hang on.
We're getting you an ambulance.
All units. Officer down.
Repeat, officer down.
I don't know. He was supposed
to be here half an hour ago.
I heard a report about a cop down.
I'm leaving. There's too much heat
around here. Stay off the airwaves.
Get his wife. Meet me at the barn.
I don't care if we have
to drive all night.
- Daddy, you're home!
- Hey, Deke! Miss me?
Deke, get back to bed.
I expected you back next week.
I finished early and now I'm home.
Al and Billy are coming over.
It's 6 a.m.
Can't they come another time?
We got stuff to do.
It'll take a few hours.
Go in and make breakfast.
Hey, Deke!
- Wanna open the barn for your dad?
- Okay.
Hey, Dekey. Thanks.
Hey, I got something for you.
Ready?
Here you go, son. Look at that.
- Cool!
- Cool.
A real Swiss Army knife.
Good boy.
Deke?
Deke, you back there?
If I never see another couple
from Massachusetts, it'll be too soon.
We've got a lot of work to do.
Any word on Earl?
- Not a thing.
- Me neither.
We gotta get this stuff off the truck.
Anything that can trace us back
to that fuck, we get rid of.
Anything, Billy. You got that?
You should have gotten that jerk
at the same time as his wife.
He wouldn't get in the truck.
I suppose you'd just chase him
with a gun. Idiot.
You should have gotten rid of them
like that couple in Ohio.
So we stay out of the area
for a couple months. Big deal.
Al! Come on.
All right, honey. Time to get up.
- Let's go!
- Come on, move it!
Get up!
Dead?
Must have died from
the exhaust, huh? Suicide!
Couldn't be any cleaner than that,
could you?
Get that plastic, we'll bury her
out back before sunup. Let's go.
Jesus! Goddamn!
Scared me half to death!
Let me do her. I'll cut her head off.
- Warren, you in there?
- Shit, it's my wife.
- Cover her. Put her in the freezer.
- Warren?
Be right there, Arleen.
She's a feisty one, isn't she?
That's right, lady.
You just keep it up.
Don't give me any trouble. Goddamn it!
Cut your fucking squirming!
Come on, baby,
it's not as bad as it sounds.
It'll take you 10 minutes to suck all
that air out. You won't even feel it.
Come on, fellas, come on.
Let's go eat!
Hey, Mrs. C.
Are you coming to breakfast?
I've been calling you.
We sure could use
some of them pancakes.
Hey, Billy! Come in the house!
It must have weighed 10 pounds.
It starts reaching out
to the highway patrol cop.
Reaches way out for the...
Give me the key.
- Mister...
- Don't "mister" me, you son of a bitch!
My wife is locked in a hole
in your fucking barn!
Give me the key,
or I'll blow your fucking head off!
- What's going on?
- I don't know. Stay calm.
Your husband's a murderer and
a kidnapper. Give me the fucking key!
Freeze, mister.
You don't wanna do that, kid.
Put the gun down.
Don't listen to him, Deke.
You just keep that gun right on him.
Dad keeps his rifle
loaded all the time...
...in case I need to protect Mommy
when he's away.
- I understand. I won't hurt your mom.
- He's lying, Deke.
Now go on, son.
Squeeze that trigger. Go on.
- Don't listen to him.
- Go on.
- Don't listen to him. He's wrong.
- Do what I say. Squeeze the trigger.
Put it down, Deke.
Nothing's gonna happen.
Do it!
Goddamn!
Don't move!
Nobody move!
Get out here, kid!
Get over by your mom.
It's all right.
Get over there! Get over there!
Shit!
All right.
Stick together
and get out that door.
Move it! Get out of here!
Move it!
Turn around. Turn around!
Open it.
Get down there
and open that freezer up.
- Warren, what is this?
- Just pull the chain, Arleen.
Open it!
You better pray she's alive.
You made it, baby. Come on.
Get away from me!
Come on, honey. Come on up.
Come on, honey.
It's all right.
You son of a bitch, get down there!
All of you! Get down there!
It's okay.
You remember this.
No matter where you go...
You fuck!
It's all right. It's all right.
Now listen to me, Amy.
Honey, listen to me.
There's one more still out there,
you understand?
We need to get out of here fast.
Shit!
- Can you make it to that pickup truck?
- Okay.
Come on.
Okay, come on!
- Help!
- Billy! Billy!
- We gotta find those keys.
- Okay.
I'm Jeffrey Taylor.
This is an emergency.
I need the police. Someone's
trying to kill me and my wife!
I don't know the address.
We're on a farm.
Just start tracing this call.
Got them!
Get away!
Come on. Come on.
Give me the keys!
Come on!
Go!
Do you see him?
- Do you see him?
- No.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
Look out! Look out!
Son of a bitch!
Want some? Come on!
- Watch out!
- Hang on!
Fuck!
Fucker! You're gonna die!
Shit! I'm out!
- Jesus!
- No! No!
Go, Jeff!
- I can't get out!
- We gotta go!
I can't get out! I can't get out!
Help!
Don't move. Don't move.
I'm gonna get you out now.
Come here. Come on, come on.
All right.
Pull! Pull!
That's it! Come on, pull!
Are you all right?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org