Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Eagle, say again.
Repeat, please, Eagle.
Zero One Zero, can you confirm deployment?
Roger that, Eagle. Stand by.
Copy that. We got target confirmed.
Eagle is green for go.
Repeat, Eagle is green for go.
Copy that. Deployment in 15 seconds.
Bombardier, give me a confirm
on target Three Zero Niner.
That's Three Zero Niner, confirm.
Copy, Bombardier. OK.
In three... two... one.
Falling.
My worst fear is falling.
Falling like a bomb.
You see, life for me is about distractions.
I try to keep looking up
and forget about what's down.
But when I dream,
I fall.
Left.
Old soldier
Combat soldier
Pick up your weapon and follow me
Follow me to victory
1-0-1
Screaming Eagles
Pick up your weapon and follow me
Follow me to victory
82nd
Airborne soldier
Pick up yourjumpers and follow me
Follow me to victory
Follow me to victory...
Man, you grabbed me. You grabbed me.
You can't do that, man. Well, it's a foul.
I didn't grab you.
Dude, you grabbed me then.
You can't do that.
Man, I didn't grab you.
Why are you lying?
Man, Elwood. Yo, Elwood, man.
He grabbed me, right? You saw it.
I don't know. Maybe.
- See, man, you can't grab like that.
- Fuck you, man.
- Fucking holding...
- You wanna try it again, motherfucker?
Let's go, baby.
Hey, Video, throw me the goddamn ball.
OK, but I'm quarterback. Can I be?
- Come on. Come on.
- All right. Let's see what they got.
Hey, yo, can I play?
Whoa, Parsons, got something for me there?
- You put it in the battery?
- Yeah, no problem.
Hey, can I play?
I was champion wide receiver at high school.
I can catch that ball, man.
- You're so fucked up, you couldn't catch a bus.
- Don't be such a pussy and let him play.
Come on. Get down. Get down.
On "hutt". Down.
Come on. Come on.
- Gimme some action.
- Hutt.
These were my guys.
Fighting the dull fight.
Soldiers with nothing to kill except time.
They know that war is hell,
but peace...
peace is fucking boring.
Give me back the motherfucking ball.
Er, guys.
Guys.
Guys!
What?
Er, just letting you know.
Parsons is dead.
Parsons McCovey
was a casualty of war.
The only difference was that this was
the Cold War and he was a fucked-up junkie.
There'd be no hero's burial for Parsons.
I regret the death of your son immensely.
There was nobody in the battalion
I would have trusted more with my life.
In him were resplendent
the virtues of honour and loyalty
to his country and God,
that keep our civilisation together.
He fell off the rooftop
while making technical repairs
to the antennae that guard against the enemy.
Technical repairs? Where did that come from?
I tried to think
what McCovey might be doing up there.
OK, go on.
He died, though not in combat,
in the line of duty,
and he had his country uppermost in his mind.
My deepest regrets, Colonel Wallace Berman,
US Army, Commanding.
You kept this one short.
I thought it might be better
not to get lost in detail, sir.
I like the touch about me
trusting him with my life.
It's a new angle, sir.
Here's something, though.
The word "resplendent".
That's not a good word to describe a soldier.
We'd better come up with something else there.
What about "contained"? In him
were contained the virtues of honour and loyalty.
- That's much better.
- Oh, much better, sir.
Don't let the word "resplendent" leave this base.
Yes, sir.
OK. What is this? What have we here?
Just some requisitions, sir.
1,000 gallons of Mop & Glo.
My God. Do we really need that much?
Cleanliness is next to godliness.
Herman the German. How goes it?
How do you do, mein Freund? How are you?
Doing just fine. Just fine.
Shall we do business today?
Sure thing. Guys.
I think you'll be pleased.
That's beautiful.
Look at the sparkle.
That's real cleaning power.
Sehr gut Sheiße, ja?
Sehr gut Sheiße, mein Freund.
US Army's finest. 500 gallons ready to go.
Three things I love about Germany:
My Mercedes-Benz:
No speed limit on the autobahn:
And a black market
for anything I can get my hands on.
Fight The Power
The number, another summer
Sound of the funky drummer
Music hittin' your heart
cos I know you got soul
Brothers and sisters
Listen if you're missing y'all
Swingin' while I'm singin'
Givin' what you're gettin',
knowin' what I know
While the Black bands sweatin'
And the rhythm rhymes rollin'
Got to give us what we want
Gotta give us what we need
Our freedom of speech is freedom or death
We gotta fight the powers that be
Let me hear you say
Fight the power
Fight the power...
Hey, Elwood, what's up?
Outstanding, Hicks. How you doing?
So...?
You don't look so good, Hicks.
- You got anything?
- Depends on what you want.
Er, it's... horse.
Can't help you.
You know, fuck, Elwood.
I outrank you, man, so don't give me any... crap.
I appreciate that, but I can't help you.
Look, man, I don't do retail. I only cook the shit.
Why don't you go see Sergeant Saad?
There's basically
two types of guys in the army -
the motherfuckers and the motherfucked.
Sergeant Saad is the third kind.
He fucks the motherfuckers.
Which is doable
when you're the chief MP by day
and the director of retail heroin sales by night.
Something that makes my life simple.
I just cook high-grade Turkish morphine
into smack and wholesale it straight to him.
Everyone's happy.
So, how much we get?
Well, after we give the Turk back his share,
we got er... nine grams.
Nine grams? Six hours of cooking
and all we get is nine grams?
You wanna tell the Turk
you're not happy, be my guest.
Bullshit. We're the ones doing all the work,
taking all the risks,
and Saad's making all the profit.
Garcia, I just need you to do your job.
Can you watch those thermometers
and keep your mouth eating those hotdogs?
Heroin, cocaine, marijuana,
lysergic acid, diethyl... Whatever the hell it is.
Amphetamines, traces of barbiturates,
estrogen...
Estrogen?
McCovey was on the pill?
How could this be possible?
- Well, he might have taken it by mistake, sir.
- What?
The pill. He might have thought
it was something else.
Fine, but he didn't take heroin,
speed and cocaine by mistake, did he?
It seems unlikely, sir.
This isn't good, Elwood,
drugs on a base like this.
Did you know anything about this?
How could someone get drugs in?
I really don't know, sir.
I always try to keep away
from people like McCovey.
Elwood, we've got to try to clear this matter up,
goddamn it.
I cannot... Scratch that.
I will not have this kind of thing
going on at my base.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
My officer evaluation report goes
in front of General Lancaster in three weeks.
If I don't get that goddamn star, I'm finished.
- Sir, you've got to relax...
- Don't you tell me to relax!
You're an E4. I'm a goddamn full-bird colonel.
You don't talk to me like that.
- You understand me, soldier?
- Yes, sir.
Oh, Jesus, Elwood, I'm...
I didn't mean to take it out on you.
Elwood, I'm... I'm sorry.
It's OK, sir. I understand
the kind of pressure you're under.
This isn't mine.
I don't know anything about it.
And there's no smoking in here.
I need someone to sign here. It says Berman.
You're Berman?
I'm Colonel Berman, all right, but I don't know
anything about any goddamn chair.
- I'm telling you, son, it's not mine.
- It is yours.
- Oh, Liz. Hello, darling.
- Isn't it beautiful? It's for you.
It's for me?
I got it for under 30.
They didn't know what they had.
- 30 thousand?
- I couldn't believe it was so cheap.
- Dollars or Deutschmarks?
- What do you think, Elwood?
Well, can you sit on it, ma'am?
Of course you can't sit on it. It's an antique.
Oh, well, it's very nice.
Darling,
can I borrow Elwood for a few hours?
There's some things I need him to do.
God.
Wait. Almost. Almost.
...under the deal signed exactly a year ago
in Stockholm to build East-West trust,
and reduce the risk of war.
East and West have always feared
that such an enormous exercise
might be used as a cover for a build-up for war.
You didn't make it yet?
Sorry. You angry?
No.
Ray, honey. I need you to do me a favour.
The Colonel's giving a party
and I need you to find out about decorations.
- What's he want a party for?
- He wants to impress the General.
His position's under review
and I thought a party would help.
Will you?
Hm?
Oh, you mean a party party?
Like for everyone's fun.
Oh.
...are procedures
to ensure no cheating in future.
And all sides agree this first onside verification
of conventional forces
is a major step forward
in building new trust and confidence.
Can you switch that off?
Just turn that engine off, come on over here.
- Is there a problem?
- Where are you taking this Hummer?
We have orders from Colonel Berman.
OK. Who are you?
Specialist Ray Elwood.
What's this?
We have orders
to pick up party decorations in Mannheim.
Party decorations?
Yes, First Sergeant.
Colonel's having a party.
Sounds like a pretty dangerous mission.
No disrespect intended,
but may I ask who you are?
Yeah, you can ask.
I'm your new Top. First Sergeant Robert E Lee.
Well, pleased to meet you, Top.
Welcome to the 3-17th.
Thanks, Specialist.
- I didn't know we were getting a new Top.
- Why would you?
I'm Battalion Clerk here.
I usually do paperwork on all the transfers.
OK, thanks, guys. I'm sorry to keep you.
No problem.
Hold it for a second there.
You got the time, son?
Oh, yeah, it's almost ten.
That's a nice watch. Show me that.
Where did you get that?
My father gave it to me.
Your father gave it to you?
He must be quite a guy. What's he do?
He's a barber.
Barber?
Gee, he must cut a lot of hair.
Yeah.
OK, better be going, then.
Don't wanna be late
picking up them party decorations.
Let's go.
Bear Witness
Bravo Two Zero.
Bravo Two Zero, come in.
Bravo Two Zero. Bravo Two Zero, come in.
Shit! Turn that down, man.
Turn down the fucking music, man.
Bravo Two Zero, please respond.
What's going on, Hicks?
Er... Bravo Two Zero here.
Bravo Two Zero, commence tactical
manoeuvre area Two Niner Alpha Romeo.
Take position on phase line
Foxtrot Delta Four Seven.
Fuck.
What the hell's Two Nine Alpha Romeo?
I got a very weird vibe from that guy.
I personally didn't like him.
- He's our new Top. What do you expect?
- What was that shit about the Rolex, man?
He could know about the operation,
he could know something.
Jesus Christ, don't get fucking paranoid, Garcia.
Just be cool.
I'm cool.
- Fuck, man. I can be cool.
- Good. That's why I'm telling you.
Figured out where we're going yet, man?
Er, no. We're going the wrong way.
Shit, er... Hey, Johnnie,
make a... a left.
I told you to make a left across that field.
I did, man. I went left.
Ich Bin Ein Arschloch
What was that bump?
Oh, shit, man.
We just ran over a car, man.
We just squashed a car.
What kind of car?
A Volkswagen. A fucking Beetle.
Oh, no.
We squashed a Beetle.
Look out, man.
Stop.
Stop!
What's going on?
What the hell are you doing here?
- Whoa!
- Stop!
Stop.
- These dudes are freaking me out.
- I don't like 'em, either.
Hey, Johnnie, why don't you just
get us away from these fuckers?
What the fuck is he doing?
Holy shit! What the fuck was that?
What's wrong with these monitors?
They've gone all orange.
Johnnie, I thought I told you
to get us out of here.
That's our fucking unit.
Just up ahead.
Is that you back there, Bravo Two Zero?
Did you complete
your Two Niner Alpha Romeo?
Er... We er... completed that.
OK, good work, guys. Get in formation.
Holy shit!
Oh, Jesus Christ!
These guys are dead.
Garcia, get in that truck and follow me.
What?
- Hey, what's in the trucks?
- I don't know. Let's find out.
- Hey, no way, man.
- Just get in the fucking truck.
All right.
Uh-oh.
Jackpot.
Oh, shit. Holy shit!
Grenade launchers.
MAG guns, stinger missiles.
Jesus Christ, this is worth millions.
3 million maybe.
- Maybe $5 million.
- It's all brand-new.
We gotta take this back.
This stuff gets us nothing but heavy jail time.
- We're not taking this back.
- It's big time. We can retire on this.
I agree 100%/.
This is way out of our league.
They kill you for stuff like this.
This is very serious shit.
- There's no time like now. If we pull this off...
- There's no time like now? Are you crazy?
We're not weapons dealers.
Would you kindly shut up?
Man, you're so negative. I'm trying to think.
Hey.
We're smart, right?
Yeah.
Now, we could do this.
- We could do this.
- Oh, man.
What do we do with this shit?
Well, first we need to store it.
And I know the perfect place.
Hey, this place gives me the creeps.
Yeah, it's supposed to.
- Hey, friend, what's up?
- Hey, Elwood.
What's going on, man?
Nothing much. I got some stuff I need to store.
Can you help me out?
Sure thing, man.
Hey, are we gonna party afterwards?
Does the Pope shit in the woods?
Hey, we can do a lot of things
with the cash we make off this.
You know what I'm saying?
Cos I was thinking about opening up a bar,
a nice, classy place.
Me and you'd be partners.
What do you think?
Sure.
Why not?
Fuck!
This one ready to go?
Yeah, almost. Almost.
Easy.
You be all right?
Yeah.
- You ain't out in 30, I'm coming in.
- Don't worry, I'll be fine.
Turkish music
- Elwood, how are you, my friend?
- Hey, Davood, how are you?
- Are you hungry? You want something to eat?
- Oh, no, I'm fine, thanks. I'd better get up.
Say hi to your sister, all right?
A lot of guns.
Where did you get all this stuff?
Santa Claus.
Santa Claus. That's funny.
He came down the chimney
and put it under the tree, hm?
Yup.
So...
...how about this?
I give you 20 kilos on top of my next shipment,
and you cook that
along with my share of the shipment,
and you make a lot of money.
- 20 kilos?
- Mm.
No. I want cash.
25.
Look, I know somebody else
who's very interested in this merchandise.
OK.
Maybe they'll pay you cash.
35.
29.
I hate to break that 30 mark.
It's a religious thing with me.
I'm afraid you'll have to,
cos 30 kilos is my final offer.
He's sending us 30Ks. One week.
30Ks?
Holy shit! That's, er...
- A lot.
- Well, how do we cook that much?
- It'll take us, like, a year.
- It's gonna be cool.
French Foreign Minister Dumas
yesterday expressed discomfort...
...has welcomed East German reforms
with such open arms.
Politically, Mr Gorbachev
has never been more vulnerable.
This is really impressive.
Hey, guys, careful with my shit.
You're pretty well equipped for a Spec Four.
I got receipts for everything.
I'm sure you do.
Hey, Top, look at this.
Check and see if there's anything inside.
Nothing.
Hm? Mm-hm.
I'll bet this don't come cheap.
This ain't exactly regulation stuff here,
is it, soldier?
I don't really know.
No, I guess not.
Look, I'm gonna come round here tomorrow.
I want this place looking like a regular quarters.
You follow?
Look, I know it ain't exactly regulation,
but the last Top didn't seem to mind.
Well, him and me are a bit different.
Look, Top,
is there a way you and I could talk in private?
These guys kinda make me nervous.
Does it really have to play this way, Top?
How do you suggest we play it?
Well, what is it you want?
I mean, you and me, I think we...
I think we got a lot in common.
Barriers are coming down in Hungary.
So must they fall
throughout all of Eastern Europe.
For example, I see you're an admirer
of Japanese technology.
No problem.
The TV's yours.
What I'm trying to say is,
what's it gonna take
for you and me to make nice?
Are you saying what I think you're saying?
The world has waited...
There's your answer.
Elwood.
Hey, this'll take a second.
- I'll meet you down there.
- All right.
Where are you off to in such a hurry?
Nowhere, really.
Just had a couple of things to do.
You're always off with your buddies.
I never see you any more.
It's just cos I've been really busy.
- Busy?
- Yeah.
- It's the guest list.
- Guest list?
Party. Are you still helping me?
Oh, the par... Yeah. Sure. Definitely.
We found out the Colonel's related
to the Iron Boar.
- The Iron what?
- The Iron Boar, as in male pig.
I had a lawyer trace his family tree,
and he's a distant relative
of a Civil War hero, John Bell Hood.
They called him the Iron Boar.
He'll announce it to General Lancaster
at the party, to help his promotion.
Sergeant Lee's daughter.
That's Top's daughter? You're kidding.
See something you like, Elwood?
Nice dive.
Thanks.
The new Top, what do you think he's up to?
He's a washed-up vet
who wants to throw his weight around.
But right now he's on your case, my man.
Yeah, well.
Hey, check out this girl.
- Why?
- That's Top's daughter.
No shit.
You know what I'm thinking?
You could be thinking almost anything.
- Maybe I should ask her out.
- You're fucking crazy, you know that?
Imagine how much that'll fuck with his head.
It's perfect.
Hey.
- So, have you got a problem with your car?
- Yeah. It won't start.
It might be the battery. Want me to look?
Hey, you're Robyn Lee, right?
Yeah. How d'you know that?
I'm Battalion Clerk here for the First Battalion.
I kinda know everything.
Hm, must be handy.
Hey, you're a good diver.
I saw you in there at the pool,
diving off the high platform. How do you do that?
What do you mean? Are you scared of heights?
Let's just say you wouldn't get me up there.
You should try it.
It's fun.
Fun? Why is it fun?
Falling through air. It's kinda cool.
You're kidding me. You like falling?
Sure. Why not?
Hey, I think I found the culprit.
You wanna give that a try?
- What a guy!
- That's me.
Actually, I'm Ray Elwood.
Everyone calls me Elwood.
- Thanks for fixing my car, Elwood.
- Yeah. No problem.
You wanna go out Friday night?
It's a vineyard I visited last summer,
just a small one in the Napa Valley.
Pinot grapes.
It's for sale.
- You thinking of buying it, sir?
- Well, I wish.
No. But I have a pretty decent collection
back home,
and I've always wondered what it would be like
to make my own wine.
I could just about afford it.
Of course it's unrealistic.
Have you heard about those two missing trucks?
- What trucks, sir?
- During Reforger two trucks went missing.
The drivers were killed in an accident with a tank
at some gas station out near Karlsruhe.
They found the bodies,
but they can't find the trucks.
How odd.
- You wanna hear the best part?
- What's that, sir?
It's Colonel Marshall's infantry,
so he's taking the heat.
Great news, sir.
Elwood, could I tell you a little secret?
Of course, sir.
Have you heard
of the Civil War General John Bell Hood?
The Iron Boar?
You know of him?
- Everybody knows the Iron Boar.
- I didn't know he was so well known.
- Mm.
- It turns out that I am an actual relative.
A relative of the Iron Boar? Awesome.
I want you to keep it under your hat.
I'm gonna surprise the General at the party.
Excuse me.
Private First Class Brian Knoll
reporting for duty, sir.
I'm not an officer, so you can cut the "sir" crap.
- Sorry.
- What do you want?
I just arrived. The orderly sent me down here.
Oh, great. Is that your 201 file?
Yes, sir. Er... yes.
You can sit down if you want.
So, how come they assigned you here?
I put in for it.
My fiancée is here on base,
so we arranged to transfer together.
Ah, how sweet.
Who is she?
Margolis, Carol Ann, Private First Class.
You call her by her last name?
What do you do, salute in bed?
It says here they put you in 5-19.
Yeah.
That's my room.
Didn't... Didn't Sergeant Lee tell you?
We're gonna be roommates.
So while Carol Ann's been here for six months,
I'm stuck in San Antonio,
just pulling whatever strings I could,
kissing the Base Commander's ass
like you would not believe, not literally, but...
Boy, oh, boy. I mean, so check this out.
- So then...
- Jesus Christ, shut the fuck up.
I guess I don't really give a shit.
You're only here cos Sergeant
fucking dickhead Lee's on my case.
Until I get that shit straightened out, I don't
wanna hear about your girlfriend, or anything.
You roger that?
Anderson underwent his rookie season
at Milwaukee as a starting quarterback...
Hiya, Top. How's it going?
- Daddy, this is Ray Elwood.
- Oh, yeah, we already met.
I'm going out. I won't be home till late.
How the hell can you afford this car?
Oh, I got a great deal.
Mercs are a lot cheaper in Germany.
I don't believe it.
What?
Your dad. He's following us.
I don't believe it.
Hey, how's it going?
- Hey, Elwood.
- Looking good.
Hey!
Alle schon da.
Tut mir Leid.
Mit diesen Schuhen können Sie nicht rein.
Blue Monday
What's going on with you and my dad?
What do you mean?
There's something going on.
I'm the natural enemy of guys like your dad,
mostly cos I don't give a shit about the army.
If you don't give a shit, why did you join?
I didn't exactly have much of a say in the matter.
I got caught stealing a car
and the judge gave me a choice -
six months in prison or three years in the army.
- I made the mistake of choosing the army.
- I get it.
My dad has a problem with guys like you.
So you're out with me to piss him off?
No. I, er...
That's it, isn't it?
Yeah, that's...
I'm fucked up. I'm really sorry.
Yeah, that's definitely fucked up.
I'll take you home.
I didn't mean to get you into this.
Are you seriously out with me
just to piss off my dad?
Yeah. Yeah, that's right.
Are you crazy?
He's the First Sergeant of your company.
He's not somebody you wanna piss off.
You realise, he's gonna cut your balls off.
Yeah, probably.
So, what if I stay?
There's a chance you're gonna lose your balls.
Do you think I'm worth it?
Yeah. Sure. Why not?
Fine.
Do you want one of these?
- What is that?
- Ecstacy.
How does it feel
To treat me like you do?
When you've laid your hands upon me
And told me who you are
I thought I was mistaken
I thought I heard your words
Tell me, how do I feel?
Tell me now, how do I feel?
Those who came before me
Lived through their vocations
I've got something I wanna show you.
What is it?
A burn.
How did it happen?
When I was a kid, my dad was drunk
and he dropped a cigarette on my nightgown
and it caught fire.
It was an accident.
It's really ugly, isn't it?
Get up! Get up! Get up!
At the armoury. Full gear. Five minutes!
Five minutes?
Count 'em.
- Elwood, what the hell are we doing?
- Target practice.
Elwood, hand me your rifle.
I want you to pack the M-60.
I'm not qualified to operate it.
There's a time and a place.
You're gonna learn in the heat of battle.
Hand it to him.
The 60's a heavy mother.
So am I.
What's the matter, Elwood?
Your fitness lacking?
You wanna do the confidence course
a few times to get you back into shape?
No, thanks, Top. I'll be fine.
I direct your attention to that spot over there
that has been marked with an X.
We have here the prototype
of a new Russian tank.
We are here to test the vulnerability of said tank
to sustain fire from an infantry platoon.
Squad...
Lock and load one magazine.
Take up a good firing position.
You will fire on my command.
Sustain fire until the order
to cease fire's been given.
Ready?
Fire!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org