Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Well, that depends upon the part
and who the director is...
and whether or not
I've had enough to drink.
That's not a very
comforting answer.
I didn't like the question.
[Buzzer Buzzes]
- Bernard?
- No, it's not Bernard. It's me.
- Lan.
- Christ, I've been waitin'out here all night.
- What are you talking about?
- Who's Bernard?
Who is Bernard leaving
your apartment in the morning?
- Lan, have you- have you been spying on me?
- Who is he?
Is he the director or the producer
of your new French film?
Lan, I can't believe you've
been waiting outside my flat.
Angela, I thought we were
making plans together.
- Well, what kind of plans?
- I thought we were going to California together.
Lan, I have a life here.
I can't just pack up and go.
You'll have your business and
I'll end up waiting on tables.
You won't have to wait on tables.
I'll be there lookin' out for you.
L- I don't understand
what you want from me.
What do you want from me? I'm-I'm-I'm
moody and I'm-I'm self-obsessed.
And I'm ambitious.
- And beyond your cool exterior,
I sense you're bluffing.
- No, I'm not.
I'm gonna take you
to California, Angela. I am.
And if you don't think I will,
then-then call my bluff. I am.
[Chattering]
Have you thought about how we're
gonna take care of Martin Burns?
No. Have you?
Come here.
I want it to be like
a hit-and-run accident.
It's tricky, 'cause someone could see the
license plate and we couldn't be sure he'd die.
- Well, I know I'm not stickin' a knife in him.
- Why not?
'Cause I can't. Can you?
I don't know, Terry. I don't know what
I'm capable of till I'm facing the moment.
- You could kill him with a knife?
- Or a hammer.
I was thinkin' like
a muggin' with a hammer.
Jesus, I'm startin' to think I don't know you,
lan. Look, if we do this, it-it has to be-
What? Nice and clean
and sanitized...
so we can fool ourselves
about what we're doing?
- I'm just sayin' there's a line I can't cross.
- A gun is the quickest way.
I'm just sayin' let's do it
as humanely as possible, all right?
- We could strangle him with a wire.
- [Sighs]
We could get him on the ground,
the two of us, and strangle him with a wire.
This isn't us, lan.
It's not the Blaine brothers.
The Blaine brothers are
a couple of losers, Terry.
- [Train Passing]
- There's no great pride to be had
in what we've achieved.
Well, look, if we strangle him,
he'd put up a fight, right?
Now, I think we could take him,
but it could get messy.
Well, we'll have to make a decision one way
or the other. We've only got three weeks.
[Sighs] I can't talk about it.
Let's just enjoy our drinks.
Carol's had an accident.
Except I don't think it was an accident.
I think she was drunk
when she took the car...
and she didn't much care if
she made it back to town or not.
Well, suppose if I told you I don't care.
In fact, I'm glad it happened.
I only wish it'd been fatal.
It might be yet.
Everything's a bit touch and go.
It's funny how life
boils down to this.
Life is nothing
if not totally ironic.
Usually brilliant.
Well done. Well done, as always.
- There she is. Hello, darlin'.
- Oh, hi.
- How are you? You were fantastic again.
- I'm all right.
- This is Kate and Terry.
- Oh, lovely to meet you.
They've been dying to meet you.
I've been going on and on and on about you.
- Brother. Nice to meet you.
- Yeah, I loved it.
Thank you so much.
It was really nice of you to come.
- Brilliant.
- Thank you. It means a lot.
What are you up to this evening?
Do you wanna- Do you wanna join us?
We're going to a party.
My friend finished filming today.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, that'd be great.
- It's okay with you?
Yeah, that'd be great. Bit of a squeeze,
though, Terry. Bit of a crush.
- I'll manage.
- Hold your stomach in.
- ##[Techno]
- [Chattering]
[Chattering]
I can see why you're
so crazy about Angela.
She's very, very different
from the women you've known.
I've never been with
anyone like her before.
And we've known
a few juicy ones.
Do you remember
Fenella Griffith?
Remember her? You passed her off to me.
How could I forget?
You make it sound like it wasn't
the biggest favor in the world.
I never said she wasn't
wonderfully depraved.
[Chuckles] Angela's better than that, though.
She's innocent and also depraved.
She's working class, but classy.
And that smile, Terry, that smile.
Lovely. Oh, she's lovely.
[Terry] Look at the two of them. Dancin'
and laughin'like there's no tomorrow.
"Ain't life grand," Terry? Do you know
what that's from? "Ain't life grand?"
- One day you reach a point
and there is no tomorrow, lan.
- Oh, Terry.
All right, look, we just
have to take care of business.
Then it'll be done
and we can move on.
- I figured out how to do it.
- Yeah?
Come here.
- Remember when we were kids?
Bobby North from down the road?
- I remember he was a bad kid.
Yeah. Yeah, well, me and Bobby
made a gun once. He showed me how.
- What, you made one?
- Yeah, we made a gun out of wood, right?
And-And-And a little piece of metal.
It fired one bullet.
- Do you ever hear of people
talkin' about a zip gun?
- Yeah, but was it reliable?
It's the real thing, lan.
You can't trace it back, all right?
Cause when you're finished, you take the
wood, which is most of it, and you burn it.
Then you take the metal pieces and
you dump 'em down different sewers.
- Yeah, but one shot, Terry.
- What?
You'll have to make
two of them- one each.
That way if anything happens,
or goes wrong, we've got a backup.
Right. Well, I think I can get
me hands on a couple of bullets.
Yeah. I don't think there's any question.
Two loaded guns.
We can make this come off quick and clean.
What are you in such deep conversation about?
Are you plotting an assassination?
- Come on, I want to dance. It's our song.
- Yeah? Oh, yeah. All right.
[Giggles]
On stage.
Who was that guy
you were talking to?
What? Tim?
He's, um, a writer.
He just sold one of his screenplays
to a Hollywood studio.
- Well, he couldn't take his eyes off you.
- Is that bad?
Well, I'm sure it wasn't
thrilling for his wife.
That wasn't his wife, that was his date.
Are you angry with me?
I know what's in his mind.
Lan, I don't affect everyone
the way that I affect you.
If I did, my career would have
taken off a long time ago.
- Look, Angela, you are always flirting.
- Oh, lan, don't be angry with me.
I was really looking forward
to taking you to bed tonight.
Sorry to interrupt.
There's Evan Macy over there. I love him.
I'd give anything for his autograph, but
I don't want to seem obnoxious or nothing.
Well, l-I know him. We did a TV film together.
I could introduce you if you like.
- No, really?
- Yeah, of course.
Oh, yeah.
[Giggles]
So just imagine it, right?
I'm there with aces up.
And he bets, bets big.
All right. I see this
little tick in his cheek.
L-I called him
for L30,000 and I won.
[Man] I've been playing poker
most of my life.
And I can tell you it's a fact...
there's more skill
to poker than chess.
Martin Burns.
I'm a friend ofJohn Fowler.
- John-
- The producer.
We were at university together.
In those days, I kept myself
in fine style playing poker.
You obviously play
high stakes, Mr., uh-
Sometimes.
I met my ex-wife
at a poker game years ago.
When she left me, she said I neglected her
because I preferred playing.
It wasn't true.
But her lawyers used it as a strategy.
My dad taught me poker.
He was a poor man, ran a restaurant
down in the south coast.
Taught me the ins and outs
of the game, lucky too.
I could never have kept myself
on my expensive habits on his salary.
Terry, Kate's looking for you.
Lan, Martin Burns.
My brother, lan.
We've just discovered
we're both poker players.
There's a wonderful game in town.
I'd invite you both to play...
but I have to leave
right after the weekend.
- This weekend?
- Yeah. Seems I get to London
less and less these days.
I thought I'd be here the month, but, uh,
seems my presence is required in California.
Well, that's a great pity
if you had your heart set on staying.
Ah, well, duty calls. And I will have time
to dine with my old mum before I go.
She's 91. At that age,
you can go at any moment.
Great old girl.
Let's hope I have her genes.
- [Chuckling]
- To life.
Good luck with the poker.
- I'm stunned.
- You turned white as a ghost.
How long have you been talking to him?
- A couple of minutes, l-I lost my breath.
- What about?
Nothing. Uh, poker, life.
What are the chances of that? The last thing
we wanted to do was meet him, and then-
- What are the odds?
- You always said how unpredictable life is.
How long will it take you
to get those guns made?
- I can't do this, lan.
- Look, Terry, you've been drinking.
You lose your confidence
when you're drunk.
Listen. I can't keep begging you to do this
with me. He's leaving in a couple of days.
- Are you in or out?
- I never said I wouldn't do it, right?
Well, then, pull yourself together.
Lan.
I had such a wonderful time.
Angela's lovely, ain't she?
She's not at all snobby.
She said she'd take me shopping.
I love the way she dresses.
I thought it might be way
out of my range, but she said no.
- What are you thinking?
- Nothing.
Who was that man
you was talking to at the bar?
- Is that Mr. Burns?
- How do you know Mr. Burns?
I was introduced.
He's sweet, isn't he?
Didn't he know
your Uncle Howard?
Is that what you was
talking to him about?
You told him
Howard was our uncle?
It just seemed to come up, 'cause he's on
the board of one of Howard's foundations.
That's what he said. Actually,
he was looking for you just before we left.
Well, why did you
have to mention it, Kate?
What are you getting so upset for?
We spoke for two minutes if that.
Although I did get the impression
he's got mixed feelings about your uncle.
Yeah, he seemed a little sarcastic.
I could be wrong.
Did-Did he, uh, imply
bad things about Howard?
Yeah, I got that impression.
Actually, he was really surprised
to hear that you were his nephew.
Christ.
Kate, my head's splitting.
- You drank too much. Take some aspirin.
- I need my codeine.
- No, Terry, you can't mix with that stuff.
- Christ, where'd I put it?
It's in the kitchen in the cupboard.
Kate, what's it doing
in the cupboard in the-
I leave it in a certain place for a certain reason.
I leave it in the medicine cabinet.
Don't move things around, please.
Jesus.
Just pull it back...
- and let it go.
- Right.
All right?
[Gunshot]
[Dog Barking, Distant]
This is his flat.
Ground floor.
It's right in the front.
If we could get in there, we could
surprise him when he comes home.
All right.
Right. I've got some tools
at the garage that can get us in.
I think it's our best shot, Terry.
- Let's do it tonight.
- Yeah? Are you up to it?
- I can't stand the waiting around.
- No, you're right.
Look, he always eats out.
So we just need to get in there.
And then we'll wait for him, and we'll
do him when he gets back from dinner.
I hope I have the nerve
when the moment comes, lan.
Don't let me down, Terry.
Look, it's simple.
I'm gonna shoot him. And then you shoot him
again in the head, just to make certain.
Or else you shoot him
and I'll finish him off.
Should have got a taxi, lan. Had to give
your name and address and everything.
No, no, no, no. We need a car standing by
in case something goes wrong.
What could go wrong?
What are you saying?
I'm not saying something will go wrong,
but if something did go wrong...
- we need to have a car.
- [Engine Starts]
Who's taking a taxi
if something goes wrong?
Here he is. Look.
All right, let's go.
- Come on, Terry.
- Be quiet.
- We have to be careful of this window.
- Right.
Don't touch anything.
What do we do now?
We just wait.
- Do you want some?
- No. Put it away, Terry.
- [Phone Ringing]
- What's that?
Just leave it.
Don't answer it.
[Answering Machine] Hello, this is Martin
Burns. I'm out. Leave a message after the tone.
[Beeps]
[Woman]
Hello, love. It's Mum.
Oh, sorry to miss you, but I've had to
change tomorrow's dinner to 7:00.
Looking forward to seeing you.
Bye for now.
[Beeps]
Terry, what are you thinking?
What if there's a God, lan?
I mean, what if...
all those nights we used to lay awake,
you know, in the dark...
and curse the fate
of every human soul...
what if we was too angry?
No. No.
Don't turn your back on what
you know in your heart to be true...
just 'cause we're facing
a d- a difficult task.
Yeah, but we're
crossing the line here.
There's no going back from this.
I tell you, I've said it before.
I don't wanna go back, Brother,
and neither do you.
- We need to look to the future.
- A taxi. It's him.
Right. All right. Now remember,
we wait till he gets in...
let him shut the door,
we let him get in the flat, right?
And then we come out quick,
surprise him, and then we just do it.
- Right.
- All right? We just do it.
Right.
Let's go.
[Chattering]
The beef was nice, wasn't it?
Can I have a drink?
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Look at that garden.
- Do you like it?
- It's gorgeous.
It's nice.
- Do you look after it?
- No, the gardener does.
- Christ.
- Terry, we're gonna have to do her too.
- Not me. I'm not doing her.
- Well, then what we gonna do?
We've mucked it up.
I'm not doing the woman.
Okay, okay. You're right.
But what are we gonna do?
I can't kill her just because
she's here, lan. It's wrong.
All right. Look, I don't disagree.
Oh, Terry, are we screwed.
San Francisco, L.A.
Anyone traveling with you?
- No, I'm traveling on me own.
- Need a passenger?
- Fancy a trip?
- I'd love to.
- Do you have what you came in for?
- Yes.
I'll be sleeping over at yours tonight.
I just need a change of clothes, and, uh-
uh, my laptop.
And we can go.
Okay.
[Door Opens, Closes]
We'll have to do it tomorrow night at
his mother's. I can find out where she lives.
I was gonna do it, lan. You saw me.
But then the woman arrived.
I would've done it, though.
You saw me, lan. I was ready. Oh, Christ.
I told you I was only borrowing
this money from the safe.
I can't believe
you thought I was taking it.
I told you it was just a loan.
And, Dad, there's a nice,
big bonus in here for you.
Don't tell me that
won't come in handy.
Where'd you get
money like that, lan?
You know, I'm involved
in certain business ventures.
What sort of
business ventures?
I told you. The hotels.
Wait, I thought you said that
your hotel deals had been delayed.
Well, this is an advance.
Will you just take it?
- Where's it coming from?
- Will you just take it?
Look, soon this place will be back on its feet
and you won't be so dependent on me.
- Where are you going?
- Well, I'm not gonna work here forever.
- Well, who's gonna run things?
- Oh, Dad, give me a break.
Look.
You know that- that I love you.
I mean, I've stuck it out here all these years,
even though it's not for me...
because of loyalty to you.
And I know that some of those business
plans in the past didn't pan out...
but this one is different, Dad.
This one is different.
And I'm just mad about the girl.
It's funny how life
has a life of its own.
- Oh, Dad, Dad-
- No, you're right, lan.
Nobody wants to be selfish,
but everybody is.
No, you're not.
I have been.
And it's because-
I think it's because I've been scared.
You're a good boy. I've always
thought you had potential.
You're both good boys,
you and your brother.
I've always wanted
to make sure...
that I've loved you
and Terry absolutely equally.
Well, you have,
you-you absolutely have.
Dad, don't worry about a thing.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Everything's gonna be fine. I promise.
All right.
I thought I was pregnant.
It's a false alarm.
- Pregnant?
- Yeah.
- I was late. I'm never late, am I?
- But you're not. That's a relief.
- Why?
- [Mutters]
- I think it would be great.
We always talked about it.
- Yeah, some day.
We can swing it. Now your
uncle's helped you out financially.
And you said that he might help you out
with that loan for that sport shop idea.
I think you'd make such a good dad.
And just think, if we had boys, you know, you
could teach them to play football or something.
Right.
- You're not hungry?
- Not really, love.
- It's very nice.
- It's your favorite.
I know. Can I get
a whiskey, please?
- A whiskey?
- Yeah.
- I don't know if we got any left.
- It's in my drawer.
[Mutters]
- You're late.
- Sorry, sorry.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
You've been drinking.
I'm fine. I said I'm fine.
Just leave it at that, all right?
Let's just do it, Brother,
before I change my mind.
- Have you got the guns?
- Here. Right here. And the bullets.
All right, all right.
Don't load them now.
- Are you too drunk to handle this, Terry?
- I said I'm fine.
- All right, let's just go.
- Right.
We'll go up to him when
he's on his own, we shoot him...
and then I'll put a second one
in him just to make certain.
I know what to do, lan. Right?
You don't always have to run things.
- Can you handle this, the state you're in?
- Worry about yourself.
- All right? I'll take care of him. Just-
- [Engine Starts]
- Have you got the address?
- Yeah, I've got it. Let's get this over with.
Don't worry about the restaurant.
I can help you if you need me.
I dreamed about the boys last night.
Again?
When they were younger.
There he is.
Let's take him now.
Wait. You don't wanna let him
see his mum for the last time?
- What?
- You make me sick.
Let him see the old lady.
You're drunk, Terry. It's a disgrace
turning up on a job like this drunk.
Look, we've probably missed
our last opportunity now.
We'll get him
when he comes out.
Christ. You don't care about anyone
in this world except yourself.
You're not a big shot, lan.
You're a small stakes player.
I don't care how many hotels you wind up
running or how hot that girl is.
Why don't you shut up?
I bet you had a big handful of those pills
that guy keeps you supplied with as well.
I'm fine.
We'll kill him
when he comes out.
- Mr. Burns.
- Hey?
Oh, that's right. I remember you.
We met at that, uh, party.
- Yeah. We-We thought it was you.
- I understand you're Howard Swann's nephews.
- That's right.
- What are you doing around here?
You live around here?
- No. Lan?
- Do it now.
- Let's just do it now.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Terry, do it! Do it now!
- [Gunshot]
[Gunshot]
What are you thinking?
That then was then.
And now is now.
And we've done it and it's over.
And it's always now.
It went much smoother
than I thought, lan.
And not a soul around.
We're lucky he chose that path.
Yeah, no one saw us.
And we did the right thing.
We didn't run back to the car.
We just walked calmly back.
Yeah.
There's a great weight off my back.
You're right, lan.
It's now.
It's always now.
You better burn his wallet.
- Are you okay?
- Go back to sleep.
[Gunshot]
- What do you think of this one?
- Oh, I love it.
I thought you would. So, are there
any new developments on California?
Yeah, I think we can leave in about four
or six weeks. We signed the papers today.
Great. Did you see in the papers...
that guy that you were speaking to
at the wrap party was murdered?
- Who?
- Martin- Martin Burns, was it?
Oh, really?
How bizarre.
Yeah, well, no one
saw or heard anything.
- Didn't he have some association
with your uncle at one point?
- I think he did, yeah.
- What do you think of this one?
- As if you have to ask.
[Chuckles]
You know, I'll never forget you boys,
what you did for me.
I owe you my life.
And the joy of repaying you
gives me such pleasure.
Now, Terry, you-
Look, you spoke about, uh...
you know, the notion of opening a-
a sports shop if you had the backing?
No, it's okay.
No, look. Look, cheer up.
The worst is behind you. I'm here
to tell you that the- the future is rosy.
Terry, Uncle Howard's right.
Stop walking around
with that face on.
This is your chance to get away
from that cheap idiot at the garage...
and make your own life.
- [lan] Where are they? Is that them?
- [Angela] Yes.
- Angela, I'm so nervous.
- [Chuckling] You're fine. They'll love you.
- Hello.
- Hello. Oh, it's nice to see you, sir. I'm lan.
Nice to meet you.
Heard a lot about you.
- Hello. You have a nice trip?
- Very good, thank you.
- Let me take your bag.
- We've been really looking forward to this.
- Yeah, it'll be great.
- [Mother] Your hair.
- So how's your play doing, love?
- It's going well. It's still selling out at weekends.
- Oh, well, that's to see you take your clothes off.
- Mom!
- So what do you do, lan?
- Uh, hotels.
- Hotels? Which ones?
- Yeah, I got a couple in, uh, California.
Oh, yes, Angela said you were
planning an extended stay out there.
- Well, very extended, I hope.
- California.
I'm starving. Where are we eating?
- I'm taking you all to Claridge's.
- Oh, is it nice?
- Lovely.
- No, it's on us, though.
No, no, no.
This treat is on me. Yeah.
Oh, thank you.
Very nice of you.
Oh, they're really lovely,
your parents. Lovely.
- Oh, I can't get California out of my mind.
- I know.
I've spoken to Uncle Howard
and everything is right on track.
Thank you.
- She's beautiful, isn't she?
- Very, very.
A bit high maintenance, though.
- You up to it?
- I certainly hope so.
She could've had
the pick of any man, that girl.
Well, I realize I'm very lucky.
I do realize that.
I always dreaded the thought that she might
wind up with some starving actor in the theater.
Not that I've anything
against the theater, mind you...
but... a man who knows his way
around the world of business, well-
There was a time when I could've
invested in some ventures...
but I didn't have
the stomach for the risk.
So I spent my life behind the wheel
of a car driving other men.
She says you've got a future.
[Gasps]
Oh, God.
- What is it?
- I can't take it.
- Take it easy. It's all right.
- I need another pill.
No, Terry. You can't take so many
of those, not with all that alcohol.
Kate, leave me alone.
I've gotta get rid of this feeling of panic.
- Why should you be feeling panicked?
- I don't know.
I just need the pill. Christ,
I can't even get a decent night's sleep.
All right.
My car didn't have that dent
when I brought it in.
- It had to have been there. Nobody's touched it.
- No, you put a dent in my car.
- How the hell would I dent it?
- I don't know.
- What's going on?
- There's a dent, look, in my car.
Someone's driven my car.
- Will you shut up? What are you accusing me of?
- Someone has to have driven it.
Look where you point your finger.
It could get broken.
- Calm down. Calm down.
- Get your hands off me.
Sorry, Mr. Finn.
Just give us a minute.
I'll sort out
your bodywork for you.
I need a word with you.
What the hell's the matter with you?
Look, I'm not at all pleased with the way
things are going around here lately. All right?
Hey! There's another one here.
Yeah, I miss you too.
- Nobu. Yeah, I made
reservations for after the show.
- [Doorbell Buzzes]
Who's that?
Look, I'll see you later. All right? Bye.
- Hey. Are you all right?
- I need to speak to you.
Well, I wish you'd called first. I'm expecting
some guys over for a conference call.
I'm having bad thoughts.
What kind of bad thoughts?
We did a terrible thing, lan.
- Oh, Jesus, can you just get past it?
- I'm trying.
- I should never have let you talk me into it.
- I didn't.
Terry, you needed his help.
Loan sharks were gonna break your legs...
and maybe even Kate's as well.
But Martin Burns...
we stepped on him
like he was an insect.
Look, Terry,
I can't discuss this now.
I've got two guys and a transatlantic
conference call coming up.
I can't go on like this.
Let's talk about it later.
Why aren't you at the garage?
- I got let go.
- What does that mean?
[Mutters] The boss said,
uh, l-I should take some time off.
He thinks I've been under a lot of strain
lately. Thanks for denting theJaguar.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I forgot to tell you.
Look. You've gotta relax. All right?
Lay off the booze and the pills.
No wonder you're
getting yourself in trouble.
- I can't get through the day without drinking.
- [Doorbell Buzzes]
Look, you've got to go home.
All right? Rest up.
I'll call you later,
we'll get together, all right?
You've gotta ease up.
You'll give yourself a bloody heart attack.
Then I'll die. So I'll die.
Don't talk like that.
What's the matter with you?
- Guys, come in, please.
- Lovely.
Look, I'll call you later.
I'm gonna get you past this, okay?
All right.
See, this is more like it,
Terry, isn't it?
Getting out of the house.
Can't sit around there too much.
Too much thinking.
Kate said you're not even
talking about poker anymore.
Where's our old Terry?
- I mean, you're a gambler. This is you.
- Yeah.
I'm not suggesting you
go mad or anything, but-
I'm not the same Terry, lan.
- I can't be anymore.
- No, you just have to focus.
Look, l-I been thinking
that you getting the sack...
- is maybe the best thing
that ever happened to you.
- What?
Yeah. Now is the perfect time to start
thinking about setting up the sport shop.
I mean, Uncle Howard said he would
start you off. You'd be your own boss.
- No more kowtowing to superiors.
And you love sports.
- I do.
Maybe you're right, lan.
Maybe what I need is just a big change.
Yeah, you need to focus on something
substantial. You can't just do nothing.
- Yeah.
- Hey?
I think I'll do it, lan.
- Yeah, it's just exactly what you need, Terry.
- [Bell Rings]
Get off the booze and the pills
and set up your own place.
Right, and not just sporting goods.
Exercise equipment.
- That's where the money is today.
- Yeah?
Yeah. Helping people set up
their own private gyms and stuff.
I like the way
you're thinking, Terry.
- 'Cause you're thinking forwards.
You're not lookin' back.
- That's right.
- You've got a really good future, Terry.
- Yeah?
You do. Listen, I'm not saying
that I haven't had moments...
where I've thought about what we've done,
and it's freaked me out.
- Go on!
- We were raised to know right from wrong.
- Did you get that one?
Look at this.
I got a winner.
It's the beginning
of a new streak, Terry.
I can feel it, lan.
Could-Could you get this model
with the same interior in a left-hand drive...
- say, in California, for instance?
- For California. Yeah, certainly.
And would there be
a long waiting list or-
I would think about
three or four months.
- Oh, can I?
- Please do.
[Chattering]
Hey, great scene.
You really nailed it.
- You were great. You were great tonight.
- Do you think so?
The bedroom scenes
were so sexy as always.
Well, I was doing it with him,
but I was thinking of you for motivation.
Don't forget. Tomorrow is Lord Eisley's party.
He's invited the whole cast.
Yeah. I'm gonna keep
my eye on you like a hawk.
You know, his son's a notorious playboy, and
I think he's asked everyone just to get you there.
- Uh, what's that?
- Nothing.
- [Chuckles] Show me.
- I got you these. Remember?
You liked them in the shop.
- Oh, my God. They must have cost you a fortune.
- [Cell Phone Ringing]
- Hello?
- I need to speak to you, lan.
Kate, Kate, Kate, calm down.
What's the matter?
It's Terry. I really need to speak to you.
What, now?
Yeah, now. Is it possible?
Well, look,
I'll see what I can do.
I'll call you back,
all right?
- Is everything all right?
- Angela, I have to go to my brother's for a while.
- There's a little family problem.
- It's nothing serious, I hope.
No. That was Kate.
You remember? You met her.
It's just something's come up.
I'll see you back at yours in a while.
Well, hurry. I want to show you
my gratitude for the earrings.
All right. See you later, all right?
I'm worried about Terry, lan.
What's the matter?
It's his mental health.
No, I know he was worried
about losing his job...
but we were just at the racetrack,
and he talked about starting the sport shop.
No, he's not
interested in that.
And now he's angry all the time.
- He's talking to himself, for God's sake.
- No, we decided.
He was gonna speak to Uncle Howard
about bankrolling it. He was very excited.
His mind's not right, lan.
You know, what he says one minute
doesn't mean anything the next.
Right. Well, I'm- I'm taken aback.
It's all the pills he's taking,
and the drinking.
He thinks
he's killed someone.
- What?
- Yeah.
You know, I knew this girl once,
she had, like, mental problems.
She was convinced that
she had run someone over. She hadn't.
You know, but she was obsessed
with it for the rest of her life.
Does he, uh-
Is he going around...
talking- talking
about this, uh, murder?
He's gotten worse and worse.
He has these terrible nightmares.
He's uncommunicative,
face of doom all the time, bouts of crying.
When we were at the dog track,
he seemed to have come out of it.
When he come home,
he was straight back in it.
You know, it's just- it's obsession
that he's done this horrible thing.
And he- he won't
let me get a doctor.
No, no, don't do that.
Don't-Don't get a doctor.
If you get a doctor,
then it can- I'll deal with this.
- Well, how?
- Well, obviously, it's a bit
more serious than I thought...
but... if you get a doctor,
it could spiral out of control.
- I really think he should see a doctor.
- Don't get a doctor, Kate. Don't.
Because I know Terry, and it will
only make things worse. All right?
Just- I'm gonna be
in the countryside tomorrow, all right?
And then when I come back, I'll spend
some time with Terry, and it'll be-
You'll see. It'll be all right.
Well, where you gonna be
if I need you though?
I'll let you know my whereabouts,
then you can call me.
I'll come-
I'll come straight back.
- So you're a fan of the Greek tragedies too?
- Love them. Crazy about them.
It's just rare that I could ever
get the chance to act in one.
God, I know. It's difficult, isn't it?
Which is your favorite, lan?
Oh, I'm not really
that-that familiar.
Oh, well. Mine's always been Medea,
Euripides.
Yeah, me too. I think Clytemnestra's
probably the best character...
- of all classical plays.
- Yeah.
I have to say, the best productions
of Greek myths I've ever seen-
better than anything you'll find
on the stage-was done in dance...
- by the Martha Graham troupe, you know them?
- Really?
Yeah. I mean, all the terror was there,
all the Aristotelian pity and fear.
- It's so much more visceral
in dance, don't you think?
- Right.
- Mr. Blaine? Your brother's here.
- Yeah?
- What?
- He'd like to see you.
Oh. Uh...
could you give me a moment?
- Yeah, sure. Bring him in.
- It must be pretty bad if he's
driven all the way out here.
No, l- Uh- It's just a little
family problem. I won't be long.
- Oh, I'm sure it's nothing.
- I'm sure.
- Your brother's there, Mr. Blaine.
- Thanks.
Terry, what are you doing here?
How did you know where I was?
Kate had the address.
- I need to tell you something.
- Well, just keep your voice down.
I don't want anyone overhearing.
Why didn't you just give me a phone?
- I want to turn myself in, lan.
- What?
- We broke God's law.
- God?
Terry, what God?
What God, you idiot?
I shouldn't have let you
talk me into it.
- I didn't talk you into it. Stop deluding yourself.
- I want this off my neck.
Look, you can't do this,
Terry, all right?
You can't do it. You'd be throwing your whole
life away, and mine and Uncle Howard's.
I won't implicate
you and Howard.
- You won't-
- This is my personal decision.
- You won't be able to keep us out of it.
- I will.
No, you're upset.
You're unstable.
Your lies will be all transparent.
- I've thought about suicide, lan.
- But why?
Stop asking the same
questions over and over.
Go and commit suicide,
and leave Howard and me out of it.
I just want the slate wiped clean.
Look. You're depressed.
You're just suffering
from a little depression, that's all.
- Kate wants me to see a doctor.
- No, no. Look, I can help you. If you'll just let me.
I just want to tell someone. Go in
and serve my punishment. Have it off me.
Just give me a minute. Give me a minute
to get my thoughts in order, will you?
I wish you could come with me.
But if you won't, I understand.
Just give me a minute.
- I feel less panic since I made this decision.
- Hi.
You okay?
Are you gonna join us?
Terry and I are just discussing a little problem.
Everything will be all right.
Just had to talk
to lan about something.
- You sure?
- Yes.
You go on, I'll only be a minute.
Okay.
- She's very beautiful.
She'd make a great wife for you.
- Look, Terry.
Terry, listen to me.
I want to help you. I do.
But this is not
the time or the place.
- I'm sorry for barging in.
- No, no, it's all right. It's all right.
Look, I want to hear what you've got to say.
We're family. You're my brother.
Yeah, we can talk, but you're
not gonna change my mind.
Maybe not. Maybe not. Maybe you'll even
change mine. But just promise me one thing.
We've gotta have a discussion
about this before you plunge ahead.
- Promise?
- Promise. Can I come in and get a drink?
No, that's not a good idea.
- You go. I'll give you a call tonight.
- Right.
Call me tonight.
I just don't see any alternative.
What are we saying?
Well, I don't know what we're saying.
We're-We're saying we want to survive.
But he's family.
Terry. He's my brother.
Well, l-I know that.
But he has to be stopped before he-
this whole thing unravels.
Yeah, I can't-
I can't let that happen.
No.
No, l-
It's killing again.
How am I gonna do that?
It's deja vu,
but a thousand times worse.
Speed is of the essence.
Terry could be doing something awful
while we sit here and curse our fate.
He was right about one thing.
It was like crossing a line.
There was no way back.
It has to be made
to look like an accident.
Yeah. Yeah,
an accident or a suicide.
Well, he just broods.
You know, he sits there
talking to himself.
He imagines that you and him
have got some dark secret.
You know, that you've
harmed someone or something.
Lan, I think
he's gonna hurt himself.
Let me be alone
with him, Kate.
Yeah.
Terry.
- Terry.
- I had a dream about Martin Burns.
Terry, listen to me.
I dreamed again...
about Martin Burns.
You need a couple of days
away from all this.
Get some fresh air,
some sea air...
just the two of us.
We'll go out on the boat
again tomorrow.
- We never go sailing anymore, lan.
- That's what I'm saying.
We'll take some sandwiches
and some beers...
and we'll just talk,
brother to brother.
I'd like that.
I wish you could see
my point of view.
It'll be great.
Just the two of us.
I think Angela said she was
taking Kate shopping tomorrow.
- She said she was gonna
help her out with her style.
- Yeah.
And we'll just relax, yeah?
Get some sun.
Maybe we can have a swim.
You'll feel so much better
when you've had some sea air.
Yeah, but we'll never
be our old selves again, lan, right?
I mean, there's no going back.
Go and tell Kate that
we're going out sailing tomorrow.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Come on.
Kate, I've got
something to tell you.
We're going sailing tomorrow.
Yeah, just the two of us.
Lan's gonna take me out on the boat.
So, did Terry tell you the good news?
Yeah, it's a wonderful idea.
'Cause you two never really got the chance
to spend much time on your boat, did you?
- And you were so excited when you first bought it.
- Yeah.
I told lan about Angela taking you
shopping tomorrow as well.
Oh, yeah. She's so nice.
Mike Eisley from the garden party
asked if we were serious.
- And then he invited me
to Morocco for the weekend.
- And what did you say?
Well, I told him that I loved you.
For the first time in my life,
those words actually had meaning.
I love you.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, yeah.
- You seem a bit distracted.
- No, I'm just thinking about what you're saying.
And I'm tired, you know.
Well, you have been
working really hard recently.
I think taking your boat
out with your brother...
will do you just
as much good as him.
- Is he all right?
- He's depressed.
He drinks too much
and he's getting sullen, and-
Kate's worried that
he might hurt himself.
Well, maybe he-
Well, he should go to a doctor then.
No, he resists. He resists.
I didn't tell Kate this,
but he's talked of suicide.
Oh, my God.
- I'm so sorry. That's awful.
- I know.
Best thing we ever did,
getting this boat, Terry, isn't it?
Eh?
Kate's right. We don't get out on it
as often as we should.
It's sad how things
turned out, isn't it?
- Don't start, Terry.
- No, I mean it, lan.
We made the wrong decision.
The way I see it,
we didn't have much choice.
You always have choice, lan.
I see that now.
I mean, l- I didn't at first.
I thought... like you,
that we had no choice, but-
All right, let's say that you're right-
which I'm not saying-
but let's say for
the sake of argument...
- that we did make the wrong choice.
- For the sake of argument?
You really fool yourself,
lan, don't you?
His testimony was gonna put Uncle Howard
in prison for the rest of his life.
Well, maybe Uncle Howard
deserves to go to jail.
Oh, what a thing to say.
Forget it.
Christ, you think we've committed
some kind of unnatural act, but we haven't.
The whole of human life
is about violence.
It's a cruel world, Terry.
You're just shaken up
because you've come-
you've come face-to-face
with your own human nature.
L-I mean,
I didn't have to do it.
Well, why did you then?
I just kept going, like- like when
I gamble over my head, you know?
I just put the bet down
like when I'm in a dream.
You weren't dreaming
when you shot him.
All right. Look, listen.
We made a mistake, right? But it's over.
All right? We made the wrong choice.
I'm giving you that...
but being punished
by it won't undo it.
Martin Burns is dead.
He's dead.
I called the police last night.
You did what?
I called them and I told them I had
information on the murder of Martin Burns.
They said,
"Who is it?"
I wanted to tell them...
who I was, but I didn't.
Hung up.
I'm gonna call them
as soon as I get back, lan.
Why would you do that?
What's the matter with you?
It's suicide, Terry.
Don't you even care that you're gonna take
Uncle Howard and me with you?
It's the order of things,
lan. It's off kilter. Can't you see it?
I have to straighten it out.
All right. I don't wanna
talk about this anymore.
We came out here just to relax, didn't we?
Just to sail and unwind, eh?
Yeah.
- I'm just gonna get us some more beers, all right?
- All right.
- Why couldn't you just let it go?
Why couldn't you let it go?
- Lan, what's wrong?
- You've ruined everything, Terry.
Terry, you've ruined it!
You've ruined everything!
- Lan, stop!
- We could've had everything!
Lan. Lan.
Lan.
Lan!
Oh, God.
God.
What we think happened,
but we don't know for sure...
one killed the other,
either on purpose or by accident...
and then took his own life,
drowned himself.
Awful.
The place reeks of booze and pills.
I don't know.
Every day, it's something else.
Oh, I like that.
- What do you think?
- Yeah.
- I would look good in that.
- Yeah, Terry would love that.
- Would he?
- Yeah, men love that sort of shape.
I wore something similar
when lan first saw me.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org