Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
(ROARING)
(SNARLING)
(GROWLING)
(ROARS)
WOMAN OVER MICROPHONE:
Flight 85 now boarding
at Gate 12 C.
Flight 85,
final boarding call. 12 C.
MAN: Over to the right.
Hello, it's
a beautiful day.
Would you care to
make a contribution
to The Lighthouse?
Excuse me, sir,
it's a beautiful day.
Would...
No, thanks.
MAN: Hello,
it's a lovely day.
Would you care to
make a contribution
to The Lighthouse?
I'm Paul.
I'm Irena.
Yes, I know.
Welcome home.
Thank you.
How was
your flight?
Oh, I hate
flying.
It scares me
to death.
It scares me,
too.
You look
really nice.
Thank you.
Welcome
to New Orleans.
Well, I wanted
to get here
as fast as I could.
WOMAN OVER MICROPHONE:
Mr. Al Curtis, please pick up
the white courtesy phone.
We can get
a taxi down there.
Did you
wait long?
No, no, just
a few minutes.
(EXCLAIMING)
You're here at last.
I'm so glad.
Oh, let me
look at you.
Oh, your hair
is so pretty.
(CHUCKLES)
Is that how
they're doing
the hair now?
Female, this is
my sister Irena.
I can see that.
I'd know those
Gallier eyes anywhere.
Oh, Paul,
she's a lovely,
lovely little thing.
Your brother
is driving me crazy
waiting for you.
Do I get
the credit
for that?
Female
keeps me
out of trouble.
And that's
a full time job, honey.
You better believe it.
(LAUGHING)
Female. Female,
like female.
F-E-M-A-L-E.
See I was orphaned,
too. You, you like
this house?
They didn't know
what name to put on
the birth certificate,
so they put
"Child, female".
But the woman
that raised me,
God rest her soul,
she didn't read
English too good,
so she pronounced
it "Female".
So here I am.
Female. Female.
PAUL: Fate wrenched
us apart as children.
Thy mercy
restores us
here today.
For this mending,
thank thee,
O Lord.
Amen.
Mmm!
Watch out.
This is hot!
I forgot
to call
the Robinsons.
I'm sorry.
Why do you
have to call
now?
They care
about me.
Sit down,
sit down,
sit down.
You can call
after dinner.
This is Female's
special gumbo.
Special gumbo
tonight from
yesterday's chicken.
That's right.
(PAUL CHUCKLING)
I just didn't want
them to worry
about me.
They've been
really nice.
You'd like them.
Janice works
at the nursery
school.
At least
part-time.
She has
three children.
And Arnold is
from the CPA,
you know?
He's
extremely
mellow.
The only time
he loses his temper
is about April 15th.
Did they ever
tell you how
our parents died?
IRENA: Yes.
What did they
tell you about me?
Not much.
I mean, I knew
I had a brother,
but I was only four.
I used to fantasize about you
when I was in the orphanage.
Fantasize?
Well, you know,
about you coming
to rescue me and things.
Daydreams.
Yes, I had
the same dreams.
I've got
a surprise
for you.
Do you remember
when we used to
practice together?
Practice?
For what?
For the circus.
I said it was
a surprise.
Now, no peeking, huh?
No peeking!
Ta-da.
IRENA: God!
(CHUCKLES)
Well, the skeletons
are out of the closet
now, huh?
When Grandfather
started the circus,
he only had one wagon.
It was a beautiful
two-tiered one.
There's a picture
of it somewhere.
Oh, there
they are. See?
Yeah.
The apes were kept
on top and the cat
underneath.
The chimp used to
tease the cat
by throwing
its garbage down
through the bars.
Oh, they were
so young.
Mother looks
so happy.
I envy you.
I wish I'd known her.
"Some little mice
Sat in the barn to spin
"Pussy came by
And popped her head in
"'What are you doing,
my little men? '
"'Weaving coats for... '
"'Weaving coats
for gentlemen"'
Very good.
"'Shall I come in
And cut your threads off? '
"'Oh, no,
kind sir. "'Oh, no,
kind sir.
"'We will snap
our heads off."'
(LAUGHING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(PURRING)
What took you
so long?
He's been waiting
45 minutes.
Fuck off! I had
to get a babysitter.
Room three.
Hurry up.
Here, that's good.
I'll take that.
"Babysitter."
You're always late.
Sorry I'm late.
Hi, I'm Ruthie.
But you can call me
anything you want,
if the price is right.
(CHUCKLING)
RUTHIE: A joke.
It doesn't cost
anything extra to laugh.
Oh, I get it.
The strong silent type, huh?
You know
the rules around here?
I guess not. Okay.
A massage alone is $25,
and for $25,
that's all you get.
Tipping is allowed
and appreciated.
You know, if you wanna
negotiate for something extra.
Now we take Master Charge,
Visa, American Express,
but not for tips.
Okay, that's not really true.
You can put tips
on Visa if you want.
Ew!
(GROWLING)
My God!
(SCREAMING)
Somebody help me!
(AMBULANCE SIREN BLARING)
Dr. Yates,
New Orleans Zoo.
Bill Searle called,
said something about
a stray cat?
What took
you so long?
Go on inside.
It's in here?
Right there.
BILL: Oliver,
you aren't gonna
believe this.
What it is, see,
it's a goddamn black
leopard is what it is.
We don't know
where it came from,
'cause we don't know.
I guess it mauled
a hooker last night.
She's all right.
We've got it
trapped in a room
upstairs here.
Look at this.
Candid Camera.
(CHUCKLING)
Let's hear it
for voyeurism.
Strictly security.
Sure.
Where'd he go?
Back under
the bed.
Must've scared
the shit out
of the john
who was here
last night.
Guy split,
stark naked.
In this neighborhood,
who'd notice?
How'd it get
in there, anyway?
I don't know.
Fire escape?
There's no
fire escape.
And the window's
got bars on 'em.
Back door?
Locked.
He must've come
in the front.
I think I would
have noticed.
Wait.
Look there.
Holy shit!
He's enormous.
125, 130 pounds.
OLIVER: More like 150.
He's big, all right.
Real big.
All right,
let's go with
the ketamine,
straight,
2,000 milligrams.
Let's knock him down
quick and get him
in the squeeze cage.
Yeah. Okay.
Can you get to
that window from
the outside?
Sure.
All right,
let's go.
(GROWLING)
Bill, if we could
borrow a couple
of walkie-talkies,
I could assist
from the monitor.
Can I borrow it?
Thanks. Thanks.
OLIVER: You got
a short memory, man.
I shot the coyote in
Baton Rouge, remember?
2,000 milligrams?
Yeah.
You got one ready
in case I miss?
Uh-huh.
Full two
CO2 cartridge?
You got room
for this?
I'll make room.
I'll hold
the ladder.
OLIVER: Hold the ladder.
Be careless.
You too.
(CAT GROWLING)
ALICE: He already
knows you're there.
I hear him. He doesn't
sound overjoyed.
You're scaring him.
What are you doing?
OLIVER: Cleaning the window.
What?
Cleaning the...
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Jesus Christ,
he's going through
the goddamn window.
(ROARING)
ALICE: Jesus.
Paul?
(GROWLING)
How is he?
He's okay.
Come on.
Good morning.
Morning. Where's Paul?
They needed him
at the mission,
bright and early.
(SIGHING)
He was going to
show me the sights.
Get yourself
a guidebook.
They sell them
all over town.
Go to the French Quarter.
You'll have a good time.
And don't worry
about him.
Now, sit down.
Would you like
some coffee?
I want to see if
you like it. Chicory.
Then I'll steam you some milk.
You want
some breakfast?
No, thank you.
That's all right.
I'll fix you
some breakfast,
don't worry.
Yes, can I help you?
I'm looking
for Paul Gallier.
I don't believe
he's in today.
Oh. I'm his sister.
Oh?
Well, I can take you
to his office
if you'd like
to wait.
No, thank you.
Thank you.
(SINGING)
What's that
over there?
That's the zoo.
Oh, wait,
I wanna go
there.
What for?
Nothing but a dump.
You wanna go
to a zoo?
Why don't you go
to the Bronx?
Why don't you
let me take you
to the French Quarter?
I've seen
the French Quarter.
Now, please stop!
It's your money.
Keep the change.
WOMAN: All right,
children, stay in line.
(ELEPHANT TRUMPETING)
(GROWLING)
MAN: He's not so
dangerous in a cage.
OLIVER: When we get
finished testing,
we're gonna have to free up
some of these other exhibits
so that we can give this
new leopard some extra space.
You're gonna have
to disarm him.
What does
that involve?
Not much.
Cut its claws,
root canals.
File and crown
its fangs.
There's a dentist
in town that does
the work.
Radenauer.
Tom Radenauer?
Yeah, he does
people, too.
JUDSON: Yeah, I know,
he's my dentist.
Shit, Oliver, we don't
have the funds for this.
And you know how it's
been coming down lately.
Aren't there any
other alternatives?
OLIVER: Not really.
Because of its history
it's no good for breeding.
We could try trading
it to another zoo.
I'm afraid
with its erratic behavior,
they just wouldn't take it.
BILL: You could euthanize it.
JUDSON: What's that? Kill it?
Yep.
Not an acceptable
solution.
How much would that cost?
I said,
it's not
acceptable!
Can we at least
discuss it?
I'll put up with
being under-budgeted
and under-staffed,
and the fact that
these exhibits
were built in
1901, and they're
falling apart,
but I will not
put up with
that crap!
Fine!
Calm down.
I only asked!
ALICE: Looks like
we have a gourmet
leopard on our hands.
He threw up in the cage.
Joe found pizza in
the vomit...
JOE: Yeah. Sure did.
Pepperoni.
Leopards
eat pizza?
Well, they're
scavengers.
He probably raided
a garbage can
before he went
to the massage
parlor.
Doesn't look like
he went there
out of hunger.
Maybe he
was horny.
OLIVER: Always a possibility.
Anything else?
Nothing.
No worms,
no distemper,
no encephalitis.
Whoever owns
him takes good
care of him.
Sure does.
He's a superb cat.
"A superb cat"?
He's a menace.
MAN ON TAPE: "Not dreaming,
noble lady, whence it is
"That I am taken
with strange semblances"
"Seeing thy face,
which is so fair to see
(BIRD CAWING)
"For else, compassion
would not suffer me
"To grieve my heart
with such..."
"...with such harsh
scoff as these
"With such harsh..."
"Or else compassion
would not suffer me
"To grieve my heart
with such harsh scoffs..."
"And bears his mastership
so mightily
"That all my troubled senses
he thrusts out
"Sorely tormenting some,
and slaying some till none but
he is left and has free range
"To gaze on thee
This makes my face..."
(STOPS TAPE)
(GROWLING)
(LEOPARD SNARLING)
Hey!
Hey,
wait a minute!
All right, you wanna
come on down from there?
Come on,
I'm not gonna
hurt you.
Watch out.
How'd you
get up there?
(SIGHING)
Here, let me help.
What the hell
were you doing
back there?
Sketching.
Sketching?
That animal's
not even supposed
to be out.
Why'd you
run away
like that?
You scared me.
But the leopard
doesn't?
You can sense how
an animal feels.
Oh, you can?
Yeah, sometimes.
We're all connected.
Who are you?
Irena Gallier.
I'm the curator here.
The zoo's been closed
for an hour and a half.
(GROWLING)
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I feel dizzy.
Jesus, you're
burning up.
Come on,
I'll get you
something.
Oh, no.
Come on,
come on, come on.
I don't bite.
(GROWLING)
Here, take these.
Oh, I don't believe
in medicine.
It's aspirin.
No, thank you.
I'm exhausted,
that's all.
I flew in
the day before
yesterday,
went sightseeing,
forgot to eat,
and when you
started chasing me,
I just got all excited.
Yeah, I do sometimes
have that effect on women.
Oh, really?
No, that was a joke.
I don't wanna
keep this on anymore.
It's wetting up my hair.
Thank you.
It'll reduce the temperature.
No, it's down already. Feel.
Just because it feels cooler
to the touch doesn't mean
the temperature's gone.
I'll go get a thermometer.
Oh, please.
I've always had
a weird metabolism.
Really.
I just need some
food and I'm all right.
How about you? You wanna
have some dinner with me?
Yeah, sure, great.
If you feel up to it.
I feel hungry.
I know a reasonably
good steak place.
Oh, I don't
eat meat.
MAN: I thought you were
supposed to be on a diet!
WOMAN: It was
not that fattening!
MAN: Oh, sure.
You don't look
like a curator.
I look exactly
(CHUCKLES)
No, you don't.
Well, you haven't
met many curators.
I guess not.
What does
a curator do?
Different things.
Buys animals,
sells animals,
veterinary work,
research, arranges
the exhibits.
Maybe gets
an expedition,
if he lucks out
on a donation
or a grant.
Expedition?
Like into the jungle?
Mostly it's
the bureaucratic
jungle.
We purchase
most of our exhibits
from animal dealers.
How long have you
worked at the zoo?
Ten years.
No, eleven years now.
But I've been
into zoology ever
since I was a kid.
I prefer animals
to people.
What about you?
I'm looking for a job.
My brother Paul's
supposed to help me.
If he ever gets back.
He's been gone for
two days now.
How do you eat these?
You take this
little wedge of lemon
like this
and squirt it
on your oyster.
Then hit it with some
of this horseradish
and red sauce...
Just a touch. Pick it up and
let that sucker slide down
your throat.
What kind of job
you looking for?
Well, commercial art,
mainly.
I've taken art lessons.
And then you chase it
down real quick
with a swig of beer.
Or Coca-Cola.
(SIGHING)
Look. How would you
like to work at the zoo?
The zoo...
That would be fascinating,
but no,
I'm not really qualified.
You're qualified
to work in
the gift shop.
They need
help in there.
If you're interested,
I could pull a few strings.
You could?
Sure.
I'll talk to the curator.
I'll be right back.
Right in
the pool, girls.
Jean, let's go,
in the pool.
Come on, girls, in the pool,
let's go! Up, up, come on,
bath time.
ALICE: Good morning.
Morning.
Alice.
I put the
new tape
in here.
You want
to give it
a listen?
Yeah.
(MAN SPEAKING ON TAPE)
It sounds terrific.
JOE: Old Tom's about
due for a worming.
Want me to handle that?
Yeah.
Hey, Tom.
Why are you so
dressed up today?
I have a meeting.
Where?
In my office.
(MONKEYS GIBBERING)
Hi, Angel.
The cheetah's been
a bit of a problem.
He's been acting
really weird.
I don't know
quite what to do.
Diet?
Yeah.
Light day,
fast day,
five days
regular.
Vary it but
keep it balanced.
Some muscle meat,
viscera.
Viscera?
A few bones
now and then,
plus the vitamin
supplements'll
straighten him out.
JOE: Okay, I'll try that.
How's the black leopard?
Fine.
A little
extra protein
never hurts...
Joe.
Oh, little
rats-a-roni.
Yeah.
(CHUCKLING)
Ratatouille.
Rat tartar?
Like I said,
the pay ain't great.
No, I really like it.
I like to be around
the animals.
Oh, yeah.
Ali the alligator.
Bambi and Oscar
the orangutans.
Every now and then
you gotta feed
these guys a pillow.
What?
Nothing.
Just plain horsemeat.
Pardon me, you don't
have to kill it.
Hey, Mr. Fabulous.
Here...
Eat, damn it!
MAN: I feel so helpless!
SARAH: I know, I know.
Let it out. Let it all out.
(SOBBING)
MAN: You don't know
what it was like, Sarah.
Coming into the house
and finding her lying
on the floor,
through all that smoke.
I'm sorry.
I told myself I was going to
stop crying on your shoulder
after that trial thing.
I'm sorry.
JOE: B.J.!
If I'd stopped on the way home
from work for a beer, she...
SARAH: But you didn't.
And that's what you've got to
remember. You didn't stop...
Pancho. What happened?
Did they operate? Here.
MAN: And my Rosemary lying
there with my baby
inside of her.
(CHILDREN CLAMORING)
BOY 1: Come on,
Brett, let's go.
No.
BOY 2: We'll be late. We gotta
go. Hurry up. What's wrong
with that thing?
BOY 1: Come on.
BOY 2: Come on. Let's go.
ALICE: Take it easy.
I thought you guys
are supposed to be
courteous.
You have to hurt it,
or it won't respond.
(REGISTER RINGING)
What you got?
Empire Strikes Back gum.
25.
Quarter.
Thank you.
Hi. I'm Alice.
Irena.
You're Oliver's
friend.
Yeah.
Well, we just met
a few days ago,
actually.
You're not
from New Orleans.
No.
Strange,
isn't it?
People are
crazy here.
I think it's
the humidity.
Have you seen
much of the city?
No. I'd like to,
though.
Why don't we have
a drink after work?
I can help you work
out a little itinerary.
Okay. Fine.
Okay. Ciao.
Just hit it real hard.
There you go.
(CHUCKLING)
MAN: That color really looks
good on you. Where'd you get
that outfit?
Excuse me.
MAN: Where the hell
did she come from?
Jesus. Don't
encourage these
assholes, please.
How do you
not encourage them?
I tell 'em
I'm gay.
What if they
believe you?
I should be
so lucky.
If you wanna get laid,
you can do a lot better
than that, believe me.
I was just
being friendly.
I was not trying
to get laid.
Occasionally
they're compatible.
I wouldn't know.
How come?
I just never met anybody
I liked enough to have
sex with.
Never?
Not so far,
no.
Really? You're still a virgin?
Don't make it
sound so perverse.
Oh, no,
not at all.
Just incomprehensible, maybe.
Especially these days.
Oh, you must have come
close once or twice.
Yeah, once or twice.
How close?
Come on.
The first parents
I lived with...
The mother was okay,
but the father was...
Oh, a lech?
Yeah. He used to grab me
when I went by him.
Overhand or underhand?
I know the type.
And there was
this one boy...
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
What?
ALICE: Friend of yours?
No, I never
saw her before.
What did she say?
"Mi hermana."
My sister.
She's
probably drunk.
So what happened?
What?
I don't remember...
The boy
you liked.
Oh, right. We petted
and stuff like that.
He wanted to go
all the way and
so did I, but...
But I don't know,
I got scared.
He looked so...
What?
Huge.
God. What's
his name? Quick.
Oh, I guess
I'm a romantic.
When it's right,
it'll happen.
It'll be magical.
I'm not
knocking it.
Here's to the magic.
(GROWLING)
(ROARING)
It's the same with
every bureaucracy.
You think you have things
worked out with these people
and then they
won't meet you halfway.
I don't know what to tell you.
(SINGING)
What's new pussycat?
Pussycat, pussycat, I love you
Yes, I do
You and your pussycat smell
(CHUCKLING)
Come on, fella,
I gotta clean out the bunkers.
(DOOR OPENING)
Clean it out, it'll be real
nice for you. Move it.
You're supposed to
be in the back there.
Back through
the door, guy.
He won't cooperate.
He's afraid.
(HISSING)
JOE: Come on, come on.
JOE: Hey, hey, move, move.
(GASPING)
Come on, come on.
Careful, careful,
stay back.
Come on, back up.
Would you back up, please?
Go to the back.
Hey, Oliver!
Yeah.
Bring the prod.
He's going ape.
(ROARING)
Simmer down!
Okay, that's fine.
Hey, come on!
(JOE YELLING)
Oliver?
(SCREAMING)
ALICE: Oh, no! Oh, God!
OLIVER: Call the paramedics!
Call them. Call them.
(GROANING)
(ROARING)
(SIGHING)
You shouldn't
be doing this.
(ALICE SIGHING)
ALICE: He's only 26 years old.
(HISSING)
OLIVER: We better
tell the police.
The leopard's gone.
(DOOR CLOSING)
Female?
(THUDDING)
Paul.
Paul,
where were you?
In prison.
Prison?
What for?
I was praying
for the condemned.
Oh, Paul, Paul,
forgive me.
I saw somebody
killed today.
Somebody I knew.
I didn't think
you were ready,
but you are.
I knew it when
I saw you with him.
Who?
Oliver?
You want
to fuck him,
don't you?
You dream
about fucking him!
Your whole
body burns.
It burns all along
your nerves, and your
mouth, your breasts.
You go wet
between your legs.
Stop it!
Every time it happens,
you tell yourself that
it's love,
but it isn't.
It's blood. Death.
You can't escape the nightmare
without me. And I can't escape
without you.
I've waited
a long time
for you.
Paul, don't
you touch me.
But I'm the only one
who can touch you,
and you're the only
one who can touch me.
Don't you see?
We're safe together
because we're the same.
I am not like you.
Oh, yes,
you are.
You've always
known it.
Do you remember, when you were
a child, the animals used to
call your name?
And you knew
in the dark when
the others were dreaming,
and you could
never get to sleep.
You're insane.
No. No, I'm not.
I'm not in love.
What will you do? Will you
leap through his hoop?
Take his head
in your mouth
like an egg?
I need you.
Who are you?
I need you!
Don't touch.
You're not
my brother! No!
(GASPING)
Stop.
What's wrong?
Can I help you?
COP: Are you sure
everything's all right?
Honest, really! I thought
someone was chasing me.
It must have been just
somebody out walking.
I'm sorry I got
so excited.
I just got scared.
All right.
I'd be glad
to write it up.
No! No, no,
thank you.
Is everything all right, Bill?
Yeah.
Turned out
to be nothing.
(DOG BARKING)
Good. Quiet! Shut up, idiot.
COP: What's wrong?
I don't know.
Something strange.
He senses something.
We better look into it.
Let me call it in.
(DOG BARKING)
I was sleeping.
I didn't hear anything!
Are you sure?
What about the basement?
I suppose
you don't know anything
about the basement, either?
Basement.
Oh, I don't
go there.
What do we hear from
the guys at the lab?
They're
on their way.
Miss Perrin,
Doctor Yates?
You're with the zoo, right?
OLIVER: Yeah.
Come with me.
I wanna show you something.
At least we know
now where the leopard
came from.
Follow me.
ALICE: What's that smell?
OLIVER: I don't know.
DETECTIVE: Yeah, the dog
picked up the scent
real strong.
You should have seen him.
He went crazy.
Take a look.
There's pieces
of three or four
bodies in there.
Probably more
buried around.
Oh, God.
I expect Gallier
killed them first,
possibly as part of
some ritual,
then fed them
to the leopard.
We found some others,
too, over the years.
Mostly prostitutes, female
runaways, half-eaten,
genitals torn out.
But why?
Listen, who knows?
Gallier's been in and out
of psycho wards since
he was 12.
He's a religious
fanatic.
Where could he
possibly have found
a cat like this?
And how could
he have handled
it by himself?
He was raised
around them,
at least until
he was 10.
His folks were
carnival people,
lion trainers,
till they blew
their brains out
one night.
And what about Irena,
is she involved?
OLIVER: What are
you suggesting?
Irena hadn't even
met her brother
until a week ago.
We have no reason
to suspect her.
In fact, it looked
as if he'd planned
to kill her, too.
And if I was her,
I'd find me another
place to live.
I'll take care
of that.
Don't touch me.
Watch it, lady.
Okay, take her in.
It's an old MG.
I bought it
two years ago.
I've been fixing it
ever since.
The room's upstairs,
if you're tired and
wanna lie down.
I've been using this room
as a darkroom, so it might
be a little cluttered.
I'm gonna grab
a few hours' sleep.
I thought we might
be going out
to the country,
first thing
in the morning.
If you need anything,
I'll be right
across the way.
He couldn't be
my brother.
My brother
wouldn't have
done those things.
No, I'm sure
he wouldn't.
Well, good night.
Look at
that boat.
that crane.
(CHUCKLING)
Look at
that boat.
This is it.
Bayou Plantation.
One of these days
I'm gonna buy you
a plantation.
Let's get the boat.
It's that or we have
to swim.
Open the back?
Pardon me?
Open this here?
Hey, Oliver.
OLIVER: Hey, Yeatman.
(GIGGLING)
I opened her up
and aired her out.
Yeatman, you old
choupique fish, you.
How the hell are you?
And you,
redneck?
Hey, Yeatman,
this is Irena.
Irena, this is
Yeatman Brewer.
Oh, she's
mighty pretty.
Here, let me
help you with
your bags.
Sure.
Yeatman helped me
build this place.
He also helped me
tear it apart a few nights.
You draw this in real slow
and I think there's a crab
on here, okay?
Then I draw him across...
Don't lift the net up!
Don't lift the net up.
Okay, now lift
the net up.
(SHRIEKING)
You got them.
You got two of them!
All right.
Not bad.
My God, look,
they're crazy.
Now, you take them
and you dump them
in that basket.
Not on me.
This one doesn't
want to come off.
Look at this.
WOMAN: Billie, me and Ted
are going back to the hotel
and take a nap
before dinner, okay?
BILLIE: Okay, honey. Don't
do anything I wouldn't do.
Is there anything you
wouldn't do, Billie?
BILLIE: Look, how dreary.
PAUL: Hold it right there.
I'm sorry.
Were you talking to me?
May I take your picture?
I'd love it.
Say cheese.
Cheese.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
Listen.
What?
Can't you
hear it?
Yeah, that's
alligators.
They're gonna
eat us.
Alligators.
Yeah.
There's only one way
to keep them away.
You know what that is?
What?
You have to
make love.
They hate
the sound.
(CHUCKLING)
I can't.
Look, don't be
upset, baby.
It happens.
I like you,
but...
Well, that's
no problem, hon,
I like you, too.
You don't understand.
Oh, sure,
I do.
You're just
a little nervous,
that's all.
I know how to
take care of men
like you.
You just need
some time.
Every time I pray
it won't happen again.
Well,
you got very,
very beautiful hair.
Thank you.
Oh, relax,
it's no big deal.
Momma will
make it better.
Oh, that's
better.
That's much,
much better.
(BIRD CAWING)
(HISSING)
(DOOR OPENING)
Don't look at me!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(BUSY SIGNAL)
OLIVER: Detective?
Looks like we got
us another murder.
The leopard?
Yeah.
The girl came back
late last night
with a man, early 30s,
brown hair.
Our people
put the actual time of
the death at around 3:00.
Who was she?
Who knows?
A tourist, maybe.
Now get this.
He picked her up
at a cemetery.
Can we look?
Hope you haven't
had breakfast.
Come on.
OLIVER: Where you going?
Hey? Where you going?
I'm leaving.
I have to.
What? Wait!
Where you going?
Somewhere!
I can't stay here
any more.
What? What?
Why? Why? Why?
Why?
Just say why.
Can't you see?
What?
(SOBBING)
Can't you see
I'm going crazy,
just like him?
Who? Paul? Paul?
He has nothing
to do with you.
I don't even think
he's your brother.
Listen, Irena,
I'm 34 years old.
I spent most of my life
looking for somebody I even
wanted to be in love with.
Now that I found you,
I'm not gonna let you go.
I love you.
Oh, yeah?
Would you love me
just as much
if we could
never sleep together?
Don't be stupid.
Yes.
I love you
and I wanna
take care of you
and that's all
that's important.
I'm afraid.
Of what?
I'm afraid
for you.
Irena, you don't
understand.
I'm afraid
so much.
I'll always
love you.
I loved you before
you were born.
IRENA: I don't know.
OLIVER: Come on in.
The bag.
BILL: The leopard's probably
out of the parish by now,
unless he's dead.
OLIVER: I'll believe it
when I see it.
I don't think
you're gonna see it.
What do you mean?
Well, I've been talking
to the Sheriff's department.
They're gonna call it off.
We can't afford
the manpower anymore
or the time.
It's been over
a week now.
What are you,
out of your mind?
Look, they set their traps,
they did everything they
could. What do you want?
Is that what you're gonna
say the next time it kills
somebody?
Hey, don't give me
that shit, Oliver.
You were the one who wouldn't
shoot the bastard when we had
him in a cage.
Look, man, I'm sorry, okay?
I don't know why I did that.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, well, fuck you!
He's right.
No, he's not.
Yeah, well,
how the hell
would you know?
What?
(SIGHING)
Nothing.
How's Irena
feeling?
Fine.
You wanna
talk about it?
Talk about what?
Jesus,
what do you think?
Irena's gonna be
all right.
I don't even...
Irena's not the one
I'm worried about.
Her type will
always be all right.
Her type?
What the hell
does that mean?
Look,
I'm not blind,
Oliver.
I've seen you
obsessed before.
Not like this.
I even thought
I'd seen you
in love before.
I guess that
was just my vanity.
Let's talk about
something else,
all right?
Okay. All right.
I know what I'm doing.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
(KNOCKING)
Save me.
Only you can
stop this killing.
You've got to
make love with me
as brother and sister.
I've searched for you
for so long,
from one foster home
to another.
We can live together as mates,
just as our parents did.
You do know
that they were brother
and sister, don't you?
Oh, no.
Oh, yes.
No.
Make love with me
and save both of us.
(PANTING)
No.
I'm not like you.
Well, that's
the lie that will kill
your lover.
At least let me
spare you that horror.
Come on, come on.
Come and lie next to me.
No!
Oliver doesn't love you.
He loves the panther.
He wants you because
he fears you.
Let Alice have him.
She thinks
his fear is courage
and he thinks
his fear is love.
Well, they were
made for each other.
So were we.
Take my hand.
No.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Then you leave me
with no choice.
Oh, Paul.
I'll come
with you, okay?
We'll go together,
you and I, okay?
And it'll be all right.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(PANTING)
ALICE: I'm gonna
make some coffee.
OLIVER: Sure.
I'll get some towels.
Irena, I'm back.
Alice is here.
We're gonna
fix a pot of coffee.
Why don't you join us?
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Irena.
(THUDDING)
(PURRING)
Oliver!
(SNARLING)
(GROWLING)
Alice!
Oliver?
Alice, get me a gun.
Get me a shotgun!
(GUN FIRING)
(WAILING)
(BONES CRACKING)
(GASPING)
(CHOKING)
(COUGHING)
Paul,
he is dead?
Then you have
no one.
Who am I?
What am I...
Shh.
Don't ask what
you already know.
No, Female,
I don't know.
What...
I don't know
where to go.
Live as he did.
Hidden. In chains.
Never love.
Pretend the world
is what men think
it is.
Wait!
Don't leave me like this.
I don't know where to go.
It doesn't matter
where you go, does it?
(DOOR CLOSING)
Where to?
How far will that take me?
Where do you
wanna go?
North.
Richmond.
PAUL: Long ago, our ancestors
sacrificed their children
to the leopards.
The souls of the children grew
inside the leopards until the
leopards became human.
We were gods then.
We are an incestuous race.
We can only make love with our
own, otherwise we transform.
And before we can become
human again, we must kill.
Welcome home.
(CAT GROWLING)
Irena.
Mother.
PAUL: You must return.
(BARKING)
(GASPING)
Hi, Sandy.
Hi, Alice.
You're late.
We're closing.
Oh, just a quick dip.
Please, I really need
it tonight.
Okay, five minutes.
Yes. Thanks.
(FOOTSTEPS)
(GROWLING)
Hey, has it been
five minutes yet?
Hey, Sandy?
(GROWLING)
(ALICE PANTING)
(ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
What's wrong, Alice?
Why are you following me?
Following you?
Don't deny it!
Hey, what's going on?
I know you wanna kill me.
Kill you?
I was looking for Oliver.
I tried the hospital but
he was already out.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm sorry if I frightened you.
Hey, what's going on?
Nothing.
(GASPING)
Oh, God.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Hello?
ALICE: Oliver.
Yeah.
Are you all right?
I called before.
Yeah.
Oliver,
Irena followed me tonight.
This is gonna sound crazy,
but I think she wanted
to hurt me.
Oliver?
OLIVER: Yeah?
Should I come over?
No. Stay where you are.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Oliver?
Are you scared?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FLY BUZZING)
(FLY STOPS BUZZING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ROARING)
(EXCLAIMING)
Please, Irena.
(SIGHING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SNARLING)
Oliver? They spotted
a leopard near the bridge.
Okay.
(SIGHING)
Let's go.
Hold it. Hold it.
Oliver Yates.
I'm from the zoo.
ALICE: From the
New Orleans Zoo.
Just a minute. Okay.
Go on through.
Detective Brandt
called us from the zoo.
COP: No. You can't
go out there.
(DOG BARKING)
(GROWLING)
MAN OVER RADIO: Car 317
patrol. He seems to be
settling down.
Stand by.
COP: Did he get away?
Oliver,
where you going?
Oliver?
(BIRD CALLING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(OLIVER GASPING)
I killed Yeatman.
Yes, I know. Why?
You could have killed me.
I love you.
Kill me.
I can't!
You must!
No.
Then free me.
Free me.
Make love to me again.
I want to live with my own.
My own.
(HISSING)
MAN: You looking forward to
a whole bunch of little bald
porcupines running out there?
ALICE: Well, whose idea was
it to put the crows and the
porcupines together?
Well, I figured since
they didn't have anything
in common,
they could share
the same space.
Uh, our new assistant
has a new problem.
I'm sorry.
The crows are plucking the
quills out of the porcupines
and I don't know what to do.
Separate them.
Brilliant.
Got it?
Yes.
OLIVER: Thanks.
MAN: Sure.
I'm gonna go have some
lunch, you wanna come?
Not right now.
In a few minutes,
all right?
Okay. I'll see you
at the house. Bye.
(KIDS GIGGLING)
(GROWLING)
(THEME FROM CAT PEOPLE
PLAYING)
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org