Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
And for dinner tonight,
we have a choice of sardines...
...or sardines.
Gosh, I think I'll have... sardines.
Sardines. Beautiful choice.
So, is this how you seduce all the girls?
Only physicists with hypothermia
who are accused of being a terrorist.
Thank you.
There's a garage.
I'm going to see what's in there.
I won't be long, OK?
Your pit bull has killed
a Wisconsin state trooper.
Well, now.
Would you rather the Bureau
got the girl and Kasalivich?
First, he was a suspect.
Worst case scenario... they arrest him.
Now he's a cop-killer.
Worst case scenario, they kill him.
For God's sake, what possessed you
to frame him in the first place?
Two words.
Convenience... and expedience.
He saw too much, he was talking.
The poor boy was
in the wrong place at the wrong time.
I need this poor boy!
This poor boy is the only one
who knows the frequencies!
Do you understand the concept, Lyman?
Poor impulse control?
Barkley, Chen, the regulator.
That was supposed to be it!
That was all of it!
I am sick to death
of cleaning up your messes.
No, Paul, no. Yours.
Not mine.
You lost it, Paul.
Lost control, perspective.
You made it personal with these people.
Well, we'll find them.
We'll find them, and when we do
and we've got this thing working,
then, my friend, then
this young man will be a liability.
That'll be my problem.
- Our problem.
- No, Lyman.
When the time comes,
I'll handle it.
You'd better.
So what does he want us to do?
We find him and give him an injection.
Lily.
Lily!
Come on.
Leesburg, Virginia.
C-Systems.
Who are they?
Not cops.
Cops carry badges,
credit cards, pictures of their families.
If it's crowded, don't go in.
OK.
- Hi!
- Hello.
Can I help you?
I'd like to send some flowers
and a note to a friend in Virginia.
It's a little strange, Mr Shannon,
but these just arrived.
I'm not quite sure where they're from.
Here's a note.
May I see that?
Thank you.
Hold it right there, buddy.
FBI.
Step outside the van, please.
Why don't you bring
your invoice sheet out with you?
Do you know if the order
originated at this shop?
I don't think so.
I think it was a wire from Georgetown.
- Mind if I take one of these?
- No, sure.
Have a nice day.
So officially this investigation
is now code-named Steel Bomb.
We'll input the data into Rapid Start.
Look what I brought back
from the flower shop.
I think this is Kasalivich.
Spawn versus Neanderthal man, 4pm today.
What is this, a wrestling match?
Bad movie, video game?
Spawn, it's a comic-book character.
- The guy who comes back from the dead?
- Yeah, like Kasalivich.
Maybe Shannon is the Neanderthal man?
Very well may be.
Hello, Eddie.
Glad you got the flowers.
Very clever.
Are you all right?
No, not really.
I guess I can understand that.
We were at Maggie's.
Caught. We were about to be arrested.
Somebody shot the cop.
Later, two guys tried to kill us.
I've got my car outside. Follow me.
We'll go someplace we can talk.
I found this... in one of the guy's wallets.
They weren't cops.
What do you know about C-Systems, Paul?
This is not the time or the place, Eddie.
We're being watched.
Eddie,
the world isn't as simple
as we'd like it to be.
It just doesn't work that way.
Shannon, who are you?
I'm your friend, Eddie.
I may be your only friend.
Is it you, Paul?
Are you responsible for all this?
Time to go, Eddie.
You've got ajob to complete.
The experiment needs verifying.
Do your work... This will all be over.
Eddie, we're beyond that now.
Let's just get this done.
Come back to work with me.
You'll have your life back, I promise you.
You don't control our lives.
You'll have to trust me, Eddie.
Just like Alistair?
Eddie!
A trip that normally takes over five hours.
But today, you'll experience the events
of that flight in just seven minutes.
The crew is preparing for takeoff.
Your pilot for today's flight
is Captain Dave Larsen.
Stay here.
Our co-pilot is First Officer...
Get in.
She's in the hatch.
Look out!
The crew are going through
their final pre-flight checks...
Eddie!
Come on, don't do anything foolish.
Get Ford. DC police reported
a disturbance at the Science Museum
by the Neanderthal man exhibit.
CQ 493... CQ 493.
Here you are, darling. Drink this.
You're dehydrated.
Wash it out of your system.
Mr Collier and I have a few colleagues
we'd like you to meet.
Dr Holloway, Dr Hamada, and Dr Orbit.
They are very interested
to discuss your work with you.
And, of course, Dr Lu Chen.
Lu.
Lily.
We would like you and Dr Chen
to continue the work
you were doing with Dr Barkley.
- You can't be serious!
- Oh, yes.
We've been impressed with your work
for a long time.
Do you drug and kidnap everyone
whose work you admire?
No.
Dr Barkley, we left behind.
Slay the dreamer, eh, Mr Shannon?
You end up sleeping on the street.
I can't believe you'd do that.
Can you spare some change?
A quarter, what's a quarter?
Can't you see me?
Can I share your grate?
You make me sick!
We can't go in! We got kicked out!
What are all youse looking at?
Let go!
CQ 493.
This is Eddie. I think. He does.
But he really does.
What are you watching?
"Honeymooner" reruns?
Kasalivich and Barkley. Look at this.
Does he look like he's about to kill this guy
and blow the place up?
The whole thing stinks.
We've got the ballistics report back
on that trooper killed in Wisconsin.
Teflon sniper round
went through the cop's Kevlar vest.
I don't buy it.
He's smart enough to blow up the lab
but stupid enough
to leave $250,000 where we'd find it?
Are you saying some cowboy's
gone off the reservation?
$100. The kid didn't do it.
You've got a nationwide manhunt
for an innocent man.
Make sure nobody shoots him.
Next shift's going down now, OK?
Yeah, right.
Help me out on this, will you?
I've had problems with the conveyor belt.
No, I'll have Jim Zinsky work on that.
OK? All right.
If you've got any problems,
call me on channel four.
How is our young charge?
Did she say anything?
We'll soon find out, won't we?
The young lady
does appear to be cooperating.
Good.
- Gentlemen, you're just in time.
- Let's get on with it.
Miss Sinclair, Mr Chen,
please, have a seat.
Attention, all personnel.
Critical path experiment
will commence in ten minutes.
Level five.
Activate the H2 compressor.
On... on automatic.
Here we go.
Lucasz, what are you reading?
- Two million kelvin.
- Activate the laser.
Four million kelvin.
You don't have it. It's unstable.
Shut it down! Shut it down!
Dammit! What ajoke.
It won't work without the right frequencies.
What did he say?
He said that's what he's been
trying to tell you for days.
Look. Let's try it again in the morning, OK?
- See you back here at 8.15 tomorrow?
- I have a feeling, Dr Sinclair,
the solution will present itself.
I doubt it.
It had better
or your usefulness will soon be outlived.
Take them back to their room.
I wish you wouldn't threaten
to kill my scientists to their faces.
It might make my job easier.
Lucasz, Hamada, seal the lab!
I want to see those printouts
first thing in the morning.
- It's working?
- Yes.
- How?
- Lucasz claims he figured it out.
Lucasz?
That's his story.
When I got here, the output
was going right through the roof!
Son of a bitch!
It really does work. Ha!
Dr Shannon, take a look at that.
We've got it.
What did you do?
Nothing.
I couldn't sleep last night, sir.
I heard this voice saying,
go and check different frequencies
because we were trying
on 15 and 20 megahertz.
So I went down to the lab
and ran the experiment
and it all worked out.
So... here we are, sir.
Did you document
the regulator frequencies?
Not yet.
I'd like those on a disk... Now, sir.
None too shabby, hey, Mr Shannon?
- Doctor.
- Thank you.
Where are you going, Paul?
I'm going to check this
against the Chicago data.
I'll try to meet you at the silo.
- Wait as long as you can.
- Yes, sir.
Hello, Eddie!
I figured it was you.
Nice place you have here, Shannon.
Ten-megajoule lasers.
Particle reactors.
Congress de-funded
most of the stuff here years ago.
They made a mistake.
Is this part of the Moore Foundation?
In a manner of speaking.
Power and money.
Is that what this was all about?
I'm afraid it's more complicated than that.
He was a 60-year-old scientist
who did nothing but good
and they put a bag over his head.
It was a mistake.
I didn't want anything
to happen to Alistair.
But a decision had to be made.
So...
Who made the decision?
- You?
- That's my job.
That's what I'm paid to do.
I'm paid to do dirty work.
Work people don't want to know about.
People want to live in split-level homes.
They want microwave dinners
and colour TV.
Is that what you think?
Alistair was a dreamer.
Clean air, free energy.
Noble concepts
but we live on a planet
that is addicted to petroleum.
What happens if you dump
free energy onto the market?
World stock markets would plummet.
Our own economy would collapse.
Recession,
unemployment, war.
The world is speeding up too fast now, Eddie.
We can barely hold on as it is.
You're right, it's not working.
So we've got to try something else.
Not bury the technology, but let it out.
You let it out, but you let it out
at a pace the world can absorb.
It can absorb it now.
There's our boy.
Mr Kasalivich!
How kind of you to join us.
Give us a moment, Lyman.
Eddie and I are having a conversation.
Please! Don't let me stop you!
Who runs this place, Shannon? You?
- Or the guy with the guns?
- Well,
we are a cooperative
of sorts.
Run at the behest
of the United States government.
But without their knowledge, right?
My, my, but your friend is sharp, Paul.
All right, Eddie.
What do you want?
There are the specs for the regulator.
You can pull the frequencies
off the computer.
Now let us go.
I get it to work. You give us our lives back.
That was the deal, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah, that was the deal.
I'm afraid, young man,
your position is non-negotiable.
I see.
I want to tell you this story
how I got inspired.
- I had this dream...
- No!
Hold on.
I will continue.
What's happening?
What did you just do?
I just told the FBI I was willing to surrender.
Oh, and er... I think your experiment
just got a mind of its own.
Check the breakers.
Everybody, back to your stations!
What the hell's going on, Doyle?
It started a few minutes ago...
hundreds of pages.
Technical drawings,
experiment specs, budgets,
personnel records, minutes,
mostly marked top secret.
- Where's it coming from?
- C-Systems.
It's like they dumped their mainframe
into our computers.
Here's a special love note just for you.
Jesus Christ, Kasalivich.
He's in a bunker in Leesburg
with his bomb-making buddies
and wants us to arrest him.
- Lake Geneva Radical Bomb Network?
- Sound like bullshit?
It sounds like you owe me $100.
Make sure that fax doesn't run out of paper.
- Hamada!
- Still off-line!
- Pressure?
- 500 psi and rising.
What the hell's going on?
We've lost control of the system, Lyman.
We can't shut it down.
Turn it off.
It's self-sustaining. It can't be shut down.
Al! How long before
we run out of storage capacity?
I don't know. It's accelerating.
- 20 minutes before it blows?
- Maybe less.
- Is he right?
- I'm afraid he is.
Well done, Eddie.
Well done.
You wouldn't blow it up
if you weren't sure you'd get out alive.
Sure I would.
Lyman, I think it's time
we got the hell out of here.
- No!
- Chen!
- Lily!
For God's sake, Lyman!
Chen! Chen!
Wait!
- Jesus Christ!
- What is wrong with you?
- Turn it off!
- That was totally unnecessary.
If you haven't got the stomach for this,
stay out of the way.
I'm going to turn down the power.
- No!
- Don't touch that!
Don't!
Hydrogen containment failure.
Potential personnel hazard.
- The compressor's just shut down.
- Turn it back on!
- You can't.
- The computers are down.
Get out!
Get out! Everybody!
- Fix it.
- I can't now.
- Fix it!
- I can't!
I wouldn't do that, Lyman.
It will ignite the hydrogen.
It's over, Lyman. It's over.
I guess it's time to go.
Go! Go!
Give me the disk.
You two, stay!
No, Lyman! Let them go!
What possible difference can it make now?
- They stay!
- When does it end, Lyman?
Never.
Well, it's not your decision.
The decision is mine,
and I say they're coming.
You can stay with them... if you like.
We must go now.
Well, are you coming?
Warning. Warning.
Air contaminants at critical level.
Come on, Paul! We've got things to do!
I'm sorry, Eddie.
- Shannon!
Please!
Warning! Air contaminants at critical level.
Evacuate immediately.
Warning. Air contaminants at critical level.
All containment doors are now closed.
The tanks.
OK, here's the elevator.
There's room for everybody.
I'm looking for two men.
Paul Shannon and Lyman Collier.
Hang onto them.
Follow the blue evacuation route arrows
to the elevators.
Move in an orderly fashion
quickly and quietly...
Our friends from the FBI
will be here presently.
Anita, we're on our way.
You two go to the north elevator.
I'll take it from here.
Come on! Come on, Lily.
Eddie, which way?
By the way, Paul, do you have that disk?
The one with the magic frequency?
Thank you so much.
You know, Paul,
maybe it's time to call it a day.
Maybe you're getting too old for this.
What do you think, huh?
But then again
what would we do?
What would we do?
I didn't tell you, Lyman,
but your retirement
had already been arranged.
Containment systems off.
Access restored to all areas.
Hey, hold on, hold on!
Take it up, take it up!
They got a 20 on Kasalivich?
They found the stolen truck
at the construction site nearby.
Hold on.
Eddie, look.
Get up. Come on, Reed. We've gotta go!
I thought you said the hole was clear!
Get back in the seat, Ernie.
Eddie.
Lily, get in the basket!
Get out of here. Go!
Eddie, come on!
Eddie!
Hold on, hold on, Eddie.
Come on, Eddie.
Aagh!
Come on, Eddie. Come on!
Pull it up, pull it up.
Holy... did you see that?
Whoa!
Come on, get him out of there.
Eddie Kasalivich.
Agent Ford. You got the message.
Yeah, we levelled a forest printing it.
What's it mean, Eddie?
- Plans for clean, cheap energy.
- Anybody else get this?
Hopefully, a few thousand top scientists.
- I knew I liked this kid.
- Yeah, right, Leon.
Come on.
You've got some questions to answer
in Washington for about six weeks.
- That's OK.
- We've got a lot to talk about
as long as everyone stops shooting at us.
Doyle, spilt 'em up.
I'll meet you at the office.
Ford!
Doctor Sinclair and I ride together.
All right, come on, both of you.
Anita,
take a memo.
To the Director of Central Intelligence.
C-Systems...
no longer a viable entity.
Will be in contact.
That's it.
Subtitles : Filou ;-)
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org