Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
This is the most amazing
I've ever seen.
- I've been with some good schools.
- All of them! All of the best.
One right after another.
You've also been with
the Lucky Erin Bar and Grill.
- Pittsburgh. Bartender.
- And a disc jockey.
In Oklahoma. I used to broadcast
in sign language.
- You've covered the map, Mr Leeds.
- I've got a lot of energy.
I'm sure you do have energy
and new ideas. I did, too, when...
But nobody's trying
to change the world here.
Just trying to help a few deaf kids
get along a little better.
Everything else is razzle-dazzle.
Am I making myself clear?
Yes, I believe that you are.
Are we being punished?
Hi! I'm James Leeds.
My signing is rusty,
so how many of you can read lips?
No one? OK. Class dismissed.
No, no, no!
Just testing. Sit down.
Lydia and Tony, good lip-readers.
Would you mind closing your notebook?
Thank you.
Give me one good reason
why we should learn to speak?
- Tony.
- To pick up hearing girls.
To pick up hearing girls.
Let's work on this.
You, you, you.
Here are two beautiful hearing girls.
You two guys want to pick them up.
What is the first thing you want to say?
Danny.
- Are you rich?
- Are you ri-i-ich? Say it.
- Rich.
- Good.
- Lydia?
- I'm very rich.
Good! Tony?
Let's go somewhere and do it.
No, thank you.
- Let's go somewhere and do it.
- I'd rather do it with her.
Cute. How about you guys?
Do you want to join us?
- They don't talk.
- Fair enough.
OK, reasons to talk. Right.
If your hands are occupied.
For example. Some guy
owes you money. He comes by.
But you just happen to be
in a handstand.
How will you tell him to give you
your money? You can't use your hands.
You've got to speak.
"Give me my money, you bum. "
"Don't call me names. I don't have
to take that. Do you want to fight?"
"Put up your feet and fight like a man!"
See.
"Take your pots... "
"... and your lousy food, and shove... "
She doesn't mince words.
Mr Leeds! Mr Leeds!
Leeds? Leeds!
- Join us.
- Sir, OK. Sorry.
- It's good you're out of my classroom.
- Sit down, James.
Mary Lee Ochs,
Assistant Superintendent.
Orin Dennis, Math and Social Studies.
James Leeds.
Did I hear Miss Ochs say
that you were one of her students?
- Yes. I started here at five.
- Really?
- That's great. I'm impressed.
- For still being here?
- No, what I meant...
- Excuse me. See you all later.
Bye.
- Who is that?
- That's Sarah.
Never mind her. She's a pain in the ass.
Always has been.
- What does she do?
- She works here.
Orin, how about the kids making
pot-holders for Mother's Day?
But they don't sell.
We've got hundreds left from last year.
Sarah came here at five, too.
We grew up together.
Is she a teacher, too?
She was one of the brightest students
we've ever had. Some water, please.
Thank you.
Leeds, you're a genius.
You will work!
Ooh, yeah.
Mr Bach!
Hear that, cat?
Ba-boo-ma-rang-rang-rang.
- Again. Faster.
- Ba-boo-ma-rang-rang-rang.
- Once more. Faster.
Great! Great.
That's great. Oh, Lydia, my Lydia.
Come here, Lydia.
Put your hands on the speaker.
Come on.
Can you feel that?
Good.
Feel it.
Like a boomerang, baby
Like a boomerang-rang-rang
Two, three, four,
ba-boo-ma-rang-rang-rang.
- Use your voice.
- Ba-boo-ma-rang-rang-rang.
A drip.
Drip.
What a drip!
Sorry.
No, no, no!
No, that's not what I meant.
I just wanted to introduce myself.
I'm James Leeds. It's Sarah, isn't it?
Would you like to sit down? Right here.
OK, we'll both stand up.
Oh, I see.
Very good. You got me there.
Look at me, please.
If you don't look at me, I can't...
So, Doctor Franklin tells me that
you've been here since you were five.
When did you graduate?
And now you work here?
Are you reading my lips?
I don't think that you are
reading my lips.
Gee, that was quick of me, wasn't it?
You could have told me.
Why? How about common courtesy?
How about me leaving
so you can mop the floor?
Man!
If you let me, I bet
I could teach you how to speak.
And you could teach me...
But I don't want to mop the floor.
That was quick.
And you don't want to speak.
Brilliant.
Schmuck.
- It's a damn shame.
- Costly, too. Re-sodding is damn costly.
- No, I'm talking about Sarah Norman.
- Right, Sarah.
- Look at this. What a mess!
- Has she ever tried to use her voice?
Sarah's not hard-of-hearing.
She was born totally deaf.
- Yeah, that makes it tough.
- The rain is lousing up the fields.
It's a shame that a bright woman
is cleaning toilets.
It doesn't bother her. Look, hotshot,
not everyone wants to be a star.
Sarah is content.
She had a rotten time as a kid.
She was diagnosed as retarded
until she was seven. We educated her.
- For what?
- She's productive, pays taxes.
If you want to try, I'll talk to her.
I'll talk to her.
Look at this, will you? Damn!
- This will cost 2-3,000 dollars.
- Oh, brother!
- Sat.
All right!
That's really good. You have to work
on the "S's", though. Go. Out.
James? Sarah has agreed to give you
an hour, and she's looking forward to it.
You're looking forward to it,
aren't you, Sarah?
What did I tell you?
Well, have fun, Jim. As usual.
Well, Sarah...
Yeah, I do mind actually.
Fire laws and all that.
But you go right ahead.
Listen...
How would you like to fake out
Franklin? Make me look real good?
I'm sorry, I didn't get that.
If...
...I don't
sign faster,
the hour will be over before I finish
my opening speech.
No, I'm all out of jokes.
Good.
I'm not funny. Oh, yeah?
If you could hear,
you'd think I was a scream.
You're deaf. I'll try to remember that.
I'll forget. No, I won't.
Listen, why don't we get
this thing started?
Well, thank you for stopping by.
Pleasure... was mine. God.
- My mama.
- Your mama. Great, go.
Glen, who is your favourite person?
- Twisted Sister? The Twisted Sister?
- It's the name of a rock group.
Try saying that. Twisted Sister.
Glen, it takes courage. I know.
Just give me one sound.
One "T".
Try! "T".
That's great, great. Yeah, out of here.
Go. Great!
Johnny?
Who's your favourite person?
Princess Di?
Benji?
Terminator?
Hey!
Do you want to play
"stand up, sit down" again?
Careful, you almost smiled.
That's the girl! That's the Sarah Norman
we all know and love.
If my jokes are terrible,
and my signing is boring,
what are you doing here? There's
a whole empty beach! Unbelievable.
I tried to call your mother.
Hold it, hold it. Come on, wait, wait!
I can't...
I didn't even talk to her. OK?
Can we stop this?
I mean, why can't we...
I mean, why can't we just...
Why don't we...
...go out and have dinner tonight?
Just give me a "yes" or a "no".
Yes. Good.
I think. OK.
I will meet you behind
the girls' dormitory, 8 o'clock.
I will whisper your name.
Hey! I know that sign.
That's the first sign I ever learned!
It's in Italian. Can I suggest something?
Will you give me a break?
My Italian is worse than my signing.
The Veal Piccata is very good.
Look. I'm sorry.
V- E-A-L P-I-C-C-A-T-A.
You see, by the time I finish,
they may be out of it.
It's veal. It's saut¨¦ed
in lemon and butter.
What's veal?
God. What the hell is veal?
Good evening.
Something to drink this evening?
Do you want something to drink?
- Our house wine is very nice.
- Wine?
Yeah, it's OK. White wine.
I'll take a carafe, please.
He doesn't think you're stupid.
He thinks you're deaf.
No, only stupid hearing people
think that deaf people are stupid.
Do you really like being
a cleaning woman?
Why?
Yeah, but there are other jobs where
people can work alone in silence.
Not with toilet bowl cleaner.
You should have told me that was
the attraction. You're smart as hell!
You want to dance?
Can you feel it?
Vibrations through your nose!
I'm not good at this.
And you are. Great.
I don't know why I became
a speech teacher. OK? Let's dance.
It's too hard to dance and talk.
Well, maybe I like to hear myself talk.
I am a really good teacher.
You should let me help you.
What is that?
Lydia does not talk like that.
Don't you want to get along
in the world?
No one wants my help.
That's your opinion.
Fine.
You don't do anything you can't do well.
Well, I would like to walk with you. It's...
My pleasure.
Mrs Norman? I'm James Leeds.
I didn't call again, because...
- ... I would have hung up again.
- It's 60 miles here and back.
- Please, just five minutes.
- I just got home from work.
This is my time to relax.
Discussing Sarah is hardly relaxing.
Five minutes.
Well?
Well, you haven't seen Sarah
in eight years?
Sarah doesn't want to see me.
- Has she said why?
- We don't communicate very well.
Did you ever learn to sign?
Some of the parents...
I'm sick of you people coming every
two years, asking the same questions.
- Blaming me.
- No one's blaming you.
Of course they are. They can't blame
themselves, so it's my fault. Fine.
I don't give a damn any more.
I came to ask you one question. What
happened when Sarah tried to speak?
What happened? She looked awful.
She sounded awful.
- People made fun of her.
- Who made fun of her?
Other kids. Her sister's friends.
Then she stopped trying to talk.
She's very pretty, you know.
Her sister Ruth
had boys hanging around,
and they started asking Sarah out
when she came home on weekends.
It was wonderful for her.
Boys really liked her.
They treated her just like
they treated Ruth. With respect.
If you didn't know there was a problem,
you'd have thought she was normal.
Hi!
It's true, I'm early today.
No, don't go.
I wanted to talk to you anyway.
No, I want to work with you.
I understand that you're scared.
I understand nothing.
Sarah, come back here. Sarah...
Yelling at the back of a deaf person.
Very good.
He's been to all the best schools.
Why did you stop going home?
Did your sister's friends,
those boys you were going out with,
have anything to do with it?
Yes, I talked to your mother.
Please let me help you, damn it!
How? By showing you the joys of sex
with a hearing man.
I think that that is one language
that you don't speak!
Yeah, I'm so... Come on, I can take it.
You have enough communication skills.
I don't. They never did?
Hey! Who is "they"?
Hearing boys.
They wouldn't try to learn my language.
I was expected to learn to speak.
Well, I don't speak.
Sex was something I could do
as well as hearing girls. Better.
At first, I let them have me
because they wanted to.
Before long...
...the boys were lined up
on a waiting list my sister kept for me.
No introduction, no talk.
We just went to a dark place and...
They didn't even take me out
for a Coke first.
No, that is not what I wanted
to know about you.
I thought I was such a big deal, coming
on to the deaf girl, giving her a thrill. No!
And all the time you were
laughing at me.
I was thinking, "Poor little deaf virgin,
who'll spread her legs for every... "
Do you think I'm threatened by that?
Do you think I give a goddamn that you
fucked every pimply-faced teenager?
I don't. I don't give a shit!
Sarah, please listen to me.
I'm not going away.
I did the wrong thing. I'm sorry.
I don't know what to say.
Tell me what to say.
Sarah...
...you are the most mysterious,
beautiful, angry person I have ever met.
I'm falling in lo...
Sarah?
Sarah, I am falling
into the pool with you!
God, what a fellow has to go through.
- How are things going?
- Great.
Good! Glad to hear it.
- We must have you over soon.
- I'd like that.
- I warn you, I'm a keen poker player.
- So I've heard.
- Are you a card player?
- Not really.
Tic-tac-toe is my game.
So much the better?
Well, thanks for coming in, Jim. We
really are happy to have you with us.
Thank you.
- Your size?
- Yeah.
- Be careful, Jimbo.
- Right.
Don't fight it.
Relax.
Daphne, you're leading again.
I've got a funny sensation in my toes.
Like someone was barbecuing them
over a slow flame.
Let's put another log on that fire.
You are the nicest person
I've ever met.
Who, me?
I'm the nicest person you ever met?
That's the craziest thing I ever heard.
You thought that after what you told me,
that you'd never see me again.
Here I am.
Yeah, I was in love,
but she broke my heart.
God, no! Please don't break my heart.
Did anyone ever break yours?
You never hurt from other people?
That's not true.
Sarah, I know people have hurt you.
I know.
Suppose you admitted that you hurt.
I'd shrivel up and...
I'll take care of you, Sarah.
I'll take care of you.
What do you mean that was my foul?
You moved into me.
You want to call me an asshole? Say it!
Say it out loud. Watch my lips. Asshole.
- Ahole.
- Asshole.
- Great!
- Asshole!
- Good. It was still your foul.
Asshole!
Did you know that waves
strike the average beach
about 750,000 times a day?
That's true.
I just made it up.
You do?
What do waves sound like?
That is what they sound like.
How did you get to be
so brilliant and beautiful?
And pig-headed?
You're the most stubborn person.
You.
You're not stubborn? OK.
Hi, beautiful.
What am I saying?
Wait.
That was a joke.
It wasn't funny.
OK, I won't do it again.
I promise.
Sarah...
Mr Harrison! How are you?
Couldn't be better, Curtis.
She's doing wonderfully.
Jim Harrison.
He donated the chemistry lab.
- Glen is really coming along. A fine lad.
- Get him to change that idiotic hair cut?
No, I like to give the kids leeway.
- Asshole! Shit-for-brains!
- Look at those shingles.
They'll have to be replaced.
Thank you, Mr Jones' class, for your
demonstration of the four food groups.
And now, Mr Leeds' 11th-grade speech
and language class has a treat for us.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org