Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
-We haven't eaten. Got anything to eat?
-l'll make you something.
-Does Joey help you out?
-He would if he could, l guess.
-How do you pay your rent?
-Workfare. Flipping hamburgers.
Until they figure out l'm dipping
in the register, which is any day now.
-Then l'll be totally fucked.
-When did you see him last?
Night before last. Said he was
gonna get some money and go.
-Go where?
-Like he knows?
Florida. Key West. Whenever
he gets rabbity, he's going to Florida.
Like it's some magic country when it's
only the dope capital of the world.
Can l ask you a question
without you getting mad?
Depends.
When you left Joey, was it hard?
Very hard.
You miss him?
Of course.
lt get easier, you know, missing him
after a while?
You just stop thinking about it.
Put your head down, keep walking.
Otherwise it'd be too difficult.
Was it better for Joey,
you think, that you left?
For a while. All l know
is l missed out on stuff.
-Like what?
-Like teaching him about things.
Like good music. Old movies.
Not being afraid to fight. Stuff like that.
l guess what you want and what you
can do are different things sometimes.
Gina, l wanna help Joey.
You can't help him.
You never did.
That's what he says.
l'm gonna go buy some smokes.
Can l borrow a couple bucks?
Yeah, my wallet is in the hall
on that table.
-You need anything?
-No, thanks.
-You don't mind watching Angelo for a bit?
-He'll be okay.
You be good.
Mommy's gonna be right back.
His Pampers and stuff
are in the duffel.
-Duffy.
-Reg.
My son's girlfriend
brought over my grandson.
-Can you hear me?
-Hello? lt's a lousy connection.
She's spooked. She just went out.
When she comes back, l'll turn up the heat.
-When she comes--
-We're heading to Long Beach.
-l got a warrant for the casino.
-Want me to meet you?
There's Mommy.
Thattaboy.
Who's this?
This is my grandson, Angelo.
Joey's kid.
His mother just dropped him off.
l didn't even know he existed.
Listen, Vincent.
l brought your keys back. l think
we need to take it easy for a while.
Why don't you come in for a second
and we can talk?
We gotta talk. Come on.
We should talk, you know?
-l didn't go out to buy smokes.
-What's going on?
Look, l've been thinking.
l'm thinking about scoring.
-l'm sorry l took your money.
-Forget the money. Let me come get you.
l'm gonna go away for a while, okay?
Don't do this, you'll regret it.
A kid needs his mother.
-Don't do this.
-He's better off without me.
No, that's not true. Please.
l'll come get you. Where are you?
You did it.
Maybe l'm like you.
l can't do it. l just can't hang.
Stay here. Or l'll get you
your own apartment. Come back.
You're gonna pay for it.
It's a big mistake. Just come back--
-Would you listen to me?
-Please come back.
Joey might be crashed up
at that old merry-go-round.
He's gonna be up in the attic.
-You won't hurt him?
-Of course not. But please come back.
-Please, you can't leave him.
-Sorry. You know, l tried.
-l'm sorry.
-What can I do to make you--?
-She's not coming back?
-No.
She told me where Joey was.
Can you...?
Take care of him? Can't say no.
l came here to give you
your key back. And to get mine.
l'll come back and take care of him.
Just let me do this.
We'll talk then, all right?
We're right outside.
Yeah. Okay, thanks.
We're down here by this casino.
-Send us some backup.
-Come on, let's go.
-You're not gonna wait?
-Vince and l were here already.
Let's see if anyone's there,
then get back to town. lt's late.
All right. Easy, easy.
-This place stinks.
-Yeah, the lovely smell of humanity.
l'm taking my gloves off.
l got them fucked up last time.
Holy shit, look at all this.
-Watch it. There's used needles all over.
-l'll bet.
Shit!
Fuck!
Officer down.
Officer down, Long Beach Casino!
Officer down!
Rossi, what happened?
He was up there with a gun.
Reg is over there.
-Oh, no. Jesus.
-l'm sorry, lieutenant.
-What happened?
-They called for an assist but didn't wait.
You don't go in for a murder suspect
without backup!
He said you and him were already here
before together alone.
Goddamn it, Reg.
One question.
Can l have a statement?
-Chief Henderson.
-Lieutenant Katt, Long Beach Police.
Crime scene is in here.
Lt. LaMarca!
Chief wants to see you.
Okay, here's the facts
as we know them so far:
A .45-caliber reported stolen
from a clinic this morning.
Suspect's name is Joseph LaMarca.
He's at--
-Wait a minute.
-Not now.
You don't have enough to make
Joey the prime suspect.
-l know it's your kid--
-Evidence. Rossi didn't see it.
-l didn't see it.
-He didn't see anybody.
-You said Joey hung out here.
-That was just a lead.
-lt doesn't prove anything.
-This is an investigation.
l'm just saying you don't have enough
to make him the prime suspect.
We got a fingerprint match
on the murder weapon.
l'm sorry, lieutenant.
lt's definitely your boy.
l'm here at the crime scene
at the boardwalk...
...where a detective was gunned down
during a manhunt for Joseph LaMarca...
...a murder suspect police consider
armed and dangerous.
They're tearing the house apart.
They say Joey killed some cop.
-Not some cop. My partner.
-l know what they'll do when they find him.
l know what cops do to cop killers. One way
or another, they'll find a way to kill him.
-lt's too late.
-lt's not his fault.
Then whose fault is it?
Did you pull the trigger?
-He doesn't know what he's doing.
-Don't start with that.
You choose right or wrong.
He's got nobody to blame but himself.
-Please help him. You're all he's got.
-Then he's got nothing.
Please, help him!
Don't walk away from him again!
--himself the son of Angelo LaMarca,
executed for a horrific murder in 1 959.
This photo shows LaMarca being booked
for the murder of the baby...
...who was strangled to death while
LaMarca attempted to collect the ransom.
Marge.
Here. Take these into the living room.
Come on now. Come on.
l'm sorry it was your boy.
That'll be hard for you.
l'm sorry. l'm just so sorry.
lt's hard to believe Reg will
never be coming home again.
Why did he do it, Vince?
Reg never would have hurt your boy.
lt's just so wrong. lt's just....
lt's just so wrong.
l swear to God, if there's
anything l can do....
Daddy, no!
Bree's gonna miss him the most.
LaMarca has had a long career
with this department...
...living down the tragedy of his father's
past and that of his troubled....
-Hi.
-Where's Angelo?
-Asleep in your bed.
LaMarca has been moved
to a different case.
There they go. The big story.
l don't know what to say.
l'm sorry, Vincent.
l went to see Reg's wife.
You know, all the other cops
wouldn't look at me.
Just like it was at school.
Nobody says anything,
but they think you're guilty too.
You can't blame yourself for everything.
ls Joey my fault?
l don't know. But you're not responsible
for everything your son does.
He's gotta choose who he wants to be.
You think we get a choice?
We just pretend that we got a choice.
lt's more like a sentence.
When my old man did what he did,
l felt so bad, you know.
l felt like l was the criminal.
No way l'd feel that way again. l'd be
so good nobody could pin anything on me.
That was my choice.
But now, whether your dad
is a cop or a murderer...
...some kid's father's not coming home.
That's the real life sentence.
Yeah.
So, what do we do, Michelle?
Want your keys back?
-LaMarca.
-l didn't shoot that cop.
-Joey?
-You hear me? I didn't shoot him.
I didn't shoot him.
Somebody did. l just left
the wife and daughter crying.
-Well, it wasn't me.
-Let's meet where we watched the planes.
-What?
-Remember we used to watch the planes?
-Yeah.
-Remember where that was?
-l'll be there, just me.
Why should l trust you?
Joey, you don't have a choice.
l'll be there by myself, l promise.
Please. You gotta do it. Please.
All right.
-You gonna meet him?
-l hope so.
-What are you looking at?
-The van down there.
-They're tapping the phone.
-But you're on their side.
l don't think they see it--
l don't think they see it that way.
-Speak.
-Let's not play games.
-Sorry, chief.
-Why get cute about the meeting spot?
l know what happens
if the wrong cop goes.
You got my word that nothing's
gonna happen to Joey.
Your word is good with me. lf l can,
l'll bring him in to you. l gotta go.
There will be a lot of cops up here
looking for me. Bring Angelo to your place.
-Where are you going?
-You can't say what you don't know.
You still watch those planes.
Yeah.
l met Angelo.
Gina brought him over.
Nice little kid.
Because of Gina, not me.
She won't let me see him.
She says l gotta stay away
till l get clean.
Which will be whenever.
-l got this lawyer ready to meet with us.
-You wanna take me in?
l wanna help.
Did you hear me? l didn't do the cop.
l come to talk to you,
you bring up a lawyer.
You think maybe your lawyer could
get me the electric chair? Fuck.
Too weird, huh?
lf l got the chair too,
just like your old man?
You ever think about him?
Sure.
-Did you love him?
-He was my father. Of course l did.
Because someone's your father means
you gotta love him? You think l love you?
-l don't know.
-Right. You don't even know me, do you?
No, l guess l don't.
You wanna tell me?
-You know l was quarterback in high school?
-No. Your mother never told me anything.
-l used to look for you in the stands.
-l would've loved to see you play.
You should have. l was good.
We beat Cedarhurst
in the county finals.
First time in 24 years.
The crowd went wild.
l didn't need drugs that night.
l was good then.
You should have seen me.
l wish l had.
All right, fuck it.
We all got reasons.
So you believe me about the cop,
or what?
-Your prints are on the gun.
-l wasn't there when the cop went down.
That cop had a name.
His name was Reg.
So who was there?
Fucking scumbag dealer named Spyder.
He's after me for his fucking $4000.
lf l had it,
l'd be on a plane to Florida.
Did you see him?
No, l didn't see him do it
but l saw him right after.
-l mean right after. ln the alley there.
-What about Picasso?
l don't know.
Look, l was fucked up...
...he came at me with a knife....
-l guess, in a sense, l killed him.
-ln a sense?
l don't know what happened. One minute
we're fighting and the next he's dead.
But that wasn't me.
All right? That wasn't the real me.
l wouldn't count
on a jury believing that.
This is something you can't run away from.
You can't. You can't run.
-Do you believe me?
-lt doesn't matter what l believe.
Plead self-defense, you could get off
with maybe six years.
What if it matters to me
what you believe?
l gotta take you in, you know that.
What are you, a cop or my father?
l'm both.
-l'm getting out of here. What are you now?
-Joey, come on!
Just fucking with you.
l knew the answer.
You know, when l was a kid,
l wanted to be a cop.
l really did.
Just like you.
Chief.
Where's your boy?
Picasso worked for a dealer called Spyder.
Spyder's after Joey for his $4000.
Joey told me he saw Spyder in the alley
by the casino after Reg was hit.
-Why didn't you bring your boy in?
-He told me he didn't kill Reg.
-You believed him?
-l believed him.
He's your son, of course
you wanna believe him.
-l've been a cop 25 years--
-The operative word is ''cop.''
You're not sometimes a cop,
sometimes a junkie's father.
You're either a cop
or you're not a cop. End of story.
This is bullshit.
You're under oath to perform
your duty. ln this investigation--
What investigation?
You already made your mind up.
Peace, all right?
Don't be playing no bullshit neither.
A motherfucking ghost.
-How come you still breathing, Casper?
-Listen.
A thousand dollars for my Nova.
Cops got your wheels, boy.
l'm sorry, man.
Will you do me a solid here, please?
l need help.
Please.
What's the ring?
-lt's a football ring. lt ain't for sale.
-Let me see.
This is worth like 1 00, easy.
But l'm saving it for my son.
We'll treat it like a loan
until l get you the 1 00 back.
Yeah, sure.
All right.
Here.
No, Carl, l can't use this.
l need cash.
-You'd be the first junkie who couldn't.
-Give me the ring.
Back the fuck off!
You lucky l'm giving you anything!
Please, the ring's important.
lt's for my boy.
You ain't gonna be around to see your boy.
And you ain't going to Florida.
You got Spyder and the cops
chasing you. You a junkie!
Only place you're going is the morgue.
County, motherfucker!
Wait a minute! What are you doing?
There's nothing in there for you.
Want to come over and see my soup?
Look, here's grandpa.
This is Evelyn Hancock.
She's an old friend.
You're a big boy, Angelo.
Evelyn is with Child Services.
What's going on?
She's taking Angelo until
Gina comes back. lt's temporary.
She's not coming back.
l can't take care of him.
-Can l talk to you?
-Sure.
Go see this nice lady.
l just wanna talk to him
for a minute.
-What are you doing?
-What am l supposed to do?
-Take care of him. You're his grandfather.
-Nice idea, but l can't.
Vincent, Gina's gone.
You think his father is coming back?
-This is the best thing for him.
-No, you're the best thing for him.
-l can help you.
-You never had kids, you don't know.
-You're gonna walk away from him.
-What do you mean, walking away?
-Like with Joey.
-l'm not walking away!
-That's what you told me you did with Joey.
-l'm not-- Walk away?
Let me show you something.
You think l want him growing up with
this? Like the son of Frankenstein?
''You never know what he might do.''
''Don't mention his father!''
Call it walking away, but l'm doing
the best thing for him.
That is not about Angelo.
That's about you.
You told me. You told me
you never had a choice, right?
-Well, you got one right here.
-Michelle, try to understand.
Right now it's more than l can handle.
l can't do it.
That's how you make a choice.
Goodbye.
Morning.
Let's try to wrap this up.
We got pretty substantial evidence.
Fingerprints are clear.
There are no others on the gun.
Shells and ballistics
identify it as the shooter's.
We know he frequented the carousel
and used drugs there.
-Excuse me, sir.
-Go ahead, Dave.
A shoe print in the blood
doesn't match LaMarca's size.
So, what do we think?
That O.J. was there?
Maybe Bruno Magli?
One last thing.
This kid has killed twice.
Don't give him a chance
to do it again. We got that?
You got a phone call on my phone.
How come you're giving out my number?
-l don't even know your number.
-This guy knows it.
Make sure you leave a nickel
in the ashtray.
Dave Simon.
l couldn't call you direct.
What's going on?
l have something you should see.
Could we meet at York
and 59th Street Bridge?
It's copies of crime scene photos
I tried to mention.
What are they?
Footprints in the blood
at the top of the ladder.
We can account for all of them...
...except for one heel from a size 1 0
cowboy boot made by Justin Boots.
At your ex-wife's
we found some of Joey's stuff.
Joey wears a size 1 2 1 /2 shoe.
There's no 1 2 1 /2 prints
anywhere in this blood.
l appreciate this.
Well, you know,
it doesn't all have to be bullshit.
-You born in Long Beach?
-No, Army brat. We lived all over.
-Distant climes, huh?
-We traveled a lot.
-Now we got a baby. l hardly get out.
-Kids change everything.
lsn't that the truth.
Sir, listen,
l'm real sorry about your son.
l appreciate it. Thank you very much.
l appreciate that.
It's more than I can handle.
-We just pretend we got a choice.
-We don't have a son, I do.
I wasn't gonna feel that again.
-You think I love you?
-I should've tried harder.
You said you never had a choice.
-What are you, a cop or my father?
-That's my son.
Please help him. You're all he's got.
He's your son!
-This is something you can't run away from.
-Just like his dad.
Sorry, sir. We're closed.
-Anybody know where Spyder is?
-We're closed, mister.
Where's Spyder?
Peace, brother. Peace.
Stick the Friar Tuck act up your ass.
Where's Spyder?
-You know who l am?
-Yeah--
Tell Spyder l know he killed
my partner. l got proof.
He wants to see me, l'm at the Seaway
Motel. Room 1 05. You got that?
Yeah.
1 05. Seaway Motel.
Here's where we're
expecting the storm.
On our map, lots of green.
And within that, yellows and reds.
These are the areas
where we're expecting heavy rain.
In New York City, the storm
will move in by tomorrow morning.
You got something for me?
Dave Simon.
Lt. LaMarca.
Got it.
l want backup and emergency units
to Ocean and Neptune. Lt. Katt?
Don't fucking move!
Don't move a finger.
Give me the gun.
Give me the fucking gun! Go ahead.
Move!
What the fuck is this?
What are you doing
telling people l shot that cop?
l know you killed my partner,
scumbag.
lt was your junkie kid.
l'm not the only one that thinks so.
You left a footprint in his blood.
Are those Justin, size 1 0?
-You're a long way from Manhattan.
-But too close to home for you.
You broke into my property.
l'm within my rights to defend it.
l couldn't take the chance
he'd hurt Gina or Angelo.
Would be just like him.
You broke in here pretty good.
You learn that in cop school?
So, what now, Joey?
Hold back and hold your fire!
Hold your fire!
Keep eyes on that door
and those windows!
Block that road!
l don't want one TV van!
Right up there.
Okay, enough. Give me the gun.
lt'll be hard enough getting you
out alive without them seeing that.
This is no game, son. Please.
You saved my life but they
didn't see it. They don't care.
-l ain't going to jail.
-l understand. l wanna help you, just....
Just give me the gun.
Lt. LaMarca, signal your location!
All right, talk.
Talk?
What are you now, fucking Oprah?
You got a son and a woman that
loves you. Don't run away from that.
-You did.
-Yeah.
l did.
And l'm sorry.
l've regretted it ever since.
We all gotta pay
one way or another, right?
What's going on?
lt's called ''suicide by cop.''
Quick and easy.
No pills. No fucking around.
l thought l'd try it.
How did we get this way?
l remember the day you were born.
Well, l remember the day you left.
So we're even.
-l'm not gonna kill you, son.
-Well....
Your friends out there will.
You know it.
-There he is!
-You two!
Hold back! Hold your fire!
Get the building secure.
Give me the gun.
-l don't want to shoot you.
-You do. You think l deserve it.
-Get back!
-But you won't. lt's not the real you.
-You don't know anything about me.
-l do. You're my kid.
You're not a bad kid. You're a scared kid
whose old man left him.
You didn't get a choice and it hurt. l know.
But you're my son. You always will be.
Then why did you leave?
l was stupid. l forgot
what it felt like to be alone.
You don't want to do to Angelo what
l did to you. What my old man did to me.
-You can't.
-He don't need a junkie.
You're not a junkie to him.
My old man wasn't a killer to me.
When my old man left, l hated him
all my life for what he did to me.
But all l wanted was for him to walk
in the door because l missed him.
l didn't want to be alone
anymore.
We all pay a price for what we do,
but when's enough?
Because l paid. And you paid. And what?
Now Angelo has to pay?
You can't! We got a second chance
here, me and you.
l let you think
you didn't matter to me.
But l swear l won't run away again.
l'll stay with you, l promise.
You just need to choose it.
Know how many people
would love a second chance?
Help me.
-Dad, are you okay?
-lt's just my shoulder.
-l didn't do it.
-l know.
Get rid of the guns!
Empty your pockets.
Don't give them an excuse.
-They'll kill me.
-lt's okay. l'm with you now.
ldentify yourself!
lt's okay.
lt's okay, there are no guns!
Raise your hands.
See the hands? No guns.
-Get down, drop the gun!
-Show us your hands!
-They're down.
-Move away!
Move away from him!
-Told you to move away!
-Take it easy.
All right, take it easy on him!
Listen! Anything happens to him,
you'll answer to me.
Easy with him!
lt'll be all right.
lt's okay, son. lt's okay.
Here he comes.
This way.
Watch your head.
I love you.
l want to go on the rocks.
Yeah, those are the rocks.
That's the jetty.
Let's go on the rocks.
Yeah, those are the rocks.
Look, see that?
You see that, the airplane? See?
-Where do you think that's going?
-Flying....
You want to fly away
with your dad sometime? Yeah?
Because he wants to go with you.
He told me so.
He told me he wants to take you
to Key West.
You wanna go?
Yeah? Good.
When he comes back,
you'll go with him to Key West.
Me, you and him.
Grandpa, Daddy and you.
We're gonna go to Key West.
-Okay?
-Yeah.
Okay, sweetheart.
You want to put the water
in the thing?
Go put the water in the thing.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org