Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shit.
Where you running off to, Luce?
- I said...
- Don't touch me.
Where's the friendly girl
I met in the bar last night?
I think we both got what we wanted.
- Are you serious?
- Just honest.
Don't fucking touch me!
You were a hell of a lot more fun
on your drunk-ass back.
Room's already been taken care of.
- Yeah, but I'd like to pay for it.
- I already ran a card through.
Well, can you credit his account
and put it on mine?
You both checking out,
or is Romeo sleeping in?
- Is that clock right?
- Last time I checked.
Can you call me a cab, please?
It's extra if he's not out by noon.
Yeah.
- Hi.
- Did you have fun?
- Mm-hmm.
Fuck.
Oh, damn it.
Where'd you stay?
- Motel.
- Why?
I think he said
he lived with his mom.
- Or his wife?
- That guy call?
No.
Only reason he asked
for your phone number
is so he wouldn't seem like a jerk
for wanting to screw you the other night.
Well, then I hope he doesn't call.
- Want coffee?
- No. Thanks. I'll get some on the way.
Pack of smokes.
- You buy two, you get a free one.
- Okay.
I don't know why y'all
don't use plastic flowers.
Look a hell of a lot better than these.
A lot cheaper, too.
- Kind of in a hurry, Sue.
- I've never seen you when you weren't.
- Stay out of the heat.
- Try to.
Oh, put my tape in, would you?
Your VCR's broke.
My son brought me a new one.
When'd you see Dad?
Oh, he stopped by.
- You want last week's?
- Yeah, it's the one on top.
Was he...
Well, how'd he seem?
He's going to some new
holy roller church.
Hey.
I wanted to stop by
and see how the new apartment was.
It's fine.
It's a nice complex.
All your stuff fit?
I had to get rid of some things.
Keep your old chair?
Yeah.
We'll probably bury you in that thing.
I just thought I'd stop by
and see how things were.
Well, I'll let you get back
to what you were doing.
I've got some errands I need to run.
All right.
Okay.
Hey, Dad.
Doll says you're going
to some new church.
Yeah.
Well, you going tomorrow?
Can I come with you?
I leave around 8:45.
I'll see you then.
I can't believe y'all can't smell that.
Smells awful.
I still ain't got a sense of smell
since that infection.
- The one you had a while ago?
- Yeah.
- Is it gonna come back?
- Beats me.
Watch your fingers, Hattie.
What you want me
to watch 'em do, Ed?
Nana, are these the mushrooms
I made at Christmas?
Well, that or mold.
What's the difference?
- I thought you liked my mushrooms.
- No, Tim likes your mushrooms.
Uncle Tim can't taste.
I can taste, I just can't smell.
I'd like some mushrooms.
- Have you heard from Mom lately?
- She called a couple days ago.
She said the weather's nice
and she hates herjob.
- I don't know why she doesn'tjust quit.
- Leslie Jo called?
- Well, you talked to her, Ed.
- When did I talk to her?
A couple days ago when she called.
- I did not!
- Did too!
- Well, you did when she called!
Nana, I can't tell if the cornbread's done.
Well, stick a knife in it.
Tonightjust ain't your night, Lucy.
I play better when I'm drunk.
No, you don't.
Corner pocket.
- Want another beer?
- You bet.
A couple Coors, Bob.
Sure thing.
This is gonna be the last one for me.
You're gonna quit while you're behind?
- What is she doing here?
- What's that?
Nothing.
Hit it a little harder, pumpkin,
and it might go in.
It's your shot, Eli.
Aren't you even gonna say hi?
Where are your manners?
Did you leave 'em out in your car?
I drive a truck, bitch.
It's your shot, Eli.
What a mouth on you.
I'd think your daddy would have
taught you better than that.
By the way, how is your daddy?
Staying out of the trash.
Ooh!
And you must really miss him.
- Fuck you.
- Hey, I'm sorry, honey.
One per family is my limit.
Easy. Easy, easy, easy, easy, easy.
Calm down, calm down, calm down.
Calm down.
All right?
Now, I'm no judge,
but I think you got the best of...
You might wanna put some ice on that,
keep the swelling down.
You might wanna fuck off.
- You all right?
- Unh!
- Want me to drive you home?
- I'm fine, Eli.
She'll be all right.
Let's have a beer.
Oh...
Shit.
- You know it's Sunday, right?
- Mm-hmm.
Why are you wearing a skirt?
Have you seen my bible anywhere?
Did I miss Easter?
Oh, I know it's here somewhere.
- What?
- My bible.
- You sure you have one?
- Everybody has a bible.
And what do you need it for?
My dad invited me
to go to church with him.
When did you see your dad?
Quik Stop.
They sell dads there now?
Buy two, get one free.
What happened to your face?
Got in a fight, Kim.
Don't really wanna talk about it.
Okay.
Praise God.
Oh, my goodness, that was beautiful.
That was wonderful.
You know, I do believe Jesus likes
a little rock 'n' roll in the morning.
Amen!
Thank you so much.
Fellas, have a seat, please.
You've worked so hard.
Ladies and gentlemen, please.
We're liable to be here a while.
Oh. You know, uh,
people ask me all the time
who Jesus is.
Well, uh, there's a whole book here on it.
But, uh, they seem to want it in a nutshell.
Well, Jesus himself said in John 14:6...
"I am the way."
Hallelujah.
"I am the truth, and I am the light."
Amen!
I liked your church.
The preacher's a smart man.
Seemed like it.
The music was different.
The last chapter of Psalms says,
"Praise him with trumpet sound.
Praise him with lute and harp."
Guess a lute player
is pretty hard to come by.
We just used a guitar.
I'd like to come with you
next Sunday, if that's all right.
All right.
It was good to see you.
You too.
See you then.
I figure they'll start
digging those footings today.
Rebar's here.
Concrete shows up Wednesday.
Are they excavating
that area marked off back there?
Yeah.
I think this neighborhood
has a green barrier
that restricts commercial building
to 30 feet.
You think or you know?
I know.
The plans the developer gave me
had that whole area marked off.
Seems like somebody was trying
to put one over on you.
Hell, yes, they were.
Somebody's ass got greased.
Probably down at the planning commission.
How was your weekend?
Got in a fight, Owen,
and I don't wanna talk about it.
I'd hate to see the other guy.
Girl.
- Anybody I know?
- God...
Let's hope not.
He got pissed off.
That dog.
- Hey.
What's going on?
Getting a new jukebox.
Well, what's wrong with the old one?
People don't wanna hear music
sung by dead folks.
Yeah, they do.
Nope. They want that new country.
Oh, God! No, they don't!
Yeah, they do.
- Well, I don't.
- Well, you're the only one.
- Eli doesn't.
- No, I don't.
Okay. You and Eli.
Mike doesn't.
Yeah, I do.
See there?
And Mike knows music.
You drinking or talking?
Need some help, girl?
How you feeling?
Fine.
I've been in a few fights. Usually I feel
like a truck hit me the next day.
Yeah. I'm fine.
Thanks.
My God, the music in there is awful!
Okay.
But you're using bigger rocks.
No, I'm not.
Well, whatever.
You little cheater.
You from here?
How about you? Where...
I don't know why you're doing that,
'cause you're already winning.
Kentucky.
What do you do?
Contracting.
Foundations mostly.
- How long you been doing that?
- Nine years.
You enjoy it?
Yeah.
What do you do?
A client asked me to come down
and help her out doing some roofing.
- Sanders Roofing... you ever hear of it?
- Yeah, yeah. Mm-hmm.
They're pretty big.
- Thanks for the beer.
- Oh, you're welcome.
- Can I get your number?
- What for?
So I can ask you out.
On a date?
Yeah.
Right.
You seeing someone?
Mm-mm.
So...
- I'm listed.
- Under what?
Little Miss Muffett?
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Lucille.
Lucille...
Fowler.
Fowler. Lucille Fowler.
Okay.
Cal. Cal Percell.
What's he look like?
Like every other guy at the Star Studded,
except he doesn't wear Wranglers.
- How do you know?
- Know what?
That he doesn't wear Wranglers.
Kim!
Hello?
Well, you don't wear
the new shirts you already have.
Blouses.
They have a sale every other week.
Okay.
How about if I come get you
tomorrow at my lunch?
I'll see you then.
Did you give him your number?
I'm not taking these back
when you decide you don't want them.
They already hate us in that store.
I forgot to look.
- Now, were they on sale?
- Of course they were on sale.
It's 100 degrees outside
and they're long-sleeved.
Well, I want my arms covered.
I'm gonna get you
some salve for your face.
No, it's fine.
Listen, Doll, I gotta get back to work.
Do you want me to put these
in your closet for you?
Yeah. Don't I have a denim blouse?
You have five.
Mm, what's that?
Food you actually have to
sit down to get.
- Is that the Bonner project?
- Mm-hmm.
What do you think our bid's going to be?
Forty?
Maybe 38, if I can get
that deal on the concrete.
You'll get it.
Oh, a Frank Bryant
from Mississippi called.
Go on, doggy. Go on!
Shoo, dog! Kyah!
Don't you got a home?
Ah, crap.
Are you mean?
Are you gonna bite me?
Oh, what happened to your ear?
Did you get in a fight?
I'm real sorry, sweetie,
but Dr. Henry won't be in until Monday.
He and his family have gone to Branson.
They got a timeshare condo there.
Well, it looks infected to me.
You could take her over to Little Rock.
Well, can I just bring her in
first thing Monday morning?
Sure, you can.
Now what's her name?
She doesn't have one.
I just found her.
Well, I gotta have something
put down in the appointment book.
Bessie.
Do you maybe have
some ointment or something?
Yeah, I think I got
a sample here somewhere.
- Oh, here you go.
- Thanks.
Oh, she sure is a cutie.
We'll see you Monday.
Is it true that when
you take 'em to the pound,
they put 'em to sleep after a week?
Yes, ma'am, they sure do.
So what's up with your face?
Nothing. It's stupid.
- Did you get a puppy?
- No, I found a stray.
Keeping it?
Taking it to the pound on Monday.
Big eater, huh?
See ya.
Go on, wanna go inside?
Did they fix her ear?
Nah. The vet was out of town.
What?
Cal called.
- You gonna go out with him?
- I don't know.
I think you should.
I don't even know him.
He's a complete stranger.
Oh, that's right.
You only sleep with complete strangers.
Maybe you should just have him
meet you at a motel then.
- It'd save time.
- And money.
Courting can be
pretty expensive these days.
"Courting." Time for you
to cut back on the Andy Griffith.
- You are such a chicken shit.
- I am not.
I just felt sorry
for your Ionely ass staying home.
You didn't tell me he had T-tops.
Oh, excuse me.
I'm Kim.
Kim? Cal. Cal Percell.
- Hi.
Oh, no!
Yeah, what can I get you?
- I got it, I got it.
- Let me get this round.
You got the last one.
I asked you on a date.
Let me take care of this. Thank you.
- Thank you, Cal.
- Sure.
Excuse me. Ma'am?
Would you like to dance?
Okay.
Well, to our date.
If you'll let me.
Have you decided what you're
going to do with that old jukebox?
Not yet.
- How come you like old music so much?
- I don't know.
Have you always?
I liked nursery rhymes for a while.
My dad used to play guitar for me
when I was little,
and he loves all the old music,
so that's probably why.
Was he any good?
Hell, what'd I know?
I was eight.
- Well, if you liked it...
- I reckon.
He had a band when he was younger,
and they played
in all the bars and stuff around here.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- But there is one problem.
- What's that?
He's kind of shy,
and my mom says he'd have to be
shit-faced to play in public,
or else he'd make
somebody else stand on stage
with a guitar
that wasn't plugged in.
But he'd still be playing?
Yeah, behind a curtain or something.
- Yeah, I'd say that's shy.
- Yeah.
He still play for you?
I gotta pee.
You want Kim to go with you?
Three shots of Jack, please.
- Is Kim still dancing?
- Uh, yeah.
You wanna?
Sure.
- You know how?
- I took cotillion.
Don't sleep with him.
Feed Bessie. Whoa!
Oops.
You all right, hon?
Ohh...
This is nice.
- Who lives in the front house?
- My aunt and uncle.
They were kind enough
to let me stay here till I get my own place.
There's a light here somewhere.
There we are.
Got any beer?
Uh, yeah.
- Is that your mom?
- Oh, that's my Aunt Wanda.
Looks like a spitfire.
- Your uncle?
- Carl.
- They still married?
- 35 years.
Shit, really?
Are they happy?
Seem to be.
What about your parents?
Divorced when I was ten. Yours?
Mm-hmm, yeah.
My dad had trouble
with the whole being faithful thing.
That woman at the bar...
She wasn't the first.
How many asses
you gonna kick, girl?
Whoa. Whoa.
When was the last time
you kissed someone sober?
Huh?
Johnny Patterson.
Skating rink, back corner.
Wasn't any good, though.
Old Johnny had a hard tongue.
Why don't I give you a hand?
You have a skating rink
where you grew up?
Yeah.
Yeah. And, uh...
I could skate backwards.
What are you doing?
I've gotta go.
What time is it?
Well, how are you planning
on getting home?
A taxi?
Jesus, Lucy, I'll take you.
- Well, thanks for the ride.
- Any time.
Kim's home, so the door is unlocked.
Just get out of the car, Lucy.
Wanna go outside? Come on.
Come on, Bessie, go outside.
- Did you have fun?
- Oh!
Scare me half to death.
You're home awfully early.
What were we supposed to do, sit around
and drink coffee and pretend we're in love?
How aboutjust sit around and drink coffee?
He didn't have any.
Anything happen with you and that guy?
No.
You give him your number?
Oh, Jesus, Kim, you didn't.
So what if I did?
Well, are you just stupid?
I mean, my God,
don't you ever get tired
of sitting around
waiting for some jackass to call?
Don't you ever get tired of not?
What do you got against
getting to know these guys?
I thought we got to know each other.
Okay, a little better.
I mean, God, Lucy,
don't you ever meet someone
and wonder what they looked like
when they were little?
Or what their middle name is?
You know, stupid stuff like that.
Do you think he'll call you again?
- Call him.
- I can't.
Why don't you go back over there?
Because, Kim,
I wouldn't know what to say.
Well...
He left about ten feet of rubber, so...
I'm guessing "sorry"
might be a good place to start.
Do you know how long it's been
since I kissed somebody sober?
You forget something?
No. I brought you the paper.
There might be places to rent.
Come on in.
You want something to drink?
There's not much.
- Cold beer, maybe a soda?
- No, I'm fine.
You kind of caught me in the middle
of gluing this damn thing together.
What is it?
It's a '71 Boss Mustang
with a 351 Windsor.
It's an engine.
What's this?
It's a passenger seat.
You wanna paint it?
Can I?
Sure.
No, you can't paint it blue.
It has to be black.
How come?
'Cause blue wasn't an option.
How do you mean?
I mean you had three colors
from the manufacturer for your interior
when you bought this car.
Black,
red,
green.
Well, you're not the manufacturer
and this isn't a real car.
No, it's not.
It's a model.
A model of a real car.
Well, what if somebody really liked blue
and they had a lot of money
and they paid the manufacturer extra?
You wanna paint it or not?
Either you paint it black,
or go down to the store
and we'll get your very own car.
And you can paint it any color you like.
Black it is.
You know how to paint?
Okay. Don't get any on your fingers.
It's really hard to get off.
Not too thick.
You done a lot of these?
Quite a few.
Can I ask a question?
What's that?
It's already black plastic.
How come I have to paint it black?
You know what?
I just remembered why I do this alone.
You wanna go for a drive?
Caught a couple of frogs out here
not too long ago.
- Frogs?
- Big ones.
- How?
- With a gig.
What? Like frog giggin'?
- Yeah. You never done it?
- No.
You've never been frog giggin'?
What do you do with 'em
when you get 'em?
You eat 'em.
- No way. Are you serious?
- Yeah.
Now, if you see one, you spear 'em
right through the middle, all right?
Look over there.
- No, I don't think I can do this.
- Sure you can, sure you can.
It's like poking a marshmallow
with a coat hanger.
You've made s'mores before, haven't you?
Yeah, I was a Girl Scout.
- I think I see one.
- Where?
Shine the light, shine the light over here.
Gig him. Get him!
Get him! Yeah, there he is.
- Oh, my God!
- Good job.
Ohh! Oh!
- Aah! Quit it, quit it!
- Big one. That's a big one.
Okay. We need about ten more,
and then we're gonna have a proper meal.
- Now get back here.
- Oh, that is disgusting.
It's pretty gross, isn't it?
All done.
I bet you thought I couldn't do it.
Never had a doubt in my mind.
Horseshit.
You want a beer?
No.
Wash 'em good.
I'm all cleaned up.
All for you.
Slow down.
Sit down.
Let me look at you.
Turn over.
Take this off.
I like your back.
It's strong.
You have little ears.
Yeah, I do.
Come here.
You okay?
Ohh. Uhh.
Planning your escape route?
Okay, look.
You suck at sneaking out.
Were you just grounded non-stop
as a teenager?
Cal, I really didn't want
to wake you up.
Oh. Okay.
'Cause I was beginning to think
you're just not comfortable
with this whole morning after thing.
So where are you going?
To catch a worm?
Church.
No kidding. I didn't figure you
for the church-going type.
Well, you figured wrong.
What are you doing later?
Those frog legs aren't
gonna cook themselves.
Well, I didn't figure you
for the cooking kind.
Well, look who figured wrong now.
You wanna cook 'em at my house?
I mean, my kitchen's bigger.
What are you trying to say?
Nothing.
Yeah, I'll come over to your house.
Can I borrow your t-shirt?
Yeah.
Can I do anything?
I'm not all that good with salads.
Okay.
Our deepest fear
is not that we are inadequate.
is that we are powerful beyond measure.
It is our light, not our darkness,
that most frightens us.
And I believe that.
I believe that with the bottom of my heart.
We are all children of God,
all of us.
And as sure as you have
your parents' DNA, you have his.
Because as Jesus said,
"On that day you will know
that I am in our Father,
and you in me,
and I in you."
Praise God.
Make manifest that which is of God
that is within you.
It's a huge gift, man!
It's a huge gift.
And how do we do that?
Very simple.
It's right here in Matthew 7:7.
"Ask and the gift will be yours.
"Seek and you will find.
"Knock and the door will open to you.
For everyone who asks receives."
The seeker finds,
and the door is open to anyone who knocks.
Amen. Amen.
Come on, girls.
You're slowing me up.
- You eat these a lot?
- Only when they're in season.
There's a season for frog legs?
Come on.
Bring it over here. Let's go.
Well, what do you think?
Tastes like chicken.
Not... not exactly.
Oh, come on. It's not that bad.
Maybe it's an acquired taste.
No, either you like it or you don't.
They're not gonna grow on you.
Lucy, would you mind
getting me another beer?
- Want one, Kim?
- No, I'm good.
If you happen to care for another,
they're in the icebox,
that big white shiny thing
in the kitchen.
Yeah. Think I've seen it.
Lucy, I didn't mean to disrespect you.
No, Cal, it's fine.
It's fine.
Could you throw it out for me?
- Yeah, I could do that.
- Thank you.
Well, good night, girl.
Cal?
What'd you do up in Kentucky?
I had a little business.
- Doing what?
- Car restoration.
Probably figured out by now
I like cars.
Why'd you give it up?
I like to think
I'll do it again someday.
Cal?
What's your middle name?
I don't have one.
Come on, Bessie.
Come on. Good girl.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
Their car broke down
somewhere near Dennard,
and it being Sunday and all,
of course nothing was open.
Anyway, they said they'd have it
fixed this afternoon,
he'd be home later tonight.
It was just a hose or something like that.
Everybody's okay, thank God.
Why don't you just leave her here with me?
It'd save you a trip back.
He'll get to her first thing in the morning.
That's okay.
You're on my way to work.
I can just stop back by.
- I am sorry.
- That's okay.
Thanks.
The pound will put her
to sleep after a week.
Mm-hmm, I know.
Did you ever hear Dad play guitar?
Yeah, that time he played
with Chet Atkins.
What?
When?
When he played with Chet Atkins.
You never heard this story?
I can't believe this.
That's where you got your name.
You really never heard this story?
- God damn it, no.
- Okay.
Well, him and Leslie Jo
used to go down to the Cimarron.
Well, shit, it's that same
honky-tonk disco you go to now.
And the way I understood it,
if your dad was drunk enough,
he'd sit in with whatever band was playing.
And I guess he got a reputation
down there for being pretty good.
So when Chet come to town,
he called him up to the stage.
I couldn't believe it.
He kept him up there most of the night.
So Chet gave him a solo
during that song Lucille.
And your dad fucking tore the house down.
God!
I'm getting chills
just thinking about it.
People talked about it for years.
Took about ten days
for Lowell's feet to hit the ground.
So why'd he quit playing?
Lucy, I don't know.
Life, I guess.
Started working for his dad.
Then little old you come along.
Oh!
Did I tell you?
That smell over at Mother's...
catfish.
I was cleaning up on top of the fridge
where she keeps all that old bread,
and I found a catfish.
Been there for about ten days
in this heat.
- Oh, that's disgusting.
- Disgusting.
Even I could smell it.
About threw up is what I did.
Nana? Got any old catfish?
- What's the matter?
- Nothing.
You, uh, you want a bourbon?
- What did he do to you?
- Nothing.
I'm fine.
- Nana!
- Leave me alone, Lucy.
What did you do to her?
Ed, you are a mean,
pathetic son of a bitch.
You're all gussied up.
You going out on the town?
- No.
- Well, you got your gold shoes on.
Oh.
My hair looks like a brush pile.
- Do you need a drink of water?
- No.
- Anybody with you?
- No, ma'am. Just me.
I brought you some peas.
They're fresh. You want some now?
No, I'll wait a while.
Well, don't forget they're in there.
I wanna go see Buford Saturday.
How come you still go to his grave?
Well, did his drinking
just not bother you?
He was my husband.
He left you, Doll.
You got no say over your heart, Lucy.
And if you think you do,
you'd best not let yours roam too far.
Lucy.
- The vetjust called.
- Oh, is Bessie ready?
Owen, do you mind
if I go get her?
I don't have to bring her here.
I can drop her off at home.
She didn't make it.
They had to put her under for the surgery
and she... she didn't wake up.
Well, maybe she is by now.
I should call.
Lucy, they said that
she had a heart defect,
that she was weak and...
Well, she's gone.
I see.
Why don't you take
the rest of the day off?
It was just a dog, Owen.
I was taking her to the pound anyway.
I don't need to take the day off.
So what are you gonna do
with thatjukebox?
I don't know.
It ain't gonna play
in the back of your truck.
- Wanna shoot some pool.
- Nah.
Well, you're about as much fun
as a sack of taters.
Hey, Mike, let's shoot some stick.
Rack 'em up.
Hey, girl.
I just talked to Kim.
Why didn't you call me?
Just a dog.
She had a heart defect.
She would've died anyway, only slow.
I know.
If you want, I could go pick her up
and we could bury her somewhere.
They said they took care of it.
How you been, Luce?
Come on, now.
Don't tell me you don't remember me.
Look, pal,
why don't you just back off?
I think she can tell me
whether or not she wants me to back off.
- Ain't that right, Luce?
- Don't touch me.
You are about two seconds
from getting your face cracked.
Knock it off, Cal.
This dirty whore ain't worth
getting your ass kicked over, buddy.
Stop it!
Take that shit out of here!
What in the hell's the matter with you?
What the fuck are you doing, Cal?
Lucy, that guy...
that guy was being an asshole.
Aw, man, I could've
handled it, Cal.
Lucy.
Lucy, he didn't have the right.
- I fucked him, Cal.
- So?
I fucked him and I don't remember.
I think that pretty much gives him the right.
- That's where you're wrong.
And I don't know where you get off
getting in the middle of something
that's none of your fucking business.
I was under the impression it was.
Well, you must've gotten
the wrong impression.
Okay.
What was he supposed to do?
Stay out of it.
Seems to me like the guy deserved it.
Answer it, Lucy.
Hello.
Yeah, this is Kim.
Yeah, I remember.
Oh.
Okay, I'd like that.
Friday sounds great.
Okay, I'll talk to you then, Lee.
I, um...
I need to talk to you
about something, Lucy.
Sure, Owen.
Frank Bryant is a business associate
over in Jackson.
And he wants me
to come work for him.
I, uh, I think I'm gonna do it.
A little less responsibility
might do me good.
When would you go?
Pretty soon.
But we just started a site.
I can get somebody else
to handle it.
Lucy.
I want you to come with me.
Look, it's a bigger company,
the money would be better,
and I could really use you.
- Owen...
- You don't have to decide right now.
Just think about it.
Okay, I will.
One new message.
Hello, Lucy?
Uh, it's Doll.
Don't forget, I want
to go see Buford in the morning.
Okay. Bye now.
You look great.
Where y'all going?
- Cajun's Wharf.
- Fancy.
- You wanna come?
- No.
- Want me to get it?
- Yeah.
Hi.
I'm Lucy.
Lee Young. It's nice to meet you.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
So where are you from
originally, Mickey?
Well, Shreveport originally.
- Right.
- Yeah.
What's your middle name?
John.
Did your mother or daddy
give it to you?
Well, that's my dad's name.
What do you do, Lucy?
I told you my friends call me Luce.
Okay.
What do you...
What do you do, Luce?
I'm a veterinarian.
You like animals, do you?
A lot.
I see. I see.
That require much school?
A lot.
Work much on horses?
All the time.
My friend's got a sick horse
over in Scott right now.
Well, God damn it, you should get me
over there as soon as possible.
Oh, right.
You know where the restroom is
in this place?
Dead ahead.
Will you excuse me?
Uh-huh. For...
...83 seconds.
How's that sound?
One, two...
What are you doing, Lucy?
Nothing.
Sure don't look like nothing to me.
Well, nobody asked you, Eli.
Come on, Lucy, you're drunk.
Let me get you out of here.
Let me take you home.
I've been calling you.
- I'm not there.
- Yeah, I can see that.
Lucy.
I hope I wasn't longer
than 83 seconds.
- Hate to get you mad.
- Mm-hmm.
What do you say, man? Mickey.
Cal. Cal Percell.
I just get in the middle
of something there?
Nah.
- You sure about that?
- Mm-hmm.
What do you say
we get out of here?
Sounds good to me.
- Thank you, buddy.
- You got it.
This is me right here.
- All right, where to, girl?
- Don't call me girl.
Okay. Where to?
Where do you live?
- Rose City.
- Rose City sounds great.
Oh, hang on.
You crying?
No, no.
- Who's the guy?
- Nobody.
Maybe I should just
take you to his house.
Maybe you should just
shut the fuck up and drive!
Hang on a minute.
Now listen.
I would've taken you home with me tonight
'cause I thought that's what you wanted,
but that don't make me
a piece of shit, all right?
You're in my car, you're crying
all over the place.
I just cleaned the damn thing up.
And you obviously got some
pretty strong feelings for that no one,
and you're dead wrong
to put me in the middle of it.
Got too much respect for it.
From what I could see,
you could use a little yourself.
Fuck you!
Not tonight, sweetheart.
- Let's get you out of here.
- I'm fine.
No, you're not. Come on.
Let me grab your things.
Take me to my dad's.
It's kind of late, Lucy.
Please, Eli.
Where does he live?
Over in Levy.
Dad?
Dad, it's Lucy.
I wanna talk to you.
Dad!
Dad, it's Lucy.
Can you hear me?
Open the fucking door, Dad!
Knock and the door shall open.
Matthew 7:7...
Knock and the door will open.
Well, I'm knocking.
Dad, I'm knocking on the door!
Open the door!
Open the fucking door!
- Come on, Lucy.
- Eli, he's in there.
That son of a bitch is in there!
Open the fucking door!
Why won't he open the door?
Come on, Lucy, it's late.
Come on, let's go, let's get you home.
You trying to make it rain?
- Brought you your t-shirt.
- Thank you.
Listen, I was drunk last night.
Yeah, I don't really wanna hear it.
It didn't have anything to do with you.
I didn't think it did.
- Cal...
- Lucy.
Let's just call it.
Okay.
And I suppose you do.
Well, I know a hell of a lot
more than you do.
You didn't even finish school.
'Cause I married you,
unfortunately.
Well, I must have been drunk!
Oh, ho, ho!
I'm thinking of killing him
and telling God, "He died."
Hey, wait, where are you going, missy?
Where you running off to?
I don't wanna stay here
and listen to you lying.
Well, that man is one sorry
son of a bitch.
- You married him.
- Oh...
Well, I didn't know
what I was getting into.
Well, guess what, you do now.
Well, I'm glad you got
all the answers.
I don't, Nana.
But if you're so miserable,
just do something about it
because I've mustered up
all the fucking sympathy I can.
Well, poor you.
No, poor you.
You're as miserable as he is.
So the part that I was looking at
that I don't really understand is,
"The Lord is long-suffering,
and of great mercy,
"forgiving iniquity and transgression,
"and by no means clearing the guilty,
"visiting the iniquity of the fathers
upon the children
unto the third and fourth generation."
Well, um, Jeremiah 31:30 says,
"But all shall die for their own sins.
The teeth of every one
who eats sour grapes shall be set on edge."
I don't know what that means.
I don't wanna hear about teeth and grapes.
I wanna know about this.
About the sins of the father.
I wanna know what it means.
Why do I have to carry
shit around that's not mine?
Why would God do that to me?
It is so unfair!
You got anything against trees?
- No.
- Okay.
If a tree has Dutch elm disease
and it drops a seed,
the sapling that grows there
is gonna have the same disease,
and you're not gonna say that's unfair...
it's just how nature works.
It's how God works.
So, what, that's it?
I'm just supposed to live with it?
I don't know.
I just know it's not God's doing.
But last week you said,
"Ask and the gift will be yours,
seek and you shall find,
knock and the door will open."
Well, I've been fucking knocking
and knocking, and I'm tired of it!
So stop knocking.
And just walk in.
Hi.
Hey.
Can I come in?
Sure.
I wanted to apologize
for the other night.
You want a beer?
No, I'm fine.
And I was thinking it would be good
if we could talk about some things.
Sure you won't have a drink?
No, sir.
You start playing again?
No. Just messing around.
That's good.
Uncle Tim says
you played with Chet Atkins?
Once.
Dad, I wanted to talk.
I'll let you get back
to what you were doing.
Thanks for the song.
Well, I hate to hear you
say that, Lucy,
but I guess I figured
you wouldn't.
Have you turned
the site over to anybody yet?
No.
Would you consider me?
Well, hell, Lucy.
I thought you would never ask.
You're gonna need... this as well.
- What is it?
- Bonner project.
I guess that deal you made
on the concrete made all the difference.
Owen, I don't think
I can handle all that.
Lucy, you have been running
this business for the past four years.
There's no reason
you should stop now.
Thank you, Owen.
- Hey.
I wanted to apologize, Cal.
I put you in the middle
of something I shouldn't have, and...
Well, I guess you figured out by now I'm...
I'm not real good with relationships.
Guess I've always known I'm...
Well...
It's like grapefruit, right?
Where it's real nice and stuff
and people love it,
but when they're done,
what's left over is pretty ugly.
- Lucy...
- Can I finish, please?
It's not often I feel I have something to say
or something worth listening to anyway.
Cal, can I use your phone?
Yeah.
Luce, um, you...
Cal, it's fine.
Really, it is.
I just wanted to say all that.
And to say I was sorry.
And that's it.
Looks like it's
gonna be a pretty sunset.
If it don't rain.
It's not gonna rain.
What was the name of this wine?
It comes in a box, Ed.
Does it really matter?
Well, yes, it matters.
I like it.
And I'd like another glass.
And I'm sure a man in hell
would like a glass of water.
You just quit showing out
and give me another glass of wine.
I'm not showing out.
That wine is three feet
in front of your face.
And it's been three feet
in front of your face for 55 years.
Get it yourself.
Lucy, you bring me
another glass of wine.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org