Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
When I was a little boy, my mom
used to play A Portrait of Merle Haggard
every night before bed.
Her favourite song was Silver Wings,
so I figured I'd surprise her
and learn how to play it.
I played that song day and night
until my fingers bled.
Finally, when I sat her down to play it,
she waited until I was finished
and then she said,
"Merle sings it better, but keep trying."
So I guess I am.
Put it out, Beau.
Yes, ma'am.
Peterson went through withdrawal all over
the dogwood deck. It's got your name on it.
And Beau?
I don't want to see you
anywhere near Mrs Canter's room.
- The what? The what was wet?
- Go with it.
- What did you get wet?
- The stage was wet.
Oh, the stage was wet, right.
I'm looking.
- That's when it what?
- You keep messing me up here.
I'm sorry.
- You know, here. You just...
- You were what?
- You sing it.
- What were you going to say?
No, that was good.
Why are you giving this to me?
- Go on, please.
- What?
I don't know. Make it yours.
I like that song.
What do you say when you start?
"I remember that day."
"I remember that day. When..." When what?
"When we first met."
- How do you do that so fast?
- I didn't do anything.
- You were there. You had it already.
- Give me that.
"Timing is everything."
- Try that one.
- I like that. That one was good.
Kell.
What's going on?
This is Beau. Do you remember him?
He's one of my sponsors.
We were just messing around.
Of course.
Hey, Beau. How are you doing?
- Hey, beautiful.
- Hi.
Beau, would you mind getting
a couple bellhops for Kelly's bags?
- You got bellhops here, don't you?
- No, sir.
Well, then, do you mind?
Because the car's out front.
- They're letting me out early.
- Well, you still got another month left.
- They think I'm better.
- Better than what?
I was going to tell you. I was...
I was just thinking,
"How am I going to tell you?"
Beau!
Are you Kelly's doctor? Because the last
I checked, Dr Stevens was taking care of her.
No, he's just being protective.
Aren't you, Beau?
He's just being a good sponsor.
Why don't you let me be the protective one,
all right, hoss?
Now, if you wouldn't mind,
I'd like to get some help with these bags
so we can get Kelly out of here.
She doesn't travel light,
in case you hadn't noticed.
The first two venues are small.
We'll ease you back into it.
And the third?
We're going to go back to Dallas, televised.
- What?
- Yeah, we're going to prove them all wrong.
Look, Kell, you're the toughest girl I know,
so if you tell me you're not ready,
well, then, I'll take that at face value.
I want Beau to open for me.
Who's Beau?
He's that kid you just met.
He's a singer. He's a good one.
Well, why don't we get the gardener
to open for you? I'm sure he's good.
It's important to me.
Besides, I've already got an opener for you.
Chiles Stanton.
The beauty queen I was telling you about.
She's playing tonight at The Stage,
and I'm going to go check her out.
I'm sure you are.
You can check out Beau while you're there.
All right. Well, how about this? Look, I'll...
Hold on. I'll go check out Chiles tonight
and if it doesn't work out,
and if she doesn't blow me away,
then we'll look at other options.
Don't placate me.
- I wouldn't dare.
- Yeah.
So, where did you find the bird?
Under a tree down there.
I waited 20 minutes for her mama
to come back,
and when she didn't, I swooped her up.
- I've been taking care of her ever since.
- It looks like a baby quail.
I've been calling her Loretta Lynn.
What if I took her for just a little while?
I'll take care of her.
You got a really big tour
that you need to get ready for.
Okay.
Hey.
- I got a good idea.
- What?
Let's get out of here.
Let's go.
Nashville's Kelly Canter was released,
once again, from rehab this morning.
You'll remember, the country music star
was arrested last year
for drunk and disorderly conduct
while performing at a show in Dallas.
She was five months pregnant at the time.
Hi, guys. Hey. Hey, how are you doing?
Be careful.
We can't wait to get on the road again.
We can't wait for the tour to start.
Kelly's feeling better than ever.
She's looking better than ever.
And it's going to be fun. We can't wait
to get in front of the fans again, okay?
Thanks, guys. Take care.
James, what about the divorce rumours?
Hey, Beau.
What are you doing here?
I couldn't just wait by the phone
for you to call, could I?
I'm here to hear you sing.
And to support Chiles, of course.
Chiles? What does she
got to do with tonight?
- You be nice, Beau. Find me after the show.
- All right.
Hi, Beau.
You better be here to wish me luck.
I'm on the board.
I'm playing three songs tonight.
- Says who?
- Says James Canter, that's who.
- Bullshit.
- Bull-true.
I happen to be in consideration as
the new opening act for Miss Kelly Canter.
James, my new manager,
booked me this gig as a rehearsal.
Not that I need it. I've been ready
for this moment since I was four years old.
The last time I saw you sing,
you froze up like an ice cube.
That was seven and a half months ago.
And it was just that one time.
I'm not playing county fairs any more.
I'm much more seasoned.
You don't have any songs.
You can't even play the guitar.
I've been writing songs.
I got a whole bunch of them right over there.
Little Heartbreaker, Summer Girl,
Rinky Dinky Town.
These aren't songs,
these are rides at Disneyland.
Clint, tell me Garth Brooks here
isn't opening up for me.
She's not. She's closing.
I can't do anything about it, either.
- It's your place. You can tell her no.
- Not to James Canter, I can't.
So you're going to let this prom queen
get up on stage?
I mean, for Christ's sake,
Patsy Cline sang here.
I don't care
if she sings Yankee Doodle Dandy,
she's still going to play.
I'm not cutting your set, Beau.
You've got the same three songs.
Don't worry, Beau.
I have no intention
of stealing your invisible career.
You see,
I want one.
- Hey, you did make it. Good to see you.
- How are you doing?
We got a packed house tonight,
I got your favourite spot on the rail right
straight through here, and Chiles is up next.
Yeah, what do you hear about her?
Well, I saw her last Tuesday at Robert's.
And to tell you the truth, I don't know
which was bigger, the hair or the dress.
Hey, she could be a diamond in the rough,
you know?
Well, I ain't got much time for rough.
Yeah, I hear that.
- Kelly's not coming?
- No, no, she needs her beauty rest.
Well, I guess I can tell the bartender,
"Put the vodka back on the shelves."
Enjoy the show.
Thank you very much.
What are you waiting for?
You're up, Kilgore. Your band's there.
I was Miss Dallas, dummy.
Dallas, Kilgore, what's the difference?
Go get that career.
- How do I look?
- Like a country Barbie.
Thank you.
All right.
This is it. This is my night.
Everything is about to change.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Sorry.
Here we go.
Hi, y'all. How are you doing tonight?
I'm Chiles Stanton.
And what a beautiful crowd you are!
I have a few new songs for you tonight,
and I hope you like them.
Watch this.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my.
I'm so sorry.
One more time.
Do you think somebody could turn down
the lights a little bit? It's awful bright in here.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
One more time.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Chiles Stanton, everybody!
No, that was fun up there, man.
Actually, we're going to work on that.
You two sounded good in there.
Yeah, thanks.
- Do you ever think about doing a duet?
- No.
Her good looks and your song writing...
The girl's more scared
than a church mouse, James.
Yeah, but once you get her wound up, boy...
We're no duo, man. I don't even know her.
I was just sleeping with her friend.
Why don't you go on the road with us, Beau,
get the hell out of these honky tonks,
step up to the big leagues?
I think your bird is hungry.
Hey.
This could be a hell of an opportunity
for you, you know that?
You know, I don't know
if this means anything to you,
but I actually enjoy playing music,
and it don't matter who it's for.
All the rest is just bullshit.
Bullshit.
Why don't you try to play some
of that bullshit in a stadium full of people?
Then see if you got anything, hoss.
I like these people just fine.
I figured you'd say that.
Beau, do you care about Kelly?
What are you getting at?
Look, I know her legs are still shaky.
I ain't stupid.
But I also know this is the only opportunity
she has to turn herself around,
maybe save her life.
And I thought, maybe since you were so
concerned about Kelly
and that you were her sponsor,
that maybe you would come out
on the road and help me take care of her.
Maybe not.
Do you think Chiles Stanton is pretty?
- Now, come on.
- No, I'm serious.
I do. That's why I'm asking.
I think she looks
like a young Linda Ronstadt.
Yeah, well, she's a talented kid.
Do you think I'm talented?
- What do you think?
- How talented do you think I am?
Very talented.
- On a scale of one to 10.
- A 10.
-10's the lowest.
- All right, a one, then. Absolutely a one.
- How about zero?
- Oh, you're definitely a zero.
For sure.
James?
I'm sorry about Dallas.
So am I.
We should talk about it sometime.
James?
I just got one of those Brazilian bikini waxes.
I just took an Ambien.
I'll see you in eight hours.
The first time I heard you sing,
I knew. I wasn't much of a church man,
but I thought that must be
what angels sound like.
I thought I'd died and gone to heaven.
- I love that story.
- That's good. Because it's true.
- Kelly, how was rehab?
- Well, good, I hope.
- Is it too soon for a comeback tour?
- Are the divorce rumours true?
We couldn't be happier.
We've got three sold-out shows.
We've got the hottest two acts in country
music to come around in a long time.
And Texas has never seen anything this big.
Kelly, how do you feel
about returning to Dallas?
I feel okay. I think it's going to be good.
- Thanks.
- Thank you, Kelly.
- Anything else to say to your fans?
- I love y'all. Thanks for coming out.
- Have you forgiven Kelly for Dallas?
- She looks great, doesn't she, guys?
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Hi, James. Hi, Miss Kelly.
Would you mind signing this for me, please?
- Sure.
- Thank you so much.
If you have any advice for a young artist
such as myself, I'd love to hear it.
- I have some advice.
- And James has been so helpful.
I won't sell it on eBay or anything.
I've just been a fan of yours
since I was a little girl.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
This is amazing, James. It's so beautiful,
I don't even want to pee in the toilet.
You didn't think this was for you, did you?
No! No.
God, no.
Okay. See you in Houston.
What, you don't like your new band?
I didn't need your help back at The Stage.
I would've done just fine.
I know. I know.
The only reason we're doing a duet
in Houston is because James liked the song.
Yeah, I'm sure that's true.
So, I was looking at the set list
for Dallas and I thought,
what if I close the show with Coming Home?
- Well, we don't have Coming Home, Kell.
- Yeah, but, I mean, Bob's going give it to us.
We've given the guy enough
number-one singles. Thank you.
Well, let's get through Houston first
and we'll see, okay? Thank you.
I love Coming Home. I mean, I think
it should be my next single, don't you?
Well, what I love is that Houston sold out
in 15 minutes. That's what I love.
Did I tell you that?
Well, JJ, he thinks it's a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity, but I don't see it that way, Kelly.
I think that we got a lot of things that...
Kell? Hey!
Do you remember when we were like that?
Did you hear anything I said?
I think I weighed
about 60 pounds soaking wet,
and I had that big old gap in my teeth
and knock-knees.
You were the first boy
who ever told me I was beautiful.
I remember your meat loaf.
Do you remember the first bite?
Do you remember what was in the first bite
that I took?
I was 20 years old, James.
I was trying to be a good wife.
Damn.
Nobody told me, "First you cook the dinner
and then you put on the Lee Press-on Nails."
I loved you so much,
I think I would've eaten it anyway.
Do you ever wonder what would have
happened if we had stayed in Bristol?
Yeah. I'd be selling insurance,
you'd be singing in the church choir,
and we'd be miserable.
Kelly, you belong on stage,
singing in front of thousands of people.
You're probably right.
I know I'm right.
Up or down?
I want it down and full. Like really...
Do you remember how it was in Little Rock?
- How could I forget?
- Well, goddamn.
Hey.
You like?
Man, you look like
you're going to kick some ass.
Yeah!
That's what I told them.
I said I want to look strong.
You look strong as hell.
Hey, guys, can I talk to Beau alone
for a minute?
Okay, girls, let's clear the room.
- Just a second, okay?
- No problem.
What are you doing?
I want you to make me a promise.
Okay.
Don't sleep with anybody else on this tour.
I'm serious.
Yeah, well, how's that fair?
You sleep with James every night.
I don't sleep with him like that.
We don't even kiss
with our mouths open any more.
All right.
You're mine.
I'm yours.
Good.
Okay, everybody, come on back in.
I just had to give Beau a little pep talk.
Okay, everybody,
we got 10 minutes till showtime.
How many of those pills
are you supposed to be taking?
I take whatever's in the square.
That's an awfully big square.
I've got some awfully big problems.
Somebody get my husband.
I want him to know how lucky he is.
- James, Kelly's looking for you.
- I'll be there in a minute.
- The blue dress. She needs to look her age.
- All right. Do you want her hair down?
Hey, how many of those pills
is she supposed to be taking?
I want her hair up because Kelly's is down.
And I want her to wear those suede Manolos
because I don't like her boots
she's been wearing. Okay? Thanks.
Do you like my makeup?
I did it to make my eyes pop.
Well, you look beautiful.
James, Kelly took a lot of those pills,
all right,
and I don't know about it.
I thought maybe you'd want to talk to her.
God damn it, Beau.
I know exactly
how many pills Kelly took, all right?
Because I put them in the pill box myself.
Now, the only problem with those pills
is if she's mixing them with alcohol.
That's your job.
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh. That's from Emmylou.
That is so nice.
Hey. Did you find him?
Yeah, he's dealing
with a wardrobe emergency.
He said he'll be in when he's done.
He had a wardrobe emergency?
It's an exciting night tonight.
Y'all are the first to hear one of the best
country lineups in the state of Texas.
And to kick it off, we have a newcomer,
Mr Beau Hutton.
Thank you.
Short and sweet
is what I'm going to make this.
It's called Chances Are.
Are you going to open up any more of these
or do you want me to write out a list for you?
Yeah. What's that red one?
It says "H. Roberts."
It's probably that damn cookie place,
heard about the diet I started yesterday.
Man, they get you every damn time.
Who gave this to you?
- Did you give this to her?
- It was with all the other packages. I'm sorry.
Who told you to give this to her?
Get security.
Right away.
I can't get any air.
Thank you.
How about it, ladies and gentlemen?
How about another round of applause
for Mr Beau Hutton?
We need security
down in dressing room A right away.
- What's going on?
- You can't go in there, Beau.
Nobody's allowed...
Nobody's allowed inside, man.
Hey, Kell. Hey. It's Beau. Open up.
- I need James.
- You're out of your league on this one, boy.
He's with her, isn't he?
Who gives a shit about any of that?
Just open the door. Come on, let's talk.
I do! I love him, you idiot! Get out of here!
Get out of here, Beau.
Let me deal with this shit. Go!
I'd like y'all to give a nice, big,
warm Houston round of applause
- for the former Miss Dallas herself...
- Baby, you got to come out of there.
...the lovely and talented Chiles Stanton.
Those people think I killed our baby, James.
Why would anybody think that?
Every time I think you're close to forgetting,
something happens that brings it back up.
Well, I'm not going to forget about Dallas.
It's not something you just forget about.
What if we tried again?
I bet you I could still get pregnant.
Kelly, listen to me.
You got a lot of people waiting out there.
Let's just get this over with
and then we can go back to the hotel, okay?
All right? Then we'll get some fish and chips.
We'll get in the hot tub.
It'll be just me and you.
You don't want to leave your fans waiting.
- So, let's just get out of here...
- It's never been just me and you.
- Let's just get out of here, baby.
- No.
- Get out of the closet, Kelly.
- Don't!
- Get out of the closet.
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
James. James.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
I'll do whatever you want, okay? Okay?
All right.
Will you remember me like I was?
Yeah.
Go on stage, give them hell.
Will you give me a kiss?
Careful of the step.
That's good. I got it. I got it.
The first song, Country Strong, right?
Yes.
Are you all right?
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
the star of tonight's show,
six-time Grammy winner,
the belle of Bristol,
our very own Kelly Canter.
Hold on one second. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Sorry. I just...
Thank you so much.
You just cannot understand
what this means to me. Thank you.
We love you!
I was just in my dressing room,
and I was looking out the window,
and I was looking up at the big, bright sky,
and there are so many stars.
And I thought,
"Man, it looks like they would take
such good care of you."
Do you know what I mean?
Come on, baby, come on. Don't do this.
I never lived on a star,
but it sure looks like fun.
Hey, what did y'all think of Beau?
Wasn't he great?
Let's go. Come on, come on, play!
Come on, baby, come on. Sing!
Oh, y'all want me to sing?
I am going to sing, okay?
I just...
I just feel like I need to sit down.
Would that be okay?
Can I just sit down and just rest?
And I am going to sing.
- Love you!
- All right, Kelly!
I'm going to sing. Let's sing A Fighter, okay?
Sing.
Sing, Kelly.
Sing, baby.
We're never going to make it to Dallas!
The whole show's going to get cancelled!
- Would you just relax?
- Hey, where the hell were you?
Where the hell were you when she had
a bottle of vodka in her dressing room?
- I was on stage!
- You were on stage?
Jesus Christ, don't you have
any tricks up your sleeve?
Yeah, don't take somebody out of rehab
before the rehab!
Who the hell do you think you are, kid?
Will you sign this?
People are ready to forgive you, but you
have to give them something they want.
I've scheduled
an emergency press conference
and a Make A Wish appearance in Austin.
The kid's name is...
- Travis.
- Travis. And he has...
- Leukaemia.
Let's go, people.
It's time to do some clean-up here.
Thanks, JJ.
We'll make it up to you next week.
She better put on a real pretty face.
Fool me once, shame on you.
Fool me twice, shame on me.
Shit. Come on, man.
You know we're all fools in this business.
What are you looking at?
No one's ever going to buy food poisoning.
She's a total basket case.
Why don't you be quiet
and tell me what you're looking at?
Don't.
"When did General MacArthur
return to the Philippines?"
1946.
"What does 'amorous' mean?"
Having a propensity for falling in love.
What the hell are these things?
Well, as a woman in this industry,
people have a habit of thinking
I'm some kind of ignoramus.
And my pageant training doesn't exactly
help things, so I have to overcompensate.
You're not the only one who thinks
I'm just some dumb beauty queen.
I'd never call you a dumb beauty queen.
Give me those.
I'm serious.
Anybody that says "ignoramus" so casually,
that's not dumb at all.
Why don't y'all just sleep together?
Get it over with. Jesus. Really.
I feel great.
I feel better than I have in a long time,
aside from the food poisoning incident.
Note to self: never trust a sushi bar
that's open 24 hours a day.
But all that's behind me now.
And I just want to say, I'm really looking
forward to playing for my fans here in Austin.
What about Dallas?
Dallas?
Yeah, your last date
will be broadcast in Dallas, correct?
Yes.
We all know that Dallas and I have a history,
and it's not such a good one.
So I'm really looking forward
to changing that.
Thank you.
Kelly!
Kelly! Kelly!
Is this on?
I guess so. I'm sorry.
My parents are school teachers.
I'm not used to running in such fancy circles.
- Chiles!
- Yes?
- Chiles, who is your idol?
I'm on tour with her right now.
And Jesus Christ, of course.
Kelly Canter and Jesus Christ.
You and Jesus Christ.
Who would have thought?
- They love her.
- Yeah, I guess.
What do you think of her?
I don't.
You're not a very good liar, Beau.
Hey, are we still going to hang out today?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
So, what do you suppose we do?
Steal a car, do some skinny-dipping,
shave our heads?
Hey, come on.
Let's get out of here and have some fun.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Well, what do you think?
I think I'm Kelly Canter
and I'm breaking the law!
Give me more! Yeah! Come on!
Get it out there! Give me more!
Yeah! I got six Grammys
and seven platinum records!
And everybody knows who I am!
And? Come on, what else?
And I have the best damn marriage
in the world of country music!
Yeah, she's good, James.
Let's talk about the Freedom Tour.
She might be a good addition.
You better hurry.
- How about this week?
- All right.
Look, I was sorry to hear about Kelly.
We were all praying for her.
Thank you, Bob, but she's doing just fine.
She's looking forward to the next show.
- She also loves the tracks you sent over.
- Oh, yeah?
Yeah. Especially Coming Home.
She thinks that could be her next single.
She'd sing the hell out of it, Bob.
The little girl right there is the one
to sing that song. I'll talk to you later.
What?
Maybe we should stop this.
You're married, Kelly, you know?
Well, I've always been married.
Yeah, but just after today, I've been thinking
that maybe I'm just not the best thing
for you in your life.
I want to be, but...
I'm just
trying to do what's best for you.
Since when?
I think the world of you, Beau.
But sometimes you don't have
the faintest idea of how to talk to women.
Hey.
- Do you want to hang out?
- No, not really.
All right.
I just wanted to show you my lyrics.
That's all.
Where have you been?
I was with Beau.
Why do you have a towel on?
We were out and I got so dirty
I needed to take a shower.
Well, that sounds like fun.
It was.
- Can I help you do that?
- Nope, I got it.
Are you going to let me in or what?
Do you write all your own lyrics?
What is this, Twenty Questions?
How come you haven't got the chorus
wrote down yet?
Because I haven't come up with it yet.
I could write it for you.
This ain't Mad Libs, Chiles.
You can't just fill in a blank
with a noun America loves.
Well, I could write good lyrics if I wanted to.
Maybe I just haven't been inspired
by anyone yet. You ever think about that?
I don't need to be singing
about my Achy Breaky Heart.
Give In To Me? That's what it's called?
- I like that title.
- Good. Then don't mess it up.
Oh, my God! The Miss America Pageant's on.
I'm just dying for Miss Oklahoma to win.
She's got the best figure,
and she does the prettiest ribbon routine.
I think I need a drink.
- Do you want one?
- Just a tiny one.
How would I change the world
if I won this crown?
I would start by putting country music
on all US outbound flights.
Then I'd change the national anthem
to Merle Haggard's Mama Tried.
This is how you win a beauty pageant.
Oh, let's see.
"Thank you, ladies and gentlemen,
distinguished judges."
That's such bullshit.
And then I give them one of my seven smiles.
- Yeah, let's see them.
- Well, I got swimsuit.
And then interview.
I like that one.
I got my formal wear.
Which one's your drunk-off-my-ass smile?
I think you're drunk.
You know, I think we should have
a swimsuit competition.
I don't have a swimsuit.
Well, you're wearing a bra and panties,
aren't you?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's the same thing.
Yeah, I'm doing it. Here we go.
You versus me.
Beau, what are you doing?
Don't be a chickenshit about this, Chiles.
I've seen plenty of ladies
in their swimsuits before.
I'll get into mine just so we're even.
Your turn.
All right.
But no pictures.
I may go on to be Miss America one day.
So, what do we do now?
Build a sandcastle or something?
Oh, my God. That must be James.
- What the hell's he doing here?
- Put your pants on.
Well, it's not like you have
to answer it or anything.
You know I do.
Put your pants on. Hurry.
- Hi, James.
- Hey.
I was just showing Beau my pageant walk.
And he was leaving.
Right, Beau? You were just leaving?
- Yeah.
- Well, that's something I'd like to see.
Is that guyliner?
That's real cute, Beau.
The Statesman's calling you
the next Carrie Underwood.
- Really?
- Yes.
You're on their
"Top Ten Country Artists to Watch" list.
- Was Beau on the list?
- Yes.
"The next Townes Van Zandt." Who's that?
- He was a singer-songwriter.
- Was he famous?
In some circles, but not nearly as famous
as Carrie Underwood.
How did you know?
How did you know I had it in me?
I just took one look at you, darling. I mean,
you might as well be holding up a stop sign.
Most people just pass right through.
Yeah, well, they'll regret it.
I promise you that.
Well, you just got to figure out
another pickup line.
Hi, Beau.
- Did you have a good time last night?
- Yeah. Sure.
Yeah, that's good.
I finished your lyrics for you. There they are.
God, how did you ever find the time?
You be quiet, Beau Hutton.
Chiles, me and the guys here,
we were talking about that year
MacArthur returned back to the Philippines.
Just none of us could think of
when that was. When was that?
Are you making fun of me, Beau?
Well, I don't know.
Let me check my flash card.
Yes, I am.
You're an asshole, man.
What are you doing here?
- You're not supposed to be here.
- Yeah, well,
I just looked for the biggest shit-hole bar
in town and there you were, Beau.
You're not that hard to figure out.
I thought you didn't want anything else
to do with me.
I'm waving a white flag.
I got a surprise for you.
Come on, Winnie's waiting for us out front.
Come on!
Seriously?
Yeah. You gotta to learn your way around
a recording studio.
After Dallas, your fans
are going to want to buy something.
What's going on?
What are you doing here, Kelly?
That's my song.
I know you liked the song, baby,
but Bob sent some other songs over
that were much better, much more
appropriate for you. I liked them a lot.
This song, it was too, I don't know what.
- It was just too...
- Too what?
Too good? Too young? What?
It wasn't right for you.
I get it.
You can't expect to be the toast of the town
after the way you've acted.
Believe me, you've made it perfectly clear
that I'm not the toast of anyone's town.
- Kelly, listen.
- Get off of me!
Hey.
Leave me alone, James.
Kell, I got somebody out here
who wants to see you, okay?
Who?
Look here.
She's been asking for you all day.
Loretta Lynn.
I'm busy, you know, today, and...
I thought you could take her back
to the hotel with you, take care of her.
You're just trying to make me feel better.
I got to run over to Stanley's this afternoon
and I can't take her with me.
They won't allow it.
You know? So...
It would help.
Oh, my God, James.
- She's so tiny.
- Yeah, she is, isn't she?
She gets hungry really fast.
So, you should probably come on out.
Okay.
All right.
You must not think I'm much of a man.
I never said that.
I don't always dance for her, you know?
I know.
She used to be tough as nails.
What happened to her?
I don't know.
She had a fire in her.
The only place she wanted to be
was on stage.
That was it.
I don't know when she got
so goddamn fragile.
Maybe she's done.
No. No, I can't let her go out like this.
Then, let's just stop her right now.
Before it gets any worse.
- No. No.
- Just turn the bus around
and put her back in rehab.
It might get better. She can get stronger.
You and I both know
she's not getting any better.
You're just talking like her sponsor.
You and I both know
I was never her sponsor.
- Where's Kell?
- She told me she was going to pick you up.
Shake it, girl!
Kelly, come on. Come on, time to go.
- Beau! Beau!
- Get down.
Hey! Just give her a break, guys.
- We're just having a good time with her.
- Stop it!
Just listen to me.
- How dare you do that to me?
- I don't give a shit!
Can you get down here now, Chiles?
It's Miss Kitty's on 38th 1/2.
How dare you? Those people are my friends!
- Because I need your help.
- Come in here
- and pull me out of a bar.
- I don't care.
- Just take a cab and pull around back.
- Who do you think you are?
You're just somebody's daughter,
aren't you?
Yes, I guess I am.
Whose daughter are you?
Her name is Sandy. I'm Sandy's daughter.
She must have done a real number on you.
Yes, ma'am, she did.
Don't call me "ma'am."
Sorry.
I always wanted a daughter.
You did?
I will, one day.
I'm going to have a daughter
and treat her just like fine china.
I'll tell her how smart she is.
And I'm going to let her drive
whenever she wants.
And I'll let her get her ears pierced.
I will.
I got my ears pierced when I was six.
I had my eye on
these beautiful diamond stars.
I told myself they were diamonds,
but I'm pretty sure they were just CZs.
My mom said I had to get
the starting-out earrings
and those were just boring old gold balls.
You know, just the real plain ones.
She said I could change them out
if I was responsible enough to clean them,
but she never let me.
- Well, they sound real pretty.
- Yeah, they were real pretty.
I think you can have one hell of a career
if you want one.
I want one.
I know you do.
Be nice to Beau, okay?
He thinks he's so tough.
But I ain't ever had a man
be so gentle with me.
He's one of the good ones.
He's one of the only good ones.
Does this mean we're friends?
No, sweetheart.
It don't mean a thing.
Kelly! Kelly! Kelly!
Where in the hell have y'all been?
Hey! Hey!
Get a hold of yourself! Come on!
Get it together!
Let her alone, James. She's sick.
JJ, she's fine.
- She's a little under the weather.
- She's done. We're done.
The sponsor's been pulled. The show is over.
JJ, look. You can fix this.
You know them well. They trust you.
- We go back a long way.
- I just lost a quarter of a million
in return tickets.
I'm probably not the person you want to ask.
JJ, come on. It's not all about money!
I cannot believe we fell for this shit again.
- We got to have Dallas.
- She's done.
How y'all doing tonight?
Thank you very much for waiting.
I have a special surprise for you.
It's a new song,
and I'm going to need my friend,
Chiles Stanton,
to come out and sing this with me.
No.
She's a very talented songwriter
and this is her song.
Will you please welcome to the stage,
Miss Chiles Stanton.
Come on.
What the hell are you doing?
Hi, everybody.
This is our first time singing it,
so please be kind to us.
I have sources that say alcohol was involved.
I don't know anything about that.
Thousands of people paid their hard-earned
money to see Kelly perform tonight,
and they're walking away disappointed.
What do you say to that?
I'd say I expect a little more loyalty.
Kelly?
- Get out of here, Beau.
- Get the hell out, kid!
What the hell did you say?
- She's not your wife!
- Yeah, she ain't yours, either!
Get the hell out of here,
you goddamn asshole!
- Do you feel tough now?
- Get dressed, Kelly.
You're the only one
that's good enough for me, is that it?
No, but I'm a hell of a lot better
than that asshole.
You're no better than him at all.
Do you think he gives a shit about you?
Do you think you give a shit about me?
Knocking on my door every goddamn day!
If you gave a shit about me, you would
have left me alone in the first place!
I'm here for you
and you're just too dumb to realise it.
- You just want what you can get.
- Give me the bottle, Kelly.
- Give it to me!
- No more.
- Give it!
Why did you do that?
I'm tired.
Come on, let's get you to bed.
I'm sorry.
PBR.
Dallas is going to be cancelled, isn't it?
She's crazy.
She's not crazy.
She's the only honest one here.
Why are you here, Chiles?
- I don't know.
- I'm tired.
- Wait!
- Wait, what?
Do you want to come in?
Stop it.
- Fine.
- Wait! Don't...
Don't make me say it.
Say what?
You're being very rude right now.
Tell me what you want.
Nothing.
Where are you going?
They found Loretta Lynn's box at the bar.
They were going to throw her out
with the garbage.
I'm going to give her to
somebody who can take care of her.
I thought we had that Make A Wish thing
today at noon.
It doesn't matter any more.
You don't have to do it.
Hey, I talked to JJ.
He's going to let us have Dallas.
I can't imagine why.
What if I told you I was never Miss Dallas?
I'd probably like you even more. Were you?
I almost was.
What happened?
I choked.
Like always.
They asked me what my stance
on global warming was,
and all I could think of was a planet
in a big, old sweater
my grandma used to make me.
I'm sure that would have kept
the whole world nice and warm.
Do you still like me?
I still like you.
- I'm serious, Beau.
- I still like you.
But I'm not what I seem.
Well, maybe that's what I like about you.
- Did you ever think of that?
- No.
Maybe that's what makes you different
from all those other pretty pennies out there.
It's just going to be a few minutes
of your time, okay, Mrs Canter?
Just take a couple of photos with the boy
and we'll have you on your way.
- Okay.
- It's right down here.
- Do you need a coffee?
- No, I'm fine. Thank you.
Hi.
Thank you so much for coming.
It just means the world to us.
It's my pleasure. Thank you. Which one is...
- Is that Travis there?
- He's right over there.
Okay.
- Hi.
- Are you Travis?
- Yes.
- Do you mind if I sit down?
- No.
Okay.
- Hi.
- Is this your class?
- Yes.
- Do you have any fun in here?
You do?
- That's good. Thanks for inviting me.
- You're welcome.
Tell her how much
you love her music, Travis.
Are you going to play a song for me?
What? Am I going to play a song for you?
- No, you don't have to.
- Yes, I am.
I am. That's why I brought my guys.
Come on in, guys.
There's just one little thing
which is, I wrote this new song,
and I'm not sure if it's any good, so I was...
Thanks.
I was hoping that I could play it for you
and you tell me what you think, okay?
Okay.
It's called Travis.
And it goes like this.
- What did you think?
- Is it over?
Travis. I'm sorry.
Is it... No. No, it's not, is it? No.
We got a whole other part. Don't we, guys?
And it goes like...
What do you say?
Would you dance with me for real?
You would? Oh, my gosh.
Come on, boys, bring it home.
This is my lucky day.
Oh, my gosh. Okay.
Show me what you got.
Come on, guys!
Are you going to dance with us?
Let's see your moves on the floor now.
Oh, yeah. I like those moves.
Okay, bring it home for me.
Yeah.
I'm Nick Beres reporting live
outside the downtown arena
where country music superstar Kelly Canter
is set to arrive any moment.
Mrs Canter came down
with food poisoning in Houston.
She didn't show up in Austin.
But her fans here have not given up hope.
Almost a year ago today,
Kelly Canter performed
at this very same arena
in what became the most talked about
performance of the year.
Mrs Canter, who was five months pregnant,
tripped over a microphone cord
and fell 10 feet off the edge of the stage.
She had a blood-alcohol level
of.19 at the time.
She's hit rock bottom.
And sometimes you have to hit rock bottom
to realise what you had.
And I think she's going to come back.
Better than ever.
I was here last year
when it all fell apart for Kelly.
I mean,
how many chances can someone get?
I don't know. Let's ask the fans out there.
What do you think?
Are you ready to hear Kelly's big encore?
- You can't afford these.
- Don't worry about that.
- I can't take these.
- Put them on.
- No.
- Put them on. I want to see them on.
Better than gold balls?
Yeah.
I'm leaving after the show,
heading to California.
Why?
There's an opportunity for me out there.
A friend of a friend
has got a ranch on the beach
and needs somebody to help him out.
Somebody like you.
And you.
- What about our music?
- That's the best part.
There's this bar right in the centre of town
that just lost its Saturday night lineup,
and I know it's not a 10-city tour or anything,
but it's a bunch of hard-working people
that like to listen to good music
while they drink their beer.
I just figured
maybe we could write during the day,
see if we come up with anything,
enough to write an album.
I already have enough songs
to make an album.
If you want to sing those country pop songs,
you go right ahead.
- But you're better than that, Chiles.
- No, I'm not.
Yes, you are. I swear it. Just because
they might put them on the radio
it doesn't mean they're worth a damn.
I've never seen the beach before.
So come with me.
Okay.
You will?
- We're ready for you, Beau.
- All right.
Okay.
Beau.
What if you gave me a little time
to think about it?
You take all the time you need.
Good evening, Dallas.
Welcome to the Kelly Canter Encore Tour.
Now, to start things off,
let's hear it for the man you fell in love with
back in Nashville,
Beau Hutton!
I love you, Beau!
I'd like to dedicate this first song
to Kelly Canter.
She's the reason I'm here. She's a true talent.
This one's not on the set list,
but that doesn't mean it isn't pretty.
This one's for you, Kelly.
Pretty.
Thank you.
- You got a pen and paper?
- Yeah, sure.
I've been thinking of some things
that I want to tell you.
Okay.
Don't ever wear satin on stage
'cause it wrinkles like anything,
and your sweat will show right through it,
I don't care how pretty the dress is.
Always travel with your costumes
and if anything ever needs mending,
send it to Arturo in Beverly Hills.
He's the best.
Don't take laxatives ever
because they never work
the way you want them to.
Don't drink anything carbonated
on a show day.
Okay? It'll make you bloat.
Wear high heels everywhere you go.
And when it comes to
writing your own songs,
don't get too concerned about it, all right?
Your motto should always be,
"The best song wins."
And don't be afraid to fall in love.
It's the only thing that matters in life.
The only thing.
Do you understand what I'm telling you?
Yeah.
You just fall in love
with as many things as possible.
You're going to have to find a way
to tell people about your parents
'cause they're not school teachers, are they?
Have either one of them been in prison
for anything violent?
Yeah.
Are they out?
My mom is.
Well, you got to work with a publicist
and decide the best way to get it out.
You never want to hide anything
from your fans. It's just not worth it.
Okay?
Okay.
How did you know?
I just had a feeling.
Thank you very much.
We got somebody special coming up.
I want you to give a warm welcome
to Miss Chiles Stanton.
Wow. That is a welcome dreams are made of.
Thank y'all so much.
Mr Beau Hutton, everyone. Isn't he the best?
Hey. Thanks for the song.
You might have been the only one
that liked it.
Come on, now.
- I guess they're not buying the bad shrimp.
- Yeah, I guess not.
- Do you think I'm crazy?
- No.
I just don't think love and fame
can live in the same place.
I loved that baby, too, Beau.
I was sadder than anybody when I lost it.
I can't change my past.
You know? I can't change how much I drank.
I'm stronger than all this.
You know that, right?
I know.
I'm going to give them one hell of a show.
I thought you would.
Come here.
You got a full house out there.
I heard.
I've never loved anybody like I loved you.
You know that, right?
Let's just get through tonight, okay?
Hey, Dove.
Give them hell tonight, okay?
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's welcome back to Dallas
the lady you've been waiting to see,
the belle of Bristol, six-time Grammy winner,
country superstar Kelly Canter.
Yeah!
That's how it's done, sweetheart.
Okay?
Okay, we got The Chronicle here.
They want pictures. Chiles, you, too.
Earlier tonight,
this stadium pulsed with excitement
over an incredible performance
by country superstar Kelly Canter.
But it still begs the inevitable question,
"How long will her sobriety last?"
Fill it up! Let's go!
- James.
- Yeah.
Hi. What can we expect next from Kelly?
Well, more songs, more shows,
and a hell of a lot more
of what we saw tonight.
- Beau, look this way!
- Beau, right here!
Well done, James. It looks like Kelly's
going to get her encore after all.
Well, now, we couldn't have done it
without you, could we?
Thanks, man. I'll see you in Nashville.
We'll talk about some more dates.
Yeah, JJ. All right. Yeah, thanks.
- Who needs a drink?
- Right here. One for me, one for you.
Next week, I'm recording my new single,
and hopefully continuing
on this amazing tour.
- Hey, Beau.
- Where's Kell?
Jesse Clark of Country FM.
She's just cleaning up a bit.
She'll be back out.
Great set. How does it feel
to have your career change overnight?
Kell? Kell...
Kell? Kell. Kelly!
Kelly. Hey, Kelly.
What did you take?
Kelly, how many did you take? Kelly!
Come on, wake up. Wake up.
How many did you take, Kelly?
Dear Beau.
You once told me that love and fame
can't live in the same place.
If that is true,
there's only one choice to make,
especially for someone as gentle
and loving as you.
I don't regret a single moment
we spent together.
You filled my last days with true happiness.
So choose love.
Take off and don't look back.
Because there is no one
more worthy of love than you.
Waylon said it best when he sang to Willie.
"If you see me getting smaller,
I'm leaving, don't be grieving.
"I just got to get away from here.
"If you see me getting smaller,
don't worry, I'm in no hurry.
"I've got the right to disappear."
Thank you. Thank you all for coming out
tonight on a Saturday night.
You've been real kind.
- Play another one, Beau.
- All right, then.
This one's called Chances Are.
Well, goddamn.
I'd like to bring a friend on stage,
a wonderful songwriter I met in Nashville.
She just so happens to be here tonight.
Will you welcome to the stage
Miss Chiles Stanton.
And this one's called Give In To Me.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player