We're just about ready
to go here.
Good.
I'm looking for James.
Has anybody seen James Ballard?
Do you know who I mean?
The producer of this epic?
I think I saw him
in the camera room.
James, are you in there?
Can we get your stamp of
approval on our steadicam shot?
Of course.
Be there in a minute.
Where were you?
In a private aircraft hangar.
Anyone could've walked in.
Did you come?
No.
What about your camera girl?
Did she come?
We were interrupted.
I had to go back to the set.
Poor darling.
Maybe the next one.
Shit.
Not a lot of action here.
Have you considered this
would be the airport hospital?
This ward is reserved
for air crash victims.
The beds are kept waiting.
Well, if I ground it during
my flying lesson Saturday...
you might wake up
and find me next to you.
You're getting out of bed soon.
They want you to walk.
The other man, the dead man?
His wife's a doctor.
Dr. Helen Remington.
She's here somewhere...
as a patient, of course.
Maybe you'll find her
in the hallways...
during one of your walks.
And her husband, what was he?
A chemical engineer
for a food company.
Where's... where's the car?
Outside, in the visitors
car park.
What?
They brought the car here?
My car. Not yours.
Yours is a complete wreck.
Police had to drag it
to the pound.
It's behind the station.
After being bombarded
endlessly...
by road safety propaganda,
it's...
almost a relief to have...
found myself
in an actual accident.
Dr. Remington?
James Ballard?
Yes.
Crash victim?
Yes. I'd...
We'll deal with these later.
Both of the front wheels
of their car and the engine...
were driven back
into the driver's section,
pulling the floor.
Blood still marked the hood...
like little streamers
of black lace...
running towards
the windshield wiper gutters.
Bloody flecks were spattered...
across the seat
and steering wheel.
And the instrument panel
was buckled inwards...
cracking the clock
and speedometer dials.
The cabin was deformed.
And there was dust and glass...
and plastic flakes
everywhere inside.
The carpeting was damp.
It stank of blood and other body
and machine fluids.
You should've gone
to the funeral.
I wish I had.
They bury the dead so quickly.
They should leave them
lying around for months.
What about his wife?
The woman doctor?
Have you been to visit her yet?
No.
I couldn't.
I feel too close to her.
I don't like the idea of
your getting into a car so soon.
I can't sit
on this balcony forever.
I feel like a potted plant.
How can you drive, James?
You can barely walk.
Is traffic heavier now?
There seem to be
three times as many cars...
as there were
before the accident.
I have to leave for work.
After this sort of thing...
how do people manage
to look at a car...
let alone drive one?
I'm trying to find Charles' car.
It's not here.
Maybe the police
are still holding it.
They said it was here.
They told me this morning.
This is your car?
You might tear your glove.
I never should've come here.
I'm surprised the police
don't make it more difficult.
Were you badly hurt?
I think we saw each other
at the hospital.
I don't want the car.
In fact,
I was appalled to find...
that I have to pay
to have it scrapped.
Can I give you a lift?
I somehow find myself
driving again.
You haven't told me
where we're going.
I haven't?
To the airport,
if you don't mind.
The airport?
Why? Are you leaving?
Not yet.
Though not soon enough
for some people.
A death in the doctor's family
makes the patients uneasy.
I take it you're not wearing
white to reassure them.
I'll wear a fucking kimono
if I want to.
So why the airport?
I work in
the lmmigration Department.
Do you want a cigarette?
No.
I started to smoke
at the hospital.
It's kind of stupid.
Look at all this traffic.
I'm not sure I can deal with it.
It's much worse now.
Have you noticed that?
Yes.
The day I left the hospital...
I had the extraordinary
feeling that all these cars...
were gathering
for some special reason...
I didn't understand.
There seemed to be
ten times as much traffic.
Are we imagining it?
You've bought yourself
exactly the same car again.
It's the same shape and color.
We're close
to the airport garage.
It won't be busy
this time of day.
"Don't worry.
That guy's gotta see us."
These were
the confident last words...
of the brilliant, young
Hollywood star James Dean...
as he piloted his Porsche
550 Spyder race car...
toward a date with death...
along a lonely stretch...
of California
two-lane blacktop...
Route 466.
"Don't worry.
That guy's gotta see us."
The year... 1955.
The day... September 30.
The time...
Now.
The first star of our show
is "Little Bastard."
James Dean's racing Porsche.
He named it after himself...
and had his racing number...
130... painted on it.
Who is that, the announcer?
Do I know him?
Here behind the seats was...
a very sophisticated air-cooled
four-cylinder racing engine.
That's Vaughan.
He spoke to you at the hospital.
I thought he was
a medical photographer...
doing some sort of
accident research.
He wanted every conceivable
detail about our crash.
Body... light,
no more than 1,350 pounds.
It was nimble.
It was responsive.
When I first met Vaughan,
he was a specialist...
in international
computerized traffic systems.
The racers of the day...
said that it was not
an easy car to drive fast.
I don't know what he is now.
Which brings us
to the second star...
a stunt man, former
race driver Colin Seagrave.
Colin Seagrave.
He will drive our replica
of James Dean's car.
How you doing?
Sure you're up for this?
You bet.
I myself shall play the role
of Dean's racing mechanic...
Rolf Voudrich, sent over
from the Porsche factory...
in Zuffenhausen, Germany.
Now, this mechanic
was himself fated to die...
in a car crash in Germany
26 years later.
The third,
and in some ways...
most important player...
the college student,
Donald Turnipseed...
played by movie stunt man
Brett Trask.
Turnipseed was on his way home
to Fresno for the weekend.
James Dean was on his way to
an automobile race in Salinas.
Salinas was just a dusty town
in Northern California.
The two would meet
for one moment.
But it was a moment that...
that would create
a Hollywood legend.
You'll notice that
we're not wearing helmets...
or safety padding of any kind.
Our cars are not equipped
with roll cages or seat belts.
We rely solely on the skill
of our drivers for our safety...
so that we can bring you
the ultimate in authenticity.
All right.
Here we go...
the fatal crash of James Dean.
OK, let's wind her up.
Go.
Is this part of the act,
or are they really hurt?
I don't know.
You can never
be sure with Vaughan.
This is his show.
Rolf Voudrich...
was thrown from the Porsche...
and spent a year...
in the hospital...
recovering from his injuries.
Donald Turnipseed
was found wandering around...
in a daze but basically unhurt.
James Dean
died of a broken neck...
and became immortal.
What's the matter?
Hold me up. I'm dizzy.
I can't stand.
I know that man... Seagrave.
I think he's genuinely hurt.
Disperse at once.
You're all liable for fines
or arrest.
Disperse at once.
- How you doin'?
- I'm all right.
What's the matter with Seagrave?
He hit his head, I think.
His balance is off.
Why are the police
taking this so seriously?
No, it's not the police.
It's the Department
of Transport.
It's a big joke.
They have no idea
who we really are.
Was I glib?
"James Dean died of a broken
neck and became immortal."
I couldn't resist.
Oh, God.
What happened?
Come here. Lie down.
They did the James Dean crash.
It seemed to go perfectly,
but then...
he started to feel nauseous
on the way back.
I'm sure it's a concussion.
Well, we're familiar enough
with that then, aren't we?
Seagrave.
Seagrave,
I really would like to...
work out the details...
of the Jayne Mansfield
crash with you.
We could...
We could do the...
the decapitation.
The head embedded
in the windshield.
The world record is
a whopping forty-two pounds.
And the dead dog thing,
you know?
You know, the Chihuahua
in the back seat?
I got it all worked out.
I'll be ready, Vaughan.
I want really big tits.
Out to here.
So the audience can see 'em
get all cut up...
and crushed on the dashboard.
Yeah, we'll do that.
Ballard...
I need your help.
Do you live here with Seagrave?
No. I live in my car.
This is my workshop.
This is my new project.
You recognize her?
That's Gabrielle.
That's her right outside
the door there.
I thought you might be
missing these.
Right.
So here you are
at the nerve center.
Vaughan makes everything
look like a crime, doesn't he?
What exactly
is your project, Vaughan?
Book of car crashes?
Medical study?
Sensational documentary?
Global traffic?
It's something...
we are all intimately
involved in.
The reshaping of the human body
by modern technology.
Nothing.
It's a Sunday, man.
She's desperate.
No, I'm not.
The length?
'Cause I'm not gonna
hold the sets that long.
He must have fucked a lot of
women in that huge car of his.
It's like a bed on wheels.
It must smell of semen.
It does.
Do you find him attractive?
He's very pale.
Covered with scars.
Would you like
to fuck him, though...
in that car?
No.
But...
But when he's in that car...
Have you seen his penis?
I think it's badly scarred...
from a motorcycle accident.
Is he circumcised?
Can you imagine
what his anus looks like?
Describe it to me.
Would you like to sodomize him?
Would you like to put your penis
right into his anus?
Just thrust it up his anus?
Tell me.
Describe it to me.
Tell me what you would do.
Could you just kiss him
in that car?
Describe how you reach over.
Unzip his greasy jeans.
Take out his penis.
Would you kiss it
or suck it right away?
Which hand would you...
Which hand
would you hold it in?
Have you ever sucked a penis?
Do you know
what semen tastes like?
Have you ever tasted semen?
Some semen
is saltier than others.
Vaughan's semen
must be very salty.
Have you come?
I'm all right.
Finish your story.
The junior pathologist
at Ashford Hospital...
then the husband
of a colleague of mine.
A trainee radiologist...
then the service manager
at my garage.
You had sex
with all those men in cars?
Only in cars?
Yes. I didn't plan it that way.
Did you fantasize that Vaughan
was photographing...
all these sex acts as though
they were traffic accidents?
Yes.
They felt
like traffic accidents.
Now...
We must accumulate
all the paper we can about her.
Some of the stuff that Helen
brought back is terrific...
tolerances of the human face
in crash impacts...
mechanisms of...
Now, where is the...
I'm sure we see this again
in slow motion.
Closer, I mean...
in detail.
We can watch another tape.
We brought lots of tapes.
No. L... I know this tape.
I know this tape.
That tape player's fucked.
That's what it is.
It always does that.
You're upset.
No. I'm all right.
I'm all right now.
I've always wanted
to drive a crash car.
You could get your wish
at any moment.
No. I mean a crash car
with a history.
Camus' Fassellvega...
Nathaniel West's
station wagon...
Grace Kelly's Rover 3500.
Just fix it enough
to get it rolling.
Don't clean it.
Don't touch anything else.
Is that why you drive this car?
Do you see Kennedy's
assassination...
as a special kind of car crash?
A case could be made.
Whoa! Watch this!
You're gonna hit him.
Oh, God.
Here. Take a look at this.
Tell me what you think of these.
You recognize this one.
This is James Dean.
This is the next one
Seagrave and I are gonna do...
Jayne Mansfield.
It's all very satisfying.
I'm not sure I understand why.
That's the future, Ballard...
and you're already a part of it.
You're beginning to see
that for the first time...
there's a benevolent
psychopathology...
that beckons towards us.
For example, the car crash
is a fertilizing...
rather than a destructive event.
A liberation of sexual energy...
mediating the sexuality
of those who have died...
with an intensity that's
impossible in any other form.
Now, to experience that...
to live that, that is...
That's my project.
What about reshaping the human
body by modern technology?
I thought that was your project.
That's just
a crude sci-fi concept.
It just kind of
floats on the surface...
and doesn't threaten anybody.
I use it to test
the resilience...
of my potential partners
in psychopathology.
- What's going on, baby?
- What's going on with you?
- Want to go for a ride?
- You and your friend?
- Just me and my friend here.
- That's cool.
- Don't go away.
- What you got under there?
- I'm clean.
- You got a place?
- The back seat of my car.
- In your car?
- He'll drive.
- We'll go driving around?
- Absolutely. $60.
- $60?
You'll get a nice scenic ride.
One fifty for the two.
- No. It's just me.
- Just you?
If he does get involved,
I'll give you 150.
- Maybe.
- What do you mean?
I'm saying, is he all right?
Come here, sweetie.
You open your mouth.
- Yes, Daddy.
- There you go.
I don't want you blowing
it up my urethra.
James, you drive.
James, we're leaving now.
Do you want a lift?
No, thank you.
What's going on?
They're questioning him about
an accident at the airport.
A pedestrian was killed.
They think he was
run over intentionally.
Vaughan isn't interested
in pedestrians.
Don't you think
he looks a bit shaky?
- Maybe I should drive him.
- Where's your car?
At home.
Couldn't face the traffic.
Why don't I drive?
You coming?
- Third westbound at Jameson.
- 793, Control. I'm 10-17.
Please advise the ambulance
that three lanes are...
Let's record this.
This is a work of art.
Absolutely a work of art.
Slow down.
Slow down. Not so fast.
Slow down. Stop.
You couldn't wait for me?
You did the Jayne Mansfield
crash without me?
Oh, the dog.
The dog is brilliant.
I must have driven
through something.
There's some blood on the car
here on the handle...
and on the wheel,
and also the wheel well.
See?
If the police stop you again,
they may impound the car.
You're right, Ballard.
There's an all-night car wash
by the airport service area.
Watch yourself.
Is there something here
that interests you?
This interests me.
I'd like to see
if I can fit into a car...
designed for a normal body.
Could you help me
into it, please?
Yeah, sure.
Are these safe cars?
Yes, of course.
They're very safe.
I'm caught.
Oh, shit.
Fuck. This is bad.
This is really bad.
James, somebody named Vaughan.
You want it?
Hello. Ballard.
I need to see you, Ballard.
I need to talk to you
about the project.
Where are you?
I think you're making it
too clean.
Medical tattoos
are supposed to be clean.
But this is not
a medical tattoo.
This is a prophetic tattoo.
And prophecy's ragged
and dirty...
so make it ragged and dirty.
Prophetic?
Is this personal prophecy
or global prophecy?
There's no difference.
Let me see here. Where is it?
James, I want you to let her
give you this one.
Where do you think
that one should go?
I thought that was you up there.
My last lesson's next week.
James, my car is...
What?
Could it have been deliberate?
One of your suitors?
It was Vaughan.
The traffic.
Where is everyone?
They've all gone away.
I'd like to go back, James.
He came from up there, overhead!
I'd like to register a claim
for the 1963 black Lincoln.
Is there a form
I should fill out?
I can give you the forms now...
but you'll have to come back
between 7:30 and 4:30...
to register a claim.
What's your attachment
to that thing?
A close friend owned it.
It's a total write-off.
I don't see what you
can possibly do with it.
Are you all right?
I don't know.
Are you hurt?
I think I'm all right.
Maybe the next one, darling.
Maybe the next one.