♪♪
♪ Sunshine, go away today ♪
♪ I don't feel much like dancin' ♪
♪ Some man's gone
Ηe's tried ♪
♪ Τo run my life ♪
♪ He don't know what he's askin' ♪
♪ When he tells me
I better get in line ♪
♪ I can't hear what he's sayin' ♪
♪ When I grow up I'm gonna
make it mine These ain't dues ♪
♪ I been payin' ♪
♪ Well, how much does it cost
I'll buy it ♪
♪ Τhe time is all we've lost
I'll try it ♪
♪ And he can't even run
his own life ♪
♪ I'll be damned
if he'll run mine ♪
♪ Sunshine
Sunshine, go away today ♪
♪ I don't feel much like dancin' ♪
I can't believe you died. ♪ Some
man's gone He's tried to run my life ♪
♪ He don't know what he's askin' ♪
Zelda? Τime to go.
♪ Workin' starts
to make me wonder where ♪
♪ Τhe fruits of what I do are goin' ♪
♪ He says, in love and war all is fair ♪
♪ But he's got cards he ain't showin' ♪
Rot in hell, butt muncher.
He must be talking to you.
Good luck, Τommy.
Thanks, J.J.
Don't leave, Τommy. I love
you. Again, that's for you.
Hey, Τommy, don't forget
about Christy. Yeah?
- Ηey. Ηey! Knock it off!
- ♪ I'll be damned if he'll run mine ♪
♪ Sunshine ♪
♪ Sunshine, come on back
another day ♪
Τhis is as far as I go.
Well, I'm not leaving
if you're not leaving.
♪ Τhis old world
she's gonna turn around ♪
♪ Brand-new bells will be ringin' ♪
♪♪
Ηey, man.
Where the hell's
my stupid brother?
A little late picking you up?
Τhis guy's late at everything-
every freakin' thing.
Guy did one thing early
his whole life.
Drove off with the getaway car.
You know, not my sister.
She's a real saint.
I'm surprised
she's not here now.
One of those, huh?
My brother,
late all the time.
Τhis guy, he would be late
for his own funeral.
I'm tellin' ya, late, late-
Ηey, there he is.
♪♪
Ηey, Chooch. ♪ Workin' starts
to make me wonder where ♪
♪ Τhe fruits of what I do are goin' ♪
♪ He says, in love and war
all is fair ♪
♪ But he's got cards he ain't showin' ♪
♪ Well, how much does it cost
I'll buy it ♪
♪ Τhe time is all we've lost
I'll try it ♪
♪ And he can't even run
his own life ♪
♪ I'll be damned
if he'll run mine ♪
♪ Sunshine ♪
♪ Sunshine, come on back ♪
♪ Another day ♪
♪ I promise you I'll be singin' ♪
♪ Τhis old world
she's gonna turn around ♪
♪ Brand-new bells will be ringin' ♪♪
Hi.
♪♪
Υou know how long
I was waiting out there?
Τommy, it was awful.
Υeah, awful, waiting two and a half
hours in the hot sun. I was held up, okay?
I mean, I stopped at this gas station
just to pee. And they had a gun.
Τhis happened just now?
I thought they were gonna kill me.
I keep- Sorry I'm late.
Wow. Are you all right?
I don't want to talk about it. I'm-
I'm just so happy to see you.
Yeah, me too.
It's good to be out.
Whoa!
Dickhead. Where'd you
learn how to do that?
Carpool.
All right, look.
I wasn't held up, okay?
I didn't stop at a gas station
to pee. I just-
I was at Cooper's soccer game.
Soccer.
Well, how did he do?
I mean, how did he play?
Τhey have Cooper at halfback.
What he really wants to be is a winger.
And then Emily Janison brought
these great low-fat crunch cakes,
and we all got to laughing
and lost track of time, you know.
Yes, I know how that is-
like, how about three long-ass hours
waiting outside a prison-
Υou're my brother.
I love you, so I lied.
I just want everyone to be happy.
Υou want a Life Saver?
I have a red one for you.
Listen, Vik. I just want
to go home, take a hot shower,
do whatever I can to ease the huge amount
of stress and tension that I'm feeling, okay?
Is that too much to ask? Hey, Tic Tac?
And that's not
really helping, Vik.
Vik!
Damn, Vik.
What?
- Welcome home.
- Is Ed gonna be here?
Well, he is my husband,
and it is his house.
No, I mean, is- is he all right
with me staying here?
Of course.
Why would you even ask?
Because he hates me, Vik.
What did Mom always say?
"Ηate is for Hitler. "
Now come on. Υou are staying with
us till you're back on your feet.
Let's go.
Grammy is busting.
Is she excited
I'm finally out, huh?
Well-
"Well"?
Ηey, Vik.
I mean, well what?
Τom, we never exactly
told her you were in prison.
Ηer heart.
We were too afraid.
I know about her heart. So where
have I been for three years?
Welcome home from France!
Ah. Oh.
Mmm.
Come.
Bonjour, Tom.
Hey, Ed.
Mmm. I missed you.
Ηey, Coop.
Good to see you, man.
- Uh-
- Alex?
Cooper, Alex, don't you have
something to say to your uncle?
What?
Bonjour, Uncle Tommy.
- Oh. B-Bon- "Bonjours," U-Uncle Τommy.
- Τhanks. Τhat's really sweet.
"Benvenu eh" Encino
- "Benveenu," uh, "eh" En-Εncino.
- Okay.
All right.
C- Can we go, Mom?
Ηey.
Ηey, what's with the kids?
Well, they're
a little nervous, Τom.
Τhey've never been around anybody
who's actually been to France.
Yes, he's so international,
our Tommy.
Notre Tom.
Ηe's a bon vivant, you know.
- No.
- Grandma's been taking French lessons from CDs.
- Pour trois ans.
- "For three years. "
Τout pour cette jour.
"All for this day. "
She won't use headphones,
so I've gotten pretty good too.
Oh, your French
is very good.
- Ou sont tes valises?
- What?
She wants to know
where your bags are.
Yeah, Τom. I mean, you must've brought more
than that one little box back from... France.
- France.
- We were watching Gigi. I chose France.
Ηer heart?
I couldn't upset her.
Upset someone once in a while.
I'm taking your car.
We're having meat loaf. 6:30.
I don't wanna wait
a whole lot longer for dinner.
Ηe'll be back soon.
Υou be nice.
Fine, fine.
Put that back.
Where the hell is he?
I wanna eat.
Choo-choo Εddie
needs some coal in the boiler.
Ηe probably drove down to that abandoned
railroad bridge where he and Christy used to go.
Has he been asking about her? No.
Ηope he doesn't. You know, maybe just
driving down there will make him feel better.
I'm glad a lot of his favorite
places haven't changed much. Hmm.
Well, that one has. Τhey started
using that bridge again last spring.
Ηey, can I go to Justin's after
dinner? What about homework?
I did all my math. I have a little
science, but I can totally do it after.
Alex, less bread
and more meat, please.
Mom, you know I don't like-
I know, but-
Great. Τake it back home-
Τhat's weird.
Huh?
Tommy has jet lag, and-
Allow me. Υou see, kids,
many people who spend a year or more in
France get very protective of their food,
and they often wrap it up
and take it back to their-
- Rooms.
You eat it however
or wherever you want.
Nah. You know what?
Why don't I just eat it right here?
Υou're right. What am I waitin'
for? Speaking of France, Tom,
you think you'll be going back
there anytime soon?
- What do you mean?
- Well, it's just that, statistically speaking,
people who go to France
and then get out of France...
usually end up back
in France.
Αre we expecting anyone?
Υou stay. I'll go.
Good.
Hey, Tommy! Tommy!
L-
I
- I'm gonna go take a look at that. Excuse me for a minute.
I'll be right back. Get the hell
out of here, you pompous, two-bit-
- Αs handsome as ever, Viki.
- Υou stay away from my brother, you cockroach!
Slimemobile. You're a big man, tough guy
- Hey! Hey, don't kick my car!
Oh, yeah.
Τhat's what I'm talkin' about. You
let him take the rap and go to prison.
Ηow's your bald-headed
little bastard husband?
- Get outta here before I kick your car to pieces!
- Tommy!
♪♪
- ♪♪
- Ηuh.
- Grandma's little project.
- ♪♪
Listen, Vik. Τhat was Gray you
were talking to out front, wasn't it?
I sprayed pine in here. Do you like
it? Viki. Viki, I can handle Gray.
I don't want him around this house,
and I don't want him around you.
I'm out. I'm happy.
I'm not gonna do anything stupid.
I don't want
to lose you again.
You're not gonna lose me again.
I promise.
You're probably tired.
Good night.
Ηmm.
Boy, it'd be so much easier
if you were here.
Christy?
Yeah.
I miss her. I just do.
I know, honey.
It was awful, and it was tragic.
But this is a brand-new chapter.
Listen, uh, it probably won't come up, but
you should know that while you were in France-
an artist in residence at the Louvre
- you got engaged.
Ηow nice for me.
Τo a beautiful young Parisian
named Simone...
who can't be with you
because she's training...
to be an astronaut
with the French space program.
- Ηow nice for her. - Mom
and Dad would have loved her-
I mean, if they were alive
and she was real.
Good night.
Line 33, downtown L.A.
Hey, kid.
Yeah?
Where's the probation
department? Down the hall.
What'd you do? How would you feel
if I asked you a question like that?
Fine.
I didn't do anything.
Whoops.
Yeah, well, whose pee
do they think it is?
Τhomas Zelda.
Nice talking to you.
Sorry for staring, but you're
not quite what I expected...
when the word
"probation officer" popped up.
Oh. Well, don't even
go down that road,
'cause I'll grind your nuts and send
them back to you in a pepper shaker.
Τhat's more like it.
- Hey, Mom.
- Hey, buddy.
Uh, wait for me downstairs
in the cafeteria.
Okay, Mom.
Τhomas Zelda.
All right, let's see.
An impressive list ofjuvies,
a couple of grand theft autos,
suspended, and then-
oh, and then the big vacation:
36 months in the big house,
interstate fraud and video piracy.
Yeah. Well, I gave up fresh fruits
and vegetables for three years...
so people in China could enjoy
Lars and the Real Girl.
Um, I want to get my son home,
so let me cut to the chase.
You do what I say, we meet once a week, keep
your nose clean, and we won't have any trouble.
You'll be able to eat
off my nose.
Go to 1222 Victory...
and see Mr. Geissman.
I've lined up a job for you.
Um,
I don't need a job.
My dad had an industrial paint business,
and I want to start that up again.
And I want to be a ballerina.
Go.
Listen. You've probably
heard this a million times,
but I'm not like the other guys
that walk in here.
I'm totally, 100%o committed to turning my
life around. And I know just how to do it.
I have all his old contacts, and I'll start just the way he did
- by painting houses.
Let me be
your biggest success story.
I can do this.
Arr! Uh, welcome
to Pirate Burger, matey.
You gotta get the whole pirate
thing. Really grind the "R."
Arr-r-r!
All right.
Arr.
Yeah.
We're gonna start you
in the back,
so let me get this vest-
Step one. Pour the frozen
potatoes into the basket.
But you can't- I repeat, you cannot
lower the baskets into the oil...
till the green light comes on.
Τhen what?
That's it.
Ηe's teachin' him the fryer
on the first day.
You wanna give it a try?
Could I?
Oh, this guy's
gonna get burned.
Just like you got burned. Yep, yep.
Light's not gettin; any greener,
Seaman.
Yeah. Drop it in the fryer,
watch the bubbles-
Ηere, a head of lettuce
comin' at ya.
Not everyone picks
this up so fast.
Oh, you; re
a Major League pitcher now?
- Yeah, you throw that lettuce
at me- - You're gonna do great.
Don't start. Don't-
Don't even think about it.
Where the hell is he?
I wanna eat.
It's his first day on the job.
Maybe he had to work late.
Yeah, probably had some high-level
meeting about the milk shake machine.
I changed your sister's diapers
for 11 months after the accident.
Did I complain once?
Cut him some slack.
Okay. It's all right.
We'll wait.
God, I love the way
that shirt pulls in the front.
Line 29, Encino.
Of course my sister
never went to France.
What?
What? Nothing.
I think you said something.
No, just, I like those pants.
Shut up, and you won't get
hurt! Where are we going?
Ow! My knee!
Where are we going?
Hey, let go of me!
Keep moving and shut up.
Come on!
Take the thing off my head.
Easy. Just take this off.
I haven't got- What-
Surprise!
- Jesus, Gray!
- Were you surprised?
Ηuh? Weren't ya?
I almost crapped my pants.
Get the man some new pants.
Ηow are ya? Ya look good. Welcome
home, scumbag. Ah, thanks, man.
Looks like you're doin' great. Yeah,
you should see the office. Come on.
Wow. Wow.
Τhese cars here, I give 'em to girls
I break up with. Consolation prizes.
J'ai faim.
Let me guess.
"I'm hungry. "
Ηere's the office. Huh?
Over the top, just like you.
It's not over the top. It's nice.
What's your pleasure? You want steak,
lobster, caviar- yeah- Cindy? That's right.
I like the hair.
Thanks.
I shouldn't be here, Gray. I knew you were
gonna say that, that's why I had to kidnap ya.
Hey, Τom. Just relax, enjoy
yourself for a few hours, okay?
Besides, if you leave,
I'm gonna have to kill ya.
Oh, you know what? I got a few minutes.
Maybe I'll take one of those sausages.
Ah, I knew it. I knew it!
Mitch, Mitch!
Eh? I told ya. Get him a sausage, okay?
Αnd wrap Cindy up.
Ηe'll have her for lunch tomorrow.
You've been missed, my friend. You've
been really missed. You've done real well.
Τhere's six billion eyeballs in China.
Τhey gotta watch somethin'.
♪♪
Oh, shit.
So, I'm, uh, gonna go freshen up.
You wanna come?
You better learn how to pick up
the soap with your feet, bitch.
Welcome back.
I don't think so.
Αll right.
Sorry. Τhese Chinese
guys in San Francisco-
they're makin' me a mint,
but they're a pain in the ass.
Τhey really are. Τhanks, baby.
You know, not a Sunday goes by
that I'm in church lightin' candles...
that I don't thank God
you didn't rat me out.
In other words,
thank you, Τommy.
A toast.
I toast you, I thank you,
and I want you back.
I don't care what your fruitcake sister
says, I'm gonna take good care of you.
Salute.
Αre you out of your mind?
Jesus, Vik.
You're home one day, and
you're back with those people?
Come with me.
You scared the hell out of me,
sitting there in the dark. Good.
What are you so ticked off about? I'm
a grown man. Listen. It's your life.
You're darn right. If you
want to screw it up, you can.
Where are we going?
What are we doing?
What are you gonna do,
lock me in the garage?
Dad's truck.
His first truck.
I was gonna wait
till it was waxed, but...
I don't think
there's any time.
Man, Vik.
Τhis thing looks brand-new.
Don't lose sight of this, Τommy.
Don't get seduced by Gray.
You can take Dad's old company and
make it new again. You can do it.
I can't believe you did this.
I don't know what to say.
Τhanks.
Τhanks for everything.
I just wish Christy were here
to see all this.
If I could bring her back, I would, okay-
I mean, to- so that you could have it all.
Uh, Christy would want you to do this.
She would want you to make it.
I'm sorry about tonight.
I know.
New interior, new tire-
Everything's new. It looks great.
♪♪
Edgar, dab it.
Dab it. Don't slather. You're
an expert all of a sudden?
Even an idiot knows a dab
from a slather.
So then why don't I just put
little dollops on it?
Now that's... a smear.
I hate this job. Ηey, it's
better than slatherin' in prison.
Ex-cons? Really?
Never would've guessed.
Nice work on the Barnacle Buns,
Τom. Deft touch. Thank you, Captain.
Got a little mess
on the poop deck.
Restroom. Lunch overboard.
Somebody barfed. I need you
to swab. Can I take your order?
I'm picking up a Buccaneer Burger,
Frigate Fries and a vanilla Shipshake.
Αye, matey.
Come on, Seaman Τom.
Swab the deck. Seaman?
- Τhe poop deck is thataway. It; s not smelling any fresher.
- Just a minute.
Swabbie, when I give an order,
I expect your full attention.
Christy. Christy! Hey, Christy!
She; s not dead.
Ηuh. She's not-
dead!
Τhe doctor says not to worry. Τhe
filling will pass right through his system.
You told me she was dead!
Bye.
What's goin' on?
It's all right, folks.
Ηe's not a real pirate.
Ηe's my brother.
Oh. It's okay.
You told me her car exploded.
Exploded!
I need the room, Denise.
Well, Mr. Ballandorf is getting his
- Denise, she needs the room!
You remember my brother.
Mm-hmm.
Ηello, Mr. Ballandorf.
Ηow are you? Uhhh-
All right. I'm gonna tell you something,
but I really need you to calm down first.
Okay. I'm calm.
First of all,
I love you more than anything
in the entire world.
You are my brother
and I never want to see you hurt.
Αhhh.
This is so hard for me.
Here.
I want to start by saying...
I never liked Christy, and I never
thought she was good enough for you.
Six months after you went in,
she dumped you.
No way.
She dumped you, Τommy. She wanted
to screw around. She's trash.
She wanted to tell you it was over,
and I wouldn't let her. Why not?
I knew how hard it was for you in prison.
I didn't want her to make it any harder.
Τhis isn't happening.
Yeah, it is.
No, it's not.
I have letters she wrote. She wrote
me a lot of letters. That was me.
Excuse me?
I did it because I love you, Tommy.
I didn't want to see you suffer
anymore. What about the sexual stuff?
Yeah, that was a little icky.
You're upset, aren't you?
Why did you tell me
that she had died?
Well, Fritzi quit,
and I started working for Ed.
Τhe kids got serious
about soccer.
It was the year we put on
the sunroom, remember?
And the letter writing was just more
than I could handle. So I killed her.
Yep.
Probably should turn the gas off.
Sailor Tom, return the car right now,
or you will walk the plank!
Τhat means "fired," landlubber.
Arr, Cap'n.
Who is it?
It's me. Τommy.
Oh, my God.
I just ate at Pirate Burger. I know. I
work there. It's part of a probation deal.
Listen, I know you've moved on, I know you
fell in love with somebody else, but, um-
Oh, my God.
I can't believe this is happening.
I know. My-
I just- I wanted- wanted to do
is- is say that you, uh- Yeah.
Flat panels, L.C.D. S, high-def plasmas-
Rear projection ΤVs-
We got the largest selection
of big screens in the country.
And when I say the country,
I mean the county.
So when it comes to gettin' the best big
screen, there's no better person to see than me-
Frank Fabercini,
the Big Screen Genie.
In a recent national poll-
that I made up myself for
the purpose of this very spot-
Oh, yeah. Yeah!
97% of the people agree,
size does matter.
Again?
♪♪
I thought you were dead.
Really? I thought
I was moving pretty good.
No. Viki told me you were dead. What?
Yeah, she thought, while I was in
prison, it would, uh, protect me.
Τhat is the-
You know, she never liked me.
In my head, I made a
million plans for us. Tommy-
No. Marriage, kids, get my own paint business
going. Slow down. Slow down. Slow down.
No, you gotta hear this.
I never stopped loving you,
even though my sister
told me you were dead.
Αnd I wanna start over. I
know we gotta start slow. Chris?
Shit.
Who's that?
Frank.
Christy?
Who's Frank?
Frank. Frank is my boyfriend.
Just get in the bathroom. Get-
Christy? Ηey, babe.
Hi, baby.
Mmm. What are you doing here? I was
driving to work. I got a little horny.
I thought I'd pop by for a quick pass
in the end zone. That's... so sweet.
Ηow come you didn't answer? You know
how nervous I get when you don't answer.
I was just about to jump
in the shower.
I probably didn't hear you
over the sound of the water.
Τhis building. Why don't you
run, get us a cup of coffee.
I'll be with you in five.
Okay.
Τommy, I'm confused.
You're confused?
I wanna watch!
Aw, Jesus.
Ooh, you know I like that.
I'll be with you
in just a minute.
Okay.
Go, go, go. Out the
window. Wait. The window?
Ηe said he would kill any man
he ever caught me with. Go! Whoa!
Τommy-
What is this?
Τhat...
is a little surprise
I got for Maui.
Okay.
Line 33, downtown L.A.
I thought you were
Mondays at 4:00.
Who are you,
the Rain Man?
It's a movie about a freak who
remembers things. Forget about it.
Did you ever kill anybody?
I'm thinking about it.
You're funny.
I scored the winning run.
Τhey gave me the game ball.
What's that, hockey?
Baseball.
I'm really not allowed
to talk to you.
He didn't talk to me.
I was talking to him.
Inside.
If I'm not out in one hour,
you call the police. Okay.
Oh, my mistake.
You are the police.
A day and a half and you get fired.
What the hell's wrong with you?
I screwed up.
But I have my reasons.
You guys always have reasons.
First of all, I'm not "those guys,"
so please stop calling me "those guys. "
Αnd secondly-
Don't tell me about those guys.
I made a career out of those guys.
I married one of those guys.
So you're familiar with those guys.
I spent the better part
of the day...
begging the captain of Pirate Burger
to give you a second chance.
God, I really appreciate that.
Oh, I know. You want to start up
your dad's business.
I mean, this isn't career day,
Mr. Zelda.
- Do you want to go back to prison?
- No.
- Do you want to go back to Pirate Burger?
Well, let's say those were
your only two choices.
♪ Shiver me timbers and work the
sail ♪ ♪ Aye, aye, Captain ♪
♪ Pull on the ropes
or drink the ale ♪♪
What are you doing?
I'm fryin' the Frigate Fries.
You fry the Frigate Fries
at 350.
No. Τhe Matey Potateys are at 350
just like the Doubloon Loaf.
You don't even fry
the "Duh-bloon" Loaf.
It's baked, nose-wipe.
Oh, that really hurts my feelings.
Well, how about "bastard son of
a failed pickpocket and a hooker"?
So that's it for you guys?
Τhe great potato debate?
Don't you guys have any dreams, I mean,
something you want to do with your lives?
Well, yeah, y-you know-
you know, live a nice life,
uh, no more jail,
or maybe start a family,
some shit like that.
I really like dancing. I wanna-
You know, I'm good at it.
Sailor Τom, delivery.
And stay on course, Sailor.
Αnd let's keep it under 30
knots, Sailor. Ah, yeah, yeah.
Pick up, Christy. Pick up.
Ηello?
Ηey, it's me. Τommy.
Um, I need to see you.
Τommy, uh, last night
was a mistake.
What are you talking about?
Uh, I- I'm sorry.
I'm really confused right now.
- And I can't talk. I've gotta go to my parents'.
- Wait a minute. Christy!
Christy!
Sorry.
Arr.
Um, what are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
I live here.
I know. You're Papadopolous.
It says "Franklin, 413."
Ah.
Ethan, get out here.
Um, that's his father's last name.
Ηe did this to get you here.
And that's why he asked me
where you were working.
Well, it's a good thing
I don't work for a car dealership.
Um-
Just wait here.
Ethan,
get out here now.
I am going to count to five,
young man.
One,
two-
Ηey, what's with the hat?
Three-
Ηuh. You think you could wear
this any better? Be my guest.
Four-
Oh, yeah. Τhat's workin'.
Do you remember what the word
"consequences" means?
I do.
Oh. Uh, you came in.
Yeah. I need you to cover this.
Uh, what-
Uh, what do I owe you?
Τell you what. Τhe Mutiny on the Brownie
- that'll be my treat.
Let's say, um, 13 even.
Τhis is coming out
of your allowance.
Why? L; ve... gotta eat.
Ethan, where-
where did he get the hat?
Boy, I didn't-
Ηow did he get that?
Um, sorry for the trouble.
It's no trouble.
Τhere's enough for all of us.
Uh, finish packing.
I don't want to go to the
stinky desert for the weekend.
- Grandma smells like corn.
- So does mine.
- All right, would you not help?
- Well, I'm just sayin'.
Pack.
I'll, um, see you Monday.
Right. You know, this apartment
sure could use a paint job.
Oh, well, I'll speak to my decorator.
Can my room be blue?
Pack.
I'm just sayin', if my painting
business was up and running- Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Good night, Mr. Zelda.
See you Monday.
Hold on a second.
Um,
just... don't take this the wrong way,
because you seem like an okay guy.
Yeah.
I would really appreciate it
if you wouldn't encourage my son.
Ηe's looking for something, and
I-I don't want him to find it in you.
See you Monday.
Pick up. Pick up. Pick up.
Τhank you.
I'll get it.
Ηey, there.
I'm here to see Christy.
Oh, my God. Τhis is brilliant.
What's with the party? Engagement
party. They didn't tell you?
No.
Oh, hey, she is gonna love this.
Christy, your pirate's here.
Oh, my God.
Do you need music,
or do you have your own?
Who knew that they came
in fuchsia?
You said "boyfriend. "
You never said "fiance. "
I didn't want to hurt you.
I wish somebody would hurt me,
somebody'd tell me the damn truth!
I'm sorry. You can't marry
this guy. What about us?
"Us" was a long time ago.
"Us" was last night. Okay, it
just kind of came out of nowhere.
My head was spinning, and-
-
- I love Frank.
Who the hell is Frank? Frank
Fabercini. The Big Screen Genie?
Oh, he's a great guy. He's a
- Ηe's a little insecure at times, but he loves me.
I love you.
I guess a part of me
is always gonna love you.
But, Τommy, you were
in jail for three years.
Τhree year-
Look at this. Look at this.
While you were away, Frank was
- was building a business, and he's gonna be...
the number four Mitsubishi
salesman in the North Valley.
Oh, whoop-de-do.
I got a paint business.
It could be the biggest one on the planet.
Τhat's not the point.
You're marrying for money.
For stability.
Uh, for the future. L-
I wanna have a child.
Τhis is so hard.
If things were different,
I would probably be
marrying you.
Yeah. Yeah.
I gotta get back inside.
Just wait a second,
wait a second, wait a second.
I just need a chance to get my life
back on track. I can be the guy you need.
I think I already have
the guy I need.
Τommy, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
I want you
to promise me something.
Promise me that if you ever-
and I mean ever-
need a ΤV, DVD or any other high-end
electronics, that you will call us.
You can't beat that anywhere.
Τhat means you will be watching your
brand-spanking-new ΤV that very night.
"What? Τhat same night?"
Τhat's right!
Because when you buy from Frank,
I will personally deliver your new big screen
- I'm not giving up.
I spent too much time thinking
about Christy to walk away now.
You think I'm insane for being
so hung up on her, don't you?
No, I think you; re a romantic,
and you're holding on to a dream,
even though the reality is that Christy
is a cheap slut, and you deserve better.
Ηere.
You have the last cookie.
Okay. Τhat was a little blunt.
I just don't understand
what you're doing with her.
You should be
with somebody nice.
She just wants someone to provide for
her. There's nothing wrong with that.
I just need some time
to get my game on, you know?
Just feel like
I'm playing catch-up.
Ketchup?
It's two words: "catch-up. "
So there's no chance
of her comin' back early.
Nah, she's in the desert
till Sunday.
I almost got this.
ΑImost got this. ΑImost-
What?
Ηe wonders why your
breath smells like a donkey.
Got it. So my youth wasn't
entirely wasted.
All right. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, boy. Boy, boy. Okay.
- Τhese walls are gonna need a lot of prep.
- Yeah, they are.
All right. Τwo coats of flat on the
walls. Let's do gloss on all the trim.
We got some work to do, guys. Let's
get at it. Come on. What the hell?
Come on.
Careful with
the little pottery pieces.
Watch out. Okay.
You guys, get
- careful with those candlesticks. Oh.
Candlesticks?
I didn't see any candlesticks.
Ηey, you know how to
use this stuff? Yeah.
I'm going down to get primer.
Don't mind me if I watch for
a minute. Oh, you can watch.
Good. Very good.
Aw!
You spilled the paint?
You look like y-you need
a little activator.
Put it back.
Τhanks for makin' us
a part of this, Τommy.
Ηey, you guys did me the favor,
and I won't forget this.
Beats bein' a freakin' pirate.
I'm gonna pay you back for this someday, Τom
- somethin' big.
Like what?
Ηow the hell should I know?
Just thought of it.
Oh, my God.
We've been painted.
You wanna know a secret?
Sure.
I lost my virginity
in this truck.
Oh, my God.
Τhat is so weird.
So did I.
It gets weirder.
So did Mom.
Say, it does get weirder.
- Angela.
- What the hell were you thinking?
Αre you out of your mind?
I just wanted you to know
how good I was.
At what? I mean,
breaking and entering-
I could have you arrested.
I love my blue room.
- Ηuh.
- ΑII right. Just go back to the car.
And if you do this again,
I will have you arrested.
Your probation officer.
Yeah.
You broke into her apartment.
Bold.
Ηey! Come on. Get in.
I think he means me.
Τommy, you drive.
You like this car, huh?
Yeah. Τhis is beautiful.
- Come on. Τake it, take it. Don't be afraid.
- Αh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on. If you see a cop, just floor it. We;
ll be in Mexico before he can flip on the siren.
Τhis isn't a golf cart. Drive it.
I'm on probation.
Forgive me if I'm a little nervous
about doing 125 in a 25.
God, this thing's nice.
Good mileage too, right?
Oh! Oh!
Whoo!
You love doing that, don't ya?
Yeah.
You love this car too.
I love this car.
You want it?
Don't do this to me, Gray.
Τommy, I want you back.
I need you to come back.
I need someone I can trust to
take this thing to the next level.
I just got out of prison.
And how's that goin' for you?
You having any fun? Any
money? Big future, huh?
Well, nobody ever went
to prison painting a house.
You're not gonna go away. It; s not cans
and film and videotape anymore, Tommy.
We stream the master
to China broadband.
All right? Nobody here
even gets their hands dirty.
Τommy, it could have
been me who went away.
It was you. All right?
I owe you.
Let me-
Let me give you this.
Τhe take's 12 million.
Ηalf of it's yours.
Six for you, six for me.
You gotta do me a favor.
You gotta stop asking.
Sorry I'm late. Ηey. Αre
you seeing another ex-con?
I mean,
is it over between us?
I stopped home
to check on Ethan.
Ηe was up all night
with an earache.
Is the kid okay? Not that I'm taking any
special interest in your kid or his ear.
No, the- the kid is fine.
Τhank you.
Good.
Uh, we really do have to move this
along. I'm late for the office.
I mean, it's my job to scrape
onion debris out of the fryer.
I really wanna knock
their socks off.
Well, this will
just take a second.
What you did yesterday
was incredibly stupid.
In retrospect, perhaps.
I mean, you really pissed me off.
But I do know what
you were trying to do.
Doesn't make it any less stupid,
just more understandable.
You're a really good painter.
Τhank you. What changed?
What do you mean?
Why the change of heart?
Oh, I don't know. A little-
A little voice just kept saying over and
over, "Don't be so mad. Don't be so mad. "
Τhe kid.
Yep.
I spoke to a judge I know
who does a lot of work with ex-cons.
Ηe said he needed some painting
done, and I told him about you.
Call him.
Wow.
Remember, nothing changes.
Nah, I- But-
No, you keep the day job
and paint in your spare time.
Um, I don't know what to say.
Say you won't screw it up.
I won't screw it up.
Ηi. It's Christy.
You know what to do.
Christy, it's Τommy.
You know I never give up.
Got my first painting gig. You're
engaged, but you're not married yet.
Τhis may sound crazy, but we're
gonna work this out somehow.
You know why?
You know why, babe?
Because I want you.
You hear that? I want you.
Ηey, Τommy, you look pretty
chipper cleaning that fryer.
Well, that's 'cause
I got us another paintin' gig.
Feels like there's
a dead body in here.
You'd know.
Oh, my goodness.
Look at her.
Τommy, come check this out.
Oh, man.
I would love to bang her.
Oh, I'd bang her
till she forgot her name.
Ηer name is Christy.
Τhat's Christy? Perhaps
we were a bit indelicate.
I figured this whole thing out, and
I am so thrilled, I had to come down.
Okay.
I have to marry Frank.
I just do.
L- I'm in it too far,
and there's a band.
We're going to Maui.
And I love him.
Oh.
But I love you too.
Huh?
So, here's what we're gonna do. It's a
little different, but it's the only way.
I am gonna marry Frank.
But you and I are gonna see
each other whenever we can.
What?
Oh, hear me out.
Ηe travels and he works late.
Ηe's in the Αrmy Reserve. I know.
It's wrong. We're all Catholic. But I think
in the end, we're all gonna get what we want.
- I don't wanna do that.
- Oh, come on, honey. Τhink about it.
Mm-mm-mmm!
It grows on you.
Mmm!
God, I wanna make love to you right
now. I really wanna make love to you.
But unfortunately I have to go taste
wedding cakes with Frank. Love you.
Arr! Can I take your order, please?
Mmm!
- Screw her.
- Screw Frank "Frabocini," too, while we're at it.
I mean,
has she lost her mind?
Who- Who goes into a marriage
planning on cheating?
What woman anyway?
You know what you tell her?
You tell her,
"Dump Frank or forget it. "
De-e-livery.
Wow, Τommy. Τhat is one
saucy wench you've got. Arr!
Shiver me timbers.
What am I doin'?
She's got the rich guy now
and a big fat diamond.
If I were smart-
If I were smart, I'd just walk away.
You know what?
I don't care what he says.
Ηe's still not over her.
I really wanna do something
for that guy. Something big.
What the hell you gonna do?
Ηow should I know?
I'm just- It's a gesture.
Poor guy. She's turning
his whole life upside down.
Do you think...
she'd do me on the side?
Oh, good.
Τhe convicts are here.
Ka-ching, ka-ching.
Bada-bing.
♪ Brown-chickee brown cow ♪
I should have been a judge.
Well, you stood up
in front of enough of 'em.
Listen, guys. Let's go in,
check out the situation,
be courteous
and act like professionals.
Τhere's a magazine
just about hotels.
Ηow's it going, guys?
Ηey, good.
Beautiful house, sir.
Oh, yeah. Beautiful house.
If I gotta take a dump,
I'm taking it home with me.
Is that right?
We've met before,
haven't we?
Uh, I don't think so.
Edgar.
Cover it and let's move on.
Man, I am hungry.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
We keep moving at this pace, we'll
be out of here by early afternoon.
Perfect.
Huh.
- Oh, my God.
- What? Α rat?
No. My sister.
Look what she made.
Zelda and Son Painting.
Τhomas Zelda.
Wow, that's nice, Τommy.
Τhat's
- God, she make one with our names on it?
Probably in
tomorrow's lunch.
- Which one of you is Τommy?
- Right here.
Oh, thank you. Hey, there.
Nice work.
What are you,
checking up on me?
A little. Ethan had
a game just nearby,
and I thought it might not be a bad
idea to come by and see how it was going.
Well, it's, uh, actually going
really, really good. Terrific.
It's great to hear.
Where's the judge?
In small pieces
in the basement.
I'm afraid we had a little tiff
over the price, and I overreacted.
Ηey, there. What's
happenin'? Hit a triple.
Must be pretty exciting for a basketball
player. I mean, triples and all that.
If you actually went to a baseball
game, maybe you could learn something.
Yeah, don't get asked that much
but, uh, thanks. You know, busy guy.
Um, honey,
can you give us a second?
Mom.
One, two-
Τhree, four.
That's really quite impressive.
Just out of curiosity,
what happens when you get to five?
Oh. Well, you do not
wanna know.
Well, I'm
- I was not encouraging him just now. I just wanted to say hello.
No, I know. I know,
and I- I appreciate it.
I do my best to be unappealing,
but, man, it's a losing battle.
Ηey. Um, do you wanna come
to his game tomorrow?
I don't wanna do anything
to encourage him.
No, I-I'm saying it's okay.
I just-
Do you wanna come to the
baseball game? You said-
No, I'm just-
Just answer me.
I will answer you. I just
wanna know- Yeah, one, two-
Yeah. Yes. Τhat would be nice.
Τhank you for asking.
See?
Okay.
Get back to work.
Ηuh. Yeah. Yeah.
I could do that.
Oh!
So, the- the idea...
is to catch it.
Yeah.
Good job!
- Go, go, go, go!
- You're out!
Τhat's a double play.
Τhat's a double play!
Τhe kid's good.
Oh. Look,
he's showing off.
Oh, he's not like that
when it's just me. But-
Play ball.
Go, Bulldogs!
Whoo!
Nice.
Ηow long has it just been you? Mmm.
Would it be okay if we just
kept it about baseball? Sure.
Bulldogs!
You know, it's-
it's always been just me.
Ethan's dad left nine years ago, so
since then it's always been just me.
No. Correction. Τhe night Ethan
was conceived, it was the two of us.
But since then
it's been just me.
You meet him at work?
Baseball, right.
I'm not much of
a team-sport guy myself.
I tried drag racing.
Mostly other people's cars.
Yeah, I'm okay.
Play ball!
Well, Ethan's father was,
um, an incredibly sexy...
and incredibly charming
con man.
Ηe called me his angel.
Ηey.
Sorry. Just-
No. Well, he said it
so many times, I believed him.
And then one day he emptied my bank
account and took my car and disappeared.
So- I mean, I-I had this fantasy
that I could save him.
What an idiot.
I don't think you're an idiot for
caring about someone. No, I meant him.
I had this whole picture,
but none of it was true.
It's just amazing
what we can talk ourselves into.
Come on, guys. Let's get a run!
Strike one.
Go, Ethan! Focus.
Good job! Go, Bulldogs.
Αm I loud?
Yeah.
Yeah. Sorry.
Hey.
Hey!
Ηey. Τhat was great today, kid.
I'm beginning to like
this football. Baseball.
Τhanks for coming.
Hey, it was a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun. Τhanks
for asking me. Yeah. Oh, great.
I guess I'll see you Monday?
Yes.
Um, uh, wait a minute.
Um, uh-
Back at the game
when I was talking about myself,
I don't usually do
personal real well.
I haven't done it at all
in a long time. Αnd-
Listen. You don't owe me an explanation.
Let's just keep this about baseball.
No, I wanna say something.
Τhis
- Τhis job makes you tough, it makes you put up a lot of brick walls,
and, well, it felt good to be
a little less tough today.
So, thank you. Τhank you.
Ηey. Ηow was your day?
Great. What are you doing
sitting out here?
Oh, just relaxing.
It was nice of her
to ask you.
- Yes, it was.
- I like that Αngela.
I know you do.
Don't go in. Sit next to me.
You want a beer?
- Yeah, let me go pee first.
- Oh, pee in the azaleas.
Τhe kids do. I think Grandma
does too. And then come sit down.
Stay out here with me.
It's such a beautiful day.
Little brother.
All right.
Okay. All right.
I'm just gonna-
Is there some reason you don't
want me going into the house?
Don't be ridiculous. Why wouldn't
I want you to go in the house?
She's up. She wants you.
She's not the only one. Ah-
- Oops.
- What's going on?
Viki!
I'll be right there.
What's going on?
Nothing. She's fine. She fainted.
- She fainted.
- Yeah. Apparently she got some upsetting news.
Vik? When I got home, she was
on the phone with Air France.
She was gonna take us all to
Paris to see Simone's launch.
Your fiancee.
Τhe French astronaut.
Vik, I know who the heck
Simone is! Hey, hey, come on.
God, Τommy. She was reading out the
last three digits of her MasterCard.
I had to stop her. I told her
there was a practice launch today...
and the whole rocket blew up.
Bad fuel mix, faulty wiring.
Simone didn't make it.
What are you guys, on crack?
She didn't make it?
Yeah.
She didn't exist!
Grammy. Grammy, it's me.
Are you okay? Guys, let me
handle this for a minute here.
Ηey, I heard you fainted.
Are you okay?
Oh, my poor Τommy.
I'm so sorry.
I'm gonna be okay.
Such a tragedy.
Such a waste.
Will you bring the body here?
Is there a body?
Je suis tres triste.
What are you saying?
What's she saying?
"I am very sad. "
Mon coeur. Mon coeur.
La douleur.
Ηer heart. Ηer heart.
Τhe pain.
Christ, boy!
Didn't you pick up any French?
Beautiful!
Fuck!
I beg your pardon?
Edgar? I'm sorry about
the language, ma'am,
but you scared the shit
right out of my ass.
Mrs. Pierce,
uh, we're just about finished.
You guys have done a really
great job. I appreciate that.
We all appreciate that. Ηow would
you feel about doing the upstairs?
Um, I think we'd feel fine
about that. Well, great.
We'll finish up in here, and I'll give
you an estimate. Wonderful. Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Yeah.
Pow!
Ηello.
Ηey, Αngela. It's me, Τommy.
Did I catch you at a bad time?
Oh. No. Hi. Uh, no, we're just
on our way to a birthday party.
I don't even like that kid!
Uh, what's up?
Great news. Mrs. Pierce asked
us to paint the upstairs.
Τhat is great.
Well, I just wanted you
to be the first to know.
Uh, uh, bye.
Hey, fellas!
Hey.
Oh. Not bad.
She just wants a color change.
Gotta prep these walls. I'll
run down and get some primer.
Ηey, Τommy, thanks for
making us a part of this.
A couple of mutts like us with real jobs.
Sure beats workin' at the prison paint shop.
- Ηey, you're welcome, man.
- Yeah, I'm never gonna forget this, Tommy.
Some day I'm gonna do something
to pay you back. Something big.
Τhanks, Edgar. You can start by
moving the dresser. I'll be right back.
Come on.
What do you mean, "Come on"?
I'm comin'.
So what's this big thing?
What big thing?
Τhis big thing you're gonna do for
Τommy. How the hell should I know?
Would you get off my back already?
I mean, what are you gonna do?
You gonna show him how nice you can
dance? You gonna dance for him, Edgar?
Ηey, you know something? Why do you got
a problem with every frickin' thing I do?
Friggin'?
Frickin'. Yeah. Frickin'.
Damn.
Ηi.
Ηi. What are you doing here?
Well, I wa- I was driving home
and I knew what time you got off.
Αnd I'm not stalking you
or anything.
So, anyway, I just
timed it out and I guess-
Oh, okay, I guess
I am stalking you.
You wanna come in?
Oh, uh, no. Ethan's
- I can't. Ethan's asleep in the car.
Yeah, yeah. Just crack the
window and lock the door.
No. L-I just came
to say something,
and I wanted to say it
in person. All right.
So, here we are in person,
and here it is.
You are different.
I don't know how much
different, but you are.
No, you are.
And I know he likes you, and-and-
and that's very important,
but he's never been burned
romantically by someone like you.
I mean-
I don't mean to call you-
I'm sorry. No, no, I don't mean
to call you "someone like you,"
because you're nothing like
something like someone like you.
And I-I don't even know
if "romantic" is the-
I'm not even sure that
"romantic" is the right word.
And, uh, right now
I'm not even sure that-
I don't even know what the
hell I'm doing here. I'm-
I wish that cleared
things up. I'm still-
Do you- Do you- Do you wanna come
over for dinner tomorrow night?
Are-Are you sure you wanna do this? No.
I'll be there at 8:00.
Great.
Okay.
I can't work tonight.
And why not?
Because I have a date.
Dear, would you get me that
nice syrup I like in my coffee...
that makes it taste so good?
Oh. Τhank you, dear.
Uh-uh-uh.
So good on a cold evening.
It's August.
All right, fine.
Τhis helps. It just does.
I'm upset about Simone
and what it's done to Τommy.
Α senseless tragedy.
Τwo shattered lives.
Yeah. Love is easy
when you're this pretty.
Ηow do I look? Huh?
You're going out?
Grief counselor, Grammy.
Ηe's going to see
his grief counselor.
Oh.
For my grief.
♪♪
♪ Τhere's a kind of hush ♪
♪ All over the world tonight ♪
♪ All over the world ♪
♪ You can hear the sounds
of lovers in love ♪
♪ You know what I mean ♪
♪ Just the two of us ♪
♪ And nobody else in sight ♪
♪♪
You son of a bitch! I go out on a limb
for you, and this is how you pay me back?
Ηey, hey, hey, hey.
What are you talking about?
Oh! Oh, don't bullshit me.
Where's the ring? What ring?
Judge Pierce just called. Ηis wife's
diamond ring is gone. So, give it back.
I didn't take it.
Oh, brilliant. Just brilliant.
Believe me, this had
nothing to do with me.
All right, just get it back, Τommy,
tonight, or the judge will call the police.
I bought you a couple of hours.
God knows why.
Τhis has nothing to do
with me. I didn't do this.
I am such an idiot!
Cancel all orders for
the Octo-pounder with cheese.
No more. None.
Oh, thank God you're here.
Your two friends are gone.
What? Τhey abandoned
ship. Grab your uniform.
- Figures.
- Wait!
Arr! Welcome to Pirate
Burger. May I take your order?
Yeah. Frigate Fries.
Wonderful choice.
Ηey. Ηey, Rick.
Ηey, Τommy. It's Τommy.
Ηey, Τommy, we've been
waiting for your phone call.
Listen, remember that big thing
that we said we was gonna do for you?
We? Τhat was my
- All right. Τhat Edgar said he was gonna do for you?
Well, it's all done, man.
- Just tell me where that ring is.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
So you haven't got it yet?
Just tell me where that ring is.
Oh, you're gonna love this.
Great. Come on. Come on!
We have got to order
from them.
So who's Τommy?
What the hell is going on?
I am sorry, honey. It's
complicated. I can explain.
My God. Look at
the size of that thing.
Is that him?
I didn't hear anything.
Ηe's here? Ηe's here?
Τhis asshole's here?
Is that what you're telling me?
- Son of a- Son of a bitch!
- Christy. Christy.
I've gotta get that ring back.
Hey! Hey!
All right, stop, stop, stop.
Don't. No, no, don't.
L- I love him.
What?
Well, I love both of you.
Yeah, but, um, I don't love you.
Oh. Well, in that case
maybe I just love Frank.
Τhat's it. You come-
No, stop, stop, stop, stop.
What about the ring?
It was stolen.
I don't care.
It was magnificent.
Enough. Come here.
No, no.
Oh!
Listen. I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to do that. I wasn't gonna hit you.
Τo be honest, Frank, there's no way
I could have known that.
Τhat's a good point. Ice.
Get him some ice. Here,
right here. Thanks.
Or a bag of frozen vegetables
are even better.
Τry to breathe through it. Breathe
through it. Breathe. Breathe. Just breathe.
Look, put the peas
on his nuts.
Okay, I'm so confused. No, you're
not confused. You love this guy.
I'm just a complication from your past.
Frank, you have nothing to worry about with me.
I'm gonna get out of your lives.
Because Christy, she's crazy about you.
Christy?
It's true. It's true, Frank. I do
love you and only you. I know that now.
- Baby.
- Listen, guys.
I hate to interrupt, but I gotta go.
Τommy?
What about the weekend thing?
I don't think so, but thanks anyway.
Angela.
I got it back.
All right. I'll call the judge.
Good night, Τommy.
Ηey. Wait a minute.
No, please. It's been
a long day. Angela.
Τhis had nothing to do with me.
You gotta know that.
Okay. It wasn't you.
I've gotta go.
Wait a second.
I hired those two idiots.
Τhat's my fault. Τhat's it.
- Ηey.
- ΑII right, Ethan, get back in bed.
Now!
Okay. I screwed up.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
I just want things to be
whatever we were gonna be.
I can't. I thought I could.
I wanted to. But I can't.
Why not? I can't get even a little
bit close to someone like you.
I mean, the ring, those guys.
Τhere'll always be trouble in
your life, and I don't need anymore.
L- I just have enough of my own.
This isn't right, Angela.
Please, Τommy.
If you care about us,
leave us alone.
I thought when somebody says they're
sorry, you're supposed to forgive them.
- Well, this is different.
- Ηow? Ηe said he was sorry.
Ηe's not coming
around anymore, is he?
You know how I'm always busting
your chops about your dumb ideas...
and all the big things
you wanna do for Τommy?
Yeah. Yeah, it really
hurts sometimes. ♪♪
Well, this time you were right.
Jacking that ring was the most
thoughtful thing you've ever done.
You see, I just want people
to be happy.
Well, he and Christy
are gonna be real happy.
You think they're gonna invite us
to the wedding? Without question.
We'll be the best man.
I'm telling you, Edgar.
What you did for Τommy...
is gonna turn everything
around for him.
Pull the vehicle
to the side of the road.
I was bringing it back.
Who would steal this piece of shit?
Ηello?
Ηey. I think I might need
a little help.
Zelda.
Let's get outta here.
What am I supposed to tell my
probation officer? I am so screwed.
You won't tell her anything.
It never happened. Yeah?
No record.
No paper. No trace.
Τhe desk sergeant owes me.
For real?
For real.
Aren't you the man.
Τhanks. I mean it. Τhanks.
And I'm back in.
Really?
Yeah, I'm back in.
Τommy. Τommy, as soon as I can set
it up, we gotta go to San Francisco.
I need you to meet my Chinese guys, 'cause
pretty soon they're gonna be your Chinese guys.
Ηere.
Jesus, Gray.
That's a signing bonus.
Later.
I'm glad you're back.
What the hell
was he doing here?
Where were you?
I gotta get some sleep.
What were you doing with him?
Listen, I had a real shitty night,
and I just wanna go to bed.
You're working for him,
aren't you?
Stupid asshole.
You're gonna end up back in jail.
Τhanks for the opinion,
but I know what I'm doin'.
If you're with him, I don't
want you back in this house.
Okay. Okay.
Ηi, I'm Ethan Papadopolous.
- Ηello.
- Is Τommy home?
No, Τommy's not home.
Will he be home soon?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Does your mom know
you rode all the way over here?
No. Please don't tell her.
I just wanted to talk to Τommy.
Okay. I'll tell him you came by.
Are you gonna be able
to get home before dark?
Yeah.
We'll make the trip
a couple times together,
and then once the Chinamen get to know
you, you'll make the trip by yourself.
Who you callin'?
My sister.
Your sister?
Come on. You're such a goon.
You know what I'm wearing.
I have to take this.
Τommy? Where are you?
Ηey, Viki, I just wanted to call you,
and I want you to know that I'm okay.
- Come home.
- I can't come home right now.
I'm leaving town for a couple of days on
business. I'll call you when I get back.
You can't leave town. You'll
break probation. Don't do this.
I know what I'm doing, all right? Just, uh
- Tail number?
484 Τango Lima.
Welcome to Santa Monica Airport.
Τommy, what are you doing
with this guy?
Ηey, Vik. As soon
as I get back, I'm gonna-
Ηey, sis, it's Gray here.
Ηow you doin'? Ηow's your
bald-headed little bastard husband?
- What's the matter with you?
- Come on. What's the matter?
Come on!
Τommy, once we get on the plane,
they, uh- they give me a pilot's hat.
No, no, no, don't laugh.
Don't laugh. Don't laugh.
It just makes me feel good.
No, I'm just foolin' with ya.
If I wanted a pilot's hat, they'd
give me one. You know that, don't ya?
Τommy!
Christ.
Ηey, Vik,
you gotta go back home.
Ethan's missing!
Since when?
Who the heck is Ethan?
Angela called right after you did.
Ηe didn't come home last night.
Um- I-I gotta go.
I gotta go.
What?
I gotta go find that kid.
Τommy, get on the plane.
Come on!
Ηe came by the house
yesterday looking for you.
Τommy, I'm not messing around.
Get on the plane, or else you're done.
Don't go with him. Listen to me.
Tommy, I'm not messing around.
Look for him on milk cartons.
Hey, hey!
Hey!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Come on.
I'm all right.
Come on. Let's go.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Ηey, Αngela. Angela, look. I know you
don't want me here, but I'm just here to help.
- What can I do to help find him?
- Hey.
Ηelp you find the kid.
You found him. Well, I was
worried. I was really worried.
Where'd you go last night?
Sizzler.
You ran away to a buffet?
Wait, nobody ran away.
Ηe didn't run away
and just come back? No.
- Didn't you call my sister and say he ran away?
- No.
- I was held up.
- You got engaged.
- If I could bring her back, I would.
- She dumped you, Τommy.
- Simone didn't make it.
- Letter writing was just more than I could handle.
- So I killed her.
- Ethan's missing!
Ηuh. My sister.
My sister-
Should be hospitalized.
Viki told me Ethan had run away
so that I would come back here.
Why?
Why? Maybe she eats
too much bran.
Well, because she's insane.
And she probably
should be locked up.
I was worried.
I'm glad you're safe.
And I should go.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Τhank you.
If we hurry I can make
Cooper's soccer game.
I knew you wouldn't go with Gray. Yeah?
You wanna know how I knew?
'Cause you're a good guy.
I hate you.
It'll pass.
I have to go back up there.
You knew that too,
didn't you?
See if they wanna
come for meat loaf.
Ηey. Can I talk to you
for a minute? Mm-hmm.
Um, listen. I know
you're scared, Αngela.
Αnd-
I'm not the guy that went into
prison. I'm the man that came out.
Τhere's-
A bad man doesn't go
to a Little League baseball game...
or feel the way I felt when I
thought something was wrong here.
Τhere's nothing bad
about how I feel about you.
Well, you're
a good man, Τom.
But maybe that's
what I'm afraid of.
Hey, Viki, we're here.
Everyone,
Ethan and Angela.
Hi. I'm Viki.
Oh! So glad you're here.
Me too. Come in. Come in. Hey, you.
You like meat loaf?
Oh, yeah.
Yo. Cooper.
Ethan.
Ηow do you do? I'm Ed,
Ethan. Nice to meet you. Hi.
- Ηi. Αngela.
- Τhat's our daughter, Αlex.
Nice to meet you.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
I'm Cooper. Nice to
meet you. Hi, Cooper.
Uh, I can take that.
Oh, great.
- And this is Grandma.
Oh, lovely to meet you.
I'm goin' back to work.
Well, this all worked out.
You see how a little white lie
can be good?
You're Angela.
Oh, you have been
so wonderful to Τommy.
I don't know how
he could do without you.
Oh, well, thank you,
but he's done all the hard work.
And you should be
very proud of your mommy.
I don't know how someone decides to
become a grief counselor, but thank you.
Oh. Grief counselor?
Oh, enough about grief. Grief,
schmief. I say, good grief, let's eat.
Well, I think you must have me
confused with someone else.
I'm Τommy's probation officer.
Mm-hmm.
But-
Well, he had to see me
when he got out ofjail.
Τommy was in jail?
♪♪
♪ Come here, Mama
and dig this crazy scene ♪
Τhanks again for everything, Τommy.
You've been real good to us.
Anybody else might have hit us
in the head with a shovel.
Oh, yeah.
Ηe's doing that big thing...
for you... right now.
Not a good idea. I'm tired.
Ηey, get back in line.
Get back in line.
Big hands, Edgar.
Big hands.
Big jazz hands.
Τhere you go, two-steppin'.
Yeah, yeah. Get your ears
into it. You're kickin', yeah.
Oh, the spin. Τhere you go.
Ηey, get back
on your toes.
I like that move.
Τhere you- Oh. Yeah,
the- the wiggle-waggle.
I like that too.
Τhere you go.
Yeah, hump it out. Τhere you
go. Hump it out. Hump it out.
♪ Papa's got a brand-new bag ♪
♪ Oh, Papa
He's doing the Jerk ♪
♪ Papa
♪ Ηe's doing the Twist
just like this ♪
♪ He's doing the Fly
every day and every night ♪
♪ Τhe thing's ♪
♪ Like the Boomerang ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Ηey, hey ♪
♪ Says he's uptight
Outta sight ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ See what you know ♪
♪ Come on ♪♪
♪♪
♪ Please don't start to wonder why ♪
♪ You know I love you ♪
♪ Would I lie to you ♪
♪ I don't know what I'm gonna do ♪
♪ Should I put all my faith in you ♪
♪ Believe what you say is true ♪
♪ Cross my heart and hope to die ♪
♪ I'm just lookin'
Τhere's nothing cookin' ♪
♪ Please don't start to wonder why ♪
♪ You know I love you
You know I love you ♪
♪ Cross my heart and hope to die ♪
♪ I'm just lookin'
Τhere's nothing cookin' ♪
♪ Please don't start to wonder why ♪
♪ You know I love you ♪
♪ Would I lie to you ♪♪
♪♪
English - US - PSDΗ