Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
under the stars.
Wow.
Those glow-in-the-dark
star stickers have
nothing on this.
That? That's a firefly.
Good grab. Nice.
Yep, they're still in there.
Bright, huh?
They're bioluminescent.
Did you know that
fireflies glow to remind us
that they taste bitter.
It's a defense mechanism.
[Fireflies buzzing]
Yeah. See? I told you.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
No, thanks. I'm good.
Yep, you know,
there's no way
I'm going to eat that bug.
So quit trying--
Oh, wow.
Yeah, that tastes bad,
definitely bitter.
Okay. Oh, listen to this.
I've got a good one for you.
What's the difference
between Neanderthal man
and Cro-Magnon man?
Linguistic competence
and polychromatic
cave paintings.
Get it?
Hello?
You're missing the punch line.
You see,
it's the difference
between the two....
It's always a winner.
[snoring]
I need some fresh museum-
related material. People
depend on me for those jokes.
[Ted yawning]
[Children chattering]
No, no, those are
dinosaur bones.
You can't park there.
There's no parking here.
That's my office!
Oh, just a bad dream.
Oh, boy.
Monkey? Monkey? Where are you?
BOY 1: A monkey flew!
Oh, no.
Run! Run!
BOY 2: A monkey! A monkey!
Wait. It's a zoo.
A zoo is full of monkeys.
Who's to say it's mine?
BOY 3: The monkey
is chasing me!
That's mine.
[Children screaming]
BOY 4: Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Look at that!
Oh, that's cold.
Oh, it's so much colder
than you think.
I suggest never
doing that. Ever.
Don't ever swim with penguins.
Swim with dolphins.
Freezing!
It's going to be okay.
Okay, your turn.
There you are.
Oh, Ted. Hi.
Miss Maggie.
Hi.
What happened to you?
Oh, it didn't rain here?
Nope, not here.
Wow, now, that's crazy.
Freak cloudburst
down the street.
BOY: Yeah, right.
Hey, where you going?
The monkey knows that guy?
Please tell me
you paid for those.
He thinks he's a banana.
So how long have you
had a monkey?
I don't. I mean, I do.
Oh, he's so cute.
I really don't.
I.... Long story.
Mr. Ted, what's
your monkey's name?
Yeah, what's his name?
He doesn't have a name.
He has to have a name.
No, he doesn't.
Let' s give him a name.
All right! Good idea.
Please don't--
Elvis.
How about Jojo?
Fred.
Hercules.
Bananas.
Mumble.
No.
Skippy.
What about Juan Carlos?
Okay, you know what?
His name's Washington.
Man, that's a dumb name.
Then call him George.
How's that? Happy now?
Oh, I like George.
It's so cute.
Oh, he's so cute.
Here, George. Take my balloon.
Let's go play.
Here, George.
Have a red one.
Here. Here's a balloon.
Oh, you like blue, too?
What's the use?
Ted, are you okay?
It's a long story,
but it looks like the museum
is going to close.
Really?
I know how much
you love the museum.
I do love the museum, Ted.
But that's not really
why I go there every week.
Yeah, I know. Everyone
likes the cafeteria food.
Gosh, it's good.
I've never had
the cafeteria food.
Really?
Really.
So you've never had
the tuna hash on Thursday?
Never.
It's really quite something.
I'll remember that.
There's also a meatless
meatloaf on Monday...
which is quite special.
Quite special.
Excuse me, mister.
You have to help George.
George who?
George needs you.
Take a message. I'm busy.
He has an emergency!
The restrooms are behind
the penguin habitat.
Mister, your monkey's
floating away.
Look. Seriously, there he is.
He's what? He's what?
There, look at him.
I'm not kidding.
Hey, monkey!
Don't be afraid.
Just keep your head together,
and don't look down!
You've got to save George.
Who, me?
Yes, you!
Hurry!
Okay.
Your monkey's going
to fall quick! Hurry!
Hurry, Ted. Hurry.
He's floating away.
I'm commandeering
these balloons.
Hey! Hey,
where are you going?
I need that.
Thank you, young fellow.
Can I borrow these?
You're going to need
a lot of balloons.
Here I go!
Boy, glad that's over.
[Lions growling]
Pay you back. Thank you.
You don't mind, do you?
Official zoo business.
Oh, my! Okay.
Wait for me, monkey!
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
I'm trying to fly.
More altitude.
Sorry, I need this kite.
How do you steer these things?
Hang on, little fellow.
I'm coming.
MAN 1: Hey, look at that!
MAN 2: It's some super-hero.
MAN: There's a high fly ball
deep in left-center field,
We're going to win!
We lost,
And the curse continues,
Monkey!
Monkey! Watch out!
Monkey! No!
Watch out!
George! Whoa!
Got you.
[Panting]
Wow.
You're safe now, George.
I've got you.
It's all right. It's okay.
It's okay, George.
George. I like that name.
It suits you.
This is how
it's supposed to be
Hey, actually,
this isn't too bad.
I can't believe
I'm doing this.
This is awesome.
I want to be where the water
below gives a gift to the sky
And the clouds give back
every time they cry
And make the grass grow green
Beneath my toes
And if the sun comes out
I'll paint a picture all about
The colors
I've been dreaming of
The hours
just don't seem enough
To put it all together
Maybe it's as strange
as it seems
And the trouble I find
is that the trouble finds me
Hey, down there! Hi!
It begins with a dream
And a feeling I get
when I look and I see
That this world is a puzzle
Find all of the pieces
And put it all together
And then I'll rearrange it
I'll follow it forever
And maybe it's as strange
as it seems
Look, George.
There's the museum.
Can you believe all
those people down there
are waiting to see this?
Hey! Here it is!
Here's the giant idol,
everybody!
If only it was that big.
Yeah, that's it, Ted.
Just make it bigger.
No problem.
Wait.
I can't make it bigger,
but I know who can.
George, now,
hand me that pink balloon,
and hang on!
That's close enough.
[George whooping]
Let's see. Not too round.
Well, this one's
not round enough.
Yes, perfect!
[Ted groaning]
Huh? Oh, I predicted this.
Balloon travel
finally coming back
into fashion.
Clovis, I've got a problem.
Wait, just a minute.
Are you returning him?
What?
Because I have
a strict no-return policy...
on any robotic animals
I create, unless, of course,
you have a receipt.
What? No. Clovis,
calm down. This is George.
He's a real monkey.
Are you sure?
Yes. I found him
in the jungle.
Actually, he found me.
[Barking]
Well, then, George,
meet Sparky.
Sparky, George.
Clovis, I really need
your help.
You do?
Here's my problem.
I see.
Oh, you're just
missing the chain.
I think I have
an extra one right over--
No, this is the idol.
Ted, I'm not one to judge...
but haven't you exaggerated
its size just a wee bit?
Thanks, Frosty.
What is that?
Nothing.
Should I be concerned?
No.
Not if you're
behind that wall.
Fire in the hole!
George, look out!
Is that popcorn?
I call it boom-corn.
It's for really big sleepovers
with a lot of kids.
Not quite right.
Soaky, when you're done,
could you....
Thank you.
All right, let's see
what we can do
with that keychain.
Idol.
Idol. Right. Yes.
[The Sharing Song by
Jack Johnson playing]
It's always more fun
To share with everyone
If you have one
Here is something
you can learn
You can still share
Just by taking turns
CLOVlS: Here's an idea.
I can make it
into a snow globe,
a rain globe, or....
Is that a real tornado?
Fun, huh?
Clovis, focus.
Focus. Bigger. Got you.
Hey, how about something
around that size?
Would that work for you?
[George giggling]
[Sparky barking]
What do you mean
George made it?
George, is that true?
Don't get mad at him.
Mad? No.
I think he may have
the answer to your problem.
Good work, George.
Clovis, I need to
borrow your truck.
My truck?
Thanks, Clove.
[Barking]
Be careful!
What?
[Barking]
You left your squeaky toy
in the back of the truck?
Come on.
This is taking too long.
Oh, no! What's going on?
When is this museum
gonna start?
There are people lined up
all around the block!
I don't understand, Junior.
I thought I told you
to cancel the exhibit.
Me? No, Father, please.
I don't think so. Look,
I would have done it.
You know, Father, I'm afraid
this has the stink of Ted
all over it.
Take a whiff with me.
[Phone ringing]
Yeah.
Hello?
Mr, Bloomsberry? Ted here,
Ted?
How dare....
Hang up, Father.
No, no, No, sir,
don't hang up, No,
Ted, I can't talk.
Please, no, I know,
This is really not
a good time.
I have the solution,
Solution?
I'm sorry.
Did he say, "solution"?
TED: The exhibit
can open as planned.
How is that possible?
Well, I'll explain it
when I see you.
All you need to know is,
the eagle has landed.
The what?
JUNlOR: Did he say, "beagle"?
No, I said,
"The eagle has landed."
Eagle?
What about the idol?
Ask him about the idol,
No, the idol
would be the eagle.
Ted, start over,
It's not a big deal.
I'll be there
in 15 minutes.
Okay, fine, Hurry,
[Jungle Gym by
Jack Johnson playing]
The city is my jungle gym
Look at this big great world
That we're living in
There's lots of fun
to be had on these streets
We can take a ride
just you and me
It's a jungle gym
TED: Would you
get out of the way?
Man on a mission here.
Trolley cars and buses, too
All the big kids
going to school
I'm going to get a treat
from the ice cream man
I'm seeing multiple violations
of rules of the road!
Multiple violations!
The city's nitty gritty
But it's so much fun
Oh, yeah.
A 40 foot monkey causing
unintentional widespread
panic? Seen it.
Sha la la la la la la la la la
Traffic is crazy.
I'm going to get off
Broadway and try Sixth.
It's a funky beat
The more I've learned
inside the city
Hey, there are lines painted
on the street for a reason!
[Horn blaring]
Oh, yeah? Well,
that's not physically
possible for me to do!
So there.
George, take that
license-plate number
down, quickly.
The city's nitty-gritty
George, what are you thinking?
Tighten your seat belt.
Every nutcase in the city
is on the road today.
Wow, Junior is right.
There is a parking problem
in this city.
Mr. Bloomsberry!
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
That's it.
Get that little jungle thing
out of here before he
destroys something else.
Hold on, there, Son.
Ted, what is this contraption?
Stand back, everyone,
and prepare to be amazed.
Oh, yeah.
This ought to be good.
Here, George.
Let's show them.
Small idol.
Big idol.
Isn't that thing awesome?
What is it?
I see.
Daddy, I'm scared.
Interesting.
I don't like it.
We optically enlarge
the statue.
Yes, I suppose
this might work.
Yes, this will
definitely work.
Well, sir, the credit
really should go
to George.
He gave me the idea
as we were floating
over the city.
Floating?
You know what?
I'll tell you about it
some other time.
JUNlOR: Excuse me.
Hi. Voice of reason.
Like to introduce myself.
Hello.
Are we so desperate
that we'll lie to our public?
Nonsense.
We promised the people
something awe-inspiring...
and we're giving it to them,
thanks to Ted and George.
I knew you wouldn't
let me down.
Well, sir,
I've got to tell you,
I came pretty close.
No. No, Ted,
I am so proud of you.
You're like the son
I never had.
Father, I'm your son,
remember?
Yes, but I had you.
Ted, this is amazing.
Yes, of course.
What was I thinking?
TED: Are you seeing what
I'm seeing? Isn't that cool?
Can you believe it?
Hey, monkey.
Monkey want a sip?
Go on. Take it.
Yummy. Creamy.
Yes. Good. Drink it.
Say, I guess the world
didn't need another
parking lot after all.
Hey, you did it.
Another great Ted moment.
Thank you.
We've got nobody
to thank but you.
George, what did you do?
Oh, Ted, I warned you
about that monkey.
You don't give
a monkey a latte.
And now he's gone
and destroyed
the last chance we had...
of saving my father's museum.
It's my father's only museum.
What have you done, Ted?
What have you done?
He's right, Ted.
We've just been
fooling ourselves.
It's over.
Agreed.
But, sir,
I still think we could--
Ted, I said, it's over.
It's okay, Father. It's okay.
I'm here. Your son.
Your real son.
Junior, not Ted.
Yes, Father, you'll be fine.
No, George.
You just stay here, okay?
I have to do this.
[Clamoring]
Excuse me.
I'm....
I'm sorry, everybody.
The museum's closed.
ALL: What?
But for how long?
Forever.
But I want to see
the giant idol.
There never was one.
It was all a big mistake.
WOMAN: We've been
waiting for hours.
GlRL: This is terrible.
MAN: What a rip-off.
I'm so sorry.
[Children chattering]
I have to go.
I'll be back. I promise.
It's too late
to cheer me up.
You think life's just
nonstop fun and games,
don't you?
Well, it's not, George.
At least, not for me.
George, please
just leave me alone.
You're better off without me.
This is not good, you and me.
You belong in the jungle.
I belong somewhere
without a monkey.
I don't want....
I can't have you in my life.
Please, just go.
Do you understand?
[Chattering happily]
No. Look, monkey,
don't follow me.
Get away.
MAN: Got him!
Easy. Easy.
Get the cage ready.
Careful. He's dangerous.
Hey, hey, not so rough.
Stand back, sir.
I know he looks cute...
but this one's supposed
to have teeth
like Ginsu knives.
Yeah, that's right.
This matches the description.
Hey, he's getting away.
All right, all right,
I got him. I got him.
Guys. Guys,
could you just take him?
Careful. Watch his teeth.
Please.
And don't hurt him.
Relax, little fellow.
Back to Africa with you.
[George crying]
It's for the best, Ted.
It's for the best.
[Wrong Turn by
Jack Johnson playing]
And I'll wait here a while
Just long enough to be
MAN: All right, come on.
Take it away.
Didn't make a wrong turn
And I'll wait long enough
For maybe an hour or two
Before I decide
It wasn't me, it was you
Peekaboo.
Aboo. Aboo.
Peek-a-boo. Peek-a-boo.
George.
He loved peek-a-boo.
You think he saw us?
[Broken by
Jack Johnson playing]
With everything ahead of us
We left everything behind
Everything we needed
and right at this time
And now the feeling that
I'm feeling, well
It's feeling like
my life is finally mine
Man, what a ride.
Hey! That's mine! Mom!
If I had a minute
For every hour that I wasted
I'd be rich in time
I'd be doing fine
Without you I was broken
Monkey. Monkey. Over here.
But I'd rather be broke down
Come, monkey. Come on.
With you by my side
Here, monkey.
He loved the primary colors.
Hey! No, no, no, no!
That's fresh paint!
That's fresh paint, sir!
No, no, no, no! Come on.
Yeah. Quitting time.
[George chattering]
George?
How'd you get out?
So that's why traffic
was so bad.
Oh, George.
Here, give me that!
Those were some good times.
We had some fun, didn't we?
WOMAN: Thank you.
Without you I was broken
But I'd rather be broke down
with you by my side
Sir, I'm only passing out
flyers, not hugs.
Ted, I've been
looking for you.
Is everything okay?
That's what I was thinking.
Yeah, sure. Why?
Why?
Well, you are hugging a man
dressed in a monkey costume.
Kind of tight, I might add.
And good luck with that, Phil.
Great to see you again.
Yeah, you, too. Remember,
the sale ends Thursday.
So after they took
him away, I've been
wandering the streets...
and you saw me hugging a man
in a monkey outfit.
That pretty much
catches you up.
I can't believe
George is gone,
and it's all my fault.
Yes, it is.
What?
Ted, do you want me
to tell you what you
want to hear...
or do you want to hear
what you should hear...
which I'll tell you,
and not just what you think
you want to hear?
Run that by me
one more time.
George is gone,
and I'm afraid
it's your fault he's gone.
So the question is,
what are you
going to do about it?
You're right.
It is my fault.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a date with a monkey.
You know
that I don't have
a date with a monkey.
It was just my way of saying
that I'm going after George.
Ted.
Right. Bye.
[Ship horn blowing]
Oh, no! I'm too late.
Or am l?
Luckily, movies have
taught me exactly what to do
in this situation.
Kids, don't try this at home.
Here we go.
What am I doing?
This isn't a movie.
It's real!
This is odd.
You guys are a little
dressed up for a cargo ship
to Africa, don't you think?
[Ship horn blowing]
Oops.
Excuse me.
I'm coming for you!
George!
[Muffled] George.
George.
George!
Where are you?
George, are you here?
I think you're here.
George?
[George chattering]
George!
There you are!
Stand back, buddy!
George, give me a hug,
you little fur ball!
There. You're all right.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I don't know how
I let them take you away.
I mean, I do.
This was so important to me,
but somehow it just
doesn't matter anymore.
What matters is you and me,
buddy, our buddyship.
Now we can do all
the monkey things
we've always wanted to do.
I'll get an organ and grind,
and you can dance for money.
Or I can dance for money.
Who knows?
We'll figure it out.
We can take turns.
George, do you mind?
I'm expressing
some feelings here.
It's kind of hard, okay?
Now, where was l?
Right, who's going to dance.
Oh, no, no. Adventure!
You brought adventure
to my life.
And now, you know,
that's all that matters.
Wait.
Where's that coming from?
It's a pictogram.
George, it's the map!
We had it all along.
Of course.
"Turn your eye to the light.
Go from blindness to sight."
I was supposed to hold
the statue up to the sun.
Pack your things, George.
We're off to Africa
on the very next ship.
[Ship horn blowing]
Wait a minute.
We're already on a ship
to Africa.
Man, what a time saver.
Okay, Edu. I got it.
That's it! You did it,
George! Give me five!
That's close enough.
Well done, Mr. Ted.
This way, men! Follow me.
Right away.
The guy in yellow.
Let's go.
Here I am.
Please, valet at your service.
We've been waiting.
Sorry.
The nearest parking lot
is five blocks away.
I know. I own that
parking lot. That's where
the real money is.
I know.
[Sobbing]
MAN: Behold the Eighth
Wonder of the World!
The Lost Shrine of Zagawa!
Okay, now that,
I haven't seen.
But now I've seen it.
WOMAN: Way to go, Mr. Ted!
As I stand in front of
the Lost ldol of Zagawa...
I just have one
important thing to say.
Anyone can memorize
facts and figures.
The real way to learn
anything is to go out
and experience it...
and let your
curiosity lead you.
MAGGlE: Oh, George.
Hi.
BOY: Hey, it's George.
So who's ready to learn?
GlRL: Wow, it's beautiful.
Remarkable.
I've never seen
anything like it.
It's gorgeous.
TED: Come on. This way.
Don't be shy.
MlSS PLUSHBOTTOM:
Oh, this is so exhilarating.
You know, Timmy,
I have an original
George in my penthouse.
Wow, that looks
just like.... Ivan!
Wait.
Ted! Ted! Over here.
There you are, 17-B.
Boy, you're light
on your feet for a big man.
I must admit, your monkey
shows real talent.
Quite the artist.
So I am taking back
kickinging you from building.
Oh, that's great, lvan.
No hard feelings.
Oh, Georgie,
you're just so cute.
I think he likes me.
Right over there.
Thanks, Mr. Bloomsberry.
I parked all the cars, Father.
Good job, Son.
Really? A good job.
Oh, Father. Oh, Father.
Hug time.
There, there, my boy.
Hug your son.
It's okay. It's okay.
Tighter. Yes.
Daddy's here.
Hold me.
WOMAN: Good job, sweetheart.
Wow, George.
You are so fast!
What is that?
I'm not one to brag,
but I call it
The Magnificator.
That's so cool.
Say, have you
seen Sparky?
I found a rib bone.
I found a femur.
I found.... Sparky.
And I am happy to say
that because of Ted--
Sir, George,
don't forget George.
And George, of course.
We are not going anywhere.
The Bloomsberry Museum
is here to stay.
All right, all right,
last question.
Ted, where will you and George
go for your next adventure?
The Arctic?
South America? Egypt?
You know, you don't need
to go around the world
for a great adventure...
I have a lot of things
to catch up on right here.
Really?
Really.
Mister, George is--
I know, he's cute. Lovable.
Very cute. Very lovable.
Yeah, well,
he's also in that rocket.
It's okay.
There's no fuel in it.
[Rumbling]
Clovis, you didn't put fuel
in that rocket, did you?
Maybe.
Oh, no.
I see a rocket
with empty fuel tanks...
what am I supposed to do?
George, wait!
MAN: Bye.
CLOVlS: See you, Ted.
GlRL: Look at all the smoke.
CLOVlS: No hard feelings, huh?
Careful, Ted! Hurry back!
Okay, but once around
the Earth and then
straight home.
Do you hear me? Okay?
I've got plans tonight.
Gosh.
No, no, no, George,
I'm not letting you drive.
Just sit back and....
No, George.
Don't push that button.
I don't know what it does.
George, don't....
Hold on, George! Oh, boy!
That is a surge
of adrenaline.
I'm going to sleep
good tonight.
[Upside Down by
Jack Johnson playing]
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org