Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
lt's a big claim. Cops want to
nail the guy who stole it too.
We have to pay out $30,000.
To them, it's another heist.
Has the owner
stashed it someplace?
ls she trying to defraud us
out of a lot of money?
lf you have a large sums of cash
in the house,
we insist on certain alarm and
security alarms
which my supervisor has to approve.
But what we usually do is handle
the installation ourselves.
Sweetheart, can l get you?
John, do you have a minute?
-l haven't had lunch.
-What do you want?
Cherry cheesecake, prune Danish
and some Hershey bars.
And something sweet.
Some chocolate covered raisins.
-l found the missing Picasso.
-l don't believe it.
Galaxie Opticals. They rolled it up,
it's in a telescope.
How'd you figure it out?
lt wasn't easy.
l was looking for a picture
of a woman with a guitar,
but it's all little cubes.
Took me two hours to find the nose.
Better call the cops.
Right away.
Would you excuse me?
Rosie, get me the fingerprints
on the Leland claim.
-Who won the 6th at Aqueduct?
-Your horse came in 7th..
Never bet on a horse
with Parkinson's.
Congratulations.
l heard you recovered the Picasso.
-Yeah, congrats.
-lt was a breeze.
Here's something till
your order arrives.
You want to be my date tonight?
-What' tonight?
-George's birthday.
We're taking George out.
Sure. But you have to get me home
and in bed by midnight.
That's exactly what l was planning.
That girl has a body
that won't quit.
lt won't stop 5 minutes
for a coffee break.
Briggsie, l forgot to tell you...
Where are my... Rosie!
Where are my files?
-Where are my files?
-Moved.
They moved the files? Why?
Streamlining.
-This is Fitzgerald?
-Who else?
Did you take the files out
of my office?
-Can you come in like a human being?
-Did you move my files?
Or like an orangutan.
That would be a step up, too.
Put them back now. This instant.
You knew about the move.
Take my files and put them back
in my office now.
You had time
to move them yourself?
lf you were a man, l'd slam you
in the teeth.
lf l were a man, you'd be hiding
under the desk.
l gave you an order.
An order?
Who you think l am
some peroxide stenographer with brains
in her sweater who rear you pinch?
Pinch? l couldn't get
my arms around it.
l work for Magruder, not you.
We're turning this place around.
l've been working here twenty years.
You're here six months.
l'm not interested in your ideas.
Get my files and put them back now.
Or what?
''Or what?''
This is the question you ask me?
Are you saying, ''or what?'' to me?
Get off my toe, or you'll sing
castrati with a glee club.
l hated you from the day you
set foot in this office.
You hate any woman who doesn't have
a double-digit l.Q.
l'm a good judge of character.
l hate you
and the chancellor of Germany with
the moustache but not in that order.
Don't let the door hit your back
and fracture the your pelvis.
You tell her who's boss?
How can she talk to me like that?
She thinks she's smarter
because she graduate from Vassar
and l went to driving school.
Does she know how many
cases l cracked?
Never trust a woman who whistles
for her own cabs.
Miss Fitzgerald?
ls that Miss Fitzgerald's lunch?
Sorry it's so late.
No problem.
Here, keep that.
This is Fitzgerald's lunch.
l'll deliver it to her.
You got to come
to some terms with her.
We don't need an efficiency expert.
The old man wouldn't have got one.
You were going to take her for
a drink to clear the air.
l did. l took her two weeks ago
to Rocky's Bar.
You and her at Rocky's Bar?
Sorry l'm late.
No problem.
lt's just and hour and fifteen.
My meeting ran long.
No, l understand.
We're getting rid of
that antiquated filing system.
l can find anything
l need.
l got a feel for where all
the stuff is in my office.
A central data file will be on
the 2nd floor. You'll get used to it.
What's wrong? You look flushed.
l'm just a little warm,
that's all.
You have all your
business meetings here?
lt's near the office.
Coat check girl's pretty.
-You don't like it?
-lt's fine.
lt gives new meaning to the word
''dive'' but it it's convenient.
l thought you'd like the thick smoke.
You don't need as much make up.
-What's the lady is having?
-Tequila.
So,...
Betty...
Betty Ann...
Can l call you...?
l can call you Miss Fitzgerald.
l have no problem with that.
l,... tell me about yourself.
Myself?
Your hopes,
your dreams.
Are you married? Obviously not
or it wouldn't be ''Miss Fitzgerald''.
Do you have a boyfriend?
ls this why you got me here?
l just,...
What's your life like?
Do you have any hobbies?
l have a meeting
in 1 5 minutes, so...
Your marital status is none
of my business.
Maybe it's a touchy point
with you.
You're possibly divorced
or widowed.
Maybe your husband committed
suicide. l could understand that.
Mr. Magruder hired me to streamline
the office. l'm going to.
But if something's not broken, l say,
why fix it?
There's a reason North Coast
has slipped from the top five.
There's enormous waste
and duplication.
Not in my department.
Any department can be run more
efficiently and economically.
Perhaps North Coast should eliminate
the investigative division
and farm out cases privately.
Would it be possible to
have a drink and discuss that?
We are having a drink.
You don't know what you're saying.
You came in here like a steamroller.
You felt threatened by me
the day l started.
l was l a challenge to your little
state-within-a-state...
and l'm not some wind-up doll
to tickle at the cooler.
l'm smarter than you.
l'm faster.
l see right through you.
You're right to feel threatened.
l am threatened by you?
lt's fascinating how many men
l meet with a fragile masculinity.
Fragile masculinity?
One more crack about
my religion and l'll...
l have to go.
Honey, let me level with you.
Despite all your highfalutin'
talk about streamlining
what you really need is
a good roll in the hay.
You wouldn't know
which end is up.
ln your case,
it would be hard to tell.
Don't see me out.
Someone may think we're together.
Do l look like
an organ grinder?
No. Just an organ.
Get used to her.
She's here to stay.
There's something about her
l don't trust. She's evil.
We have a reservation at the
Rainbow Room for George's 50th.
That'll be fun.
l don't have time to go home
to change. Does look okay?
No matter how bad the economy gets,
you'll never starve.
Good.
Wait. Miss Fitzgerald?
Okay, take a card.
You got to see this, Fitz.
That's the six of hearts.
That's amazing! How'd you do that?
-Magic.
-He could do it all afternoon.
l want you to teach me
one of those tricks.
Mr. Magruder, the report
will be done tomorrow.
You coming to George's birthday
celebration?
No. l'm up to my neck in work.
lt'll be fun.
George is a great guy.
Everyone here's nice. Only Briggs
gives me the dry heaves.
C.W? He's cracked
a lot of cases.
l don't see how. Such a drone.
Gets his tips from street contacts,
like ex-cons and blind beggars.
There's something about him
l don't trust.
-Any examples?
-Many.
He's smarmy, with those wisecracks
and double-meaning jokes.
l mean, who is he, really?
A shallow, skirt-chasing egomaniac
who's probably more lucky than good.
Sometimes it's better to be lucky.
You're being too rough on him.
He's just an insecure schnook.
He has no wife or family.
He was married. Short and stormy.
Picked a tramp.
That's a surprise.
Come tonight.
We'll get to be together.
lt's the perfect excuse,
an employee's birthday
How much longer will this go on?
Not much longer.
l'll be free by the end of year.
You love me, but spend all the
important holidays with her.
Life can get so complicated when
you think it's simple. Come tonight.
So we can eye each other and
play little games in code?
Yes. That's part of the romance.
We'll look back and know that...
when one of us brought up Paris,
it meant...
we are dying to make love.
You are such adolescent.
But cute?
Look at this.
Here's to George Bond,
insurance man, father.
Amateur magician.
George, no card tricks tonight.
Happy fiftieth, George.
Everyone, l'd like to make
a toast to C.W. Briggs.
Thanks to you, the police now
have the stolen Picasso.
What made you think of looking
in the telescope?
What l do is put myself
in the criminal's position.
l try to anticipate what
he'll do next. l think like him.
Fantastic.
l would hate to have me
after me.
What are you thinking, Mr. Magruder?
You look lost in reverie.
Sorry. l was just reading about
the Germans occupying Paris.
Doesn't look good.
-C.W., ever been to Paris?
-l've never been out of the country.
Six-zero-dash-six...
eight-dash-five...
eight-five-seven.
That's right.
That's exactly correct.
And now for something l call
''The Power of Jade Scorpion''.
For this, l'll need some victims,
l mean, volunteers from the audience.
A few nice people.
Miss, would you?
Sir?
-Here's another one!
-There's a sucker born every minute!
Represent us well, Briggs!
Many years ago...
an emperor in China received
as a gift this precious pendant.
A Jade Scorpion.
lt was said to possess extraordinary
powers to darken men's minds.
l can't get hypnotized.
l'm a bad subject.
Eyes only on the Scorpion, please.
Ears open...
to the sound of my voice.
Look at the Scorpion.
The surrender of the mind.
They resist and resist.
But the Scorpion
likes resistance.
What is your name, sir?
C.W. Briggs.
And what do you do, Mr. Briggs?
l'm an insurance investigator
for North Coast Casualty and
Fidelity of New York.
What is your name, miss?
Betty Ann Fitzgerald.
l also work at North Coast.
So you work together?
l can't stand her.
Don't pay attention to him.
He's a sleazy megalomaniac who's
frightened of women.
Enough. Sleep.
Silence.
The Jade Scorpion wants
you to go to the deepest level.
When l say ''Constantinople'', you'll
drop into the deepest trance.
All resistance will disappear.
When l say ''Madagascar'',
you will go to the deepest level
of hypnotic sleep.
You will obey all my orders.
Ready.
Constantinople. Madagascar.
C.W. Briggs,
Miss Betty Ann Fitzgerald,
l now pronounce you man and wife.
When l snap my fingers you'll awaken,
not knowing you're in a trance.
You will be madly in love
with each other.
You're on your honeymoon
on a desert island.
Maestro?
The moon shines down
its magical glow
on you two honeymooners.
You're deeply in love.
Ready?
One, two, three. Awaken
to your tropical paradise.
What are you thinking?
l'm thinking
l'm the luckiest man
in the world
to have you.
l'm the lucky one, C.W.
l was in love with you
the first moment l saw you.
Make love to me here
under the stars, to the sound
of the ocean.
Miss Fitzgerald.
You're making a mistake.
l'm not longer Miss Fitzgerald.
l'm Mrs. C.W. Briggs.
Betty Ann!
Make love here to me here. Now.
Stop. Enough.
Unfortunately, every dream must
turn to reality.
When l snap my fingers, you'll awaken
with no memory of this event.
You'll return to your regular lives,
with whatever destinies await you.
l hope they are pleasant ones.
Ready?
On the snap of my fingers.
One, you're beginning to come up.
Two, the memory is fading completely.
Three, the Jade Scorpion has created
the miracle of love.
And four, awaken.
How do you feel?
Waiting for something to happen.
l'm not very good subject.
Me, neither. l told you wouldn't work.
Well, l tried my best.
George, back me. You gazed into
her eyes and said you loved her.
You're crazy. Never. lt's a
conspiracy to make me look crazy.
l hope someone talks to me
like that someday.
l can't bear Fitzgerald.
Speaking of that
shouldn't we be getting home
to feed your cat?
l'm getting a cold. l want to
go to bed with some tea.
lf you got a cold, someone has to
rub your chest with Vicks.
Anyone rubs my chest,
better bring a ring.
Good for you.
Good night, baby.
l knew we'd get some
time alone if you came.
l'm glad l came.
Hello?
Constantinople.
You are
in a deep trance.
You will fall deeper
under the sway of my words.
You will obey my instructions
carefully.
You will go to the Kensington
estate, where you will obtain
all the jewels
from the safe.
With the utmost secrecy,
you will use all the information and
techniques at your command.
You will do it with
ease and facility.
Then you will return to
your apartment, with the jewels.
You'll hide them in a safe and
secure hiding place,
awaiting further instructions
from me.
You'll then fall into a deep slumber
and awake refreshed
without no memory
of what has occurred.
You will wait to hear from me.
Your life will be as your life is,
until you hear from me.
Obey my instructions
to the letter.
You'll remember nothing that occurred
under trance. ls that clear to you?
Very clear.
Go. the Jade Scorpion
commands it.
Awful late, Mr. Briggs.
Hot on a case?
The Kensington safe
was broken into.
Jewels worth millions,
all gone.
Cops haven't a clue.
Magruder is numb.
l don't understand, l burglar-
proofed that placed myself.
Tell that to the perpetrator.
We're on the hook for big money,
so get over there fast.
Those stones could be on the market
in Tangier or Cairo.
Everything, my emerald tiara,
my sapphire necklace from lndia.
That sapphire is the most perfect
in the world.
No fingerprints,
but a partial shoe print.
-Man or woman?
-l can't be sure.
l want to interview everybody,
butlers, gardeners, everybody.
l think your gut reaction
is betraying you, C.W.
Nobody in this house is involved.
l'd bet my life.
l want to search.
Can l go upstairs?
lf you must, be fast. We've had
enough excitement for one day.
Mrs. Kensington? You know
Alfie and l would never...
Lotte, of course not.
What are you doing
in my mother's closet?
Well, hello.
You're one of those grubby
private detectives, aren't you?
A private eye, they're called.
A shamus. A gumshoe.
No, l'm a grubby
insurance investigator.
Private eyes are romantic.
l'm just grubby.
You always get your kicks
fondling women's shoes?
No, once in a while l'll fondle
a whole woman.
You have a fresh mouth.
l'm not sure l like you.
l grow on people. We could meet
later, and l could grow on you.
You don't seem tough enough
to go after criminals.
Maybe if l slap you around,
you'll change your mind.
l could slap you back.
This is starting to sound like fun.
Shall we put some music on?
Why are you snooping around?
You're Laura Kensington, right?
That's right.
And l have a strawberry mark on
my thigh to prove it. Want to see?
Maybe later, when l can take
the full tour.
My fiancé
might not appreciate that.
Which one?
So you follow my life.
l read the tabloids.
You've seen photos of me
diving into a public fountain.
And getting arrested for speeding
and throwing champagne at El Morocco.
While l live the fast life,
you snoop in people's closets.
Can l help it
if l'm paid by the clue?
-Did the burglar leave any?
-No. Because he's still among us.
-Says who?
-The little man who lives inside me.
So you're C.W. Briggs.
l hear you're a sharp investigator
with an impressive record.
l looked forward to meeting you.
They say l always get my man.
Me, too.
Right.
l'm glad we could have this chat.
Too bad the house is full of people.
Where shall we go tonight?
Chinatown or Harlem?
You prefer jazz or opium?
l prefer the rug
in front of my fireplace.
Directly to your apartment?
You always begin with the dessert?
lt depends what l'm eating.
This will be
an interesting experiment.
l usually prefer more attractive,
athletic, muscular men.
Maybe l could do a few push-ups
before you came over.
What about your fiancé?
lf you don't invite him, l won't.
-Any leads?
-lt's an inside job. No question.
-That's not what the cops say.
-They're wrong.
The Giants playing this afternoon?
They're playing the Cardinals,
in St. Louis.
Call my bookmaker. Make a bet for me
1 00 dollars on the Giants.
The Giant to win?
Naturally. What do you think,
to place?
Mr. Magruder? Tilt.
-The Kensington situation?
-lnside job, l'd bet my life on it.
You bet your life on the Giants,
and they're in 6th place.
Can we talk without the warden.
Miss Fitzgerald is part
of the company.
We must work together
in harmony.
Why do you think
it's an inside job?
Only an inside job would be
that smooth.
Miss Fitzgerald suggests
expanding our investigation.
-Meaning what?
-l appreciate the value of intuition.
But we're moving into a decade
of scientific innovation.
Miss Fitzgerald suggested
we might get you some help
by farming out some work to
an outside detective agency.
See if a new approach, fresh
techniques make a difference.
Don't be threatened immediately.
You said l'm only threatened by
women with high lQs.
North Coast has to keep up
with the marketplace.
There's a lot of money at stake.
The trail's growing cold.
lf Coopersmith Detective Agency
contributes, fine.
lf not, we're only out
a few bucks.
The Coopersmiths are like
Fric and Frac. They're submental.
We're moving into a new decade,
the 1 940s. Things are different.
Max Baer needs
a sparring partner.
You're the only person giving me
this kind of resistance.
You're a dinosaur, with your street
ways and disorganized methods.
Please. My father
always stressed harmony.
l've got to go.
l'm working on a case.
We'll have lunch. l know a restaurant
you'll love. Gestapo food.
Don't get hit by a bus, your body
mangled beyond recognition.
l ain't heard a word
about any job.
Nobody tried to fence anything
or do any bragging.
Charlie, you've got to help me
with this.
Keep your ears open. Anything
you hear, l got to know.
lt's very important to me.
50? You must be desperate.
You know where to reach me.
Keep eating carrots. They're working.
l think they're gone up there,
Mr. Briggs.
l just have to check something.
l'll be right down.
You startled me.
l was working late.
Eddie said he didn't think
anyone was up here.
Well, l'm here.
Obviously, l'm here.
Why are you so nervous?
l'm not nervous.
Why would l be nervous?
l'm working alone.
l didn't expect to see you.
Don't you always work late?
That's what l hear.
ls this Twenty Questions?
You scared me.
l'm alone, filling out reports.
Asking Magruder to remove
the water coolers?
Make wisecracks somewhere else.
l'm busy.
Don't work too late. The bags
under your eyes are getting bigger.
Good night. And if you have a sudden
coronary thrombosis,
go straight to the hospital.
You were right. We shouldn't
fool around at the office.
-He gives me the willies.
-He's harmless.
-How did you get in?
-lt wasn't hard.
You had your father
buy the building?
A small tip to the super
was all it took.
For you, maybe. l give the super
a small tip, he spits on my shoes.
l brought some very expensive
Russian vodka, 1 20 proof.
Don't drop that.
You'll blow up the building.
There's nothing to read but detective
magazines and the racing form.
No, l have a deck of cards
with naked women on them.
Let me guess,
you use it to play solitaire?
l used to date
the six of spades.
l love where you live.
lt's just what l thought,
a grimy, little rathole.
l'll tell my decorator.
lt's the effect we were going for.
You dying to see
my strawberry mark?
lf it's in the same spot
it was this afternoon.
This is a novelty for me.
l'm used to penthouses and yachts,
gorgeous European lovers who...
sweep me off my feet.
Yet, l find it strangely exciting
standing here in a grungy hovel
with a myopic
insurance clerk
There's a compliment in there
somewhere l just don't know where.
You taking that coat off?
lt hasn't rained in here in 20 years.
What do you think?
lf l happen to pass away while
we're doing anything,
have the embalmer leave
the smile on my face.
Perfect timing.
l'll slip into something more
comfortable and wait in bed.
More comfortable? Are you going
to put on Jergens lotion?
Constantinople.
You are in the power
of the Jade Scorpion.
You will proceed
to the Dillworth mansion.
You will enter and open the safe.
Ever heard of an lndian book
called the Kama Sutra?
l'm sorry, but we have to postpone
our little rendezvous.
Pardon me?
l just recalled a prior engagement.
l hope you don't mind.
The doorman will get you a taxi.
l had a wonderful evening. Thank you.
You're joking.
l'll turn around so you can
get dressed. Please hurry.
l'm rather pressed for time.
Have you got a loose screw?
Tonight was very meaningful to me.
l'll think of it in a cherished way.
lf you're in the neighborhood
again, drop in.
What's come over you?
Should you want a snack for
the way back home,
l have a dish of peanuts
in the other room.
You hate women, don't you?
Not at all.
They're a splendid gender.
Really.
A very pleasant variation.
l should have known.
A mousy, little clerk like you,
chasing criminals your entire life.
Laura, don't be cross.
Drop in again in the spring.
The oleander will be in bloom.
l'm going. l'm getting out.
l'm not used to getting kicked out
of a man's bed.
You're very sick.
Thanking you in advance for
understanding.
God bless you.
You have splendidly shaped buttocks.
l can't believe it. lt's identical.
Think someone from the Kensington
house pulled this one, too?
We did the security here.
We made the place foolproof.
Someone's a step ahead of you.
l want to speak
to the Dillworths.
The Coopersmith detectives
are grilling them.
l can't believe it!
She convinced Magruder to hire
the Coopersmiths.
We need all the help
we can get on this case.
You want to talk to me, fellas?
We're in on this now, C.W.
This is my case,
just so you know.
Like we horned in.
Hey, they called us.
-That was their first mistake.
-Maybe they think you're slipping.
-You know my brother Joe?
-The one who died at birth?
l hear you're having trouble.
-You guys got any clues?
-A few.
Want to share them with me?
l'll let you know if they're
real clues or a laundry list.
lf we make a collar, it'll mean
a long-term deal with North Coast.
l hear they're
making changes up there.
l'm going to make this bust
them you'll be back at your
old jobs finding lost poodles.
We laughed when we heard you said
the Kensington's was an inside job.
l can see we'll be tripping
all over each other.
One of us is going to fall down.
We don't plan on falling.
You're in over your heads.
This is a very smart burglar
and you can't figure it out
if you get a confession.
We figure we're looking for
a tall man, heavy set,
athletic, about
thirty years old.
Belly button in or out?
lf he's short, he's too fat to
squeeze through the kitchen window.
Show him the big clue.
Did the guy leave behind
his birth certificate?
Show him.
No one in this house was ever
to Rocky's Bar.
l've been to Rocky's Bar. Big deal.
6 million people eat there.
We're gonna nail this guy.
The important thing is,
don't think of us as competition.
Don't worry.
l don't.
Why are you upset? We'll get him.
Can you believe she talked Magruder
into hiring those jerks?
You've been moping all day.
What's going on?
l have a confession to make.
l woke up this morning and found
this on the floor of my apartment.
So?
l have no memory of being
with anybody last night.
That happens to everybody.
You pick up a broad, get drunk.
You didn't remember.
There was an empty bottle of vodka
on the floor. l don't drink vodka.
That's why you blacked out.
Vodka does funny things to a person.
l've gotten up with some
strange-looking heads under my arm.
No, there's something wrong, Al.
l came back here.
I wanted to check something
in my office. I remember that.
This was about nine o'clock.
Wait a minute. I ran in.
Wait a minute.
What?
Of course. No wonder l thought
it was an inside job.
But not inside the Dillworths'
or the Kensingtons'.
lt's inside our company.
lt's obvious.
Why didn't l see it right away?
Only Mize, Bond and me have
access to your security set-ups.
And what if someone else
was given access?
Someone we don't know as well
because she hasn't worked here
as long as we have?
Fitzgerald?
Why not? Why not?
We've had female
jewel thieves before.
She always saying she can do
anything a man can do.
l doubt she meant stealing.
What do we know about her? Nothing.
She has expensive tastes.
She wears good jewelry.
-l got to get into her office.
-Don't.
-l must.
-lf you get caught,
she'll take a gun a shoot you.
She goes duck hunting.
lt makes perfect sense.
She's here late every night.
We've given her the files.
She knows the security information.
l got to search her place.
Don't rifle her desk.
You'll get caught.
-What are you doing?
-Me?
You're going through my desk.
l beg your complete pardon.
You were snooping in my papers.
Only a suspicious, paranoid mind
would say something like that.
l doubt Amish people or Quakers
would come to that conclusion.
You wormy little ferret.
Now you're mixing metaphors.
-l know why you're snooping.
-l wasn't snooping.
To find the Coopersmiths' report.
You hired them to give me
a hard time.
lt's too many cooks,
we're all over each other.
They made more progress in a few
hours than you have in 2 days.
Were you crying? Your mascara.
Don't tap dance out of getting
caught searching my desk.
l wasn't searching.
l was rummaging.
Get out. lf l catch you going
through my stuff again...
-What are you afraid l'll find?
-You can't find your nose in the dark.
Watch out. l'm onto you.
l know what you are.
This is silly. We should both
calm down.
You could have a stroke
killing you instantly
or paralyzing half your body.
She hit the ceiling
when she caught me before.
Because she's guilty.
Look behind her eyes. She's bad.
She has pretty eyes.
l said look behind the eyes.
There's something wrong.
The minute l met her,
l sensed trouble.
lf you two were boxers, we could get
a millions dollar gate.
l got to get into her place.
Being an investigator doesn't
put you above the law.
She could get you locked up.
That ever stopped me before?
She's out tonight.
-How do you know?
-l went through her appointments.
She's meeting her sister for dinner.
She said her sister's
an invalid in Detroit.
See? Nothing she says ever
checks out.
You can't break into her apartment.
lt's unethical.
l won't break in. l got the key.
-How'd you get that?
-Stole it from her purse.
What happens when she finds it
missing?
She won't. l copied it and
put the original back.
You've a touch of larceny in you.
You'd have made a great thief.
lt takes one to catch one,
don't forget that. See you.
Can l take your coat, honey?
What did you want to tell me?
No drink?
How much alcohol do you need
to be completely honest?
-You're not making this easy.
-Why should l?
Because we care about each other.
Before you loved me.
Now you care for me?
-Betty Ann, sit down.
-l won't faint. l've been dumped.
Don't say things like that.
You got me out of the restaurant
because you were afraid
l'd make a scene or pass out.
You are a volatile woman.
Am l? Most men complain
l'm cool as ice.
-l care about you.
-You said that.
-l want to leave Caroline.
-But you're not.
l've tried to find the courage
a hundred times.
All those promises? Stories about
how miserable you were at home?
-You're making this into a nightmare.
-lsn't it?
Try to understand.
We can still be friends.
We can even continue
to sleep together.
Are you nuts? l only got involved
because you told me
your marriage was
on its last legs.
-Sounds like l deceived you.
-Haven't you?
l didn't mean to.
l respect you too much.
We went from ''love'' to you
''care for'' to you ''respect'' me.
Soon you'll be buying me
a prayer shawl.
Leave me alone. Okay?
Just go. l'll be fine.
-Honey, listen.
-Leave me alone!
l hope you stay at North Coast.
You're turning our company around.
Guess we won't be honeymooning
in Positano.
l feel like such a jerk!
Don't. l got into this against
my better judgment.
-Oh, honey.
-Just go.
Goodbye, Chris.
Goodbye, New York.
Miss Fitzgerald!
What are you doing?
What are you doing here?
-What do you mean?
-What are you doing here?
l was passing through.
-l was hiding behind your screen.
-Behind what?
That nice Japanese screen.
l was hiding behind it.
How did you get in?
How long have you been here?
Quite a while, actually.
-You broke into my apartment?
-No.
-How did you get in?
-You want to know?
-l made a copy of your key.
You what?
You can have it for no charge.
lt's good to have two keys.
Why did you do this?
l'm convinced that someone
at North coast
is responsible for
the jewel robbery.
Who, me?
-You're a prime suspect, yes.
-Based on what?
l know everyone better than you
and you have access to the data.
So do you.
But you were so nervous
the other night.
You acted strange and you have
a Rocky's matchbook.
Remember we had a drink at Rocky's?
lt didn't go too well.
So you broke into my apartment
and spied on me?
l wasn't spying.
l'm a big rummager.
You what?
l was rummaging and the afternoon
and saw ''dinner with my sister''.
All those dinners with your sister
were Magruder, right?
God, l'm mortified!
lf not for me, they'd be scraping
you up with spoon.
That's none of your business.
And over a jerk like Magruder.
He's not a jerk. He's twice
the man you are, you roach.
Don't you see? He tells you
stories to get in your pants.
He won't leave his wife.
You witnessed my humiliation.
lt's humiliating taking advantage
of a smart woman like you.
You're not fit to discuss
Chris Magruder.
Look at this. She still loves him.
Get out before l call the police
and have you arrested.
l'm not letting you alone here.
Are you crazy?
l'd ask if you had any friends,
but l know the answer.
Give me this. Jesus.
Great.
Are you okay?
Hello?
What are you doing here?
l'm making coffee.
l remember. You came here because
you thought l stole the jewels.
This is a very confusing case.
l'll say you're confused.
Why didn't you go home?
And let you do something crazy?
-like what?
-Like dive out the window.
-l wouldn't even with you here.
-Because l watched over you.
You stayed up watching me?
Yes. And you snore like a grizzly
bear with a sinus condition.
l had a bad moment.
l'm fine now.
-You talk in your sleep.
-You probably took notes, inchworm.
-Who's Rita?
-The woman my ex ran off with.
You sure know how to pick men.
There's not a lot to pick from.
You mentioned me, too.
You said l should rot in hell.
-l was probably awake.
-l figured you were felling better.
Now, if you'll go. Don't gossip
about what you saw last night.
Nobody's going to because l
couldn't care less about your life.
l couldn't stand you when l met you
and can't stand you now.
l find you obnoxious and pompous.
Do me a favor, if you see me
in the office walk the other way.
And if Magruder tells you
he's leaving his wife...
if l were you,
l'd keep my legs crossed.
Don't choke on breakfast
and die, unable to dislodge
a piece of toast,
no matter how hard you cough!
Mr. Magruder?
lf you'll all open your hymn books
to page 90.
Sit down, C.W.
We have a situation.
Your brother looks good.
The embalmer did nice work.
l'll let the Coopersmiths
fill you in.
After a careful search, using
up-to-the-minute techniques...
we found some interesting clues.
Leading to who,
Eleanor Roosevelt?
We got a shoe print
at the Kensington place.
So?
An 8 1 l2-C Florsheim cordovan.
Worn by 20 million Americans.
l wear them.
For this money, you cannot get
a better shoe.
We also found a couple of hairs.
One on the rug at the Kensington's,
the other in the Dillworth safe.
They match.
Forgive me if l'm not knocked out.
We don't mean just each other.
They match yours.
Just like the 8 1 l2-C cordovans.
l know you're angling
for my job...
-We got a print off the matchbook.
-A fingerprint off a matchbook?
Our lab uses sensitive apparatus.
-You're not going to say it's mine?
-lt is.
Well, so what?
So l leave a footprint or
inadvertently drop a matchbook.
The matchbook was found before
you got to the place.
You don't doubt my honesty, do you?
l was a Boy Scout for three years.
l have several merit badges and
my clergyman
who is wanted for pederasty,
will vouch for me.
Nobody's making any accusations.
You do have outstanding debts from
betting on baseball, the ponies.
Are you investigating me?
l assure you this is only
an inquiry in-house at this time.
We're not looking for bad publicity.
Miss Fitzgerald, what do you think?
You're a bright woman.
You think l did it?
Let's not have the daily bloodbath
between you and Miss Fitzgerald.
-She's not an investigator.
-But she has lots of ideas.
She brought these
mouth-breathers in.
C.W., lt's nothing personal.
We all want to catch the thief.
l'm on your side.
l think we have to get
team jackets.
Rosie, l want to get resumes
of all our employees.
Don't worry, C.W. We'll get
to the bottom of this.
Miss Fitzgerald, l wanted to meet
with you later.
-About what?
-Our Paris account.
l believe that account is closed.
l have to see you,
just to talk.
l behaved like such a fool.
Later, just for a drink.
Well.
Can l come in?
Sure. l'm shocked.
The place is a little messy.
lf l knew you were coming, l'd have
had the maid rearrange the dirt.
Are you alone?
Alone? Of course.
l'd have called, but l decided
it was safer to talk in person.
-''Safer''?
-l can't stay long.
You meeting Magruder in Paris?
That's none of your business.
Thanks for defending me today.
lt was nice of you.
That's what l want to discuss.
The Coopersmiths questioned
Laura Kensington today.
She said she was with you
the night before last.
You got a phone call,
began acting very strangely...
and got rid of her because
you had somewhere to go.
She's lying.
Why would she lie?
Use you head. Would l kick
Laura Kensington out of bed?
Even if the President needed me.
-Why are you lying?
-Why this crazy story?
Because l should've spoken up today.
Even if you are a mealy-mouthed...
-Reptile.
-...reptile, you're no jewel thief.
Why are you so positive?
lt's too daring for you.
You're not romantic enough.
lt requires flair, imagination.
My instincts say it's not you.
-l didn't think you had instincts.
-l do.
l don't usually trust them
about men, but this time l do.
You're good at weasely things,
like snooping and spying.
You're not man enough for a burglar.
Sounds like you're attracted to
men who break the law.
Let's not discuss me.
Let's discuss what Laura said.
Laura Kensington was not here.
She...
She was not here.
She said she left
her stocking here.
That could be anybody's.
Lots of women pass through here.
There's a lot of action here.
l'm sure you're not particular.
Look, what do you want from me?
l enjoy a well-proportioned
member of the opposite sex.
That's how God created us.
Who am l to quibble with His concept?
A case is building against you.
Be honest with me!
-l'm honest.
-Where did you get this stocking?
Some broad's. Women lose an
earring, a stocking, l don't know.
Laura says it's hers.
She says the super let her in.
The story checks out.
Whoever that is, l'm not here.
-Who is it?
-Herb and Joe Coopersmith.
l don't want to be seen here.
Why? Am l a leper?
You're a suspect.
l'd have explaining to do.
You're still hooked on Magruder.
Go to the bedroom, shut the door.
Can l sit down,
or will l catch something?
Germs can't live in your blood.
lt's too cold.
Open up, C.W.!
Coming.
Sure you got the right apartment?
The mousetraps are in the basement.
Can we come in?
Wait. l got a chorus girl
in the back room.
lt isn't Laura Kensington, is it?
l don't know. They all look
the same upside down.
She says she was here
the other night,
till you dumped her to go out
on some mysterious business.
Would l dump Laura Kensington?
l eat Wheaties.
But Eddie, the night guard
at the North Coast building,
said you made strange, middle-
of-the-night visits to your office
the nights of both robberies.
l'd love to chat, but there's
a nurse in the other room.
-l thought she was a chorus girl.
-Who does a little nursing.
Gimme a break. Can we talk tomorrow?
How can you make love?
You're facing a long jail sentence.
That's why l got to get in
all l can now.
We'll turn this over
to the police tomorrow.
The case is pretty incriminating.
lt's just circumstantial evidence.
Many a man's gone to the gallows
on circumstantial evidence.
The gallows will have to wait.
l got a cocktail waitress.
Cocktail waitress?
A nurse who's a bit of
a chorus girl
and works a lounge now and then.
Tell me if you catch the thief.
l'll get you both new yo-yos.
What is this?
l was browsing through
your bookshelf...
and l found this deck of
naked playing cards and these.
What? This is the
Kensington jewels!
This is the Dillworth jewels.
And this is...
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Because you found them among
my collection of female art studies?
What? l used to go with
the six of spades.
Then the four of diamonds
caught us together and...
l knew you sneaked up to the office
and the guard caught you.
You have Laura's stocking and
she swears you kicked her out of bed
to take care of
some sudden business.
They have a footprint,
a matchbook with your fingerprint.
Still, l believed that
you didn't do it.
But now the stolen property
turns up hidden in your bedroom.
And what?
This makes you suspect me?
l was touched you stayed up
all night watching over me.
l thought, ''Maybe he's not the
scummy vermin he seems to be.''
l may be scummy vermin, but l'm
honest. l didn't take these jewels.
How can you deny it?
Yes, l grant you,
there's a fingerprint of mine,
and a footprint and the jewels
are in my bedroom.
l'm starting to think
l'm in tremendous trouble.
l'm calling the police.
Forget logic. Give me
the benefit of the doubt.
-That makes me an accessory.
-Not if l'm innocent.
lnnocent? You haven't a
kosher bone in your body.
That's how you get into problems.
Magruder's waiting for you, right?
You make wrong decisions because
you make them here, not here.
They're not reliable because this
is gray cells and this is blood.
Blood circulates, it gets around.
lt knows the score.
Gray cells just lay there
and think. See what l mean?
Constantinople.
You will take all of the jewels.
Make sure you have them all.
Wrap them in brown paper so
no on can tell what they are.
Go to Grand Central Station.
Rent a locker. Lock them in.
Go home, taking the key with you.
Put it in your mailbox.
Leave the mailbox open.
Then you will go into
a deep, refreshing slumber.
When you awake, you will remember
nothing of what transpired.
Miss Fitzgerald,
have l ever told you...
you're one of the most beautiful
women l've ever met?
-l'm turning you in.
-l mean it.
Your eyes are what made me
first fall in love with you.
Unbelievable. You're trying to
sweet talk me?
l resisted because down deep
l thought you might hurt me.
l don't want to be
in that position again.
l wouldn't be interested in you
if you were the last man on Earth.
And l'm insulted you think l would
fall for such a heavy-handed ploy.
You must have a low opinion of me.
Thank you for dropping by.
l'm a little busy now.
Maybe tomorrow night
we can have dinner.
l can look into your eyes and
tell you how crazy about you l am.
lf l didn't know what a
squirming, trapped rat you were,
l'd think you had a brain tumor.
-You're late.
-l'm still trembling.
Over last night?
l didn't sleep.
lt's not that, Chris.
lt's Briggs.
He's guilty, isn't he?
lt's a sad story.
Don't make me
go into the details,
but l wonder if he's
having a mental breakdown.
He may be realizing
the consequences of his deeds.
Could he have a split personality?
Many criminals play crafty games
when it suits their purposes.
l need a drink.
lf l tell you something, promise
not to go off half-cocked?
Okay, but hurry.
l have some big news.
l found the jewels.
Keep me apprised, will you?
Thank you.
The police are on the way.
lt's an open and shut case.
l hate the publicity,
but l'm elated at the recovery.
lt's clear there's much more
to this, Chris.
Being around big money
can drive men to extremes.
These guys expose exotic schemes
to defraud and rob people.
Some think ''l know why they fail.
l won't make mistakes''.
So he's cracked from
so many years of hard work?
He's a driven man. He had a
terrible marital experience.
Turned him off women, except for
secretaries and barflies.
Crushed when he caught his wife
cheating, he's feeling older,
he looks around and says
''Maybe it's time l get mine.''
Guy named Peterson tried the same.
Now he's a houseguest in Sing Sing.
l'm sure you know him
better than l do.
lt'll resolve itself.
Betty Ann, l spoke with Caroline.
You did?
l told her
l wanted my freedom.
Really?
-lsn't that fabulous?
-lt's surprising.
l thought you'd be
knocked off your feet.
Well, it was last night.
lt's sort of a roller coaster.
Forget last night. l knew
l made a mistake right away.
What did she say?
She sensed we were drifting apart.
She was very poised.
Said if l was sure
that's what l wanted.
Another one of these, please.
You're not as euphoric
as l'd imagined.
You can't expect me to
change gears and turn on a dime.
Have you changed your mind?
No.
-You haven't met someone else?
-No, l haven't.
l don't understand.
What's going on? What did l do?
These are the ones.
They were in his bookcase.
He bets every day
and he usually loses.
He's into the bookmakers
for a bundle.
l was with him Tuesday till 1 2.
He got a call and was different.
lf it was anyone but C.W.,
we wouldn't be discussing this.
The jewels were in his locker.
An air-tight case.
l knew you guys wanted my job,
but l could get 30 years for this.
With good behavior,
you'll be out in 20.
l'll check every low-l.Q. club.
l'll find you and kill you.
Low l.Q., some genius.
lf you needed money, C.W.,
you could've come to me.
l'd have listened, though l
warned you about your gambling.
Can't you see
this is a conspiracy?
They plant some prints.
The night guard forges my signature.
This crazy girl who smokes opium
invents a story.
Fitzgerald plants the jewels
in my house.
There's a word for people who think
everyone's conspiring against them.
Yeah, ''perceptive''.
You tried to swallow
the key to the locker
where we found
the stolen goods.
-You got any witnesses?
-Yeah, me.
You'd take your word over mine?
Let's get him to the courthouse.
You better get a lawyer, C.W.
l'm shocked.
He was one of my best men.
You know how long l've know him?
Tommy, come with me.
Okay, Mike. Sorry, C.W.,
l'll arrange things. Stick around.
Well, well, if it isn't
Mr. Fast-Talking lnvestigator
caught with his hand
in the cookie jar.
Did l really throw you out of bed?
Why? You planning on using
the insanity defense?
Honey, l need help,
and you're going to help me.
Am l?
What makes you think that?
This is your kind of thing.
lt'll look great on your resume.
A suspected felon, a daring escape
in broad daylight.
You like this kind of thing.
Check the top drawer.
There must be a handcuff key.
l'm nervous.
See if there's a key.
Go. Hurry up.
l got to make this fast.
Or they'll put me away. l'll be
showering with men my whole life.
Miss, l'm sorry.
No one's allowed in here.
You want to come with me?
Let's go, unless you want to
be locked up, too.
-Sorry things didn't work out.
-Let's go.
-You want to lock me up?
-What's wrong?
-Take your hands off me!
-Something wrong with you?
Caroline and l are working on
the separation agreement.
l move out in 2 weeks.
The divorce will take longer.
That's why the agreement
must be secure.
l could get killed if
we were found together.
-Where are you?
-Do you think he's guilty?
-That's what you're thinking about?
-l have this uneasy feeling.
That he's innocent?
He was caught red-handed.
lt just doesn't feel right.
l don't see that snoopy termite
as a romantic jewel thief.
l'd hardly call breaking
the law romantic.
l didn't mean it that way.
Well, what did you mean?
l don't know what l mean anymore.
Yes, he is. Hold on.
lt's the Coopersmiths.
Really?
How?
Okay. Yes, l certainly will.
This should allay your doubts
about his culpability. He escaped.
Unlocked the handcuffs and
leaped to the building next door.
-C.W. Briggs?
-Like a common burglar.
l'm starting to realize
none of us really knew him.
l have to go to police headquarters.
Your little termite ate his way out.
-Did you forget...?
-Resist the urge to scream.
What are you doing here,
you jewel thief!
l'm not a thief, l'm a suspect.
Completely different.
A promising suspect, but l didn't
do it and l need time to prove it.
Or they'll lock me up and you could
only insult me on visiting days.
-Why did you come here?
-l have no one else to turn to.
Everyone knows you hate me
so no one will look for me here.
l need a place to sleep.
l'm exhausted.
You can't sleep here. l can't
afford the fumigation bills.
You want to call the police,
call them. l don't care.
l'm sleeping here. lf you want to
call them, then call them.
Get me the 1 1th Precinct.
Miss Fitzgerald?
Madagascar.
You are in a deep trance.
You will obey every command
the Jade Scorpion gives you.
You will acquire all security data
for the Adrian Greenwood mansion.
You will proceed there,
and after disabling the system
you will remove all the jewels
from the safe, each and every one.
These jewels you will hide
in your apartment. ls this clear?
Yes.
What's the matter?
Can't sleep?
No.
l've had the strangest dreams.
l've had some crazy dreams
myself lately.
l dreamed we were
finally together.
You and Magruder? A match made
in heaven by a retarded angel.
You misunderstand. l dreamed
you and l wound up together.
That's funny.
l didn't hear screaming.
The minute l met you,
l knew inside l'd found...
what l'd been searching for
all my life.
A roach? A vermin? A worm?
Did l call you a Black Widow?
l knew that sooner or later
we'd wind up in each other's arms.
Have you been gargling
with the tequila?
You're a very romantic man.
What did you smoke
before l woke up?
And if l told you l had the most
passionate crush on you l ever felt?
l'd fear for my life because
l'd think it was a set-up.
This song was playing
the time we met at Rocky's Bar.
You remember? Not that l didn't have
a good time, but l didn't.
My passion for you is so intense,
it scares me.
Can't you see l've submerged it
under hostile acts and words?
Don't worry, l never really
took it seriously.
''Crush you like an insect''
just meant ''back off a little''.
Couldn't you see l was
just protecting myself?
-Miss Fitzgerald...
-Call me Betty Ann.
l hate to be a killjoy,
but if this is a scheme to take
advantage of me, it's not subtle.
You're the man l'm going to marry.
l knew it right away.
We should call Bellevue.
You need electric shock, honey.
Kiss me?
Me? Lay a wet one on you?
l imagined if you kissed me,
l'd feel those fireworks.
-Are you like this out of the office?
-What are you thinking?
lt's a pity we hate each other
or we could've had a large family.
l'm going to swoon.
Steady. l affect women
this way sometimes.
-l can't stay awake.
-Easy.
l'll rest my head on you.
Easy. l must remember what soap
l used this morning.
What are you doing here?
Good morning, sweetheart.
Don't call me that.
What's going on?
l stayed awake thinking about
those things you said.
And all of that rang
a deep bell with me.
There were so many times when
we were arguing in the office
that l had the feeling that
down deep, underneath,
you were crazy about me.
About you?
Were you dropped on your head?
Hey, toots, l got to tell you,
last night, for a cold fish,
you were hot stuff.
Buster, don't call me
''toots'' or ''sweetheart''.
l'm not some Available Annie
who takes dictation on your lap.
What'd you do, sneak in here
and slip into my arms?
What's going on? Last night you
tried to undress me and kiss me.
What? You came in here and
passed out. l'm confused.
The Kensington and Dillworth
jewel thief has struck again.
C.W. Briggs, former employee of
North Coast Fidelity and Casualty,
is the chief suspect in the
Adrian Greenwood robbery.
The details of the crime
are the same as the first two.
The thief took $ 1 million in
jewelry and a like amount in cash.
Police recovered the jewels
from the earlier burglaries
which led to the capture
and arrest of C.W. Briggs.
So that's why you escaped.
Not to prove your innocence,
but for unfinished business.
But l was here with you!
For some reason l can't remember.
But l was asleep.
You could've awakened,
robbed these people and come back.
You used this as a safe haven.
l could've, but l didn't.
You tried to undress and kiss me.
l've never tried to undress you
in my life.
l wouldn't kiss you if we were
on a desert island for 20 years.
After 20 minutes l'd make a bow
and arrow and kill you.
What are you thinking?
l'm marrying Chris Magruder.
-You are?
-Yes.
We set a spring date,
when his divorce is final.
So if l was trying to kiss you,
l must have multiple personalities.
lf you marry Chris Magruder,
you have multiple stupidity.
lt must have been
the booze.
You were like a changed person,
and a much better one.
lf you're here after l take
a shower, l'm calling the police.
For a minute you dropped your guard.
Your were actually sexy.
Though in some lights,
you resemble Mussolini.
Pretty snazzy
for an office worker.
Magruder must love you
in an extravagant way.
He probably likes going to Paris
with you more than with his wife.
l understand you and Charlie
got something.
l came up with a name.
Really? Well, lay it on me.
Eddie Polgar.
Who's that?
l don't know,
but it's come up twice.
Eddie Polgar?
There's no police record.
lt could be an alias.
Blue men coming.
Keep moving.
-Charlie.
-C.W., is that you?
-l heard you wanted me.
-You're hot as a pistol.
The police want to give me
a lifetime achievement award.
Does the name Eddie Polgar mean
anything to you?
-Zero.
-l can't get a break.
Stick your hand in the cup.
-ln the cup?
-ln the cup, yeah.
38 cents and a wad of paper.
And someone threw away their gum
in your business establishment.
Open the wad of paper.
-Why?
-lt's a clue.
What kind of clue?
From last night's heist.
Coopersmiths found it on the driveway.
Charlie...
The burglar dropped it.
How'd you get it?
A friend of a friend works
in the Coopersmiths' building.
l thought you might want it.
These earrings
are grand larceny.
l see by the look on your face
that l helped you.
Cherchez la femme.
You know what that means?
''Find the woman''.
ls there a woman?
At first l thought so.
Then l didn't.
Now l think l got her.
You work next to a person
for years and one day...
l don't believe it.
Not C. W. lt makes no sense.
None of us expected it,
but there is proof.
Fitzgerald saw the jewels
in his apartment.
-He fought the cops over that key.
-Exactly.
lt's open-and-shut. You don't run
from the police if you're innocent.
What about the nerve it took to strike
twice? C.W. deserves some credit.
He turned out
to be a gutsy guy.
Where are you?
Never mind where l am.
l got to get up to the office.
l think more people are involved
in this thing.
l think Fitzgerald
is behind it.
Does the name Eddie Polgar mean
anything to you?
No.
l got to get to the office and
go over the Coopersmiths' report.
And l want to check out
Fitzgerald's desk again.
There's no question, Fitzgerald
is involved in this up to her neck.
You can't let your feelings
for this woman color your judgment.
lt has nothing to do with that.
lt's the only thing that makes sense.
l go to her house, figuring no one
will look for me there
because she hates me so.
l go to sleep.
Middle of the night, l hear
a noise and wake up. l find her.
l figure, she can't sleep,
either.
But, no. She'd done the Greenwood
heist and coming back.
l'd caught her, so she starts
to act very peculiar.
l trap her, so she starts
seducing me with her feminine wiles.
Meaning what?
Suddenly, l'm handsome and
and she can't her hands off me.
Does that sound like
Fitzgerald?
Or a schemer trying to play me
for a sucker?
lt sounds like that magic show
demonstration by Voltan Polgar.
Yeah. The night
of the first robbery.
l think she has feelings for you.
Don't be ridiculous.
She hates me.
What's the name of the magician
whose name
l've completely repressed?
Voltan.
Voltan the lnscrutable.
The Jade Scorpion.
What is his name?
Voltan Polgar.
Eli Voytak Polgar.
l'm just theorizing...
on an incredible sequence
of events.
You look like my Uncle Jerry
after a truck hit him.
What happened? l know you told me
before, but what happened?
They brought me onstage...
He put you in a trance, easily,
despite your resistance.
Right, yes. Then he brought...
Fitzgerald was with me
at the time.
Then you were awakened
in a post-hypnotic state
with a word that
would put you back under.
''Constantinople''.
Then he started making these...
C.W.?
Yes?
Are you okay?
l'm fine, Alvin.
How is your aging mother?
Obviously, he was never released
from the key word.
Wake him up, George.
This is scary.
Don't be scared.
This is right up my alley.
When l snap my fingers,
you will awaken.
You will have no memory
of what occurred. ls that clear?
You'll awaken feeling happy
and refreshed. ls that clear?
So the guy gets me onstage.
Then what?
Wait. l have an idea.
Constantinople.
What a sense of power.
Can you make him recall everything,
then free him from it for good?
When l snap my fingers,
you will awaken.
Your memory will be clear,
crystal clear.
The events of the past week
will come to you vividly.
And with no distraction.
You will be freed
from your trance...
and the word ''Constantinople''
will have no meaning to you.
lt will not put back into your
hypnotic state.
One, you're coming out of it.
Two, your memories of the past week
are coming back.
Three, you're fully awake.
l took the jewels!
The Kensington and the Dill...
Then he probably tried to get me
and couldn't.
The Greenwood thing was her...
what is Fitzgerald's key word?
Madagascar.
The Jade Scorpion
wants the jewels.
Wrap them in brown paper
and bring them to him.
Mark down the following
address in Chinatown.
Miss Fitzgerald?
Sergeant, his name's Voltan Polgar.
Someone just gave me an address.
Miss Fitzgerald.
The Jade Scorpion welcomes you.
You have my package.
Thank you.
You will now return home
and go to sleep...
a wonderful sleep, from
which you'll awaken cheerfully.
You will remember nothing
of these events. Ever.
l was just passing through.
l thought l'd say hello.
C.W. Briggs, l seem to have
underestimated you.
The story of my life.
Everybody underestimates me.
They think l'm a pushover.
lt makes my work much easier.
l've seen some exotic schemes,
but this one was a beauty.
But l figured it out.
That's why l get top-dollar.
Don't force me to take extreme
measures, Mr. Briggs.
-You'd never pull that trigger.
-Oh? Why?
Murder's not your game. My instinct
tells me that. You're a jewel thief.
There's a big difference between
doing time for stealing jewels
and frying
in the electric chair.
Once they pump 200 millions volts
of electricity through you
you have a tendency to spend
the rest of your days in an ashtray.
For a minute, l thought
l overplayed my hand.
You're the bravest, most brilliant,
most courageous man l've ever met.
l would go to the ends
of the earth with you.
Everybody should have someone
they feel that way about.
lt's such a shame that
you have to wake up from
this fabulous illusion.
Just once,
before the ugly curtain
of reality
drops on both of us.
You kiss great.
What a wrap-up.
-See Herb Coopersmith's face?
-Serves him right.
Where will Fitzgerald and Magruder
go for their romantic getaway?
His divorce isn't for months.
l hear his wife couldn't care less.
l hear the wedding's in June.
l heard him talking about
going to Paris.
Mr. Magruder, l just came
to say l'm leaving.
What can l say?
We all make mistakes.
You have to admit, they had
a strong case against you.
l know you could get
a job anywhere.
But if you decide to stay,
you'll have a raise.
Miss Fitzgerald won't be in your way.
Between us, once we marry
she's retiring
whether she wants to or not.
l'm not having a wife at work
in my own office.
Think positively. l'll be away
a few weeks, we're going to Paris.
The actual city, or...?
You need a vacation. Why not see if
you can get Laura Kensington to go?
l wouldn't mind that action myself.
She seemed struck by you.
She's a bit demented, but
in a hotel room,
that can be fun.
l came to say good-bye.
Right. Chris and l have
a plane to catch.
No. l mean l'm leaving.
l'm quitting.
lt should make you happy.
You can enjoy your vacation
because when you come back,
you wont see me.
You can revamp everything.
No static.
Want to have a parting drink?
At ten o'clock in the morning?
lt's only tequila.
What can you say about a woman who
keeps Mexican booze in her desk?
Let's drink to both
our futures.
Today, Mr. Magruder.
Tomorrow the world.
l'll let that pass because
this is goodbye.
You're really going to marry him.
For a brilliant woman
l've got to say you have
the worst taste in men.
l didn't take up with you.
How bad could my taste be?
You know behind those
nasty remarks...
is a very vulnerable, sweet,
sexy woman.
But don't ever let that come out
because you could risk being happy.
And that would kill you.
We will be happy. Your instinct
said he'd never leave his wife.
My instincts are good,
but they're not infallible.
This was one where l was wrong.
Have a terrific rest of your life
and try not to jump out of windows.
Be sure the elevator's there
before you get in.
One man plunged 1 5 stories and
wound up a vegetable.
l'll let that pass,
'cause this is goodbye.
Briggsie, l was just saying,
you quit, l go with you.
C.W. you're our hero.
This was a tough nut to crack.
No, this was all luck.
lf George didn't know hypnosis,
l wouldn't have known anything.
lt's amazing.
You can put someone under and force
them to do outrageous things.
That's absolutely wrong.
A hypnotized person won't do anything
they won't do in real life.
Really?
Are you saying, at heart,
l'm a thief?
We knew there was a little bit
of larceny in you.
You always said
''lt takes one to catch one.''
There was also a bit of larceny
in miss Fitzgerald. What a shock.
Turns out there are a lot of
surprises in her.
Come here.
You have a crush on her,
don't you?
Who? Fitzgerald?
What are you talking about?
l've always known it.
You can't hate someone that much
without feeling some attraction.
Says who?
My instinct. Come on, you were
the one who taught me to trust it.
l think l'm in love
with her.
lt's the stupidest thing
that's ever happened to me.
Take the bull by the horns.
She's leaving in about 3 minutes.
Go!
Miss Fitzgerald,
marry me.
l guess C.W.'s had a few.
Pretty early for that.
l had some tequila or l wouldn't
be able to say this.
l love you. Marry me.
You embarrassing me.
You can't marry the wrong person,
when you love me.
You're making her uncomfortable.
What could make you think l could
think of you that way, you...
l know. ''nearsighted cockroach''
Can't you see the venom under...
Betty, let's go.
C.W., leave here at once.
Your idea of moving on
wasn't so crazy.
l'm opening up to you.
l'm putting my heart in your hands.
l was hard because l feared you,
like you feared me.
This is the real thing
and it terrifies us.
Yes, l fear you.
You and Boris Karloff.
Your heroics do not entitle you
to be an obnoxious boor.
How is a man confessing love
be an obnoxious boor?
Betty and l have a plans,
and they don't include you.
You want to spend your life
married to the wrong guy?
-Why would l marry you?
-Stop talking like l'm not here.
Because it's me you love.
You're too old, too nearsighted
for me too short for me.
You left out the best part.
l'm losing my hair.
Goodbye, C.W.
And l mean for good.
Wait a minute.
Betty Ann, where are you going?
Madagascar?
Someone call the plane.
Say we might be late.
You go ahead, Chris.
l'm staying here.
l'm staying with C.W.
We have an announcement
to make.
Betty Ann, You have
a crazy look in your eye.
l've never felt so normal
in my life.
l can't guarantee every time
l kiss you there'll be fireworks.
l fell in love the second
l saw you.
l want this woman helped!
Get an ambulance.
Call my wife's attorney!
Have them halt the separation!
She'll take you back, with some
new ground rules, but you'll adapt.
So much passion
in a lousy insurance office.
Congratulations.
A little going-away
present for you.
Should we get out of here
and find somewhere to start
making up for lost time?
How about my place?
l think l can live with that.
God bless everyone.
And God bless Tiny Tim.
Shall we?
Good luck, you two.
What'll happen when she wakes
up and is back to her old self?
He'll have to say ''Madagascar''
first thing every morning.
My gosh, who'd have thunk it?
What a break for C.W. that you
forgot to deprogram Miss Fitzgerald.
What are you saying?
l deprogrammed her last night.
You don't have to worry.
l'll never leave you.
Tell me how you feel about me.
You're the most wonderful man
in the world.
The handsomest, the most brilliant,
the sexiest.
Someday l'm going to make you
really feel those things.
Anything's possible.
l made you feel that way and l
didn't have to say ''Constantinople''.
That's right!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org