Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
My lord.
What's wrong?
She's lost consciousness.
At last, the time has come.
My love...
My love.
My lord... it's a girl.
Her shoulder.
Please have a seat.
Honorable one, what brings you here
at this late hour?
My lord, please listen.
Your child...
She will be sacrificed to lmoogi.
That is heaven's will.
How could you say such things?
My wife has just died while giving birth
to my child.
Why do you speak this nonsense?
Your child...
...was born with the Yuh Yi Joo which
heaven intended for the Good lmoogi.
The dark lmoogi, the evil Buraki...
...has defied the will of heaven...
...and wants what rightfully belongs
to our Good lmoogi.
What are you talking about?
If the dark lmoogi gets hold
of the Yuh Yi Joo...
...an unimaginable disaster will befall
this entire village.
And how can you be sure?
The child bears the mark
of the Red Dragon.
Very good!
Soon you'll be able to beat me.
You've taught me well.
Haram...
...we don't have much time left.
They will be here soon.
Yes, I know.
Come, there is someone
you must meet.
Haram, bow before the Good lmoogi.
This is the lmoogi that has been
chosen by heaven.
It has to unite with the Yuh Yi Joo
and ascend to heaven.
That is the only way we humans...
...can remain a part of
the great cycle of the world.
Honorable one, do not worry.
The Yuh Yi Joo will be formed inside
Narin's body the day she turns 20.
I've been having
such good dreams lately.
We cannot miss our chance.
From now on...
...always keep it with you.
It is a pendant that has been formed
by heaven.
It belongs to the guardian of the
Good lmoogi.
This will protect you from danger.
Hey, what's that?
She is here.
Fire!
Find the girl!
Not my daughter!
You are looking for the girl who has
a tattoo on her shoulder!
Aren't you?
I know where she is!
Stop!
How dare you break into my house!
You scoundrels!
Father!
Narin!
Where...? Where am I?
Don't be scared.
This is a secret place.
My father...
...my father.
I am sorry.
Narin.
Listen.
I must tell you something.
Incompetent fools.
You've let them escape!
I should kill you all.
We must find the Yuh Yi Joo.
What's this?
I love you!
Narin!
Master Bochun...
Young man...
...shouldn't you be looking for
the Yuh Yi Joo?
You won't escape this time.
Now you must...
...die!
Come on!
Where do you think you're going?
Rise.
Atrox Army.
The time has come again.
Mighty...
Dawdler!
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org