Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Previously on Damages:
We've got money, Joe.
How much money?
Enough for
generations.
Your father's
going to go to jail.
You're my priority now.
We never invested with
Louis Tobin.
We gave our money to Leverett,
and Leverett gave it to Tobin.
We've lost everything.
I especially want to
thank my sister Ellen.
Even though, uh, I've got three years on
her, Ellie's always been my big sister.
PARSONS Carrie.
Do you know Danielle
Marchetti? No.
Your father purchased $14,000
worth of clothes for Ms. Marchetti.
Were you sleeping with her?
Patty will never find
her.
Where is she?
Hello, Danielle.
Get out.
Did he throw money at
you right away?
Get out!
Danielle Marchetti applied
for an expedited passport.
So Joe must have tipped off
his father that we're onto her.
If we don't find Marchetti, she's
gonna be able to travel tonight.
Danielle?
No, no, no, no.
Are you Marchetti?
What?
I'm picking up a Danielle
Marchetti.
Uh...
Daniel, actually.
Yeah, that's-that's me.
You're heading to
Farmingdale Airport?
Farmingdale?
Right.
I know I'm a little early. I just figured
since your flight's international...
I'm sorry.
You got, uh,
luggage inside? I do.
Uh, just, um- I'm sorry.
I think someone screwed up.
Uh... this is embarrassing.
Did... I was gonna drive myself.
My assistant didn't-didn't call,
give you a call?
No one called.
I'm sorry.
Sometimes she's, um...
She...
It's a real trek out here,
you know?
I understand that.
Next time, you're gonna get
charged for it.
Okay.
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
Do we know what airport Danielle
Marchetti is flying out of?
No, the State
Department checked for us.
She's not scheduled on any private or commercial
flight leaving tonight from the tristate area.
What about the address she used
on her passport application?
It was bogus.
But the health club where
she worked is still open.
I spoke to the manager.
He's going to let
me check her file.
Good.
Even if we figure out what airport she's leaving from,
we don't have the authority to keep her in the country.
Just find her.
I'll worry about the rest.
Is the plane on time?
I'm afraid not.
There's been a slight delay.
Weather over the Gulf.
What's the new departure time?
It's scheduled for 11:08 p.m.
Jesus.
That's four hours from now.
I know.
But, uh, it's the
best we can do.
You arrange
everything else?
Yes, sir.
And, uh, customs won't be a
problem.
Neither you nor Ms. Marchetti
are on the flight manifest.
Let me know if anything
else comes up.
We got to fly her out tonight.
I'm so sorry about that, Janine.
No, um, Mrs. Tobin warned me when she
gave me your number, "He's a busy man."
And I have been...
and I've been wanting
to meet you for so long.
Oh, well, Marilyn's wonderful.
Yeah.
They, um, they don't let Mrs.
Tobin come in the salon anymore,
so I go to her.
And I'm-I'm happy to do it.
You know, she-she really got a
bad rap, what, with her husband
and all of that.
She sure did.
Um, you are a lawyer?
I am.
Um, how is that?
Do you ever feel
blessed?
Um, I-I do.
I do, absolutely.
I have a lot of great friends
down at the salon.
Well, that's how I
feel about the law.
Heading out?
Dinner with my
family.
Uh-oh.
An evening with Gary and Denise.
My sister's
coming from Oregon.
Oh, triple whammy.
No, it's great.
I get to meet my niece.
Oh, that's right.
You're an aunt now.
Crazy, huh?
Is, uh,
what's-his-name coming?
The husband.
No. Thank God.
He's stuck at work.
His boss wouldn't let him off.
Well, sounds like a
party.
Rock it out.
You gonna hold down
the fort?
Yeah, someone's got
to.
This Tobin case is never
gonna end.
Have a blast.
Thank you.
Mmm.
Mmm?
See what I mean?
I do.
It's very, um, effervescent.
Wait, is that, is that a word?
Yes.
Is it? Okay.
It certainly is a
word.
Oh.
Darn it.
I'm sor- Last one, Janine.
Sorry.
Okay, this is a client.
So I'll-I'll be a minute.
Just take your time,
'cause I wld hate to stand in
the way of justice.
One second.
Hey, Joe, what's up?
Wait.
Tell me where you are.
Patty.
Ellen.
ARSONSWhat are you doing
here?
Seeing your boss.
You're leaving early.
I'm going to Jersey.
Parsons family dinner.
Oh.
The name you gave Tom turned out
to be significant.
Have you subpoenaed
her?
Trying to.
She's, uh, not very keen on
being found.
But thank you.
And if you ever need anything...
No.
It was a one-off.
Tom came to me and I was happy
to help.
But, uh, that's it for me in
the Tobin case.
Are you sure you don't
want to stick around?
I think this witness is trying
to flee the country.
It could be an exciting night.
I bet.
But, uh, I have a train to
catch, so...
Oh, right, right,
right, of course.
Family.
Your top priority.
I'm sorry, I'm
running a little late.
Well, it's almost 7:30.
I know.
I'm trying to find a witness
who may be fleeing the country.
Doesn't Patty have
anyone eo that?
No, I don't want
anyone else doing it.
It too important.
pents are
gonna be here any minute, and
I thought we were going to tell
them together.
We will.
Look, I'm the one who got your
parents to invest with Tobin.
I want to be the one to explain
it to them.
You really think this
witness could help your case?
This is the best lead
we have right now.
All right, babe.
Do what you have to do.
Look, have dinner
with your folks.
I promise you I'll be there
by dessert.
We'll tell them together.
What happened?
I hit you with my car.
Oh, yeah, I was
looking for my cat.
Yeah. Put this o
your face.
How long was I
out?
I don't know.
Just a little while.
Oh, my head hurts.
I called for help,
so don't worry.
My whole side
is sore.
Here.
What time is it?
Why, you have someplace
to be?
Stay down.
Oh!
Jesus, Joe,
what's going on?
Where is she?
In the other room.
What are you
doing here?
Did you know my father
was sleeping with Danielle
Marchetti?
No.
Did you, Lenny?
No. He told me
after you confronted him.
I'm sorry.
Why is he putting her
on an airplane tonight?
All he said was
he didn't want Patty Hewes
questioning her.
Oh. Then Danielle must
know about the money.
Jesus Christ!
Could he be that goddamn stupid
to put his whole family's future
in her hands?
Her?!
Joe, I'm as much in
the dark as you are.
But she is in there, and we need
to decide what to do with her.
We don't have a choice.
If she knows about the money,
we get her out of the country.
I think we have to
do that.
Patty?
Curtis, I was asked
to wait.
You're off to a fund-raiser?
A wake, actually.
My great-uncle.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Man was a prick,
but thanks.
I'm afraid this
is urgent.
Danielle Marchetti.
She used to be the
receptionist at Louis Tobin's
health club.
Your people questioned her
a couple of months ago.
And?
She and Tobin may have
been having an affair, but
that's not the exciting part.
You think she might
be involved in the fraud?
Yes.
I also think she's trying
to flee the country tonight.
Uh, Sheryl, can you
track down Judge Reilly's cell
number for me?
You have a flight number?
Not yet.
So you'll talk to Reilly?
Yeah.
We'll need a warrant to detain
Marchetti.
What do you have on her?
This is nothing.
Patty, you're asking me to
detain her without evidence?
I'm asking you to
prevent a person of interest
from fleeing the country.
Based on a hunch?
You're the court-appointed
trustee. There are rules.
I know you're not used to that.
This woman could prove
critical to our case.
If you let her slip through our
hands, we'll both regret it.
Well, then give me
something real.
I'm sorry, I can't detain her
without cause.
She's beautiful.
She's perfect.
Here you go.
Did you pump?
No, it's organic
formula.
Charlotte loves it.
Oh, you're not
breast-feeding?
Oh, she had trouble latching on at first,
and my nipples got all cracked, so...
Not at my table.
Your father's
squeamish.
I'm not squeamish.
I'm eating.
And I gotta tell ya, formula's
no good.
It's fine.
I looked it up online.
There's nothing wrong
with formula.
I'm telling you girls,
when you were babies,
your mother never
would've dreamed of it.
Say, whatever happened
to that guy you were
seeing with the, uh,
with the cowboy name?
Wes.
Uh, that ended a few months
back.
We never even got to meet him.
It's not a big deal. I don't
even know what he's doing anymore.
I'm sorry that Eddie couldn't
make it.
I was looking forward to
seeing him.
Yeah, he really
wanted to make the trip,
but, you know, just bad timing.
League semifinals.
You know how Eddie is and
his sports.
Bowling's not
a sport.
I thought you said
he was working.
I did?
Yes.
Well, who can keep
track of these things?
Nice priorities;
bowling over family.
Danielle stopped working at the
health club a few months ago,
but she had a forwarding address that
she wants her last check to be sent to.
I'm heading there now.
All right.
Where did you get
with the D.A.'s office?
Nowhere.
Curtis Gates is determined to
play by the rules.
So unless we find her first, Danielle
Marchetti is free to leave the country.
All right, I'll be in
touch.
You remember Lenny.
Barely.
It's been a while.
I'm sorry this
happened, and I know you've
been shaken up, but we need to
know if you're on board with
Louis' plan.
We know about your
flight.
I need to see
a doctor.
I've already
arranged one. He's on his way.
Okay. If he says
I'm safe to fly, then I'll go.
Your father wants me on that
plane.
And you give my father
anything he wants, don't you?
Where are you
going?
I need some air.
Hey, what happened to
your wake?
He'll still be dead
at the funeral.
Did you find anything?
No, and I've been
through everything we've got on
Marchetti.
Who did the interview
with her at the-the health club.
I did, a month and a
half ago.
I got the transcript right here.
I don't like Patty knowing
something that we don't.
Boss, I'm telling you
I talked to Marchetti.
There's nothing in here.
Well, then why does Patty
want me to detain her?
I don't know.
Maybe she's wrong.
Or maybe she's keeping evidence
from us.
Just give me that.
Danielle Marchetti?
Miss Marchetti?
♪ ♪
Can I help you?
Oh, uh, do you
live around here?
Yeah, across the street.
I'm looking for a
Danielle Marchetti.
I think she lives here.
Danielle- yeah, sure.
Terrific girl.
She helps me wife with
the shopping once in a while.
When was the
last time you saw her?
Well, I can't say for sure.
She in some kind of trouble?
No, I just, uh, I just
wanted to talk to her.
Well, I'll be
sure to tell her.
Great. Thank you.
Good night.
Hey, Patty.
I'm at Danielle Marchetti's.
There's a car in the driveway,
but no one seems to be home.
Um, call me when you get this.
Hey, Deb.
No, I haven't been able to find
her.
I don't think traffic's going to
be a problem.
Just tell your mom and dad I'm
on my way.
Leonard, you still here?
Thank you for
coming.
You know, some guy was
snooping around out there.
Tom Shayes.
He works for Patty Hewes.
Did he see you?
No. He's gone now.
Good.
This way, Dr. Brandt.
Patient's in here.
Just relax.
That hurt?
Yeah.
What do you think?
How did this happen?
She fell on the stairs.
What-what does it matter?
Can she fly, Karl?
Looking for
something?
Someone.
Having any luck?
No.
That's why I need you.
Can you stick around here for
a while?
I have no plans.
What do you have in mind?
I'll tell you later.
I have to make a phone call
first.
She's definitely
sustained a concussion.
I'm a little worried that her
rib may be broken.
Karl, we need to
know if she can fly.
If this were any
other patient, I'd say get her
to a hospital.
But if it's necessary...
She needs to be watched to make
sure there are no complications.
What time's the flight?
11:00.
Observe her until
then.
And make sure her speech remains
lucid.
Now if she seems to start to
slur her words or seems a little
light-headed, or if that nausea
get any worse, you need to get
her right to a hospital.
Karl, we can't
thank you enough.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
You-you look a little...
I'm fine.
Leonard Winstone
speaking.
This is Patty Hewes.
What a pleasant
surprise.
But, uh, perhaps I could call
you back first thing tomorrow?
I know about Danielle
Marchetti.
I'm not familiar
with that name.
Then you won't mind if
I leak her affair with Louis
Tobin to the press.
Ms. Hewes...
I'm waiting for you in
my office.
In 30 minutes, everything I've
got gets released to the Post.
What?
I have to, uh, meet
Patty Hewes.
What does she want?
Uh, she's
threatening to release your
father's affair to the press.
This is Danielle
Marchetti.
We spoke a while back.
I think that we need to talk
again.
Please call me.
I'll stay here and
watch her.
You okay doing
that?
Why wouldn't I be?
All right, uh,
well, then meet me at
Farmingdale Airport, hangar 6.
Flight's at 11:08, okay?
You find anything?
No. You?
Why the hell do you
think I'm asking you?
Call your wife.
Tell her you're not coming home
tonight.
I'm not married.
Jesus- how long have I worked
here?
Dad, where does
this go?
That one?
No idea.
Ask your mother.
You know, you're looking good,
kid.
You seem happier than usual.
Thanks, Dad.
Hey, Mom, where's this go?
Oh, I'll put it away,
honey.
I never meant to
hurt you.
You asked when it started.
I'll tell you if you still want
to know.
Was it when you were still
with me?
Yes.
When?
About a year
before you went into rehab.
I'm sorry, Joe- you were a
wreck.
So you dump me, and you
start with my father.
I don't know what
you want me to say.
Joe...
it wasn't what you think.
You don't know what I
think.
He did it for you,
you know.
What?
You were a wreck,
so he did it.
What? He did what?
DANIELLE He was only
on and off.
So he did it.
I don't... I don't want to wreck
anymore.
So you start with my father.
Danielle...
what are you talking about?
He wrecked it on
and off.
Danielle?
Just say what you
want me to say.
JOE Shit.
I thought you should
see this.
What is it?
My statement to the
press about Danielle Marchetti.
It's very well
written.
But I don't think you want to do
this.
Why not?
Because not one
word of that is true.
Tell me where she is.
I couldn't even
tell you who she is.
I'm trying to do you a
favor, Mr. Winstone.
The choice is yours.
Either deal with this privately
tonight, or explain to your
clients in the morning why you
let the whole world know that
Louis Tobin was screwing a towel
girl half his age.
I wonder what option Mrs. Tobin
would prefer?
I... appreciate the
courtesy call, but I'm not
worried about Marilyn.
No?
I'm just worried
about the truth.
And that woman...
has nothing to do with the
Tobins.
Well, then it's my
mistake.
I'm sorry for getting you all
the way down here for nothing.
Hello?
Hey, it's Joe.
Oh. How's the girl?
I don't...
Something's wrong.
Uh, her nose is bleeding, she
can't finish sentences.
Well, it could be a
subdural hematoma- bleeding
in the brain.
Well...
what happens if she flies?
Fly? She can't fly.
You need to get her to a
hospital.
You hear me?
Uh, yes.
Joe... you put her on
that plane, and she will die.
I understand.
Yeah?
This is Chris Sharp
from the District Attorney's
Office.
I'm returning Miss Marchetti's
call.
Well, that's weird.
A guy answered and he hung up.
Next time keep your
damn cell phone on you. Okay?
(Danielle sniffles, clears
throat)
What'd the doctor
say?
Uh, he said you need to
stay hydrated...
and not to take any aspirin, but
it's nothing to worry about.
Okay, good.
You're good to go.
Yeah.
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
Hi, Ginny.
Art.
Hi. Sorry.
Thank you.
Get yourself the
steak frites- it's delicious.
I had the halibut.
Uh, not a fan.
I'm actually, I'm not
very hungry.
Um...
Uh, Tom and I really
just wanted to talk to you guys.
Your husband's been
running around all day- let
the man eat.
No, no, no,
I'm-I'm-m fine.♪
Um...
I'm sorry, I just need one more
minute.
I'll be right back.
Patty. Yeah.
They were still in the house.
Look, write this down.
It's a license plate number.
N- Z-E-4-7-4-5.
Did you ever think
when you were up here making out
with Mike Delvecchio
that you would be changing
diapers someday?
God, no.
What's going on,
Carrie?
CARRIE What do you
mean?
Downstairs...
with the envelope- Mom looked
like she was crying.
Did something happen with Eddie?
Um...
I'm sure it's temporary.
What's temporary?
What did he do?
Um...
he... he left me three weeks
ago, and I haven't heard from
him since.
Why didn't you tell
me?
'Cause I just, I
didn't want to bother you, you
know?
You have... too much on your
plate already.
Don't be silly- let
me help.
Don't ask Mom for money.
They can't afford it.
How much do you need?
No. You know what?
Ellen, I can't.
It is not a problem.
Truly. I'll write you a check.
Thank you.
Are you gonna stay
here?
I mean... just till I
get on my feet.
Does Dad know?
No.
And he's going to freak out.
You know he's going to blame me.
I just... I can't take that
right now, Ellen.
I just don't... I don't want to
be yelled at.
I know, I know.
But you're going to have to tell
him soon.
I was going to in the
morning.
Can you, um... can you stay?
I just really don't want to do
this alone.
I really want to be
there for you.
I do. I...
But I have to work.
I know, you know
what, I totally understand.
It's okay.
Do you know how
long the flight will be?
Uh, we can ask when we
get there, okay?
You look like your
dad right now.
Stop talking, please.
How do I know you?
Your voice sounds so familiar.
Just rest, okay?
So, what is it you
want to talk about, Tom?
You two look tense.
Look, uh, there's no
good way to say this.
But I want to tell you before
you got your next financial
statements.
Financial statements?
What's this about?
I, uh, screwed up.
Jesus, one day in
this house and your crap's in
every single room!
You and Eddie want to be slobs,
fine, do it in your house, not
mine!
Gary, I don't think
she's a slob.
I said I'm sorry.
I didn't even put this stuff
here, Mom did.
Oh, don't you blame
your mother!
Dad, stop it.
I think she gets it.
Are you ready to
leave, honey?
We can take you to the train.
No, Ma, I think I'm
gonna stay the night.
Oh, well, how
wonderful.
Our two girls under the same
roof.
Fine with me.
One less trip to the station.
Gary, honey...
It's gonna be okay.
How far away are
you?
I'm ten minutes from the
airport.
We found her.
She's on the way to the airport.
We have a license plate number.
I told you, Patty,
we're not gonna detain her
without cause.
We have cause.
What is it?
He's driving with a
broken taillight.
Shit.
How are you?
License and registration.
Is there a problem?
Your taillight's busted.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What's wrong with her?
She's, uh, she's ill.
I was actually just taking her
to the hospital.
Really?
'Cause the hospital's a mile
back.
You just passed it.
Oh, really?
Um...
1-2-Alpha to HQ.
I need rescue.
(woman talking indistinctly
over P.A.)
She's not coming.
I thought I'd get here to stop
her myself, but it turns out I
didn't have to.
The police pulled her over.
Actually, they pulled Joe Tobin
over.
Danielle Marchetti was
unconscious in the backseat.
Gee, that all
sounds terrific, but I have no
idea what you're talking about.
It took me a while
to find the airport she was
flying out of, but I figured it
out.
And surprise, surprise, I find
you here.
Yeah, I'm off for
a weekend in the Bahamas.
Care to join?
Danielle's in the
hospital, in case you're
wondering.
What happened, Mr. Winstone?
Joe told the police she fell?
Patty, listen,
before you issue the press
release...
There's no press
release.
There never was.
Oh, I see.
You had me followed.
That's how you found the
airport.
I'm impressed.
Tonight's been
educational.
I always knew the Tobins were
hiding something.
Now I know you're helping them
do it.
My colleague's already served
Danielle with a subpoena.
So, I got what I wanted.
Good night, Mr. Winstone.
Here's a check.
Thanks, Ellie.
There's a T-shirt and stuff
upstairs if you want to borrow
it.
Find everything you need?
Yeah.
GARY Remember
this?
I do.
Look at you two.
Were we not adorable?
I'll be right back.
Hey, Patty, it's Ellen.
I was just, uh, wondering-
did you find that witness?
Transcript by www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org