Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I've been over and over this stuff.
It doesn't add up.
Who does these books? If I ran
my office this way, I'd be out of business.
What can we do?
I see places you could save,
but I can't make those choices.
I'm not the president. I mean...
You know, I mean, I'm not the one
pretending to be the president.
I understand.
Let me try.
You?
You want to try?
All right. Here's something right here.
Look at that.
It's a work of art.
Look at this.
"Vice-president linked to S&L scandal."
Alan, you're a genius. We're on our way.
What's with the cameras?
Hundredth cabinet meeting.
It'll be a nice touch.
Oh, right.
Good morning, Mr. President.
How's everyone?
Before we get started...
...I'd like to go over the budget.
-Anything on the budget today?
-No, I don't think so.
I've found some ways to put back
the homeless section...
...of the Works Bill.
Mr. President, I don't believe
that's on your agenda today.
No, it's a last minute change, Bob.
Now, the way I see it,
we need $650 million in order to...
...keep the project.
Some of this can be done...
-...through some simple changes...
-It's all right.
...in our cash management.
For example...
...according to the OMB, we've got...
...17 defense contractors
who are delinquent in their contracts.
Is this true?
I believe so.
Even though...
...they're late,
we keep paying them on time?
Well, in a sense.
Okay, now...
...instead of paying them
for something they haven't finished...
...we could hold back that cash,
put it in an interest-bearing--
Mr. President.
Nothing.
Great.
Like I was saying, if we took that cash
and stuck it in a savings account...
...we'd be making
$23 million a month in interest.
Well, technically, that's true, but...
I suppose it's true.
Okay, so that's $23 million...
...times 12 months.
Good.
Fortunately, money management
gets us halfway to our goal.
In order to get the rest of the money,
we'll have to make some tough choices.
The Commerce Department.
Yes, Mr. President?
We're spending $47 million
on an ad campaign...
"...to boost consumer confidence
in the American auto industry."
It's designed to bolster
individual confidence...
...in a previous domestic
automotive purchase.
We're spending $47 million for somebody
to feel good about a car they bought?
I wouldn't categorize it that way.
I'm sure that's important, but...
...I don't want to tell an eight-year-old kid
he's gotta sleep in the street...
...because we want people
to feel better about their car.
Do you want to tell him that?
No, sir.
No, I sure don't.
Well then, that's another $47 million.
So this is good. Real good.
We're on our way.
Let me just add that to the tally here.
That'll be plus 47...
Five, carry the one...
...makes $656 million...
...which means we can keep the program.
-Thank you, sir.
-Thank you for your help.
Excuse me.
What is it?
You won't believe what your husband did.
I'll kill him.
You can't kill a president.
He's not a president.
He's an ordinary person.
I can kill an ordinary person.
I can kill 100 ordinary people.
He's only doing what you told him to.
What I told him to?
I heard you. You said,
"Cut $650 million off the budget...
-"...and you can keep your shelters."
-I didn't mean it.
Why would I want to save a shelter?
He was only doing his job!
His job? His job? It's not his job!
It's my job!
Will you calm down?
Was he on the Trilateral Commission?
Was he a senator?
Was he in "Who's Who"
nine years in a row?
Hello, Judy.
I'll destroy him. I'll shred him!
I'll lock him away.
Then we'll all go to jail together.
What do you mean by that?
What do you think I mean?
Are you threatening me?
Well...
Yeah.
I guess I am.
Thanks, Murray.
You did great.
Maybe you can come back.
We can go to Camp David.
Camp David?
Get out of here as fast as you can.
Come on, seven.
Come on, six.
We both lose.
I saw your light was on, so I...
Mind if I sit down?
Please.
Would you like...
No, thanks.
That was quite a thing you did today.
Anyone would've done that.
I don't think so.
You helped a lot of people.
You know...
...it kind of reminded me...
...of that thing you did a long time ago
in the state legislature.
Me, too.
You weren't in the state legislature.
Hi, I'm Ellen Mitchell.
Who're you?
I'll make this easy on you.
I never see him anymore.
I barely know him anymore.
I'd just kind of like to know where he is.
This could get me in trouble.
Open it, please, Duane.
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry, you're not allowed in here.
-We have strict instructions.
-I'll explain it later.
What happened?
It was a stroke.
It's pretty bad.
I don't understand.
Is he going to...
I'm sorry.
You're leaving?
I'm not the first lady anymore.
I shouldn't be here.
Where're you going?
Home.
Where's home?
Can we stop with the 20 questions?
I'm really not in the mood.
Souvenirs. Towels and stuff.
You're leaving, too?
I never wanted to hurt anybody.
I even thought I was helping.
You know...
...you make this little deal
with yourself that...
...you can put up
with all the other women and...
...you can even do without a life and...
...you can even do without children...
...because you believe
in what you're doing and think...
You thought you had a chance
to help people.
How are you gonna get home?
I don't know. I hadn't really...
...thought it out that far.
Are you sure this goes somewhere?
They say LBJ used it all the time.
Duane said he'd leave a car
right over there.
When did you...
...first know? I mean, about me?
In the car, I think.
On the way to the shelter,
you looked at my legs.
Bill stopped looking a long time ago.
I thought it was in the shower.
Oh, my God.
Police.
-What'd you do?
-I don't know.
-See your driver's license, sir?
-Here.
And registration.
No, I must've left it at home.
Step out of the car, please.
-Both of us?
-Both of you, please.
You may not be aware...
...but there is a "No left turn" sign
just down the block.
You went through it.
I don't know what was I thinking.
We're look-alikes.
Not like each other, but--
I know what you think.
People hire us to impersonate
the president and first lady.
We work out of an agency.
You sure look like him.
Thanks. We work very hard at it.
She got her hair cut to look--
Perfect match.
We just played the Sapperstein wedding.
They loved us.
We did our Club Med routine...
...where they go down to Club Med...
...and Bill Mitchell says,
"at 0700, I want an hour of volleyball...
"...and then at 0830, I want
a complete briefing on the surf situation."
And then the big finale at the Talent Club.
"The sun'll come out tomorrow.
"Bet your bottom dollar that tomorrow..."
I'm okay.
"There'll be sun
"Just thinking about tomorrow
"Clears away the cobwebs and the sorrow
"Till there's none
"Tomorrow
"Tomorrow, I love you
"It's only a day away
"Tomorrow, tomorrow
"We love you, tomorrow
"You're only a day away"
Thank you. Thanks.
We haven't worked out the final harmony.
This is a full-time job?
Yeah, lately.
Lately, it's been pretty much full-time.
Mr. and Mrs. Kovic,
I'm not going to give you a ticket.
You're not?
You should save all the money you have.
He won't give us a ticket.
He says we should save our money.
That's very funny.
You're very good.
But she needs a lot of work.
Yes, I know. She's kind of new at it.
Drive safely.
Thank you, Officer. Thank you very much.
I'm not sure I'm this hungry.
Wait. This is a very special sandwich.
This is good.
What's in it?
That's a secret.
You have a lot of secrets.
I guess.
So, what do you do the rest of the time?
When I'm not running the country?
I run a temp agency.
You know, secretaries and stuff.
You find people jobs?
Is that funny?
It's just more than most people do here.
Don't get carried away.
I'm not that good at it.
And your family?
I assume you're married.
I was.
Once.
It didn't take.
You know, Dave--
It is Dave, isn't it?
I can't keep this a secret.
Yeah, I know.
I liked doing it though.
I mean, not the fancy stuff with all...
...the helicopters
and the TV cameras, but...
...I liked saving that shelter.
I liked helping people
that I hadn't even met before.
Just then, I felt I wasn't
pretending anymore.
I don't think you were pretending.
What would you do if you were still in?
I mean, if you had one more chance
to be president...
What would you do then?
Lots of things.
Excuse me. You can't stop here.
No visitors.
Mr. President?
-I'm sorry, sir, I didn't realize--
-Just getting fresh air.
Certainly, sir.
I was wondering, if you don't mind,
how did you get--
The president wanted some ice cream.
You make a nice president, Dave Kovic.
Thanks.
See you.
We are glad you're visiting
the White House.
Keep moving, folks. We're walking.
More than a million visitors come here
every year...
...making it the most frequently
toured home in the country.
We're walking and we're stopping.
Whatever changes
from one administration to the next...
...the White House always maintains
its dignity.
We're walking.
He's walking.
He's Bob Alexander, the chief of staff.
I can't believe it!
What an honor for all of you.
Forty-two presidents have lived
in the White House.
I had no part in this. He called her.
What do you think you're doing?
You mean, the press conference?
I have a couple ideas
to share with the country.
Share?
You don't call a press conference.
I call a press conference.
You're nothing. Do you understand?
You're nobody.
I'm not nobody.
You're lint!
You're a flea!
You're a blip!
Well...
...maybe I am.
But you're fired!
I said you're fired. Get out of here.
I'm fired?
You're fired!
Fine.
Fine?
The whole press corps is out there.
Should I go tell them?
Or did you want to?
Darling, they're waiting in the Press Room.
I think you should get in there.
I'm sorry. I thought we were alone.
I'd like your resignation on my desk
by the time I get back.
Don't touch anything on that desk.
What's up?
It must be the vice-president.
The ex-vice-president.
He'll be a prison reformer soon.
They're coming. Let's go.
Good luck.
Thanks for coming on such short notice.
I'd like to begin
with an announcement that...
...may come as a surprise for you.
I've...
...asked Bob Alexander to resign
as White House chief of staff.
Over the last months, Bob and I
came to believe in different things.
He thinks this country's fine and we
should go about doing business as usual.
I just don't feel that way.
Not anymore.
Because things aren't fine.
We've got so many problems,
we don't want to look at them anymore.
They blend together into a big noise...
...and soon we can't hear ourselves think.
But that's not even the worst part.
The worst part is...
...we feel we can't do anything about it.
And that's a tragedy...
...because we can.
We don't know where to start;
maybe that's what it is.
But I have an idea...
...of where we can start.
From today...
...I'm making it the responsibility
of this government...
...to find a job for every American
who wants one.
Have you seen the look
in someone's face...
...the day they finally get a job?
I've had some experience with this.
They look like they could fly.
And it's not about the paycheck.
It's about looking in the mirror...
...and knowing you've done
something valuable with your day.
And if one person could start
to feel that way, then others...
Soon all these other problems
we're facing may not seem so...
...impossible.
You don't know what you can do
until you...
...stand up and decide to try.
That's it. Let's get to work. Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. President.
In the boldest initiative yet
of the new Mitchell administration...
...the president has proposed
a full employment program...
...unparalleled since the days of FDR.
The proposal brought swift reaction,
here on Capitol Hill.
The president's on the right track.
We should be putting people to work.
It's better to have people working
than collecting welfare checks.
We're carrying the water for him.
I've carried a lot of water for him.
And then now to say this.
The guy's out to lunch.
The lights are on but no one's home.
I love it. It's great. All we've gotta do is
cut "Star Wars" and we can pay for it.
I want to look at Mitchell's proposal
to see how he intends to pay for it.
It's like the program I presented
when I ran for president four years ago.
Has the president taken leave
of his faculties? I'm asking you.
It's the definition of modern leadership.
You set out a bold goal
and you don't say how you'll do it.
They tried this in Russia
and wrecked the country.
I wonder if the Communists got to him?
If you look at a photo of Mitchell...
...taken before the stroke and one after,
you will see distinct differences.
Are you saying this is a conspiracy?
Yes, I am saying it's a conspiracy.
Do you think you're a bit paranoid?
Have you compared the photographs?
This is crazy.
The "US News" hammered us, but they're
always tough. Rosenthal loved us.
That's good.
Mr. Nance is waiting for you.
-Who?
-The vice-president.
The vice-president.
Nance. I thought--
I want my ears checked.
Sorry, I didn't understand.
Ever since the stroke I get a little--
Oh, my God!
Mr. President...
...these are a gift of the King of Togo.
Fertility beads.
And these are from the people of Burundi.
Thank you.
They know hats in Burundi. Look.
Mr. President,
may I speak frankly with you?
Yes, please. Sit down.
It's good to see you.
I know we don't always get along.
We've disagreed, politically.
And I suppose I know
what you think of me personally.
But I've tried to respect
the role you wanted me to play.
When I disagreed with this administration,
I've kept it to myself.
When you wanted my support,
you always had it.
Damn it, Bill.
How could you do
something like this to me?
Do what?
Come on, we're not children!
I didn't have anything to do with this
First Liberty nonsense and you know it!
First Liberty.
All I've got is my integrity, Bill.
That's all I have left.
I don't know why you've turned
your attack dogs on me.
They're not my attack dogs.
What?
I'll take care of this.
-We made it up.
-What do you mean?
We had to, Dave. The guy's a Boy Scout.
But this is wrong.
Wrong?
I know. It looks awfully bad
and I'm really embarrassed, but...
It was Bob's idea.
When I first began to look into
the allegations concerning First Liberty...
...I thought the wrongdoing
was restricted to the vice-president.
You better take a look at this.
But as I began to investigate,
I realized that...
...this pattern of corruption
extended much higher.
I was saddened to discover at least 15...
...separate acts of intervention
by this administration...
...most with the full knowledge
of the president, and all of them illegal.
Federal regulators were influenced...
...records were destroyed...
...and pressure was brought to bear...
...in some cases...
...by President Mitchell himself.
-Now he's making up stuff about me.
-He's not.
He's not?
I did all that?
You didn't. Bill Mitchell did.
This is a mistake.
We shouldn't be doing this.
I can't go into hiding.
Is this job stuff just a smoke screen?
I don't know how else to put it.
This dog won't hunt.
We may be able to hold off
on this First Liberty thing for a while...
...but if you're pushing this new jobs--
Just put us on a spit and bring the sauce.
-If you'd just wait a few months.
-Yeah, wait.
I don't want to wait. We can't.
Mr. President,
I understand how you feel, but...
...we're talking about obstructing
federal regulators...
...violating election laws.
I got people up on the Hill
talking about impeachment.
What is with President Mitchell lately?
I know the president's supposed to serve
four years, but now it may be 15 to 20.
We make fun of the president.
But it's a tough job.
Today the president woke up, broke
the law, got caught and pardoned himself.
That is a full day.
Mr. President...
...may I come in?
A dirty business we're in, sometimes.
Mr. President...
...whatever happens, I want you to know,
I think your jobs program is...
...a wonderful idea.
Thanks.
Not many people will
pay attention now, but...
Thanks.
Would you like to...
...sit down for a minute?
Do you ever...
...think back to how you got started?
I was a shoe salesman.
But not happy about it.
One day, my wife says to me:
"Why don't you run for office?
"You talk about it all the time.
"Why don't you just do it?"
So I tell my boss...
...I have a dentist appointment...
...and I go down
to the Registrar of Voters...
...on my lunch break.
Next thing I know, I'm a councilman.
Really?
My wife is my campaign manager.
We had...
...a budget of $2,000, with advertising.
How about you?
Me?
How did you get started?
Kind of the same way.
Vice-president's a good man, isn't he?
He's a very good man.
I don't want to lose you.
The president requested this rare,
joint session of Congress...
...so he can personally answer
the allegations raised by Bob Alexander...
...his former chief of staff.
It's hard to recall the last time
both houses of Congress...
...convened without any idea
of what the president plans to say.
One would speculate that it's about
the charges against Mitchell and Nance.
Those rumors have circulated
on Capitol Hill for several weeks.
It's time to go. Better get inside.
It's set with Duane? Everything's here?
Okay, let's go.
Relax.
Enjoy the moment.
-Hello, Ben.
-Big day, Bob.
-Thanks for coming.
-I wouldn't miss it.
You know the Claghorns?
Hey, Bob, what do you think?
Put that away.
Let's wait till the speech first.
The House will be in order!
Mr. Speaker,
the President of the United States.
Thank you.
Here it comes.
Mr. Speaker.
Vice-President.
Members of the Congress.
Fellow Americans.
I wish I could be here today
under different circumstances.
There are many things
about this country we should discuss.
But I realize that's not possible now.
As you know, my former chief of staff
has implicated me in a scandal...
...involving
the First Liberty Savings and Loan.
Once people start discussing a scandal,
it's hard to talk about anything else.
Let's talk about it.
Bob Alexander has accused me of--
I'll read this to make sure I get it right.
"...illegally influencing regulators
on behalf of campaign contributors...
"...interfering with an ongoing
Justice Department investigation...
"...and violating federal election laws
in the area of campaign finance."
Let's get to the guts of it.
Each one of these charges is true.
Die, you pond scum.
I'm the president, and as they say,
the buck stops here.
So I take full responsibility
for every one of my illegal actions.
But that's not the whole story.
And I think each one of you
is entitled to the whole truth.
I have here written proof...
...in the form of notes,
memoranda and personal directives...
...proving that Bob Alexander
was also involved...
...in each of these incidents,
and in most cases, planned them as well.
Allegations of wrongdoing
have also been made against Nance.
As this evidence will prove, at no time...
...and in no way was the vice-president
involved in any of these.
Bob just made all that up.
Vice-President Nance...
...is a good and decent public servant...
...and I'd like to apologize
for any pain this caused him or his family.
While we're on the subject...
...I'd like to apologize
to the American people.
You see...
...I forgot that I was hired
to do a job for you...
...and it was just a temp job.
I forgot I had 250 million people...
...who were paying me
to make their lives a bit better.
I didn't live up to my part of the bargain.
There are certain things
you should expect from your president.
I had to care more about you
than I do about me.
I had to care more about...
...what's right than I do about
what's popular.
I ought to be willing to give up
this whole thing...
...for something I believe in...
...because if I'm not...
...if I'm not...
If I'm not...
If I'm not, then...
...maybe I don't belong here on a first...
Get a doctor!
Well?
You okay getting home?
Yeah, it's not far.
Take care.
I would've taken a bullet for you.
Thanks, Duane.
The stroke hit at 8:42 p.m...
...just as the president was concluding
his remarks to a joint session of Congress.
Spokesmen of the First Naval Hospital...
...have confirmed it was a massive edema.
Unlike his previous stroke,
it has left the president incapacitated.
The nation mourned
as President William Harrison Mitchell...
...was laid to rest at
Arlington National Cemetery.
After lingering in a coma
for almost five months...
...the president succumbed Thursday,
at 4:20 p.m.
In a bittersweet ceremony in the capital,
Vice-President Gary Nance...
...was officially sworn in today
as the 45th president of the United States.
Under the terms of the 25th Amendment,
Nance was acting with full authority...
...since Bill Mitchell's incapacitation.
I plan to continue
Bill Mitchell's call to arms.
This isn't my presidency,
it's his presidency.
And I can't think of a better way
to ensure his legacy...
...than to continue
the principles he initiated.
Bob Alexander and eight other members
of the Mitchell administration...
...were indicted on 34 counts
of election law violations...
...and obstruction of justice.
Ironically, the indictments came
just 48 hours...
...after passage of the Mitchell Jobs Bill for
a comprehensive employment program.
We have limited amounts of posters,
so no buttons in the envelopes.
Dave Kobic. Time for a change.
Kovic. Kovic.
We have a limited amount of posters.
Put them in busy places.
She's terrific. She'll do anything.
Okay, but she's changed.
It's the middle of winter.
They'll turn off her heat. She needs a job.
Would you like to volunteer?
You're a good man.
Did you get the fund-raising thing
I sent you? City Council.
We have flyers here.
We're on a roll now. Karen, you got a job.
It's Monday.
And everybody works on Monday.
I understand you find people jobs?
You look great!
I saw you on TV at the funeral and...
That's finally over.
Why don't we go into my office?
Excuse us.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org