Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
[Screaming]
[Helicopter blades whirring]
- Nothin', nothin' at all.
- Send it again.
I've been sendin' it up and down the
coast from Sarasota to the everglades.
It's still getting back
the same day it aired.
There's nothing. There's nobody,
or at least nobody with a radio.
All right then. Let's set
down. We'll use the bullhorn.
[Man] Set down? Wait a minute.
That's not in our contract.
It's the biggest city within 150
miles. We're gonna give it every chance.
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
Set down, John.
I'll set us down, but I won't leave my
seat, and I値l keep the engine running.
Now, the first sign
of trouble, I知 going up.
If you ain't on board when that happens,
you're likely to have a lousy afternoon.
Calling anybody
on this frequency.
This is
helicopter 4-0-alpha.
If you can hear me,
please listen carefully.
Hello?
Is anyone there?
[Flies buzzing]
[Wind whistling]
Hello?
Is there anyone there?
[Footsteps approaching]
[Gasping]
Hello?
[Moaning]
Is there anyone there?
- [Gasping]
- Hello?
[Moaning]
Hello?
Is anyone there?
[Grunting]
[Low moaning]
[Moaning intensifies]
We can lift you out to safety. Please
answer my call if you can hear me.
Forget it, Billy boy.
It's a dead place.
They got the others,
you know.
Listen.
[Muffled moaning]
You can hear it
over the engine.
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
[Moaning nears]
[Helicopter blades whirring]
[Low moaning]
Hey, you find anything?
Yeah. A bunch of real estate
for sale at closeout prices, man.
Gas up the machine.
She's down to fumes.
No. Wait till it's dark. There
are too many of them out there.
Yeah-hey, it's no good to
leave the gas tank empty.
- Suppose we need to get out of here in a hurry.
- Then we're shit out of luck.
They're getting too riled up. Do
it tonight when they can't see you.
They know we're in here even if they can't see
us. What good is it to leave the gas tank emp...
the activity excites them. There are too
many of them. And more and more every day.
If we get a lot more, come out and shoot
some. Otherwise, stay inside the building.
Stay out of sight. Be thankful
you live in the suburbs, Johnson.
You oughta see how congested
the city's gettin' to be.
Miguel, come on.
Let's get below.
Miguel, what can I
do? You... you... what?
Let me help. No. I... I don't
need help. I don't need help.
Come on. Give me this. I'm
all right. I'm just tired.
You're not. You're collapsing from stress.
Now, let me help... collapsing from stress?
We're all collapsing. This whole
fucking unit is collapsing...
everybody except you.
I know you're strong,
all right? So what?
Stronger than me. Stronger
than everyone. So what?
So fucking what?
[Moaning continues]
- That's a new grave.
- Major cooper. He died this morning.
And then there were 12.
A burial this morning. That's
why there are so many of them.
What's gonna bring them tomorrow, Sarah?
And the next day and the next day after?
There are hundreds of 'em over
there, thousands. A million of them!
You stick your head in the sun, they're gonna
come up behind you and bite off your ass!
This is bullshit. Crazy. If you've got an
alternative, we'd be happy to listen to it.
I got an alternative. Yeah,
yeah. I got an alternative.
Let's get in that whirlybird, find us
an island someplace, get juiced up...
and spend what time we got left
soakin' up some sunshine.
How's that? You could
do that, couldn't you?
With all that's going on, you could
do that without a second thought?
Right. I could do that even
if all this wasn't goin' on.
[Hydraulic whirring]
[Electronic beeping]
Another waste of time,
right? Got that right, man.
[Whirring]
What'd you find?
Nothin'.
Nothin'? How far
up the coast did you go?
- A hundred miles each way.
- [Groans]
Jump in here, soldier. We gotta bring
in two more dumb fucks. Let's go.
- [Sarah] two more? What's Logan doing to them in there?
- [Man] get in here.
He's been awake for 24 hours.
Can't you get anyone else?
What "anyone else"? There
isn't anyone else. We're it.
The two of you can't go in
there alone. It's too dangerous.
Christ. I'll go!
- What's the matter with your friend there?
- There's nothing the matter.
All right. Let's go.
[Man talking,
indistinct]
[Man #2]
You got it, Steel.
[Men continue chattering,
indistinct]
[Man laughing maniacally]
[Screeching]
[Maniacal laughter continues]
Let's kick it out.
Come on. Step forward.
[Mechanical whirring]
[Spitting]
[Wind whistling]
This shows the 15th as the
last time you took any out.
That can't be right. Oh, yeah. We
forget to write 'em up sometimes.
You've got to write them up.
It's essential.
Can't you get that
through your thick skull?
How the hell are we supposed to
keep track of how many we got left?
[Screaming]
[Whistling]
Let's go, you dumb fucks!
Get over here!
Hey! Here we are!
[Low moaning]
Come on!
[Steel] Come on, you dumb
fucks. Come on. Come on.
- [Steel knocking]
- Come on, you fish brains. What the hell's the matter with ya?
They're scared.
Huh?
They know what'll happen
when Frankenstein gets 'em.
[Sarah] If you're right,
Rickles, then they're learning.
They're actually
learning. [Steel] come on!
Come and see what I got for
you! Come on, you dick faces!
Here's a nice one hangin'.
Come on. Come and get it.
- Come and try to bite it off!
- That's it. Whip it out. That'll bring 'em on.
Fuckin' "a. " Biggest
piece of meat in the cave.
I don't wanna excite the lady
though. Not with her boyfriend around.
You're incapable of exciting me, Steel,
except as an anthropological curiosity.
- What the hell's that mean, Rickles?
- It means you're a caveman.
You're a fuckin' throwback. You've been
spendin' too much time underground, huh?
It's okay, Steel.
Throwbacks all got big dicks.
Oh!
[Laughs hysterically]
All right, you dumb fucks!
Get over here, you scumbags!
Your old pal Steel
wants to see ya. [Growls]
- Shit.
- I'm coming up.
You're not strong enough for up here. Send
up the pole. I'll watch out for lover boy.
Don't worry. I'm not strong enough?
I've done it dozens of times.
I don't want you up here, lady. Send
up the pole. They're gettin' closer.
He's clamping. Look at
'im. Let go of the pole.
Listen to me.
Let go of the goddamn pole.
- Here they come! Let's go!
- [Moaning continues]
Dumb fucks.
Pus-breeding bags of shit.
You dumb-fucking bags of shit, I値l
kick your fuckin' asses. Come on!
- [All growling, moaning]
- [Laughing mockingly]
Come here, scumbag.
[Continues laughing]
[Growling]
[Steel] Hook her up, will
ya? Hook her. [Growling]
Hey, nice hat,
asshole.
[Screeching]
Come on! Get the other one out of there!
[Zombie grunting,
screeching]
[Continues grunting]
- [Steel shouting, indistinct]
- [Screaming]
Steel, Steel, Steel,
cover! Cover!
- [Steel] I got it.
- Geez.
That's it. That's it. That's
it. I got it. I got it. Come on.
Come on. Come here. Come here.
[Zombie continues growling]
You almost killed Rickles.
Yeah. You almost killed Rickles.
- [Screaming]
- Let 'im go, Steel.
- He shouldn't have been up there in the first place.
- [Yelling, indistinct]
Steel, stop it!
[Continues roaring]
You dirty son of a bitch!
Let him go! Let him go,
goddamn it,
or I値l cut you in half.
[Growling]
[All yelling, indistinct]
Shut up, you dumb fucks. I hope
they chop you up for dog meat.
Come on, Rickles.
Let's get out of here.
I hope you fuckin' rot!
Fuck you!
[Groaning,
whimpering]
I am not gonna let you
dope me up.
You need a sedative.
You're behaving dangerously.
- I'm just trying to help you, Miguel.
- Well, I don't need your help.
You made me look like
an asshole out there.
You made me feel
like a piece of shit.
You stay away from me
with that, Sarah.
- You stay away from me.
- [Gasping]
Ohh.
[Crying]
[Shrieks]
[Gasping]
You bitch.
[Groans, sobs]
We've got to have sterile
conditions. Half the work we do...
goes down the toilet
due to contamination.
You'll work with what you
got, Fisher. But it's madness!
- Can't you understand...
- I understand this: You and your playmates,
you're running out of friends
fast around here.
[Sighs] Look, major
cooper promised that...
major cooper is dead.
I'm in command now,
and I知 telling you...
that you work
with what you got.
And you'd better
start showing me some results...
or you won't have that
very much longer.
How can we show you results when we
don't have the proper working conditions?
We're in a desperate situation
here. We need each other.
Can't we just get along? [Man] you
need us, the way I see it, lady.
I'm not sure we need you at
all. [Steel] Fuckin' "a. "
I'm not even sure what the hell
it is you're doin' in there,
just what the hell my men
are riskin' their asses for.
If there was more cooperation, your men
wouldn't have to risk their asses as often.
[Rifle cocks]
- Miguel Salazar痴 in bad shape.
- [Chuckles] no shit.
I want him pulled off active duty for a
while until we can evaluate his condition.
- Can't spare 'im. - He's over
the edge. He's turning into jell-o.
- Jell-o? - That's the way the
spicks say "yellow": Jell-o!
Miguel is seriously disturbed.
He's close to the breaking point,
and that's dangerous
for all of us.
He can't handle
any more stress right now.
Well, maybe I should cut off
his extracurricular activities.
Maybe you're
keepin' him too busy at night.
We're talking about a man's
life here, you son of a bitch,
and the lives of others
he might put in jeopardy.
Maybe I should put him in
quarantine. How 'bout it, Steel?
You call it, Captain.
I'll build him a cage.
[Captain] Yeah. Might
not be a bad idea...
give some of the rest
of us a shot at some lovin'.
[Steel] Hey, it's
gonna be a long winter.
Come on, Ted.
Let's get out of here.
[Captain] I'm callin' a
meeting for 7:00 tonight.
I want everybody present.
Everybody, lady,
including dr. Frankenstein
and including your boyfriend.
- I gave him a sedative. He won't be awake.
- Look here, woman.
I'm short on man power.
I won't have you goin' around...
dopin' up any of my men
without orders from me.
- Is that clear?
- Yes, sir!
Fuck you, sir!
[Door slams]
Out of the frying pan,
into the fire.
I thought cooper was an asshole, but
he was a sweetheart next to Rhodes.
We could be in real trouble. You'd better watch
yourself... I mean, physically watch yourself.
I can handle it. Don't worry.
It's not going to come to that.
We've just gotta pound some logic
into their heads. Impossible.
[Sighs]
Where's dr. Logan?
Frankenstein? He's in his
laboratory. Where else?
[Man] there's a loss of initiative, caution,
many of the human cognitive functions.
Apparently the result of
decay in the frontal, parietal,
temporal
and occipital lobes.
On revival, the rate of
decomposition slows substantially.
[Switch clicks] Indications
are that these beings...
could function
over a period of years...
in cases of early revival, 10 to 12 years
before decay would threaten mobility.
- [Screams]
- [Growls]
[Moaning]
The brain is the engine, Sarah,
the motor that drives them.
They don't need any blood flow, don't
need any of their internal organs.
Now, I致e severed all
the vital organs in this one.
There's nothing left of the corpse but
brain and limbs, and still it functions.
Oh, look, Sarah. Look.
[Grunting]
See, it wants me. It wants
food, but it has no stomach.
It can take no nourishment
from what it ingests.
It's working on instinct, a
deep, dark, primordial instinct.
Decomposition occurs first in
the frontal lobes, the neocortex,
and next in the limbic
system, the middle brain.
But the core... the core is the last
thing to be attacked by the decay.
It's the "r" complex, Sarah... that
central bit of prehistoric jelly...
that we inherited
from the reptiles.
Here. I've gone into the center here
and attacked the "r" complex discretely.
I've removed it from the
equation... this corpse.
I believe this creature would be benign even
if it had its eyesight and its other senses.
Its primitive instincts
have been erased.
[Machine whirring]
It still has motor function, probably
still has powers of deliberation.
It can be domesticated,
Sarah, don't you see?
It can be conditioned to behave
the way we want it to behave.
And all that's required
is 15 hours of fancy surgery...
that only a handful of people
are trained to do.
We were going to stop work on the neurophysical,
concentrate on something more practical.
These finds are central to the
condition. I will not stop work...
that might lead to an answer, let alone in
an area that is central to the condition.
[Exhales forcefully] But you're just proving
theories that were advanced months ago.
And you're not even proving them correctly.
You're making a lot of assumptions.
You're wasting time trying
to define what's happening...
instead of looking
for what's making it happen.
And just slicing up too many
specimens. It's extremely dangerous...
to go up on top
and round them up in the wild.
Well, we can't control them.
What happened to this one?
[Doctor] it was too unruly. I couldn't
handle it. I had to destroy it.
- We can still get information from it.
- Dr. Logan,
we are losing
the cooperation of the men.
I'm not even sure they'll go up top
when we run out of the specimens we have.
I'm not sure they won't just
try to shut us down completely.
Well, I値l show them results.
I'll show them results.
I'll show them that these creatures can
be domesticated even without the surgery.
Knowing what they are, we can
begin to approach them properly,
condition them,
control them.
We've got to do this, Sarah.
It's our only hope.
Yes, this is major cooper.
I needed him, Sarah. He's helping us more
now than he ever did when he was alive.
- But I saw the grave.
- They buried one of the specimens.
Jesus. God, Logan.
Do you know what they'll do to
you if they find out about this?
- Do you know what they'll do to all of us?
- They'll never find out.
He can't be recognized.
[Moaning]
[Gasping]
Not a peep. Long-range or short,
high-band or low, I can't raise anybody.
[Man] how can that be, McDermott?
There must be other groups like us.
Somebody else must be tryin' to
radio. Yeah. What the hell is this?
Maybe we are the only ones left.
I'm sure there's others.
This is not the best place to be sending
from, and a lot of the equipment I知 using...
has been rotting down here
since the second world war.
Well, it's up to you
to get it workin' right.
Lay off the fuckin' booze
for a while, why don't ya?
And get somebody
on that fuckin' horn, pronto.
Well, if we stay down here long enough, I値l
have to lay off the fuckin' booze, Steel,
'cause there won't fuckin'
be any of it fuckin' left.
In the meanwhile, I will continue to indulge
myself, and I will continue doing my best...
in the good fight
against dry rot and rust.
Yeah? Well, your best
ain't good enough, asshole.
You think I知 not aware of our situation?
You think I want to stay isolated down here?
You know, I壇 make a desperate
effort to raise somebody...
just in the hope of gettin' away
from your nasty mouth, Steel.
The fact is...
the fact is...
either we are
the only ones left...
or there's nobody within range of my
puny little second world war signals.
We used to talk to Washington all
the time. They could hear us then.
We were on relays then.
We weren't over the air.
You know, the power's off on the
mainland now, in case you haven't heard.
All the shopping malls are closed.
We don't appreciate your jokes.
Keep it up, and I値l shove that
bottle of yours right up your wise ass.
I've got better things to do than listen
to this kindergarten. Are we finished?
No, we ain't
finished here, lady. Sit down.
What else do you want? We've given
you the reports for this week.
We've given you everything you've
asked for. You've given us greek salad.
Formulas, equations, a lot of
fancy terms that don't mean a thing.
I wanna know if you're doin' something that's
gonna help us out of this deep shit we're in,
or if you're all in there
just jerkin' each other off.
She doesn't have to jerk off like the rest of
us, Captain. She got an honest-to-god dick...
to get off on, huh?
[Laughs mockingly]
It may be yellow,
but it's still a dick!
[Yells, laughs]
[Others laugh]
I said we ain't
finished here, lady.
Sit down.
Sit down, or so help me,
god, I値l have you shot.
- You'll what?
- I said,
"I値l have you shot. "
Have you lost your mind?
No, ma'am.
Have you? I just told you I was willing to
kill you if you didn't get back in your chair.
You didn't get back
in your chair.
Goddamn it! You can't
shove us around like this.
Since when did this
become a military operation?
Since I took over.
Steel, shoot that woman.
Bang! You're dead.
Shoot that woman
or you're dead.
You think
I知 fuckin' around, Steel?
You're wrong.
Now, you got till a count of
five, and that's two you wasted.
- [Spits]
- That's three.
- Four.
- Sit down, Sarah.
What is this?
Shut up and sit down.
That's five, Steel.
[Gun cocks] All right.
All right.
- [Gun cocks]
- No!
Anybody else have any questions about the way
things are gonna run around here from now on?
This ain't
a goddamn field trip, people.
This is a fuckin' war!
I'm not down in this cave for my
health. I'm down here on orders.
Your orders are to facilitate
the job of this scientific team.
This is a civilian team, and we don't
have to be subjected to your tyranny.
Who's being subjected
to what, Fisher?
You've lost one man. [Men] Yeah. Right.
We've lost five.
[Men murmuring agreement]
Where does it say we gotta keep those
dumb fucks next door to where we sleep?
Where does it say we should do any one
thing but shoot the mothers in the head?
[Logan] We don't have enough ammunition
to shoot them all in the head.
The time to have done that
would've been at the beginning.
No. We let them overrun us.
They have overrun us, you know.
We're in the minority now.
Something like 400,000
to one, by my calculations.
I haven't eaten.
Is there food?
You were supposed to be
here at 7:00 sharp, mister.
I know. Sarah told me. I'm sorry. I
couldn't break away. Is there food?
Listen, egghead, let me bring you
up to date on what's... excuse me.
Let me...
excuse me!
- Is there food?
- I'm runnin' this monkey farm now, Frankenstein,
and I wanna know what the fuck
you're doin' with my time!
'Cause if we're just
jerkin' off here,
I知 gonna have my men
blow the piss...
out of those precious specimens
of yours, [Men murmuring agreement]
And we're gonna get the hell out of here and
leave you and your highfalutin asshole friends...
to rot
in this stinkin' sewer!
Is that food enough for ya?
Where will you go, Captain?
You can destroy my specimens,
but what about the millions more
that are waiting to greet you outside?
Do you really think you can
"blow the piss" out of them?
All of them? They have you in a
hopeless situation, strategically.
You're lost. Well,
you're lost unless...
unless what? Unless what, Frankenstein?
- Unless you can make them behave.
- [Men scoffing]
This is a fuckin' loony bin! I ain't bein'
paid enough to work in a fuckin' loony bin!
- I ain't bein' paid at all!
- Paid? What the hell are they payin' him for?
[Captain] All right.
Shut up! Just shut up!
What the hell are you
talkin' about, Frankenstein?
I'll be able to show you
soon enough. Sarah knows.
She's seen the progress I致e been
making. Isn't that right, Sarah?
Yes. There's been some progress.
What kind of progress?
What are you talkin' about, "make
them behave"? What does that mean?
It means keeping them from
wanting to eat us, for one thing.
It means keeping them in
check, controlling them.
- Controlling them.
- When are you gonna show us something we can understand?
Very close. Very close.
I think in a matter of weeks...
I don't think there's any way you can
tell how long anything is going to take.
It could be months; it could be years before
we know exactly what we're dealing with.
[Men murmuring]
Sarah's research...
[Louder] Sarah's research is more
esoteric than mine. [Murmuring stops]
She's looking for a way to reverse the
process, a way to eradicate the problem.
That could take a long time,
a very long time.
She may never find
what she's looking for.
We have a limited supply
of chemical agents.
Our equipment
is hopelessly inadequate.
McDermott doesn't
have decent radio gear.
Now you're tellin' me that you
don't have the shit you need?
We're runnin' low on ammunition. We're
runnin' low on men, for chrissakes!
It was very rushed. This operation
was put together in a matter of days.
Yeah, well, it can all be taken
apart in a matter of minutes, lady,
and I知 here to tell you that
I知 ready to do that little thing.
I'm ready to
take the next train outta here!
[Logan] I ask you again,
Captain: Where will you go?
You have no choices. You'll have to
give us the weeks that we've asked for.
You have to give us
however long it takes. Look.
There have to be survivors
in Washington. [Man] my ass.
They have more sophisticated shelters
than this one. [Man] bullshit.
There have to be people in those shelters
who know about us, who know where we are.
With no radio contact,
they'll come looking for us.
- [Men murmuring]
- I said shut up!
You got
a little more time.
A little more.
I ain't sayin' how much.
But you'd better start showin' me some
results, and you'd better not piss me off.
You understand? Nothin' happens around
here without my knowin' about it!
And anybody fucks
with my command,
they get court-martialed,
they get executed.
You'd better know
I mean it, too, people.
[Men murmuring] He wouldn't have
done it. I can't believe he would've.
No, he wouldn't
have done it.
- He would've had Steel do it.
- He can't be that inhuman.
No. He's human. That's
what scares me, you know.
He won't shoot Billy 'cause he doesn't
have anybody else who knows electronics.
He won't shoot me,
'cause I知 his ride.
He probably won't shoot old Frankenstein,
'cause the old doc can talk him silly.
But the rest of you...
better start worrying,
you know.
Maybe if we tried working together,
we could ease some of the tensions.
- We're all pulling in different directions.
- That's the trouble, Sarah.
People got different ideas
concerning what they want out of life.
[Gasps]
You are afraid,
aren't you?
Just as afraid as I am.
Why don't you take a sedative,
Sarah, so you can sleep?
You're full of shit, Sarah, you know
that? You're really full of shit.
I'm through with you.
Fine then. Get out.
Just get out!
[Clattering]
[Growling]
[Growling continues]
[Clattering]
- Hey, guys! Come on, man!
- [Sarah] for goodness sake!
[Men grunting, muttering]
I'm all right.
Thanks, bill.
Here.
I've just filled it up.
Got a refill as well.
No, thanks.
I'm all right. Really.
It's just brandy.
Good for the heart.
It's shit for your heart,
and it eats up your liver.
[Coughs]
We don't get a lot of visitors
out here, and we like it that way.
Here it is: The Ritz.
Madam.
John's probably
out the back.
Hey! Well,
what do you know.
Welcome
to civilization, Sarah.
The last holdout.
It's pretty nice.
Nicer than we got inside.
- Not a bad idea.
- It's a little safer where you are.
But we like to live dangerously,
Billy boy and me, you know.
That's a laugh. I haven't seen you do
anything dangerous since we got here.
We stickin' around.
That's gettin' a bit dangerous,
as I hope you noticed
this evening.
You're a mystery to me.
You really are.
Not like
those other goons in there.
You have a sense of...
[Scoffs]
Of what? [Chuckles] Never mind.
No, no, no. Come on.
Let's talk about it.
I came down here to get
drunk. I don't have the energy.
Hey, hey. It takes more energy to keep
quiet than it does to speak the mind.
Go ahead. Let go of what you got, now.
You were sent down here
to do a job.
My job is to fly the whirlybird.
I've been doin' that job just fine.
You have the protection of this facility.
You eat our food. You drink our water.
And you don't lift a finger
to help. Neither one of you.
[John laughing]
We don't believe in what
you're doin' here, Sarah.
Hey, you know what all they
keep down here in this cave?
Man, they got the books and the
records of the top 500 companies.
They got the defense department
budget down here.
And they got the negative
for all your favorite movies.
They got microfilm with tax
return and newspaper stories.
They got immigration records,
census reports,
and they got official accounts of
all the wars and plane crashes...
and volcano eruptions and
earthquakes and fires and floods...
and all the other disasters that
interrupted the flow of things...
in the good old U.S. Of A.
Now, what does it matter,
Sarah darling?
All this filing
and record keeping?
We ever gonna give a shit? We even
gonna get a chance to see it all?
This is a great big
14-mile tombstone!
[Voice echoing] Tombstone!
[Distant moaning]
With an epitaph on it that
nobody gonna bother to read.
Now, here you come... here you come
with a whole new set of charts...
and graphs and records.
What you gonna do? Bury them down
here with all the other relics...
of what once was?
Let me tell you what else. Yeah,
I知 gonna tell you what else.
You ain't never gonna figure it out,
just like they never figured out...
why the stars
are where they're at.
It ain't mankind's job
to figure that stuff out.
So what you're doin'
is a waste of time, Sarah.
And time is all
we got left, you know.
What I知 doing...
is all there's left to do.
Shame on you.
There's plenty to do.
Plenty to do. So long as there's you
and me and maybe some other people,
we could start over, start
fresh, get some babies.
And teach 'em, Sarah, teach
'em never to come over here...
- and dig these records out.
- [Distant moaning]
Hey.
You want to put some kind
of explanation...
down here
before you leave?
Here's one as good as
any you're likely to find.
We're being punished
by the creator.
He visited a curse
on us...
so we man could look at...
what hell was like.
Maybe didn't want to see us
blow ourselves up...
and put a big hole
in his sky.
Maybe he just wanted to show
us he was still the boss man.
Maybe he figure... we was getting
too big for our britches...
trying to
figure his shit out.
[Growling] [Fisher] You son of a bitch!
[Continues growling]
[Fisher]
Damn it!
It's no good.
It's no fuckin' good.
What is that stuff?
It's something called beef treats,
which the army provides us with...
so generously.
- He won't touch it.
- Shit. I wouldn't either.
Sorry. We're fresh out
of filet mignon.
- [Groaning continues]
- What is this? Part of Logan's plan...
to try
and socialize these things?
He told me himself they don't eat for
nourishment. What are we hoping for here?
Hoping to satisfy the urge.
You see, Sarah, they're...
they are us. They are
the extensions of us.
They are the same animal, simply
functioning less perfectly.
They can be fooled, you see? They can be
tricked into being good little girls and boys,
the same way we were tricked into it
on the promise of some reward to come.
[Moaning]
They have to be rewarded.
Reward is the key.
I'm convinced of that now.
Come. I've got something
to show you.
That wasn't very nice, you know.
That wasn't very nice at all.
Let's go.
And you can just sit there in the
dark and think about what you've done.
Think about it.
Think.
[Moaning over p. a.,
feedback] I call him Bub.
That's what the club fellas used to call my
father. Can you imagine a surgeon called Bub?
Nobody seemed to mind,
though. He was rich.
[Moaning]
My father was rich.
He used to say I壇 never
be rich doing pure research.
I'd never be rich.
Uh, Bub's been responding so
well lately, I致e let him live.
Well, is he alive or dead? Well, that's
the question these days, isn't it?
Well, let's say that I
let him continue to exist.
Hello, Bub!
[Both snickering]
[Over p. a.]
Here are some toys for you.
Some nice things
for you to play with.
You remember them from
before? From before.
Well, he's seen the other things
before, but the book is new.
Look, look, look.
I thought he'd do that.
[Scribbling]
[Moaning]
- Open it up.
- [Gasps]
He remembers. He remembers
everything that he used to.
Bub, I知 very pleased.
Very pleased.
What's he trying
to prove?
I saw one of those things
sittin' in a car in d. C...
tryin' to drive
down independence avenue.
It didn't make me wanna be
its friend. No. It's amazing.
It's not what this one does,
but what he doesn't do.
What do you mean?
He doesn't get excited...
and doesn't get agitated
when Logan walks in the room.
He doesn't see Logan as... lunch.
Dinner.
Breakfast.
Having fun? What's he doin' in there?
[Logan] No need for that,
Captain. He's quite docile.
Come in.
You can all come in.
Bub won't mind.
[Moans]
Extraordinary,
isn't it?
That's right, Bub.
Say hello.
Come on, Captain. Give
me a break, will ya?
Say hello
to your aunt Alicia.
Say, "hello, aunt Alicia. "
"Hello, aunt Alicia. "
[Moaning, muffled] Hel-lo,
aunt Alicia. "Hello. "
[Logan] apparently, he was in the military.
Return the salute and see what he does.
You want me to salute
that pile of walking pus?
Salute my ass.
Your ignorance is exceeded
only by your charm, Captain.
How are we going to set an example
for them if we behave barbarically?
Take the bullets out, please, and
let me have your pistol, Sarah.
[Steel laughing hysterically]
[Moaning]
[Gun cocks]
It's empty, Captain. We
saw the bullets come out.
Let's see what he does. Let's see
what Bub does in this situation.
[Gun clicks]
[Moans]
Jesus... Christ.
What are we supposed to do?
Teach 'em tricks?
What the fuck is wrong with
you people? They're dead!
They're fucking dead, and
you wanna teach 'em tricks?
They have to be rewarded, Captain. Why
else will they do what we want them to do?
I don't want 'em
to do anything but drop over!
Yes, well, apparently they're not
inclined to do that for you, Captain.
Is this your progress?
Is this the shit that's
supposed to knock our socks off?
It's the beginning, yes. It's the
bare beginning of social behavior.
Of civilized behavior.
Civil behavior is what distinguishes
us from the lower forms.
It's what enables us
to communicate,
to go about things in an orderly fashion,
without attacking each other like beasts.
Civility must be rewarded,
Captain.
If it isn't rewarded,
there's no use for it.
There's just no use
for it at all.
- [Grunting]
- [Zombie growling]
[Growling continues]
- 'Possum ready?
- [Growling]
Come on. Grab it.
Come on.
You got it?
Hey. You got it?
[Growling continues]
No!
No! No!
Miller! Miller!
- [Screaming]
- [Gunshots]
I can't do it.
I can't do it!
- [Screaming] I can't do it.
- [Moaning]
[Yelling]
[Growling]
[Screaming]
- [Gunshot]
- [Continues screaming]
[Groaning]
[Departing footsteps]
Don't let this happen.
Don't let this happen to me.
I don't wanna be one of them.
Take me. Please. Take me.
[Gasping]
[Gunshot]
[Body thudding]
[Bats screeching]
[Miguel yelps]
[Miguel yelling, screaming]
[Miguel grunts]
I need fire.
[Screaming]
[Men talking,
indistinct]
Jesus, Mary and Joseph!
[Weapon cocking]
[Panting]
Get out of the way, lady.
No. I amputated the infected
area. I think I caught it in time.
Yeah?
But what if you didn't?
If I didn't,
I値l shoot him myself.
It's the spick.
The yellow son of a bitch. It's his fault
this happened. It's his yellow fuckin' fault.
Get out of the way, bitch, or I値l
go right through you with this.
We're getting to make this a habit, man...
pointing guns at each other, you know.
We just lost two men
'cause of this motherfucker.
Weli... that kinda evens
the odds between us then.
[Steel] The spick's been bit,
Captain. We gotta blast him.
He's been bit! I got
the infection in time.
That's bullshit, lady.
I seen a thousand of 'em.
He's gonna die.
If he dies,
I値l destroy him myself.
Unless he gets you first.
You may still want to sleep
with him.
I don't want him
inside the complex.
We'll keep him out here,
with us.
We gotta blast him,
Captain.
That'd be doin' 'im a favor,
Steel.
You think he wants
to walk around after he's dead?
You think he wants to be
one of those things?
Think about it, lady.
And think about this,
all of ya...
from now on, you ain't gettin'
shit from me and my men.
Tomorrow morning, we're going inside
that corral, and we ain't comin' out...
till every one of those rotten
piles of garbage has been wasted.
Come on, Steel.
[Shouting] Get out of there,
Steel! We got better things to do!
You're on my shit list,
flyboy.
[Holsters gun]
Thank you.
Let's take him inside,
clean him up.
Think you can move him?
I- I think so.
[Torch clatters]
[Sobbing]
It's all right.
It's okay.
Shh, shh, shh.
Shh, shh.
- It's a man's sweater. Try it on.
- Thanks.
I have to go to the lab.
He's going to need
some morphine...
along with
some other supplies.
I'd better go along. I'm sure those
boys haven't calmed themselves down yet.
I'm sorry I said
those things about you.
I'm sorry too. Really.
Well, what do you know?
We are heroes after all.
What a relief.
Sarah.
He might not make it,
you know.
I know it.
At least we gave him
a chance.
I'll keep an eye on him.
Hey.
You guys be careful. You're not back in
half an hour, I知 coming out to look for you.
They'll leave us alone.
Half an hour.
We'll be back.
[Liquid Bubbling]
Jesus god almighty.
The resident surgeon has been
burning the midnight oils.
What the hell has he been doin'
down here, slaughtering cattle?
In his mind, that's probably
not far from the truth.
[Clicks, rewinds]
[Stops]
[Man on tape] Grandfather's
talking. His mind's talking.
There. I've put it away. I've put
it away, mother. I've put it away.
- Bastard. Be civilized! Be civil.
- [Man groaning, growling]
Christ! Take that off.
Take that off! Take that off!
[Groaning, growling continues]
Five minutes, mother.
Just five minutes.
Oh, my god.
[Tape continues,
indistinct]
- [Crashes]
- No, Sarah! Don't!
It'll just bring out
Rhodes and the men.
Leave it be,
leave it be.
Let's go.
Let's get outta here.
I'm beginning to think we should take
that helicopter before somebody else does.
[Door opens, shuts]
[Faint groaning]
Hello, Bub.
Mother is very proud
of you.
Very, very proud indeed.
You did quite nicely today.
[Groaning]
## [Choir: "Ode to Joy"]
[Soft groaning]
- [Clicks off]
- [Angry groaning]
## [Resumes]
I don't believe it.
Logan's star pupil.
- Now, tomorrow, we can play with these things again.
- [Clicks off]
Now it's time
for your reward.
I brought you
something good.
[Groans]
What is that?
Is that...
it can't be.
Oh, god. I can't look.
Can't... [Gasps]
- [Soft groan]
- Good night, Bub.
What are you givin' him in
there, Frankenstein? What?
- Huuh!
- What is it, huh?
What do you give him?
Scum!
No, you... you must listen to me,
Captain. You must listen.
Listen to this.
Hold it, Fisher.
Torrez, get his gun.
Take all the guns.
All of 'em.
All their fucking guns!
Take all their guns.
All their guns!
Those are my men in there.
My men. [Shouting] Those
are my men in there!
[Rhodes talking,
indistinct]
Hold it right there.
Frankenstein's dead.
This scum gets it next unless you
throw your weapons out right now.
He means it, Johnny. He
killed Logan in cold blood.
I killed Logan
because he was a butcher.
I'll kill the rest of them one at a time,
unless you get your black ass out here, flyboy.
- Let him go, Rhodes.
- Torrez, get his machete.
We're gettin' outta here
right now.
You give me any shit about it,
I blow his head off.
Whirlybird can't
hold us all.
"Us all" ain't going.
Me, my men, you. That's it.
You'll never get me to do that,
Rhodes.
No!
Hey!
Rickles, open the gates.
Steel, shove 'em in there.
[Indistinct talking,
laughing]
Have a nice visit
with McDermott, huh?
[Zombies growling]
Rhodes...
don't do this, please.
Gonna give us a ride,
flyboy?
I'll do whatever you say, man.
Let her go now.
Rhodes. Let 'em off.
I'll take you...
wherever you want to go.
Like you said,
chopper can't hold us all.
[John]
Rhodes, don't do it.
You do it, and I won't fly.
I swear, you got to kill me
before I fly.
Let 'em out.
That's the deal.
I make the deals around here,
not you.
Now you get your shit together,
whatever you need.
Isn't there
an old silo back there?
No. We can't go back there
without guns.
- [Sarah] we can't stay here. They'll tear us apart.
- Oh, Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
Don't shoot 'im!
We need his ass.
Steel, kick him around
a little bit.
Might knock some sense
into that jungle-bunny head.
- [Rickles] Captain!
- [Rhodes] that's it.
Run, you fuckin' lunatics.
[Zombies groaning]
Oh!
Uuh!
[Grunting]
They're gone, flyboy.
Let's go.
Not a chance.
[Whirring, beeping]
- Jesus Christ. That's the elevator.
- Check it out.
[Lips smacking]
[Groans]
[Zombie groaning]
Aw, Jesus.
Rock slide.
We can't get through.
This way.
We can try and get around.
[Groaning]
Aah!
[Shrieking]
- [Screams]
- [Gurgling]
[Gasps] Oh, it's you. This way.
[Bat screeches]
Let's go, Torrez. Get up.
[Gunshots]
Uuh!
Aw, shit!
Somebody took this apart.
The only other control's up on
the platform with a hand box.
Stuck.
- Rickles, we can't get out of here.
- Fix it. Can't you fix it?
It's that fuckin' spick
that did this! Fix it!
Come on, man!
Fix what?
Fix the box, man! Come on!
Fix it! They tore the guts out!
I can't fix it! We got the
book here! We can fix it!
The bastard.
[Bat screeches]
Sarah!
[Echoing]
Willie!
John!
[Echoing]
[Groaning]
[Gunshot]
[Distant gunshots]
[Zombie groaning]
Uuh!
[Barks]
Let's keep moving.
[Growling]
Aha!
[Grunts]
Uuh!
[Groaning]
[Zombies groaning]
[Muffled scream]
Hold down. Aw, fuck!
What's goin' on?
That spick.
He ripped these controls out,
the little yellow bastard.
The little shit.
The little fuckin' shit.
You tried to make
a run for it.
[Whirring, beeping]
[Steel]
Holy shit.
Holy fuckin' shit.
[Shouting]
Rhodes!
Rhodes, you bastard!
[Moans softly]
[Wailing]
[Sniffling]
[Screaming]
Oh, shit!
Aah! Shit!
Fuck!
Ha, ha!
[Whooping]
Holy shit!
[Cackling]
[Screaming]
Shit!
Rhodes! Goddamn, Rhodes!
Open the door,
you son of a bitch!
Rhodes!
Shit!
[Gunshot]
[Nasally voice]
Come on, Bub.
Come on, you pus-brained
bag of shit.
You wanna learn how to shoot,
Bub? I'll teach you how to shoot.
Come on, you bag of...
[Growling]
[Screaming]
- [Zombies groaning]
- Oh!
[Sarah]
Let's go. Follow the red lights.
- It's temporarily out of service.
- The ladder! Go ahead. Up, up.
Up!
[Screeching]
[Growling]
[Gunshot]
Come along, Johnny.
We're countin' on ya
to fly us to the promised land.
Come on, come on.
Come on!
Oh, shit!
Aah!
Uuh!
You fuck.
Aah!
[Groans]
You pus fuck! You fuck!
You pus fuck! You pus fuck!
[Screaming]
You f... aah!
Come on!
Come on! Come o-o-on!
Come o-o-on!
[Zombies gasping
delightedly]
[Screaming]
[Gasping]
Salazar!
[Ghostly moaning]
[John] let's hope they filled up
the gas tank from the other night.
Oh, my god.
Come on, come on!
[John]
Get in, get in!
Aah!
[Screams]
[Gulls cawing]
# Eyes#
# Eyes, eyes#
# Is it you#
# Is it me#
# Holding on for so long#
# Trying desperately#
# Is it right#
# Oh-oh-oh, is it fair#
# Wanting more, so much more#
# And it's never there#
# I am with you when#
# I feel like I知#
# Alone#
# It's easy to pretend#
# This world could never end#
# Come take my heart, my soul#
# My love#
# My life#
# Tonight#
# Love me#
# Tonight, babe#
# Take me to the world inside#
# Your eyes#
# Tonight##
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org