Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Thanks for comin'. Nice to see you.
- Why are we slouchin' ?
I don't have that much time.
The gates are gonna be open
between 11:00 and midnight.
I got my guy on the gate.
You go right through, no fuss, no muss.
- What are you worryin' for ?
- Let me worry !
Where's the stuff, huh ?
That's a lot of toxic waste you got.
You got a problem, baby.
No, you got !
Just get it to Jersey and dump it !
- Dumpin' it's a federal rap.
I'm takin' all the chances.
- That's why we pay you !
All right, come on.
Where's the money ? Yo, the money.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on !
What is this, the tip ?
This the tip ?
- You deal with the E.P.A.
See what it costs you !
- Make sure you're there by 11:00.
Aaah !
What are you guys, crazy ?
You wanna blow up the goddamn joint ?
[ Jackhammers Pounding ]
You drive carefully.
I don't want you to hit anybody.
Oh, here we go,
into the tunnel of love.
All right, get over, get over.
Who's got the cards ?
[ Horns Honking ]
We collected 32,563 tolls
between the first and second rock.
[ Chattering,
Typewriters Clacking ]
Grace !
Grace, are you in there ?
Come back. Grace !
[ Horn Honking ]
I found this
under my bed.
You think you could be
a little less discreet ?
[ Laughing ]
I found this under my bed.
I'll see you after work.
Listen, when I return this,
I have somethin' to tell you.
If it is good news, why not get it now
and have a completely good day ?
As opposed to one filled
with apprehension and tension,
which can lead to other related
physical disorders and high anxiety.
No, I will tell you later,
Island Girl.
- Tell me now.
- No. I'll tell you tonight.
- Hey, Frankie, how's your load ?
- Mostly in my shorts.
- I need a pit stop, bad.
- Just hold it. We're behind schedule.
- [ Dog Barking ]
- [ Men Laughing ]
- Need some help with that bag ?
- Maybe you need some
other kind of help.
[ Man ]
Stuck-up bitch !
[ Woman Shouting ]
Ugh.
[ Siren Wailing ]
[ Coughing ]
"Dear Mr. Thompson."
Thanks a lot.
"Thank you for your submission.
Regretfully, at this time, we--"
Are laughing our asses off that
you even wasted the stamps...
by sending us your play.
[ Keyboard Clicking ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Phone Ringing ]
[ Answering Machine ] Hi, it's Maddy.
I'm out. The machine is in.
[ Beeps ]
Maddy, hi. It's Kimberly.
I have this important audition, and I
told Claudio you'd take my shift today.
I did it for you
when you went to Bermuda. Bye !
- Got ya !
- [ Phone Ringing ]
Hi, it's Maddy.
I'm out. The machine is in.
[ Beeps ]
Maddy, it's David.
I feel really bad
about the way things ended up...
and I want you to give me
three more months, and I--
I promise I'll--
I promise I'll tell her.
[ Woman ]
Honey, you've got to cut the cake !
- [ David ] I'll be right in.
- Oh !
It's George's birthday,
and we're having a party,
and call me on Monday.
I-I-I love you.
Oh ! Oh !
Go !
Traffic report says the bridge
is backed up to Westchester.
Forget the bridge.
Take one of the tunnels.
# [ Electric Guitar ]
[ Man ]
The "Territory: Beyond."
It's still out there.
- The "Territory: Beyond."
- It's still out there.
The "Territory: Beyond."
It's still out there.
It's exhausting being me.
[ Everybody Laughing ]
- Now the question is,
what do we do with it ?
- Sales are down 12%.
Broadening our marketing target
from inner-city youth...
to the more affluent
off-road vehicle group--
I know that.
Give me something
I don't know.
We're gonna have to stack some
G.R.P.'s with this commercial,
no matter where we run it.
- Now, the test results are maxing out--
- Speak English, Elliot.
We wanna put it
on the Super Bowl, first quarter.
Super Bowl.
- That's a whole pile of money.
- It's time to gamble, Roy.
It's not like
we have any choice.
We'll buy 60 in the first quarter and
we'll do a cut-down 30 in the second.
You wanna gamble ?
Let's gamble.
Jonno, let's go.
- How are we doin' on time ?
- Traffic's a mess.
- But if we take the tunnel,
we'll just make it.
- Let's take the tunnel.
Come on, Cooper.
Okay. It's all over.
- We're gonna have
a nice day in the city.
- Good boy.
Whatever good that specialist does
is undone by the long drive in.
He hates riding in the car.
It puts him off for days.
We're not taking him back
to that quack in Colts Neck.
Look, Eleanor,
he's perfectly capable.
- We don't even know
what's wrong with the dog.
- Who knows him best ?
- Me or a complete stranger ?
Let's go this way.
- All right.
You know what I'd like to do ?
I'd like to go to Rumpelmayer's.
- Cooper loves their cherry-vanilla.
- That's a brilliant idea.
- What'd they get you for, man ?
- They got me for stealin'.
What you up here for ?
Cheating on your expense account ?
No, I sell cellular phones
with cloned numbers.
So, how much you get
from the register ?
- A hundred, two hundred.
- You use a gun ?
No, I used my looks.
Of course I used a gun !
I sell five to ten phones
a week for $500 apiece.
I don't use a gun.
Can you multiply ?
I ain't stupid, man.
I know my math.
If you so smart,
why you up in here ?
I guess I shouldn't have bought
that BMW for cash, huh ?
[ Horns Honking ]
[ Tires Squealing ]
[ Tires Skidding ]
- That's ridiculous !
- He's the top man in his field.
I wouldn't dismiss him lightly.
Dr. O'Corr, it says here
you got a 5:30 flight out of Newark,
but you want to stop off
at St. Vincent's first, right ?
- That's right.
- Lewis has been working--
- That's gonna be tight.
- There's a $50 tip in it
for you if you make it.
Then again, miracles do happen.
Right, Doc ?
[ Horn Honking ]
This sucks. I wanna go back
and skate at Rockefeller Center.
Hey, how about somebody else
does something they enjoy ?
You wanna visit old school friends,
leave me out of it.
A family vacation is about
staying with the family.
Let's not talk about
staying anywhere, okay ?
[ Alarm Beeps ]
- Hey, asshole !
- Hey !
- What do you want ?
What do you want ?
- Hold still !
- No, not that, please !
- Shut up !
I got it !
Come on. Let's go !
Come on !
[ Tires Squealing ]
Good afternoon.
Thirty-six channels and nothing's on.
Norman, one of these days you're
gonna surprise me with a new line.
[ Tires Squealing ]
Hey !
What ?
"Stop now ! You are being
tracked by Electroguard."
- What the hell is Electroguard ?
- [ Siren Wailing ]
[ Siren Wailing ]
[ Tires Squealing ]
The guy's a goddamn genius.
Right into the tunnel.
I'll call Jersey.
[ Horns Honking ]
"This tunnel was drawn up
by Edward Trammel in 1918...
on a napkin
in a Manhattan tavern.
Work on the tunnel
began in 1921,
employing thousands
of Irish immigrants
nicknamed 'sandhogs.'
The tunnel, which runs
under 24 feet of riverbed
and 72 feet of water--"
Hey, Dad, how many vacations
did you take Linda on ?
Ashley, that's enough !
Honey, listen.
Linda's history.
We're a family again.
That's all that counts.
[ Horn Honking,
Tires Squealing ]
- Aaah !
- Christ !
- [ Beeping ]
- What the hell is that ?
Oh, we got a live one here.
- Get a crew ready.
- All Jersey units,
requesting north tube roadblock.
- Black Cadillac now passing
through station seven.
- I want you, putz !
What'd we get ?
Come on. What'd we get ?
What's in there ?
Oh, that's a big one !
[ Horn Honking ]
Move it, jerk !
- Oh !
- You stupid bitch !
Pick 'em up !
- Oh, look what you did !
- Shit !
Now it's your fault !
[ Engine Revving ]
Heidi, it's helicopter skiing.
Think of it as a cordless chair lift.
[ Engine Revving,
Tires Squealing ]
Breaker, breaker !
We got a smoker ! We got a smoker !
- [ Honking ]
- Up yours, buddy !
# Start spreadin' the news #
# I'm leavin' tonight #
# I'm up to here
with all your shit #
# New York, New York #
[ Tires Squealing ]
Pass him, man !
- Ass !
- Take 'em !
[ Honking ]
- Get off my leg !
- I can't !
No !
Aaah !
Jesus Christ !
Here I am in the tunnel.
[ Tires Squealing ]
Aaah !
[ Panting ]
[ Tires Skidding ]
[ Groaning, Screaming ]
Aaah !
You're doctors !
Come on !
Get down ! Get down !
Somebody get him down !
Get him on the ground !
[ Screaming ]
Down !
Roll ! Roll !
- Roll !
- [ Moaning ]
Get over here !
[ Siren Wailing ]
I got him !
- We're gonna need some C-collars !
- Shit !
Let me see that arm.
You're gonna be okay.
Keep going.
There's emergency workers that way.
My father,
he's trapped in the car !
I can't get him out !
There's blood everywhere !
Can you help him out ?
- Help !
- We're comin' for you.
Don't worry about it.
- [ Groaning ]
- Look at me. Look at me.
I'm gonna try to move you
on the count of three.
I want you to help me out.
- Okay, one, two--
- Aaah !
Aaah !
- What's your name ?
- Susan.
- It'll be okay.
- He's severed an artery.
I'm gonna tie this off, and I want you
to hold it as tight as you can.
- You got that ?
- Yeah.
[ Woman Screaming ]
- All right, how is he ?
- He's dead.
I got a second-degree burn
over there. Get to it.
You, I've got an arterial bleeder
that needs an I.V.
- What are you still doin' here ?
- I thought you were a cab driver.
I am a driver.
Come on. Move !
- Give me a B.P. cuff.
- Sure, I got it !
[ Police Radio Indistinct,
People Shouting ]
Latura.
Jesus Christ.
Latura !
- Weller, right ?
- Get the hell outta here
before somebody sees you !
-Was it a bomb ?
-Accident, something about a toxic dump.
What's the status
on the Jersey side ?
Oh, man,
it's sealed up tight.
- It's a wipeout clear up
to the tollbooths.
- Where's the chief ?
- Standin' in front of me,
as far as I'm concerned.
- I'm talkin' about the new chief.
The dispatcher said Mr. California's
headed for the mid-river passage.
- Mid-river ?
- Yeah.
Hey, Latura,
watch your back.
[ Fire Engine Horn Honking ]
[ Shouting ]
George !
George, come in, please !
Are you there ?
This is Grace. George !
- [ Radio Static ]
- Oh, God, please be there.
George, come in.
George, are you there ?
George !
[ George ] Can anybody
hear me out there ? Come back.
We got a toxic fire.
It's burning toward the New Jersey side.
[ Coughing ]
Can anybody hear me ?
The ventilation system doesn't seem
to be pulling the smoke through.
Is anybody out there ?
Come back !
The New Jersey side
has completely collapsed !
[ Coughing ]
Oh, God, Jesus !
Oh, God, we got
fatalities down here !
Can anybody hear me ?
[ Horns Honking,
Sirens Wailing ]
[ Helicopter Blades Whirring ]
[ Sirens Blaring ]
[ People Shouting ]
Hey, you can't
go in there !
[ Screaming ]
[ Cops, Rescue Workers
Shouting Orders ]
No, no, no !
We're working the mid-river !
We got some wormholes here.
We'll find a way through.
- It will work in the mid-river !
- Thompson needs you !
- What ?
- Thompson !
- I'll be with you in a second.
- Okay.
- What's the ratio ? All right.
- [ Radio: Indistinct ]
Frank, you got any hope
on the New Jersey side ?
Fifty-yard cave-in, minimum.
Whatever's burning in there
is toxic as Trenton. They got samples.
Demo ! Demo !
Come on, people, speak to me !
- Give me another reading, Bob.
- I would if I had time,
but we're running out of it.
If you wanna buy some time,
you gotta blow the tunnel shut.
- What are you doin' here, Kit ?
- You're not part of this.
I know that,
but just listen to me.
We ran a terrorist hypothetical
in '94.
The only way to fix the fire
is to blow the roof in and seal
the survivors from the fumes.
Where I come from, we don't blow up
a tunnel that's already been blown up.
- Chief wants to go through mid-river.
- No, wait a minute.
Frank, you don't have to
rationalize my actions to this guy !
I know you know your job,
but we did a simulation.
You'll all be dead
before you get through.
I know you ran a drill in '94,
but right now you're not
running a goddamn thing.
Copy that.
- You're right. I just wanna help.
- You don't get it, do you ?
You don't work here anymore.
You understand that ?
Wilson, if I could just talk--
Come on, Kit.
He's gonna have you arrested !
You gotta blow the tunnel shut.
Talk to him.
You owe me that, Frank.
[ Man On P.A. ]
Your attention, please.
We've decided to evacuate
the south tube.
Please collect your valuables,
lock your cars...
and proceed in an orderly fashion
back to New Jersey.
[ Shouting ]
[ Man On P.A. Continues:
Indistinct ]
- [ Gasping, Coughing ]
- What do you got ?
Sorry, Chief.
It's blocked about 20 feet in.
That structure's so shaky,
I wouldn't even risk a firecracker.
- What about hydraulics ?
We brace up as we go.
- It can't be done !
The person who says it can't
be done is always interrupted
by the one who just did it !
Feed him the line !
[ Woman ]
Wilson !
Jesus Christ !
Watch the metal.
It's hot.
Aaah !
[ Coughing ]
What are you doing ?
Ashley, no, this way.
No, no, no, Ashley,
you don't have to take pictures now.
[ Ashley Sobbing ]
- Ashley, look at me. Look, honey.
- It's okay.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
- Hey ! Hey !
- What's happened ?
- I don't know. You're alive.
- [ Coughing ]
I'm gonna go on up
through the tunnel.
Stay here with your family so I'll know
where you are when I come back.
- How do we get out of here ?
- It's sealed at both ends.
[ Coughing ]
Jonno ?
Oh, shit !
[ Coughing ]
- Officer, over here.
You raise anybody on that walkie ?
- Hey !
Nothin' but static.
But you got a phone.
- $2000. It doesn't even work in here.
- "Territory: Beyond."
- Man, I know you.
- Roy Nord.
George Tyrell.
I got a pair of your shoes.
- Good, good. You like 'em ?
- Yeah, they're great !
I wear 'em on Saturdays
on my day off.
Bet you wish it was Saturday now, huh ?
What are we gonna do ?
Is there a way
out of this mess ?
There was a passage to the south tunnel
about a half mile back.
- You check it out ?
- Of course I checked it out !
It's all collapsed.
Well, think
I'll take a look.
I just told you it was collapsed, man.
You'd be wasting your time.
It's all blocked in.
There's no way out !
George, I was born
six weeks premature.
My own mother
couldn't keep me in.
[ Coughing ]
Eleanor.
[ Sobbing ]
Aaah !
Oh, my God !
Are you people okay ?
Yes, we're fine. We're fine.
Thank you for asking.
- How do you get out of here ?
- I'm still trying to get information.
- Cooper.
- Who's Cooper ? What's he look like ?
There he is !
He's all right.
No, no, no, darling.
Come on. I'll get him.
[ People Screaming ]
[ Coughing ]
- [ Screaming ]
- [ Coughing ]
Lady, get to the front of the bus !
The key is in the ignition.
Okay.
[ People Shouting ]
[ Shouting Continues ]
Hey, come on !
You gotta break it !
Hey, hurry up !
[ Electricity Crackling ]
Hurry up !
Come on, come on !
- Help !
- Oh, my God ! Oh, my God !
- Get the key over here !
- I'm gonna try to find you some help.
Help ? You are help !
You are our help !
N-no, n-no,
I'm just me.
[ Banging On Screen ]
Aaah !
- Aaah !
- The key's in the ignition !
Lady, lady, the keys !
The keys are in the ignition !
Hurry up ! Come on !
Come on, lady, open up.
- That one right there ! Right there !
- Go, go, go !
Did it ! Hurry up !
All right, man !
- You okay ? You all right ?
- My hero !
Thanks, lady.
What about him ?
That boy havin' a crack attack.
You might as well leave him alone.
- Come on, help me.
- Yo, help yourself, lady !
I'm tellin' you--
No, I'm telling you !
We are not leaving him here !
[ Electricity Crackling ]
Okay, uh, uh,
what's your name ?
Mikey.
I'm like-- I'm like--
Like scared, okay ?
Yeah, I know, Mikey,
I'm scared too,
but I'd feel so much better
if you were out here with me.
No, no, no, no, no !
- [ Sobbing ]
- Okay, okay.
Okay, uh--
Hey, Mikey.
Okay, uh,
uh, hey, Mikey,
you think we're pretty ?
[ Sobbing ]
Yeah. So ?
Wouldn't you rather be out there with
a couple of pretty girls than in here ?
- [ Electricity Crackling ]
- Oh, God !
Oh, shit !
Hey, yo, Mikey !
We are all scared !
Now get your crack-sucking
skinny ass out that window !
- Now !
- Okay ! Okay !
[ Sobbing ]
Okay. Okay.
You gotta get noisy
with these kids !
- Aaah !
- Hey, girl, you listen to me !
- Jump now ! Jump !
- Aaah !
Come on, now. Get up !
Let's get you outta here.
That's gas under the bus !
Lady, get the hell outta there !
You take care of her.
I don't want any trouble outta you.
No trouble, man.
Baby, are you in there ?
Uh, I need you to cut the power.
How do I say "cut the power" ?
Cut the power.
Lightning, what do you do ?
You get under a tree.
No shit !
You get back in the car.
Right ? 'Cause, 'cause,
'cause tires are rubber.
The what ?
What are you doing ?
What are you doing ? No, wait !
- What are you doing ?
- This is it.
No ! Wait a minute !
- Aaah !
- Oh, my God !
Cut the power. Cut the power.
Cut the power.
[ Indistinct Chatter ]
Is anybody watching these monitors ?
Oh, my God ! Norman !
Norman, it's George !
He's alive !
Cut the power, baby !
Down here ! Move !
Down here ! Yes !
- Mikey, go !
- Something must be done !
- No, you're not doing it.
- Live ! Live !
Come on, baby,
cut the power !
- You gotta cut the power.
- That would shut down the exhaust fans.
- Those fans are on a separate system.
- Hey, who the hell are you ?
- Please, go !
- Wait, lady !
Mikey, go !
- Just go, Mikey !
- Aaah !
Oh, don't splash !
Don't splash !
If you don't cut the power now,
that woman's dead.
[ Shouting ]
- Go !
- Jump !
Cut the goddamn power !
Jump !
Cut the god--
[ Gasping ]
Yes !
- Yes !
- You did it.
Now, who the hell
are you ?
I did a terrorist hypothetical here
in '94.
Yeah, Latura.
You were canned in '95.
You're back with the
Emergency Medical Service ?
Not exactly.
How's the monoxide level ?
You've got no authority
to come in here !
No, but I've crawled through
every part of that structure...
and I might be of use,
so how's the air ?
It's changing at a rate
of a million cubic feet an hour.
That's one-twentieth normal,
and it's getting worse !
[ Norman ]
Great, it's here.
Look at this thing.
When they glued this together,
they were still fighting World War One.
Okay, anyway,
here's the north tube,
south tube,
river, the riverbed,
and here's the tunnel:
a rectangle
set inside each tube.
What's this ?
I don't recognize this.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's--
The sandhogs worked 36-hour shifts
building this thing.
They had bunk rooms there, chapels,
kitchens-- They had everything.
But it was all sealed off
in the renovation of '72.
Hmm. Hey, Frank.
Did Wilson give an estimate
when he'd get to the mid-river passage ?
Nothin' that he
can share, Kit.
We had another collapse.
Mr. California got pancaked.
[ Kit ]
So what are we lookin' at ?
We don't know the stress points
in the mid-river.
We can't risk any explosives.
- It's all gotta be done by hand.
- That's gonna take forever.
If another shaft don't give,
10, 12 hours, minimum.
-How long's the air gonna hold ?
-Three hours, max.
All right, Frank,
here's what I think we oughta do.
I think we gotta cork it up and
seal off the survivors from the fumes...
until you can dig out
the mid-river passage.
Frank, are you
the acting chief or what ?
- Yeah, I'm the acting chief.
- So why don't you act ?
What are you tryin' to do,
nothin' ?
So you'll be held blameless
in case you have to testify later on ?
Don't pull that on me, Kit.
That's past history.
I had to take a chance.
Now you do.
I was in the same situation as you.
There's nothin' to think about.
Frank, it's three hours.
You wanna go in, Kit ?
Give me clearance.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
That tunnel is sealed from both ends.
I mean, the mid-river here
is hanging, like pick-up sticks.
Now, what the hell's
the way in, huh ?
Here.
[ Man On Walkie-Talkie ]
This is Engine Seven,
E.T.A. about five minutes.
[ Grace ]
There are four of those.
- We can shut them down
for two-and-a-half minutes.
- Each ?
Total. They're revved all
the way up to compensate for
the damaged exhaust shaft.
When we shut them down,
it'll severely cut their oxygen.
When the level gets too low,
the computer automatically
kicks the fans back on.
There's no override,
and there's no second shutdown !
- That's a safety feature.
- Anything else I should know ?
There are more problems.
You don't come out above the
roadway, you come out under it.
Norman, what's the combined force
of all the fans ?
- About 160 miles an hour.
- Great.
- Frank, where's the demo team ?
- On the way !
Listen up, please.
I wanna go over
a couple of things.
- You got tape in that camera ?
- Yeah.
Get over there, start shooting.
World's gonna wanna know
how we did this.
- New York City: the Territory Beyond !
- It's still out there !
Are you sayin'
you've found a way out of here ?
Not yet. If you wanna get
your hopes up, go ahead.
A little hope
never hurt anybody.
I will tell you
that this passage,
which George tells me leads to
the south tunnel, has some wormholes.
I'm gonna go in and see if they add up
to a way out. So if you pray, pray.
And if you don't, it might be
a good time to take it up.
[ Everybody Laughing ]
I promise you this, though--
Miss ?
- Huh ?
- Right here.
- All the way.
- Okay.
- You got me ?
- Yeah.
I promise you this:
If there is a way out,
I'll find it.
[ Everybody Laughing ]
Okay, hold on to that.
We're gonna make it.
- I'll be back soon.
- Yes, sir, we'll be waiting !
Listen, I'm gonna make one last sweep
of this tunnel, just in case he's right.
You keep trying to get somebody on
the other end of this thing. Take it.
- Hello ?
- [ Static ]
Need a refresher
on that Semtex procedure ?
- Set, wire, contact, run like hell.
- That's pretty much it, Chief.
[ Maddy On Walkie-Talkie ]
Can anyone hear me ?
I hear you.
Frank, got 'em !
[ Maddy ]
You can hear me ?
George ! George !
Okay, now, talk to me. How many people
are left alive down there ?
There's maybe a dozen,
and we're in the middle of the tunnel...
and there's a man who thinks
he knows the way out.
- How ?
- Something about a mid-river passage.
No, no, no, no.
Listen to me.
Tell them not to go in there. Tell them
we're coming down. Can you do that ?
- [ Static ] I can't hear you.
- Can you do that ?
- Hello !
- We lost 'em. Come on, Frank.
You got two-and-a-half minutes.
The fans are timed logarithmically.
Fan one kicks on
after one minute,
the remaining three
in sub-15 second intervals.
- You follow me ?
- I got it.
There's a guy down there
named George Tyrell.
You tell him
I want my bracelet back.
- [ Walkie-Talkie: Indistinct ]
- Ready to shut down.
Kit, what I did,
I did for the good of the department.
It wasn't personal.
He was your brother, Frank.
It doesn't get more personal.
I was angry.
I'm sorry.
Hey, don't apologize.
You make me feel like
you don't think I'm coming back.
You're probably right.
- Let's do it !
- Norman, now !
Fan one down,
fan two down,
fan three down,
fan four comin' down.
All fans down !
Go, Latura, go.
[ Beeping ]
It's not stopping !
It's not slowing down, Grace !
- Hit the brake !
- There are no brakes !
It's going on momentum !
You've got to stop it !
Frank !
[ Grinding Sound ]
Pull against it !
Pull ! Pull !
You got it !
It's stubborn !
- I got it !
- Just a little bit more !
- You got it ! Take it out !
- [ Beeping ]
[ Beeping,
Alarm Blaring ]
[ Beeping Stops ]
[ Maddy On Walkie-Talkie ]
Hello ? Can you hear me ?
- Yeah, I hear you.
- Hello ?
- How are you doin' ?
- I'm all right.
I just thought you should know
that the man has gone through.
Really ? Where ?
- He's-- Hello ?
- [ Static ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Beeping Quickly ]
[ Alarm Blaring ]
[ Beeping Stops ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Beeping Quickly,
Alarm Blaring ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Beeping Quickly,
Alarm Blaring ]
Aaah !
[ Panting ]
[ Grunting ]
I've seen worse.
[ Mikey ]
Oh, we're saved !
[ Chattering ]
[ Panting ]
Did you guys
stop for coffee ?
- It's a rescue team ! We're out !
- Where are the rest ?
- There is no rest !
- You're joking.
- Aw, come on, man !
- He can't be the only one.
There has to be some more !
- Are some more comin' or what ?
- Shit !
- Tell me this is not happening.
- Are we gonna get out ?
- Oh, man, this can't be right !
- Where's the team ?
He's it ?
You're it ?
- You are it ?
- Yeah, I'm it.
- You're the woman
with the walkie-talkie ?
- Yeah.
I thought I was clear.
No one was supposed to go in there.
- Excuse me, it was a lousy connection !
- How many are in there ?
- Bitch, he's talkin' to me !
- Who are you ?
My name's Latura.
Now, who's in there ?
There's one man in there,
and it's Roy Nord himself.
That shaft's unstable.
We gotta get him.
What you up to, man ?
I'm in charge !
If you want to be in charge, fine,
but that shaft's been compromised.
Anybody trying to get through,
that whole thing's gonna come down.
It's not exactly safe
in here, either !
We can't even breathe, man !
We gotta get outta here !
I know you've been through hell,
but I'm just asking you to be patient...
a little bit longer
and just trust me, okay ?
We'll go out
the same way you came in.
- That's not possible.
- If you made it, we can make it.
Just give us a chance, man !
The fans are giving us air.
Shut 'em down, we're dead.
That's it. That's a fact.
That won't work.
Neither will this.
- Roy's on top of it.
- Roy's gonna be under it.
Now let me do what
I gotta do, all right ?
I told you,
I'm in charge here !
I'm in charge !
You understand me ?
Let him go, now !
Hello ? Serena ?
Serena, Roy.
Actually, no.
We ran into a little problem on the way
to the airport. Yeah, listen.
Before we get cut off,
I'm gonna be leading some survivors
up through this ventilating shaft.
[ Nord Continues Indistinctly ]
Hold the plane at Teterboro
and, uh, I'll do press in Denver.
Tell 'em I'll have
some videotape.
No, no,
Jonno didn't make it.
Yeah.
Listen, I gotta go.
- Why don't you take this ?
- Just keep it.
- Take it, man !
- Try to get somebody on it.
The battery's dead !
What's the point ?
- Don't give me any trouble !
- Trouble, man ?
- We're just standing here, Steven.
- We don't know if it's safe.
- We can't just go in there.
- According to who ?
Get that outta
my face, please !
[ Arguments Continue ]
- Hey, where's he going ?
- Hey !
[ Shouting ]
Get back here !
Hey, you all heard
what the man said !
I heard Mr. Nord,
and I believe what he said !
- Women and children first.
- You done this before, man ?
She's a child,
and he needs that tape.
I don't know any more
than you know !
[ Shouting, Arguing ]
[ Tiles Shattering On Ground ]
Nord ?
Nord ? Oh, there you are.
Nord, you're a tough man to find.
My name is Latura, with E.M.S.
You gotta come down now.
That sounds like an order,
Mr. Latura.
You wanna give me an order ?
Call my "800" number.
No, no, seriously,
listen to me.
You and I are gonna
crawl outta here together,
so why don't you just come down
real slow-like, okay ?
There's no way through.
This shaft is like a house of cards.
If it collapses, they're gonna
be moppin' you up for a month.
It's not going to collapse.
How do I know that ?
You don't achieve what I have
without an instinct for
the torque of a given situation.
- [ Structure Groaning ]
- If you think I'm gonna start...
second-guessing myself
because of some gutless paramedic,
you'd better get
a reality check.
- Start sending those people in here.
- Nord !
- Stay there !
- Get me outta here !
I'm ready to go !
Stay ! That's it.
Don't move, please.
Nord, I hope you make it.
Get outta here !
I always make it, Mr. Latura.
Move it !
Keep going !
Faster ! Faster !
Don't look back !
Keep going !
- It's caving in !
- You played me, fool man !
Get down !
Aaah !
All the D.T.A.'s
are pulling double shifts.
I don't care if some guy's wife
is having a baby.
[ Indistinct Conversations ]
Quiet, everybody.
Everybody, quiet down.
Hey, shut up !
Shut up, everybody !
The mid-river just went down.
[ Barking ]
No, no, no, no, no !
[ Shouting ]
Mr. Latura !
- Easy, easy.
- I'm gonna die, right ?
Don't talk, don't talk.
Give me a scarf.
Please, I can't be goin' out
like this, man.
[ Gasping ]
I can't feel nothin'.
- Shh.
- I can't go out like this.
That's right.
Don't talk.
Tell my father I was helping people
down here, all right ?
I'll find him.
I'll tell your father
that you were a real hero.
[ Gasping ]
He won't--
He won't believe you.
[ Gasping, Gagging ]
[ Structure Groaning ]
Oh, Christ !
Oh !
Oh, God, this is too much.
- Hey, stop him !
- Get off me !
Let me go !
We're gonna drown !
No, you're not gonna drown !
Listen to me !
You're going the wrong way.
This tunnel runs downhill.
- The Manhattan end will be
the first place to fill up !
- He's right.
Come on. This way.
It's higher.
Excuse me. Excuse me !
I don't know what you know
and what you don't.
All I know is I've got a 14-year-old,
and her life means more than anything.
So I wanna be involved in any decisions.
Am I clear, Mr. Latura ?
- That's fair enough.
- Latura ? I read about you.
It was in the papers.
Some kind of scandal ?
- What kind of scandal ?
- Not the kind that matters down here.
I beg to differ, Mr. Latura.
Scandals matter to
Mrs. Trilling and myself.
Excuse me, ma'am,
what kind of scandal ?
He was chief
of the Emergency Medical Service.
Some people got killed, and he
was involved. That's all I remember.
What about it, Latura ?
Is that true ?
I asked you a question,
and I want to know the answer !
- Is it true ? Is that true ?
- Hey ! Hey !
Let's remember that
he came down here to help us,
so let's stop focusing on him
and focus on the problem !
She's right.
I'm sorry, Mr. Latura.
That was very rude.
Rude ? What is this, some kind
of goddamn New York country club ?
- Watch your mouth.
- You don't have a child down here !
And his past may have
a great deal to do with our future !
We're gonna drown down here,
and he's all we've got !
If I'm all you've got, why don't you
meet me halfway ? Is that fair enough ?
- Are we gonna drown ?
- No.
- What is your name ?
- Ashley.
Ashley, there's time to stop
the leak before it gets high
enough to worry about drowning.
- That's the good news.
- What's the bad news ?
This water's 38 degrees. What we
have to worry about is hypothermia.
- Hypo what ?
- Hypothermia.
Your body loses heat
and shuts down.
You feel like you're getting tired,
but you're really getting dead.
But that's not gonna happen
to us, because we're gonna
look out for each other.
We're gonna stay high and dry
right on this car dam over here,
so everybody
get on the car dam.
Get the hell outta this water.
Let's get outta the water.
Excuse me, could you
please help me with the dog ?
[ Cooper Whimpering ]
Thanks very much.
Here, boy.
Come here.
Okay, so here we are.
We're high and dry.
So what do you plan on doing ?
In a situation like this,
it's very important that everybody
knows exactly what is happening, okay ?
That last thing we need
is any more surprises, right ?
What I'm gonna try to do
is collapse a section of that tube...
to seal us off from the fire
and try to plug that leak.
- How do you plan to do that ?
- I have to use an explosive.
- Wait, please, let me explain !
- Another explosion ?
- That's your idea down here ?
No wonder you got people killed.
- Steven.
If anyone has a better idea,
now is the time to tell me.
You don't know what kind of damage
this substructure's already sustained,
so how do you know you can
contain it to one section ?
I don't know !
I don't know anything !
The only thing I know is we're
not gonna make it another hour
unless I shut this thing down !
That I do know.
What we need is someone
to go to the Manhattan end...
to see if we're making
any progress, okay ?
- [ Explosion ]
- How about you ?
No, you can't go, Daddy !
- I have a family.
I don't want to leave 'em.
- But you're so good at it.
[ George ]
All right, I'll go.
- I know the place best, anyway.
- You're hired.
She wants her bracelet back.
- What ?
- You're George, right ?
- Yeah.
- Grace said to tell you
she wants her bracelet back.
- She told you that ?
- Good luck, man.
She can't keep anything
to herself.
Listen, you were the one
handling that live wire ?
Uh, yeah, but that
was a very different thing.
I didn't know--
- I need your help right now.
- I appreciate that,
but I don't know anything--
Listen. It took a lot of guts
to do that. What's your name ?
- Uh, Madelyne.
- Madelyne, I need your help, okay ?
Look at this.
A stress hold design.
Better than we did
on Brooklyn-Queens.
-What do you think we're gonna do here ?
-Open it up.
Open it up ?
Let's open it up.
Okay. Still not getting
any trace of them, am I right ?
There was a meltdown on the
phone lines. Walkie-talkies
have been known to go dead.
Am I wrong in saying that
you don't know whether there's
anyone to transmit, period ?
- We saw people !
- Hours ago.
We're gonna break through from
the Manhattan side. That's the
consensus of the city engineers.
- Consensus my ass !
- Who's this ?
- That tunnel's being held up
by counterpoint pressure.
- I asked your name !
Why don't you forget what her name is ?
Listen to what she's saying to you.
You bring in heavy equipment,
cause a pressure shift,
the whole thing could implode.
- That's speculation.
- Maybe a little more time.
We are time poor.
That tunnel is an artery.
The city is bleeding.
Look, you try to redirect
half a million people
in and out of this city...
without that tunnel, you got a problem
you don't wanna think about.
Are you saying that because
of a traffic problem...
you're giving up
on possible survivors ?
Come on, man.
You gotta hold off on the drill.
Look, the city engineers
make the decisions.
You clean up the mess.
- [ Kit ] You're doing real good.
- [ Maddy ] Doin' real good ?
Try scared to death.
Maybe, but you're
dealing with it.
I think you should get someone else.
This is not one of my specialties.
Not a lot of people could handle
that cable the way you did.
- Well, it's not like it had a lot of--
- [ Both Gasp ]
- It's okay. It's okay.
- I can't. I can't.
I know. You have a choice.
It's like the first person
that ever ate a raw oyster.
- What are you talking about ?
- Well, think about it.
A person would have to be
starving to death to get
involved with a raw oyster.
- He probably had to eat it
or die. Stay with me.
- Uh-huh. I'm here.
It was slimy. It smelled. It looked
like something out of a bad chest cold.
So there had to be that moment
of truth before he sucked that
slider down. Staying with me ?
- I'm here.
- Think of that moment of truth.
Do I really need this ?
Do I want this in my life ?
But he had to eat.
So he dug down and found the guts
just like you did.
- Is that a compliment ?
- Yes. Come on. Where're you from ?
- La Porte, Indiana.
- And what do you do ?
I write. I try to get my plays produced.
Nobody goes to the theater anymore.
- And you were going home ?
- Yeah. I was.
So, uh-- So tell me something,
all right ? For real.
I probably won't be able to take it,
but are we gonna get out of here ?
Madelyne, I wouldn't be down here
if I didn't think so. I swear.
- Promise ?
- I promise. Now trust me. Come on.
So, this explosion
that we're setting could cause
the whole thing to cave in, right ?
- It could happen.
- It's better than a blowout.
A blowout ?
I really hate the way that sounds.
- You okay ?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Go back to "blowout."
Please explain.
If the water level was higher,
the pressure would build and
the air would blow to the top.
- Like a cork ? A geyser ?
- It happened to a couple of guys
digging the Baltimore Tunnel.
- And what happened to them ?
They died, right ?
- Help me open this pack.
One made it.
Help me out.
All right, keep a tight grip.
We're gonna make it.
[ Metal Clanging ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Panting ]
[ Blows On Hand ]
[ Grunts ]
- [ Metal Clanging ]
- [ Screams ]
[ Screaming ]
Kit !
[ Gasps Loudly, Grunts ]
[ Panting ]
- You're insane !
- Gimme that, Madelyne.
We're hot ! Go !
[ Panting ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Screams ]
Hey, what are you doing ?
Go on. It's snagged !
[ Terrified Chattering ]
Stay in there.
- What about you ?
- The hell with me ! Go !
Go ! The hell with me.
[ Grunts ]
- [ Explosion ]
- [ Gasps ]
[ Gasps, Panting ]
[ Panting Continues ]
Aaah !
[ Screaming ]
[ Mikey ]
Yes ! He did it !
[ All Cheering ]
[ Panting ]
You okay ?
We gotta stop asking
each other that.
[ People Continue Cheering ]
[ Firemen Chattering ]
- What do you got ? How big ?
- Three-point-three.
That's a hell of a bang, sir.
- [ Crewman #1 ] Three-bar !
- [ Foreman ] Look out below !
We're coming down !
[ Helicopter Blades Whirring ]
[ Fireman ] Make more room !
We gotta back up the ladder !
[ George ]
Hey ! I heard machines !
I think they're going to try
to dig us out from the Manhattan end !
- No !
- What ? They're digging.
What's wrong ?
The digging can shift pressure and bring
the place down. They're not thinking.
- Or maybe they are
and they think we're dead.
- Digging at the Manhattan end !
Latura ! They're coming !
[ Excited Shouting ]
[ Screaming ]
Oh, shit.
No !
George !
- Hold on, big man ! Hold on !
- I can't-- I can't move.
- Can you feel your body ?
George, can you feel your body ?
- I can't move.
- I can't feel my body.
- Okay, hold on, big man ! Hold on !
[ Panting ]
Am I okay ? Am--
Am... I... okay ?
Oh, God.
- [ Grunting ]
- Am I okay ?
[ Disgusted Scream ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Spits ] It'll keep you alive.
Breathe through this, George.
Breathe, breathe. Please. Come on.
Steady breath ! Breathe !
Don't let it beat you !
Come on, George ! Breathe !
In and out ! In !
Come on, George ! Come on.
- Breathe !
- [ Coughing ]
Breathe, breathe, please.
Leverage ! We need leverage !
Get that truck up !
[ Panting ]
Come on.
Oh, George.
[ Ashley ]
Come on, come on.
We're coming.
- All right, got it ? Take it.
- I'll take it.
- We're gonna make it.
- Thank you.
- Come on. Move, move, move !
- [ Ashley ] We got him !
Take that !
- All right, lift, lift, lift, lift !
- We're with you.
- We're right here.
- We're with you, George.
- [ Eleanor ]
Breathe as strong as you can.
- That's it, you got it !
- George can't hear
'cause the water's going !
- [ Grunting ]
Come on, George.
Stay with us, George. Stay with us.
- Oh, my God. He's going under.
- [ Grunts ]
[ Vincent ]
Keep them coming !
- He's going under !
- Get it off him !
- All right !
- [ Grunts ]
- Okay, let me know when.
- Okay !
One, two, three !
[ Both Straining ]
- We got him !
- He's out.
Okay, come on.
Get him out of the water.
Hold his head. Don't let his head go !
- Get the planks outta there !
- Keep it moving. Come on !
- Come on ! Come on !
- Here it comes.
[ Mikey ]
We got it.
Bring it down. Come on !
[ Sarah ]
Get over here !
Everybody get ready to lift him
on the count of three. Ready ?
All right, altogether.
One, two, three !
- You got him ?
- Keep moving so we don't--
- We need somebody up here !
- Here we go now, all right ?
- [ Shouting Indistinctly ]
- [ Mikey ] Come on. Let's go.
- Let's go. It's freezing.
- You're doing great.
Together we can do it.
We can do anything.
You're doing great. Ready ?
All right,
one, two, three. Lift !
[ Reporters All Chattering At Once ]
I hope they're alive. Hang on.
We're doing the best we can.
I don't know. I don't know !
Now, please.
- Do you have any survivors ?
- I can't answer that.
- Are you going to guard the place ?
- Is it completely collapsed ?
Are there any survivors ?
I said that's it !
That's it !
[ Helicopter Blades Whirring ]
[ Reporters Continue Chattering ]
Why George ?
Why not some piece of trash ?
Why-- Why is it always
the good people ?
I can't answer that. You just hope--
I mean, you just gotta believe it.
I think some people
are gonna make it out of there.
And George is gonna be one.
- [ Sighs ]
- Well, yeah, we gotta think that.
Yeah... we do.
[ Boat Horn Honking ]
[ People Chattering ]
[ Steven ]
George, I'd give you my shirt,
but I don't think it'd do much good.
[ Eleanor ] George, we'd give you
the shirt off our backs.
- It'll be all right.
Keep calm. We're here with you.
- How'd you get fired ?
[ Grunts ] It's a long story.
I wouldn't worry about it.
[ Latonya ] Stay awake now.
Stay with us.
She said she read
you got people killed.
She's right.
Did she mention it was
a building collapse in the South Bronx ?
- No, she said--
- And that we were the
first ones on the scene ?
No.
And some of the guys said, "Forget it.
They're probably dead anyway" ?
Or read the part where I said,
"if we were goin' in--"
Or mention that
I was wrong ? Hmm ?
That a gas main blew on the way out
and three men died ?
My friend's brother
was one of them ?
Did she mention the press,
the inquiry, the funerals ?
You're a writer, you can
fill out the rest, can't you ?
So you never had
a way out of here, did you ?
No.
[ Air Hissing, Water Bubbling ]
- What's that ? What's the noise ?
- What's going on ?
[ Eleanor ] What does that mean,
Mr. Latura ? What does that mean ?
[ Steven ] Kit, what's going on ?
What's happening here ?
[ Mikey ] The water wasn't
that high last time I looked.
- The water must be coming
back in from somewhere !
- I thought you stopped it.
I slowed it down.
Nothing can stop it.
So what you're saying is nothing
can save us. You asked us to
trust you. We did. For what ?
- To die a slow death in here ?
- [ Eleanor ] Are there no options ?
- There's always a chance.
- [ Sarah ] How can you lie like that ?
- Since you're already in hell,
I guess it's not a problem.
- [ Roger ] Just let him talk !
We've heard enough talking.
We don't need any more speeches.
[ Vincent ] That's bullshit !
She's speaking for herself, Kit.
- [ Eleanor ] We're still alive, Sarah.
- [ Latonya ] It ain't over !
Very over ! You wanna kid
yourself. Go ahead, do it.
False hope and now no hope !
You've given us both.
Thanks for nothing.
Thanks for nothing !
- Sarah. Sarah.
- I can't stand this shit.
[ Sobbing ]
- What's plan "B", Kit ?
- There's no plan.
- We're with you !
- We can try taking down
another section.
- We could build another dam
if we all pitched in.
- We can beat it.
I could check the Manhattan end.
I think I could do it. Let me try, Kit !
Can you get us outta here ?
I'm sorry about what my mom said.
Just please, just try
and get us out of here ! Please !
[ Crying ]
[ Panting ]
[ Cooper Whining ]
- I need your help, George.
- Yeah ?
- The bunk rooms off the tunnels,
is there a way in ?
- I don't know.
George, I know you're hurt,
but think.
Bassett said the sandhogs had bunk rooms
down here for long shifts. Think.
Maybe there's a trapdoor,
a hatch, a ladder, something.
- Uh, there's a booth.
- Booth ? Where ?
Uh, booth three.
At the New Jersey end.
Booth three.
Steven, keep everybody together
until I get back. George ?
- Yeah ?
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
- [ Dives Into Water ]
[ Metal Banging ]
[ Squeaking ]
[ Panting ]
[ Blowing On Hands ]
[ Sneezes, Grunts ]
[ Panting ]
Come on. You stay with us.
Did you ever have a dog ?
My mom's liked everything in the world
'cept two things: dogs and me.
Well, she was probably bit once.
I know I was.
- [ Vincent ]
So, Ashley, where do you live ?
- [ Ashley ] We're from Maryland.
- Maryland. Maryland's nice.
- Yeah.
Well, listen, if we don't die
in here, I was wondering if
maybe I could give you a call.
- [ Chuckles ]
- [ Mikey ] He thinks
he's being attacked now.
- Exactly.
- Uh-huh.
- Why don't you go ahead and pet him.
- We've had him for ten years.
- That's a long time.
- Yeah, it is.
Do you have any children ?
Our son Jonathan.
He went trekking in Nepal.
He, uh... caught some kind of a fever.
Nothing could be done, they said.
We, uh-- We lost him.
- Oh, I'm so sorry. I didn't--
- Oh, no, no.
- No, no.
- I didn't--
Ever since Jonathan died,
Cooper's all we've had left.
I guess I spoil him.
[ Chuckles ] You understand ?
- Yeah.
- [ Water Sloshing ]
- [ Panting ]
- [ Ashley ] Kit ! It's Kit !
Everybody, Kit !
[ Shivering ]
I found some dry ground.
There's always a chance.
[ Panting Continues ]
Come on. Let's move.
[ Ashley ]
Why don't we take George now ?
[ Steven ] We're gonna check
out booth three, then go back
and get him. Keep moving !
Okay.
- George.
- Hi.
My neck's broken, isn't it ?
You-- You find the room ?
Yeah, it's, um-- it's through
this underwater passage.
It's very difficult. I-- I think that
with a little bit of luck we could--
Christ, I don't know what to think.
I do. You just
have to leave me.
- No, no, that's dumb. That's stupid.
- Yeah.
- We can make it.
- Not with a broken neck.
Yes, George. I just need
some time to figure it out.
Really, I just need some time.
Hey, take the bracelet for me.
Please. It's in my pocket.
My right pocket.
- George, don't quit on me.
- Take it.
- Don't quit on me.
- Take it, please.
- No.
- Take it !
Please.
- Please, give me that--
give me that much respect.
- [ Opens Pocket ]
Jesus, there's just
so much I wish I'd done.
I never had me a nice car.
Never had any kids.
I finally meet a woman I love,
I didn't even get the chance
to tell her that I love her.
- You think she-- she knows ?
- Yeah.
- You think so ?
- She knows. I'm sure she does.
That's good.
Get them to daylight.
Don't let them die
in this place ? Hear ?
Tell them I'm gone.
You've done all you could do.
You know it... and I know it.
I'm very sorry.
I-- I love you, Grace.
[ Shuddering ]
I'm sorry.
[ Shuddering Continues ]
- [ Loud Creaking ]
- What does that mean ?
I don't know, Ellie.
The structure's shifting.
What about George ?
George didn't make it.
- Huh ?
- [ Both Crying ]
[ Mutters ]
Don't.
I know everybody's freezing, but we
have to make a short swim underwater.
Underwater ? Well, I'm not
so sure I can do this.
Look, if I can do it,
you can do it.
Everybody take three deep breaths...
and go. We can do this.
- Come on, baby. Come on.
- [ Gasps ] I can't !
I can't do this ! I can't.
- One, two, three.
- [ Breathing Quickly, Gasps ]
[ Gasping ]
And go. Come on.
- [ Gasping ]
- Come on. Keep going.
Get up there.
...three !
[ Gasping, Shivering ]
- [ Panting, Gasps ]
- I'm right behind you, Eleanor.
Yes ! Go !
[ Straining ]
[ Grunting ]
Here we go, boy.
Go, boy.
[ Whimpering ]
[ Coughing ]
Quick, get her out of the water.
Help her out. Help her out.
- [ Coughing ]
- [ Kit ] Go ahead.
[ Kit Mutters ]
[ Panting ]
All right,
everybody stay together.
All right, everybody stay
together. Use each other's
body heat. Fight the cold.
Stay warm.
Stay in groups.
- Don't stay alone.
Okay ? Stay in groups.
- Okay.
- What do we do now, Kit ?
- We don't do nothing.
We just sit here and wait
and pray they get here.
[ Vincent ]
Wait ? Wait ? That's it ?
[ Shivering ] There's--
There's nothing we can do ?
You did what you could.
- [ Shivering ]
- You did great. You did great.
- [ Kisses Head ]
- You gotta fight it.
- Fight the cold.
- I'm trying.
Just fight it.
[ All Shivering ]
Where's Cooper ?
[ Shouts ] Where's Cooper ?
It broke.
I couldn't hold him.
- [ Sobbing ] Oh, my God !
- My God, I tried. I tried.
- Oh, my God ! I can't lose him !
- Ellie. Ellie ! No.
- No.
- It was Jonathan's dog.
Look, look, Eleanor.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
We can't bring them back.
They're both gone.
- We can't change that.
- [ Shuddering ]
We've gotta...
help each other let them go.
[ Crying Continues ]
[ Shivering ]
Don't let's... fight.
[ Shuddering ]
Hold me.
[ Crying Continues ]
[ Metal Screeching Loudly ]
- [ Screams ]
- [ Rumbling ]
Jesus ! They're gonna
save us to death.
Oh, my God !
[ Screams ]
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
- Get back. Get back.
[ Vincent ]
Don't let those things touch you !
Move away ! Move away !
Latonya !
- [ Steven ] Come on, Sarah.
- [ Sarah ] I'm not leaving.
Move, move, move, move !
[ Screaming ]
- Come on. Sarah.
- [ Vincent ] Listen !
I don't wanna die like this !
[ Screaming ] Oh, God !
It's okay, Latonya.
I'm coming.
I'm coming, Latonya.
Hold on.
[ Latonya ]
I don't wanna die like this !
[ Screaming ]
- I hate 'em !
- All right, here I come.
- I don't wanna go like this !
- Hang on. I'm coming.
I'm coming. I'm here.
They can't hurt you, okay ?
They're just shit with feet.
Okay ? Shit with feet.
Can you say that ?
- [ Rats Squeaking ]
- Don't look down.
- Watch out !
- All right ! All right !
[ Vincent ]
Keep 'em away from your feet !
[ Maddy ]
Shit with feet, baby.
They know a way out.
[ Rats Squeaking ]
Steven, help me get this thing
off the wall ! Get it off !
There's a room !
There's another room !
[ Rumbling ]
No, no ! Not now !
Gimme some tools ! Anything !
Find anything you can !
Come on !
[ Steven ] Let's try
to pop these rivets.
- Roger !
- [ Steven ] Sarah, over there !
Roge-- Roger !
I thought she was resting.
I'm sorry.
[ Metal Creaking ]
Roger, we gotta
get out of here.
There's no way she wanted
you to die down here too.
Roger, she wants you to live.
I'm not gonna leave her !
Okay. Okay.
If you're staying,
I'm staying.
I'm not leaving anybody
behind again.
[ Chattering, Indistinct Shouts ]
- Roger, come on !
- Let's go. Come on.
[ Steven ]
We're moving out. Out !
Come on. Get up !
We're not leaving you. We gotta go.
-Come on. Get up. We gotta go.
-[ Steven ] The water's gettin' higher !
Come on, come on !
- [ Wood Creaking ]
- I see 'em !
Right there, the rats !
A-A-At the top of the stairs.
Kit, they're going up
the stairs. There's somethin'
at the top of the stairs !
[ Grunts ]
[ Light Bangs Floor ]
[ Rumbling ]
Oh, no !
[ All Screaming ]
Get up. Come on.
Come on, Madelyne, up.
Get up !
All right, go, go, go !
Move it ! Up the stairs !
Up the stairs ! Go !
- [ Steven ] Keep going !
- [ Rumbling ]
Kit ! I got you !
- Hold on !
- [ Grunting ]
All right. Go !
- [ Ashley ] Come on. Let's move !
- [ Mikey ] Let's go !
Kit, I've got a way out !
I found a way out ! Come on, everybody !
- It looks like some kind
of unfinished sewer system.
- [ Cooper Barking ]
- [ Latonya ] Oh, my God !
It's the lady's dog !
- [ Roger ] Cooper !
- No, no, no. Forget it.
- Cooper !
- [ Vincent ] It's just a stupid dog.
- [ Mikey ] Shut up, Vincent !
- [ Vincent ] It's just a dog !
- [ Whimpers ]
- [ Roger ] Let me get him !
- There's a way out up here !
Will you forget it !
- [ Whimpering ]
- [ Vincent ] Leave the stupid dog.
- [ Mikey ] Shut the hell up, Vincent !
- [ Sighs ]
[ Sarah ]
Oh, no.
I don't believe it !
- [ All Shouting ]
- Come on.
[ Mikey ]
Come on, Cooper !
- [ Rumbling ]
- Oh, shit !
[ Wood Creaking Loudly ]
- [ All Scream ]
- Kit ! Kit ! Kit !
- Keep going !
- [ Maddy ] Not without you !
- Forget about me ! There's no time !
- No, we'll make time !
- Steven, do something.
- [ Steven ] Yeah, yeah.
- Pull it !
- Damn !
[ Mikey ]
Roger, there's nothing to throw.
We can't find anything !
- [ Mikey ] Hold on !
- This place is comin' apart !
- You wouldn't leave us !
- I would leave you !
I left George !
I left him to die ! Get out !
- Take this. Here.
- Come on, come on.
- No, no, no ! Don't do it !
- [ Steven ] Reach for it.
- Madelyne, no. No.
- [ Rumbling ]
[ Screaming ]
- [ All Screaming ]
- It's collapsing !
Oh, my God !
- Why didn't you leave ?
What the hell did you do ?
- Damn !
- [ Crying ]
- [ Steven ] Get a hold of something !
Go, go, Steven !
You gotta keep going !
What the hell are you talking about ?
You can't leave us !
- [ Kit ] They gotta leave !
- Mikey, there's gotta be another way !
- [ Mikey ] We can't find anything.
- Sweetheart, look for some--
- There must be something else !
- [ Grunting ]
[ Panting,
Mutters Indistinctly ]
- [ Straining ]
- [ Steven ] Can you make it ?
[ Gasps ]
[ Loud Grunts ]
There's no way out !
You can't reach us !
That's home up there !
[ Screams ]
- [ Rumbling ]
- [ Mikey ] No !
[ Latonya ]
What do we do ?
[ Panting ]
Ashley, flashlight ! Here !
- No.
- [ Mikey ] Ah, man, no.
Kit !
No, Steven !
Don't leave me !
- Go ! You heard me !
Go ! Everybody, out !
- [ Maddy Screaming ]
We gotta go !
I didn't leave you, Mikey !
I'll die !
[ Sobbing ]
- [ Mikey Crying ]
- Go, go ! Watch your head !
[ Sobbing Continues ]
Oh, God !
- Go ! Come on. Keep going !
- [ Rumbling ]
Go, go, go, go, go !
Nooo.
[ Grunting ]
[ Panting ] We're not gonna
get out of here, are we ?
Come on.
Kit, I can't.
[ Panting ]
What's that ?
Fuses. We've gotta go back
to where we started.
No. No, Kit, it's too far.
No, no. Anything I can do,
you can do. Here, hold this.
- [ Gasping ]
- [ Gasps Loudly ]
We-- We gotta try it !
[ Panting ]
What ?
A blowout.
- A blow-- A blowout ?
- We gotta do it ! Come on !
We're gonna try a blowout.
Come on.
Where... are we... going ?
Gotta get up to the ceiling
and blast out the mud.
If it works, the pressure
will take us right to the top.
Why don't you leave your car here
and I'll drive you home.
[ Banging ]
[ People Shouting ]
- [ Shouting Continues ]
- Oh, my God.
[ Groaning ]
- I got you, girl. I got you.
- [ Crying ]
- Easy. Easy. Take it easy.
- [ Groans ]
Easy. Easy.
Okay, come on.
- [ Panting ]
- [ Paramedic ] Take it easy now.
- You're all right.
- Easy, easy.
- Roger, we did it !
Come on. We made it.
- Okay.
[ Shivering ]
Come on. It's okay.
Good dog.
[ Groans ]
Easy. All right.
Come on. We got you.
We got you.
Okay. All right, all right.
That's everybody.
Everybody's out.
[ Bassett ] Are you sure
there's nobody else down there ?
[ Paramedic ]
Hole's fillin' up with water.
Everybody's out.
- Nobody else ?
- Leave me alone.
I'm okay. I'm all right.
- I'm okay.
- No, Daddy, it's okay.
It's okay.
We're okay.
[ Crying ]
[ Water Sloshing ]
[ Panting ]
[ Grunts ]
Come on. Come on.
- [ Groaning ]
- Go ahead.
[ Panting ] I'm gonna sit.
I'm gonna sit... over here.
- I don't even care. I feel so tired.
- You gotta fight it.
I never thought
I'd end up like this.
You weren't supposed to.
I always...
thought I'd die old.
[ Panting ]
[ Metal Creaking Loudly ]
Keep trying, you piece of shit !
Keep trying !
How many chances do you need ?
You killed everybody else,
but you know what ?
You should've killed me !
'Cause I found your heart !
I found your heart,
and I'll blow it out of your body !
[ Panting ]
[ Grunts ]
We gotta go.
Give me your arm, Madelyne.
[ Panting ] You never...
would have left us... would you ?
[ Whispering ]
No. No.
[ Straining ]
[ Gasping ]
Kit.
[ Coughs ]
[ Panting ]
[ Boat Horn Honking ]
- All right, easy. Easy. Easy.
- Slide it over.
Clear a path.
Come on. Easy.
- We have a wheelchair for you, ma'am.
- It's all right. I'm gonna walk.
[ Sighs ]
Hey. All right.
You're doin' fine.
Stop. Stop, stop, stop.
[ Panting ]
Grace.
[ Frank ] All right, come on.
Let's get him out of here.
Come on. Let's go.
[ Crowd Cheering, Shouting ]
Since we're both going to the hospital,
I wanna ride with you.
Don't you have
something better to do ?
Well, considering I'm homeless
and broke and carless...
and I'm not lookin' my best,
I think I'll ride with you.
- One condition.
- What's that ?
We gotta take the bridge.
[ Woman ]
# Like the well #
# Becomes a spring #
# Like the light #
# That you bring #
# To the skies
that were empty #
# And gray #
# Mm-hmm #
[ Woman, Man Together ]
# Just your breath #
# In the night #
# Can make it all right #
# When you sigh
as you're drifting away #
- # Ooo #
- # Oh, baby #
# All that is simple and good
lives in the places you stood #
# The things that are pure
and true #
# Paint a picture of you #
# And you are all
I can think of #
# Whenever there is love #
# Ooo #
- # Like a brief desert rain #
- # Like #
# Desert rain #
# Like the air that remains #
# Making everything suddenly new #
- # Oh, baby #
# And like #
# The light in your eyes #
- # Like the light in your eyes #
- # As if you and I #
# Found a world that was only for two #
- # Oh, tell me, baby #
- # Ooh #
# All that is simple and good
lives in the places you stood #
# The things that are pure and true #
# Paint a picture of you #
# And you are all I can think of #
# Whenever there is love #
# Ooo-oooh #
- # if you are lost I will find you #
- # I'll find you #
- # No matter where you go #
- # Ooh #
# if you fall I'm here behind you #
# All that is simple and good
lives in the places you stood #
# The things that are pure and true #
# Paint a picture of you #
# And you are all I can think of #
- # Whenever there is love #
- # Ooo #
- # Whenever #
- # Baby #
- # Whenever there is love #
- # Whenever, whenever #
# Whenever there is love #
- # Whenever there is love #
# [ Woman, Man Harmonizing ]
# Whenever there is #
- # Love #
- # Whenever, whenever #
# There is love #
# Ooo #
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org