Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Eat me, asshole.
Careful, now.
Come on, bird. Come on.
Please, baby.
Dickhead.
See Daddy smiling?
Come on.
Bring your feathery ass here. Come on.
-Explosion caused that?
-No.
Nothing in here could've blown
with enough force to move that damn sub.
Whatever. It's junk.
We could all just dive in
and see who makes it to the top.
Isn't that the old Aquatica spirit, Dr. Susie?
Just dive in.
You could go first, to lead by example.
He was my best friend, Janice.
I'm not going in the water.
-No way, man! The sharks are in there.
-Listen!
We put these on. They help
fight hypothermia. That's a start.
And unless someone's got a better idea...
...we're going to have to swim out of here.
This isn't happening.
I'm not Daniel when he faced the lion!
So I appreciate the irony, Lord!
"Cook dies in his own oven!"
But I've got other plans!
You ate my bird.
Was that the surface?
No, the vibrations are too deep.
That was from inside.
I wouldn't get that close.
Just a suggestion.
Water's murky. We might make it.
No way! No, we won't!
It's 230 feet...
...from the lagoon floor
to the lagoon surface!
The average human swims
two feet per second.
The average shark swims
50 feet per second.
There's no way I'm getting into that pool!
What we have here is
your basic maintenance ladder.
This leads up to the surface.
I love you, Scoggs. I really do!
Why do I feel a "but" coming on?
But we don't know what shape
the surface level is in.
The shaft is air-locked.
But if the explosion breached the shaft
at surface level...
...we won't have enough pressure
to stabilize the wet pool.
If the pool isn't stabilized,
there's tons of ocean dying to get in.
You'll bring the whole facility down.
We're better off with the sharks.
You want to swim with your fishes?
Go ahead!
I'm opening this door
and climbing out of here!
-The hell you are!
-I don't work for you anymore!
-I don't have to take orders!
-Enough!
That's enough now, from all of you!
You think water's fast?
You should see ice.
It moves like it has a mind.
Like it knows it killed the world once.
It got a taste for murder.
When the avalanche came...
...it took us a week to climb out.
And somewhere we lost hope.
I don't know when we turned
on each other.
I just know...
...that seven of us survived the slide...
...and only five made it out.
Now, we took an oath
that I'm breaking now.
Swore that we'd say it was the snow
that killed the other two.
But it wasn't.
Nature can be lethal.
But it doesn't hold a candle to man.
You've seen how bad things can get
and how quick they can get that way.
Well, they can get a whole lot worse.
So we're not going to fight anymore!
We're going to pull together
and find a way to get out of here!
First, we're going to seal off this pool!
Oh, my God.
It just ate him.
It just ate him. Christ!
I'm not moving.
I'm not moving. Someone will come.
They'll come and they'll get us,
and we'll be fine.
No. I'm not moving.
Listen, Tom, what is the precise
structural failure limit for Aquatica?
3,200 tons.
What happens when we get more
than 3,200 tons of water in this rig?
The support struts go first.
Their tolerance is about seven tons.
They'll crack like toothpicks.
The walls will buckle. They can't handle
more than 10 tons of pressure.
You want to be here for that?
Hell, no.
The moment of truth. Again.
Go! Go! Go!
I got you.
It's burning!
The elevator's blocking the top.
If we make it to Level 1,
we can take the stairs out.
Let's get out of here!
Go! Go!
What are you doing?
If they break through,
water will bring them right to us.
Level 2 is only partially flooded.
If I can get that door open...
...the water will run off there,
buy us some time.
Big, real big.
-What's that?
-The size of your brass balls.
Be careful.
Go!
Jan, stay there!
Get me out of here, Carter!
I don't want to die!
Grab my hand! Come on!
I can't!
I can't reach!
-Take it!
-I can't reach!
Can you reach that door above you?
It's too high.
Sharks probably flooded that level too.
Good thing you came to this side.
The other side's underwater.
-We didn't exactly plan it.
-Yeah, it wasn't planned.
Are you all that made it?
We did it.
We're on Level 1.
We can take the stairs to the surface.
The stairs are flooded. Trust me, I know.
Are you sure?
Give us a goddamn break, can't You?
He always answers.
Sometimes, the answer you get
isn't the answer you want.
We're 60 feet from the surface.
There's an emergency hatch
on this level, right?
This level has bilge pumps on it
for storm runoff.
If we re-route the emergency generators,
we could drain a stairway.
You sure?
Who you going to trust?
-You.
-That's right.
You trust me.
We had poker here tomorrow night.
She'd always draw to the inside straight
when she could've stuck with a pair.
Big dreams.
Even in death: Standards.
Jan was a healthy girl.
Something in here has to run on batteries.
-Nice.
-Where would a girl keep her...
...thing?
What's the matter with you?
My skin's starting to hemorrhage.
The sharks smell the blood.
This'll coat it with oil.
Look, Carter, what you said down there...
...maybe you were right.
Everything I've done...
...I don't think I could've done it
without you.
I know, Susan. That's the problem.
Four a.m.
I know.
One night feels like a whole week.
Relativity.
What do you mean?
Einstein's theory of relativity.
Grab hold of a hot pan,
a second can seem like an hour.
Put your hands on a hot woman...
...an hour can seem like a second.
It's all relative.
I spent four years at Cal Tech. That's
the best physics explanation I've heard.
It works.
You stay with the doc.
Me and Scoggs are going to try
to get to the wet lab...
...drain that stairwell.
-Preach?
-What?
Would you zip me up, please?
We got one, there's two sharks left...
...and you and the doc are doing
a little bathroom love.
They got a pill for what's wrong with you?
I need to get some things
from my quarters. Research data.
The tests, they worked.
So much death around us,
to risk any more life for some numbers....
Without that data, everyone dying
isn't just tragic, it's useless.
Death is always useless, Doctor.
This is it.
Stay here. I'll be back before you know it.
What's going on?
What the hell's going on? What is that?
It's okay!
-What is that?
-We're all right!
-What the fuck?
-It's okay.
I thought you were coming back for me.
One of your monitors is blocking the panel.
You want to help me move it?
I say we do everything right together.
Right together.
Hello.
My name is Sherman Dudley...
...and if this message finds you,
I did not survive, so this is my legacy.
I have loved the pulpit
and I have loved the bottle.
I did my best to be a good husband,
a f ather.
I came up wanting.
So what do I have to say to you?
What mark do I have to leave behind?
We'll begin with the perfect omelet,
made with two eggs, not three.
Amateurs often add milk for density.
This is a mistake.
Come on!
I got you. Come on.
Damn you, Scoggs.
Where's Susan?
I'm done.
Brothers never make it out
of situations like this. Not ever!
Did you do it?
Where's Scoggins?
I hate to interrupt this moment
of burgeoning intimacy...
...but can we get the fuck out of here?
-Is this the only way?
-Exits are flooded.
Whole place is sinking.
It's this way or no way at all.
You can bring on the good news
anytime now.
Sharks are attracted to churning water,
bright colors.
These extinguishers will be a distraction.
What about us?
The vest'll bring you up too fast.
Your lungs'll pop like a balloon.
You weren't the sunny kid in your class.
I never went to class.
How far to the surface? Sixty feet?
There's nothing to it.
Exhale on the way up,
and get the hell out of the water.
I got to equalize the pressure
before we blow the air lock.
I got to let the room fill up with water.
It'll only take a few seconds.
You ready?
No.
Not in the least.
"Though I walk through the valley
of the shadow of death...
"...I shall fear no evil...
"...for Thou art with me...
"...Thy rod and Thy staff, they comfort me.
"Surely goodness and mercy shall
follow me all the days of my life... "
...because I carry a big stick...
...and I'm the meanest motherfucker
in the valley.
Two sharks down, Lord.
One demon fish to go.
Can I get an "amen"?
Amen!
-I can't hear you!
-Amen!
Give me an "amen"!
-Stay with us, Lord!
-Amen.
Okay, hold on three! Ready?
One! Two! Three!
Swim!
Oh, my God!
It's the devil, you know.
He'll be okay if we can get out of here.
Son of a bitch.
What?
Those fences are titanium underneath,
but on top, they're just plain steel.
They've been herding us,
pushing us where they want.
Using us to flood the facility.
Oh, my God.
That's the answer to the riddle.
Because that's what
an 8,000-pound mako thinks about.
About freedom.
About the deep blue sea.
We have to kill her.
That's the first real smart thing
you've said all day.
Here we go.
Let's go.
We ought to get 2.5 sticks of dynamite
out of these flares.
From up here, you ought to be able
to see me spear it.
When I do, you take this end of this cable...
...hook it up to the positive side
of the boat battery.
And boom!
Damn! I can't get her!
She's too far away!
I know how to get her.
How?
Bait.
She may be the smartest animal
in the world...
...but she's still just an animal.
Come to Mama.
No!
Susan, don't!
Get out of the water!
All right, Lord....
Shoot it, Preach!
This is for Scoggins.
Shoot it!
Damn!
Blow it, Preach! Blow it!
The battery!
Blow it!
Do it!
Bring me some sushi!
Forty-five-foot shark...
...and you hit me.
Nice.
Could've been worse.
I could've let him eat your ass.
Carter, we're sinking, right?
Yeah.
Let me ask you something.
Are you sure it was just three sharks?
Yeah.
That's more like it.
Here comes the next shift.
Let me tell you, man...
...I quit this job.
Take me back to the ghetto.
Amen.
English subtitles conformed by
SOFTITLER
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org