Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Tobe!
- What?
- Where are you going?
- Out.
- Can I come?
I'd rather be alone.
Let me come!
- You don't even know where I'm going.
- So what.
Okay.
But don't be a pain.
You're lousy at spitting!
Cigarettes help.
Try.
But don't inhale,
and keep the smoke in your mouth.
Yeah, like that...
Hold it...
Enough, breathe out.
See?
Then he gets a bolt,
it was pretty big one...
- And sticks his hand out the fence...
- Wade's here!
Hold on.
Anyway, the fool sticks his hand out
and drops it down, can you imagine?
He smashed the windshield
of a passing car!
Hello!
- Anyone home?
- Hold on.
- Ever heard of knocking?
- I'll knock when you get a job.
Talk to you later.
Get dinner for you and Lonnie,
I'm going out.
I can't, April's on her way,
I gotta get ready!
She can wait.
I was with Lonnie all day,
I wanna go out.
15 minutes isn't a tragedy.
Buy chicken for him
and you keep the change.
- Can you manage alone?
- Sure.
- Come on, give me them!
- Take 'em!
- What was that?
- Nothing, the cat.
Really?
Can I?
I told you a million times
not to sleep in Tobe's room,
why don't...
you sleep in your room
with the light on?
I thought someone was outside.
If you heard noises,
why didn't you call me?
You don't like being bothered.
Not if it's for a shadow.
- Coming!
- You're a knockout!
- You're going to school like that?
- It's vacation.
Too many vacations,
that's why kids are ignorant.
- Where are you going?
- To the beach.
Wait!
- What now?
- Don't be late again.
Okay.
Where's your shirt?
She got a boob job at 18?
- That's sickening.
- No, I think she looks better.
- She must feel better too.
- Right, all the boys stare at her.
I say she's a stuck-up slut.
Yeah, she's a skank!
- Look, the tired pistolero!
- Does he work here?
Check out his hat,
he's a real cowboy.
What a riot!
- Here he comes.
- It's about time!
- Hilarious!
- What a weirdo!
Be quiet!
- Howdy.
- Howdy!
What'll it be?
Fill it up with unleaded, Tex.
My pleasure.
- He said "howdy"...
- Oh my gosh, he's pathetic.
Knock it off, Jeremy.
Tex, can you check the oil?
Sure thing,
I'll clean your windows too.
- Great, a real cowboy.
- Full service.
We promise a certain quality here,
so I have to deliver.
- Are you for real?
- What?
Are you for real?
I think so.
Wanna touch?
Yeah!
He's real!
- Can you believe it!
- In the flesh...
- You touched the cowboy.
- How cool!
How's the oil?
Fine.
The belt's a bit worn though.
Going far?
- Just to the beach.
- Really?
Lucky you, I've never been.
How long have you been here?
Not long.
Why don't you go?
It only takes an hour.
I can't, I don't have a car.
How come?
How come I don't have a car?
I don't like 'em...
they make us lazy.
Funny, you don't like cars
but you work here.
It's a job like any other,
I need it to get by.
So what about this belt?
It'll hold up.
Have fun.
Hey...
Wanna come?
To the beach with you?
Nice idea.
But maybe you're busy.
Dunno, I'll go ask.
Wait here.
Can we go?
I invited Tex to come with us.
- I can't believe it!
- Are you nuts?
- What are you thinking?
- Maybe he's a psychopath.
- Is he coming or not?
- I'm waiting for my change still.
Get lost!
Is the offer still available?
Sure.
You got the day off?
- More or less...
- More or less?
He said if I go,
I won't be able to come back.
Then why go?
I wanna sea the beach with you.
All right.
Come on.
- So, what's your name?
- Harlan.
That's it?
My full name
is Harlan Fairfax Carruthers...
Very full...
- What's your name?
- Tobe.
What's that short for, Toby?
Tabitha?
Tobias?
Manitoba?
October.
Really?
Cute.
- It's a pleasure to meet you.
- Likewise, do you smoke?
You smoking a joint?
No thanks, I don't touch that stuff.
Where are you from?
- South Dakota.
- Really?
I knew a guy from there,
but he looked nothing like you!
What can I say...
Who would've thought
I'd see the ocean today.
Wanna swim?
- In the water?
- Yes.
I'd rather watch than drown.
I'll protect you.
I don't have a swimsuit.
Swim in your underwear,
like the Mexicans do.
I'd rather not.
Then swim in your pants.
These jeans can face the sea.
C'mon.
- You sure?
- You'll see, it'll be fun.
Gimme your hand.
Here it comes!
Are we too far out?
You okay?
We won't drift out to sea, right?
Relax, I won't let you drown.
This is how
I always imagined infinity.
Don't look out there,
just look at me.
Oh my goodness.
Well...
did you like the beach?
What time is it?
Dunno, it's late.
It's almost dawn.
I'd better go
or my father will kill me.
Hope not,
'cause I'd like to see you again.
You wanna see me again?
Yes, I had a good time,
but this isn't how people
normally get acquainted.
You're funny.
Hi, how do you do?
I'm Harlan, what's your name?
Lonnie.
Nice to meet you.
Darn, hope I didn't break it.
No, you just need to wind it up.
Right.
Good thing.
That's authentic, right?
I never saw one that works before.
- You a friend of dad's?
- Huh? No...
I'm here to take your sister...
to the city.
We're going downtown.
Is that all right?
Yes.
Great.
You're Tobe's brother, right?
- How old are you, 11 or 12?
- 13.
Really?
Sorry...
- I'll grow.
- Yeah, of course!
I just meant...
Sure.
I was smaller than you, at your age.
My uncle called me Twig,
said the wind would blow me away.
I was real small!
Then I grew.
- Where's Tobe?
- She's getting...
How do I look?
Dang!
Amazing!
- Hope it fits you.
- It's perfect.
- Aren't I cute?
- Yes.
You're real cute.
Would you like...
to get something to eat?
We'll bring your brother too,
then go dancing.
Hey,
wanna come get a sandwich with us?
Wanna?
Okay,
done deal!
Hi dad.
Hi.
- This is Harlan.
- Nice to meet you sir.
Wade.
- Where'd you get that outfit?
- Harlan bought it for me.
- What?
- Nothing.
I haven't seen you dressed like that
since you were 13.
A shame, with such a pretty daughter.
What do you do?
I...
I'm still finding my way.
- I've worked on farms.
- Not many farms here.
No, but you can't imagine
the work experience it gives you.
Nope, I can't imagine.
We're taking Lonnie to get a bite
then going dancing.
If you agree.
All right.
Shall we?
I'd like to say
I truly admire your daughter.
She's a beautiful person...
I hope to gain your trust.
C'mon.
Who is he?
- I met him at the beach.
- What?
- I gotta go.
- No, hold on.
- You worked on a ranch?
- Sure did.
Where?
In South Dakota?
There too.
But more here.
There are still ranches here?
Yes, some.
Most of them
were transformed or sold, but...
- You like animals?
- Yes.
Really?
Well, if you'd like...
we can go visit a big northern farm.
I don't mean
one of those tourist traps,
I mean a real ranch,
what do you say?
Yes.
- Can I ask you something?
- Sure.
Is that kid okay?
- Lonnie?
- Yes.
Yes, why?
Dunno, he seems like...
he needs to get out more or...
like he needs...
something.
He's still afraid of the dark.
He sleeps with the light on.
At least he can sleep!
Anyway...
he's fine.
Plus, I look after him.
You're a good girl.
I'm serious!
You have a big heart.
April!
Look who's here!
I wanna take it with you,
it'll make us happy.
I'm already happy with you.
Not this happy.
Let's go!
Hold on, be right there.
Howdy.
Window's open, what's going on?
Where's the cowboy?
What are you doing John Wayne?
C'mon!
We should love people, not cars.
I'm serious!
What'll we do?
We don't belong to all this,
you're all trapped inside.
We're just trying to go somewhere.
Look!
- Everyone out!
- The hell with cars!
- Hug me!
- No, you do it.
- Preach it, Texan!
- Yeah, I'll preach!
Preach it, brother.
See, I'm preaching!
- Quit it.
- What?
- Are you nuts?
- No, I'm the sanest of all.
- Yeah, right.
- It's true, look.
They're sitting
in their boxes driving.
Look how many boxes,
an endless line!
When'll the effect wear off?
In a while.
You'll be fine tomorrow.
What's on your mind?
Dunno,
there are lots of things
I'd like to do, but...
I'll never be able to.
You can do anything you want.
You can even become
anything you want, if you just...
Decide and...
do it.
It's like waiting
for life to start over.
A new start, understand?
At times I'd like
to step outside of my heart.
Take a walk under a starry sky.
And listen to nothing but the wind.
I'd like to talk
and hear my real voice.
- Do you talk with your real voice?
- Dunno.
What is it?
When you don't hear any other voices
in your head while talking.
You can say what you really want,
you don't say things
you're not interested in.
Are you sincere with yourself?
Not always.
But I am now.
Me too.
- Hi.
- Where the hell have you been?
I slept at April's.
Hold on, dammit!
Were you with him?
I was up all night
worried sick about you.
- Your girlfriend didn't comfort you?
- Come here!
- I'm not done talking.
- Leave me alone.
Come out!
- Open the door.
- No way!
Open the damn door.
We'll discuss this tonight,
make sure you're here when I get back.
- Hear me?
- Yes.
- What?
- Yes!
You have something of mine,
I won't give up easily!
If I come in, I'll open fire!
You got some nerve shooting me.
Half that stuff's mine,
there's plenty for all!
Knock it off!
Leave me alone, idiot!
Mind your business
if you don't want trouble.
You have some screws loose!
Your greed will be your death,
'cause you...
You are greedy
and you'll squeal like a pig
when I come in that door!
Fuck.
All this for a few gold nuggets.
I bet this is part of human madness.
Almost there.
- Is that them?
- Sure is.
Like 'em?
Good.
Pick one.
Hey there.
Easy...
Good boy.
Let's go.
What do you think?
It's beautiful.
Yeah, it sure is.
Do you think things have meaning?
Huh?
Do you think everything's destiny
is already...
written?
That's an interesting thought.
I came here often.
I looked at that branch and
asked myself if it had a purpose.
Maybe it's here...
to create shade.
Or maybe...
it'll get cut to make furniture
for somebody's home.
Maybe it's just here for the swing.
Maybe it's just here
to balance the entire tree.
I'd opt for the swing idea.
It seems like a good idea.
And seeing you on it,
I know I'm right.
Can I watch?
Sure.
Where's your sister?
Dunno.
Are you still mad at her?
I love your sister, it's just that...
at times
she makes me lose my patience.
What do you like about her?
She's got moxie.
What's that?
It means...
she's got guts,
she's not submissive.
This upsets me,
but it's also positive.
America's rough on the meek.
But they'll inherit the earth.
- What?
- They'll inherit the earth.
That's bullshit.
I heard it on TV.
The meek may inherit
money from relatives,
but not the earth.
The only good thing about the meek
is they make...
life easier for those who have moxie.
Can you learn to have it?
You either have it or you don't.
Stop!
Hey Charlie,
you've kept him in good shape.
We've been riding him all day.
Get off.
- What?
- Get off my horse.
Am I speaking Arabic, get off!
You're scaring my girlfriend.
This is my property,
that's my horse,
if I decide to shoot you
the law is on my side.
- Not so sure about that.
- Get off.
Relax, it's a misunderstanding
but we'll resolve it.
I don't know
what your friend's thinking
but you'd better tell him to get off!
Get down.
All right.
Not for you or your rifle,
but 'cause my girl asked me,
and I'd do anything for her.
Unlike you Charlie, I have priorities.
I don't give a damn
about your priorities.
And quit calling me Charlie.
I'm rather disappointed,
after all our chats, now you embarrass
me in front of my girl?
I should kick your ass just for that.
Let's go baby.
- You're not going anywhere.
- Put the rifle down!
- Put it down.
- They're the thieves.
Thanks, officer.
Charlie, are you insane?
- Pointing a gun at your friends?
- Calm down.
Both of you calm down.
What happened?
- He stole my horse.
- Not true.
The horse is here!
They came on my property,
stole my horse
and that guy threatened me.
What?
- Don't you start!
- Calm down.
- Where's the horse?
- There.
The white one,
they took it without asking.
- From my property.
- Wait!
Charlie always lets me use the horses
so long as I bring this.
He wasn't here so we took the horse,
came back then he attacked me.
You think this is the Far West?
- This is the valley.
- You're holding the rifle!
I don't even know him.
He takes medication,
this is what happens if he forgets to.
- Liar!
- You should take your medication.
- My name isn't Charlie!
- Put them in the car.
Do you really know Charlie?
Sure, why do you ask?
You can tell me if you don't,
it's all right.
He keeps insisting
his name isn't Charlie.
So? I don't know
if he has a different name,
I've always called him Charlie.
You mad at me?
Shit!
Great.
I take better care of my animals
than you take care of your children.
Right.
Tell me exactly what happened.
Sir, I just want to say that...
I know you're upset but...
Tobe had nothing to do with it.
I take full responsibility
for what happened.
You don't need to apologize.
I think it's important to take
responsibility for our own actions.
Nothing's more important
than taking responsibility...
Not even
involving a minor in a crime?
Okay...
But this isn't the case
'cause I didn't break the law.
It was a misunderstanding.
Tobe, tell your friend here...
he needs to be more honest
to gain my trust.
- I don't care if he has your trust!
- Hey!
See you, Lonnie.
Thanks.
- Stop!
- Let go!
You sit down and talk to me!
I don't want to talk to you.
- Let go!
- Stop!
Fuck you!
Don't say that to me, I'm your father.
Understand?
I'm her fucking father.
If I see you with that psychopath,
I'll kick your ass!
Wait, go back in.
- Stop it, dammit!
- Let go!
Go back in, what are...
Sorry.
- Please, leave me alone.
- You okay?
Get the fuck away!
- What are you doing?
- Knocking on your window.
- What were you doing?
- Sleeping.
What happened to the window?
It was an accident.
- He didn't hit you, did he?
- No.
- You swear?
- Yes.
What did he say about me?
He just said he never wants me
to see you again.
- Do you plan on obeying him?
- No way.
Wanna take a walk?
I can't.
There's a religious parade tonight.
Spanish Lutherans,
never seen such enthusiasm.
I can't, not tonight.
- How about tomorrow?
- I'll be away.
I'm going to San Diego for the weekend
with April and her folks.
- Can I see you Monday morning?
- Yes, but not here.
'Cause of my dad...
- I'll come to your place.
- Okay, when?
How about 10:02.
- Why so late?
- How about 10:01?
That's better.
Crazy cowboy!
You love me?
Yes, now go!
Bye.
Dear Joe,
sorry it's been so long
since I've been in touch.
You thought this cowboy
had galloped into the afterlife?
Hope you haven't forgotten me.
I've been meaning to write,
but was busy working
and trying to have fun
in my free time.
I know you worry
about me being lonely
but you'll be glad to know
I found a super gal,
her name is October.
There are 8 million people here,
but she's the one for me.
She introduced me to her folks,
I'm like part of the family,
we're inseparable now.
Hey, it's me, Twig.
- What's up?
- Nothing.
- Enjoying vacation?
- Yes.
- Is Tobe home?
- No.
- She's not back from her trip yet?
- Dunno.
Wanna wait for her?
I was waiting at my place,
she was...
supposed to come by but...
Well, when she gets back
tell her to come see me.
Okay.
See you.
Wanna see something?
Sure.
Holy cow, what a collection!
Know what this is?
- A 1921 Colt Pacemaker.
- Yep, it's his favorite.
Amazing!
- Ever go shooting with him?
- No.
- He says not until I turn 16.
- Really?
- Was your dad in the war?
- I think so.
Nice.
Got plans for today?
So if Wade's not your real father,
who is?
Dunno.
- I never met him.
- So Wade's a father to you?
Yeah, he buys us food and everything.
It takes more than that
to be a father.
Where's yours?
He left me and my mom
when I was your age.
This is a single action Colt 45.
They started making it in 1873.
It was never modified.
Because it's perfect.
All the greats: Wyatt Earp,
Billy the Kid, they all had this gun.
Single action
means you can pull the trigger
all you want and nothing'll happen.
You have to manually cock it to shoot.
You have to do it every time,
it's not easy.
Great pistoleros had to pull it out,
cock it, and shoot.
You get used to it after a while.
You want the last two shots?
Stand here.
When you're ready, cock the hammer
and gently pull the trigger.
Watch out for the recoil.
Don't aim,
point as if it were your finger,
as if it were an extension
of your arm.
Nice!
Great shot!
That's my favorite song.
With a little practice,
we'd make a great duo.
Tobe's not home.
I don't want you
spending time with her.
I'd prefer if she says
she doesn't want to see me.
I was with Lonnie, anyway.
I don't want to see you around here,
the end.
I know you're upset
by what happened,
I'm sure you consider me
a threat to your daughter.
But I'm not.
I have only good intentions.
Would you accept my apology?
You're the dad, I wouldn't
want challenge your authority.
- Okay, your name's Harlan?
- Yes.
Harlan Fairfax Carruthers.
Listen Harlan, I know you,
you can't fool me.
How do you know me?
It's my job,
I see guys like you every day.
- Like me?
- Yes.
- What does that mean?
- Want me to explain?
- Thanks.
- Know what you are?
You're trailer trash, a nobody
who wants to become somebody.
You pull some stupid stunts
to reach your goal
hence, you're dangerous.
That's why
I don't want you around my kids.
Really...
Do you honestly see me like that?
- Shut your mouth and go inside.
- He can have his own opinion.
- Go in.
- He's my friend, he knows me!
Go in!
- You can speak your mind.
- Shut up!
- Hey.
- Get the fuck inside!
Why don't you talk to me,
I'm right here,
I'm not a nobody, I'm a person.
And I won't leave just 'cause
a son of a bitch tells me to.
I know I'm not worth much
but I will fight
for my love.
Shit.
I'm sorry pal, really.
You'd better go.
I can't.
It's too late.
He has a gun!
Okay...
No need to shoot me.
Get lost.
You're setting a bad example
for that kid.
Understand me now?
Yes, yes I do.
I understand you clearly.
- Wanna shoot or want me to leave?
- I want you to go to hell.
Okay, put it down,
I'll go.
You're a good kid,
don't let them tell you otherwise.
You can't threaten my friends
with a gun!
What if he's a pervert?
- You're a fucking bastard.
- How dare you!
- I'll tell you off when I please.
- Really!
Fuck you.
- Let go!
- No, stop it!
Stop it.
Knock it off, I said enough!
All right.
I love him!
Why can't you just let me love him?
Hi.
Where were you? I was worried.
Come sit down.
I'm okay.
I'm sorry for what he did to you.
Yeah...
But it's done.
At times...
these things helps clarify situations.
He said some bullshit,
like you tried to kidnap Lonnie!
I didn't believe him, he got pissed.
I brought Lonnie home before sunset.
Want a donut or some hot chocolate?
Wait.
Did you really take Lonnie out?
I came to look for you
because I was worried.
Lonnie was at home alone
doing nothing.
I felt bad for him
so I took him to the canals to shoot.
You took him shooting?
Why?
He was all alone,
I felt bad for him.
But you know dad would've gotten mad!
Yeah...
But...
I thought we'd get back
before him but...
You can't behave like that.
Now it'll be even harder
for me to see you.
October...
are you happy living with Wade?
I have to get you out of there.
What?
I gotta get you and Lonnie
out of there.
- We'll go somewhere else.
- Stop this.
- Why?
- You have to stay calm!
I am calm.
Listen...
we can't see each other for a while.
- No!
- Until things cool off.
- How long will that take?
- I don't know.
Where are you going? Don't go!
I want to go home.
Listen...
everything will be fine, okay?
I'll figure something out, I promise.
What do you do?
What's your job?
I worked...
in the...
car industry and I'm a fucking cowboy.
What do you do?
Fuck, why did I mention the ranches.
The truth is, I'm a Native American.
Yes, an Indian.
The last of the Mohicans.
Why, what's your job?
What do you do,
Wade?
Imprisonment?
So you're a jailer?
Yes, you're a jailer,
that's what you are.
Do you come
from a long line of jailers?
I'm from a long line...
of kings...
warrior kings, I fucking should be.
See this?
It'll look like this
when it flies toward you.
So, who's a nobody now?
Harlan, can I come in?
You here?
- What is it?
- Don't tell me that's a bullet.
- Why I think it is.
- Have you lost your mind?
- You don't shoot windows!
- Go back to your room.
- Why does he have a gun?
- Go to your room!
- Are you nuts?
- I'm sorry, it was an accident.
I don't care.
You know I care for you
but you have no respect for me,
so you gotta leave.
Don't talk,
I don't wanna hear your stories,
just pack your bag and go!
- I'm serious.
- I'm getting my stuff, all right?
End of the line.
End of the line,
buddy.
Dear Joe,
isn't life funny?
We all fight furiously,
but we don't even know
what we're looking for.
People say all sorts of things
to make you feel better.
I've never heard so much
useless advice.
I tried to live in the valley again.
I tried my best this time.
I looked everywhere
in search of a sincere face,
but most of the people I met
don't even seem human.
I often sensed
something mysterious within me.
I spent years trying to figure out
what it was.
Then suddenly, life revealed
my purpose to me.
All the rest seems like an illusion,
like a painted wooden horse.
- Can I help you?
- Maybe, I'm looking for someone.
Who?
A friend...
You're disturbing prayers, leave.
Fine, but...
- Leave, you're disturbing us.
- All right, get your hands off.
Don't touch me, brother.
Hands off!
Let go! Stop it!
Let go!
Is this how you treat people?
It's been a long time, Joe.
You're probably surprised
to hear from me.
We wouldn't even
recognize each other if we met.
Maybe it all happened
without us realizing it.
I often wondered why
you did what you did,
why you left us.
I think I know what you were after.
I hope you know, in my own way,
I'm after the same thing.
Hope you are in good health,
though I would've liked to see you
one more time.
The winter rain scattered the smog,
for the first time
I see the path before me.
I'll find greener pastures.
If you happen to think of me,
wish me good luck.
With love, your son.
Hi sweetie.
- What are you doing here?
- How are you?
- Goodness!
- Where were you?
Around, I didn't...
I had some things to do.
I was worried about you.
I thought you didn't want
to see me for a bit, so I...
left you alone.
You shouldn't have disappeared.
I was upset when I said those things.
You sure?
You're not mad at me anymore?
Thank God.
That's all that matters.
So long as we're together.
Are you okay?
Yes, I...
I know I shouldn't be here but...
I needed to see you,
talk to you about some stuff.
- How did you get in?
- I came around the back.
The door was open.
I didn't see your dad's truck,
so I wanted to surprise you.
- Let's go for a walk.
- No, come here.
Come here, we gotta hurry.
What's this?
What do you mean?
Why's my suitcase on the bed?
Because we're leaving.
What?
I told you I'd figure something out,
look...
It took time but I got some money,
we'll live of off it,
we can settle down...
take Lonnie in,
or do anything you want.
I put some things in it.
Didn't know what to get, I was so
excited I got 7 of everything.
I didn't find 7 bras though.
But I did get your dress.
I'm sure you'll need other stuff
that I don't know about.
Honey, why that face?
My dad will be here soon,
you'd better go.
Wait, there's time...
Grab your things, this is our chance.
- Put away the suitcase, please.
- Wait, why?
- My dad will kill me if he sees it.
- Wait, stop!
Relax, we'll be far away
once he notices.
I already told you
I don't want to leave!
That wasn't you talking, I know.
- Then who was it?
- The voice of someone else.
It was your fear talking.
I don't know what you mean,
but you should go.
October, listen! Honey...
I know you're afraid
but this is our chance.
Look inside yourself
and listen to your heart's voice.
This is my heart, this is my voice,
I want you to go!
- Don't shout!
- Well you're not listening to me!
I said you have to go,
what's with you?
What's with you!
Sweetness...
Sweetness, I didn't...
Do you hear me, honey?
Can you hear me?
Keep breathing.
Please keep breathing.
Breathe.
911, can I help you?
Hello? 911 here, hello?
You home?
Tobe?
Lonnie?
Somebody help my daughter!
- Do you own other guns?
- Yes, but they're locked up.
Was that one?
He managed to get at it.
But the lock wasn't broken.
Listen, he managed in some way!
Did she say anything?
No.
She'd already...
Iost consciousness.
- And your son?
- No.
He wasn't there.
- Does he have access to the guns?
- No way!
- His prints were on the gun.
- What!
- Maybe it was an accident.
- No, it wasn't!
It was...
Nobody's ever seen
that cowboy you mentioned.
Hey, Twig!
Hi.
Tobe got shot.
Yeah, I know.
- I'm wounded too.
- Who did it?
She didn't say anything to anybody?
She's in a coma.
It was Wade.
- Really?
- Yes.
I came to say hello.
I'd decided to leave,
to go away for a while.
She wanted to come with me.
We were talking
and didn't hear him come home.
He shot at me but Tobe
got in the way so it hit her.
She was trying to protect me
and got hit!
How could something like that happen?
He shot at me too but I ran away.
Where did it hit you?
- Does it hurt?
- No, it's just a scratch.
I'll be fine.
My fingerprints were on the gun.
I have to talk
to the Police tomorrow.
Twig...
I want you to listen to me.
It's best if you grab your things
and leave with me now.
- I can't.
- Sure you can.
Sooner or later
the Police will figure out
that your dad did it.
When that happens, they'll arrest him.
Then they'll stick you
in a foster home.
- No they won't.
- They will.
It's the truth.
You'll end up in a state orphanage,
do you understand?
It's the worst thing
that could happen to a kid.
I don't want that to happen to you.
If you want,
I'll take you out of here.
We'll hide out for a while.
When Tobe's better
we'll come back to get her.
What do you say, pal?
Wanna come with me?
Yes.
All right.
Then pack a bag
and grab me a blanket,
we'll meet in the alley out back, go.
C'mon champ.
Mr. Sommers, she woke up!
Hi.
What happened?
You were unconscious.
I feel...
so strange.
Where's Lonnie?
This is the highest point
there is around here.
Are you crying, buddy?
Sorry.
Don't say sorry for crying,
it's nothing to be ashamed of.
The only time I don't cry
is in front
of people I consider enemies.
Will Tobe get better?
Is that what you're worried about?
Yes, she sure will get better.
- Did you find him?
- He's not here.
A guy saw him in Santa Clarita.
His real name is Martin Lassen,
he's from Receda.
He spent a year in jail for robbery.
We almost there?
Almost.
Come here,
let me show you something.
What?
C'mon, trust me!
Let's go.
You hold it for a bit.
Where are you going?
Relax!
I'm not going anywhere.
Where are you?
Here with you.
Now try to find your way back.
- What was that?
- An animal that's scared like us.
Don't run.
Move, but not as if you're afraid.
Move like a panther, with courage
and you'll be fine.
- Lonnie!
- Relax!
Down there.
- There he is!
- Stop!
C'mon, hop on Lonnie.
Don't shoot!
They'll never find us,
I don't even know where we are.
Where are we?
The horse doesn't like
how I treated him, he's right.
No, he's fine.
Darn.
This isn't exactly how I pictured it.
I'm really sorry.
Don't worry.
When real cowboys used to live here,
they called each other "partner",
it was right.
They were used to sharing everything.
Know what?
We need to get some sleep.
- Music cheers people up.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Don't you agree?
- Yes, a city...
isn't a city without dancing.
Would you care to dance?
I don't reckon I'm worthy
to dance with a lady like you.
But I asked you!
- All right.
- Good, let's dance.
Be right there.
- I believe this is yours.
- Thanks.
Time for our new sheriff
and his lady
to dance!
- Duty calls, see you around.
- Sure thing.
- Stop!
- Take it easy.
You take it easy.
Twig, come here and bring Lightning.
Lonnie, step away.
Wade, take one step near him
and I'll shoot you.
Hold on, nobody hurts anybody.
- Let's put the guns down and talk.
- Put your gun down, now!
Easy, with one finger, slowly.
You too, take off your belt.
Take it off!
Untie the horse.
- He shot Tobe!
- Shut your damn mouth!
The girl's not dead.
Lie all you want,
but we know you shot her.
- You're crazy!
- Even Lonnie knows!
- Nutcase, you lied to my son!
- Harlan!
Come on Lonnie!
Let's go.
Damn!
- You okay?
- Yes, hold this here...
and press hard.
C'mon, keep pressing.
We have to get out of here.
We've gotta move, help me get up.
And Lightning?
Go!
Stay down.
Will you be okay?
Hope so.
Don't wanna die in a place like this.
I don't like it one bit.
Listen,
stand up and see who's outside.
- It's Lightning.
- What's he doing?
- Nothing, just standing there.
- He'll give us away.
Bring him around back,
put him in the garage.
Wait, look at me.
You can do it, go!
Go, you can do it!
He was spooked, but he's fine now.
Stop!
Don't!
Stay here.
Listen, he shot your sister.
Lonnie, he's the one who shot Tobe.
- That's not true!
- She'll tell you herself.
She'll tell you.
What should we say?
Nothing,
just pray for him.
Subtitles:
Laser S. Film s.r.l. - Roma
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org