Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
The place: New York City.
The time: now. 1 962.
And there's no time or place like it.
If you've got a dream, this is the place
to make that dream come true.
That's why the soaring population
of hopeful dreamers has just reached...
...eight million people.
Oh, make that eight million and one.
-Hey, taxi! Taxi! Taxi!
-Taxi!
Wait. Where are you going?
Down with the bomb.
Down with the b--
Barbara?
-Barbara Novak?
-Oh, l think so.
-Oh, thank goodness you're here.
-Vikki?
Vikki Hiller, your editor, in the flesh.
lt is so nice to finally
meet you in person.
My goodness, you're gorgeous.
We'll have a photo shoot for
the book jacket. There's time.
The book doesn't come out for a week.
One week. Oh, my.
Don't be nervous. Cigarette?
Barbara, this is my secretary, Gladys.
Gladys, Barbara Novak.
Oh, l know. lt's a pleasure.
Hello, Gladys. l'm glad to finally
have a face to put with the voice.
Vik, l need you to sign off
on this pronto.
Maurice Johns, art director.
Barbara Novak, your cover.
Oh, Maurice. l love it!
Down With Love. Hear, hear.
l wish someone had
written your book...
...1 0 years ago before
it was too late for me.
Gladys, it's never too late.
Great job. Sorry if the guys in
reproduction have been riding your tail.
Well, l'm not.
They're ready for you in the lion's den.
-Lion's den?
-Oh, don't worry. You'll be fine.
Just take a deep breath.
Gentlemen, this is Miss Novak.
-E.G.
-C.B.
-C.W.
-J.B.
-J.R.
-R.J.
-Okay.
-O.K. can't make it. He's down with T.B.
Oh, what a shame. ls it serious?
No, they're just having breakfast.
T.B. is Theodore Banner.
The owner of Banner House.
The fellow publishing your book.
That's his portrait, there.
Sorry if we've kept you, but Barbara hit
a storm on her way down from Maine.
So you've come down from Maine, huh?
Well, you remember, C.B.
Miss Novak is the farmer's
daughter librarian...
...who spent the long, cold New England
winter writing her manuscript...
...by the light of a lonely oil lamp.
l'm at a loss here, ladies.
l'm afraid l don't know exactly
what Miss Novak's book is about.
Miss Novak's book is a serious work
of nonfiction entitled--
Vikki, excuse me, it's right behind you.
Would you mind pouring me
a cup of coffee?
lt's a serious work of nonfiction entitled
Down With Love.
-This is empty.
-lf you're making a pot, l'll have a cup.
-Count me in.
-Likewise.
-Ditto.
-None for me, Vikki.
Thanks, R.J.
l'll have a Sanka.
As l was saying, the central thesis of
Miss Novak's book, Down With Love...
...is that women will never be happy
until they become independent...
...as individuals by achieving
equal participation in the work force.
And how do you propose
women do this, Miss Novak?
By saying, ''Down with love.''
Love is a distraction.
lf women stopped falling in love,
it would be the end of the human race.
Not at all.
l say women should refrain from love,
C.W., not sex.
lsn't that the same thing?
l mean, for women.
lt won't be, after they've mastered
the three levels in my book...
...that will teach any woman
to live life the way a man does.
Level 1 instructs women to abstain from
men altogether so they'll stop thinking...
...that the pleasures experienced
during the sex act are related to love.
They're not. As women will learn by
practicing the self-pleasuring technique...
...that l've detailed in chapter 7,
entitled:
''Up With Chocolate.''
You see, gentlemen, the female
experience is a biological reaction...
...to chocolate that triggers the same
pleasurable responses in the brain...
...as are triggered during sex.
By substituting chocolate for sex,
the female will soon learn...
...the difference between sex and love.
Love for a man
will no longer occupy her mind.
She will now find that she has the time
and the energy to move on to Level 2...
...where taking on new challenges will
lead to the self-sufficience of Level 3...
...where the woman becomes active in
the workplace and earns and achieves...
...an unequivocal equality with men.
And all this time the woman
is abstaining from sex?
Heavens, no.
By Level 3, she can have sex
whenever she likes, without love...
...and enjoy it the way a man does,
''à la carte.''
Well, Miss Novak,
your theories may have worked...
...with the gentlemen up in Maine,
but the men in Manhattan...
...are not the fine, upstanding,
straightforward men of Maine.
The men of Manhattan are devious.
They're dangerous.
They'll be coming at you
from every angle.
When you're watching your front,
they'll attack the rear.
And when you're protecting your rear,
they'll drop out of the sky.
One more kiss.
Easy, baby. Careful you don't fall out.
Bye-bye.
Very good. l'll let him know.
Mr. McMannus, Catcher Block
has just landed on the roof.
-Are you Catcher Block's secretary?
-Yes, Mr. McMannus.
l'm Sally. l'm new.
They're always new. When he gets in,
tell him to see me. He's fired.
-You're fired.
-No, l'm not.
Oh, yes, you are.
You can take your Pulitzer
and your beloved Underwood...
...and your change of underwear
and clear out.
Do you work for me?
You had a story due yesterday,
but l gave you more time.
l held the presses so you could get
your scoop on Nazis hiding in Argentina.
Then l see this.
''ltem:
Know magazine's star journalist,
Catcher Block, ladies' man...
...man's man, man about town,
was seen leaving the Copa last night...
...with a doggy bag and three girls
from the floor show.''
l took the bossa nova triplets
to Cocoa Beach.
NASA was throwing a luau.
Oh, well, l hope you enjoyed it.
Because unless you found Nazis
hiding at your luau, you're fired.
There were Nazis hiding at your luau!
l knew you'd do it.
What do you got for me, Catch?
Argentina isn't the only hiding place
for Nazis. They're hiding in Florida too.
Wow. How? Who's hiding them?
-We are.
-We-- Americans?
Why? Nazis are bad. We're good.
Yeah, but some bad Nazis
are good scientists.
Like the guy building the rocket to land
on the moon and win us the space race.
He's a Nazi. And l saw
the top-secret file to prove it.
Here, l brought you a souvenir.
A top-secret NASA
security clearance badge.
-How did you get this?
-Blame it on the bossa nova.
-The triplets?
-Yeah.
You see, Lo shakes her maracas
and Rosa bounces her bongos...
...while Nena is all hands.
1 20 words a minute.
The story, it's written?
Whoa, Catch!
But is it safe to print?
NASA is gonna blow its stack.
Well, they forgave Germany,
they can forgive us.
Get someone from Legal up here.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
My analyst says l only react
to you with such vehement loathing...
...because l admire you so much.
He says l resent you
for being a self-made man.
As opposed to the son
of a self-made man.
Here, l hope you have your garters
from last night. There's none in here.
Garters?
l haven't worn garters
since Nixon conceded.
What are you, turning into a beatnik?
Oh, step into the future, Mac,
garters are a thing of the past.
l don't know, Catch.
l have enough of an insecurity
complex without worrying...
...about my socks falling down.
How can you know you won't show
a shiny shin when you cross your legs?
lt's a miracle of the space age.
Sock manufacturers are using new
fibers like Lycra, Orlon and Dacron...
...to put super stay-up power
into their over-the-calf sock.
What is the average length
for most men?
How would I know? Do you think I spend
time in the locker room looking around...
...making a comparative study?
Let me see yours again, then.
-We could measure. I'll get a ruler.
-Better make it a yardstick.
Let's be accurate.
Make sure you've got it fully extended.
Here you have it. Up the whole way.
It stays up all the way
all day long, Mac.
That's the miracle I told you about.
Better living through chemistry.
You got 1 6 inches.
Sixteen inches!
How long does a man's hose
have to be?
That's 32 inches of confidence
in every step.
Don't forget, l've got two of them.
l don't believe it.
You went through another one.
That's three this month.
What is it about the workplace
that women just can't seem to handle?
Men. They want us to fail.
lnviting me to New York
to launch my book...
...when they have no intention
of promoting it.
-Don't worry. l have a plan.
-You do?
Remember when you called to say you'd
like publicity where men would see it?
''Perhaps in a men's magazine,'' you said.
A prestigious men's magazine.
The most widely circulated
and highly respected men's magazine.
-Know?
-Yes, you did.
No, l mean Know.
Know magazine for men in the know.
Oh. Yes, exactly.
-You got us advertising in Know?
-l did better.
l got you a cover story written by Know
magazine's star journalist, Catcher Block.
Catcher Block? The ladies' man,
man's man, man about town?
Oh, Vikki, you're the best friend
a girl from Maine who wrote a book...
...and came to New York
could ever have.
You don't know the half of it. l hear
Catcher Block is gorgeous and eligible.
Not that that matters to us.
Down with love.
l can't believe it.
Me on the cover of Know.
Know.
-No.
-Catch, please, l promised.
lt's one cover story.
A girl's never called me in my life,
let alone invited me for a drink.
l think this Vikki really likes me.
l think l might really like her.
l'm sure l would if she likes me.
And she does, because l told her
as owner of Know magazine...
...l had pull with my staff.
Then pull your staff with one
of your other writers. l'm not doing it.
No, it can't be anyone else.
The best thing
l have to offer a woman...
...is the same thing
you offer a woman. You.
Yeah, but l'm all tied up, Mac.
l'm using me.
Come on. lt'll be fun.
-You like fun.
-Fun?
lnterviewing a man-hating, embittered
New England spinster librarian?
How do you know what she's like?
Who else would write a book called
Down With Love?
You don't have to be a Nazi
rocket scientist to figure that out.
Catch, please, please, please, please.
l hope you won't be disappointed.
Oh, Vikki, it's adorable.
My first New York phone call.
lt must be Know magazine.
No one else has your number.
lt must be Catcher Block.
-This is Barbara Novak.
-This is Catcher Block.
Catcher Block? Catcher Block?
-Know magazine.
-Oh, yes, of course.
What can l do for you, Mr. Block?
l think it's what
l can do for you, Miss Novak.
l'd like to invite you to lunch
to discuss your book.
Well, that sounds very nice,
but l'll have to check my schedule...
...to see when l'm available.
We've already ordered. Can you be
in the Mahogany Room in 1 0 minutes?
l'm afraid that will be impossible,
Mr. Block.
Well, some other time, then.
Right, l'll see you in 1 5.
Catch, you are the best friend a guy
with 20 diagnosed neuroses ever had.
We've been friends a long time.
l knew you when you had 1 2.
Oh, this is great. l'll be right back.
Gotta go put in my shoe lifts.
-Guess who?
-As if l'd need to guess.
-Tell me my name.
-Tell me you love me.
Blimey, Catch, you know l love you.
And l love you too, Gwendolyn.
-How long's your layover?
-Never long enough.
There's always time for a matinee.
Well, hello, Peter.
Barbara Novak, Peter McMannus.
Nice to meet you, Mr. McMannus.
Where's Mr. Block?
Yes, Mr. McMannus,
where's Mr. Block?
l don't know.
-Henri, where is Mr. Block?
-l don't know.
Mr. Block for you, Mr. McMannus.
Here he is now.
-Catcher, where are you?
-Mac.
Something sprung up. Is she there?
-Yes, she is.
-Let me speak to the spinster.
Mr. Block would like to speak with you.
-This is Barbara Novak.
-l'm so sorry, Miss Novak.
The darnedest thing.
l was waiting for you at the bar
and a little English foxhound...
...walked right in, came up to me
and started nuzzling me.
She seemed so lost, and didn't
want to go with anyone else...
-...so l just had to take care of her.
-Mr. Block, that is so thoughtful.
l remember reading that
the true test of a man's character...
...is how he treats
a defenseless creature.
Tell me, Mr. Block,
how is the little bitch now?
Well, l've got her all nestled in a box,
but l don't think she'll be content...
...until l'm holding her.
Miss Novak, could we
rain check until dinner?
Of course.
-Well, goodbye, Mr. Block. Until dinner.
-Goodbye.
This is Barbara Novak.
Miss Novak, l am so sorry,
the darnedest thing.
Yes, Mr. Block.
l'm out in the park with
my little French poodle...
...and she's just not ready to go in yet,
if you know what l mean.
Oh, l do.
But here's a little advice
from a farm girl to a city boy.
You'll find that if you stick
a little twig in her bottom...
...she'll remember why she
went out with you in the first place.
l'll keep that in mind.
Miss Novak, l hate to ask, but could we
rain check until breakfast?
Of course. Goodbye, Mr. Block.
Until breakfast.
l just don't know.
lt's not like Catch to be late.
No, he usually calls to cancel
right on time.
Oh, Barbara, l'm sure he'll call.
l mean come.
Elke and l missed you at lunch
yesterday, Gwendolyn.
Oh, l took in a matinee
with Catcher Block.
ls that so?
Elke and l missed you
at dinner last night, Yvette.
l took in a night game
with Catcher Block.
l told him l'd give up flying for him.
l did too.
-Now l wonder if he ever loved me.
-l wonder if he even cared.
l wonder what's keeping Elke.
This is Barbara Novak.
l'm so sorry, Miss Novak.
The darnedest thing.
l got waylaid by the sweetest
Swedish Lapphund...
...who kept me up half the night,
and l'm afraid l'm still in bed.
My, you do get way laid.
-Would you care for another beverage?
-Thank you.
-l beg your pardon?
-l was saying thank you, Miss Novak.
You are very understanding.
Could we rain check until lunch?
Oh, Mr. Block,
you can take your rain check...
...and as we say
on the farm at harvest time...
...put it where the sun does not shine.
Miss Novak, if you're looking to get
dinner, then just say so.
Oh, Mr. Block.
l wouldn't meet with you
in 1 00 years.
Goodbye, Mr. Block. Forever!
Mr. McMannus,
thank you for your trouble.
Not at all.
Vikki, l'll call a taxi.
-Guess this means we're through.
-Oh, it's sad, isn't it?
This is the first time l've eliminated
having a future with a man...
...before we've had the chance
to have had a past.
Goodbye, Mr. McMannus.
lt was nice while it lasted.
l haven't had dinner and breakfast with
the same woman since l had a nanny.
l'm sorry, Peter, but Vikki
is not the only girl for you.
That's why l brought you here.
You brought me here
because we're buddies, right?
Bosom buddies.
-Get a load of those rockets.
-Here's to antigravity.
Stay with me, buddy.
You'll get the spins.
And whatever you do,
don't close your eyes.
Don't close your eyes.
Open your eyes. Open your eyes.
lt's your book.
On sale, Scribners Fifth Avenue.
One?
Just one?
All that work, and, and, and one.
lf somebody buys it,
well, then there will be none.
lt'll be as if it never even existed.
No, no. Doubleday also has one.
Barbara, l know you're thinking
this is a real setback...
...but l promise you
l will think of something.
lf only we could get your book
on The Ed Sullivan Show.
How exactly do you get a book
on The Ed Sullivan Show?
Vikki, you're incredible.
She wasn't even on the bill.
How did they fit her in?
Oh, the best luck.
The Singing Nun fell off her scooter...
...coming across the Triborough Bridge.
l guess somebody up there likes me.
--a really big surprise.
Because it coincides with the arrival
of a new book, Down With Love...
...which this week is at your
booksellers from coast to coast.
We have a very, very special friend
of our show to do a song of that book.
Now, I want a really big, warm
welcome for Judy Garland.
Yes, ma'am.
Down With Love by Barbara Novak.
lt's called Down With Love
by Barbara Novak.
You said she was a spinster.
l never used the word spinster
in my life.
Okay, once. When l told my mother it
was incorrect to call her son a spinster.
-You said she was a brunette.
-l did not.
She didn't sound blond on the phone.
Do you still wanna date Vikki?
Of course. You think
l wanna die a spinster?
Call her. Tell her l'll do
the cover story.
Oh, Catch, you are the best friend
a guy--
Just call.
Not since Johann Gutenberg's invention
of the printing press...
...which changed forever the landscape
of man's destiny...
...has one book reached so many
and achieved so much.
Reminding all of us here today
of the noble goal...
...which called us to toil in the field
of publishing to begin with:
Sales.
So here's to Banner House's
new number one author...
...and our new number one editor.
Say cheers, everyone.
Cheers.
Those men are livid, B.N.
You're a hit. You're bigger
than the pill.
Oh, talk about big, V.H.
This office is huge. Congratulations.
We did it.
Well, hello, Gladys.
You look wonderful.
As you told me, Barbara,
it's never too late.
Oh, Vikki, Peter McMannus called again.
Now it's every half-hour.
Tell him we're too busy.
What do you mean? Too busy?
You know what it means.
They hate us.
Too busy? Kennedy, Khrushchev
and Castro...
...weren't too busy during the Cuban
Missile Crisis to sit down and talk to me.
But this Down With Love chick
is too busy?
Doing what? Eating chocolate?
I'm sorry, panel, you've been stumped.
The author of the bestseller
Down With Love...
-lt's Novak!
-...Barbara Novak.
Barbara, I know every woman bought
your book. And I know every man...
...sneaked out and bought it to find out
what their women were reading.
Oh, well, that's when the sales doubled.
But then they tripled.
How did that happen?
It seems that church groups
in the Bible belt were so zealous...
...about being seen burning my book
that every time they had a bonfire...
...they would call the next day and
reorder, so they could have another one.
Now, I've heard a lot of talk
about Chapter 8...
...about the worst kind of man,
the kind every woman should avoid.
-What's that title again?
-Oh, yes.
Men Who Change Women As
Often As They Change Their Shirts.
And have you met a lot of that kind
of man in your research?
You're not asking me to name names,
are you?
No, of course not.
Catcher Block.
Four million women in the naked city...
...and the one you let get away, the one
you had to get on the bad side of...
...is the woman all the other four million
are listening to.
You blew it, buddy.
The age of Catcher Block, ladies' man,
man's man, man about town, is over.
The king is dead.
l hate to spoil your fun, Mac, but
the four million women l go out with...
...don't listen to Barbara Novak.
Hello.
Hey, Gwendolyn, baby.
Where are you?
Well, then get out of the airport.
We have reservations for 1 0:00.
Well, you can't sit in the terminal till
3 a.m. Aren't you gonna get hungry?
No, l'm pretty full. Besides, l have
to catch up on some reading.
Reading? Reading what?
Good night, Gwendolyn.
What's the matter, Catch?
Lose another one?
l am going to bury that Novak broad...
...and turn this crazy upside-down-
with-love world right side up again.
l'm gonna write the exposé of
the century, so the world will know...
...once and for all that deep down,
all women are the same.
They all want the same thing:
love and marriage.
Even Miss Barbara ''Down With Love''
Novak. And l am going to prove it.
How? Novak won't even see you.
That's right. That's why Novak
won't even see me coming.
Barbara, you're not dressed.
Aren't you coming?
No. l'm just gonna stay in tonight.
Why? Because you don't have a date?
My date's a quarterback with 27
teammates. l'm sure he can fix you up.
l'm sure he couldn't.
l am persona non grata to all men.
l can't even get picked up
by a taxi driver.
Now, this is crazy.
All of this fame and success...
...and Miss Sex à la Carte is the only
woman who can't have sex à la carte.
At least not on this earth.
Maybe we can find you an astronaut
who's been in orbit the past two weeks.
lt's all right, Vikki. l'm perfectly content
on my own.
Well, when it comes to not needing
a man, you wrote the book.
-Taxi!
-Wait a minute.
-l have to pick up my dry cleaning.
-Can't. Gotta go back to the office.
Skip in Research is doing a fact-check
on Novak.
Who she knows, where she goes, what
she likes for dinner, à la carte.
Two minutes? l waited for you
to eat your hot dog.
You're right. l'll pick up your cleaning.
Go back to the office.
Oh, but l--
Oh, make sure they starch the socks.
l'm getting it.
-You iron.
-No, you iron...
...and l'll spend all day up front
kibitzing with the customers.
We're equal now.
Again with that book.
Hello, Novak.
Hello, Mrs. Litzer.
Where's Mr. Litzer?
He's ironing.
lrving, say hello to Novak.
Hello, Novak.
l'll get your things, dear.
Thank you.
Yours too, mister.
Pardon me, miss, but you
sure look familiar. Are you...?
Yes, l am.
Well, l'll be a monkey's uncle.
Wait till l tell the folks back home...
...l took my clothes to the same
dry cleaners as Miss Kim Novik.
No, no, my name is Novak.
Oh, that's right. Miss Kim Novak.
No, no, l'm not Kim Novak.
l'm Barbara Novak.
Oh, well, that doesn't ring a bell.
You mean you've never heard of me?
Oh, l'm sorry.
Oh, no. No, don't be.
l find it very refreshing.
You, Mr. Absent-minded Professor.
You left a lot of things
in your pockets.
Why, thank you, ma'am.
Excuse me. l'm sorry.
Do you mean that you've never heard
of my book...
...the worldwide sensation,
Down With Love?
No, ma'am, l have not.
But lately, l've been out of this world.
Oh, look, my NASA security badge.
l've been looking all over for that.
-You're an astronaut?
-Why, yes, l am.
Well, what's your name?
Maybe l've heard of you.
Zip.
Zip...?
Martin. Major Zip Martin.
Well, tell me, major...
...are those parties in Cocoa Beach
as wild and uncivilized as they seem?
Oh, now, l couldn't say, ma'am.
l'm not much for going to parties.
My idea of a good time is to sit at home
with a good book...
...and smoke my pipe.
Pay later. lrving's burning the ironing.
Pardon me, miss.
Oh, we're stuck together.
Let me fix that.
There you go, Miss Novak.
Well...
...goodbye.
One, two, three, four.
Zip?
Yes, Miss Novak?
Well, l don't suppose that
you're staying in New York?
Why, yes, l am.
NASA sent me here to work
on a special project.
A top-secret project.
-Can you keep a secret?
-Yes.
Me too.
Gee, it sure seems like we got
a lot in common.
Why, yes, it does.
lt might be nice to see
just what we have in common.
And what we have that's different.
l'm sorry?
Would you like to go to my place and
get to know each other a little better?
-A little better?
-A lot better.
-A lot better than what?
-All the way better.
Oh, gee. No, now, l couldn't do that.
Why, l couldn't get to know you
all the way better...
...until l knew you much, much better.
Do you think that you know me well
enough to let me buy you a drink?
Well....
l'd sure love a Tang.
Lose another pair of glasses?
No, l'm keeping a low profile.
Vikki's over there with some guy.
That's not some guy. That's
Johnny Trementus, the quarterback.
Fourteen hundred and thirty-two
complete passes.
ls he going for 1 433?
Well, Vikki's left herself wide open,
but Trementus surprisingly fumbles.
Now what's he doing?
ln layman's terms.
He's leaving. Now's your chance.
l can't go over there. She hates me.
She doesn't hate you. She hates me.
Now, stop warming the bench
and get in the game.
Once you run my Novak exposé, she will
hate you, and the clock will run out.
Can't you get off your Novak warpath?
Nope. l've got her surrounded.
And it won't take a surprise attack
to enter her tepee.
l'm telling you, Kimo Sabe,
you want big wampum?
Make Vikki love you now.
Okay, okay, enough
with the football talk. l'm going.
-Here you are, Monsieur Block.
-Thanks, Henri.
Only, from now on it's Maj. Zip Martin.
Spread the word to the other maître d's,
the doormen...
...theater ushers and taxi drivers.
Done, major.
lt'll be all right, McMannus.
Just be normal. Be cool.
Hello, Vikki.
Hello, Peter.
Are you in love
with that football player?
Not anymore. He only wanted one thing,
to slip me his manuscript.
He didn't even have the professional
courtesy to try and seduce me first.
The men who resent my success
won't give me the time of day.
And the men who respect my success
won't give me the time of night.
l don't know about other men,
but l swear if l had the chance...
...l would respect you and resent you
night and day and day and night.
-Peter, you would?
-You bet.
You're on.
Oh, Zip, isn't this exciting?
We must be the only two people in New
York who haven't seen Camelot yet.
You're not just being nice?
You really haven't seen it either?
Oh, l can honestly say l have
never seen this show.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org