Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Welcome to San Francisco,
the city on the bay.
With its 30,000 hydrants, 4 million
tennis balls and flexible in-the-gutter-law.
I'm Lucky. A dog, if you have
not had. And this is my boss.
You know Dr. Dolittle right?
The guy who can talking with animals.
Let me just catch up.
He is a doctor and talk to animals.
He is busier than ever.
You have Mr. Carson for ten hours
and the ECG of Mr. Wennington at 12 hours.
Mrs. Bloom has rash.
I am 11. 15 said.
Buster ontwormen, then the cough of Misty.
And after an hour nothing but castraties.
- Dinner of the Rotary.
- Breakfast at the Kennel Club.
Do Carson at 11 am, Buster 12,
the ECG and Misty at 12. 30 to 1. 15.
And sorting my files.
I had almost Mr. Panitch castrated.
As you would Mrs. Panitch
a fun with it.
You're welcome, ladies.
How busy he had,
Doc helped all animals.
- Hello. I'm Bandit.
- How you doing, Bandit?
- And I'm a stray dog.
- Shows nothing.
We know that your first time.
You do the leg to leg.
Exactly. Never give up hope.
This applies to all of you.
Any dog can find a family
person and his faithful pet.
Say after me:
I am someone's faithful pet.
Again.
A family in North Beach
looking for a good watchdog,
that love for children.
Anyone here experience in security?
Then Rusty gotta have.
Who is Rusty?
- Is it important?
- No, Rusty.
It says: Can not lick...
on his ass.
Each zoo wanted him.
He was especially good in soul choked.
When was your party last Friday?
Not so long ago. A year or 20.
Monday was 48 years ago.
I see what the problem is.
I give you pills for your eating to do.
What are they?
What you look hot.
I'll be there, baby.
He became an international star,
from Alaska to Australia.
I stand here next to the famous Dr. Dolittle,
which the animals talk.
We are an unsuspecting alligator
stalk and save.
Still, he hears otherwise.
The trick to catching alligators,
is that you should watch out for their teeth.
I let Steve think that I do not doorheb
that he is behind me.
I wait until he wants to tackle me, then turn
I huppekee around, his arm off.
I turn my arm around his neck and...
- Steve, he knows that we are here.
- I have to surprise him.
Now.
Jeez, my arm.
Everyone wanted to help the good doctor.
His family understood. Largely.
But there shortly.
Now moetik the door open.
- Who's there?
- I forgot my key.
Then you'll have to beg.
Go ahead, kid.
You know him? Reverse world.
Because usually it is the man
- Against the dog says...
- Put the door open but now, Lucky.
Because you give me food,
I leave you this time inside.
Who's back from France?
- Hello, darling.
- How is it?
I have a gift for you.
- Is that for me?
- For you. For us.
I enjoy the fun with this gift.
You know what a nice gift would be?
If you crowd had disappeared.
I will talk to them.
- Papa.
- How is it, honey?
- I have something for you from Mexico.
- Gracias. What can it be?
Earthquake. Alarm.
- Do not shake it.
- My spleen. Pain.
- What a baby.
- This is not Puerto Vallarta.
It is a chameleon.
This change of color.
Make way for the disappearing maestro.
Attention, big trick.
Doll seen close box.
- We can still see.
- Really?
- Have you thought to Charisse's birthday?
- Have your cake?
- They do not want to celebrate with us.
- Why not?
- We always do.
- Is there anything green?
- Bring that thing to your room.
- Guacamole? A pickle?
She has a date.
What?
- Who?
- Have I not asked. She is great.
That we will ever see.
Where is she?
- They can not speak.
- Why? Where is she?
In her room with the door locked.
You can SMS her.
She is home and I can not speak?
I have her SMS?
That we will ever see.
Nothing SMS.
Careful. She is 16.
That is a difficult age.
Open the door.
- Do not believe it.
- Try her cell phone.
I ga her mobile phone
in her bedroom.
Open the door.
These teenagers, though.
You should it go bust.
- What are you drinking?
- Gatorade.
Oh, yeah? Please come here.
Gatorade even makes wine?
Do be quiet, you.
- Who of you is Dolittle?
- What now?
- I got a message from the chef.
- From whom?
The Peet Bever.
No questions, come with me.
You will not invade.
First, make an appointment.
Say that but at that beaver.
Then I can sleep with the fishes.
I would like in the paper that Dr Dolittle
an opossum from the roof throws?
- No. But I do it.
- Watch your words.
- Say it again.
- With Dad. How are you?
I want to ask.
Why should I rise against the house
to talk to you?
Dad, where are you?
- Dad, what are you doing?
- I can just reach.
What are you doing here? And what is that?
- Do you think in public?
- Dancing?
That is not dancing but sjansen.
Why four you disagree with us?
A dinner with the whole family
is something for when you're small.
- I have a date.
- Bring the boy along.
Sure. ''Eric, my parents and sister
go along on our date. ''
No, he may join our trip.
That is tradition.
I do not even know why...
- What is this?
- It is private.
Because you ashamed, for sure.
You have two zesminnen and five.
I ashamed? You are the last
those which may say.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean?
Should not I help animals
Because you ashamed you have?
- That happens anyway.
- Exactly.
You go out to eat.
Look.
- A week is not GSM.
- What should I not GSM?
Here, stamps to write letters.
Look at me.
You think what I could care?
Can I shit?
Hell, no.
There are 50 numbers and I is not here.
- Since you can not see.
- Why not?
Biggie Mack GSM.
Biggie Mack SMS. Biggie Mack home.
- Who is Biggie Mack?
- No idea.
Since I'll be back.
What is that name? I think it is anything but.
- What is that?
- The GSM of Marcus.
- Since when has a cellphone?
- Since last week.
- What are you doing?
- I see who is Biggie Mack.
- Who is this?
- Is this Biggie Mack?
- Who are you?
I suggest here the questions snot.
- How old are you?
- That is your business.
Then I make it my business.
- Is that a threat?
- I is not threatening, I promise alone.
- Is this John Dolittle?
- Sorry, I've turned bad.
- That was a mature guy on the line.
- Not on this side.
- The bell.
- That I hear it.
- Please open it.
- Am I suddenly the butler here?
I bowl.
Hey, Dr D. How you doing? I am.
Who is I? Back, I do.
Let me inside you, man?
- Dr D, all kits?
- Pardon?
I, Eric. Domino's Pizza.
Extra cheese, anchovy, tomato...
You are the pizza farm.
- Thanks. I forgot you tip?
- You've given me something much better.
- I get it on, because...
- Hi, Eric.
How is he, honey? Are you ready?
- Is he your date?
- Dad, Eric. Eric, my Dad.
- Good man. Alles kits?
- No, Eric.
We must stay home to eat.
Fine.
Charisse not do.
Do not ruin it for everyone.
You know, old man. Do not worry, man.
This strongly as I do.
Old?
When Charisse half was
they wanted no more diapers.
Remember?
She had on accidents, because they
still was not clean. There was...
- You can not, huh?
- We are family.
- Shows nothing. I learn something from.
- Oh, yeah?
Because you have not learned
for your pet to do at the table.
I get it hot
I look at you with your pet.
Sixteen.
In two years you can house,
study.
One year, 10 months and 16 days.
If you go to Berkeley is
you can stay home.
Good idea, but I have a moving van
hired after my graduation.
- Do you have a rented van?
- Someone you want to speak.
Yo. Come smoothing out.
- Thank you. Sorry, honey.
- Bye, Dad. I love you.
I love you too. Sorry, Eric.
- Yes, here.
- What do you want?
First of all, congratulations on your daughter
behalf of the beaver.
Very nice. Say that beaver
on my nerves.
Why so touchy?
He wants you just speak.
- And if I say no?
- That seems to me unwise.
Tomorrow morning at eight o'clock
in my consulting room.
The beaver travel for anyone.
He knows you're a busy man.
But this is a matter of life and death.
All right, but am still.
My car, seven hours.
Good. For example, the beaver hearings.
- Thanks.
- Jimmy, the car.
Blow out the candles and make a wish.
- Surprise.
- Congratulations.
- You're birthday.
- A mouse in the house.
- Specify.
- I lick the candles out.
- Oh yeah? Kiss my fat...
- Not so greedy.
I am so sorry.
Beware of my Bontje.
We wanted to surprise her.
If the kitten was
had you found cute.
- You are not cute pussy...
- Welles.
- . . But dirty rats...
- Nietes.
- . . Which have ruined the cake.
- Not so fake.
If you''swap''rats, ''get''star.
- I'm a star, buddy.
- Oh, yeah?
You know what you get
if you ha''swap''?
Exactly.
- Is this what I think?
- Nappies.
My favorite precarious. Chocolate.
Say''Maya''.
- What are you doing?
- He wants to say something.
Bring me a bone.
And a large portion super fly.
Bring me ham, German sausage and meat products.
- Lucky, out.
- Can I Charisse alone speak?
Come on, kid.
Sorry about tonight.
I ga bit calmer about it,
so I can be home more often.
- Even more animals here.
- But we can go.
Shall we all go to Europe?
- Are you serious?
- We can go to Paris, Rome.
We have so often talked about.
Would you like that?
Try me to buy?
Yes, yes.
- It works.
- Another thing...
- Tomorrow.
- What?
Tomorrow.
On holiday to Europe. Tomorrow.
Tomorrow we go to Europe.
Doc, the raccoon and opossum were
towards this mysterious beaver.
- Nice cart. Which one is it?
- A Mustang.
- Is there a car to my name?
- Opossum does not exist.
- Why not?
- They call them not to rodents.
Just a few lines
if you meet the beaver.
No sudden movements.
Not to his teeth, staring.
That stabbing a bit off.
I think he is unacceptable.
And lest the rest:
Treat him with respect. Capisce?
We are talking about a beaver?
- Tootie, how you doing?
- Doctor, how is it?
Reverse.
A little more respect, animals.
- The raccoon has met Doc.
- It is a miracle doctor.
Paulie, contact the chief.
I ga get some acorns.
Dr Dolittle, I presume.
Welcome to my home.
- Would you like to fish?
- No, thank you. I've already eaten.
If the beaver offers a fish, then eat your fish.
- Shut up.
- Sorry, boss.
I hear good things about you
of the families from the Bay Area.
Families in the Bay Area?
Are you the mafia or something?
We know nothing of the mafia.
Hey, guys?
- Never heard of it.
- Chimera.
I am a simple fisherman who many
friends. Do you want one of them?
- What do you want?
- I get my lost territory.
- To other animals?
- From the human species.
They cut our homes to
get families apart.
- The whole forest is flat.
- Then you do not have.
Please prefer to contact
natural associations.
You are the only
the spoken word goes.
We humans can not
with its guns, knives, sleeping banks.
Okay, I have rabies
and I may bite someone. But then?
- You understand me.
- Yes. Man against nature.
With you on our side
it is a different story.
I have not said
I would help you.
Before you say no, I want first
show what I am talking about.
It is gone.
Everything is gone.
- How do you save a forest?
- That will not be easy.
The timber has a big influence.
But if there is an endangered species
In that forest lived
- Then there was ground for protection.
- How do I get back there?
You should be able to ask Eugene.
There was an endangered bear species.
A motherless female.
- She is the only western Pacific bear.
- It must be protected.
Potters Houthakkerij claims that
since it is the only one,
the species no chance.
You still need a man.
Find a man
and its natural course.
The only west-Pacific male
is raised in captivity.
There has never been a bear
successfully put back into the wild.
Because they never help
the love doctor had.
- Doctor.
- Excuse me.
Soon his little bird flies away.
- Is something wrong?
- The...
Jeez. Hopefully, nothing Bambam seen.
It was the giraffe who took offense at.
I understand how disappointed you are.
Because we do not go to Europe?
- Why would I be disappointed?
- I love me to my promise.
Let me know if you do not want me to do this.
And me the rest of my life
feel guilty, sure.
- When are we going?
- Once the court prohibits logging.
Who will take the case?
- Why look around?
- Me?
Who, me? Not me. You.
For the animals.
- I do not animal rights.
- For the animals.
That is kind of ism. You are a Specist.
We ask only for an execution,
so we can save the species.
This is time stretch c. q. a publicity stunt.
I have statements under oath
of a number of experts
that restore a tame bear
in the wild
dangerous and irresponsible.
A circus bear can no food
finding or dealing with real bears.
Let alone the winter comes.
He would go under
to the survival laws of Darwin.
- On...
- Darwin not know my dad.
That is inappropriate behavior.
And who is your father then?
That's me, Your Honor.
I am Dolittle.
Can you tame a bear in the wild off
and to mate with that female?
Absolutely.
In that case I give one month delay
on the hood of Campbell's Grove.
- One month ahead. Nothing more.
- Thank you.
And if the bear but a claw
on a campsite or in this city move
I then pull the order in subiet.
I understand. Thank you.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Dr Dolittle, this way.
You talk with domestic and wild animals.
Are a circus bear and forest beer together?
He has long been in captivity.
So he will be happy
to return to nature.
Road vacation with the family.
Doc thought:''This is a cinch. ''
But when he had not yet met Archie.
Ladies and gentlemen, he is a bear
of a gentleman, the talking fire rug:
Archie the bear.
They game me.
Archie. And the show is over.
Good girl, huh?
- A bit of it.
- Have you no action photos?
No, but you're a lucky man
if you hook it to the stores.
Girls Saturday I got to each finger ten.
Okay, I've never had a girlfriend,
but bring her Monday visit.
You can not. You have to go to her.
- Back to her? Where?
- She is in the forest.
I do not forests.
I am a beer for celebrations and parties.
- You know what kind of beer you are?
- Once thought.
- A singer and dancer. Three years draft.
- You are an endangered species.
Start a threat?
My lawyer picked you...
I just want to say
that you are a rare Pacific beer.
You know what that is?
I do each bear. I do grizzly, panda, polar bear.
Look:
- ''I am freezing. What a cold. ''
- I will say it clearer.
Your ancestors came from California.
Humans have you removed
and learned to''Hound Dog''to swing.
That I have learned.
I grease a little syrup to the people,
but that is not miraculously?
Very nice, Archie.
But I want you back
to the country of your ancestors
and you learn to be a real bear.
I am satisfied with the bear I am.
I'm famous.
There is even a Beanie Baby from me for sale.
If you do, you
the most famous beer in the world.
- More famous than Pooh?
- What did you think?
If it succeeds, everybody says''Winnie the Who?''
This bear does it.
And now one of the strangest posts
of the year.
Dr Dolittle duplicate any nature to his boot.
He is a circus bear in the wild to restore
so a forest
logging for the future.
- It is contra Darwin Dolittle.
- Shut up.
I have two sawmills
at that wood waiting.
I understand, but it is difficult.
Especially if the bear survive.
If I get my quota,
I do not know whether you survive.
That ridiculous beer
is definitely on the writing.
If that happens, you have a trophy to.
I have a spot for him.
We moved into the forest
and waiting for Archie.
While it turns out,
I went the dog just exhausts.
This seems an ideal spot.
The simple pleasures of life.
Good grace. What a piece of that wolf.
I hope I do not stink out of my mouth
van 't to lick my...
Beautiful, huh? Yes, I am.
I have much more of that stuff.
From the same.
What is that?
''I like you''in the wild-teefs?
I do to breakdance.
This is the ruggenkrabber.
Not too bad, huh?
Ladies Dog not leave.
Will you call me?
The big day had arrived.
Now we had the bears to dance.
You know why we are here.
We will just do what has never been done.
They think that it is not possible.
Their trucks are already ready.
But we will prove the contrary.
Equally the claw gently together.
Applause for the bear
take the lead.
Here's Archie.
Come on.
Who wants to save the forest here?
Legs in the air.
Come on, do it.
You gotta be kidding me.
Now even the serious side of the track.
I know it will be heavy.
But with your help...
All of them.
- We have been there.
- Never in his life.
- It's over.
- Come, under the wool.
- This is a job, Doc.
- Past. Turn it off.
You are Wayne Newton in a berenpak.
What is it nasty.
That you have in the forest. There is sand.
- Wait. Is she? What a piece.
- Yes, that's it.
Look how she moves.
That I do not see wet.
I will up its proposals.
Wait here.
Say that I fall on its pin,
but keep it clean.
I will see if I can drop.
Wait.
If you come here?
I am the foraging.
- Hello, I'm John.
- I'm Ava.
What a beautiful name. Nice.
- Hi.
- Just a question.
Would you the man of your dreams
want to meet?
You're a baby,
but I do not cross with other species.
I had no man should say,
but beer.
What do you think of that splatter there?
I see him.
- Is he the loser?
- No, it is...
I will explain.
They go the whole forest fell.
The only thing they hold, as I
two Pacific bears can attach.
You are a Pacific beer, just like him.
If you are baby bears, then...
- Understand what I want?
- I 'm not talking bears pimps.
Let me call him.
Archie, come here.
Oh, there you are. I had thought that we
perhaps even could be sports.
- Your turn.
- What should I say?
- Tell her about yourself.
- I'm Archie.
I love walking in the moonlight,
lebberen enter with a special someone
and the sultry sound of the Backstreet Boys.
- You're weird.
- Are you crazy sexy?
No, just weird.
- I take it just about. Good.
- Damn.
What do you think of Archie? Is not the baby?
But only that I can not eat.
He is not his comfort with a female there.
This is not the point. I want a real beer.
One that can hunt and for me to worry.
- That is understandable.
- And I already have someone.
Do you have a boyfriend? Bears a boyfriend?
- Are you in love with him?
- My cousin married out of love.
But they knew
He deceived her with a grizzly'tje.
So you're not in love.
Let us agree on what.
Do not rush for a month.
Then I make at the time of Archie
a bear cub that you can get.
I role in the fabric for you.
Dennenappel.
Perfect evening.
Beautiful in the fresh air,
listen to the crickets.
You know what they say?
No idea. You are the person
which the animals talk.
Monkeys do not ask me to drink.
I am not saying: 'What is it, beast?
I listen to music.
I ever talk with animals?
I just wanted to say that crickets
the thermometers of nature.
The colder it is, the faster they tsjirpen.
- It's quite cold tonight, huh?
- A little fresh.
Ga I think I get my vest.
Yo, Dr. Dre and Snoop.
And let that car checked, man.
Yo, how you doing, baby?
- You forget your buddy.
- How you doing, Dr. D?
I know a lot. You tell me.
I thought, I go along. You may
m so happy, so I'll stay.
Nothing it.
I do not.
- What do not you, Dad?
- Eric in bags.
- He will stay. It was Mom.
- It was your mother.
You sleep on the floor
in the living room, in your sleeping bag.
If you do not mind.
And I love you.
And the whole forest, too.
I talk to the birds.
- Thanks, Dad.
- So beware.
- I get it.
- Yes, you drum? Good.
I have you in mind, though.
Bears are opportunists. They eat everything.
- Is there anything else on?
- Nothing of it.
You should look at
to learn how to survive the winter.
Is he digging?
Have you ever wondered
why you have claws?
- Bears can swim excellent.
- Not this one.
Can not you swim?
Have you never heard of boats?
That is the door. We are
early and then I'll learn to fish.
- Around noon?
- Unbelievable.
So began the calculation Thon, a bear
of a job, just brutal.
Enough.
- In this river is bursting with fish.
- At the viskraam too.
- Not to me, rather than to the water.
- They move. One has just touched me.
Not so childish.
Head in the water and fish.
- No.
- As you have seen on TV.
Head under water and a fish bite.
You can do it best. I stay with you.
I will try.
- There is Archie.
- How you doing?
How you doing?
Grab one.
Who forgets that now his head out of the water
to achieve if he can not breathe?
I saw a bright light. It was beautiful.
Enough. We will make you hard sometimes.
- We started something that even you handle it.
- I saw my opoe.
Come on, eat.
- Go, eat.
- I do not eat... I do nothing.
- Am I already in the neighborhood?
- Cold.
Use the Force.
- Colder? Warmer?
- You freezes.
- How are you?
- It's crazy. Three weeks is enough.
He looks as grapes.
- Why is he gone?
- He runs around.
- Why? Are they dangerous?
- No, they are not dangerous.
- Where are the grapes then?
- We are exactly on schedule.
I'm dizzy.
Do not panic. The concrete has
my fall broken. Bruise.
Put another out. I have six months
in a close black hole sleep?
- That do bears. The winter.
- Sounds more like a depression.
- How should I eat?
- You do not eat.
You eat the summer enough
the winter to come.
- And the bathroom?
- That you do not.
You are kidding.
A week before you go hibernate,
eat your sand, moss, hair and grass.
This is a plug in your...
It stops you... You know.
- It blocks my hole?
- Exactly.
With a big fat plug
of hair and grass. Big fat plug.
Ho minute.
I sleep half years with a cork in my hole?
- A bit of it.
- Yes, bye.
- Come back.
- I go by. Bye.
- Going south?
- Nobody picked up on a bear.
I pay the petrol and fun children.
- Come on, Archie.
- Sorry. It is nothing.
I almost drowned. Ava likes me not.
I lament that you tired.
Look in the tree. What do you see?
- Bird.
- A bird in his house.
That branch is a squirrel in his house.
There is a rabbit in his house.
These animals need you.
So let the inner bear loose.
Trust him.
He says do what you gotta do.
My inner bear has trouble
with that ass cork.
I will show you animals
not home anymore.
Hello, Clarice.
- This really does not.
- Sometimes a hard approach is best.
What is it, kid?
Could you live outside not?
Come on in, pussy.
- Inside.
- Why?
Go talk to that bear.
Ga I just sit there.
- I'm tired.
- Do not be afraid.
- I bite you.
- Dolittle. Hello, dear.
Keep your not hunt or fish?
You know how much I would be in the woods?
Did anyone what?
That is the problem with the youth
today. No respect.
We should teach him a lesson.
I take it in the bear grip.
Come here, uk.
It is fine.
I finally got it under control.
Can I call back?
These folks here love musicals.
Just kidding. I better do my best.
If the cat house, the dancing mice.
I mean teenagers.
- Do your eyes closed?
- Here they come.
- Have you done this?
- You know what Doc said.
If he means to be affected, we deal with him.
- There are wings, drumsticks, taco's.
- Did anyone''''taco?
Change color. You betrayed us.
There is something I have
a long time I want to do.
What then?
This.
Now.
He told me getongd.
That went well. I treat you, Jenny.
Meanwhile, Archie and I were taught by Doc.
Leave some for me. It is my...
- It was just an idea.
- What is going on?
I must be back for the ladies dog.
That you do not have to pick up. Get out.
- What a whopper.
- What do you have?
Any female looking for the strongest man.
- Is not love nature?
- I remain a virgin.
Listen. The strongest man
hot alpha male. He is the boss.
You should be.
The boss of all males.
You must run as an alpha male.
Loop it for sale.
- And speaking as it should.
- I still walk.
It is about power and respect.
Pure, onbeknotte by testosterone
driven, male power.
- You should change the bin liners.
- Do it yourself, bitch.
- What?
- I was talking to the animals.
- I had something to tell.
- Keep it up and go eat out.
I'm gone, baby.
- Now.
- I ga al
- Well, say.
- Shut up.
- Who should be close to his head?
- I was talking to the animals.
I eat out.
- You no longer?
- No, thank you.
Suppose your whole life in show continues.
What is your grand finale?
Finale? Headline in the San Francisco Bee:
''The best number to Archies
after the final. ''
I mean in life.
With whom you share your success?
Your hope, your dreams, your fears.
What I do mean nothing
without my wife and children.
I am lonely.
I have never been in love.
This is your chance. Ava, you can expect.
Did she say anything? What then?
You may have a good understand others.
- Does she love me? I said it.
- Not immediately exaggerate.
I feel like I'm apart ga blows.
Do it for love too?
Or are the marshmallows?
You've eaten a whole bag is empty.
Tomorrow you will see a whole new beer.
I think I just go to sleep.
Do not leave. I think this is a bit scary.
Stay with me until I sleep?
I wait until you are asleep.
- Can you leave the light on?
- Good.
I love it here. Good?
Good night.
Give me a holler
if you want a marshmallow.
Attention, Ava.
Here is the all-new Archie.
That feels good.
Can you feel it?
Feel the pain.
Feel the wind.
Feel the cramps.
Come on. Not give up.
I Ol, slit my glutes.
My butt hurts.
Will you massage my ass?
Rub my butt on. Please?
Doc realized that Archie not easily
Or was strong enough for Ava.
But perhaps sweet enough.
- That someone so beautiful can be...
- Why did not you tell?
I do not know.
What is that?
This is Sonny, her boyfriend.
She told me about him.
- But that is a Kodiak bear.
- Do not be discouraged.
For a woman to tempt
you must find out what they like.
- Take my wife.
- No, thank you.
- She likes surprises.
- If you screaming from the bushes jumps?
No, they like romance.
Just what they mean
you always think they are.
Fun, say. And do it all the time?
Previously it.
But lately I have this rather
pressure and is there made the shot.
Candles, fruit, cheese, wine. Perfect.
- What are you doing?
- Hey, baby.
Tonight I heart you.
The children are to the cinema,
the bear is in the forest.
- We are alone.
- All alone.
- Excuse me.
- You can not see me.
I am one with the bank.
I ga coating on each filament. I...
We are not disturbed.
There is nothing like your buddies can see nothing.
Where were we?
You thought you could compensate
that you have neglected me.
I feel resistance. As I had anticipated.
So I just irresistible bass.
- Is this our wedding song?
- Not fair.
The number where you
as Mrs Dolittle on dancing.
- The show will begin.
- Which show?
That is the real.
Really
I'm really in love with Mrs Dolittle
What is he good.
He scratched last on my belly
and my leg was like a raging at once.
- What happens here?
- He is really in love with her.
Give her some garbage.
There are the girls like.
If Dr D something sweet on his lips?
That is very possible.
Ga it, Doc.
He has broken.
Get out. All of them.
- This is not a peepshow.
- But here I learn.
- Really.
- We have it on tomorrow.
- Packed.
- What are you talking about tomorrow?
I was just...
Honey, where were we again go?
Honey...
But you sleep on the couch.
What did she say?
She loves me so much
I can sleep on the couch.
What a guy.
Yes, what a guy.
The guy on the bench.
Romeo is in motion.
His hormones effervescence.
There we go.
Halt.
I wish only the toilet.
Keep it up. I know that trick.
- Hey, baby.
- What is your vote?
You look good.
I might get something sweet in my...
Will Archie...
really
No, huh.
Is that our number?
Hard ground. Back.
You must learn climbing trees. Really.
Yet another bruise.
- Come out, Archie.
- Never.
- So much was it not?
- I have never been geschaamd.
And I got in a tutu
on a unicycle driven.
- We can do what to do.
- I start now my hibernation.
- We make myself a berenpak.
- It is not good.
Good, because otherwise all animals
next week you stay.
No more games.
Externally, large coward.
Who do you call a coward?
Jou. You are a coward,
because you have the courage up.
- It is so difficult.
- Difficult?
My wife and daughter are mad at me
and I leave with a four pizza farm
who always says: Yo Dr D, how you doing?
And now I have a hairy crybaby
listening, which is difficult.
Ava laughed me off.
I love her, but she laughed me off.
You should not Ava.
What do they like you a coward?
- A beer you should not jog.
- Which bear?
If I have a real bear porde,
he would tear me.
- I warn you.
- And I por you.
- Stop it.
- Por, por.
It is enough.
That hurt.
That felt good. Really like beer.
I can not help.
Fuck it to your circus.
A bear?
I am a bear.
I am the alpha bear.
Bears do it''''grr?
What happened to you?
Potter called. He has a proposal.
Listening does not hurt.
- For you, madame.
- Thanks.
- Does Sonny you fish?
- Mostly a hundred.
Hundreds? So much he can not bear.
But he says sometimes
You the most beautiful eyes in the world have?
He promises you a life
full of love, fun and poetry?
Usually he asks when I am drafty.
What a charmer.
Where is it?
- Would you like to walk?
- With you or alone?
- I.
- Fine.
This is not walking but running.
Why should we run?
There was love in the air.
Be a man. Be a man.
Listen here.
Yes, you. This is my house.
Yes, my house.
My house. These are all my houses.
You're a lucky man, you know?
You 're lucky. Not me.
- Would you like me steps?
- Excuse me.
- What are you doing?
- Me? I do nothing.
I go in the correct position.
- You marked my tree.
- No.
I would never do. I do not even know how.
I had plenty of water for drinking. Then I have that.
- It smells like lemonade.
- There's a good point.
Those of you is strong. Net ammonia.
I am even dizzy from.
Come on, let go by.
Are you? Have fun.
You are a nice set together.
What do I hate myself.
- Bears for that basket died.
- Say it if you want.
- There is nothing in.
- I get it for you.
I mean it. That is too dangerous.
Promise you?
- I like you, Ava.
- I think you also fun.
- What are you doing, girls?
- No, Sonny.
Get out, circus clown.
- And you keep your mouth.
- You charm surpasses almost your perfume.
- And what does that mean?
- You are a malodorous nitwit.
What does he do? I do not
and love I do not like.
- That is true.
- Is he there or not used?
- Come. He wants me in daze.
- Do not leave.
I'm not ten, but not with those ga zero.
You found me anyway?
Yes, but you are a city of beer
and I do not have enough.
City Beer. Fine.
- Shall we play cards?
- Sure.
This beer is as much chance
for baby bears for as Riley.
It is not.
But thanks to you I not baad
in the favorable publicity.
This is my proposal.
I leave four acres off
as a reserve for your animal friends.
No one comes to know
you have failed, so you will not.
- Four acres is ridiculous.
- That's my offer.
The deadline is Wednesday at 12 pm.
To send us a twelve
lumberjacks and all our machines.
And Friday is no more tree.
- I need to consult my wife.
- Behind is a phone booth.
Excuse me.
The women discuss.
That is a sign of weakness.
- What are you doing here?
- I know what I should do a final.
- Come in soon.
- Best.
I can not here yet?
It is finished.
Sorry that I got you this question.
I can arrange an audition in Vegas.
They want to negotiate.
You can not give up the courage.
That you have said.
''Let the inner loose bear. ''
Remember?
I know how I can win Ava for me.
I'm mad as a hatter.
Okay, I give you another chance.
- What is it?
- My ice cream comes to top.
- Which ice cream?
- I was so depressed that I went to Sonny devoured.
After a two-liter I knew that I loved Ava
and Cherry Garcia ice cream.
- Not vomiting.
- It is not that way.
- Go to the toilet seat.
- I can not stop.
- First, the lid up.
- That is not big enough.
They did. Sit down.
Ga while I watch.
I do so. I'm busy.
- Who did it?
- I talk to myself.
Sometimes you need to talk it out.
A pep talk for the base pier.
- Oh dear.
- Let me open the window.
Wait until the window is open.
The window is open but a bit.
That is not enough.
You are already started, huh?
It is worse than I thought.
Was it really just ice? I do not believe so.
It is best to. Come on.
Gentlemen. The answer is no.
Thank you for coming.
Was I?
- Can you hear me?
- Cataracts not. I get a complex.
- I try to camouflage.
- Change even color.
- What are you doing again?
- He understands me.
If he understood me, I would say
I baalde of those animals.
If you understand me, I would say
you just had to do to your roses.
- The white Christmas.
- I am sick of this house.
So young and already mad at the world.
That rapmuziek too.
How was it?
- It is not.
- But it's still not Archie?
Archie thinks he knows
Ava for how he can win.
So we continue to sit here?
It is a final walk to the city.
- We collide, huh?
- I want to go home.
Me too, but you're more like.
I am not saying that it is up to you.
Perhaps it is to me.
Your mother thinks you anything about.
- No.
- Sure that nothing is?
Absolutely.
It is fine.
But if something is
then we can talk about.
Fine.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Good.
Because your mother is worried and I...
- Dad?
- Yes?
I knew what it was.
You can talk with me.
Father and daughter. Paid your heart out.
We can cry together as...
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Stop.
It will be the mountain air are. There is nothing.
Is everything okay?
Everything is good.
Please take a moment for yourself.
Fine.
No more posturing. Now brave for Ava.
He goes out the beehive.
- Who?
- Archie.
- Archie, loser.
This rock is much higher than I thought.
Goodbye, endangered species.
Was that your big plan? Come back.
- I must try this, although I keep it.
- The beer is a peer.
- What are you doing?
- Come back. No games.
I do not Ava by worms to eat.
I will never bosbeer such as Sonny.
I have to prove that it is serious.
If you fall, proves the
you stupid and dead.
What happens?
This circus clown has a new trick.
- Silence.
- It is al
This tree holds him never.
And I am the expert.
Not moving.
- Careful.
- Do I buy honey.
Break.
- This was not a good plan.
- Come back.
It is best.
Bees. Damn.
- I talk to them.
- They stabbing.
I see nothing. They stabbing.
- Attacks.
- Stop it.
Defend the hive.
Get him.
- Defend the hive.
- Attacks.
Come back.
- Jumping.
- Insert a salmon.
Ava, I got it for you.
- All right, Archie.
- You got him pulled.
That boy has pit. I like him.
How you get it in your head?
Who would do something now?
Are you crazy?
I had the best basket businesses.
Come on, Ava.
It is nothing between us, but so ga.
- Honey, bear?
- What is it?
- I mean if you still want to honey.
- No, thank you.
Will we have the conservation
the type of talk?
Or you can count to one hundred and tackle me.
Count. Fine.
- He still has too.
- Come on, shut up there.
- I must remain in the open field.
- 1, 2, 10, G, H, P.
- Green, orange, fish...
- Not so fast.
1, 2, 3, 10, five ten.
Hundred.
What happens now?
Papa is back.
What is wrong?
It is Archie.
All backwards.
Make way for the wild animal.
You know the program
As an animal attacks it.
So you know what happens when he attacks.
There is nothing so dangerous
as half dazed bear.
- With these teeth and claws.
- I am Dr Dolittle. What happened?
He has the door open.
We found him in the kitchen.
- Not true.
- Sorry, Dr Dolittle. Very bad for you.
On the side. There is nothing to see.
Keep moving.
I am. What happened?
I was so close.
It was so unexpected.
Who wants to save the forest here?
We have four acres off.
And we call it 't Dolittle reserve.
We are very gold.
If you have the devil...
- Do not think you've won.
- We cut 'the forest, then we are even.
Thanks, folks. That was all.
Has anyone seen what has happened?
There is only one problem. It is a weasel.
- Oh yeah? What has he done?
- No, it really is a weasel.
- Wezel, the doctor is here.
- You mean Mr. Wezel.
- Did you see what happened with the bear?
- The big bear. Of what I saw?
Have you seen something?
If you give me your watch, I will tell you.
You're a weasel.
- It was Potter. I have a witness.
- An animal?
- That can not testify.
- Do you know something better?
A private detective hired.
The trucks are ready.
Archie goes to a zoo.
If you are witnesses,
Riley leaves nothing great.
- What have I got to lose?
- Your good name.
I do not care.
I let those animals not just in the lurch.
It has been against us.
Therefore we ask for an extra week.
Perhaps the plaintiff the animal
in the Betty Ford Clinic for inclusion.
Or the Yogi Bear Clinic.
And if there was malicious?
That is a serious allegation.
Do you have proof?
We have an eyewitness.
Can I just address the court?
- Go ahead.
- We have a witness
who heard a gunshot and saw a truck
the place where it was shot.
Is that a witness in court?
He is not here, because it is...
It is a weasel.
Order.
I know it sounds unlikely,
but I can talk with animals.
I have no objection to
as Dr Dolittle or claimant
eyewitness to the question.
I ask only for a short break
for my camera.
I want a picture as that animal oath.
If the weasel remain anonymous?
We can offer him immunity.
Enough. Dr Dolittle, I does not take walk
my courtroom.
The deadline has passed. Motion dismissed.
Too bad. That I want to see.
Can you tell us what the weasel said?
Come fetch me?
- Sort of.
- What do you mean, ''something''?
I could not prove your story, so...
So what?
They find it too dangerous
you to release them, so...
You're a Mexican circus sold.
I am so sorry.
- Why?
- At all.
I dragged you here,
you gave false hope and have your life ruined.
You got me just one life.
You have taught me what love is.
That does me no longer.
- What are you doing here?
- Mama would not appeal.
We knew that there was little chance.
- You can at least be an artist again.
- I want no more.
- I want Ava.
- I know.
Maybe I do not deserve love.
- Everyone deserves love.
- Exactly. Everyone...
- Charisse, since when?
- A couple of weeks.
First, it was still a bit vague.
But now it is very clear.
- So that was you hidden.
- I did not want to be freak.
You do not freak. Absolutely not.
I was also afraid in the beginning,
but you see it wrong.
- It is good.
- How?
Look at the good things it brings.
- What then?
- Do you see us. The only al
Now I know what I miss. Family.
I will never have.
You must help him.
Can we really do nothing?
And not only him, but all animals.
There are so many.
There are indeed many.
- You provide the courage.
- What can I do?
I am six years.
That is not young for a beaver.
How long we live here now?
Around 100 years we presses forest is already decreasing.
This is a great time.
I've tried, but I can
not alone. You need help.
And believe it or not,
but you have much power.
All expressions for the best
have an animal inside.
Brave as a lion, as strong as an ox.
An eagle eye or rank as a gazelle.
Or smell like a skunk.
Sorry. You know what I mean.
Together we can.
We can not just give up.
Spread the word, from Sicily to SeaWorld:
The trucks come by.
The beaver is right.
Boys, on the side.
If you let it.
Everyone in his place.
Hasta la vista, baby.
Windows closed.
Something I have never seen.
- They do not give milk.
- What?
They are all dry.
- What is it, Anna Belle?
- Tied.
Strike, strike.
- You want some scrambled eggs?
- Strike, strike.
Fetch it, fetch the frisbee. Grab him.
Strike, strike.
Enter here the belt.
All the animals work together. You are so Friday
Ridiculous.
Animals can not organize.
- Then you look.
- All animals are held.
They strike from Texas to Paris.
In Brooklyn, Mexico and Canada.
Maybe gotta anyway
Dolittle to talk.
And me a bunch of animals
leave on the head?
If I can handle the democrats,
can I animals too.
Attacks.
- Opgehoepeld.
- Watch.
- Get out.
- Retreat.
Hup.
Organized.
Two boom Annen on alpha, tango, nine.
Target in sight, the leader.
- Do you want some?
- Bombs go.
- Roger.
- Well done, guys.
The party is not over.
No sudden movements.
Attacks. Opening salvo.
Clot loose. Salvo song two.
Back to base and recharge.
- You have the...
- What?
You've done the door.
- Run.
- I am a lawyer.
- There he is again. Get that kid.
Attacks.
Not my face.
Please, no. Let's talk.
I grab my phone and call Dr. Dolittle.
No crazy things that I little bee in your cannoli.
The number of Dr John Dolittle?
Not Stuart Little. Dolittle.
- Mr. Potter. How are you?
- Can better. Your friends are here.
Do you believe now that they can organize?
I do not know what to believe.
I would best a discussion with the animals
arrange for the problems to talk.
That is the only way to here
to arrive without any sounds.
I think all good, as you call them back.
Well. Enter the raccoon on.
He wants you to speak. Keep it short.
Everything under control. I still call.
I'm intermediary
for negotiations between Potter
and Members
of the federal forest department 534.
About the order of the day.
This is my new proposal.
What are the conditions? How much land?
It is only 4. 5 hectare.
- I have 4. 5 in the claws.
- They feel good.
I'll just give what you find.
That means''no''.
Or''no''to my never.
The strike continued.
Even the pros did it.
The last riders appear
the starthek.
The Derby starts.
The doors close and they go.
thick beet
we do not
Walk the stupid race yourself.
- Run a mile.
- And by that whip.
Ladies and gentlemen, Shamu.
Here is Shamu.
I do not want to jump. You?
I do not. I've just eaten.
Mr. Potter, we have a deal?
- All right, Doc.
- Is he all mine.
Vive le bear. Vive le Archie.
Vive le docteur.
- Come to the big bear.
- Nothing of it.
I am not for you I've had in the claws.
- Moment, then.
- Come on.
You broke my spine.
Drive gently. Belt.
Archie, are you in?
I came to say goodbye.
- Thanks for everything.
- Sure.
Archie, I'm ready.
It is drafty.
Sorry, just to save the species.
Do your best, Archie.
It was the summer did.
- What are you doing?
- What I do?
Let me put it this way.
You too?
Charisse and Doc were thick with each other.
No worries. You learn it well.
I can not turn.
My verkleurder is broken.
You learn it to discolor.
How? Pepito can not understand.
Pepito is pet.
Look. I fall not.
- I am invisible.
- Yes.
- Good.
- Who would ever doubt?
The large verkleurder is back.
King of the Third World.
May the whole house in that color?
It is very feng shui.
But the best news
then came the spring.
Come on, kids.
Here.
Step, step, spin, kick, step.
Papa, it was still
step, kick, spin, step, step?
Come on. The premiere is about six weeks.
- You could hack it.
- We are just to play.
From the chorus.
I have never been a dull party.
You do so stiff. Come on, polonaise.
Are they real?
The party can begin. Come on.
What a party, what a party.
From your roof. By the ribbon.
Can you see me?
Fixed not. I am invisible.
Sure does. I see you both.
I know a place on the Seine
where the naked monkeys deinen
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org