Don't tell me
about my visa.
My wife is stuck in that hellhole,
and I am getting on that plane.
It's bad,Joe.
They're evacuating the villages.
The roads are washed out.
We're hearing gunfire now.
Can you-
Can you get to Calamar?
Can you get across the border
to Colombia?
They're putting us on the bus.
I don't know where they're taking us.
Joe? Joe?
Emily! Em-
Emily Darrow was not
just a doctor...
and a credit
to the medical profession...
she was a healer
and a credit to the human race.
Those who knew her
were changed by her...
inspired by her commitment
to give...
literally everything
of herself...
which is why
we're gathered here today-
to celebrate
this unique life...
not so much taken from us...
as given to us.
From her colleagues
at the university...
to her young patients here...
in Chicago Memorial's
pediatric oncology ward...
she will be sorely missed.
We're told in medical school that
the face of an emergency room doctor...
is the last thing a lot
of people will ever see.
I've tried to keep that in mind when I
see those frightened eyes staring out at me.
But I don't know
what Emily saw.
What image she took with her.
If there was
a compassionate face...
or she died
in a world of chaos.
And that I don't know this...
haunts me.
The divers saw inside, señor.
There is no one alive.
Then where is she?
Where's her body?
We are searching the shoreline
and jungle now...
but the bus is
under ten feet of water.
The river runs at 17 miles
an hour, señor.
There is nothing
you can do.
Por favor, go home.
I'm not going anywhere.
Not till this is over.
I assure you, señor,
it's over.
No vitals, no pulse.
Put him in E.R. Three on the left.
What are you doing here?
I was paged.
What do we have? Wasn't this morning
your wife's memorial service?
There's nothing I can do for her, okay?
Except keep anyone from joining her.
Now, what do we have?
Six-car pileup.
Eleven injuries. Four went over to County
and six are coming here.
All right, let's go.
Stay with me. How extensive?
Third degree. Forty percent, maybe 50.
Did you tube him?
- Airway's crushed. Couldn't do a cryc.
- Pronounce him.
- Hit the windshield.
- All right, that's a blowout fracture.
Get a C.T. Find out
what else he's got.
What's this?
O.D. Attempted suicide.
Give her to Simon. I'm interested in
people who want to live tonight.
- What's her term?
- She hit the steering wheel.
- How pregnant? Anybody know?
- She looks no more than six months to me.
- She's souring. Let's get it out.
- At six months?
It might have a chance, but
not in there. Look at her color.
It's still got a heartbeat.
Let's get it out of there.
- This requires consultation- - Yeah, and let's
order out for pizza while we're at it. Move.
There's a procedure in place
for terminating a pregnancy, Joe.
I'm not terminating a
pregnancy. I'm delivering a baby.
Get Prenatal
down here now.
It was the right call.
Delivering a technically unviable
fetus by Caesarean section...
without consultation
or permission of the mother-
Who was dead.
Not officially.
The baby's alive, Hugh.
I'm concerned, Joe.
So is the rest of the staff.
You refused to treat a suicide
today. I passed her on to Simon.
As though she were
unworthy of you.
Can we discuss this
tomorrow?
Since Emily's death, you have
been working around the clock...
24-hour shifts, I'm told,
seven days a week.
Think I'm losing my edge? Just the
opposite. It's getting too sharp.
You're starting to cut people
around here. You need time off.
You need to grieve.
I need to grieve?
Mm-hmm.
I am serious, Joe.
Take that time off.
Was it you
who reported me?
Passing on the suicide?
How is she doing?
She's waiting for a bed
on the psych ward.
- Why did you do this to me?
- Do what to you?
Bring me back.
Where were you going?
Someplace better.
Is that right?
I'll do it again too.
It's all I want now.
Well, unfortunately,
your heart disagrees.
It's waged quite
a battle tonight.
No one knows my heart.
Maybe that's why
it's still beating-
to give somebody
a chance to.
Let me tell you about that better
place you think you're going to.
You better be
damn sure it's there.
'Cause crappy as this
place is, it's all there is.
So go ahead.
Be my guest.
But when you never wake up again,
don't say I didn't warn you.
Hi, Father.
Time for a rebuttal?
'And on her footfall,
in rustle of leaves...
"her whisper on the wind...
she speaks from a place
beyond mortal pain. "
Hey, look who's here.
Joe!
Hey, you! You're just in
time to finish the toast.
Pour him a beer. Linda, can
I have another one, please?
Hey, Joe, "Rachel in Heaven" Remember
that poem, third-year lit class?
Remember? Yeah. To Emily.
To Emily.
How are things
in the hospital?
I don't know why we try
so hard to save them...
if they've got such a
wonderful place to go...
like "Rachel in Heaven. "
That's where Emily is.
You can bet on that.
If anyone deserved
to go there, it was her.
Hear, hear. She was the
best of us. The best of us.
I don't know what the hell
she saw in you, though.
Lord knows I tried for
years to talk her out of it.
She was the best of us. And I
have no idea what she saw in me.
She saw the second best of
us. You were a great team.
She was the heart, you were the
mind. Together, you were unbeatable.
Where are you, Joe?
Nowhere.
I'm gonna go.
No, come on, man.
You just got here.
Like you said, Eric, I'm
a mind without a heart.
Joe, come on.
Joe, that's not-
Don't leave, Joe.
Buddy, that is not what I
meant. I know you didn't mean it.
But you were right on, buddy.
I love you anyway.
All of you.
Thank you
for coming today.
See ya.
Hey, Doc.
Hey, Miriam.
Sorry I missed the service. I didn't
want to cough all over everybody.
Was it nice?
I guess.
I couldn't handle it.
Well, then you're not
gonna do too good with this.
They needed somebody to sign for it. I
didn't want to leave it out in the rain.
It's a toy company
in Texas.
That'll teach her
to shop the Internet.
Yeah, that'll teach her.
You'd think a professor of law could
be more precise with her language.
It's all right.
You have a good night.
Hey, I saw through the kitchen
window Big Bird didn't eat again.
- Should he go back to the vet?
- The vet said Big Bird will outlive us all.
Hey,Joe, it's Hal.
I forgot to tell you we are
going on that white-water trip.
Gotta come,Joe! Don't leave
me alone with these guys!
I sent you a packet, okay?
See ya, buddy! Love you!
Sound good, Big Bird?
You wanna go rafting
with my old college chums?
Nice to see you too.
Why is that funny?
I just don't picture you
with a beak, I guess.
All right. Well, just imagine soaring
around with me up there, flying.
If you do, you're on your own. Why?
Because eagles eat bunny
rabbits. I'm a vegetarian.
In your next life too?
Yes.
You mean, if you got a chance to come
back, you'd want to be earthbound again?
No. I'll fly around
with you up there.
But you know what
I'm gonna be.
Yeah, but...
if I'm a bird and
you're an insect, Yeah?
how are we gonna-
You know.
We'll just have to do enough
of that in this lifetime...
to make up
for the next ten.
I'm going
because I have to,Joe.
Because it's who I am,
who we are...
what we dedicated
our lives to.
For God sakes, Emily, you're
pregnant. We addressed this, Joe...
when we first met...
that we'd pack our kids in
on our backs if we had to...
to show them what was important,
to teach them our values.
It was naive, Emily,
all right? It was naive.
Our values?
I'm needed there, Joe...
and I'm going.
Whether you choose to
or not.
So this thing was a paperweight? Yes.
It was a present I gave her
for Valentine's Day.
Got to weigh half a pound, and
it was squarely- I mean squarely-
on the bedside table
when I went to sleep.
So what are you saying?
I don't know.
Nothing, I guess.
Just that...
dragonflies were sort of her thing,
you know, like a personal totem.
How Indians have buffalo heads
or tiger heads or hawks...
hers was a dragonfly.
She even had this small birthmark on her
shoulder that kind of looked like one.
Said her grandfather
had one too...
on his-
on his butt, I think.
It's called
familial hemangioma.
I once skunked
an entire graduating class...
by putting it
on a final exam.
When she was alive, I had to
scour for anything I could find...
with a dragonfly on it
to buy her a present.
Now? Now I see 'em
everywhere.
There was one
- There was one bouncing against my office window yesterday.
A real one.
Last night a package arrived. She
had bought over the Internet...
a mobile to put on
the baby's crib...
of dragonflies.
And then this thing last night
with the paperweight.
You know what I think?
I think you are literally going
buggy living in that house.
Yeah, you should move. You're
rummaging around in an empty nursery.
You're living with a talking
parrot who won't even speak to you.
Never would.
Never liked me.
Would only talk
to Emily.
She even taught it to announce her
arrival when she came in the door.
"Honey.
Honey, I'm home. "
You ought to sell that
thing, Joe. Get rid of it.
Stuck with it.
I promised her I'd keep it forever,
and I'd put a provision in my will...
that if anything ever happened to me,
someone I trusted would take care of it.
Would you?
Oh, no. It's your promise,
buddy. It's not mine.
I need to live up to
my promises to her.
That's one thing I
need to do. Okay, fine.
Any other promises
that I should know about?
Just one, but I'm taking care
of that one myself, starting...
today.
Hi, Joe.
Hugh.
- I was kind of hoping you took our conversation seriously.
- I did.
I convinced Joe to take a couple of
months off, with all that's happened.
- Right,Joe?
- I promised Emily I'd look in on her kids...
on the oncology ward while she was gone
- I never did.
I thought this might be
a good day.
After six months?
On oncology?
I'm not sure how many are left,
but if it's for Emily, fine.
Asshole. You should get away, Joe.
Isn't there someplace
you can go?
Joe!
Joe, can't you hear me?
- All right. Hold C.P.R.
- I'm getting nothing.
Continue it. Shock him
at 30. Let me in there.
Come on, Jeffrey. Hang in
there. Clear. Keep it going.
Still nothing.
Charging to 60.
Shock him.
Clear.
- Nothing. - Go again.
- He's not responding.
I said again.
There's no pulse at all.
- He's not coming back this time.
- Damn it, do it again!
Clear!
He's gone.
He's got a rhythm.
- He's back! Jump on it!
- He's coming back!
Yes, Jeffrey, yes!
Do you need to be here?
Put that O-2 mask on him. Clear
the room, please. Get me an E.K.G.
You'll have to leave. Don't let
him pull out that I.V. Jeffrey.
Jeffrey, can you hear me?
Ah, pupils reactive.
I just came on.
What happened?
They're stabilizing him.
He flat-lined,
and his heart started again.
That's our Jeffrey. His heart stopped more
times than anyone in the history of science.
He'll come out of there with all kinds of
stories about who he met in the tunnel...
and what they said.
Hi, I'm Dr. Darrow
from Emergency.
I know who you are.
The hospital administrator heard that
you got in the way in I.C.U. yesterday...
and asked to be notified
if you came back here again.
Did the boy who was being
resuscitated last night-
Jeffrey-
Reardon.
Right. Is he-
Is he still on the floor?
Mm-hmm. He was one of
your wife's favorites.
Actually,
that's why I'm here.
I promised I'd look in on her kids,
but there don't seem to be many left.
Be great if you could give
me a little help, maybe not...
put in that call to
the hospital administrator.
Between you and me, Doctor,
the hospital administrator is-
how do I put it-
I use the word "asshole. "
That about captures it.
Three-one-five.
He's a real trip.
You'll love him.
Thanks.
- Hello.
- Hi.
How's he doing?
Great.
Nice.
What is it?
I couldn't say.
Guess.
All right.
Crucifix made of Jell-O?
Man, you're good.
He's good.
He hasn't stopped drawing them since
he got out of the I.C.U. yesterday.
So what is it?
I don't know.
That's why I'm asking.
Just woke up
thinking about it.
I happened to be in the
I.C.U. yesterday, Jeffrey.
I know.
I saw you in there.
You saw me in there?
Yeah. You came in through the back
of the room standing over my bed.
You saw me
come over to your bed?
Pretty sure it was you.
But the tie was different.
Jeffrey!
Could I ask-
We're not encouraged
to discuss these things.
There was a nun on the ward interviewing
kids who'd had near-death experiences.
Sister Madeline
from Chaplain Services.
Stirred up all kinds of trouble for
the hospital when some of it appeared...
on a TV tabloid show.
She never even
talked to me...
and I've got the best
near-death experiences of anyone.
I'm allowed a coffee break
if there's a doctor with him.
In spite of hospital policy, I
think they need to talk about it.
You're scheduled for a CAT scan,
Jeffrey. Don't go without me.
So what are we talking
about here, Jeffrey?
What we shouldn't.
In the I.C.U. yesterday,
when I approached your bed...
it seemed to me
you were pretty-
- I was flat-lined.
- Exactly.
So how could you look
up and see me? Couldn't.
- But you said-
- I looked down.
You looked down?
From the ceiling. That's
where I was when I saw you.
Okay.
Don't believe me?
Should I?
Ever see that little
bald spot on top of your head?
Bend down here.
Come on.
Yeah, that was you.
Jeffrey,
do you know my name?
You look like a-
a William to me.
I'm a Joe.
Does it ring a bell?
Emily's Joe?
Joe Darrow.
I saw her yesterday too.
What do you mean,
Jeffrey, you saw her?
She was there.
Where?
All around me.
Inside the rainbow.
The mist.
I was falling...
falling through it...
until she caught me...
then brought me
back up.
She kind of flew me.
She flew me out...
so I could come back...
and tell somebody something.
Tell what, Jeffrey?
To who?
Joe.
Tell me what, Jeffrey?
Tell Joe what?
It was loud in the rainbow...
like thunder in there.
- Tell me what, Jeffrey?
- I don't know.
You were calling my name.
Joe.
Joe!
Joe, can't you hear me?
All right, Jeffrey.
Joe! Joe!
Jeffrey, slow down.
Whoa, whoa.
Look at my eyes.
Just breathe.
Just breathe
a little bit, okay?
What happened?
I'm fine.
We were-
He wanted to know
what happened yesterday.
His heart stopped again.
I know.
- I was there, actually.
- He wanted to know what happened...
while it was stopped.
Oh. Telling one of
his tall tales again.
Trying to get on TV.
I'm gonna give him a dust mop next time so
he can sweep the ceiling while he's up there.
My daddy don't believe me.
He do the "bald spot"
on you?
It don't work
on everybody.
Just us bald guys, huh? Phew!
Yeah, he got me with that one too.
You had me going there,
Jeffrey. It was the truth.
You don't believe me?
What if I do remember what
she wants to tell you...
then would you believe me?
Do you remember it?
If you come back, I might.
What who wants to tell him?
His wife. She wants me
to tell him something.
Probably to take
out the trash, huh?
What?
He even had me believing
he saw my bald spot...
from the ceiling, till I
saw a mirror behind my head.
We can thank Mom for those
genes, right, Dad?
I hate to burst your bubble, Joe, but
I can see your bald spot from here.
I think bald is sexy.
Really?
Yes.
I've got a parrot
that might turn you on.
Are you still living with
that messy thing? Joe!
We're working on our relationship.
Is it a talking parrot?
A listening parrot.
A bird after my own heart. That's
what I do for a living: listen.
Really?
Gwyn's a grief counselor, Joe. That's why I
thought it might be a good idea for you to meet.
Is that right?
I've heard a lot of clients talk about the
near-death experiences of their loved ones-
how they'd wake up talking
about being in a dark tunnel...
moving toward the light.
And what's
your thought on it?
I'm just your parrot,
Joe. Just listening.
I can tell you as an eye
surgeon, it's all very simple.
The tunnel is
literal tunnel vision.
And the white light is the gradual
bleaching out of the optic screen.
As it grows bigger, it would
seem like you're moving toward it.
How do you explain their ability
to recall what everyone said...
around their deathbed after
they were declared dead-
to describe what
the doctors were wearing...
down to the patterns
on their ties?
It's the way
we measure death.
Obviously the brain is still
functioning on some subliminal level...
soaking up all the last bits
of what's left to hear and see.
That's what you get for having
dinner with a family of doctors-
no discussion about floating
around on the ceiling;
no tunnel;
no bright lights.
Next thing, they're gonna
tell us there's no tooth fairy.
Funny thing is, I thought I
heard him calling out for me.
This kid.
I heard his voice
calling 'Joe. "
And when I introduced myself to him,
he asked me if I was Emily's Joe.
Said that Emily
was trying to reach me.
Do you believe she's
trying to reach you, Joe?
No, Counselor, I don't.
I can give you
an hour for free.
Bye, Joe. You want me to
package up dessert for you?
Sorry.
Use your phone?
Excuse me.
I am kind of busy
at the moment, yeah.
Well, isn't there anyone else
who can cover for me tonight?
All right. I understand.
I'll be right over.
I'm sorry. I'd really like
to stay. No, you wouldn't.
It's too threatening.
It's about unresolved issues
you're not ready to deal with yet-
guilt, anger
toward our loved ones-
that's why
we conjure up spirits-
from the Virgin Mary
to our dearly departed-
because we need to talk to
them, not the other way around.
You asked if I thought she was trying
to contact me, and I never answered.
Let me answer now.
She was my
ultimate partner...
my best friend and lover,
and I miss her beyond belief.
I also know I'm never
gonna see her again.
Not ever.
And I'm just beginning to understand
what that means so intensely...
that I sometimes wish that I
didn't have to wake up anymore.
And the last thing I need is
someone telling me what to feel...
or how to feel.
Anger, yeah.
Guilt, you bet.
But I don't need you crawling up my ass
with a flashlight to tell me about it.
Keep going, Joe.
This is what you need.
I'll drop you
a check in the mail.
Hi.
Hey.
What's your name?
Ben.
I'm Joe, Ben.
I know.
Just admiring your artwork.
What is it?
She said you should
go there.
I'm sorry?
The lady. The lady in
the picture down the hall.
She said you'd...
be coming to see me.
- The nurse?
- They said she was a doctor here.
What doctor?
- She wants you to go there.
- Go where?
I'm not
- I'm not sure what you mean, Ben.
Go where?
I dreamed of her...
in the ambulance
when I came here.
Then... I saw
her picture in the hall.
You know,
the lady doctor?
In the picture of the Easter
party, with the cake on her nose?
Are you talking
about Dr. Darrow?
She died, I guess.
And you dreamed of her?
She wants you
to go there.
Go where, Ben?
The rainbow.
That's a rainbow?
This-
This is a rainbow?
Have we met before, Ben?
I don't know.
How do you know
who I am?
She showed me your face.
In a picture?
In my mind.
She said
I have to come back...
to tell you to go there.
To a rainbow?
Yes.
Well, how would I-
How would I do that, Ben?
Christine, the boy in 312
- Ben?
Yes.
Did he know my wife?
I don't think so. I think he
just came in two weeks ago.
Yeah. On the third in
a coma. Septic shock.
Why, Joe?
Nothing.
Miriam-
The first kid,
he calls my name...
I follow him in
to the I.C.U...
where he flat-lines,
dies.
Then when he's resuscitated, says he saw
me while he's floating around the ceiling.
And that Emily-
who he met in a rainbow-
sent him back
to tell me something.
Tell you what?
He doesn't remember.
But the next kid does.
You want jelly?
I got two kinds.
Are you taking me seriously?
Yes. Is strawberry okay?
What does it matter? Do you
- Do you hear what I'm telling you?
I'm just trying to focus
on something real here, Joe.
And you think this isn't?
Doesn't sound it so far.
Listen to me, Joe.
After Hannah died, I-
I saw her everywhere.
She told me I know
she was watching over me...
if I saw a daisy growing out of the ground
with all the petals missing except one.
We used to play "She Loves
Me, She Loves Me Not. "
And one day, I saw an entire
field of one-petaled daisies.
Well, there you go.
How do you explain that?
I was delusional.
Well, I'm not, okay?
I had these conversations.
Aren't you the guy that
doesn't believe in heaven?
This isn't heaven.
This is rainbows.
Oh. And she wants you to
join her inside a rainbow?
According to these kids,
that's accurate.
Well, according to me,
they're putting you on.
So you think they're
lying. I'm a lawyer, Joe.
Nothing is real
without evidence.
Have you personally had any
experience with Emily since her death?
And if so,
has it been documented?
- You know the answer. Of course I haven't.
- And why haven't you?
Because I haven't gone
halfway to heaven...
and she has no way
of reaching me.
It does sound nuts,
doesn't it?
Well, I wouldn't employ you
in my hospital if I heard that.
And if I were you,
I'd stay away from there.
Isn't there somewhere
you can go?
I could go
on a white-water trip.
Just what I've always
wanted to see-
white water. I'll take care of Big Bird.
Get out of here.
Go see white water...
and get your head straight.
Wanna see?
They were the last thing
she sent us.
Hmm.
Sorry to break it
to you, pal, but, uh...
she was cheatin' on ya.
It's just a bug, Big Bird.
Attracted to the light.
Let's not get crazy here.
Honey, I'm home.
Big Bird!
Big Bird, no!
Hello?
Miriam?
Joe?
Miriam, listen to me.
The bird, it's sick.
I had to leave it. I'm
on my way to the hospital.
- Are you okay?
- Actually, I'm not.
I feel-
I feel like
I'm losing my mind.
What can I do?
It was acting like it used
to when she'd come home.
I felt like she was there...
in the house.
Jesus, Joe.
I don't know what to do about the
- The bird?
I'll take care of it.
I'll wake up the vet
if I have to.
You just...
hang in there, okay?
All right. Thanks.
Is Jeffrey awake? Not
a good idea right now.
Is he in his room? Visiting
hours aren't until 10.:00,Joe.
Joe!
Joe.
Joe, there was some talk around
here I think you should know about.
Where is he?
Jeffrey?
He's downstairs getting blood
work, but can I tell you what I-
His nurse
- Is she with him? Would you just listen to me for a minute?
She said there was
a nun on the ward...
interviewing kids about
near-death experiences.
Sister Madeline. Do
you know where she is?
She's no longer
employed here,Joe.
And you know why?
Because she overstepped
her bounds.
Where is she employed?
Would- Would
Chaplain Services know?
Could you leave us
alone for a minute?
What are you doing,
Joe?
You know what I'm doing.
You gave me permission-
To look in on Emily's kids. That was
two days ago, and you haven't left since.
I told you,
I promised my wife.
That you'd upset them?
Jeffrey's cardiologist saw the readout on
his E.K.G. from 2:30 yesterday afternoon...
and he was damned upset
that your visit...
put him under
that kind of stress.
What is going on, Joe?
The bird's okay.
He will outlive us all.
I tried to clean up
some of the mess in there-
overturned lamp,
broken vase.
You didn't have to
do all that.
I didn't do all that.
I left some of it...
to discuss with you.
That weird picture you told
me the kids were drawing?
The wiggly cross?
Is it the kids
drawing it,Joe?
Or is it you?
'Cause if you did this,
you need some help.
It's all over
the windows too.
Watch the bird for me,
will you?
Excuse me.
Excuse me. I'm looking for
Sister Madeline. Is that-
May I ask what this is about?
It's personal. Is that her?
- You'll have to call the office for an appointment.
- Excuse me!
- Sir. Sir!
- Sister Madeline?
Sister Madeline,
could I speak to you?
Sir! Please. Sister Madeline?
Please,
are you Sis-
Please.
Are you Sister Madeline?
This is private property.
You are trespassing.
I know, I tried to call.
I'm sorry.
Chaplain Services only
gave me an address.
He'll call the police.
Please-
Just five minutes.
You people have done
enough damage.
- You don't understand.
- You don't.
No more journalists.
No more interviews.
I'm not a journalist.
I'm a- I'm a doctor.
Head of Emergency Services...
at Chicago
Memorial Hospital.
Joe Darrow.
Emily's Joe.
Yes.
That's why I need
to talk to you.
I need to know
about your work.
I've called the police.
I'd advise you to leave.
It's all right. He's not a
journalist. He's still trespassing.
I'm sorry. We agreed to
hire Sister Madeline...
with the understanding that her presence
here wouldn't cause any disturbances.
Sister.
Yes, sir.
The police respond quickly.
I'd advise you to leave.
Do you have business
at the school, sir?
Beg your pardon? Step over here, please.
And I realized that in an age
where no one believes...
in miracles anymore, I was
witnessing miracles every day.
And the pediatric
oncology ward...
was the perfect laboratory
to study it-
the near-death experience.
Being kids, they were
more open to what happens...
on the other side.
You're convinced it's not
just in their minds?
Just in their minds?
What we're experiencing right
now could be just in your mind.
You're a doctor
because you dreamed...
of being one, right?
You imagined that...
for yourself.
If we can create this world
with what we imagine...
why not the next?
S- So you're saying,
belief-
Gets us there.
Did Emily believe?
Because I think
she got there.
I believe she's trying
to contact me.
Two kids have seen her.
One was flat-lined,
another in a coma.
In the tunnel?
In a rainbow.
Trying to tell me something,
something urgent.
But I don't know what.
And they- they-
they draw this...
after they've-
after they've seen her.
Have you ever seen
this before?
No.
I don't know.
Am I-
Am I just going nuts?
As nuts
as Christopher Columbus...
thinking there was
another side to the earth.
Talk to an anesthesiologist.
They'll tell you.
There are a hundred steps on
the ladder of consciousness...
between being
fully alert...
and being dead.
To put a patient under,
they bring them down...
only to the tenth rung.
Beneath that is
a descending gray scale...
like the depths
of an ocean...
no one has explored.
It's in those depths,
those murky depths...
she's finding them-
the children.
They're her conduit,
because she knew...
you'd find your way
to them.
Stay close to them.
Be with them when they slip away
so you can be with them...
when they first awaken,
before the details fade.
One of them...
will come back
with the answer.
Careful. Careful.
Okay, let's go. Sit back!
Release forms.
I'll get it.
- Where is it? - Down the right.
- Careful with the transfer.
Watch your line here. Keep
it pumping. Right here.
Hook him up to the ventilator when
you get inside. I'll get the monitor.
This is Jeanette in Nephrology. I
need to speak to Dr. Dickinson, please.
Monitors are ready.
Dr. Darrow!
Yes, it is an emergency.
No, I can't hold. Keep me
on the line. Dr. Dickinson.
We've got a healthy kidney
up here. Just Dr. Darrow.
Joe.
Yeah. Joe, I'm on my way
over to harvest a kidney...
and I want you to protect it
for me. Tell me what to do.
All right. They're coming in for
other organs, but that kidney is mine.
I want that made clear in case anybody
choppers in and tries to grab it.
Stay on top of his vitals. Don't leave
the room and hold off the vultures.
I don't want anybody cutting until
I get there. Consider it done.
Put Jeanette back on the phone,
buddy. I'm ten minutes away.
Jeanette.
Yes, sir.
- You're Dickinson?
- Darrow.
They told me not to leave him, but I gotta
get this monitor over to the recipient.
I'll keep watch
in here.
Ventilator's set at 16. That
oughta keep the organs fresh.
Joe.
Come closer.
Dear God.
- We're from Lakeview. What room's the donor in?
- 215.
- Double doors on the right.
- Call air support. I'll be right up.
Guys, we're gonna have to-
We're from Lakeview in Lansing. We have
a heart recipient prepped and ready to go.
You're not supposed to be
in here. Are you Dickinson?
Get out.
Just get out, please.
- Hey, take it easy, Doctor.
- Get him out of here, all right?
Get everyone out. Dickinson said
- No, it's okay, Joe.
Dickinson's in the parking
structure. I just spoke to him.
He said let's move 'em
both into surgery. Let's go.
Wait, okay?
Hey, Joe.
It's all right. It's not all
right. He's not ready to be moved.
Hey, what are we waiting for?
Come on. Move him out.
Charlie, wait a second.
What?
This man's not dead.
The brain scan jumped.
I saw it.
I saw it on the monitor.
Come on, Joe. It's flat as a pancake.
Come on. Move him out of here.
Come on. Let's go.
Charlie, listen.
Charlie, there's something
going on. Don't do this yet.
Don't kill this man. Get ahold
of yourself. This man is dead.
He spoke to me. I'm
telling you. Joe, please.
Joe, this man did not
speak to you. It was Emily!
It was her voice. I am
not crazy. You back off.
Don't talk like this.
You've gotta-
You've gotta listen to me.
Charlie, just hold off.
For one minute. Leave me alone
with him. This is nuts, Joe.
- Come on. Get him inside!
- Hey! Easy! Easy!
Back off, man!
Get him inside!
- Somebody get Security!
- Get him out of here!
- For God's sake, Joe!
- Get Security, will you?
Charlie, one fucking
minute. Get him outta here!
Joe! We need Security
in two south right away.
Please, listen to me!
All right.
We're going down.
Thanks for coming down.
You posted bail? First
offense. Got it waived.
I also spoke to the hospital administrator
who's willing to drop all charges...
if you'll agree to take a
lengthy sabbatical. I'll bet.
He said you claimed a brain-dead
organ donor spoke to you. Is that true?
No.
Good.
It was Emily.
Speaking through him.
You know, I could almost understand it
with the kids, because they all knew her.
Of course they're gonna dream about
her. She was key to their survival.
Okay, then how about the kid
who never even laid eyes on her?
What kid? The kid I told
you about in the kitchen.
The first time he ever met her
was in a coma, Miriam. Remember?
I've got his admission records
to prove it.
That's evidence, right?
Isn't that what you wanted?
She's trying to reach me,
and she's becoming desperate.
Why?
Why desperate, Joe?
Oh, you don't think
she's still alive.
If a kid could see her
in a coma, then why...
couldn't she be trying to
communicate from one?
There were no survivors. The Venezuelan
government searched the jungle for a month.
And never found her! Exactly.
And that's why we're here tonight-
because you never saw her body
and never got closure.
Emily's dead, Joe.
That's what
this is all about-
your refusal
to accept that.
Look.
I understand it.
If I hadn't seen Hannah's body, I
wouldn't have believed it either.
I'd still be waiting for her
to come home, just like you are.
You have to
end this, Joe.
You gotta do the hard stuff, like I did.
Like everyone does.
You gotta clean out the
closets, empty the drawers...
and take down the vacancy sign that
says "Emily's ghost is welcome here"...
and get on with your life
without her.
All right.
What about
that rafting trip?
What do you mean,
what about it?
Well, anything to get
your mind off of this.
So, you think
I should go?
Maybe I'll go
with you. Huh?
I'm mean with a paddle.
The river's up
this time of year.
It's gone from a two-point
difficulty to a five.
I want us all to go home,
go over our river maps.
Note the hazard points,
the portages, the waterfalls.
Oh, check out these safari
pants. It says to pack light.
I'm just bringing my thong. Well,
then, I'm bringing my camera.
Well, it better be disposable, because it's
likely everything is going into the drink.
Speaking of drink,
here's to adventure.
Yeah!
Adventure.
What do you think?
I think it's an idea
whose time has come.
No, I mean- I mean,
do you think it'll sell?
The agent said
it needed a paint job.
Oh, get what you can
and get out.
Leave the memories behind.
You didn't after Hannah died.
Yeah, but I didn't have corpses
playing ventriloquist with me either.
I'm gonna miss you, Joe.
I'm gonna
miss your waffles.
Would you show it for me
if I'm gone for a week?
- I'm taking that white-water trip.
- With pleasure.
It's good to see you
joining the world again.
Hello. Hal. Reading
the map of the river...
there's a symbol
- two wavery lines that crisscross in the middle.
Waterfalls. Put a big red circle around
those. We'll have to portage there.
They're too high
this time of year.
Joe?
A rainbow.
You are, uh, the doctor? Yes.
Muy bien.
Is my pilot here?
That is me. Eh, Victor.
¿Cómo te vas?
I take you bags. You
been flying long, Victor?
Don't worry.
I know how.
You have a license, though, right? ;Sí.
Pretty much.
Juanajuapa.
Juanajuapa,
you've been there?
Sí, Juanajuapa.
This is it, right?
With the waterfall?
I don't know. I've only
been there in the dry season.
Is my interpreter here? The
Yanomami speak a little Spanish.
I speak a little Guaharibo.
You talk to them
through me.
Okay, we go.
Is that your girlfriend?
In the picture?
It's my wife.
Used to be.
You come
to get her back, eh?
In a way, I guess.
There was an accident
here last spring.
A bus? That washed away on a road?
La Cruz Roja. The Red
Cross. Yes, that's right.
You can probably see it now
that the river's not so high.
It's just up ahead.
It's on the way.
The rock slide took more
than just a bus.
It isolated an entire tribe
from the outside world.
Can you see it
down there?
Nobody lived.
The Yanomami are still wearing
some of their clothing.
That's Juanajuapa
up ahead.
Some of the bodies
washed out of the bus...
down the river
and right into the village.
The guides we are meeting...
they work with all
the tribes in the area.
Did I mention
they don't like outsiders?
It's a good thing
you have me with you.
He said he cannot take you
to the village.
But, for a price, he can
take you to their graves.
Señor.
We should go.
They, uh...
they wouldn't know,
would they, which, uh...
body was buried where?
Look. If-
If the weather gets...
any worse,
we don't get outta here.
And- And that's
no good for nobody.
Señors.
Señors, uh...
my wife.
Su esposa.
Mi esposa.
Red Cross.
- La Cruz Roja.
- Cruz Roja. Where?
¿Dónde?
Does any-
Does anybody know where?
Which one?
- What are they saying?
- They say they know her.
What's he saying now? He says he
wants to take you to the village.
And he says that, no,
you need permission.
- What is he saying?
What the hell is he saying?
I- I don't know!
Señor!
Señor, you cannot go into the
village! It is forbidden, señor!
Señor! Señor, stop!
Señor, we can return
with government people...
but you must come back
with me now.
I said now, señor!
No, no, no, no jump!
She wants you to go there.
Joe.
- Join her.
- Joe! - Joe!
Joe, can't you hear me?
Joe?
A hundred steps on the ladder
of consciousness. Go there.
No survivors.
Where's her body?
Think she's still alive.
- Emily!
- Joe?
- Listen to me!
You are one crazy son of
a bitch, you know that?
You are lucky to be alive,
señor. You were not breathing.
It's been over an hour.
Get up.
We will cross the river
downstream.
And with a little bit of luck, we can
get to the airstrip before nightfall.
Vamonos. She lived
through the bus accident.
She made it
to the village.
No, you cannot
go to the village!
Stop! I cannot go back without
you! They'll take away my license!
Stop, señor!
Señor! Señor, stop!
Don't do this!
Señor!
The man said
we must have permission.
I've got permission.
No one's keeping me
out of there.
Please. My wife.
Did you know her?
Mi- Mi esposa.
Mi esposa.
Doctore.
Doctore. Mi esposa.
Mi esposa.
The waterfall.
She was here.
She say
they knew her alive.
She came to help them...
until the river
brought her back...
dying.
They could not save
her body...
but they save her soul.
She said, "dragonfly. "
I don't know if Emily
ever saw her...
at least while she was
of mind and body.
And I don't know how the
baby survived- premature-
so small and fragile
in the middle of the jungle.
What I do know is that Emily made sure
our child found her way into my arms.
What she taught me in life,
she taught me in death-
to trust, to have faith.
Because as a friend
of mine once said...
"It's belief
that gets us there. "
Subtitled By DeliXiosO