Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Third place. So, what'd she get?
$1,100.
- Sonador. Ben Crane?
- Yeah.
Claimed.
- What? You got to be kidding me.
- Claimed?
- Wait a second. Hang on.
- You said she wouldn't get claimed.
- Cale, listen to me.
- What was the tag?
How much did you get for her?
15,000.
You just sold Sonador.
I don't believe this.
Cale...
I wasn't trying to sell Sonya.
Out of 100 horses
that could have been claimed,
you know how many got claimed?
Two.
Do you understand
that you got to claim the horse
before the race is even run?
I figured there's no way
anybody'd take a chance
on a filly that'd already
broken her leg.
I guess there was some chance.
She's gone.
She was a good horse, Cale.
I'm going to miss her, too.
Please don't treat me
like a little kid.
You were trying to get
some of your money back.
I get it. It's business.
That's right, it is.
But I wasn't trying to sell Sonya, OK?
You lied to me.
You said I'd always have Sonador.
You stood right there and said it.
You raced her and she got claimed.
Well, everything doesn't end up
the way you want it to.
She wasn't for sale.
Every racehorse everywhere
in the world, right now, is for sale.
Get that.
She wasn’t just some racehorse.
She was our horse.
I told Pat I would work
the dinner shift tonight.
You said you'd go
to Cale's school for Parents' Night.
Eight o'clock. I got it.
All right.
Have a good time.
"My shirt was wet
and it smelled like French toast."
"So even though I threw up, I was happy
my dad took me to the firehouse."
"The end."
Thank you, Miss Richardson.
Thank you.
- Ben Crane.
- Yes, ma'am.
I'd love you to read Cale's story.
It's very inventive.
It's right there in the blue folder.
Come on up.
"Once upon a time
there was a noble king."
"He lived in a beautiful castle
overlooking green fields."
"An evil storm cast darkness
over his castle."
"And before he knew it,
dark knights had begun
to take away his kingdom
one piece at a time."
"But our king was a warrior and he knew
that if he could find his magic horse,
he could restore the kingdom
to greatness."
"He was not like most kings.
He was quiet and kind."
"Everyone loved the king,
which he may not have known."
"He searched and searched and finally
rescued his horse from a raging river."
"But by the time
he'd freed his horse,
his kingdom was gone
and he had given up."
"But the horse knew better than he."
"The horse took him over mountain ranges
and across raging rivers."
"When it finally looked like they would
die, the horse asked him to trust him."
"The king didn't know if the horse
had really spoken to him
or he just hadn't had anything to eat
in a few days."
"Not soon after, the horse attempted
to climb a mountain so steep
the king was sure
it would be their deaths."
"But the horse reached the top."
"And at the top,
they found his kingdom restored."
"All those who loved him
greeted the king with pie and coffee."
"By Cale Crane."
- Can we keep these?
- Yes.
I read your story tonight at school.
The stupid one about the king?
Yeah, the stupid king.
I made mistakes, Cale.
I'm sorry.
So you like the stupid king?
Yeah, I like the stupid king.
I love the stupid king.
He loves you, too.
Ben, there's some guy here
to see you.
Cale.
I got Pop a new goat.
Want to pull him out of the trailer?
Thanks a lot.
Sonya! Sonya!
You came home!
I'm so glad you're back.
How'd you get her back?
It wasn’t just me.
Pops helped out. Too.
I did?
We're both out of coffee for a while.
All right,
I got all the paperwork here.
Cale, we put 51 percent
of Sonador in your name.
So from here on out,
you make all the decisions.
Don't worry, you'll have 39 percent.
Balon, you and Manny
can split the other ten, huh?
What are you saying, Ben?
Well, I'm saying as soon
as she signs this paper,
the new owner of Sonador
is Cale Crane.
Welcome to the race business.
Congratulations.
You work for her now.
OK, boss...
- Me?
...what's it going to be?
- Come on.
- Let's go, señorita. Come on.
Should I warm her up and then push her
a little for three furlongs? Maybe four?
You want us to blow her out, right?
Then we can start to build her up.
Yeah. Let's just blow her out.
Appreciate it, Bob.
If anything comes up,
you let me know, huh? All right. 'Night.
Hey...
- You're up kind of late.
- Been reading all of Sonya's records.
She won over 200,000
in graded company.
Oh, yeah, I know.
Qualifies her for a lot of stakes races.
I looked through the conditions book.
Well, I'm sure
you'll figure something out.
I want you to help me.
I want you to help me train her.
I see.
Well, you'd be getting a trainer.
What is it I'd be getting?
Ten percent.
- 20.
- 15.
- Done.
- Sign here.
Straight across. Not too tight.
That's it. There you go.
Come on, girl. Come on.
Get up. Let's go.
She look good?
- All right, here we go.
- Hello.
I want to thank everyone for coming.
I've scouted all of Sonador's
possible races
and picked one I know she can win.
Really?
And when is this race?
Saturday, October 29th.
Gotten the best jockey.
His name is Manolin Vallarta.
Well, I'm Manolin Vallarta.
Great idea.
You once told me you were the greatest
jockey in the world and I believe you.
Thank you, Cale.
Thank you, but I can't. I'm not ready.
I'm...
Fat and I got to slim down.
Right, Manny?
October 29th is the same day
as the Breeders' Cup Championship,
isn't it?
Biggest day in racing.
Breeders' Cup is eight races
worth 14 million dollars?
I don't think you want to run in a race
on the same day as the Breeders' Cup.
You're right. We shouldn't run in a race
the same day as the Breeders' Cup.
That's why we're going to run
in the Breeders' Cup.
That's ambitious.
You can’t just show up
with your horse at the Breeders' Cup
and say "I'm here.
I want to run in the Classic."
- It doesn't work that way.
- Be nice if it did.
Do you know
what the selection process is?
Fourteen horses.
First seven are graded stakes wins,
points, I don't know.
Last seven are...
No. No, I don't, really.
The last seven they base on
performance during the year.
But they can make a judgment call.
I'm going to take a shot.
It's a long shot
but why not Sonador?
Why not us?
- Why not Sonador?
- That's right.
We going to the Breeders' Cup.
Did you really not know
how the last horses were chosen?
No, I didn't. Why would I?
I never been there.
But if Sonya does get in, there'll be
huge fees for a race like that.
So, you know, this is a pipe dream.
Remember dreams, Ben?
Well, this one's Cale's.
Help her live it.
I want to, Lil. I do.
I'm just saying, it isn't going
to happen. That's all, honey.
So what? So what?
Just let it take her as far as it can.
All right.
Five furlongs in 1.01 and change.
That's better, but...
She was breezing, Dad. Don't worry.
They're good. They look good.
Hey, guys.
You guys got my favorite.
Balon, where's mine?
Yummy.
This is an orange?
It looks like a painted golf ball.
Manny, run her
closer to the rail, will you?
The donuts aren't that good.
- Oh no!
- Give me another jelly.
Back up.
Are we lucky?
Good girl. Yes. Come on.
Come on, Sonya.
Cale?
I'm up. I'm up.
But, my horse Rapid Cat, is the son of
Storm Cat, the best sire in the world.
He deserves to run
in the Breeders' Cup.
Mr. Sadir Abal,
Rapid Cat is 18th on the point list.
We've got 14 spots.
There's not much hope
for Rapid Cat. Next.
Is Mr. Cale Crane here?
I'm Cale Crane.
Why don't you stand up?
Miss Cale Crane.
Your horse Sonador has 20 points
and that puts her 16th on the list.
Though I see that last year
she had 42 points.
Yes, sir. She'd have that many points
this year, but she was injured.
She was injured? Well, do you have
a vet's report says she's sound?
Right here, sir.
Thank you.
Now, you know there are
14 horses that get to run.
And your horse got a shot.
But to enter this horse in this race,
there'll be a fee of $40,000.
Did you bring a check?
I mailed it.
Today.
Let's say that the panel determines
that Sonador belongs in this race.
Now, there's another
80,000 dollars in fees
that's going to be due
on October 26th.
You prepared for that?
She'll mail it to you.
Yes, sir, I am.
Final selection
will be at 11am tomorrow.
- We got a deal?
- You got a deal. Congratulations.
My knight in shining armor's
come to rescue me?
Bye. I'm going to take off.
I'll see you tomorrow.
See you later.
Is Cale with Pop?
Yeah, they're going over
race strategies.
- She going to get in?
- Selection's in the morning.
How did Cale do
in front of the committee?
Truth? It was rough.
She got kicked around pretty good.
- Why are you smiling?
- Because she kicked right back.
Yeah, she reminds me of somebody.
You were right, Lil.
It was great just letting her try.
So you're saying that I'm smart?
I'm saying you're smart and beautiful.
You think she has a chance
of getting in.
There's a chance.
And the entry fees
are $120,000. OK?
Did you hear me?
Why are you smiling?
I feel like I'm on a date.
Cale?
Time for bed, honey.
Well, that works a little better
than a bucket now, doesn't it?
Yes.
So how much will you bet
on Sonador to win the Classic?
Don't you think she can win?
You got to think she can win.
What's the harm in that?
- Say "I think she can win."
- I think she can win.
Good.
She needs to hear you say that.
I would like to see you
run against those boys.
May I have your attention, please?
I am proud to announce the field
for the 22nd running
of the Breeders' Cup Classic.
We start in alphabetical order.
A.P. Flyer.
Argus.
Bicycleman.
Bijoco.
Chief Balaz.
Full Of Flight.
Goliath's Boy.
Grand Duke.
Icondoit.
In The Rooms.
Note's Weasel.
On The Hops.
And our last two runners are:
Point Twice...
...and...
...Sonador.
Yes!
Way to go!
No. No.
I gave it away.
You gave it away.
You don't even know the joke.
I can't believe I just did that.
Well, I had to see for myself.
It's amazing.
Well, it's good to see the Cranes
all in one spot.
Pop Crane.
The famous Pop Crane.
Evening, fellas.
How can we help you?
Well, you have to ask yourselves
how much it's worth to you
to have this broken filly
finish 14th in a field of 14.
How much you want
to embarrass yourselves.
Because we all know that this horse
has got no business in that race.
Ben, I feel bad about
what happened between us.
No, look, honestly, I do.
And I'd like to make it right.
I'll give you...
...20,000 in cash for her.
- 20 grand?
- Yeah.
Let's see. Manny,
that's $1,000 for you.
$1,000 for you, Balon.
A whole 1,000 for me?
I guess I could get me
a couple of steak dinners now.
Maybe some wine,
maybe some tube socks.
$1,000 for me, too?
I could buy me a thousand pair
of dollar underwears.
Wait, my share's
about eight grand.
I've only got 20 invested.
Where do I sign?
$40,000.
All right?
I brought my guys and a trailer with me.
So your luck is changing.
I know what you paid for that horse.
- Are we done here?
- Not my horse, Everett.
Well, what do you say, honey?
I'm not selling her.
OK, I found my other pocket.
All right?
And you listen to me.
This is your last chance.
I have a certified check for $100,000.
And if you take this offer
I'll give your dad his job back.
I can't believe it.
The Cranes have finally won one.
Dad?
If it was me...
...I’d tell him to take his money
and his empty trailer
and get the hell off our farm.
But...
...that's just me.
You're running Goliath's Boy
in the Classic?
That's right. He is the favorite.
And when he wins the Cup,
it'll be my fifth horse of the year.
Do you think Goliath's Boy remembers
what Sonya's butt looks like?
Why?
Because it's all it will be
seeing of her on race day.
That's a good one, kid.
That's funny, ain't it? That's funny.
Suit yourself.
Dad.
Any luck?
I can't find a sponsor for this race.
Nobody wants to take a chance on her.
Called everybody I can think of.
You ever seen a kid
so happy with a horse?
Yeah. I have.
Pick it up.
Come on. Pick it up.
Good girl.
There's other races, darling,
that don't cost so much to enter.
I've lost 15 pounds in three weeks.
You should stop training.
We don't have the money to run.
Going down to the Breeders' Cup to tell
them we're dropping out of the race.
I had a dream last night, Cale.
I was on a horse.
A fast horse. That horse and me...
We're flying like angels.
How'd it end?
I woke up and my hunger was gone.
It was God telling me to race again.
Thank you, Cale.
May God bless you.
Nobody ever thought we'd get in.
No, they didn't. But you did it.
Cale. Pop. Come on.
Get in the truck.
Come on, let's go.
- Great idea, Dad.
- He said he'd talk to us.
- What are you going to say?
- I'm not. You are.
I'm here to see Prince Sadir.
The prince is expecting you.
Please join him.
Prince Sadir, I'm Cale Crane.
- I remember you.
- This is my dad and my granddad.
- Morning.
- Appreciate you taking my call.
120,000?
40,000 for the nomination fee
and 80,000 for the entrance fee.
Prince Tariq is sure he's going to win.
Goliath's Boy is a big, big horse.
Goliath's Boy is a bully.
He's a bluffer and her horse knows it.
Cale, you look me in the eye
and you tell me
you think your horse has a chance
of beating my brother's horse.
My horse will beat every horse
that shows up.
Yeah, we're in!
We are in the Breeder's Cup!
I can't believe it!
"You are a great champion."
"When you ran, the ground shook,
the sky opened
and mere mortals parted."
"Parted the way to victory, where
you'll meet me in the winner's circle
and I'll put a blanket
of flowers on your back."
Run hard tomorrow.
Run hard for my dad.
He deserves a good run.
Pop?
Just a minute.
- What?
- In 21 Breeders' Cup Classics,
you know how many fillies
have ever won it?
None. Only four fillies ever ran.
She's not even ready.
Palmer's right.
This is going to be an embarrassment.
What am I doing here, Pop?
You're taking your kid and your horse
to the Breeders' Cup tomorrow.
Because that's the dream
of every real horseman.
It's the dream of every father.
Dream damn few ever get to see.
Damn few, trust me on that one.
Listen, Lilly and Cale
are driving down in the morning
and Lilly doesn't really know
where to go so...
I want you to come to the race.
Pop, as your son,
I'm asking you to come.
Be with me and Cale.
OK.
OK. Good.
Good.
OK, Sonya. Here you go, mama.
You are done. You are ready, mama.
OK, Manolin, looking good.
Good job. Good job.
Good job, sweetie.
- You got her?
- Yeah, I got her.
You look muy bella.
Well, thank you, Balon.
I was talking to her.
Here you go, Manny.
Here's the original silks
of the Crane Race Farm.
I'm taking this good-looking thing to
the owners' box and show off that hat.
- Have a great race, Manny.
- Thank you, Mrs. Crane.
Sure wish we had
another couple of weeks.
She's ready to run.
You saved her life.
She's just returning the favor.
She's here to run for you.
Mr. Palmer. So, what do you expect
from Goliath's Boy today?
What do I expect
from Goliath's Boy?
I expect that Goliath's Boy's
going to have some fun today.
There's Ben Crane and Sonador.
80-1 shot.
Hey, Ben.
How about we get a picture here
with Sonador and Goliath's Boy.
Just a little photo opportunity.
No.
- Get him away!
- Control your horse!
Sonya! No, no, no!
Get him away!
Easy, easy, easy!
It's all right. I got him.
- Will you control your horse?
- I got him.
Easy, boy. It's OK.
- Grab a hold of her.
- Easy.
Going to be OK.
I don't believe it.
I'm feeling heat in that leg.
I don't know if it's me or...
What do you want to do?
What do you want to do, boss?
- What do you want to do?
- Bring her in here.
Dad...
What are the chances
she's cut on the same leg
we've healed for over 6 months?
This is beyond bad luck.
Are you afraid?
Are you afraid that we're going
to come in dead last?
- I'm sorry, sir.
- Bring her in here.
- Sir, it's Sonya.
- Just bring her in here.
She won't come in!
Manny. Manny. Hang on.
- She doesn't want to move.
- Hold on. Come here.
She tried to kick me
when I tried to bring her in.
Come here, girl. Come on, now.
Hold on. Come here, girl.
Easy now.
What do you want?
Easy.
What's she telling you?
I don't know.
Something about...
...the ground shaking.
Sky parting.
She wants to run.
Let's go.
Balon, take Cale to our seats.
Good luck.
Come on, girl.
I got a special package here.
This is going to be great.
- I'm very excited, ain't you?
- Hello.
This is just for owners.
I know. That'd be us.
That would be us. Yeah.
- Thank you very much.
- Good luck.
Here we go.
Are we down this way?
This way, yeah. That's it.
- Do you know anyone here? I don't.
- No, I don't.
Horses coming out onto the track
for the Grade 1
$4,000,000 Breeders' Cup Classic:
The biggest race in North America.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Eighth race.
20 to win on the seven.
Seven? That's Sonador.
That horse is 80-1.
You know what?
You're right.
$257 on Sonador to win.
You like that?
Good luck.
A reminder
of two jockey changes here.
Number 11, Grand Duke
will now be ridden by Alan Reid.
Well, you ready?
Pop.
257 to win?
You're crazy.
That's for you.
Here's the moment
we've been waiting for.
They're ready to load into the gate
for the Breeders' Cup Classic.
And here's Goliath's Boy.
Is he full of himself this afternoon.
Goliath's Boy is good
and he knows he's good.
Very aggressive this afternoon.
Goliath's Boy looks like he's going
to run a huge race.
He's loaded in the gate now,
joined by Bijoco and Note's Weasel.
Icondoit and Point Twice coming up.
Now, here's the filly, Sonador.
Only the fifth filly
to even run in this race.
Sonador joined now by Bicycleman.
And here's young Manny Vallarta,
the rider of Sonador.
Certainly never been in a race this big
in his entire career.
Grand Duke and Full Of Flight
are going in. Almost all set now.
Chief Balaz to come to the outside gate
and they'll all be set for a start.
They're all set.
And away they go.
Broke in a perfect line.
In The Rooms on the inside.
The favorite, Goliath's Boy, comes away
beautifully and joins the leaders.
Note's Weasel is right there.
Bijoco in the middle of the pack.
Icondoit towards the outside.
Then it's Point Twice and Bicycleman,
setting a very fast pace early on.
A.P. Flyer behind that.
On the Hops as they go wide.
Then back to Grand Duke
and Full Of Flight.
Sonador is second last at the back.
In The Rooms on the inside
but the favorite, Goliath's Boy,
right there with them.
Hold on, Manny!
It looks like the rider's foot
has come out the irons on Sonador.
Get back up.
Make her settle.
- She's last.
- There's a lot of race left.
First quarter, 22 and one.
Go, Sonya!
Sonador's passing a horse
with each and every stride
as they come to the top of the lane.
In The Room's the leader.
The filly Sonador
moving into the picture.
- This big long shot, Sonador...
- Come on, Sonya.
And Sonador could be a danger
to the favorite, Goliath's Boy.
And Goliath's Boy goes on for home.
Come on, Sonya. Take him out.
The filly Sonador is up
alongside of Goliath's Boy.
They come down to the wire,
Goliath's Boy and Sonador.
And it's Sonador!
Unbelievable. The filly Sonador
has come from last.
And look at this, the odds 80-1.
The biggest stunning upset...
Oh, baby, I had a dream.
It was a dream and I didn't know
the end of it till today!
Yeah!
Thanks, Pop. Thanks for everything.
Thank you.
257 at 80-1?
That's $20,000. I'm back.
"You are a great champion."
"When you ran, the ground shook,
the sky opened
and mere mortals parted."
"Parted the way to victory where
you'll meet me in the winner's circle
where I'll put a blanket
of flowers on your back."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org