DYING BREED (2008)
Run, you bastard!
I think I see something there.
Over there!
Come on!
Let go the dogs!
Get onto him.
There!
Let's go, then!
Down you go!
Hold fast, you Irish shit!
So you thought you'd leave hell, would you?.
Timmy! I have Pearce!
Timmy!
Your hands, get 'em up!
Up!
Well, as you will.
Irish are all the same.
Over there!
You okay?.
Yeah. I'm good.
You sure your friend is fine with this?.
Yeah.
Jack's an old mate.
Plus, I told him his picture would be
plastered across the front page
of every newspaper in the country
if he helped us find this tiger, so...
That's if we find it.
A small detail.
I can't wait to meet him.
Hey.
Yeah, I know. Relax.
- Yes.
- I'm good. I'm excited.
Good.
Wow! You look the same.
Obviously been working it off.
I'm proud of you, mate.
You know, we grew up as neighbors.
Did everything together.
Yeah, I heard.
Not everything.
So this trip of ours-
Let's agree on 60/40?.
- 60/40-
- All right, 50/50.
But that includes marketing rights.
What?.
Oi!
Go easy, mate.
This trip means a lot to her.
I'm doing her a favor, remember?.
Yeah, you are.
It's just her sister.
- Remember?.
- That was ages ago.
That was eight years ago,
which isn't long.
This is the same trip--
Just be aware.
That's all I'm saying.
Be sensitive.
Okay. Hey, I'm Mr. Sensitive.
- All right?.
- Okay.
Does she swallow?.
Is this it?.
Yeah, absolutely.
Plenty of room for the four of us.
Who's the fourth?.
Rebecca.
Who's Rebecca?.
You didn't expect it to be
just the three of us, did you?.
I mean, that would be like traveling
with my parents, for fuck's sake.
Come on.
Yeah.
Nina, shotgun.
Get in the back.
God, it's beautiful.
Still pinching myself
we finally made it here.
Beats sitting in a real estate
office all day.
That bad, is it?.
No.
Hey, how long was your sister here?.
About two years.
She kind of fell off the radar
towards the end there, so-
Hey, Nina, there's money
to be made, isn't there?.
If you can prove that this tiger exists.
Is that true, Nina?.
I'm not going to bite.
A local paper offered
over a million dollars, apparently.
Mind you, though, if we do find this thing,
we probably won't recognize it
because it'll be so fucking inbred.
You're full of it.
- Do you have an "off' switch?.
- Mm-hmm. Right here.
So which drop we heading for again, mate?.
I think it's this one.
Hang on. Is it-
Maybe it's this one.
No, no, no
We're not lost yet.
Must be weird, though-
following your sister here after so long.
Yeah.
I just want to finish what she started.
You know?.
Well, Pieman River.
Welcome.
- Nothing.
- Oh, yes.
- We must have arrived, then.
- The house of serenity.
Oi! Tasmania!
You awake?.
Right here.
Thank you.
Done a little bit of acting in my time.
I got to wee.
Watch out for leeches.
You know, I could've been
in Thailand with Emily.
You would have missed me too much.
Need a hand?.
Hey, sis, come here.
No teeth.
Hey! They're here.
Check out the color.
What is it, rust?.
It's not rust.
Looks more like blood.
Yeah, right.
Come on.
Fuck!
Jeez!
You all right?.
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
We're going to drive the car up.
Oi! Oi!
I'm okay.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Fuck.
- You're going to do it?.
- All right. Don't scratch it.
- Oh, God.
She's definitely always on top.
You don't get a say ever, do ya?.
Steady. Oh, God.
Okay, okay, okay.
Yep.
All right. Straight up.
- Great.
- Well done.
It's a freakin' antique!
Look at her go.
Hey, tell them about your idea for a bridge.
Yeah.
What's with the water?.
Why's it look like blood?.
Blood?.
That's tannin.
Said the pieman to Simple Simon...
Hi.
- Simple Simon...
- What are those?.
Simple Simon met the pieman
playing with a knife.
Said Simple Simon to the pieman,
"Will you take my life??'
That's a nice rhyme.
Can I have a look at those?.
Shit! She bit me!
Yeah, well, pick on
someone your own size.
- I'm bleeding!
- Wheelhouse! Now!
Which is fine.
It's her boat and I'm a guest.
You know, they made
a whole X-Files series
on people like that.
Freaks.
Freaks!
Measuring 6 foot from tail to hood,
it was a formidable pest.
This, supposedly, is the last
known footage of the tiger
since it was hunted to extinction.
Hey. Hey.
However, unconfirmed sightings
in Western Tasmania
have cast doubt that, in fact,
the tiger's extinct at all--
This is all very interesting,
but nothing new.
I see no reason to fund your proposal.
To the right!
If you'll take a look at this--
What, precisely, are we looking at?.
A paw print.
1 6 separate points of reference.
As you can see, it's a perfect match.
Come on!
And where did you source
this one from, the Net?.
My sister took it.
You all right?.
You lost anything?.
Yeah. My desire to have children.
She tried to eat me alive.
Look at that.
What do you want me to do?.
Do you want me to kiss it better?.
Yes.
Shite!
Look out! Look out!
- Any damage?.
- Better not be any fuckin' damage.
Jack, calm down.
She didn't hit anything.
Didn't you see him coming?.
He came out of nowhere, Jack.
Don't blame me.
Let's not lose the plot. Everyone.
I mean, you were the one driving, Nina.
You ever heard of a rearview
fucking mirror?.
I swear it was a car.
Look, why don't we just get to the town
and we can have a drink, okay?.
I think we all need it.
Thanks.
Just let him drive.
Make it a double.
Sarah.
Welcome to the winner of Tidy Camp.
Wave to the locals.
Making friends.
This Pieman guy's popular.
He owns everything.
We should get the fuck out of this car.
Oi. That look familiar?.
Toilet?.
Okay.
What did that achieve?.
Nothing, but I feel better, eh?.
Come on, let's have a beer.
Jesus, Matt, we only just got here.
I know. I know.
Do you want anything to drink, babe?.
Yeah, just whatever.
Can we stay out of trouble?.
Can we do that?. Please?.
Let's sort out the rooms.
Hi.
Be with you in a minute.
Don't even think about the towel.
- I think it's alive.
- Great.
Look, are you okay with me being here?.
I know that Jack
can railroad people into things,
and I don't want you to think that I'm--
No, no, no. It's fine.
- Are you sure?.
- Yeah.
Okay, good.
It's just--
This place was the last stop
that my sister made,
so it's a little bit weird.
Before she died?.
Before she drowned, yeah.
It was an accident, apparently.
It was eight years ago, so I was young.
Yeah, and look.
It hasn't changed a bit.
It's that old-world charm.
Interesting wildlife.
Lovely.
Thank you.
They jump, you know.
I've nothing.
You're kidding.
I didn't know it was pig season.
Try the next town.
If you don't mind roughing it.
Anything's fine.
Harvey. Fifth generation lrish.
Hi, I'm Matt. Matt.
Hey, thank you.
You see that?.
It belonged to my great-great-grandda.
Wow. Cool.
Gareth!
You got a flat.
You must have picked up something.
As he says,
if you don't mind roughing it.
Liam.
- Awesome.
- Here you go, guys.
Let's see if Pieman lives up to his name.
Yes, except I'm on a no-carbs thing.
That you may have to forget.
It's traditional Wangan's food, apparently.
It's good. Cheers.
The mines around here
may have shut down,
but the pies have hung on.
It's important to us. Traditions.
Tradition.
So, are the rumors true?.
- Rumors?.
- Yeah.
That the tiger's alive and kicking.
That's what brought you here.
That and the cooking.
It's good.
So are they?.
There hasn't been a tiger
around here for a hundred years.
Seems to bring in the odd tourist, though.
Fine devils, but they got the teeth
that'll rip through bone.
- Devils?.
- Aye.
There's little hairy creatures
that'll creep up on you in the bush and--
That was funny.
Come on, now,
let's have us shenanigans.
No.
Come on.
Come on now!
Let's have a party!
She doesn't dance.
Come on.
You're out of the city now.
Let's make this quick.
Yeah. Welcome to Sarah,
the shallow end
of the fucking gene pool.
There's something
seriously wrong with this place.
- I mean, that old guy with the teeth?.
- You nearly wet yourself.
Well, do you blame me?.
I mean, a bunch of inbreds
in a fucking time warp.
What are they doing here, anyway?.
The mines dried up years ago.
And where are all the women?.
They heard you were coming.
Funny.
Wasn't this meant to be hooked on?.
Shit.
Anything missing?.
- Anything?.
- It doesn't look like it.
You see?.
Descended from convicts, mate.
Once a thief, always a fucking thief.
Look at that.
Fuck, look at that!
- What?.
- Look, my fucking car!
Look at that!
- It's not funny!
- I'm laughing at--
Look at my car!
Fifth generation wankers!
Look at that.
Don't touch it.
Fuck! God!
Can you close the top up?. Fuck!
Yeah, I will. Wait for me.
Come on!
You know, I haven't thanked you
for helping me do this.
It really means a lot to me, Matt.
Thanks.
Hey, I want to show you something.
Look at this.
My gran used to do this.
Yes, please, let's talk about your gran.
- Hikers disappear, right?.
- Mm-hmm.
And here, more hikers disappear.
"The Pieman's Curse."
1954. See?.
This one is from the '60s.
- I don't have to read all this, do l?.
- God.
Look at this.
Here.
"A timely reminder of 1824,
"when Alexander Pearce
escaped into the bush
and survived off human flesh."
He was a cannibal.
Who was?.
The Pieman, Alexander Pearce.
He ate people to survive,
right here in the hills.
And that is what that little girl
was singing about.
I'm gonna have a shower.
Hey, come here.
Oh, shit.
Jack, the lights. The lights.
Jack, shush, shush, shush.
What?.
I don't believe it, Jack! Shit!
You all right?. I heard screams.
You dirty bastard!
But, Jack, wait!
It's okay.
It's probably just a fuse.
What happened?.
There was some fucking weirdo
behind the door watching us.
You sure?.
Yeah, I know what I heard.
Do you mind?.
You sick bastard!
Please, it wasn't me, I swear!
You sick fuck!
Is that what you do,
huh, you sick fuck?.
Come here. Come here.
Did you get a kick
out of scratching my car?.
Did you?. Huh?. Come here.
Yeah, you fuckin' rat.
Well, I'll tell you,
I like my car to stay brand new.
Fucking...
... new!
You get it?.
Fucking pervert.
Here.
That was for my girlfriend,
you fucking rat boy.
It's me, you idiot!
Well, it would have been a good show.
An adventure, right?.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- Sleep tight.
- What?.
It's all sorted.
You know, I don't know
who unnerves me more--
the locals or Jack.
He took care of it.
There you go.
Thanks.
- Watch out.
- Sorry.
Yay!
We're off. Thanks.
All right, I'm in charge of ropes.
Hold on. Wait.
My camera bag--
I think I've left it.
- Oh, really?.
- No, it's in there.
No, I left it in the truck.
It's not here.
- I'll get it.
- That's okay. I'll get it.
You sure?.
Yeah, it's in the brand-new car
with the brand-new scratch on it.
Let it go, let it go.
The parents are brother and sister.
Tried to keep 'em apart, but--
I warned 'em this would happen.
Always does.
Play?.
No.
Look, I don't want to play with you, okay?.
I have to go.
What?.
Katie!
Hey!
- You got everything?.
- Yeah.
- You all right?.
- I'm fine.
Let's go.
See you, Sarah.
Oi, this is good.
Is that dam on the map?.
No. It shouldn't be there.
Well, trust me, brother,
we're not imagining that.
We've come too far.
No shit, Sherlock.
- Is it safe?.
- Yeah, yeah, it's safe.
Well, if it breaks, we can
surf our way back to Hobart.
Hey, Jack, that's not helping.
That ridge is this one right here.
Got it.
Hey, look, we've got company.
- Hey, do you know how to read a map?.
- Jack, shh.
He can't read a map!
How'd he get there?.
He got there on an access road.
It's not marked.
- What do you want me to do?.
- Come on. Give us it.
- How old is this map?.
- I bought it on the way in, thank you.
They're locals. It's their territory.
They know their way around.
Jack.
Let's go, kids.
Come on!
Thank you.
- Here's yours, babe.
- Thanks, Matt.
Can you grab my camera bag, too?.
Camera bag. Yep.
Hey, whoa.
What the hell is that doing here?.
Babe.
All right, all right.
- Jack.
- Nina.
If you want to go waltzing around
Deliverance country, fine.
However, I like to travel
with the William Tell Mark 5, aka Willie.
- He's my little friend.
- Well, you know what?.
I'm not interested
in your macho bullshit, all right?.
I came here to study wildlife,
not to kill it.
Really?. Is that why you came here?.
Look, you know what they say, Jack,
big crossbow, really little--
You leave my Willie alone.
Well, you've got the map.
Lead the way.
Come on. I'll be good.
It's just-- This is how he is.
Right. So now
you're defending him, Matt.
- That's good.
- No, I'm--
I'm not defending him.
I was just--
I'm just saying if--
if you let him do his thing,
he'll let you do your thing,
and we can all...
get along.
So how much longer
are you gonna sulk for?.
I just need to know.
Probably about another 30 minutes, I think.
Okay, good. Just checking.
Hey, Nina, love you.
Jack, you know, I pity your poor mother.
I really do.
How the hell did she cope?.
Pity me, Nina.
Yeah, I do.
I pity you, too, Bec.
I can just imagine
you two as kids, you know.
Now you know why I went overseas.
Hey, I heard that.
Why are you leading?.
Where are we going?.
Where's that map?.
Why are you laughing?.
You watch out.
I don't know
what you've been told
Becky's ass is solid gold
Sound off
Three, four
Here, tiger.
That's it.
My blisters have blisters.
Yeah, I'm putting my foot down.
We're sleeping here.
Look at this place.
There are places out here
nobody's ever seen before.
Ever.
It's amazing, don't you think?.
How far have we come today?.
About 1 5 Ks, I think.
You're kidding.
- Yeah.
- Who needs the gym?.
I tell you, I've discovered muscles
I didn't even know I had.
Hush! Listen.
Listen.
- Your serenity.
- Hey! This is good!
This is seriously good.
Hey, Matty, you got a torch?.
Yes, sir.
Why?. Jack, you're not going in there.
Come on. Why not?.
It's a cave.
Better than sleeping out here.
Jack, I'm not sleeping in a cave.
Jack.
Jack, you're not listening to me.
I'm not going in there.
Come on.
Come on, babe!
There is no way
I'm going in that cave, Jack.
Yeah. Dry enough.
It's good for me.
I'm sleeping in the cave. Okay.
Wait for me. Shit.
Shit!
Yes!
You fuckin' idiot.
Jack, what the hell is wrong with you?.
What's wrong with you?.
There's no law against popping rabbits.
I mean, they're pests.
You hunt extinct dogs,
and I'll hunt rabbits.
You know, I came here to have fun.
Wow.
That's very impressive, Jack.
You know, I thought
apes like you were extinct.
You know, I came here
because Matt asked me
to help him help you.
Do I hear any thanks for that?.
Nah. All I hear is your selfish,
whining tantrums.
You know what?.
We're really sick of it.
Then thank you, Jack.
Couldn't have done it without you.
Yeah!
Rabbit season!
That's disgusting.
Where do you think the stew comes from?.
I mean, you are a carnivore, babe.
Not anymore.
What is-- That's crap, isn't it?.
Mm-hmm.
So he's gone primal
and you're collecting crap.
It's a very different kind of holiday for me.
Oh, hey, Bec?.
That's so disgusting!
Put it down.
That side's still furry.
Bind her legs!
Come on now.
Kids love to kick.
Katie?.
Where is she?.
Think! Think!
- It doesn't have to be--
- Then where is she?.
It's the smell of them.
It's everywhere since they arrived.
I don't want to lose the child.
Find her.
There's something out there,
in the trees.
Look. There.
There was something here.
Shit.
It stopped.
My camera.
Yeah. Go.
Hey.
There's a tiger out there,
right outside the cave.
Yeah, right.
Are you serious?.
Very.
Where is it?.
It went back into the bush.
We need a picture.
What?. You didn't get a picture?.
We can still get one if we go after it.
It's worth a try.
You wanna go?.
Did I miss it?.
- I can't believe you didn't get a picture.
- Well, we didn't. All right, Jack?.
Let's try and fix that.
Yes. Let's just hurry up because
I'm freezin' my tits off out here.
Nina! How big is it?.
It's small, isn't it?.
I can handle that.
Here, doggie, doggie.
Nina!
- Matt!
- Sorry.
Sorry.
Found anything?.
Not yet.
Oh. This way.
Stuff this.
What are you doing here?.
Are you lost?.
Are you okay?.
All right.
Okay, I think you better come with me.
All right?. Who's that?.
Do you mind?.
Do you mind not shining that light in--
- Anything?.
- Sure you even saw it?.
I saw it.
I saw it, Jack!
Where's Rebecca?.
Probably having a pee.
Bec!
Hey, beautiful lady!
Beautiful lady! Bec!
She should be able to hear us.
She can't be far.
Bec!
Babe!
She might have--
I saw a mine shaft earlier.
Where?.
It was near where you killed that--
Babe, what have you done to yourself?.
I don't know. I--
I don't know. Fuck.
It's not mine.
Fuck.
Well, what happened?.
It could just be an animal.
- I don't know, Matt.
- Did you see an animal?.
- Did you see--
- No! I didn't!
- Hey, come on.
- Jack!
- Show me where.
- What?.
- Show me!
- I don't-- I don't know!
I started there,
and I circled around, I guess.
I heard some sounds.
What sounds?.
- What sounds?.
- I don't know!
Bec!
Jack! Fuck.
Hey, hey. Nina!
Just stay here. Stay here.
Bec!
Bec! Babe!
Can't see a thing out there.
It's like the bloody Amazon.
Where's Jack?.
I have no idea.
I did this.
I pushed for this.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- It was my fucking trip.
We don't know what's happened.
I'll go and look again, okay?.
I'll try again.
How the hell did she get there?.
Hi, there. Remember me?.
What happened to you?.
Are you hurt?.
It's not her blood, either.
Is it, Matt?.
It's Mama.
What happened to you?.
How'd you get the blood on your dress?.
- Can you tell me?.
- How the hell would she know?.
She's just a kid.
She didn't walk here on her own.
Did you?.
Simple Simon met the pieman
playing with a knife.
Said Simple Simon to the pieman...
- That's a nice rhyme, little girl.
- "Will you take my life??'
I need you to tell me what happened.
- Okay?.
-...when the time is right.
Katie!
Jesus.
We came for the child.
She's okay.
She's okay?.
What about us?.
Rebecca's disappeared.
So has Jack.
And the blood!
Look at her, for God's sake.
- She's covered in it.
- Now, now.
- Get away from me!
- Anything could have happened to her.
The bush is different at night, lad.
There are hundreds of mine shafts.
You must have realized the dangers
before coming here.
It's easy to lose your way.
I'll take them.
She won't be hard to track.
Get your stuff.
Get your stuff! Move!
Come on. At least they're willing to help.
Come on.
Keep close.
Why'd you come here?.
You tourist turn up.
You always interfere.
You trample on everything.
You spoil everything.
Tell me where's my sister.
She died here eight years ago.
She stayed for about a year,
looking for your tiger.
That little girl recognized her.
When a bitch is on heat,
she'll go out of her way to mate.
That's how it is.
Jesus. What kind of stone age--
What are you saying?.
What the fuck are you saying?.
That that little girl is m--
Jesus Christ.
Who are these people?.
I can't go with him.
What else can we do?.
He's the only one helping us right now.
Come on.
Come on, baby.
Fuck.
Hey! Hey, hey.
Where are you taking us?.
You want to find your friend?.
It's an old miner's tunnel.
I used to play here when I was a kid.
Like you said, what else
are we going to do?.
Wait!
Man trap.
Troopers used to sit 'em
outside the convict camps.
This is as far as I go.
What?.
Where are you going?.
It'll bring you out on the other side.
Do you trust him?.
Stay by me.
Go home.
Stay close to me.
- Watch your step.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- It's okay. Just--
- Slow down, Matt.
Stay in the light.
- Can't see.
- Okay.
- Just step over it.
- I see it.
There's the exit.
Is that Jack?.
Jack!
Matt! Careful!
There he is.
Rowan?.
Listen, we don't have to do this.
We don't...
have to live by the rules.
You hear me?.
Rowan?.
I can't hear anything.
Let's go back.
What do we do now?.
Shall we go back?.
Where the fuck are they, Matt?.
Shit. Shit.
What's that?. What is it?.
Jack?.
Let's go.
It could be Jack.
Jesus Christ, Jack.
What the fuck have you done?.
Wha--
Shit.
Matt, can you do something?.
Can you pull it out?.
What?. Pull it--
I don't know.
Here. Hold him. Hold him.
I'll make this as fast as I can, mate.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
- Jack?.
- Pull it through.
Huh?.
Pull the prick off it.
Do it!
How is he?.
Has he lost a lot of blood?.
I don't know.
I'm not a doctor.
Who gives a fuck about him?.
What about the blood
on Rebecca's jacket?.
Jack, wait up.
Just come back and think rationally
for three seconds.
For Christ's sakes, Jack.
Can you please stay with us?.
Matt needs you here.
I need you here.
You don't get it, do you?.
Doesn't matter what we do.
It's their turf, and they're watching.
Where is she?.
We will find Rebecca.
Okay?.
And then we're all gonna get out of here.
And he's gonna help.
I can walk.
Jack, come on.
Come on, mate.
Let's get outta here.
Hey! Who lives there?.
The child's father.
What do you mean?.
The girl from the cave?.
- Matt?.
- Care to take a look?.
No, I don't want to go in there.
Stay here. Okay?.
We'll be back in a second.
I promise.
Hello?.
Fuck.
What the fuck, man?.
Jack.
Jesus, what's that smell?.
Wait.
No, you bastard! No!
You fuckin' evil bastard!
I'm gonna kill you!
Come on!
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
I'm gonna kill you,
you miserable fuck!
Fuck you! Fuck you.
Come on!
Jack!
Go. Go help.
Fuck it!
Fuck it.
Shit!
Goddammit!
Jack!
Jack.
Fuck.
Nina, let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Get up.
Nina!
Come on. Hang on.
Nina, please.
Come on!
He's in the bushes.
We heard him.
Shit.
Stay here.
Stay here, okay?.
Yes?.
Come on.
Come on!
Harvey?.
Please, please, please.
What did you hope to find?.
Please.
We've been here a long time.
Almost as long as the nation.
We have a life to protect.
A tradition.
You tourists have no tradition.
Fuck!
I can feel the family resemblance.
You fucker!
Oh, shit!
- Fuck!
- Nina.
Nina?.
Nina.
Nina, is that you?.
Come on.
What--
Nina!
Nina?.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Nina!
Over here.
Shit!
You're a silly girl.
All this trouble.
The lrish.
Stubborn and willful.
Willful and stubborn.
Come on now.
You know you want this.
Your sister, she did.
A good breeder.
Fertile, as you are.
For the good of the family.
No!
Should have been done
when you were a pup.
You killed her.
You fucking killed her!
I'm sorry.
Harvey.
Until then.
You head back to your city life.
We'll know soon enough.
Be safe.
I never asked.
Did you find one of those tigers of yours?.
Well, if he's still around
after a hundred years,
he be one slippery shite.
Try this. They're bloody great.
How'd he manage to set
a man trap on his own?.
Don't worry about it.
I was born here.
I know these people.
You gonna eat that or what?.
Rebecca's.
It should go with her other stuff.
Righty-ho.
Ta.
Good, huh?.
See?.
We do need you...
to survive.
It means a lot to us.
To keep the family going.
The Pearce family.
But it's hard...
to obey rules...
...to stay pure.
Like your tiger.
There's so few of us left.
Things have to stay hidden...
to survive.
You understand that.
Simple Simon met the pieman
playing with a knife.
Said Simple Simon to the pieman,
"Will you take my life??'
Said the pieman to Simple Simon,
"When the time is right."
Said Simple Simon to the pieman,
"Then I'll die tonight."
I'm hungry.
Burbank, CA