Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Hey, take it easy!
Hey, who's the big
birthday girl, huh?
Oh, boy. How old are youme! I'm this.
Call me when you're this, okayhere we go.
You got it straight, okay?
Hold it there.
Beautiful, beautiful!
Okay!
Hey, what happened here?
What's the matter, huh?
Johnny hit me.
He don't like me anymore.
Oh, i know what
you're goin' through.
You gave him the best
three months of your life, huh?
Then he left you
for a pail and shovel.
What do you see in him, anyway?
What are you in love with?
He's not in your class. He's afraid
of the dark. He wets his pants.
When he eats, he gets food all
over his face. He's a mama's boy.
What are you,
in nursery school now?
I guarantee you, by the time you get to
kindergarten, you'll forget all about him.
Hey, look who's here! Show
time! Bobby bunny, huh?
Here we go, let's go.
Bobby bunny's here-
what's that?
Oh, nothing, nothing.
Bobby bunny just dropped
a few carrots, that's all.
You don't have to talk
all night?
I'm a man
who can't say no?
You don't have
to twist my arm?
Just point me
where you wanna go?
Take me to the action
take me to the track?
Take me to a party if
they're bettin' in the back?
I've been workin' all my life
can't afford to wait?
Let me call my wife so i
can tell her i'll be late?
I want the easy
mmm?
Easy, easy money?
I could get lucky?
Oh, things could go right?
I want the easy?
Easy, easy money?
Maybe this one time?
Maybe tonight?
You don't have to try
too hard?
I don't need
a song and dance?
an invitation?
If you've got
a game of chance?
Take me to the tables
take me to the fights?
Run me like a numbers
roll me like a dice?
When you're countin' on a
killin' always count me in?
Talk me into losing
just as long as i can win?
I want the easy?
Easy, easy money?
I want the good times?
Oh, i never had?
I want the easy?
Mmm, easy money?
Oh, i want the good life?
Mmm, i want it bad?
Easy money?
You say i fool myself?
But better me than being
a fool for someone else?
I got a hot slot machine
of a system ready to go?
Easy money?
I got a one-track mind and a
good reputation layin' on the line?
I'll either come back
a bum or a king?
Baby, i don't know?
Let's go over today's schedule.
It is exactly 6:33.
It is exactly 6:34.
At 7:00, we're meeting with the head of the
furniture department regarding inventory.
Postpone the meeting. Double-check the
inventory, and fire the cleaning staff.
7:20, you will crush the hopes
of the loading dock workers...
regarding better
working conditions.
Cancel the meeting,
and send out a memorandum...
that the working conditions
at the loading dock...
will remain as they have for
the past 35 years. Mm-hmm.
At 7:30, we'll be meeting
with the accountants...
regarding donations and
charitable contributions.
Cancel that meeting, and
cancel my check to boy's town.
What time
is scrappleton coming?
Uh, 7:50, with the legal
papers you requested.
As soon as you finish with scrappleton,
we leave for staten island...
to attend your granddaughter
allison's wedding.
Well, i hope she's made a better choice...
than her mother did!
Jesus! Rose!
How did you talk me
into this?
You should use allison.
She's the one has to wear it.
It's unlucky for the bride to wear
her gown before the wedding day.
How unlucky can she getlook who she's
marrying. You shouldn't talk like that.
Julio's a good boy.
Come on, rose, will ya?
See the guy for what he is.
He belongs to a gang.
It's a good boy's gang.
They help people.
- Ooh, take it easy, will ya?
- Oh, i'm sorry. Where'd i get you?
If i show you, we'll never
get outta here. Hold still.
I've gotta finish this. You gotta pick
up the cake, and mother will be here soon.
Your mother.
I gotta go to the john.
Monty! Oh, the dress!
No, you're wonderful.
Allison, i need the phone.
I'm in here.
Get outta there!
Get off, will ya?
I am so hung up on you.
Good idea.
I'll see you in church.
Daddy! Don't worry, you won't lose him.
Belinda, let's go.
Someday i'll be out
of your life.
Yeah, but right now
get outta the bathroom.
It's the best thing
about having daughters.
Nicky boy, it's monty.
Close the door.
Yeah?
Nicky, rose's mother,
she's on her way over.
So?
What do you want from me?
I need the truck. I gotta pick up the
wedding cake. What am i, allied vans?
You really know how
to push a friendship.
When's the last time you did something
for meyou got a short memory.
Who drove to atlantic city to
bail you out when you owed $400?
At belmont, you had
four losers in a row.
Who gave you the winner in the
fifththe cake's for your godchild!
All right, all right. Give
me a chance. I'm comin'.
Where's my stuffby the
front door. What's the rush?
I gotta go to work. I got a wedding
to pay for. Don't forget the cake.
How many years you know me?
Did i ever forget anything?
Nicky, just in time.
Beautiful!
I don't wanna see her fucking
- mother!
- Was it nicky?
- No, no. It's not nicky. No.
Oh, it's mother! Leave him,
dear. Simply walk out on him.
His entire body is
bloodshot. He'll never change.
Nice to see you too.
It's gonna be so much fun having
everyone here. Yeah, a lot of fun.
Well, if it isn't my favorite
relative. Don't start that bullshit.
Monty, please bring
mother's luggage upstairs.
What's clive, a footstool?
No, no, monty, let me get this.
How can you stand him?
You gotta get to know him.
The wedding
is gonna be wonderful.
We never get to see you. The
store takes up all my time.
Mother, why do you push yourself
so hardthe money doesn't matter.
When your father was alive,
he ran monahan's like a tyrant.
He paid the help
next to nothing.
- He drove them like sled dogs.
- Wonderful man.
Wonderful! Now that he's
gone, i carry on his work.
Rose,
i don't know how you can live
with that... man.
We're happy
just the way we are.
Happyyeah, we were
until a few minutes ago.
And we don't want a dime
from you. You understand?
No offense.
No offense?
You are an offense!
Why, you can
barely walk erect.
You pollute the air
with your smoking.
You reek of liquor and god knows what
else. You're an ecological menace!
You were the inspiration for twin
beds. I'll tell you something else.
Don't start with mother. I'm not
startin' nothin'. It never ended.
And to think of who you could
have married. Pat flannigan.
Don't start throwing up the
guys she could've married.
I'm outta here. He started as a
bricklayer. Now he owns his own company.
And tom o'rourke.
He started as a busboy.
Today he has
his own restaurant.
I started out as a baby.
Today i'm a baby photographer.
I'll see you later. And i'm sure you're
gonna talk about me when i'm gone.
Where do you live, in
vermontwhat took you so long?
Why do you let her mother
get to you?
Forget about her,
will ya?
She never wanted rose
to marry me. Never.
She says i drink too much,
i smoke too much, i gamble.
She's right, but what am i
gonna doi can't control myself.
I got no- what's the
wordi got no- class.
Nah, we know i got class.
It's a certain word. What's the
word for someone who can't say "no"?
Sonya. Not sonya. No, not sonya.
I got no-
willpower! That's the word i'm
lookin' for. I got no willpower.
Yeah, willpower.
Make a left on elm.
I got a quick shoot.
You didn't say anything
about a shoot.
Leave me alone. I got enough
problems. Just take a left on elm.
I got a quick shoot. I'll be quick.
You can help me. Well, thanks.
You really think
i got no class?
No, i don't think
you gotnoclass.
I'm gonna be sad. Mmmmm. Very good!
Now, i'm gonna be a
monster. Watch this. Grrrrr.
Now the big one.
Okay, the big one.
Can you be happy?
That's a good one!
Okay, be happy.
Okay, here goes.
Smile pretty.
Beautiful!
We got it.
The other door. The other door! I got it.
Get outta here.
Oooh!
Oh!
The cake, the cake!
Watch out for the top.
I'm watching, i'm watching.
It's not gonna slide around in there?
No, i got it wedged against a toilet.
Just great.
My favorite system a lock.
And i got monty in the truck
with a wedding cake.
I gotta pick up my mother,
take her to the beauty parlor.
What's the tip?
Big boy in the fifth.
Forget it!
The fifth goes off at 3:00.
- We goin' to the track?
- I can't go. I got a bar to run.
This here's a sure thing.
It's forty to one.
Hey!
Wake up, we're closing up.
I didn't finish my drink.
You're finished now. Get
outta here. Here's your dollar.
Come on, we've got
five minutes to post.
Hey! Get the hell
out of there!
Slow down.
They're kids.
Nicky, take care of it.
What're you doing?
Sixty seconds to post time.
You're next.
What?
Are you gonna place a bet?
Oh, yes, yes. I'd like the
number... seven horse please.
Thirty seconds to post time.
I'd like to put two dollars
to win, two dollars to place...
and two dollars to show.
Okay, buddy, good luck.
The next time you bet,
remember, instead of saying...
fifteen seconds to post time. Two dollars to
win, two dollars to place, two dollars to show,
just say,
"two across the board."
Gee, instead
- what are you buyin', a house?
Let's go while we're young.
We're gonna get
shut out!
I have a friend that wants to bet the
number seven horse. Two seconds to post time.
Number six horse.
Six horse.
No more bets.
And they're off!
Here they go! Nicky, come
on. We're goin' to the rail.
Big boy making up lots of ground
on the outside,
moving to the fourth spot.
Here comes big boy
on the extreme outside.
How's he doin'?
Gettin' farther ahead all
the time. Gimme those things.
Five lengths ahead!
Fifty bucks
at forty to one!
That's two grand apiece!
Two grand!
You dragged me out here!
I love ya, i love ya!
That's two grand apiece!
I'm goin' to hawaii! I'm goin'
to hawaii! He's fallin' back.
I'm not goin' to hawaii!
He's too far ahead
to lose.
He thinks he's water skiing!
We were in. What happened?
Yeah, there's our winner.
I closed my bar!
Get outta here!
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you, bosco!
I'll kill him.
I'll kill you!
There was supposed to be-
crooks!
I was gonna buy
a new neon sign.
Yeah, that's it.
Step on his face!
That son of a bitch!
Go get him, nicky!
My bridesmaids' dresses
are lime green.
And my maid of honor
is wearing lime green.
The maid of honor's dress should always
be in contrast to the bridesmaids.
This is, um, delicious!
What do you call itchicken.
I know it's chicken, dear, but
what kindthere's kiev, florentine-
shake & bake!
Mother, i'm glad
you could come.
I've always been sorry
you missed my wedding.
You know i couldn't go to your
wedding. That's 'cause daddy was there.
Where is your father tonight,
deartaking baby pictures.
Ha! What kind of a baby is it
that's still up at 9:00 at night?
Sweetheart,
watch out for this guy.
He'll buy you a bottle of beer, and
then squeeze the "schlitz" outta ya.
He's my friend.
Don't worry about him.
Excuse me, miss. I don't mean to
interrupt while you're working.
I was wondering if you could come
over to the house sunday for dinner...
and meet my mother?
You gettin' tiredwanna go
homehe's kiddin' around.
Excuse me, pal. You got a
problem herethis is my friend.
Who are you?
Who am i?
I'm the guy that put the bathrooms
in this joint. That's who i am.
Now i know why the place stinks,
okay, pal?
Break it up, will ya?
What's the matter?
Take it easy, will ya?
Ma?
Hmm?
Am i pretty?
Oh, you're beautiful,
sweetheart!
Julio's a very lucky boy.
I wanna make him happy.
But there's so much
i don't know.
Like what?
Like about, you know.
I know what?
You know!
Oh, that!
Didn't your father tell you
everything you need to know?
He keeps starting,
but he never finishes.
What do you wanna know?
Foreplay. Have you ever heard of foreplay?
No, not with
your father.
It's nice we can have
these little talks.
Let's go help belinda
pour the coffee. Wait, mom.
How did you know
you really loved daddy?
We were at coney island
on the ferris wheel.
We got caught
at the top.
Later on,
i found out...
he paid the man a dollar
to stop the ride.
Your father said things
to me...
that were so sweet,
so romantic.
I said to myself,
"here's a sensitive man."
Once, a fuckin' four!
Four!
Got a four!
Gimme the dice, i'm hot. Gimme the dice.
Hold it, hold it! You
won, rightright, yeah.
We're ahead. We can leave
winners right now. Okay, so we go.
Let's go. Double or nothin'. Here we go.
Oh, monty!
You did it again, huh?
We were winners.
We could've walked away.
That's how i am. Once i
get goin', i can't stop.
Come on. Forget about it.
It's history. Let's go.
Good stuff. It oughta
be. I got it off a cop.
I'm starvin'. Let's go to
lucky's. He's open late.
He's closed. Come on, pop's
inside. He'll let us in.
Pop's last dish.
We're drivin' a half hour. The closest
we came to food, we almost hit a deer.
Here's a place.
I'm so hungry,
i could eat a waitress.
No, no! No! It's wrong.
Nicky, it's wrong. I wanna see-
it's wrong!
It's wedding cake flavor.
I love wedding cake.
Why don't you get married?
Let me just lick the bride.
That's my daughter!
It's a little plastic thing.
It's not your daughter.
Only one little flower each.
There's a lot of flowers.
Nobody will know the difference.
Forget about it.
Let's get outta here.
And don't drive fast.
You're drunk.
Don't worry about it. I
drive better when i'm drunk.
You got a weird sense of humor.
You know that?
You laugh at everything.
Weather reports, car chase.
Keep it straight. You're
swerving all over the place.
I'm goin' straight. I'm on
the yellow line, i told ya.
Move over to one side. You're
on the other side! Get over here!
Keep to the right! Get
your hands off the wheel!
Look out!
My head!
I hit my head!
What's so funnyeverything's
funny to you. You laugh and laugh.
Watch the road, will ya?
Will you watch the road?
I lost my joint.
Where's my joint?
Just watch the road.
You got some aspirin?
Oh, no!
I'm sorry.
It was an emergency.
Are you sure this is a good ideadaddy.
Isn't she beautiful?
Yeah, but who's that
with her?
What do you see
in this guy?
He has everything i ever wanted.
You don't ask for much, do ya?
Did your mother tell you
everything you need to know?
She taught me how to fry
bananas. Oh, beautiful.
You'll end up working
in a spanish restaurant.
You're not pregnant,
are you?
Daddy!
The way you brought me up?
All right.
Welcome, allison.
Welcome, uh, julio.
Julio vidal o'campo,
will you have allison...
juliana capuletti,
to be your wife,
to live together in the
covenant of marriageshh!
Will you love her, comfort
her, honor her and keep her...
in sickness and in health,
and forsaking all others, be faithful
to her for as long as you both live?
I do.
Where's your father?
He's directing traffic.
Please, let's go. Get outta
here. Come on, towards me.
Back up, back up! Turn the
wheel to the right. The wheel!
Where're you goin'what's happening
herewe gotta get outta here.
Hold it, will yahe ain't goin'
nowhere. What's your problem?
Hey!
Whoo!
Why didn't he fix the walk?
It's been this way for months!
Why can't you make everybody happy
and shake hands with this kid?
Not me.
Shake hands with him.
Go ahead.
Look at him. If i look at
him, i won't shake hands!
Look at him.
Go ahead.
Look, julio. We're family now, all right?
Just do the right thing.
Make allison happy.
She's a great girl. I know,
i lived with her for 18 years.
Can i call you... dad?
Oh, it's wonderful
to see you two get along.
Good-bye, honey!
Hey, what are we doin' heremy
glass is empty. Come on, will ya?
Wow.
This is it.
Yeah,
our first motel room.
Okay, let's get the guy up
here who paid for this shindig.
Hold it, hold it.
Let him talk.
I got nothin' to say.
Then sing a song. I sang.
I can't sing. Are you
kiddin'sing "la consonetta."
I'm no sinatra,
but here it goes. Okay?
Some think the world was made
for fun and frolic?
And so do i
and so do i?
Some think it's right to be
so melancholic?
They'll pine and sigh
they'll pine and sigh?
But i i like to spend my time a-singing?
Some joyous song
some joyous song?
To set the air
with music ever ringing?
Is far from wrong
is far from wrong?
Hark it, hark it
music from afar?
with a happy heart?
Funiculi, funicula
funiculi, funicula?
Joy is everywhere
Hark it, hark it
music from afar?
with a happy heart?
Funiculi, funicula
funiculi, funicula?
Joy is everywhere
Hark it, hark it
music from afar?
with a happy heart?
Funiculi, funicula
funiculi, funicula?
Joy is everywhere
How do i look?
You look beautiful.
I always dreamed
about my wedding day.
I guess i never thought
about the night.
Be gentle with me.
Julio!
This is foreplay.
I have a headache. I don't
wanna touch your head.
Please, julio, i've never
been with a man before.
Neither have i!
Julio!
What's wrong with you?
I don't know what to do.
I brought a book.
A book?
El joyo de sexo.
It's in spanish. I'm
gonna translate it for you.
It has a very happy ending.
You're gonna love it.
Allison?
What do you want from me,
julio?
I never seen anything
like that.
Try to understand.
I keep hearing
my father say, "don't."
He meant before
you were married.
I'm not so sure.
You don't know my father.
Allison,
listen to me.
My cousin
once knew a guy,
and the guy went out
with a virgin...
for six months.
And on their wedding night,
when they got married,
and they wanted
to consummate the marriage,
the woman wouldn't let him.
And in the morning,
they found
the guy dead...
in the bed
next to her.
Oh.
Allison?
I don't wanna die.
You're my wife.
Yeah.
I love you.
We're all alone.
And your father,
he is a
million miles away.
Hello?
Julio, i just wanna say
good night to my little baby.
My father!
You hung up on my fatheri
wouldn't hang up on your father.
You wouldn't understand
my father.
Yeahwell, i'm not so sure
i understand you either.
Then why don't you go spend your
wedding night with your father?
Okay... i will!
Monty, don't forget to fix the walk. Yeah.
Watch it, watch it!
Watch where you're goin'!
My air mail!
Oh, my air mail!
Listen to me.
I want my wife back.
Look who's here.
Don juan.
It's your fault she left
me. What, am i responsible?
When eddie fisher broke up with debbie,
you blame meshe don't wanna see ya.
You gotta help me, man. Give her time.
She'll come back when she's ready.
You oughta give her
a few drinks.
That's how
i got her mother ready.
I'm in.
It's up to you, paddy.
Yeah.
What the hell is that you got
onthis used to be a shirt.
You know rose. She don't throw nothin'
out. She keeps lookin' at the cuffs.
Soon as they get frayed, it
becomes a short-sleeve shirt.
When the collar goes,
i end up with a pajama top.
Right now i got
23 short-sleeve pajama tops.
You know what i found in the
closeta hundred 1978 calendars.
That's rose!
If 1978 ever comes back, we're in great
shape. We gonna talk or play cards?
He'll talk.
Nicky, take it easy.
Take it easy.
He didn't mean it.
Monty, the phone.
Hellohello?
Monty,
you have to pick it up.
You got the wrong number.
There's nobody home. We're asleep.
Mr. Capuletti?
Are you there?
Monty, who is it?
Hellohello!
Anyone there?
Ah, ah.
Who know a scrappleton?
That's mother's lawyer.
Yeah. Yeah?
That's awful!
No, no. I'm sorry. I'll tell her.
I'll tell her.
I'm sorry.
Monty, what happened?
Rose, you better sit down
for this.
Is it... mother?
Rose, there was
a plane crash.
Your mother...
earned her wings.
It's all right.
It's all right, baby.
"And to my nephew clive,
"son of my beloved
departed brother,
"whom i've undertaken
to raise as a son of my own,
"inasmuch as he has always
led a simple, virtuous life,
"and because it is my wish
that he continue to do so,
"i bequeath to him an additional
income of $5,000 a year...
for the rest of his life."
Ah... there must be
some mistake.
There must be some more zeroes. No.
Um, a comma?
No.
"To my beloved daughter, rose,
"burdened as she is with cares
and responsibilities,
"i bequeath the remainder
of my estate,
"which includes
monahan's department store,
estimated worth,
$10 million."
Oh!
"If, and only if,
her husband monty...
can reform himself
in one year."
What kind of reform?
There is a codicil attached
to the will, mr. "capalooti."
That's capuletti.
Mr. Capuletti.
Which lists the activities
which are to be proscribed:
That is, the things
you must refrain from.
No smoking.
No philandering.
No gambling. No drugs. No alcohol.
No alcoholdoes that go
for beer toocertainly.
And you must weigh not more
than 175 pounds. Question.
Assuming monty can't reform-
perish the thought.
Oh, then you get the money.
I do?
- Forget about it. I'm not doin' it.
- You're right, forget it.
Daddy, you can do it!
It's $10 million!
Oh, and mr. "capalooti,"
should you decide to accept
these terms,
remember...
we'll be watching you.
I need a drink and a cigarette
so i can think this over.
Twelve months?
Forget about it.
You can do that standing on
your head. It's easy money.
Hey, that's a lot of money.
That could parlay
into a fortune for you.
I couldn't care less, monty,
but think of the kids.
- Think about mommy.
- Think of your wife, and your kids.
Think of me, ya bum!
Monty, breakfast is ready.
Oh, breakfast.
Beautiful.
I stopped smoking.
I'm starvin'.
Dad, pass the syrup.
Here, here.
You gave me the wrong plate. Where's
the rest of my eggs and my home fries?
These are the rest of your
eggs, these are your home fries,
and this is applesauce.
Belinda, i can't eat all my
home fries. Want some home fries?
No, thanks.
Here, monty.
Oohhh, pass them to belinda.
If you wanna lose weight,
you should start now.
Ooh, food.
It's a tough give-up.
Allison, eat.
Allison, you gotta eat.
I know marriage is rough.
It's not all moonlight and
canoes. That's in the movies.
I don't wanna talk about it.
What's the matter with you?
You don't eat.
You don't talk to no one.
You lock yourself
in your room all night.
The way you're carrying on,
you'll never meet another guy.
What'd i say?
"You'll never meet
another guy."
Take out the garbage.
I didn't even eat,
i gotta take out the garbage.
Hi.
She ain't worth
$10 million.
$5 million, maybe.
Hey, not here!
Not here!
I'm your new neighbor, bill
jones. Call me bill. Not here!
- Take him on your property.
- You interrupt king's business, he gets very upset.
What makes you think
i wanna inherit his business?
If you feel so bad,
i'll clean it up.
So you're monty capuletti!
Congratulations on your daughter's wedding.
Some party, i heard. What am i
telling you foryou were there.
Look, i'm your neighbor, so we
gotta get to be good buddies.
I wanna have a relationship. Most important
thing for us, we gotta have a good rapport.
Wait till you meet ginger.
She's my better half.
I already saw your better half.
In fact, i saw more than half.
She's a dynamite girl. I met her
in vegas a couple of years ago.
Oh, man, she's a loving, caring, sharing
person. Maybe you can become friendly.
I need you two to move in. I'm nervous
enough this morning. Are you kiddin'?
Nervousmaybe you need
a little... smoke.
Little ups, little downs, little
somethingi got anything you need.
What are you talkin' to me about drugs
fori got my daughter here. She's 12.
Look, you got a connection in
the family already, stick with it.
But just this once, i'll tell you
what, my friend. Let me be santa claus.
There's one, two, from me to
you. We'll take a hike. Come on.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Two, four, six, eight, ten.
This is ridiculous.
But jogging's
good for you.
Thanks to jogging, more people than
ever are dropping dead in perfect health.
Five more.
Celebrity pizza. Send
the usual. Eight pies.
Two lollobrigidas, two
jerry vales, two pavarottis,
one caruso
and a frank nitti.
Monty, is that youyeah. I got a cold.
Stay right there.
I'll get some money.
What am i askingfor one slice.
You can stay up late, all right?
The top one
had anchovies.
All right, who's in?
Come on,
pick the date he blows it.
Great guy you are,
you know that?
Can't wait till he blows it,
huhbettin' on it and everything.
Listen to you. You some kind of altar boy?
Huhyou're some influence. You gamble in
front of him, you drink in front of him.
Monty see, monty do,
you know.
Hector, hector.
Don't push me.
Listen to me.
It's gonna work.
See these pennies?
You take these pennies, you throw 'em
at the window. I'll be in the bush.
I saw it in a movie.
It's gonna work perfect.
If you need help, listen to
what i'm gonna tell you to say.
Go get 'em.
Where you goingi'll be in the bush.
Throw the pennies.
You're gonna be behind the
bushi'll be right here.
Who's there?
Hey.
How are you?
I was just, uh-
i was in the neighborhood,
and thought i'd stop by,
see what's cooking.
That julio?
Yeah.
What do i say?
Tell her to come down.
Prove to her
you're the man.
Come down.
I'm the man.
Get tough.
Tell her you're bad.
I'm bad.
Like you mean it.
Allison!
I'm bad.
No, no, no!
Jump up and down.
I am so bad! I am so bad! Be angry.
Who are you talking to?
Julio... and a hedge.
I'm so bad,
i should be in detention.
No. Be mean.
Wave your arms.
Make believe you're angry.
Listen to me.
I'm not that kind of guy...
that's gonna start playing around
in the driveway of a tract house!
I'm not gonna lose my temper
in front of the woman i love!
Get on your knees.
Beg her.
Tell her you're thinking
of killing yourself.
No.
I don't talk like that.
Do you hear me?
If you know so much about
women, you talk to her.
The hedge,
allison capuletti.
Allison, the hedge
has a few words to say to you.
I don't know what to say. Oh,
now you don't know what to say!
Allison, julio's
very unhappy.
You made a fool out of me! Get
off of my ear! Let go of my leg!
Saturday lunch. I can have
a piece of fruit, citrus,
or four ounces of fish.
I think i'll have
the fruit.
Sometimes with the fish, these
guys go over. What'll you have?
Two with sauerkraut and a yoo-hoo. Got it.
Two with sauerkraut.
Yoo-hoo.
What do you want, buddy?
Nothin'. I'll just smell his.
You know why i'm going through this
whole thingfor my kids, that's why.
That's the greatest love in the
world, your kids. You can't beat it.
That's why you do things.
That's love, for your kids.
See that man over there
with his kid?
That's love. Look at the way he loves
the kid, bouncing him on his knee.
That's love, baby. There he is!
Thank goodness he's all right!
I'm sitting here minding my
business, he jumped on my lap.
Get away from my kid!
Everybody calm down.
Do you have some identification?
It's in my other raincoat.
Never wander away from mommy
again. Spit that out right now!
Come on.
It's all ready.
Come on, give it a shot.
You gotta go
30 miles an hour...
for 15 minutes
for it to do anything.
Faster, faster.
Come on.
Faster. You gotta
get it up to speed.
Faster, faster, faster!
Faster. 30 miles.
Faster. Faster.
Oh, my-
oh, no! Oh.
Come on. Keep quiet.
Keep your head down.
Is my hair too flat?
No.
You look great.
Come on.
Come on. Okay. Gimme that.
It's locked. Let's go play space invaders.
No. We'll go up
the drain pipe.
Don't worry about it.
Everything's gonna be all right.
All you gotta do
is climb up.
Come on.
You can do it!
You bad!
I had to hook up with the only virgin
in new york. Didn't they teach this...
at schoolthey taught math at
your school, but you can't divide.
At least
i can multiply.
You sure this is
allison's bedroom?
I know this place
like the back of my hand.
What happenedi got the back
of my hand stuck in the toilet.
Listen to me.
You gotta be quiet.
We gotta be quiet.
Where's the light?
Shh!
That isn't a light.
That's not the light.
And this is not the light.
That's the water pik.
Here's the plan.
I'm gonna go talk
to allison.
When i leave the room,
you-
we're in here.
Just be calm.
Just be calm,
and get out the window.
Ow!
I'll meet you down by the car. Yeah.
I'll be all right.
Don't worry about it.
Julio!
I'll have a number three
with flour tortillas.
Mmm.
Two of them.
Um, i'll have the special. Number one.
I'll have a junior salad.
No dressing.
Why don't you stop
carryin' on?
Rate you're goin', i'll bet you a
hundred bucks you're not gonna make it.
If i bet you,
then i won't make it.
When the going gets tough,
the tough get going.
What if
you're not tough?
You gotta be strong
like me.
Look. What is this?
Nothin'.
Put it right out. It's
not gonna be my master.
Gimme a light, lou.
Mm, monty, gotta
have "discilton."
Discipline.
Can i have your olive?
You got extra olives?
You want the black one
or the green one?
Which one you wantit's up
to you. Take the green one.
Just a minute. Okayyou
gotta stay still. Okay, kid?
You gotta stay still.
Kid, you gotta stay still.
Have you ever seen
a face like that before?
No. If i did,
i'd remember it.
Okay, i'm gonna get a real
good picture now. Okay?
- Look at him! He's got my eyes.
- He's got my nose.
And my sympathy.
All right.
We want some
wallet-size pictures too.
This kid won't fit
in a wallet-size.
Make good pictures.
My wife's very particular.
What about you, john?
He's very particular too.
I'm surprised
you married each other.
All right.
Look, kid.
I'm tired of telling you the same thing.
You gotta stay still. I'll tell you what.
Anthony, i'm gonna make a deal
with you. Anthony, pay attention.
You gotta stay still.
If we wanna get a good picture, we gotta
stay still. We wanna get a good picture.
Stay still.
Help that kid out.
Talk to him, grandma.
Here we go, anthony.
Be quiet.
Stay still.
Quiet, will ya!
Quiet! John, talk to him.
Stay quiet!
Hey, kid,
be quiet, will ya?
Somebody! Will you shut
the fat little bastard up?
What is the law?
Not to go on all fours.
That is the law.
What is the law?
Not to shed blood.
...his prices are insane!
[Star spangled banner
all we need is one pin,
rodney.
Now, back tolost weekend.
He who breaks the law must
go to the house of pain.
Back to the pain!
Monty.
Tsk, tsk.
Monty, it's 3:00
in the morning.
Come to bed. You haven't had
a decent night's sleep in weeks.
I don't know how to sleep.
I know how to pass out.
Maybe you should see
a doctor.
If i see a doctor, i'll blow the whole
thing. They give you sleeping pills.
You know what i do
when i can't sleep?
What?
I knit.
Maybe i'll knit myself
a beer.
How about some hot milk?
It'll do you good.
I'll try anything.
Hot milk.
Come on.
Monty, i know what
you're going through.
Do you wanna talk
about it?
You know your friend
blanche genarouh-huh.
Her kid anthonyi called
him a fat little bastard.
Very funny. We're laughin'
and i'm out of a job.
Monty, you're
a great photographer.
You'll get another job.
Yeahwhen?
Meanwhile,
i got nothing to do.
What do people do when
they're not getting loaded?
What you have to do
is change your habits.
Yeah?
Who you been talking to?
Mrs. Dugan.
She's an expert.
She had three husbands.
They all died of alcohol.
She's no expert,
she's a carrier.
You know what
i was thinking about today?
Coney island.
When the kids were small?
Remember the time you put
allison on the pony...
and you tried to make the pony
smile to make allison smile?
I never laughed so hard.
That was the good old days.
If i make it through this,
i'll buy you coney island.
I don't need coney island.
I need you.
[Violin continues
[violin continues
hi, nicky.
Hi, rose.
Hey, kid.
Oh, yo, nick.
- What are you playing, mozart?
- Scales.
Scales?
Never heard of him.
[Violin continues
rose! Rose!
Rose!
Hey, whoa!
What are you doin'?
Are you crackin' up?
I tell you, nicky, it's rough. It's rough.
What's the matter with you?
What is this?
Rose told me
i need hobbies.
I'm making a plane.
It's a messerschmitt.
It's a nice job.
I'm fed up with everything.
I wanna go to sleep and wake up four
months from now when it's all over.
You know what your problem is?
This whole thing ain't real to you.
You don't know what you're coming into.
Did you ever see monahan's department store?
Once from the outside
when i dropped rose off.
Why don't we go see it from the
insidewe'll have a few laughs.
Huhcome on.
I need a new shirt anyway.
Rose, there's a messerschmitt in
the kitchen. Clean it up, will ya?
Some joint, huh?
When you take over,
let me fix the bathrooms here.
They don't go
to the bathroom here.
See this?
Could somebody help us here?
I don't think so.
My friend here,
he's look-
my friend here,
he's lookin' for a shirt.
Yeah. You have something in a dark black?
He wants something he can
wear four, five days in a row.
You have any men's shirts
for men?
Have you tried
the army/navy store?
Very funny. One more word
out of you, and he gets it.
Come on.
Why don't you two put your heads
together, make an ass out of yourselves?
Where're you goin'it
says, "come in and browse."
May i help youno,
thank you. Just browsing.
What have they got
in this place, antiques?
No, those are
the customers.
May i help youno, thanks. Just browsing.
How long do you
intend to browse?
That lady, you didn't ask her
how long she intends to browse.
How come you're asking us how long we intend
to browseyou don't look like browsers.
What do browsers look like?
Maybe i'm half browser.
On his father's side. Nevertheless, i
prefer that you do not browse any longer.
It's a free country. If these
people can browse, we can browse.
Nicky, let's show the lady
we're browsers, huh?
Hey, look at us.
We're browsing.
Hey, ducks in heat.
Please! That's 18th century.
Folks, better keep browsing
or she'll kick you out of here.
- Look at us. We're browsing.
- Is this an odd or an end?
Lady, if i buy two odds,
will you show us your end?
Ohh!
Security. Security!
Security!
Yesyesmr. Barlow please.
What is itdo you know a monty capuletti?
Yes. Well, he's on his way upstairs.
Is he?
Gentlemen, let's shelve these
petty matters for the moment.
The son-in-law of our late, beloved
president is on his way to join us,
so let's just sit around
and smoke and drink.
Brent, brice!
Make up your mind.
Which one of us do you like?
Down the hatch.
Mr. Barlow, this joker
says he knows you.
This joker is part
of the monahan family, gus.
Oh, sorry, sir.
People, this is monty capuletti
and his friend, nick "marino."
No need to stand. Monty,
what brings you here?
Nicky was lookin' to get a
shirt, but we couldn't find any.
You got nothin' in this store
nobody wants to buy.
Monahan's has
an upscale clientele.
All our gentlemen customers
are very conscious of style.
Men don't have style.
Men wear clothes.
Women have style.
What sort of shirt
were you looking for?
A regular shirt.
See this shirtevery guy on
our block's got one of these.
You guys don't dress regular.
You got on vests.
It's hot as hell here.
These gentlemen and ladies were
handpicked to work for me...
and dress accordingly.
Where'd you find these guys,
noah's ark?
And you. There's a lot of
trouble finding your fly.
I really must apologize.
I've made a mistake. I didn't
realize what your true talents were.
Oh, no. You have such fashion sense.
Everything we've been buying...
wrong. All wrong. Tell us more.
Your pants.
Our pants.
You gotta have pants
with lots of room...
so when you sit down,
they don't split.
And zippers that work easy so you
can fix your shorts. Know what i mean?
Les slacks blousants avec
le zip. Whatever you say.
What about shoesyou need
shoes that go on and off easy.
You know, no shoe horn. And
no laces. They slow you up.
Yes, i see that.
Chunky, black mailman oxfords,
with adorable white cotton socks.
Big blousy bowling shirts.
"Mel.
The regular guy look."
Whatyou can't be this crazy.
He looks like a rummage sale.
I know what i'm doing. This is the
opportunity i've been waiting for.
The boredom of unemployment
could really drive a man to drink.
So could you too. Take it
easy, nicky. Take it easy.
We need a mind
like yours.
I'd like to offer you a position
as fashion consultant to monahan's.
Who mei'm no fashion consultant.
What's the matter with you?
Take the job.
The first thing we do
is fire that broad downstairs...
that stopped us
from browsing.
Get me sergio. Track down alfonso.
Draw up a budget for mr. Capuletti.
Let's leak the story
to the press.
Hello.
Mr. Capuletti, please.
It's for you. It's your wife.
Rose, they took
all my clothes!
When are you
coming home?
How can i come home?
I got nothing to wear.
I'll call you later.
Take this.
Turn away, please.
Next shirt.
Take it easy, honey.
I got no good side.
Could you please
turn away?
Scrape the gum off the soles
and analyze the shoes.
Should these shorts be duplicated?
Duplicated and fumigated.
Next. I have the blacks for the shirts.
That's mr. Capuletti's
department now.
I have midnight black,
raven black, licorice black-
if nicky was here, you'd
have black-and-blue black.
Twelve inches.
Boy, you're way off.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Compliments of monty capuletti,
invitations to the premiere of
monahan's "the regular guy look."
Barkeeper, i'll have
a perrier with a twist.
I'm sorry. I only have
perrier on draft.
Nicholas, patrick,
how good to see you again.
I know what you're thinking.
Why am i slumming?
I'm here to hand-deliver
these invitations to you.
But i'm not sure
if you should attend.
We're his friends.
We'll be there. Gimme.
It's your decision. I'm sure your
intentions are the best, but think about it.
It's not good for monty to associate
with people who do what heusedto do.
We would protect him from
that. He's talking about us.
If you really are monty's friends,
you'll stop making it hard for him.
Look at you.
You're smoking, drinking.
We're in a bar. What
do you expect us to do?
You must think
i'm stupid or something.
I look like
i just got off a boat?
I know what you're trying to do. Get
out of here before i give you a slap.
Nicky, take it easy.
Nick, you do want monty to
have the money, don't you?
What do you let it get to you
forhe just wants the money.
But what bothers me is
he's right. So he's right.
Think he's right?
I mean, nicky's his coach.
He tells him eat fruit,
tells him to exercise.
It's not what he says, it's
what we do. It's peer pressure.
Oh, yeah.
Our lives are attractive.
I guess nicky and paddy
won't show.
They didn't call,
either, huh?
No.
Tonight, we present...
our tribute to
the american silhouette.
Ladies and gentlemen,
"the regular guy look."
Jonathan and billy are wearing the
regular guy leisure look for fall.
Bold print, double-knit
polyester pants...
with totally non-coordinated
print shirts.
Pie is wearing
the italian restaurant look.
Perfect for picnics where you
can be your own tablecloth.
Tie has the bowling alley
sportif look.
Next up, peter,
wearing...
the regular guy
lounge look in black...
on black, on black.
I think they like it.
Everyone's smiling.
You like to gambletake a
chance on the regular guy robe.
American classic...
iridescent blue
sharkskin.
That suit.
Look at that suit.
Have you seen
the suit-
and now...
i'd like to introduce the man
responsible for this evening.
Mr. Monty capuletti!
Take a bow, monty.
Fatty. Eating again,
fatty, fatty?
Fatty, fatty.
Eating again, fatty, fatty?
Fatty, fatty, fatty-
who put this in here?
I was trying to help.
Don't help. I'm tired of
people trying to help me.
Monty, calm down.
What are you lookin' at?
Go clean your room.
It's a pigsty.
Leave me alone!
I know what you're thinkin' too. Oh, god.
All i ever wanted
was a happy family.
That's all i ever asked for,
a happy family.
A family that loved each other.
I never cared about anything else.
Stop it.
I can't take it no more.
Money caused all this.
I don't wanna be rich.
We're not supposed to be rich.
We don't look rich, we don't
talk rich, we don't smell rich!
No more rich! I want our
house to be the way it was.
Hey, fatty, fatty.
Monty, where are you goingi'll
be at louie's... gettin' drunk.
Take this, julio.
Go and get her.
She's your wife. Go get
her. Right, she's my wife.
A gun.
I don't want a gun.
Go back and get her,
julio.
I must've been nuts
to do this for-
ah, look who's here.
I want her back, man.
She's mine.
Put that thing away.
You'll hurt yourself.
I'm in no mood for you.
There is no mood for you.
Nurse!
Where is she?
They're never here
when you need 'em.
Boy, oh, boy.
Oh, nurse, you're here.
Where were you, huh?
Three hundred and fifty bucks
a day, where are ya?
Where are ya?
Look at this.
I'm dying of thirst here.
Hey, how ya doin'i heard
about your unfortunate incident.
Where were you
when i needed you?
I came to make up.
I'm sorry.
All right, nicky, we're friends.
All right?
It must be tough
eatin', huh?
Eatyou should see me go to the bathroom.
Monty! Hi, nicky. We're
back. Rose, you're here.
How's our patient today?
Oh, he looks much better.
How did you sleepare you
kiddin'i was up all night.
Let's look at the chart.
He was hit in the fleshy
area of the gluteus maximus.
Ah, you're wrong.
He got me in the ass.
No vital areas
were damaged.
No doubt he'll recover. How
long do i have to be here?
Let me see now. Perhaps we
might have to keep you here...
for four,
maybe five weeks.
I'm not hangin' here
for five weeks.
At least i know you're
gonna be all right.
I gotta pick up my mother at the
beauty parlor. So long, nicky.
How are you feeling today?
You're looking good.
Oh, daddy!
I never realized how much
julio loved me.
It was the most
romantic moment of my life...
when he almost killed you.
Can i call you "dad" now?
Take it easy!
These are new stitches,
you know.
Why can't you forgive
and forget?
How could i forgetevery time
i sit down, i'll think of him.
Monty, how are you?
What an insensitive question.
You've been shot.
This'll cheer you up.
We're a hit.
What are you talking about?
They all laughed at me.
But we're laughing now,
all the way to my bank.
Look at this.
What?
We put the clothes in the window,
and the kids went crazy for it.
I don't understand it,
but who cares?
The regular guy look
is a big success.
You did the regular guy looki just
bought two of your short-sleeve pajama tops.
Rose, i gotta get out of
here. Daddy, this is great!
By the time you get out of the
hospital, we'll have the money.
And you'll lose weight too.
I saw the food. Monty, she's
right. Your ship's come in.
But my pier collapsed.
Everyone out. Visiting
hours are over. Please!
We have sick men in here.
You too, doctor. Please.
Excuse me,
the two of you.
This is a hospital.
Hey, come on, let's go.
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
My good-
excuse me. Will you get outlet's go!
Daddy!
How are you, mr. "manuccl"bye, monty.
Martha's gonna take good care
of you today. How was your lunch?
I see you haven't eaten much
of it. I don't blame you, honey.
While i'm up here,
check my oil.
Jesus. We trust you had
a pleasant swim, sir.
Your shirt. I don't want
that shirt. Are you kiddin'?
But you should be dressed to your
station. I don't want to wear that!
Yesthis is mr.
Capuletti's business advisor.
What can i do for youbetter
yet, what can you do for me?
Silver is downcall the lone
ranger. He'll cheer him up.
Hello.
Oil wells?
Very interesting.
Meatballs, sir?
No.
Madam?
Meatball, sir?
Where's the pistachio nutsthere's
too much trouble with the shells.
Oh, yeah?
I like the shells.
Hmm.
You got any salami
or provolone?
Salami, salami.
Provolone.
Give it to him.
Why don't you get some sun
and come back next week?
Julio?
Julio.
Oh, you bad boy.
You were hiding from me.
No.
I found you now.
You gonna play with me?
Not... again.
Look what i wore just for
you. Allison, i'm exhausted.
Chapter six,
"el joyo."
You hired a captainyep.
Everything's taken care of.
He know how to get to coney
islandyeah, i told him. It's easy.
Here, i'll show you.
You go north up the atlantic,
west into the hudson.
Come to the statue of that
broad, you hang a right.
Takes 20 minutes,
a half hour with traffic.
Tell him to shove off as soon as i
sign those papers with scrappleton.
What's that,
a fire drill?
It's lunch. Come on.
I'm starving. Let's go.
Congratulations. Daddy, i
just saw the cutest dingy.
Allison, you're married
to julio.
This is the life, huhand they
say money can't buy happiness.
At least you can pick
your own kind of misery.
Clive, you're the only one who hasn't
seen my stitches. Want to take a look?
Ooh. Ooh. Ahh!
Oh, no!
Ahh!
Excuse me.
Mr. Daniel scrappleton,
sir.
Hey, scrappy, show me
that dotted line, huh?
And mrs. Kathleen monahan.
Oh, no!
My god! It's mother. She's back from
the dead. She's better than houdini.
I've never felt better
in my life!
Grandma, did you bring me
anythinga hat just like mine.
You never felt better?
You were in a plane crash.
There was no crash. I
made up the whole thing.
Whyrose, i did it for
you and the grandchildren.
Someone had to stop
monty's debauchery.
He was going to hell in a
hand basket. Yes, quite true.
And to test you as well. You failed!
I'll kill her. I'll kill her! Take it easy.
I'll kill her!
Let me go!
Boy, you got some nerve
still being alive.
I went through
this whole thing for nothin'?
No, not for nothing, monty.
You proved yourself to me.
And to make sure that you
stay on the straight and narrow,
i'm moving in with you.
What's for dessert?
Spumoni, miss.
Your favorite, monty.
Shrimpton,
none for mr. Capuletti.
Right, mom.
And shrimpton.
Mr. Capuletti is skipping
the coffee too.
It'll keep me awake,
right, momright, dear.
And shrimpton, i noticed a bottle
of beer in the refrigerator.
Get rid of it. Tsk, tsk,
tsk. Right again, mom.
Well, i guess that's it
for me.
I think i'll go out and walk
off all these vegetables.
And after that...
it's bedtime.
Good night, honey.
Good night, sweetheart.
And shrimpton?
Yes, sir.
You better get rid of that
glazed fruit too. It's fattening.
Certainly, sir.
Good night, belinda.
Good night, daddy.
Ooh.
Good night, mom.
Hey, mom. That perfume is driving me crazy.
I think i married rose
to get to you, huh?
Good night, all.
Rose,
he's a changed man.
- Finally, you've got a good marriage.
- We had a good marriage before.
Yes, but now you're married
to a human being.
I don't mind telling you,
i'm proud of what i did.
It wasn't easy,
but now i've got him
under control!
Where's the pizza?
I'm starving!
Monty, where you beenwe're
keeping it warm for you.
Wait a minute. Don't
get grease on the cards.
Gimme the red pepper,
will you?
Gimme a napkin.
What'd you tell her tonighttonight?
I told her her perfume
is driving me crazy.
Then i told her i married rose
to get to her.
Gimme a beer.
My mother-in-law. For years i wouldn't
kiss her face, i ended up kissin' her ass.
All right?
You don't have to talk
all night?
I'm a man
who can't say no?
You don't have to twist
my arm?
Just point me
where you wanna go?
Take me to the action
take me to the track?
Take me to a party if
they're bettin' in the back?
I've been workin' all my life
can't afford to wait?
Let me call my wife so
i can tell her i'll be late?
I want the easy
mmm?
Easy, easy money?
I could get lucky?
Oh, things could go right?
I want the easy?
Easy, easy money?
Maybe this one time?
Maybe tonight?
You don't have
to try too hard?
I don't need
a song and dance?
an invitation?
If you've got
a game of chance?
Take me to the tables
take me to the fights?
Run me like the numbers
roll me like the dice?
When you're countin' on a
killin' always count me in?
Talk me into losin'
just as long as i can win?
I want the easy?
Easy, easy money?
I want the good times?
Oh, i never had?
I want the easy?
Mmm, easy money
ooh?
Oh, i want the good life?
Mmm, i want it bad?
Easy money
you say i fool myself?
But better me than being
a fool for someone else?
I got a hot slot machine
of a system ready to go?
Easy money?
I got a one-track mind and a
good reputation layin' on the line?
I'll either come back
a bum or a king?
Baby, i don't know?
Ahh-hah?
You sure don't have
to start a fight?
I'm a man
who can't say no?
If you got
a little risky business?
Just point me
where you wanna go?
Take me to the power
take me to the heat?
Take me to the cleaners
if it's open to the streets?
Something's got to pay off
someone's got to break?
Someone's got a fortune that
they're begging me to take?
I want the easy?
Easy, easy money?
I could get lucky?
Things could go right?
Oh, i want the easy?
Easy, easy money?
Maybe just this time?
Oh, maybe tonight?
Easy money?
I don't want no hard cash?
I just want the easy money?
Oh, oh
i could get lucky?
Easy money?
Oh, i got to, got to-?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org