Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
How I miss Scotland and the sea.
The sea. There's nothing like it
in all the earth.
Salt in your face, the wind at your back
and all the world before you.
Freer than a bird in the air
or a fish in the ocean.
To be free. I reckon that's why I joined
the second war to end all wars.
I was studying to be a teacher
when the call to arms occurred.
I eagerly put aside my studies
for the glory of action.
I stopped reading history
and became a part of it.
I joined the Argyll
and Sutherland Highlanders
and became Captain Ernest Gordon.
My commanding officer was
Lieutenant Colonel Stuart McLean
the finest commander
the 93rd Battalion ever had.
A man of deep loyalties to his country
his duty and his men.
A loyalty that was soon to be matched by
his second-in-command, Major lan Campbell
a man of passionate devotion
to the Colonel as well as the cause.
It was our loyalties
that would eventually be tested.
The Argylls had a legacy of being
the last line of defence.
And we were to prove that legacy
once again
in the face of defeat and capture
by the enemy.
Sir? Sir?
Are you all right, sir?
You look the devil in the face
with pride, boys!
And try not to shit your kilts!
Bastards are playing with our minds.
When you surrender in war
you're stripped of your dignity as a soldier.
All you've got left is your fellow comrades
many of whom you've just met.
Lieutenant Jim Reardon, Merchant Marine
one of the few Americans in the area.
Attached himself to the Argylls
during the Allied surrender.
We called him Yanker 'cause he was
an American and a bit of a wanker.
Parade... halt!
What's that stench?
That'll be death, Major.
Parade... right wheel!
Parade... halt!
Left turn!
Stand at ease!
Stand easy.
Tenko!
Kiotsuke!
What the hell does "tenko" mean?
Must be roll call.
Today, you will count off in English
but tomorrow and for ever, in Japanese.
- Start counting!
- One.
- Two.
- Three.
Big-eared Nip!
Bastard!
Kora!
This is a shame culture. Make 'em
lose face, you'll pay. Stand easy.
This is an outrage! I am a senior officer.
I will not tolerate this barbaric behaviour.
This man has rights!
Kiotsuke.
Attention, prisoners. You are now captives
of His lmperial Majesty, the Emperor.
Behold... the extreme penalty
for those who try to escape.
This is for your own sake.
You will sign these papers
promising not to escape.
- No escape, my Yankee ass!
- This is against the Geneva Convention.
They don't give two shits about that.
Tomorrow, you will bring these
signed papers from all prisoners.
You are dismissed.
Go, go.
- What did you just say?
- I told him you were stupid.
I don't know whether to thank you
or kick your arse. Lan Campbell.
Dusty Miller.
Where did you learn to speak Japanese?
What about the Colonel?
You want your Colonel back?
I owe the man my life.
- The more hair, the more lice.
- Ow!
Stay close to your cobbers.
But when it comes down to it, it's survival
of the fittest. Every man for himself.
Barter is the name of the game, gents.
They call the hospital the Death House.
You don't wanna end up in here.
Relish your health now, gentlemen.
It's the last you'll see of it.
There are thousands more prisoners
in camps all along the river.
Not too much skinny here from the outside.
Japs keep us in the dark.
No radios. They catch one, they'll kill you.
Officers, try to keep your shirt on.
It'll distinguish you from the grunts
the only thing keeping us from degenerating
into a bloody anarchy.
Shit!
- Where you goin'?
- To find out about the Colonel.
You're just asking for trouble.
- Doc.
- Get him down here.
Easy... easy.
It's my back, my back... my back.
- What the bloody hell happened?
- You didn't bow.
- What?
- Always bow before a guard. Korean or Jap.
Never look 'em in the eyes when they're
bashing you. That's pure defiance.
- Rules of Bushido.
- Bushido?
Their kind of chivalry.
Respect and obligation.
If you don't respect 'em, they feel obligated
to bash you. Nothing personal.
It sure bloody well feels personal.
It works both ways.
They do the same to their own.
- That's a comfort.
- Now, listen, you must understand.
These monsters truly believe
we're an inferior race, less than human.
Now, beating a prisoner to them
is like beating a disobedient dog.
The fiercer the beating, the fiercer
their dedication to the Emperor.
You'll be all right, son.
Make space for the Colonel.
You're buggers
for punishment, you lot.
You should've let him take me instead, sir.
- Anything we can do for you, Colonel?
- Aye... start preparing.
- Preparing for what?
- Escape.
What else, you tow-headed Yank?
Dusty...
...thank you.
Colonel, I've been watching these Nips.
There's never more than a handful guarding
the perimeter. They're not watching closely.
- It doesn't make sense unless...
- What?
Unless every prisoner's been caught
or died in a thousand miles of jungle.
Unless local villagers will turn in
a POW for a bowl of rice.
Unless... escape is impossible.
Excellent!
Yanker... you find the best escape route,
hm?
- Lan...
- Yes, sir?
Start getting survival gear together.
Ernest... get things together
we can trade with the locals.
Yes, sir.
As soon as I'm well... we're on our way.
- Yes, sir.
- OK?
- Yes, sir!
- Sir.
Good boys.
You're good boys. That's my boys.
Hey... how about some extra for
my Colonel. He's in the Death House.
If he can't make it, it means he can't work
so he can't eat. Nip rules. Move along.
- Come on, pal, I'll owe you one.
- He said move along!
You sheep-humping Highlander!
Come on!
What are you, bloody chicken?
- I'll kick your arse!
- Come on, you English fuck!
Come on, then, wanker!
Come on!
What does it take
for a man to lose his dignity?
Come on, you English fuck!
How far can he fall
to pay the price of survival?
Dusty built a sanctuary outside the camp
called The Church Without Walls.
We were allowed to visit it freely.
They knew we had nowhere to go.
Tell you what I'm gonnae do
when I get back to Glasgow.
I'm gonna visit my favourite pub
I'm gonnae sink 14 whiskies
and seven pints...
...and spend the night in the arms
of my wee wife.
- You married, sir?
- No. If you've got a sister, I'm available!
What about you, Ernie?
Probably teach.
I've always fancied teaching.
- I thought I'd see the world first.
- You got that wish.
Aye.
When I get outta here, I'm gonna go
into business and get stinking rich.
- What kind of business?
- Black market, prostitution.
You're not gonna make much money
as a prostitute!
What about you, sir?
What are you gonna do after the war?
Start preparing for the next war.
In the Bushido code, the nation is
everything.
The individual is nothing. Conformity is
how they gain their sense of purpose.
They expected us to fall in line, as well.
What are we saying, Dusty?
Loyalty, politeness, frugality. Soldier's duty.
Just dandy!
Carry on, Sergeant Major.
Parade! Parade, 'shun!
About face!
All show respect for Honourable
Lieutenant Colonel Nagatomo
Chief of Thailand POW Administration.
I think she fancies me.
It is great pleasure for me
to see you at this place.
You are few remaining skeleton
of our victory and our pitiful victim.
You should weep with gratitude
at His lmperial Majesty, the Emperor
who pity you for being coward.
- What's he talking about, cowards?
- Rules of Bushido.
They believe the losers
should kill themselves.
You will give me great pleasure
to build a railroad
through the jungle to the glory
of His lmperial Majesty, the Emperor!
Saviour of Japan!
Saviour of Asia!
We will build this railroad
if we have to build it
over the white man's body.
It is your purification.
Railroad to be 420 kilometre
from Chungkai base camp
to Thanbyuzayat in north.
You will build the railroad in 18 months.
18 months?
How will my men manage that
on the rations you're feeding them, hm?
Officers work, as well.
Royal Engineer will oversee building.
Where are the signed papers?
Gentlemen... as you have violated
the Geneva Convention
the Hague Convention
and every human right
for properly supervised prisoners of war
may I respectfully recommend
that you and your fascist monkeys...
...stick your head up your arse
because we will not sign
your bloody paper!
Now, translate that!
I am sick of this drivel!
Gentlemen.
Look after my boys, lan.
It is regrettable
but we take each of you
and shoot one by one...
S... Sir?!
...until you respect Emperor!
Fuck! Fuck!
- Come on, man, out of here!
- Fucking bastard! Fucking bastard!
- What happened? What happened?
- Fucking shot him! Fucking shot him!
It's the Colonel's blood!
Fucking shot him! The bastard!
Major.
Don't let him go!
You fucking bastard!
There's nothing you can do.
What are we gonnae do?
What the fuck are we gonna do now?
Verily, verily, I say unto you.
Except a corn of wheat fall into
the ground and die, it abideth alone.
But if it die
it bringeth forth much fruit.
There is suffering before glory.
There is a cross...
...before the crown.
Outward turn!
Slow... march!
Cheers.
I'm no' leaving.
What?
I said, I'm no' leaving.
What about our plan?
I owed the Colonel my life...
and I watched him die in front of my eyes
and I just stood there doing nothing.
You think you're the only one
suffering here?
Oh, waken up!
There's a reason every escape has
failed and why the Japs don't give
a toss about security!
We were fools to think we even stood a
chance.
I've got my own plans now.
You are a selfish bastard.
Come on, Ernie.
Ernie!
Fine!
Yanker, wait a minute!
Yanker, wait! You'll never make it
on your own in that jungle! It's suicide!
Take a look around you! Look in the eyes
of these men! You tell me what you see.
That's right. They're dead already.
You know it and I know it.
Everybody in there does, too
and that scares the fucking hell out of me!
Because at least with escape...
it gave us one thing.
Hope. Hope. Because without that
we might as well be sitting in there
with our thumbs up our asses waiting
for the end! Is that what you want?
Let me tell you something about me.
I am not a stupid man
and I am not a kamikaze.
If I can't escape, I'll do the next best thing.
I will take care of myself
and that's exactly what I plan on doing.
Yanker, we are all in this
all of us, together.
Sure, kid, every single one of us.
The Japanese
were preparing to invade India.
The railway would be their supply line.
We would be the means to their end.
When you're living to die
every minute is an eternity.
Days are lost.
Months blend into one another.
The only reality you know is in the moment
and the moment hangs over you like death.
It's difficult to describe what it's like
to live with permanent hunger
and the stench of disease and death
with every breath you take.
Malaria, diphtheria, pellagra, dysentery
sucks every ounce of fluid out of your body.
Your muscles cramp up
and your circulation collapses.
Major!
He's burning up. Ernie!
I don't know anybody
who could survive that lot.
Oh, Ernie, son...
...you were a good soldier...
...and a good friend.
So this is death.
Dark...
...cold.
All alone.
No more reason to fight
so they gave up on you.
In death, there is no second chance.
That's what you think about
when you're dying.
The real value of all that you've done with
your life... and all that you might've done
if only you'd had a second chance.
Bloody hell! These Nip bastards
are eating like the Prince of Wales!
Life doesn't wait for the individual
especially life as a prisoner of war.
If you want to survive, you need
a bit of luck, a quick wit
and a mate to pick you up
when you fall.
- Where am I?
- You've been unconscious for days.
I thought if I got you into the fresh air
you'd have more chance of surviving.
I don't know if I want to survive any more.
Open up.
- How did you get the food?
- I have my connections. Open up.
Why are you doing this?
Hey, Ernie.
Er... me and the cobbers
we've been chewing it over...
...and we got thinking.
What's the purpose
in what we've been suffering?
Where's the justice in Nips bashing us
and working us to death?
What's worse, we're killing each other
to save our own skins.
What exactly are you asking me?
You said you wanted to be a teacher.
Yeah.
We thought that you might have
some answers, sir.
Would you like me to take a lecture
on the meaning of life (?)
Oh, that's a bloody fine idea, sir!
Please...
...just leave me alone.
That's what I figured.
You know, a man can experience an
incredible amount of pain and suffering
if he has hope.
When he loses his hope...
...that's when he dies.
Shit. I gotta take a shit.
Come on!
Reardon made a connection
to the local Thai black market.
He wouldn't share it for fear of being
discovered. That's what he told us.
Good God, Yanker, that's stinkin'!
My dear Major Campbell
this is the scent of happiness
nectar of the gods.
Our ticket to numbness.
Fermented rice alcohol.
This one's on the house.
Bastard!
- He's done it!
- 'Course I've done it!
- Nice one, Yanker. Let's have a swig.
- Whoa, gentlemen!
If you want charity, go to church.
I'm bartering my way to happiness.
So pony up with some cash.
Don't be shy. Line starts right here.
Two cigarettes.
You've got to get out of this rain.
Come on, walk.
- Ernie, you're still alive!
- Lazarus! Back frae the dead!
- I kinda wish I'd stayed there, sir.
- Bollocks! We need you alive! Hey!
- Come on.
- What's wrong?
He hasn't eaten.
He got me extra rations.
He never got you extra rations.
He was giving you his.
Help me with his legs.
I learned that
while Dusty was taking care of me
the Major was preparing his own plans.
Just what... I couldn't tell.
No, no, no.
Where did you get the food?
Multiple anonymous donors.
Eat.
I've decided to start a school
for the Jocks.
A jungle university.
I've already made my own blackboard.
Yanker rustled me up a text book.
For no small price.
First class is this evening.
I've got six students already.
I know it's small but... um...
...it's a start.
I don't wanna be the sceptic here
but how can you engage in a group activity
without the Nips seeing you?
In the one place the Nips will never go near.
- This stench is intolerable.
- Shut your cake-hole!
We're doing the best we can. Get used to it.
Make yourselves as comfortable as you can.
Let's get started, eh?
I'd like to speak to you about Plato.
Um... right.
What...
...is... justice?
Excuse me, sir. Sir.
Is it true you're giving
educational classes?
We'd like to help teach.
What's your story?
Roger Primrose, trained in the fine arts.
Lieutenant Foxworth used to teach
Shakespeare at Cambridge. I'm his
platoon sergeant.
Poor blighter's at a loss
without his books and the Bard.
If I can keep him busy long enough
he won't end up killing himself.
I'm... not joking, sir.
Unfortunately, we don't have
any Shakespeare.
To die, to sleep, -
No more; and by a sleep to say we end
The heart-ache, and the thousand
natural shocks that flesh is heir to
'tis a consummation devoutly to be wish'd.
To die... to sleep;
To sleep! Perchance to dream:
Ay, there's the rub;
For in that sleep of death
what dreams may come
When we have shuffled off
this mortal coil
Must give us pause:
There's the respect
That makes calamity of so long life;
For who would bear
the whips and scorns of time
The oppressor's wrong
the proud man's contumely
The pangs of despised love
the law's delay
The insolence of office...
- Looks like we do have the old Bard.
- Looks like we do. You're in.
Come on, Foxworth.
The oppressor's wrong
the proud man's contumely
The pangs of despised love
the law's delay
The insolence of office, and the spurns
That patient merit of the unworthy takes
When he himself might his quietus make
With a bare bodkin?
Who would fardels bear
To grunt and sweat under weary life...
...of something after death -
The undiscovered country
from whose bourn no traveller returns
puzzles the will and makes us
rather bear those ills we have
Than fly to others that we know not of?
In the second book of "The Republic"
Plato says "What will happen
to the just man
"should he enter this world?"
Well, the just man will be scourged
racked, chained...
...and after every kind of misery...
...he will be crucified on a pole for all to see.
Any questions?
I've got a question.
- Do you mind?
- Sure.
My question. If the just man...
is treated as you say...
...then what's the just response?
Roll over and let evil have its wicked way?
- What would you recommend, Major?
- Oh, I'd recommend defiance.
Justice for the captors. An eye for an eye.
And what price mercy?
Yeah, mercy. The last bastion
of traitors and cowards.
So you would take a man and crucify him
on a pole for all to see?
I would seek justice.
Any of you?
Sergeant Major?
Heave... heave...
Major Campbell was a natural leader
amongst men.
He seemed to draw them
from all nationalities and groups
and he'd a way with uniting them
in a common cause, HIS cause.
Very good. Two more of us.
The guards change between 5 and 5.30
so we have to be there.
Sorry, Major, are we interrupting
a church service?
So what's the story?
Major, let's say your plan works, right?
You've confiscated the guns
captured the guards
taken over the whole camp.
What then?
You have still nowhere to go.
And when the Nips find out
we'll have a regiment a thousand strong
descend on us with a vengeance.
You can't possibly hope to survive.
Who's talking about survival?
So this is a suicide mission?
So what are you gonna do, eh?
What are you gonna do?
Throw yourself at the mercy of Bushido?
- Aye, that would be suicide.
- Save us the bullshit, Major.
What are they paying you, Yanker?
Huh?
What, he didnae tell you?
Some of his best trades are with the Japs.
How do you think they get
such good medicine?
Ain't that right, Yanker?
Yeah, tell them, Yanker, eh?
Huh?
You are endangering the life
of every man in this camp.
They don't agree with your idea of justice.
So what are you
the voice of the people now, eh?
Or are you just a wee bit too Jap-happy
for your own good?
Ernie...
...we Argylls have got to stick together.
And you know
that's what the Colonel would say.
Good boy.
"Greater love hath no man
than this
"that a man lay down his life...
for his friends.
"You have heard that it was said
that you shall love your neighbour
"and hate your enemy.
"But I say to you...
"...love your enemy...
and pray for those who persecute you.
"For what shall it profit a man
if he gains the whole world...
"...but loses his soul?
"Or what will a man give...
in exchange for his soul?"
You're making a terrible mistake. I can
get you chocolate, whisky, cigarettes...
The Major imagined Reardon a threat.
To him, a man without a sense of duty
loyal to no one but himself
is already a traitor.
Please... please!
It's my school!
It's... It's my school!
Major Campbell struck a deal
with the Japs.
I was to be left alone.
In his mind
this was not considered betrayal.
The school had delayed his plans.
Men were changing their minds...
and Dusty had been the catalyst.
This book... teaches to turn the other cheek.
We read these books...
...and we become better slaves
for the Emperor.
He says the book is superstition.
Captain Noguchi says
the railroad progress is too slow.
He received orders from headquarters
requiring us to finish six months earlier
than it was scheduled.
Honourable sir, that's... that...
You are dismissed.
Superstition.
I'm still alive, you Jap bastards!
You can understand that!
They could take away our books
but they couldn't take away
what we had learned in our university.
Dusty led men out of the Death House
to trawl water.
His example of what we were learning
inspired us to work like never before.
And our captors noticed.
As for the Major
we refused to get even with him...
...to pay him back in kind.
It began to eat at him.
Captain Noguchi says
he gives you your books back
for you to keep learning.
Captain Noguchi
graciously gives you these gifts
for being good workers.
What is it?
We're back in business, lads!
- Oi, these are three years old!
- Japanese import laws!
- There's mail in here!
- Let me see it!
From that day on
Yanker never spoke much.
Something had changed inside him.
It was hard to tell
whether it was for the better...
or the worse.
Chip chip, muckers.
Graduation ceremonies are coming.
I want a tiptop performance out of you.
Continue.
Gentlemen... let's continue.
To do our country loss; and if to live
The fewer men
the greater share of honour.
He that shall live, and see old age
Then shall he strip his sleeve
and show his scars
And say
"These wounds I had on Crispin's day."
MEAT! MEAT!
BEEF!
Yanker decided to join us.
A bit late in the term
but eager to catch up.
You're a good teacher.
- What's your name?
- I'm Nagase. Takashi Nagase.
Hello, Takashi.
I'm Ernest.
I've actually been wondering
where you learnt such excellent English.
I was educated at Cambridge.
To be a good translator, I thought
one must understand the culture.
What do you think of the British?
I think there is a lot to learn from them.
And can I ask you, Honourable Takashi
what you are doing here in this camp?
I... I was classified low physical fitness.
A prisoner of war camp is not
honourable place for Japanese soldier.
It is more like a punishment.
Shame for his entire family.
Well, what about... Sergeant lto?
Surely he's the consummate soldier.
He accepted the blame for
the bad decision his superior made.
It resulted in the deaths
of most of his squad.
- So that's why he's so bitter?
- No.
In Bushido, it is an honour to be punished
in place of your superior.
According to our lmperial Rescript
in the Emperor's army...
...a single life... weighs less than a feather.
No matter how good things got
we were still slaves building a railway
being starved to death.
Thousands of us in a dozen
other prison camps, as well.
And as if that weren't enough
the Major and his dangerous plan seemed
ready to explode at any moment.
We realised we weren't the only slaves
being used in the name of the Emperor.
They called them "comfort women"
spoils of Japanese conquest.
A conquest whose original intent
was to purify the spirit.
The true warrior deems his sword
the soul of Bushido.
The key of heaven and hell
a symbol of what he carries
in his heart - loyalty and honour.
We finished the railroad in October 1943.
Six months ahead of schedule.
A real cause for celebration (l)
Like we were told in the beginning
they built it over the white man's body.
Those damned yellow Nips!
Acting as if they built the bloody thing!
Bloody railway of death.
That's the least of our concerns.
What do you mean?
We've built the railway.
They don't need us any more.
Those of you to the right of me
will be transferred to another camp.
It seemed like the final hindrance
to the Major's plan.
Half of his men were split apart that day.
Sent away, never seen again.
Attention, all prisoners.
There is a shovel missing
from the tool shed.
The one who has taken the shovel
return it now.
If the shovel is not returned
the entire camp will suffer punishment.
You will respect us.
The shovel was found.
There was a miscount
a simple bloody miscount.
You are dismissed.
What would compel a man, once so selfish
to sacrifice himself for others?
Boys...
...I can't feel my legs... I can't feel my legs.
Tonight's the graduation ceremony.
Japs have all been invited.
That means a slim chance of anyone
being left in the guard house.
You're not still going through with this?
There's only six of us.
We lost six men.
It was near impossible with twelve.
God knows, we haven't got
a chance with six!
- Now you're privy to the mind of God?
- Well, no, but...
I will not tolerate double-mindedness.
I'm staying.
Well, that leaves five.
Don't worry, boys. You don't worry, boys.
We'll have our justice.
Major Charlie Fraser, Language.
Sergeant Bingo Johnson, Philosophy.
Last, but by no means least
Private Wallace Hamilton, Ethics.
Gentlemen...
...the graduates...
...from our jungle university.
Well, let the festivities begin!
The music we heard that night
was less than perfect.
In fact, it was bloody terrible
but we didn't care.
In our hearts, we heard what it could be.
We heard the true spirit of the music.
Pure freedom.
If we are mark'd to die, we are enow
To do our country loss...
Guard, guard! Down, down!
- Glad you made it!
- The bloody music was awful!
He that shall see this day
and live t'old age
Shall stand a-tiptoe
when this day is named
Then shall he strip his sleeve
and show his scars, and say...
- There's no ammo in this thing!
- Find it!
Shh, shh, shh!
It's a B24. It's liberators!
- How can you be sure?
- It's unmistakable, man! Sweet music!
Liberators!
Allied aircraft.
They couldn't see us
but we could sure hear them.
We knew the war was turning.
- Speedo, speedo!
- Speedo, my arse!
Attention, prisoners. These men are
guilty of murdering two guards
who represent the lmperial Army
and of committing insurrection.
They have violated the mercy
of the Emperor...
Honourable Sergeant lto will now dispense
the prescribed and just punishment.
Major?
Bastard.
Ito.
Dusty?
What are you saying?
No!
No... no!
NO! DUSTY!
Major! Major, what did he say?
Major, please, what did Dusty say?
Major!
My boys!
Sorry.
No, no, no! No! No!
Superstition.
Do it!
Dusty!
When Dusty Miller died
something in the hearts and minds
of every man died.
What we had somehow managed
to hold onto for years of survival
now seemed utterly meaningless
like God himself was playing
a cruel joke on us all.
Until I remembered Dusty's words
so very long ago.
"Except a corn of wheat fall
into the ground and die
"it abideth alone.
"But if it die
"it bringeth forth much fruit."
I never found out
what Dusty said to lto that day
but I knew I had witnessed
the power of forgiveness.
Attention. Soon all inferior races
will bow before the Emperor
and the Knights of the Bushido.
When we heard the planes again
we thought our deliverance had arrived.
- Then it happened...
- Hail, Knights of Bullshitto!
Our own allies thought we were the enemy.
I'm fine! Help the other men!
Help me! Help me!
Help me! Help me, Ernie!
Just don't look at it, man!
It's nothing, it's nothing!
They thought we was Nips, Ernie!
I almost made it!
I got killed by my own side, Ernie!
- You're not killed, you're with me!
- They thought we was Nips!
Don't leave me, man! Don't you leave me
man! Don't you leave me, man!
Stay with me, man! Stay with me, man!
Stay with me! Stay with me, man! No!
Get up! Get fucking up!
An enemy location was also hit nearby.
The wounded had abandoned
their posts looking for help.
Their arrival at our camp would
compel us to make the most important
decision of our lives.
A decision that would defy
the Bushido code
of honour and shame.
No goodka! No goodka!
Ernest.
Captain Gordon, I forbid you
to give comfort and aid to the enemy.
Major... those...
...are wounded, dying human beings.
They're no harm to us.
Ernie, get back to your own men.
Can someone get me some water?
Could someone please get me
some water?
We were left alone
by our captors. Nowhere to go.
Nothing to do.
An uncertain future
with only a makeshift radio left behind
hoping for any word from the outside.
"To all Allied prisoners of war.
"The Japanese forces
have surrendered unconditionally
"and the war is over."
For he today that sheds his blood with me
Shall be my brother;
Be he ne'er so vile
This day shall gentle his condition.
From this day
to the ending of the world
But we in it shall be remembered -
We few... we happy few
We band of brothers.
Where are the guards?
Th-They left.
Fled into the jungle... from us.
Which direction?
I've no idea.
You're a man of true principle
and devotion.
And, you know...
I wanna be just like you, just like you.
Major Campbell.
Hey, Ernie...
...you're just in time.
You're making a mistake.
No... l'm making justice, man.
Don't you think... I want this?
Eh? Eh?
We all deserve to see him suffer
but this is not right.
Mm?
Aye.
You stupid... stupid wee boy!
Stupid wee boy!
God forgive me!
Oh, God forgive me!
Oh, God forgive me, son!
Forgive me, son.
No!
What is the consequence of a single life
weighing less than a feather?
Bastard! Bastard!
What is the final destination of hatred?
When you look in the eyes
of the enemy and you see yourself...
Come here.
Come here!
...at what price mercy?
Who is my neighbour?
How many times shall I forgive my brother?
What does it mean to love one's enemies?
What can a man give
in exchange for his soul?
These are the questions that I faced
in my prison camp.
The answers... changed my life for ever.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org