Oculus Deum.
She must be killed!
She was chosen
to bear his child.
If she lives to bring about the End
of Days, there will be no redemption.
All our souls
will perish.
Tomaso.
Okay, now give me
a big push.
That's it.
You're doing great.
That's it. Okay, stop pushing.
... fýve, six, seven...
I have the baby's head.
Don't push yet.
One little push oughta fýnish
this off. One little push.
You have
a beautiful baby girl.
Oh!
She's so beautiful!
Just gonna take her
and clean her up.
Not yet.
Hospital rules.
Please. You'll have her
back before you know it.
Here she is.
All fresh and clean.
You thought of a name
for her yet? Christine.
Her name is Christine.
Happy birthday,
Christine.
WBAZ time is 8:06.
Three more nights, New York. Three
more nights left in the century.
Three more nights left
in the millennium.
Three more nights
until every computer fails.
Three more nights until the biggest
celebration in the history of this city...
starts in Times Square.
Where will you be?
Hey, Bobby, come over here.
Something weird's goin'on.
What do you got there,
Charlie? I don't know.
Pressure's climbin'
off the gauge.
Go the other way!
Excuse me.
What the hell are you...
Mmm.
You're on Gotham Talk.
Say something interesting.
I'm trying to figure out
what everyone's predicting here.
Is the world going to come to an end
at exactly 12:01 on New Year's, or...
I'll tell you what.
You should play it safe,
not quit yourjob
just yet.
Tell you something else:
in two more nights,
this place is gonna see
the wildest party ever.
We're gonna be there with the first hundred
callers, we're gonna make the most noise,
and we're gonna be the craziest,
and if the world comes to an end,
what the hell,
we're all gonna be together!
And if it doesn't,
and I don't think it will,
then we'll all have the best
time anybody has ever had.
Let's go.
We're gonna be late.
Honey, I'm home.
I was just
pulling myself together.
It's gonna take
a lot more pulling.
You are looking
very sharp this morning.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
You got about fýve minutes
to get ready. Here.
There's enough caffeine in this
to kill an elephant.
Oughta get you
started.
- So what's today?
- Transport.
Anyone special?
No, just some
Wall Street scumbag.
Why the hell does he need
all this protection?
Well, I guess he fucked
with some people...
that didn't like
being fucked with.
Personally, I like scumbags.
They pay better.
They say breakfast is the
most important meal of the day.
No, I'm good.
Thanks.
Striker One, F.D.R. Drive...
Follow Three,
F.D.R. southbound.
Striker One, stay close.
Striker Four...
Okay, you zeroes.
These people are
paying us good money.
Get your heads out of your asses
and start earning those paychecks.
Follow Three,
give me a visual sweep.
Striker One,
rooftops 125 to 136 clear.
- Keep them clear.
- Striker Four, advise and contact the...
Follow Three is on approach.
E. T.A., two minutes.
Striker One, Follow Two and Three to
report tight formation. Do you copy?
Air One, make a final sweep.
- Roger that.
Follow Three.
We have nest in sight.
Air One, westbound
over zone two.
Ten seconds out.
Roger. Ten seconds.
Follow Three,
we have arrived.
Keep everyone close.
- We're exposed.
- Roger.
Sky Two,
fire escape, southwest corner.
Fire escape's negative.
You're wrong! Shooter!
Evac! Evac!
Get in the car!
Call N.Y.P.D.!
Get me an ambulance!
- What the hell's goin' on?
- I see him! I see him!
Shit!
Oh, shit! Tell me
you remembered! Come on!
Get up,
you pussy.
Where's the shooter?
- Headed for the roof.
- So are we.
Sky Two, get the fuck
down here, now!
Come on! Hurry!
Take us up there!
Move in! Move in!
- Set us down! Hurry!
- There's too much crap on that roof!
- We'll tear off the main rotor.
- Then get us down as low as you can!
Hurry now! Go!
Strap me in!
You're good!
- He's gonna jump
off the roof! Shit!
He's got him!
Gun! Gun!
Oculus Dei!
The thousand years has ended!
The Dark Angel is loosed
from his prison!
Get down on the ground and
put your hands behind your head.
You don't know
what you've done!
- Get down, or I'll put you down!
- The thousand years has ended!
You don't know
what you've done!
Priest that drinks.
Can't be all bad.
I think the police
may want that at some point.
- They call it evidence.
- I like to get a head start.
- No reason to make it easy for them.
- Yeah.
All right.
Watch the lines.
Go through here.
She doesn't look happy
with the statements.
Should've just killed that son
of a bitch. Less paperwork. Yeah.
Hey, Detective. Bobby.
Hey, Jer, it's been a while.
Hey. How are you, Marge?
Can't complain. You?
It's a nice day to jump
out of a helicopter.
Well, just doing
my job.
Now, listen. Something I gotta ask you.
Yeah, what is it?
You still drinking?
Oh, yeah, we got all
liquored up this morning.
- We start every day that way.
- I'm just reading his statement.
You said here the guy
spoke to you. Yeah. So what?
The guy doesn't
have a tongue.
- What?
- He has no tongue?
Why don't I just leave
that little detail out for now.
No big deal, right? Are you
saying that I imagined all this?
No, I'm just saying.
I saved a life today.
What the hell did you
do? All right, let it go.
- No, no. I know what I heard.
- All right.
Those people who don't belong
here, get them out of here.
Make sure this place
is secure.
A drunk hangs out in a neighborhood
bar, passes out enough times,
people would know where he
lived from carrying him home.
I mean,
it's one thing I know.
Yeah, well, it's important
to be an expert at something.
Oh, it took years of
research. This must be it.
What do you want to bet
it's rent-controlled?
Well, I don't think
this is paint.
A real art buff.
I don't go for this look.
It's just too damn busy.
Listen to this.
"I have seen the Earth
laid to waste.
"I have seen the horror to come. Is
it a sin to wish you were never born?
"The thousand years
have ended.
Twenty... seven. "
It ends in a football
score. That's nice.
Hey, I found something.
Can you see
what it is?
His tongue.
He must have
cut it out himself.
Okay. And why is it someone
would cut out their own tongue?
To keep from talking. Right.
Well, I could eat.
Ah!
- Shit!
- What?
All right, I knew
that was gonna happen.
No, it's all right.
There's something
in here.
Have you ever seen her before? Nah.
This guy
is no ordinary hit man.
No, this one's
extraordinary.
Let's get the hell outta here.
This place is making me itch.
- Drop it! Don't move! Don't move! Freeze!
- Don't move! Freeze!
Oh. It's us.
Jesus! How the hell
did you two find this place?
Lucky guess. So what did you fýnd out?
His name's Thomas
Aquinas. He's a priest.
Why don't you tell us
something we don't know?
- A homicidal priest. That's good.
- Yeah? Well, it gets better.
He studied at the Vatican. He was
one of their alleged visionaries.
Came here in '81 to St.
John's Church downtown.
Six months ago,
he disappeared.
Priests there say he was
having a spiritual crisis.
Oh, yeah.
That's what this is about.
Spiritual crisis.
Doesn't make any sense.
What's a priest doing shooting
at a Wall Street banker?
A Wall Street banker, by the
way, who suddenly disappeared.
Maybe we should ask the girl.
What girl?
Uh, the guy.
The guy. Priest guy.
There's fýve million women
living in New York City.
How we gonna fýnd her
without a name?
Here.
Look, I already gave you some
money. Can you just move on, please?
He's comin' for you.
He's comin' for you, Christine.
How do you know
my name?
He's gonna fuck you. He's gonna
fuck you, Christine. Can you see him?
Can you see him?
- Who are you?
How do you know
my name?
He's gonna fuck you, Christine.
I'm sorry.
Ohh.
The thousand years
have ended.
Thousand years have ended.
"When the thousand years
are ended,
Satan shall be loosed
out of his prison. "
"Twenty... seven. "
Christine?
Christine? I'll be there in a sec!
Doctor's offýce.
Hello.
Is Dr. Abel in, please?
Who's calling, please?
It's Christine York.
Christine, listen to me.
We've been over this before.
It's a terrible thing to lose your
parents. I know it was a long time ago.
The holidays always make something
like that feel much worse.
Understand, these dreams are your
creation. There's nothing real about them.
You control them.
They don't control you.
Take another Xanax
to relieve your anxiety.
You are fýne. Trust me.
Another vision?
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want you to worry. I'm your
stepmother. It's my job to worry.
No big deal, really.
Just someone on the subway car
turned into porcelain and shattered.
What's wrong with me? Why do I
see things? Why am I so different?
Oh, you don't know
how special you are.
You're better than everybody
else. Just remember that.
I don't want to be better or
worse. I want to be normal.
I want a normal life.
You have to have patience.
All good things will come
to you. You'll see.
Oh, excuse me. I'm sorry, we're closed.
I would like to talk to
you about Thomas Aquinas.
Father, please, I need you
downstairs. Just take these.
Father, please.
Go.
I've already told the police. Thomas
was a friend of mine and a colleague.
He had nothing to do
with what happened today.
There was no one else
on that fýre escape.
You don't understand. I understand
getting shot at, and I don't like it.
He shot at you? No,
he shot at my client.
- I happened to get in the way.
- Who's your client?
That's irrelevant right now. What I want to
know is why would a priest try to kill someone?
You've been drinking. I've got 14
years sober, and I can spot that.
Well, good for you. Your friend and
colleague, was he working for someone?
Yes, he was working for God.
So God ordered a hit
on an investment banker?
There's a lot that you don't know.
You think you've seen everything?
You haven't. There are
things you never dreamed of.
There's another world out there.
Thomas saw it, and it destroyed him.
I've seen a lot too, but there's nothing
that would make me cut my tongue out.
Yeah, well, wait a few days.
What happens in a few days?
Did Thomas tell you
about a girl?
- No.
- I see. Do you believe in God?
Maybe once,
but not anymore.
What happened?
We had a difference of opinion.
I thought that my wife and daughter
should live, and He felt otherwise.
I'm sorry to hear about the loss. Maybe
it's time for you to renew your faith.
This girl.
Is she in trouble?
Does she need help?
I have a lot of things to do
here. Excuse me. Excuse me.
I have more questions, if you don't
mind. I've got a question for you.
If you don't believe in God, how
can you understand his adversary?
Now I have to believe in God
in order to solve a crime?
I'm sure that you
can fýnd your way out.
- How many have received the stigmata?
- She's the third this week.
- What is she saying?
- For your own good, get out and forget what you've seen!
Was Thomas part of this? There are forces
at work you couldn't possibly comprehend!
Now, please,
leave!
# God rest ye, merry gentlemen #
# Let nothing
you dismay #
# Remember Christ... ##
No, it's just I hate the fact that
they put fýnals after the holiday.
It ruins the whole meaning of vacation.
I wouldn't worry.
You always do fýne.
Besides, a bad grade
isn't the end of the world.
It's you.
I didn't...
Where is she?
The girl is safe.
And what of the world?
Everything is
as planned.
Our acts go unnoticed,
unquestioned.
- We're everywhere.
- Daddy, who is it?
- Is this your daughter?
- Yes.