Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I am happy you came back.
Hey, Jerry, what's wrong?
I could not go with you.
It is no longer my life that matters.
I am not fat.
I am not lazy.
I await a new life.
A new life?
From where?
Oh, my God.
Are you telling me you're pregnant?
What, you're gonna have a baby?
What, a little Drac?
What?
But how'd...
Well, don't look at me.
Jerry, Jerry, you can't do this to me.
With you humans,
birth is a matter of choice.
With us Dracs, it happens.
When the time comes, itjust happens.
That is why I could not go with you.
My child is all I have now.
So, Davidge, tell me.
What did you find out there?
Nothin'.
Like you said, it was just a dream.
Soon.
Jerry, look out.
I can't see. I can't see.
Over here.
Help me.
Come on, Jerry. Don't you quit on me.
Tell me about Zammis.
Yeah. What kind of a name is Zammis?
There are five names in a Drac lineage.
I am Shigan.
Before me was Gothig,
and before Gothig was Haesni.
Come on. Keep talking.
Before Haesni was Ty.
Before Ty was Zammis.
Up there. Look.
One day I must stand with Zammis
before the Holy Council on Dracon
and recite our lineage,
so that Zammis may join
the society of all Dracs.
Wanna eat?
I can't.
Maybe we should open up a little place here.
I could ruin the food.
You could frighten the customers.
Davidge.
I will teach you the Jeriba line.
Before or after breakfast?
It is an honor I offer you.
I'm sorry.
Right now just stayin' alive's
honor enough, huh?
All right.
I will learn your lineage.
Let us begin with your parents.
Who were they?
My dad's name's Carl.
My mom's name's, uh, Dolores.
And their deeds?
My dad works for a company
that makes computers.
And my mom, she used to be a waitress.
- Waitress?
- Yeah, before they got married.
And their parents?
We used to visit my grandpa
when I was just a kid.
He had this place out in the country.
I think he was a farmer.
And, uh, Grandma was just a good cook.
That is your lineage.
Here stands before you Willis E Davidge.
Fighter pilot, son of Dolores,
who used to be a waitress,
and Carl, maker of computers,
who in their time were born of
Grandpa, possibly a farmer,
and Grandma, good cook.
You make it sound pretty thin.
It is thin.
But I am honored
that you entrusted it to me.
My own lineage is very rich, Davidge.
Learn it from me.
Allow me to do you this honor.
It will be like a gift between us.
Jerry went on, singing its lineage
back to the founding of its home planet,
170 generations ago.
To keep Jerry happy as the winter raged on,
I too learned to sing the Jeriba line.
What's wrong?
Zammis is coming.
Oh, God.
God...
- What do I do?
- I don't know.
Something is wrong.
Oh, no. No, no. No, no, no.
No. You're gonna be all right.
Women always get nervous before labor.
I am not a woman.
But pregnant people... things
get nervous.
Everybody gets nervous before labor.
Besides, if anything happened to you,
I'd be left here all alone.
Just because business has been slow lately,
you expect me to run the whole place alone?
You are alone.
Within yourself, you are alone.
That is why you humans
have separated your sexes
into two separate halves.
For the joy of that brief union.
You don't know diddley-poop about humans.
You think because you Dracs got a lineage
200 miles long, you can blah-blah this name...
Listen to me.
You must be a parent for Zammis.
Don't kid around, Jerry.
What do we do now?
You must take my place.
When the time comes,
you must find a way
to take Zammis back home.
You must stand beside Zammis
before the Holy Council on Dracon
and recite its lineage.
You must, Davidge.
Swear this to me.
Shut up.
Keep pushing. Do whatever you do.
You must take Zammis to Dracon.
- Swear.
- No.
Swear.
All right.
All right. I swear it.
I swear it.
Just don't die on me.
Now you must open me.
Here.
This place.
Don't be afraid, my friend.
- I can't.
- Damn you, Irkmann.
You have sworn.
I did.
You have ss... ss...
No.
Oh, please.
God, Jerry,
what am I supposed to do now, huh?
You taught me all about the Talman
and the line of Jeriba.
But you didn't say nothin'
about taking care of baby Dracs.
So long, Jerry.
All right.
OK, you gonna try it again, huh?
Come on, now. Come on.
Come on. Zammis...
Zammis, come on.
Come on.
What am I supposed to do? Run down to the
market for ajar of Gerber baby-Drac food?
This is all there is, pal.
Watch. Watch me.
Come on.
OK.
Try it like this. Come on.
Come on, see if you like that.
You like that?
Come on, kid. Yes.
That's it. That's it.
Chew it, now. There you go.
Hey, squirt.
I guess he was an ugly little cuss,
but no uglier than the pictures of those other
kids that were shown around the mess hall.
Of course, he grew slightly faster
than a human child.
I'd better start calling you beanstalk - you
outgrow clothes faster than I can catch 'em.
Don't spread your fingers.
Fingers?
Yeah. Yeah, these. Fingers.
Kutta - fingers.
Not the same.
Well, of course they're not the same.
I mean, you're a Drac. I'm a human.
Look.
You have three fingers.
One, two, three.
I have five fingers.
One, two, three, four, five.
Zammis get four, five?
No.
You're a Drac.
- And I'm a human.
- Human?
Yeah.
Human is me. Drac is you.
Now, I'm a human
because my parents were human.
And your parent was a Drac.
So you are a Drac.
Got it?
- I'm a Drac.
- Yeah.
Yeah, great.
Uncle.
Uncle, wait. Wait.
Huh? Uncle, what was that?
Spacecraft.
- Were there humans inside?
- I don't know.
- I'm gonna go find out.
- Uncle, please, can I come?
No. You stay here until I get back.
Uncle, why are you afraid? Uncle, please.
No. You stay inside the cave.
So that's why, when we walk or we hunt,
we always go in the direction
of the rising of the sun, huh?
Never in the direction of
the setting of the sun. Is that clear?
- Yes.
- Cos if those men ever find us,
we'll never see each other again.
But, Uncle, they are humans, like you.
Shut up and eat.
I tried not to think about the scavengers.
Instead, I concentrated on Zammis.
I finally figured
it was time to start his education.
The name of this game, Zammis,
- is football.
- Football.
Now, these trees are my defensive line.
Those trees over there are your team.
They're a bit bigger than real players - like the
Houston Oilers - and slower, but not much.
All right?
You go down to that end of the field.
That's your end zone, OK? Go on.
There you go.
All right, now, when I kick the ball to you,
you catch it and you try to run past me -
if you can - through these two guys there.
- That's your goal line. You got it?
- No.
Well, just do what I tell you.
It'll be fine, all right? It'll be fine. All right?
Here comes the kickoff.
Pick it up. Pick it up. Now run. Run.
Now, run, run, run.
Come on. Come on. Go on. Go on.
Oh, look at him weave through the defense.
- I like this game.
- Yeah, it's a great game, isn't it?
Of course, you don't normally
get to eat the ball. That's a bonus.
And I've simplified the rules for the
conditions here. Small teams and so on.
I've been thinking, Uncle,
about those humans you saw.
Maybe they are friends with the Dracs.
Maybe they asked them to come and work.
I wish that was true.
I have never seen a Drac.
Only my own face in the water.
I wish I was not a Drac.
- I wish I had your face.
- Oh, Zammis.
- I wish I had five fingers.
- Oh, Zammis. Zammis.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
Now, as Dracs go, you are a great-looking kid.
You are a great-looking kid.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
It's just that you've never seen
your own kind.
Now, someday you're gonna go home
and you're gonna forget all about
this God-awful planet and all about me.
I will never forget you, Uncle.
No, I guess you won't.
I won't forget you either.
Uncle?
What was my parent like?
Zammis, your parent was my friend.
No.
All right, move it now.
Get back in there. Get to work.
Hey, Jonny, look here.
A fine little woggie, if I ever saw one.
Surprise, surprise.
Looks a bit stringy to me, though.
No, he's just fine.
Tough as nails. A born worker.
Energetic little bugger.
Come on. Run about. Run about.
Look at that speed.
How d'you suppose it got here?
Let's have a look.
See if his daddy's around.
Hey, you slimy bastard.
Hot damn.
Woggie's got you hot and bothered.
Don't worry. I'll slow him down for you.
You ripped my face, you slimy little Drac.
I'll make you pay.
- Who the hell are you?
- Let him go.
Zammis, no.
We entrust our brother
to God's merciful keeping.
And we commit his body to space.
From ashes to ashes, from dust to dust,
in sure and...
Jesus Christ.
Didn't they just fix that thing?
Shit. Who's listening anyway?
Next.
Gavorki, George W. Agnostic.
No music.
So long.
Next.
So where's the damn tag on this one?
- Those jerks in Prep are really gettin' sloppy.
- So have a look inside.
- Look at this poor freak.
- At least he's in one piece.
- Yeah. Some guys have all the luck.
- Right.
- Nope. No tag.
- We'll give him a John Doe. Protestant.
- Hold it.
- What?
Go ahead. Take it.
All stations. All stations, stand by.
Jesus.
He speaks Drac.
Three years.
Where the hell has he been?
That's Will. Turning up
when you least expect him.
- Heavy breathing.
- Heart rate: 120.
- Several readouts.
- Extreme shock. Oxygen pressure dropping.
This guy's been in some deep shit.
He was found on the fourth planet
of the Fyrine system.
Where he just might have
been working for the other side.
Are you crazy?
That's Will Davidge in there.
I don't know how long I lay there
before the surveillance team picked me up.
They thought I was dead.
Well, the medics have had time to nail me
back together. Now I've got to go back.
- Hold it.
- I'm going back with or without your help.
No way. I'm sorry.
Now, we put our asses on the line for you.
You owe us for that at least.
I can't let you go, Will.
Never mind. Let him go
if he wants to be an asshole.
Hello, pilot. Please identify.
Davidge, Willis E.
Gotta log a couple of hours.
Mr Davidge, you have no authorization.
Please deplane immediately.
No way, Charlie. I'm going out.
Cut down those engines, Mister.
Get outta there.
I'm going through. I swear it.
Now, you open those doors.
We have an emergency.
I'm going through. Open 'em up.
Open the doors.
Now.
Hey. What's all this standing around?
Hm? Come on. Back to work.
You miserable slime.
Where do you think you are, huh?
A goddamn retirement home?
Move. Move.
What are you staring at, slimebag?
You son of a bitch.
You are Uncle.
Of course we know your Zammis.
He spoke only to me,
for only I know the Irkmann speech.
- Where is Zammis now?
- Somewhere in their ship.
If he is still alive.
What a lousy hand this is. Let's redeal.
- That you, Daggett?
- Yeah.
- What's going on out there?
- Trouble.
- What kind of trouble?
- This kind.
Wake up.
It's Uncle.
Oh, no. No, no, no...
Hi.
Hey, this guy's BTA.
Thanks for the hot tip.
What are you doin' here, BTA man?
You see that I'm impatient, don't you?
I remember you now.
You killed my brother Jonny.
I thought you croaked out there.
Wake him up and bring him along.
Get up, freakface. We don't carry you.
Shit.
Hold it, sucker. Yeah.
Let's try the little woggie in the soup.
Whaddya say? Boil his bones.
- Don't do it. Stop.
- Yeah.
Hey, BTA man, where are you?
I want you to see this.
Where are you, you son of a bitch?
Come on.
Don't. No, don't. Zammis.
No. Zammis.
No. No.
Wait, wait. Wait.
Bubble, bubble, toil and trouble.
Go on, ride little brother.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
It's time to say good-bye.
Hey, it's me. Wake up.
Zammis, wake up.
Wake up. It's Uncle.
It's Uncle. Huh?
Zammis get four, five?
Uncle, you look terrible.
I do?
I really do.
So do you, you little tadpole.
I told you I'd never forget you, huh?
And so Davidge brought
Zammis and the Dracs home.
He fulfilled his vow and recited
the line of Zammis'forefathers
before the Holy Council on Dracon.
And when, in the fullness of time,
Zammis brought its own child
before the Holy Council,
the name of Willis Davidge
was added to the line of Jeriba.
Visiontext Subtitles: Natasha Cohn
US ENGLISH
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org