Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
In the late 20th century,
hostile forces inside
the United States grow strong.
The city of Los Angeles
is ravaged by crime and immorality.
To protect and defend its citizens,
the United States
Police Force is formed.
A presidential candidate
predicts a millennium earthquake
will destroy LA
in divine retribution.
Like the mighty fist of God,
Armageddon will descend upon
the city of Los Angeles -
the city of sin,
the city of Gomorrah and Sodom -
and waters will arise
and separate this sinful,
sinful city from our country.
An earthquake measuring 9.6
on the Richter scale
hits at 12:59pm,
August 23 in the year 2000.
After the devastation,
the Constitution is amended,
and the newly-elected president
accepts a lifetime term of office.
The country's capital is
relocated from Washington, DC,
to the President's home town
of Lynchburg, Virginia.
Los Angeles island is declared
no longer part of the United States,
and becomes the deportation point
for all people found unfit to live
in a new, moral America.
The United States Police Force,
like an army,
is encamped along the shoreline,
making any escape from LA impossible.
From the south-east of Orange
country to the north-west of Malibu,
the Great Wall excludes LA
from the mainland.
The President's first act as
commander in chief is Directive 17-
Once an American loses
his or her citizenship,
they are deported to this island of
the damned and may never come back.
Attention. We are on tactical alert.
Remain at battle stations.
I repeat, remain at battle stations.
This is the Police Channel,
and this is Prime News.
In a late-breaking story,
the Force has announced
the arrival of the most
notorious outlaw in US history
at Firebase Seven, the deportation
centre for Los Angeles island.
Now this on-the-scene report.
War hero. Criminal.
The Force's most wanted man.
Convicted of 27 moral crimes.
Arrested two weeks ago on a charge
of gunfighting for profit
in New Vegas, Thailand,
US territory.
It's been 16 years since
his famous rescue in New York,
and the reports
of Plissken sightings...
Commander?
I'm still getting a trace
from the rescue team, sir.
- Stationary signal?
- Has not moved from this location.
That means he's hiding,
captured, or dead.
So we go with Plissken?
He's all we've got.
Hello, Plissken.
Welcome to LA.
Come on. Move it.
- That's Snake Plissken?
- What did you expect?
He just looks so retro.
Kind of 20th century.
Good old days. Let's get going.
You are now entering
the deportation centre.
You have been found guilty
of moral crimes against the USA
and sentenced to permanent expulsion
beyond its borders.
Failure to follow instructions
will be met with use of force.
Look at 'em, Plissken.
Prostitutes, atheists, runaways...
We're throwing out the trash.
"SD Bob Plissken,
Special Forces." Two Purple Hearts?
Youngest man ever decorated
by the President.
Rescued a different president in '97.
So, what happened to you, war hero?
You were the best.
Now you're just like them.
You had it all and you turned away
from your country. Why?
The whole nation's watching.
Every good and decent person
who works hard and follows the rules.
Be my guest.
What do you have to say, Plissken?
Call me Snake.
You are now entering
the processing area.
The next scheduled departure
to LA is in one hour.
You now have the option
to repent of your sins
and be electrocuted
on the premises.
If you elect this option,
notify the cleric sergeant
in your processing area.
How's it going, hotshot?
You know, I got to admit.
I thought we had you in Cleveland.
- How'd you do it?
- Get to the deal.
- What?
- You need me for something. What?
Show him.
At 1030 hours, Wednesday,
a group of government officials
began a tour
of the Benford Space Defence lab.
The President's daughter,
Utopia, was among them.
During the tour, she came into
possession of a top-secret prototype.
Then she boarded
Air Force Three for Lynchburg.
To the American people -
now is the time to rise up and demand
the surrender of the President
and his corrupt theocracy
of lies and terror!
At 1140 hours,
she hijacked Air Force Three.
We scanned this onto the VR.
Check it out.
Today is day one
of a brand-new world.
The days of empire are finished.
To the President, my father...
You know what's in here,
and unless you open your borders,
allow all the wrongfully accused
to return to their country,
I will use this on you
and on the United States.
Her emergency escape pod
landed somewhere in LA.
Her ELT signal ceased immediately.
After that, silence.
We sent a five-man rescue team.
Within hours of landing
all but one was killed.
Hell of a team.
Skip the commentary, Plissken.
Call me Snake.
Get on with it.
After her sister committed suicide,
Utopia began to withdraw
into her virtual reality simulator.
She'd punch up her own world
and stay in it for days.
Somebody else was in there.
Utopia made tapes of her VR
experiences and tried to erase them,
but she missed one image.
We found this fragment
on the end of her last tape.
Cuervo Jones. Peruvian terrorist.
Shining Path member.
Runs the Mescalito Justice,
biggest, baddest gang in LA.
Somehow, Cuervo Jones managed
to tap into the VR master data bank.
Utopia was looking
for something to believe in,
so he used her
to steal the black box.
Sad story. You got a smoke?
This is serious, Plissken.
The black box is a matter
of national security.
Looks like it belongs
to Utopia's lover-boy now.
Yeah. We want it back.
I'll bet.
What's it do?
Top secret. Only on a need-to-know.
Evidently, I don't need to know,
so fuck you, I'm going to Hollywood.
If you go into LA,
bring back the black box,
and you will receive a pardon for
every immoral act you have committed.
Sounds familiar.
An immediate answer.
Yes or no?
Who are you?
I'm your president.
I understand you got
some domestic problems.
Put that black box in my hand,
and you're a free man.
I can see you're real concerned
about your daughter.
Utopia is lost to me.
My daughter is gone.
- Last chance, hotshot.
- For what?
Freedom, sir.
In America?
That died a long time ago.
I've heard enough of this.
Explain to this foot soldier why he's
going to do what we tell him to do.
What's he talking about?
The Plutoxin Seven virus.
Genetically engineered.
100% pure death.
Complete nervous system shut-down.
You crash. You bleed out like
a stuck pig. It's not a pretty sight.
I see.
You figure I'll do whatever you
want, just like New York, huh?
- You got it... Snake.
- One question.
Which one of you assholes gets to die
trying to stick me?
You don't understand.
It's already in you.
Catches on quick, doesn't he?
Your countdown clock
is now activated.
Designer viruses, Plissken.
Wave of the future.
You've got less than ten hours
to live.
It's already moving through your
bloodstream. Go on-touch that pad.
Of course, there is an antidote,
and it neutralises the virus
immediately upon injection.
Which I will personally authorise
once your mission is completed.
The man is too dumb to survive LA.
We're holograms, Plissken.
Give us a little credit.
We're not that stupid.
Get this crap out of me.
I guess we've got a deal.
Nice to be working with you, hotshot.
You'd better hope
I don't make it back.
All of you.
Core burner, magnesium ammo,
500 extra rounds.
Oral projectile. Mouth dart, filled
with urolyde. It will stun the enemy.
Every member of the rescue team
had a tracking chip in his arm.
One might still be alive. Use the
tracer in your watch to locate him.
This holographic camera will project
your image up to a half-mile away.
100% audio capability.
It's a prototype.
Confuse and deceive the enemy.
Its mini-nuke battery is good for
eight minutes, but only works once.
Save it for when it counts.
Plain old-fashioned matches.
Never know when you might need them.
Where are my guns?
I thought you might want those.
Stealth clothing. Fire retardant,
nullifies heat detection.
Put them on.
I'll take the coat.
You'll take 'em all.
All right. LA's being primed as a
beachhead for an invasion of the US.
War is being declared,
Plissken, or didn't you know?
Oh, I forgot. You don't give a shit.
Cuervo Jones runs Shining Path.
They want North America.
The revenge
of preindustrial societies.
Shining Path has united
Third World countries.
The Cubans and Brazilians
will invade Miami.
The Colombians are at the border,
we've got a full-scale attack.
- High stakes.
- How am I going in?
Under the San Fernando Sea. Shark
Three submarine, one-man submersible.
Just like the turbine model,
only this one's nuclear-powered.
It's very simple.
Throttle up, throttle back.
Put ashore at the Cuegan Pass.
Go through the mountains
toward the Hollywood Bowl.
Locate the survivor
of the rescue team.
He's your only source of information.
- Do I bring him back?
- Negative.
- Figures.
- He's probably already dead.
Once you go inside,
you're on your own.
Get the black box
back to the submarine.
It's your only way out.
Plissken!
You know what to do with the girl.
We don't need to waste any more time
and money on bullshit trials.
Kill her.
Is that order from the President?
Absolutely. Let's just say
it's best for the country.
By the way,
who gives me the antidote?
- A medical team.
- Neither of you?
- No.
- Good.
Thought you'd try that, hotshot.
The first clip is loaded with blanks.
Bye bye, Snake. Good luck.
Nice and easy now.
- Com check.
- Yeah. I'm here.
Stand by for launch.
Eight hours, eight minutes,
26 seconds
to neurosystem shut-down.
Ignitor.
Fuel rod injection.
She's in the green.
- Lock fuel rods.
- Locked.
Nuclear turbine to 75% power.
75% power.
Hands on switches and counting.
Five...
four... three...
two... one.
Launch.
Watch your speed.
There's lots of obstructions.
His reactor's starting to overheat.
Slow down, you're overloading
the power plant!
You slow down, dickhead.
I'm dying.
Plissken!
Power plant overload.
Guidance systems malfunction.
You no longer have
control stick function.
Obstruction ahead.
Plissken.
Yeah. I'm here. Cuegan Pass.
'What happened to the submarine?
It disappeared off our screens.
Plissken!
I gotta go.
Too bad about your boat, man,
but we'd appreciate it
if you'd stay off our beach.
Just passing through.
You look kind of familiar.
- What do you want?
- Nothin'.
- I just recognised you, that's all.
- That's all?
Come on, man.
I'm not looking for trouble.
I used to see you a lot
when I surfed, on the Police Channel.
You're pretty far out, Snake.
I mean, cool.
But I kind of thought
you'd be... taller.
Which way to the Hollywood Bowl?
Down that way.
It's just an aftershock.
We get them all the time.
Thanks for not killing me, man.
I owe you one.
Acid rain.
Hey, Snake,
what are you doing here anyway?
I heard they busted you
pretty good in Cleveland.
Location of rescue team member -
50 yards from your present position.
40 yards from your present position.
Rescue team member is located
10 feet from your present position.
100 bucks says you can't
put three blades into him.
Want a throw?
Hey, one-eye, I'm talking to you.
Where can I find Cuervo Jones?
What do I look like,
a fucking tour guide?
- It's wintertime, baby.
- I'm looking for Cuervo Jones.
Why? Hershe's looking for Cuervo too.
- Where is he?
- He's on Sunset. He's gonna come by.
Sunset.
Boulevard. Ooh-hoo,
you really are new, aren't you?
Come on, baby. I'll show you.
Keep going down that way, honey.
You can't miss it.
Hey, one-eye!
Look in my face
when I talk to you, shit-heel.
Whoa!
Neurosystem shut-down-seven hours.
Plissken.
Yeah?
Did you find the team member?
Yeah, they're using him
for target practice.
What will you do?
Amigos, no matter
where you come from,
or what colour you are, we're
all the Russia of the oppressed!
- Watch the parade.
- What?
We've got the north by the balls.
Come on! Right? Right?
Meet me at the Happy Kingdom.
Let's party tonight,
because tomorrow we're going to
start our way back to glory!
Yeah! We got our freedom!
We got a future!
That looks like Snake Plissken.
Who?
Used to be a gunfighter. Faded
out from the scene a few years ago.
I hear he slowed down some.
Doesn't look that slow, Cuervo.
Watch it! Watch it!
No!
Nobody rolls into town
and disrespects me.
Not Snake Plissken, not nobody.
Bolas!
Take him out!
I'm gonna give
you assholes a chance.
What do you say
we play a little...
Bangkok rules?
Nobody draws
until this hits the ground.
You ready?
Draw.
Hey, he left his coat here, man.
Malloy.
Plissken.
Have you got the black box?
Negative. And I've lost
the core burner and holocam.
I don't need to know your problems,
I just want my black box.
You've got seven and a half hours.
Do you read me?
Listen, Malloy. This guy's got more
heat around him than the President.
I'll get your box,
but I need time, understand?
Listen, Plissken, that headache that
just kicked in will only get worse.
You're starting to feel
the effects of the virus.
Soon you'll have a fever.
Now, you bear that in mind.
Just push on through, soldier.
Oh, don't shoot. Don't shoot.
I thought it was you.
Yeah, I recognised you right away.
I've been hangin' round here
for years,
but I never thought I'd see
Snake Plissken.
It's a real pleasure to meet you.
I'm Map To The Stars Eddie.
Where's Cuervo Jones' place?
He's the man with
the President's daughter.
He's setting up something big, but I
got a feeling you know that, right?
Location.
That way.
If you're going through Beverly
Hills, you're gonna need a map.
It's pre-recorded.
I narrated it myself.
Welcome to your own map to the stars.
That's me.
The big one wiped out the
entertainment industry in LA,
but the glamour of Hollywood
is still alive,
so come and see where the stars...
Hey, Snake, you'll need this.
I'm telling you.
I'll give you a deal. 50,000 bucks.
That's a real bargain!
...Map To The Stars Eddie,
and here we go.
Sucker.
Stay down, man, or they'll see you.
It's only their second shift.
Don't make one move.
If you want to make noise,
go and find another bush.
You're the one making all the noise.
Ah, shit!
Plissken's tracer just went down.
Terminated?
Yes. We can't locate him -
he's wearing stealth.
- Now what?
- We sit tight and wait.
Wait? For how long?
He's probably dead.
Wait, Mr President. Be patient.
I told you to stay down.
Look what you've done.
I can't believe this.
Are you Snake Plissken?
You look like him... in a way.
By the way, genius,
we're both dead meat.
What are they?
Surgical failures.
They live here.
Too many implants and face-lifts
over the years.
Their muscles turn to Jell-O.
They only survive
by having fresh body parts
transplanted over and over again.
Oh, my God.
Who's that?
The surgeon general of Beverly Hills.
These are no good.
You couldn't give them away.
And this...
I can do nothing with this one.
Wheel it away.
I can't work with garbage like this.
Now, these two...
They look very good.
My God, they're real.
What a beautiful blue eye.
Shame he only has one.
Nurse!
Still...
One eye's better than none.
Anybody moves, I'll blow
his brains out and then yours.
You... get my guns.
Now.
Back off.
Now, everybody relax,
and he won't die.
Hey. Hey, man, help me.
You'll never find your way
out of here without me.
Really.
Cut her down.
Down there.
Quickly.
Get in.
I think we lost them.
I think we're lost.
This way.
I used to run guns
with the Black Jihad last year.
We drove golf carts
up and down these tunnels.
I know them
like the back of my hand.
You are Snake Plissken, aren't you?
I used to be.
I thought you'd be taller.
- What are you doing in LA?
- Dying.
Ooh. But first
you got to find something?
President's daughter.
She's with Cuervo Jones.
You want to go to Cuervo's place?
- I've been there once.
- Show me.
All right.
I always heard about you,
like they couldn't catch you
no matter what you did.
Very cool, Snake.
Sooner or later, they get everybody.
Up.
Cuervo Jones' place is down that way.
Get off at the Vermont exit.
Go south. You can't miss it.
Be careful, though.
This is Korean Dragon territory.
It's very dangerous around here.
Bye.
Snake?
When you find
the President's daughter,
are you going to take her back?
No.
- You're staying in LA?
- Not if I can help it.
Sun is coming up in a few hours.
UV's gonna be bad today.
I know a place where
we could crash...
if you want.
My boyfriend and I
broke up tonight, so...
I'd love to take care of you...
and make you feel good.
I'll read your future.
The future is right now.
...and condemn the innocent blood.
Dear God, we call on you to be
our defence and our refuge.
We give thanks for being alive,
and pray that in your mercy...
Snake, it's me - Taslima.
I'm coming with you
to Cuervo's place. Yeah?
They're new.
They don't belong to any gang.
They're just scared, that's all.
That's how I was
when they first deported me.
- Why are you here?
- I was a Muslim in South Dakota.
Suddenly they made it a crime.
I mean, why stay?
You can go south - Mexico.
LA's still the place. What's happened
on the other side of the world...
That's the prison.
This is the only
free zone left... anywhere.
Dark paradise.
At least we get something.
A girl can still wear a fur coat
if she wants to, for example.
No, no, once you
figure out this place,
it's really not so bad.
Get down!
Where's it coming from?
The car in the street below!
Hop in, Snake. Come on.
Nobody ever gets out
of Beverly Hills alive.
- That's why you let me go there.
- You need one of my maps.
Listen to me, Snake.
I got connections here.
You can't just walk around
without knowing the ropes.
Take the wrong street, you're dead.
Stop the car.
All right, anything you say.
Although I was going to take you
to Cuervo Jones' place.
- Where is it?
- Right over there.
It's pretty neat, huh?
It's Cuervo's car. He lets me use it.
Don't worry, you've just
been shot with a fun gun.
Feel it? You feel it?
It's pure mesh, man.
100-proof artery choker.
When the hit pulls you an inch
from death, that is living.
I'm actually Cuervo's agent,
I'd love to represent you too.
We could make a bundle.
Help your career.
Last couple of years,
it's like you've disappeared...
I know what the cops sent him to do.
Plissken was the second rescue team,
looking for the box and the girl.
All I'm asking for is a finder's fee.
Maybe Wisconsin. I don't know.
- We're almost set up, Cuervo.
- Good.
I originally heard about this
when I was working for NASA.
Common, ordinary remote-control unit.
Yeah? Everyone's got one, right?
Here's the kicker.
This instruction disk hooks you
into the Sword of Damocles,
the ultimate defensive weapon system.
You see that?
A ring of satellites
encircling the earth.
Attached to each satellite
is a mega neutron bomb.
When detonated, each satellite
unleashes an intense
electromagnetic pulse,
but EMP doesn't harm a living thing.
But it does shut down every known
power source, all electrical devices,
cars, aeroplanes, toasters,
computers, everything...
even batteries.
But this... makes this
an aiming device
that gives the user
incredible accuracy.
You can pinpoint precisely
what you want to shut down.
A taxi cab in Buenos Aires,
the entire country of Spain. Amazing.
You could shut down the whole planet,
send it right back to the Dark Ages.
- He's dead.
- I agree.
Plissken's been dead before,
but he never stays down.
The mission's scrubbed, Commander.
I shouldn't have let you
talk me out of that air strike.
Well, it's on now, effective
immediately. Full-scale.
Target Los Angeles.
Flatten it. Burn it.
No!
What did you say?
Cuervo Jones is holding
all the cards now, sir.
He sees our aircraft,
he pushes that button... kaboom!
There goes our aircraft
AND the United States.
We don't even know if he knows
how to work the goddam thing.
Snake Plissken, American outlaw.
You'll like this.
Remember, Cuevo, you've got to punch
in the world code first - 666.
That brings all
the satellites on line.
Eh, pendejo, you think I'm stupid?
No. No. No. I'm sorry, Cuervo.
Bring them in.
OK, OK, go on.
'Hello, North America.
Buenas noches, Sud America.
Yes, I am Cuervo Jones...
Wait a minute.
That's Plissken.
This is LA, people without
hope or a country.
I knew it. He's alive.
You know what they want-liberation.
Now it's their turn.
I am taking over with this.
I told you not to try
to get this back, didn't I?
But you disobeyed me. Well...
He's entering the target code.
Bend over, Mr President.
Time for a spanking.
He's targeting Lynchburg.
That'll shut down the capital.
Get me the White House.
- This broadcast is live...
- Get me my wife, please.
- Are you watching TV?
- Yes, I'm watching it.
Yes, I know.
Curfew.
Hello? Hello?
Hey, Presidente,
silence is golden, no?
Don't tell me you didn't
enjoy this just a little bit.
I mean, if your wife's
anything like your daughter,
she's sweet,
but you just can't shut her up.
Knock it off, Cuervo.
All right, now this is set.
We shut down
the entire United States.
I want a police chopper to come
and get me at the Happy Kingdom,
no later than 5am.
Once I'm airborne,
you'll get your orders.
Remember, don't piss me off,
or I'll... pull the plug.
I'm at the mercy of this madman.
Don't count Plissken out, sir.
He's tanked. He's a POW.
But he's still alive.
Six, five, four, three, two, one!
Shot clock!
Get him. Get him up.
But this is insane.
It is. That's the point.
All right, all right.
I promised you tonight
was going to be special.
I also promised one last spectacle
of death in this historic arena.
Now you will see that death.
I give you...
the death of Snake Plissken!
Some people think
you're already dead, Snake.
Some say you never will be.
You may have survived Cleveland,
you may have
escaped from New York,
but this is LA, vato.
And you're about to find out that
this fucking city can kill anybody!
LA! LA!
Game time!
Basketball.
Two hoops. Full court.
10-second shot clock.
Miss a shot-get shot.
Buzzer goes off
before you shoot-get shot.
Two points for a basket.
No three-point bullshit.
All you got to do is make
10 points. That's it.
By the way,
nobody's ever walked
off that court alive.
Nobody.
All right!
Six, five, four...
three, two,
one!
Five, four...
three, two, one!
- Nice shot.
- He's getting tired now.
Four, three, two, one!
This town loves a winner.
He won, Cuervo.
- You can't kill him.
- I have to.
Get off!
It's the big one!
Find him!
We're going to Anaheim.
Come here.
Cuervo. Cuervo, wait up.
Give me a minute!
- Get lost, agent!
- We got a relationship here, man.
Let me make something clear.
I'm getting irritated,
and that's not good.
Irritated with me? Cuervo, I'm
taking care of you, understand?
- We can't find him, Cuervo.
- Keep looking!
Get in the car.
If I'm being too rough on you,
just let me know.
Snake, don't shoot. It's me - Utopia.
I'm alone.
This whole place is a nightmare.
Cuervo's a killer.
He's worse than my father.
I want to go back with you.
Oh, my God.
My father sent you
to kill me, didn't he?
Shut up.
Get out of here.
Go.
Wait. You can't
take that back, Snake.
Oh, God.
You can't give that to him.
He wants to control everything,
just like Cuervo.
If I don't take it back, I'm dead.
Another one?
Run!
It's over.
Get me a damage report
as soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
Oh, thank God almighty.
Maybe that's the answer
to all of our problems.
Maybe... maybe they're all dead.
Maybe.
Oh, Cuervo, man!
We almost bought the farm.
The whole place
just fell in right behind us.
Where is Plissken?
He's down there. He's dead.
He's history, and I did it.
I killed him. I shot him.
Right? Tell him.
Give it to me.
Oh, yeah. I brought it
back to you, Cuervo.
It's all there.
Whoa, dude, is that you, Snake?
Far out, man.
Hey, did you find Cuervo, man?
Hey, Cuervo, wait.
I've done it all, man.
I killed Plissken.
I got your girl back for you...
So where is he?
I shot him.
He went down, OK?
His body's probably in
Wilshire Canyon somewhere.
Good! So then you know where he is.
Bring me his head.
- Where's the Happy Kingdom?
- Anaheim. The invasion staging area.
Everyone's gonna be there,
except me.
I'm staying here, man,
I'm ready for the big wave.
- Take me there.
- What?
Take me there.
You're not well, Snake.
You need help.
Hold on.
- Who shot you?
- It doesn't matter.
Yeah, you're right.
Talk to Hershe.
She hates Cuervo.
They used to be partners,
and they split up.
- Who?
- Hershe.
She lives in a big boat.
Hangs with Saigon Shadow.
Man, they don't take shit
from nobody.
What is that?
Tsunami, Snake. Tsunami! Woo!
Surf's up big-time now,
mister. Ha ha!
Start feeling better quick, man,
cos you ain't got time to escape.
This is going to be some ride, man,
some kind of bitchin' ride.
Let's go. Come on.
Bitchin', man.
Let the front edge pick you up. Don't
get on till you ride to the top.
Don't blow it, man. If you fall off,
it's the big wipe-out. Got it?
Whoo! Bitchin'.
Hang on, Snake.
You got to be kidding me.
Later.
Ooh, Snake!
Tell me how to get downtown -
somebody named Hershe.
- Sure, Snake. No problem.
- Hey, hey!
Are you going to kill me?
Hershe.
Right. Keep straight.
Two blocks down, right.
Warning.
Neurosystem shut-down. One hour.
I first met Hershe
when I got deported.
She helped set me up.
We're talking a power player.
Cuervo's got numbers and firepower,
but Hershe's got big-time ambitions.
The two of you hooked up together,
I'm talking box-office material.
What?
Easy, Snake. I see him, too.
We're OK. Come on.
She's going to love you, Snake.
You'll love her, too.
We'll make this thing happen.
I'm through with Cuervo. The guy's
got no sense of loyalty whatsoever.
Through here.
What?
How you doin'? Long time, no see.
Remember me? Map To The Stars Eddie.
I got somebody I want Hershe to meet,
Snake Plissken,
right here in the flesh.
Your gun.
Great. Thanks, pal.
All right, we're in. Strange scene
here. Let me do the talking.
Hey, Hershe, how you doin'?
Hang on, guys. This is big.
It's Snake Plissken.
I brought him to see you, Hershe.
He's got a business proposition.
- What's in it for me?
- Wait a minute.
I know that voice.
Yeah... You're Carjack Malone.
Not any more.
You two know each other?
The more things change, the more
they stay the same, huh, Carjack?
Still packing a gun
between your legs.
Hold on, honey...
You bolted on me in Cleveland.
Hershe, you were in Cleveland?
With me and Texas Mike O'Shea.
You looked different then, Carjack.
Get one thing straight.
I'm no longer Carjack Malone.
I'm Hershe Las Palmas,
the most drop-dead number.
What the hell happened in Cleveland?
- I got caught and you didn't!
- Don't lie to me!
So I made another deal! I've
been here five years, not you!
I got a new deal.
You help me, you live.
I wouldn't do that, Snake.
See, anything happens to me,
and you're dead.
I'm already dead.
I see your point. What's the deal?
Get me to Cuervo Jones.
I got one hour.
Dream on, blue eye.
Say good night, Carjack.
Cuervo's got firepower.
No one gets near him.
And he's got the black box
and the girl.
- What black box?
- That shuts down the power.
Oh, yeah, right! And the Plutoxin
Seven virus kills you in ten hours.
- What?
- It's bullshit!
Rumour control. Government
propaganda. Just one more lie.
It's true. I represented
the guy who invented it.
Swear to God, Snake.
What's the deal, gorgeous?
Get the girl and the box,
and get out.
All of us?
- Yeah.
- Me, too?
Why should we leave?
I love LA.
Where we gonna go?
What's the big payoff?
A million dollars
for whoever helps me.
A million greenbacks?
I got ten million the next room.
Uh-uh. Bluebacks.
- Come on, Snake.
- Swear to God, Eddie.
This is bigger than Cleveland.
It sounds thin to me.
You want Cuervo to rule the world?
No. That sucks.
So how do we get out?
I'll tell you that when we get there.
Oh, Plissken, man,
you are such a loser!
Making up shit along the way.
That's why I left you in Cleveland.
You're just a chump
like the rest of us. No deal!
Government chopper. It'll be there.
OK, that's better. How are we
getting there in an hour?
That's your end.
Edward.
Best you could do is take the five.
The shape it's in,
two and a half hours minimum.
No. Use the air. They're burning.
The Santa Anas. The night wind.
- What are you talking about?
- Death from above.
I don't know about this.
You don't like it, don't come.
Where'd you get these rigs, Carjack?
My name is Hershe.
Understand, Plissken?
I got an idea.
Got any red nail polish?
- What?
- Come on.
I expect that back, Eddie.
There. Looks just like the Sword
of Damocles instruction CD.
Maybe we can pull a Texas switch.
- If you get close enough.
- Don't worry.
The wind's up. Let's go!
Shut-down - 34 minutes.
Are you ready for the new world?
The attack is now under way!
- What's going on?
- We're fucked!
You see Plissken anywhere?
Shut-down - 25 minutes.
Get my jet ready.
Get it fuelled ready to go.
You can't run away. It's too late.
You have to stand and face it down.
Mr President.
Commander, we're receiving reports.
An armada of warships
has departed Cuba,
ETA, Florida in 45 minutes.
They're starting the invasion.
I'm going to my quarters!
I've got to pray!
Go with him. Make sure
he doesn't do anything crazy.
Hey, Eddie, is that
what I think it is?
Yeah. It kept changing owners.
Finally went bankrupt.
That thing in Paris killed them.
We need a diversion.
Hey, Cuervo! Hey!
Hey, Cuervo! I made it!
I made it! Wait for me! Whoa!
Oh, shit!
Hey, Cuervo!
Will you please kill him for me?
Hey! Hey! I got news!
There's about to be an attack!
You're about to get hit, man.
It's Plissken.
You told me you shot him dead.
Yeah, I thought I did,
but I found him... sort of... alive.
Sort of. Where?
- Oh, Cuervo.
- What?
- It's so good to see you.
- Where is Plissken?!
- He's near.
- You're stalling, Eddie.
Aah! Jeez!
Talk, gringo,
or I'll rip your balls off.
Look out behind you!
You have lied to me
for the very last time.
Come on, hurry up! Let's go!
Get inside the chopper.
It's bulletproof.
I'll take my coat back now, asshole.
- Take me back.
- Secure the latch.
You got the remote. Great.
Yeah. Give me the real one.
I didn't make a switch.
Yes, you did. I saw you.
Give me that gun!
Damn it. Carjack, we're hooked up
on your side.
I hit him!
Get back here, Plissken!
Aircraft entering quadrant four, sir.
- I'm getting radio contact.
- Boost it.
Get the antidote ready, assholes!
Plissken, do you have the box?
I got the remote control unit
and instruction disk.
Get the trucks, we're on fire.
Shut-down, two minutes, 27 seconds.
All emergency vehicles,
proceed to the north perimeter.
Shit! Shit!
This is a full alert.
Where the hell is he going?
Get ready to jump.
Head for the tree line and disappear.
Go.
Go!
Oh, thank God almighty!
Thank God almighty!
Welcome back, sir.
Give me the goddam shot.
Your countdown clock has now
terminated function. Your time is up.
I told you he was dumb.
You took the fake, hotshot.
Plutoxin Seven is a fast,
hard-hitting case of the flu.
Pretty good.
Relax, war hero.
We took you for a little ride,
and you came through.
Now, give me that unit.
You want this thing?
Come and get it.
- Sir...
- What can he do?
Let go of me! Quit it!
You didn't finish the mission, Snake.
Looks like I'll have
to do it for you.
Hold it, Mr President.
Shit.
We'll take this one.
Get her out of here.
Daddy...
Take her to the chair.
For he so loved his country...
he gave his only seditious child.
Prepare to broadcast...
worldwide.
Worldwide!
She didn't know that she had it
in her pocket, did she?
I was wondering what kind of
lame switch you'd try to pull.
You're becoming very predictable.
Yeah, I guess so.
You got a smoke?
The United States
is a no-smoking nation.
No smoking, no drinking, no drugs,
no women-unless you're married.
No guns, no foul language,
no red meat.
The land of the free.
I don't need the teleprompter.
This is the President
of the United States.
I now demand an immediate
retreat of all forces
now threatening
this great nation.
If my demand is not met immediately,
I will destroy your ability
to function permanently.
Mr President, the Cuban aggression
remains mobile. ETA, four minutes.
Four minutes.
Bring the aiming co-ordinates
for Cuba and Mexico online.
Cuba-seven, seven, nine.
Seven... seven...
nine.
I now render this final solution.
Welcome to your own map to the stars.
The big one wiped out
the entertainment industry in LA,
but the glamour
of Hollywood is still alive...
Very funny.
I hope it was worth it,
for now you are going to die.
Everybody does.
Kill him...
and bring me the real unit.
- Sir, we're still broadcasting.
- Good! Let them watch!
Do it!
On my command!
Fire!
He's not even here! He's a hologram!
She catches on quick.
Got to be within a half-mile radius.
Round up every available man.
Hold it.
Sir, the enemy is less than
two minutes from our shore.
What's it to be, Plissken -
us or them?
Shut down the Third World.
They lose, you win.
Shut down America...
you lose, they win.
The more things change,
the more they stay the same.
So what are you going to do?
Disappear.
He's entered the world code.
No target code.
Sir, that will shut down
the entire planet.
I told you you'd better hope
I didn't make it back.
You push that button, 500 years'
worth of work will be finished.
Our technology, our way of life,
our entire history.
We'll have to start all over again.
For God's sakes, don't do it, Snake!
The name's Plissken.
He did it.
He shut down the Earth.
Welcome to the human race.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org