Kikina presents
Well, here we are!
You're Tony and you're Tia!
- Ma'am.
- Hello, Mrs Grindley.
Such fine-looking children!
I know you're anxious
to see your room,
but first, we have some forms
to fill out,
then we'll join the others
for dinner, all right?
Tia, what a pretty case!
Well...
It ain't nothing
writing out those entry forms.
Wait till she lays one of those
enlightened punishments on you!
"And after you watch
the five o'clock news
you can write
a 500-word composition!" Brother!
Tony, what should I put
after "sports"?
Put "spectator".
Dumb pen's out of ink!
I'm finished. You can use mine.
Hey, I lost one just like this
when I was coming into this barn!
- Tia's had that since Christmas!
- Sure she has!
Give it back!
Take it!
Now, children, that wasn't
so difficult, was it?
No, ma'am.
Now, Truck, I want you
to wait for me in my office.
We'll read this together.
I keep forgetting
what it feels like to sit down!
I know how both of you must feel.
Your foster parents
are the only parents you remember,
and now that they've passed away,
you're just a little bit scared.
- We loved them very much.
- Yes, ma'am. We miss them.
You only remember
your adoptive name, "Malone"?
Well, Tia was around three and I was
five when the Malones adopted us.
Did either of you ever receive
a birthday card from a relative?
Perhaps a phone call at Christmas?
Maybe you've forgotten.
Often, the most trivial thing
is important. Tia...
Were you remembering something?
No, Mrs Grindley. I'm sorry.
There's nothing
to be sorry about, dear.
You're out, Truck.
Nobody can jump that high, Malone.
You stood on something!
You're just trying to rip me off.
I was safe at third.
There's something funny about this,
and I'm gonna teach you a lesson!
Tony!
Cut it out, will ya?
Tony, why did you do that?
You don't think we're gonna
get away with it, do you?
You see?
Tony, you promised me
and I promised you
we wouldn't do the kind of stuff
you did with Truck.
Remember when we thought
it was all funny, like a game?
And all the other kids thought we
were freaks or witches.
I know, Tia.
We lost all our friends until
we quit doing the spooky stuff.
- You should have let Truck hit you.
- Are you kidding?
He's much bigger than me!
Then you should have made it
look like he won.
I suppose.
Tony, do you hear the dogs?
No. How far?
About 20 miles. Big dogs.
Six or seven.
Yeah, I can hear them now.
That's awful far, even for us.
Why are we hearing them, Tony?
I think it means
we're gonna see 'em some day.
If the bus is any later, we'll miss
the beginning of the picture.
- Yeah!
- I'll see what's keeping them.
Want to see something really neat?
- That's my star case, Truck.
- And you're his sister!
Tony, please. Not another fight!
It's your star case, Tia.
He might smash it.
Give it back to Tia now!
- I'll fight you with one hand!
- I'll fight you with none!
The bus is here!
Nice going, Winkie!
Tony and Tia!
What's taking you? Come on!
Hurry up!
Tony, across the street!
The big car? What about it?
Something's going to happen to it.
There's a man.
He mustn't get into that car!
There he is!
Come on!
- Sir, don't get in that car!
- It's no joke, sir!
My sister, she gets these feelings.
- You mustn't get in the car.
- Please, sir!
Children! You know the rules
about leaving the group!
- I'm terribly sorry, sir.
- That's all right.
I've changed my mind.
I'd like to take a walk.
- Pick me up by the park.
- Yes, sir.
- Are you all right?!
The moon is moving into Aries.
Friday, it will near
the middle of the transit.
The bottom line, Mr Meikeljohn!
The bottom line, Mr Bolt,
shows considerable indications
of some advance towards your goals.
House guru, do you concur?
There are profound vibrations,
Mr Bolt.
Are there indeed?
Vibrations. My moon in Aries.
Mysterious words and phrases haven't
added one cent to my fortune!
Wealth is like flesh,
it has to be nurtured and coddled!
Ah, Mr Deranian!
I'm sorry, Mr Bolt,
but when you've heard my report,
you will understand.
I have found
what you're looking for.
Wait here a minute.
I haven't had a chance to thank you.
Was the man in front all right?
Yes, but you knew he would be or you
would have kept him out of the car.
I suppose this sort of thing happens
to you all the time, young lady?
Knowing about things
before they happen?
The lunch bell. We have to go.
Excuse me.
Those two children that just left.
I've been trying
to think of their names.
Tony Malone and his sister, Tia.
A couple of weirdos!
Suppose somebody else walked in?
Everybody knocks.
Pine Woods rules!
Look.
Maybe it happened when Winkie
knocked it out of Truck's hands.
Can you fix it?
It's a map!
- Stony Creek?
- Misty Valley?
It's funny, Tia.
Every once in a while
you get that look on your face,
like you're remembering something.
I kind of do,
but then I forget again.
It's not someplace big
like a state or a country,
but more like a road map -
I just don't know where.
When I can figure out
where this place is, we'll go there.
Tony, what were you drawing?
It's where those dogs are.
- They're barking now.
- I know. I heard them,
and then I began
to visualise this castle.
Tony, you can only visualise places
we know something about!
Or places we're gonna be at.
I was drawing a place
we're going to.
Soon, Tony. We're going there soon
and I'm afraid!
Since the Malones lived in a village,
it was easy to find people
who knew the two children.
These insights,
these sixth sense incidents -
the postman, the school teacher,
the woman who lost her parakeet -
how do I know these are not figments
of your very fine imagination?
I have sworn affidavits.
People lie very easily. The very
young can deceive the very wise.
I'm not lying.
If I'm in any way disappointed
in this Tony and Tia,
you are through here, Deranian.
Yes.
I understand.
Then, bring them here. You say they
have no family - well, now they do.
You are their uncle,
do you understand?
Perfectly.
Alter records. Forge documents.
Provide proper papers.
I will back you
with every means at my disposal.
Just bring me the children!
There's no question,
considering these documents
your uncle has produced,
that he has custody of you.
The judge signed those papers
just today.
- Mr Deranian...
- Uncle Lucas.
- Better get used to it.
- Uncle Lucas,
did you tell Mrs Grindley
about the first time we saw you?
Yes, he did. The day the tow truck
ran into your uncle's car.
That was a lucky day for all of us!
You see, Tia, you look so much
like Mr Deranian's sister
that he's convinced
you both are her children.
My sister, your mother,
died six years ago.
If you have any doubts,
I can show you these documents
that prove he is your Uncle Lucas.
I won't have
to leave Winkie, will I?
He's very smart, and he knows
how to deal with dogs.
Did I mention dogs?
Well, thank you very much,
Mrs Grindley.
I'll see you out, Mr Deranian.
Children, don't forget your coats.
Do you have any feelings
about this Mr Deranian?
Only that he isn't our uncle.
Must we leave, Tony?
That's what these papers mean.
We haven't got a choice.
It's all right, Lorko. I'm just
bringing through the children.
I'm sorry, sir,
but I'm allergic to cats.
Let us through.
Those are the dogs we heard.
- There's the mansion.
- It's just the way you drew it!
Uncle Lucas, what's "Ex-anthus"?
It's "Zanthus", Tony.
Mr Bolt calls his house "Xanthus".
Who's Mr Bolt?
He's my employer. And your host.
I have spacious apartments here,
and thanks to Mr Bolt's generosity,
they've been enlarged
and redecorated
to accommodate the two of you.
So this is your long-lost family!
You've a very beautiful niece,
Deranian,
and a most attractive nephew.
You are Tony and you are Tia!
Here!
Our favourite flavours!
Vanilla and strawberry!
- Thank you!
- You're welcome.
After that long drive,
I'm sure you'd like to see
your new quarters. Come with me.
Wow! It's beautiful!
- Isn't it cute?
- I must be dreaming!
Tony, look at that!
Hey, look!
Oh, wow!
Look at these dolls
and stuffed animals!
Hey, Tony!
- When this is completed...
- There's more?
Yes! We haven't had time to install
the carousel or the gymnasium.
The tennis court
is being resurfaced.
Your riding lessons start tomorrow.
- Oh, wow!
- We love horses!
I forgot!
Winkie's private quarters.
I think he likes it!
They're really great.
- You still have school work.
- Your tutors arrive next week.
Where are the others?
- Other kids?
- Neighbours, I mean.
There are no neighbours.
Look out of the window. Go on.
Look as far as you can see.
Mr Bolt owns everything in sight.
Well, I could see the sky.
I saddled him myself
because this is your first time out.
Always mount a horse
on his left side because...
Tia, you'd better pay attention
or you'll be sorry.
That horse over there...
Thunderhead's never been broke.
I don't envy anyone who tries!
It should be ladies first,
but show Tia how easy it is.
A little filly the size
of your sister can get scared.
Thunderhead, that's not nice!
My name's Tia.
I want to be your friend,
all right, Thunderhead?
Tia, stay away from him!
Hold on!
Good boy!
I've never seen this in all my life!
Tia! Come here.
Why don't you try it
without your harmonica?
I forget how. Come to think of it,
you can do a lot of things I can't,
like working locks,
and the way you can talk to me
without moving your mouth.
Maybe it's because you're a girl.
That's the most incredible thing
I've ever seen!
Thank you. I'm having
more hidden cameras installed,
and as soon as I have
enough evidence,
I'll show the tapes to the children.
Good. If that doesn't put them
on my team,
we'll have to resort
to cruder methods.
Tia?
Tia!
Tia, what's the matter?
Oh, everything. And nothing.
I mean, maybe it's because we've
gotten everything we've ever wanted,
more, even.
I don't know.
It doesn't leave us anything
to wish for, is that it?
I think so.
Tony, we've got to get out of here
before it's too late. Please!
- What do you see?
- Mr Bolt, and he's mean.
He's never going to let us go, Tony.
You're not always right about things
like this, and I think this time...
Well, this time...
You're right.
I've enjoyed this.
Tony, Tia, we should arrange it
so that you dine with me more often!
Thank you, Mr Bolt.
There's fine, stimulating
conversation.
However, let us dispense
with the kid gloves
and admit that you're
two remarkable children!
I really don't think you...
I don't care what you think!
If these youngsters are psychic,
they've begun to see
through us by now!
Don't lay all...
You have power! I've seen it,
though I don't mean to ridicule
those gifts of yours as others do.
- I revere them. Do you believe me?
- What power do you mean?
He knows, Tony.
He knows all about us!
What do you mean, Mr Bolt?
What you did with Thunderhead
and the marionettes,
and the dozens of things
I've seen on my TV console.
I want to be able to understand
these powers, but I need your help.
You can make it possible!
You could walk across a field and
tell where there's oil beneath it!
You could foresee revolution,
disaster!
Please, Mr Bolt, you're too excited.
You're going to make yourself sick!
You should go right to bed, sir.
Yes.
Yes, I will.
Anything. Anything in this world
you ask me for, I'll bring you.
Just never leave me!
Not another word. Into bed.
Uncle Lucas, you look like you
could use some extra sleep yourself.
You heard what he said. He wants
to learn all the things we know!
We couldn't teach him,
even if we wanted to!
We don't know
why we do all these things.
We don't know how it all started.
Tony, we've got to get out of here,
please!
But to what, Tia? Where do we go?
Not to mention how?
The map.
- Mr Bolt.
- Listen!
Don't lay all your cards
on the table!
They're cunning. I don't
know the full extent of their power.
Here they could escape,
but the chalet is an island
in the sea of blinding snow.
They'll never escape from there!
Nutty as a fruitcake!
You see? We have to get out of here!
I know, but there's that high fence
and the guards and...
Children...
...finish your ice-creams
and I'll show you to your bedrooms.
He's coming.
Come on!
So far so good.
Those dogs will ruin all my plans!
What do you mean it's too late?!
- Now!
- Dogs, stay!
Stay!
Good dogs! There's some
very bad men after us.
Go get 'em!
There's still the main gate.
They're not gonna stop chasing us.
Call Thunderhead.
Thunderhead,
remember what I told you?
We're at the gate now.
- Lorko's on that lever!
- I'll help!
Winkie! Winkie!
Find them! I don't care how!
Chase 'em on a magic carpet if you
have to, but I want those kids back!
They rode out of here!
They're quite a challenge.
I will not rest until I get those
children back and neither will you!
I'm a vengeful man, Deranian.
I don't make idle threats!
Find them!
You'll be all right here, big fella.
Thank you, Thunderhead.
We'll miss you, Thunderhead.
Those sirens are for us.
We gotta keep moving. Come on!
They're getting closer.
Looks like you're taking
a mighty long trip, friend.
Yeah, I figured to drive
all over the United States.
Well, a covered wagon
pulling out of St Joe
didn't take near as much supplies
as you got here, Mr O'Day!
You're sure
one well-informed man, aren't ya?
Now, could you hand me that
without straining yourself,
or are you tuckered out from
sticking your nose in my affairs?
We're looking for two children.
A boy and a girl. Runaways.
If I saw 'em,
I'd let 'em keep running,
as long as they're going
opposite to where I'm headed!
What do you know about that?
A drifter, huh?
You're a friendly little fella,
aren't ya?
I got some canned tuna for you!
Hey! What are you doing here
in my...?
When I was loading supplies,
they were looking for two kids.
A boy and a girl! You two!
Let's get one thing straight
here and now! I ain't no bus line,
and I ain't partial to hitchhikers!
And I don't like kids!
And I'm a mean, impatient, selfish
man, so get on your way! Out!
Come on! Out! On your way!
Wait a minute. It ain't right
for no human being to go hungry.
I'll make you some breakfast
before you go.
Don't get any ideas.
I got no patience with kids,
especially runaways!
It's just the opposite, sir!
We're trying to find where home is.
Excuse me,
but did you see a black cat?
Oh, yeah. Yours, huh?
Well, she's around somewhere.
Go on down to the water
and clean yourselves off.
He just likes to bellow a lot.
He's not really mean.
You got to be kidding!
Sorry, sir, no sign of'em.
A grocer loaded up a camper
around the time the kids got away.
- They may have hidden in there.
- Did anyone spot a camper?
I let one go through.
The driver was alone, a big fella,
older guy, zip-up jacket, fair hair?
That's the one.
He was in a recreation vehicle,
heading north on Highway L38.
All right. North on Highway L38.
Now get out an APB
on an RV heading north on L38.
You see, Mr O'Day, we don't expect
to find our real parents,
- but maybe someone who knew them.
- And can explain things to us.
And we gotta make sure Mr Bolt
and Deranian don't catch us.
Well, maybe that's the truth
and maybe it ain't,
but I'm not gonna complicate things.
I'm gonna be on my way.
What did I do with my keys?
I know I had 'em in my pock...
- I must have lost 'em out there.
- You should have a spare key, sir.
I know that, young lady.
I am not a losing man,
at least not till you showed up!
Do you know a place
called Stony Creek?
Stony Creek?
Yes, there's good fishing there.
If we get the motor started...
and clean up the back section,
will you take us there?
Oh, so that's it?
You're nothing but a conniving pair
of undersized land pirates!
You swiped my keys
to make sure you'd get a ride!
Give me my keys.
Sir, the engine will start now.
All right.
You go back there and clean up.
Make everything ship-shape.
I'll see that you get to Stony Creek.
You just remembered something!
It has something to do
with the ocean.
Come on! Go on back. Clean up.
Let's get on the way!
Sure is a nice day!
Not with the prices
you're charging for gas!
Keep still. This fella's
acting mighty peculiar.
- Nobody could know we're with you.
- Maybe not.
You'll be out of my hair by tomorrow
once we get to Stony Creek.
- How much?
- Ten dollars even.
Ten. There you are.
Mr O'Day,
I think you bought too much.
Winkie can't drink four quarts
of milk between now and tomorrow!
If you weren't joshing me about
Aristotle Bolt being after you,
we might be together
longer than we planned.
He's a powerful man, too power...
Motorcycle cop!
That attendant at the gas station!
You won't get in trouble, will you?
It's not me he's after!
On second thoughts,
I might not drop you off too soon.
I might get an honest day's work
out of you! Take you fishing!
Deep sea fishing. Pit you
against half a ton of blue marlin!
Tia, what are you thinking about?
About before.
It had to do with fishing.
- With Daddy Malone?
- No...
But we were on a boat.
A trawler...
...like Daddy Malone had.
That's all I remember.
Every lawman in the county
is probably looking for this camper.
Here you are. Hot chocolate.
Thank you.
What's that you have there?
My star case.
Look at what we found
in the secret compartment.
- You see where Stony Creek is?
- Yes.
There's a path that leads
away from it up into some mountains.
We think maybe that's where we come
from, somewhere in those mountains.
No, I don't think it was that way.
Not exactly.
- There was an accident.
- Well, go on!
I... It's gone.
- What kind of an accident?
- I don't know.
- In a car?
- No.
On the ocean. And someone
helped me save my star case.
- Well, who?
- Whoever put the map in the case
hid it so well, it took you
all these years to find it.
That's right, Mr O'Day.
Why would anybody do that?
I don't know. Maybe...
Maybe waiting for you to get
old enough to do something about it.
- Like now!
- Very peculiar, huh?
I wonder...
I wonder how I'd handle you kids
if you were mine?
Maybe that's why I never married!
But, Mr O'Day, you were married.
What?
A long time ago. She was so pretty!
And you had a little house.
Yeah! I can see it!
It was white, with yellow shutters.
There was a big elm branch
over the whole roof.
Tony knows about people.
He can see places they've been.
What else?
Your wife died a few months after
you were married. You were so sad.
You swore you'd never give your love
to another woman or to anyone,
and you never have.
I'm sorry, Mr O'Day.
The name's Jason! You know so much
about me, you might as well use it.
Jason, you understand?
I like the name Jason.
We didn't mean
to make you sad, Jason.
Well, come on!
Are we gonna dawdle here all night?
Let's clean up here
and get some sack time in.
We'll pull out of here
a couple of hours before sun-up.
They're going to Longview,
do you understand?
Mr Deranian, $ 1,000 reward
speaks mighty clear in these parts.
You can count on me!
- Yes, I'll do that, Sheriff.
- It's been a pleasure!
A real pleasure!
Ubermann! Over there.
This time, no mistake.
Now, listen close.
We're coming into Longview.
My brother's house is two miles
outside of town, up the north road.
His name is Hiram O'Day.
There's a car behind us, Jason!
In Longview, I'll find a place to
make a fast turn and a quick stop.
You two jump out the side door
and hide. You got that?
Sure, Jason. You watch Winkie.
Yeah, I'll keep going.
If luck is with us,
Deranian and his pal will follow me.
You wait till he gets past.
Then we'll head
for your brother's house.
Hiram O'Day.
Don't lose him.
Well, now! Welcome to Longview!
6.10 a.m. OK, let's have your names.
- Tony Castaway.
- Tia Casta...
"Castaway"?
That's no name, it's a word.
Your legal name is "Malone"
and don't kid me about that.
I think I'll let you see
what lying to the law will get ya!
Come on.
In you go.
Tony, I've been thinking about
why we said our name was "Castaway".
It might have something to do
with us speaking another language
when the Malones took us in.
Another language?
That's why we didn't talk.
You mean, we had to learn English?
We spoke a funny kind of language.
- Uncle Bene spoke it to us.
- Who's Uncle Bene?
- I think he died. Drowned.
- What did he look like?
He had white hair...
We don't want no panic.
Well, Mr Deranian's on his way.
I'll be home if you need me.
We've got to think of something fast!
Hey, Tony, look!
Tony, that bear looks so unhappy!
Tia, we need my harmonica.
Now, open the cell door.
When I get the star case,
you run to the edge of the woods.
After I've freed the bear.
How can we get any place
with a big bear?!
- He's counting on me!
- But this is an emergency!
We have to get past the sheriff.
Why don't you think about that?
Get off me!
I hope we don't have to pass a zoo
before we get where we're going!
I know what I saw, and I say
there's only one explanation!
Those two kids are witches
and they're from Witch Mountain!
Arm yourselves
and divvy up into hunting groups!
What you gonna do? Chase 'em
all the way to Witch Mountain?
We'll stop 'em before they get there.
Now, listen close and I'll give you
the areas to cover.
Those look like hunting parties.
They got away, but we know
what they are - evil itself!
- We got to catch 'em!
- They're from Witch Mountain!
We need more ammunition.
We'll get 'em, Mr Deranian.
They've really got blood
in their eyes.
There's no use trying
to reason with them now.
Security. This is Deranian.
I want a complete check
on a Jason O'Day.
Tia, I know how you feel
about the bear,
and I think he's real neat, too,
but a lot of people
are gonna be looking for us,
and he'll be safer on his own.
Anyway, they might shoot him
just for the sport of it.
Look! He'll be safe there
until tonight.
- He can move on when it's dark.
- You're right. I'll talk to him.
You be a good bear
and wait in that cave.
We don't want anything
to happen to you.
Tony, his feelings were hurt.
Watch it!
Jason!
Hunters are everywhere!
They think you're witches!
My brother ain't home, but I'll get
you some food and you can rest.
There's a brother. Hiram O'Day. 244,
Cayhill, just north of Longview.
We can be there in 15 minutes.
I still can't figure out why we both
came up with a name like "Castaway".
I noticed that you two
are very smart for your years.
Do you know what a castaway is?
Sure. It's like being shipwrecked
and left on a desert island.
I just remembered. "Castaway" is
the name of someone we have to see.
That's funny.
I just remembered the same thing!
Suppose you two are castaways?
Then it would fit things
Tia's been remembering!
- Uh-huh.
- We were in some kind of wreck.
- And we were in the sea!
- You mean like a boat sinking?
I guess, but if it was a boat,
I don't remember where it came from.
We had an uncle. Uncle Bene.
He kept us afloat
and then he drowned.
For a long time, we didn't
understand anything anyone said.
You must have come
from another country.
We won't know everything till we get
to the mountains above Stony Creek.
- Like it shows on the map.
- Witch Mountain.
Hiram mentioned that place
to me in his letters.
He said some strangers settled
there, they kept to themselves,
and nobody ever knew
where they came from.
You think they might be your people?
They must be!
Security. Have you notified Mr Bolt
of our destination? Then do so.
We just heard from Mr Deranian, sir.
He's on his way to a Mr Hiram
O'Day's cabin, north of Longview.
Don't just sit here! Get going!
When Hiram gets home, he's gonna
find his cupboard is bare!
Come on. The camper's out the back.
Tia!
Can you hear me?
We need another favour.
- Come on!
- Tia!
There's no way we can get by 'em
without their seeing us.
I remember more. It wasn't just
Uncle Bene who died in the ocean.
A lot of other people died, too.
And those people
that live here in these mountains,
all of us came from the same
country, but on different ships.
You mean, yours sank
and the others made it to port?
But, Tony, it wasn't a country.
It was a place!
Yeah. A place
that isn't there any more!
Castaways?
That's why my people
call themselves that!
And this was the emblem
for where we used to live!
Two stars?
I don't know no place named that.
- It wasn't called that.
- No...
Two stars... because our world
had two suns!
Double stars!
Another planet!
A whole other solar system!
Then it wasn't a boat...
...it was a spaceship.
Our planet was dying.
The only industry left was
the manufacturing of spaceships.
Like ours.
We had to find
another planet to live on.
Then the other ships in your cluster
landed here in these mountains,
and yours didn't make it?
I think we might be the only ones
in our spaceship to have survived.
We lost them again.
We're going south on Highway 211.
Why don't you search the north?
Not too many people around,
are there?
"Misty Valley Cooperative"?
This is it.
Maybe they've gone out to lunch.
We'll wait.
Are you the Longview bunch
chasing after those two witch kids?
That's right. I'm Cort.
Are you putting up the reward?
That's right,
except it's now $5,000.
But there's a catch.
I want those two children alive.
I don't care about the old man. They
were in a camper headed this way.
- Sounds good, friend.
- Any idea where to look for them?
Well, they're not around here.
Maybe the next town up the line?
Stony Creek.
Stony Creek?
We're changing course now.
They've sure had time enough
for a lunch break.
It has something to do
with the phone book!
Let me have another look
at that map.
Misty Valley Cooperative.
I was calling the Castaway family
and I was wondering if...
Were you looking
for Mr Castaway?
Yes!
Watch it! Here comes Deranian!
- Is this Tony?
- Yes.
- Is Tia with you?
- Yes. Who is this?
Thank the stars! We've been
searching for you for years!
Listen carefully.
Everything must time out.
Take the back door
and go to Mr O'Day's camper.
Children, we want to make sure
Mr Deranian doesn't lose you.
We have a plan that will stop them
pursuing you again.
Come on!
Everything's all right.
You've got a funny idea
of what's all right!
Maybe Bolt can spot
the RV from the helicopter.
Men! Come on!
We've got a fix on them, sir.
Robertson Canyon, headed north.
How can he lose us in that monster
he's driving? Close in on them!
He's not exactly crawling.
They're getting closer, Tony!
Good driving, Al!
How did we wind up here?
Let's get out.
Very ingenious!
But remember we want Deranian
to see what's coming up.
I don't understand, sir.
We have something planned
that will convince Deranian and Bolt
that you're both
out of their reach for ever.
Deranian, I've spotted a route
that will let you cut ahead of them.
It's the second turn on the left.
I'll signal the others
not to follow you.
- Repeat, not.
- Understood.
- I don't believe it!
- It's what you call levitation.
That ain't what I call it!
You two got powers beyond belief!
We're not doing this. This is
something too powerful for us to do.
Somebody else is making this happen.
That thing's flying upside down!
That's impossible!
That kind of vehicle
can't fly upside down.
It's not supposed to fly at all!
They're not upside down, WE are!
The voice says
we should get out here and wait.
We'll never forget you, Jason.
Would you take care of Winkie?
Oh, no, Tia. Winkie's your cat.
It wouldn't be right for her
to be with anybody else.
It would make us happy.
It sure would,
and Winkie would like it, too.
Maybe we ought to ask Winkie
how she feels about that.
Winkie...
...how do you feel about going
around with a crusty old man?
Look...
...if you don't mind,
I'd like to plan
on remembering you two...
...as if you were my kids.
The kids I never had.
Uncle Bene!
You all did so well!
Congratulations, Jason O'Day!
You're a man of courage
and compassion.
We thought you'd drowned.
Well, if you know exactly
what to say to a shark,
he can be very accommodating!
Tia, you never forgot.
You didn't lose the star case.
We only found the map
a few days ago.
I knew when you were old enough
to understand it, you'd find it.
It's good to know that there are
earthmen such as you, Mr O'Day.
If the stars are willing, perhaps
the other children who survived
will find men equally as kind.
- There are more?
- Yes. All with star cases and maps.
So far, only Tia and Tony
have found the way.
Now that I know what to keep
my eyes peeled for,
perhaps I could spot some
of these kids and bring them here.
Deranian's car.
I'll have to attend to Bolt's
helicopter. Stay and watch.
You'll see how we came
into this world of yours!
What?! Stop this thing!
I'm all right!
Where are the children?
I should have known there was more
than ESP with those two!
Well, they're home now.