Second, you know I'd never do anything
to injure you.
You know I'd never do anything
to hurt my opinion of myself.
If the beret bothers you, it bothers me.
If it upsets you, it upsets me.
How did you enjoy shopping today?
Wait until you see what I got.
I got it because the saleslady
said it's one of a kind.
I'll never find another like it.
I know it's silly...
...but I only got it for you.
Honey, I wouldn't want the kids
to see me in something like this.
Sparky, it's our first night in Paris.
Let's do something romantic.
- I'm taking you out to dinner.
- "Out"?
I felt like staying in.
I thought it would be really nice
to be alone.
I'd never go anywhere without you.
Cheer up.
I promised you a night on the town.
We'll see some French culture.
You'll love it.
Down with the feet, hip distance apart...
...stomachs pulled in, buttocks tight.
Let's start with head rolls.
To the right and back and left and forward.
Isn't this great?
They've done this for eons in France.
This is real culture.
Exhale and raise your arms over your head.
Reach with the right...
Clark, could I have the coat check?
I think I've had enough French culture
for one evening.
- Look.
- I am looking.
Back there.
- It's just a hooker. They're everywhere.
- Look who she is with.
Russell Griswald.
Oink, oink, my good man.
- How did you get in?
- I paid.
- I'm surprised at you.
- I'm surprised at you, Dad.
Don't talk back.
- Who was that cheap slut?
- Cherie's not a slut.
I'm disappointed in you.
Who said, "When in Rome,
do as the Romans do"?
I said Rome, not Paris.
This is Paris, and you're drunk.
Hold it!
Let me have it!
Today is my turn.
- Give them to me.
- No!
Look what you did to them.
They're mine!
How many times do I have to tell you that?
Will you slow down?
The kids are exhausted.
It closes in 15 minutes.
There are 100,000 works of art to see.
Great. Are you happy, Dad? She's dead.
I'm proud of you guys.
We've seen everything in Paris,
and we're on schedule.
Can't we slow down a little bit?
I'm exhausted.
We'll have a relaxing time
with my relatives in Germany.
Enjoying Paris?
Have you seen the Louvre yet?
Not yet.
The Left Bank is charming.
We plan to go there.
- Been up the Eiffel Tower yet?
- No, but it's on our list.
Have a good time.
What a waste. We've seen 10 times
as much as they have.
Hi, sweetie. You want some breakfast?
I'm not hungry.
He's got his hands on her tits
right at the table.
Stop staring.
European standards of public behavior
are different than ours.
But they're from Akron.
Audrey, I've missed the shit out of you.
Luckily, Debbie came by to cheer me up.
- That bitch!
- Something the matter, Audrey?
It's time we asked ourselves
this question:
Is this relationship strong enough
for us to consider seeing other people?
I think it is.
Pass the croissants, please.
And the butter and jelly.
I'm glad your appetite's back.
Who have I got to be thin for?
He's going to pork her.
He isn't going to pork her. Now eat.
I think he is.
He may pork her. Just eat, okay?
There it is, kids.
My motherland.
Dad, Grandma's from Chicago.
Shut up, Russ.
I can't wait to meet our relatives,
in person.
Dipplestrabe.
What are we looking for?
- Sechs.
- That will do, Audrey.
That's German for "six. "
Is that true?
My family and I are looking for sechs.
There's number six.
Fritz, Clark Griswald. Good to see you.
Remember Ellen from her letters?
There she is.
And Rusty and Audrey.
They've gotten bigger since the pictures.
Sorry we're late. I went to
the wrong door. Thanks for the invitation.
This must be the German dining room.
Isn't it nice?
Clark, it's just as I imagined.
It's so quaint.
Yeah, maximum quaintness.
You must be Helga. We made it.
You know Ellen, my wife,
and Rusty and Audrey.
Let me help you in the kitchen.
Come on, kids.
Go help in the kitchen. Help Helga out.
So, Fritz, how you been?
Long time never seen.
Here's your cousin Al.
He's a hotshot lawyer.
They'll probably get him on tax evasion.
Here's the baby.
You don't believe that cock-and-bull story
about the baby being premature?
I didn't think so.
When me and Jack got together,
we'd been seeing other people.
But this is different, because Debbie
is my best friend, don't you think?
God, it's so good
to have someone to talk to.
I tell my parents stuff but they don't seem
to know what I'm talking about.
- What are you talking about?
- You see?
God, I miss Jack.
I was just thinking.
Blood really is thicker than water.
It's amazing how family ties
break through language barriers.
This has been my favorite part of the trip.
Dad, look. Bedpans.
You've been so sweet. Here's our address.
When you come to Chicago,
come stay with us.
Thanks for the marvelous conversation.
We'll write.
A festival.
It looks like fun. Come on, kids.
- What's your name?
- Claudia. And yours?
- I'm Rusty.
- Hello.
Do you ever get to leave here?
What's so funny? This is great, isn't it?
I love these.
Who wants bratwurst, mustard and relish?
Holy shit!
Hey, you! Come on!
Very good. We need one more.
A big strong man.
Hey, you! Come on!
Come on, don't be afraid.
I don't know if I can do that.
Just follow the others.
Isn't he great?
- Those bells haven't rung in years.
- What does it mean?
They're going to hang somebody!
Dad.
Hurry up!
Oh, shit.
- It's too narrow!
- There's plenty of room.
I know this car.
Get out! There goes the paint job.
Why the sour puss?
You ruined what could have been
the best day of my life.
What are you complaining about?
I lost my boyfriend thanks to this vacation.
- I vote we stop talking about Jack.
- I vote for that.
I vote we don't talk
about schedules anymore.
Me, too.
I'm for that.
I vote we don't talk at all until we get
to Rome and everybody calms down.
Maybe then we can act
like mature human beings.
Clark, I thought we'd talk.
What are we doing?
We're going to a travelers checks place
to get our money refunded.
We'll rent a new car, buy some clothes...
...and finish the best goddamn vacation
of our lives.
Let's go.
I think Dad's lost all sense of reality.
Let's get out of here.
What are we going to do with him?
Kill him?
Don't be stupid. We never kill anyone.
Then, what do we do?
I've got a better idea.
We can hold him for ransom.
He must be worth something.
Clark! I think this is something historical.
It looks real old, Dad.
That's great. We'll see it later.
Only four more miles. Let's go.
What we need now is a dupe.
Someone above suspicion...
...who will believe anything you tell him.
A real idiot.
Anybody here?
We have no proof
we lost the travelers checks.
We left the stubs in the suitcase.
Can I help you?
I'm Clark W. Griswald. We're
the grand prize Pig in a Poke winners.
We're in a bind. We lost our luggage,
a videotape camera, rented car...
...and $1,000 in cash.
So, I'm just here to get my money back.
I certainly hate to see
our customers inconvenienced.
- Name?
- Clark W. Griswald.
Ellen Griswald.
These are our children, Rusty and Audrey.
Come over here. Show yourselves.
Here we are.
Excuse me. We lost only $1,000.
This is $3,000.
That's to make up for your trouble.
I lost about $200.
Stay quiet. We'll get you out later.
Unfortunately, we somehow
misplaced the key to the trunk.
If you tell me where you're staying,
we'll send the key there.
At what hotel are we staying?
- The Nazionale.
- Very nice.
I didn't know you rented cars.
I'll see you, then.
Let's see some Roman ruins.
We've been in these clothes for ages.
Let's go shopping.
I vote for shopping.
I feel totally scuzzed out.
We'd all look good in some Italian fashions.
Got plenty of money.
- You look cool.
- I feel cool.
Looking good, Mom!
Let's go. We ready to conquer Rome?
I'll be back and we'll hit the fountains.
I'm terribly sorry. Are you all right?
No problem at all.
It's you. The guy from London.
You're the American I ran into.
What are you doing in Rome?
On sick leave. A little holiday. Recovering.
Still on holiday with the kids?
Yeah, we're here.
We've just been out shopping.
Nice choice.
They're right there.
Kids, look who it is! Say "hi"!
You've got a cast on your leg.
This? Think nothing of it.
Hardly matters at all.
It's just a big sock, really.
That's pretty nice of you. I feel bad.
At least, let me give you a hand.
No, thanks!
Isn't this your hotel?
No, my hotel's over there.
Have a nice holiday.
Okay. Cheerio!
This is the Piazza Navona.
Jack?
It's one of the most fabulous squares
in Rome. What's wrong?
I want to go home. I miss Jack.
We have a few more fountains to see,
then the Colosseum.
I don't want to see the Colosseum.
I want to see Jack!
Jack will always be there.
The Colosseum will always be there.
It's been there 2,000 years.
If I don't go home soon, Jack will fall
in love with Debbie, and I'll die.
Don't you want to see the Colosseum
before you die?
I hate you.
I'll meet you later at the hotel.
What about the fountains?
I'm fountained out.
Clark, let him go.
We're leaving in two days.
These are our last moments together
as a family.
Dad, we've been together every second
for the last two weeks!
By the way, I've been good.
I haven't complained or tried to escape.
Why can't you treat me like a man,
for once?
Because you're not a man.
I am, too!
I'm 15 years old, a world traveler.
I have a part-time job.
I need my independence.
If he's going, I'm going.
Why don't we give the kids
some free time?
Sure. Let them go.
They're just a couple of ingrates.
They're not ingrates, they're teenagers.
- Where's my allowance?
- Where's my passport?
Just a minute!
Let's settle down and be reasonable.
If we think about it,
we can all make some compromises.
Oh, my God!
- Take it easy.
- I don't believe this!
This is the most humiliating thing you've
ever done to me! This is the last straw.
It's not my fault they stole the camera.
You promised to erase it!
I was going to erase it.
The guy stole the camera.
This is the lowest, the worst, Clark!
Where are you going?
We're going to the Colosseum at 2:00.
I'm going back to the hotel!
We didn't vote on that.
Forget your vote!
I'm seceding from the Union...
...forming my own government,
and declaring war on you!
- She knows I didn't do it on purpose.
- I don't blame her.
Yeah, it's not even a good likeness, is it?
I guess it's just you and me, Audrey.
Buongiorno.
That's bellissimo.
Really choice?
And I think that
you are really bellissimo also.
You're not too shabby yourself.
- You speak English?
- I'm from California.
All right! I'm from Chicago.
Do you want to go scarf
some grimace proportions?
What are you doing in Rome?
Traveling with my folks.
Me, too. We won...
- Pig in a Poke. I saw the show.
- You saw the show?
You answered the Thomas Edison
question and won car wax.
- You remembered?
- Yes, I thought you were cute.
You thought I was cute?
Finally, there's one of them.
And she's alone.
Let's get the guy out of the trunk.
Too many people here.
We'll move the car first.
I'll get the keys from her.
I hate to see a beautiful woman
drink bad wine.
Then you should leave,
because I'm going to get plastered.
What is it?
Is it your husband?
That pig?
He's not a pig.
He is a pig. He is!
Thank you.
Operator, I'd like the number
for information.
I want to call the airport.
Numero, please-o.
Pan Am.
Va bene. Non si preoccupi.
Faccio io. Lasci stare.
È stata una disgrazia.
Ora rimedio io, piano piano.
Che fa?
Then I rolled on the floor
and started going...
I was completely naked.
Not completely, I had on a towel.
He promised me he'd erase that.
He promised me he'd erase it.
I'm a ruined woman.
I thought this was going to be...
...like some kind of second honeymoon.
We should have left the children
with Helga and Fritz.
I'm sorry, but I should go to my room now.
I'm going to throw up.
Let me help you.
No, no. I'll be fine, really.
I think you'll feel better if you lie down.
I have a philosophy
about dealing with my parents.
If I'm in school or hanging out
or something...
...there's all this pressure
to act cool or do the right thing.
But if I'm with my parents,
who really cares?
They don't know what's cool and what's
not, so I just put everything on hold.
That's a great way to look at it.
I'm having a great time.
Me, too.
Imagine coming all the way to Rome
to meet someone from California.
Whatever happened to us?
We were high school sweethearts.
We never even did it until we got married.
Well, at least until we decided to.
And I left him all alone in that piazza.
I said the "F" word in front of my children!
What kind of woman am I?
Exciting.
Don't fight it, Ellen.
What are you doing?
Let me take you away from this.
I don't want to be away.
I want my Sparky back.
It was just a little argument.
He'll be here any minute.
He's very jealous.
I'm calling the manager.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Are you taking any calls?
The police are here.
Stay away from the Fiat.
I'm leaving.
I'll be right down.
Debbie, Audrey!
We've got a score to settle,
and you know what I mean!
If you want to salvage our last shred
of friendship, do me this favor.
I want you to book me on a Pan Am
flight out of Rome into Chicago today!
Yeah, I'll hold.
Bitch.
Take the car keys!
Find your father!
Don't move.
Mom, where are you going?
- What's wrong?
- Mom's been kidnapped.
- Where's the car?
- Over there. Here's the keys.
There they are!
Hey, Dad, there's the Colosseum!
I've talked so much. What about you?
What are your parents like?
There's really not that much to say.
They're just normal parents.
My Dad's all right.
He's a little slow sometimes.
God, that's Dad!
- What happened?
- Not much. Mom's been kidnapped.
Darn it all!
Excuse me. There's a man in the trunk.
I'm coming!
Take my hand!
Clark, where are you going?
Get back here!
You bastard!
Come here.
Still on holiday?
Sorry. I'm looking for someone else.
No problem. I'm used to it. Good luck!
He kidnapped my wife.
You all right?
I love you, Sparky. You're my hero.
I know.
Your parents are actually pretty cool.
Yeah, they're good
for a few laughs, sometimes.
Now can we go home?
Look.
The Statue of Liberty.
I never thought I'd be so glad
to see the Statue of Liberty.
Me neither.
The great thing about traveling
is you really appreciate coming home.
I've got to go.
I never realized
how much I've missed America.
I bet America's missed the Griswalds.
I'm very sorry. Let me get...
My jacket is caught.
Yup. The Griswalds are back!