Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Thank God you're safe!
- How much was the ransom?
- It doesn't matter. This girl does.
Do you want some more coffee?
Hello. Are you okay?
- Not having a happy day?
- I've never really had one.
It's men, isn't it? They make you
promises they never intend to keep.
They say they'll buy you a house,
but they don't. You can't trust 'em.
She's not bad. I bought the CD, too.
I might make you a gift of it
if things work out between us.
That's a lot of money back there.
- I earned it, and without a gun.
- You stole a lot of cars.
- It pays well. What do you do?
- What did Emily say I do?
Not much... but it don't look good.
How come? Did I hurt you?
Did I shoot you in the groin?
Are those options?
Is that seat taken?
Coffee, please.
- Miss me?
- I guess. Was I supposed to?
Look at this place.
This is really a slice of Americana.
Yeah, Rockwell should've painted it.
I'm not going back with you.
- Okay... Let's talk.
- Nothing to talk about.
This is family business.
Let me go.
Vincenzo, por favor.
Sit over there.
- Did I lay a finger on you?
- No, he didn't do anything.
Thank you. Who paid for that
motel room last night? Right, I did.
- You're giving me a headache.
- I need some peace of mind here.
Right.
You look good. Pale, but good.
How come you're pale?
I thought you lived in Costa Rica.
I stay in the house a lot.
If you're here because you're
worried about me, I appreciate it.
But if my father ordered you
to bring me home, I'm not going.
Emily... can we go someplace else?
Don't you think it's strange that
my father isn't sitting here now?
Yes, it's strange, but strange
and normal are not my job.
This isn't about tattoos
and burning down the school library.
- The cops and the FBI want you.
- Daddy's lawyers will get rich.
They'll earn it this time.
You're facing felony charges.
Attempted grand theft.
Theft by deceit. Conspiracy...
- What are you talking about?
- Tell me.
I don't have my wallet.
There's the check for the coffee.
I'll get the bag myself
and bring you back the keys.
Yes! That's what I'm going to do.
Give my car keys to a car thief.
I've been a good sport till now.
I can't wait much longer.
- Go order yourself some waffles.
- Two minutes.
Two minutes. I'm tired of tossing
salad, if you know what I mean.
There goes my bargaining chip.
I'll give him to the police.
- He could name names.
- You can't do that.
- He's a thief.
- He's an innocent thief.
What are you saying? Have you
formed some attachment to him?
You're not turning him in.
I'm trying to keep you out of jail.
Away from all those sociopathic,
gang-banging lesbians.
With that mouth of yours, I'm sure
your dance card would be filled.
I'll take you home.
I'm not asking.
Let's go. What's wrong with you?
I'm taking you home!
I ain't going with you!
I never should've married you.
My papa made me do it.
That man beat me!
He's trying to keep me from my baby.
Vincent, let's go. He's got a gun.
- This is good.
- He's got a gun!
The lady wants to leave,
and you're not going to stop her.
- I'm saving your ass.
- Save the trees.
- It's not your concern.
- I'm making it my concern.
- That could've been you.
- He landed on his head.
He's going to turn you in
to try and clear my name.
- It'd be your word against mine.
- Don't be a jackass.
He's going to kill you.
I'll stand here and watch you die.
Peace!
- Do you think he's going to shoot?
- Yes, run!
I'm the only person in the world
who can get your money back.
- Quit being so stubborn.
- Right.
Come on, get off.
A guy left the keys in his pickup.
I'll start it up, and you jump in.
We're gonna get pulled over.
I can feel it.
- Just act like you own the car.
- How do I do that?
- Act like you're in control.
- Where are we going?
- Knotty Pines.
- What for?
So I can meet my man and say,
"Greg, how are you doing?"
"It's so nice to see you.
I just got robbed of $200,000."
"I enjoyed it. What? By her uncle."
- Is this science fiction, or what?
- Why tell him that?
- That money doesn't belong to me.
- I'll get the money for you.
- How are you going to do that?
- Trust me, I'll get you the money.
If you can do that for me,
I'll give you a million thanks.
- Start thanking me right now.
- All right, thank you.
- Have you got a boyfriend?
- No.
Why not? You're a pretty girl.
Watch the road. I mean, you are.
- You got a girlfriend?
- No, I gave that up.
I always see the potential failure.
- This is Greg from the warehouse.
- What's going on?
I thought you lost her.
She's sitting here in front of you.
- Sit down. We need to talk.
- Yes, we do.
- Hi.
- Scotch on the rocks.
- Do you have any I. D.?
- Scotch for me. Chocolate for her.
I really don't feel like
lounging over drinks in Heidi-land.
- Just give me the bag.
- I don't have the bag.
- Where is it?
- I left it in her uncle's car.
You left it in her uncle's car?
God, I don't believe this!
- Relax, it's not your problem.
- How the hell do you know?
- They think we did this together.
- Why?
Criminals think the worst of people.
They think we're in St. Bart's.
- St. Bart's?
- Well, you'd have already gone.
- Is she always like this?
- Yes, she don't listen.
Her father's going to give us
the money. Right?
- Her father? You said her uncle.
- My father will give it to him.
- He gives it to me. Understand?
- Your father...
- I don't believe this.
- Easier than collecting dust.
I can't believe you brought her.
Thank you.
She's an alcoholic, too. Wonderful!
Drink much?
I'll be taking this.
I'll get some toothpaste and a room.
Yeah, go freshen up.
- Do you know what you're doing?
- She took your money.
You make a great couple.
Like Bonnie and Clyde.
Emily? How did you know I was here?
You can't do business at home
with the phone tapped.
You had to be in your car,
on your plane, or on your boat.
You're a very smart girl. You know
I have to be overseas tomorrow.
Was the timing of this whole fiasco
in any way connected with that?
- Leave? Your daughter's in peril.
- What do you want from me?
Uncle Ray ripped off my friend.
When he's okay, I'll come home.
- Then you can get back to business.
- Very well.
You have my word.
Meet me at the boat tomorrow.
When she does come back,
there'll be some trouble.
I'll look after the police.
You take care of the rest.
I'll take care of it.
- What does your father do?
- Businessman.
- What does your mother do?
- She died when I was three.
- I'm sorry about that.
- It's all right.
- Can you remember her?
- No.
- Can I ask you a question?
- What?
What are you running away from?
I'm not running away.
- I'm trying to get your money back.
- Come on...
You're running away from something.
Why did you get in the trunk?
- Oh, we're talking about that.
- Yeah, I want to know about that.
- I wanted to make my father feel.
- Make him feel what?
Something.
How can I explain 18 years
of being unwanted and unwelcome?
- I was always a commodity to him.
- So you wanted to get even?
I always thought that there was
no one in the whole world -
- who could make me feel like I knew
who I was, except for my father.
You find yourself.
You show yourself who you are.
You don't need your father
to tell you who you are.
Do you know what's the best way
to make a dream come true?
Do you? Wake up.
You'll find... your eternal mother.
You'll find whatever you want.
It's true.
- Is there any more gin?
- We finished the gin.
No, we finished the vodka.
Maybe under your bed.
- Why under my bed?
- You hogged 'em all.
What have we got? Cognac.
I don't want any cognac.
I've got a question for you.
What do you want in the big picture?
I want to open my own chain
of karaoke bars down in Brazil.
A friend of mine told me
there's no karaoke bars in Brazil.
- That's a stupid idea.
- It ain't stupid.
I could be an entrepreneur.
You want to make money
just so you can make more money?
I've had that my whole life,
and it doesn't make you happy.
It's not about the money, okay?
I know what I do is wrong.
Believe me, I know.
I go home, get your money...
Then what do we do?
We?
If you want to come,
after we get that money...
I don't want to intrude.
I've got my own stuff to do.
No, really.
If you want to come, you can come.
I'm telling you, you can come.
I'm not making a pass at you.
Check it out.
Those guys are fast.
- Shut it off, please!
- I don't know how to.
- Here you go. Happy?
- Yes.
Listen, don't be telling anyone
about the karaoke plan.
I've got rum, tequila and rum.
What would you like?
You don't have to be drunk
to kiss me.
Well, I'm not drunk.
I stained my shirt. I was playing
with the hotel pen and it broke.
There's postcards in the room.
People write on them.
Do you like my tummy?
It's nice.
- Do you like my laugh?
- If you smile.
- I know you like my car.
- We never really got that close.
I guess you like me.
Let's go and have some breakfast.
Get in there.
Go.
- So you spent the night together?
- What do you need her for?
Are you kidding? We know who
her father is, and he's rich.
- Greg knew I'd get the money.
- Greg's deadline has passed.
- Right, Greg?
- I'm sorry!
- They gave it to me, too.
- Shut up! You want some more?
- Do you have to point that at me?
- Shut up.
You're not stealing cars, she's
a human being. Are you on drugs?
- Are you?
- Calm down, everybody.
- Drive the car!
- I don't need this for 200 grand.
We want a million. You can
yell and scream all you want.
Great!
Keep driving.
- We want a million, cash.
- All right.
Don't be late.
This is serious.
I'm way out of my league.
- Are you leaving?
- I'm out of here. First plane.
Tell Mr. Dokas those guys took
his money and burnt his warehouse.
- I'll take care of this.
- You've known that girl two days.
I know. Make that phone call.
Vincent...! Christ!
Emily Hope.
DOKAS
- I'm going to call Dokas.
- I'll get the luggage.
Wake up, my little princess.
Give Mr. Dokas a message.
The situation's under control.
We've got all his money.
I'll call you back
to make the final arrangements.
- Put me down!
- Put her upstairs in the office.
- We were expecting Emily.
- She's been kidnapped.
- They want a million dollars.
- I've a distinct sense of deja vu.
- She ain't crying wolf this time.
- What's your relationship to her?
I didn't do what she said I did on
the phone, if that's what you mean.
- She knows I'm leaving the country.
- Sir, you're not listening.
They want a million dollars
plus the 200,000 he stole from me.
They're stupid and dangerous.
That's a bad combination.
Perhaps, but I've already paid
a million dollars once this week -
- and I have no intention
of going to the well again.
It ain't about money.
It's about your daughter.
Isn't she worth a million dollars?
Mr. Perkins will return the money
he took from you, not a cent more.
Turn your back on me, but don't
turn your back on your daughter.
You have your money.
Now get out of here.
I've known this girl for two days.
Do I care more about her than you?
You son of a bitch! You should've
sold her when she was born for cash!
This is not the place for that.
Come on.
Scumbag!
- Come on.
- Get out of here, man.
- I have a plane to catch.
- Make sure she's okay first.
You make sure she's okay.
Put that thing in a paper cup
and let's go.
- Where is she?
- Show me the money.
- Watch out.
- How do I know you have the money?
You're going to have to trust me.
I've got to see she's all right.
There's a protocol with this.
I get the money. You stay here.
- Hi, how are you doing?
- Good.
- How's it going? Who are you?
- I'm with Vincent.
- He's my friend.
- He's my bodyguard.
That's a Colt Python
with a silencer up your ass.
How does it feel, Stick?
- Walk. You better tag along.
- Did I surprise you?
- May I ask you something?
- I don't know. Ask me.
How could you work
for a jerk-off like that?
What do you mean?
We go back a long way.
- You should've looked after her.
- I did that, too.
It was my job to make sure
she could take care of herself.
- She's got some ass!
- Your mother's got some ass.
- What's your name?
- Stick.
- Stick? Drive.
- All right.
I'm her uncle. Watch your mouth.
Gus?
- Hands up. Is he armed?
- Hey, your money. Where's the girl?
Give me that bag. As I was
trying to say, there's a protocol.
I check the money. Understand?
- That's a nice car.
- Stand still and shut up.
A million bucks.
I've waited a long time for this.
- There's no million dollars here!
- That's what I owe.
- Can't anybody count around here?
The 500 SL is a beauty, but do I
need that kind of horsepower?
- Who is this guy?
- Her uncle.
I trusted you.
He took 800,000.
He ripped us off, man!
- Step up with the girl.
- Did you rip us off, man?
Did you rip us off?
Don't be stupid.
- What did I say? What?
- Let's get back to business.
Did we disturb your shopping spree?
Do you like that car? Do you?
- That's not right.
- What?
- I have to see the girl's okay.
- We want the money first.
- Or do you want half the girl?
- You think we're fooling around?
Don't do it.
It looks like we're about done here.
Give me the gun.
I know what I'm going to do
with you, but what about you?
Your father's instructions were
not to let you embarrass him.
Are you going to kill me?
No, he's not.
What are you saying?
This is for him?
No, it's for me.
- Hope residence.
- Is my father there?
- What happened?
- We got a trace. 260 Terminal.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
She's had a hard time.
The kidnappers are tied up inside.
Come on.
- I guess you don't need me now.
- I can always use my friend.
I'm only a phone call away.
This is damage control. My lawyers
will prepare your statement.
- I'll tell them I started this.
- Why would you want to do that?
It's my mess. It's my responsibility
to sort things out.
- Well, it's good to have you home.
- I'm going to be moving out.
Emily!
As distasteful as it may be to you,
you're still my daughter.
And I'm still your father.
I know.
Not bad. How are you doing?
I've seen better days.
I'm hot. Sit down.
I need to decompress.
Red wine.
Is that for me?
1991... my favourite.
You want some?
How old are you?
Old enough.
Oh yeah... what a view!
I mean, that's a view.
What makes this a view?
You.
Come on. Come on.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org