Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Are you all right?
Forget him. Clear the room!
Clear.
It's empty.
Colonel Travis,
we've secured the building.
But. . . .
Collins took one, sir.
He's dead.
Clear to land. 2-Tango-Sierra.
Okay, so we're clear to land.
What else?
Eight-knot crosswind
from the right.
There's the interstate.
Runway 2-6.
And I got 2-6-0 on the D.G.
Undercarriage.
Coming out.
Good.
It's down and locked.
Anything else?
I don't know. What am I forgetting?
Nothing.
Just relax and fly the airplane.
FREDERICK FIELD, MARYLAND
Very nice touchdown, David.
Very smooth.
You've got this wired.
I don't know about that.
Stop here a second.
You are more than ready.
It's time to cut the umbilical cord.
-You sure about this?
-Come on.
I wouldn't let you go if I wasn't.
Quick, or I'll change my mind.
Solo time. Just remember:
Keep it simple. Stick and rudder.
Relax and fly the plane.
Take it easy.
God, why am I doing this?
Phone!
It's happened!
According to informed sources...
...El-Sayed Jaffa, perhaps the most
feared terrorist in the world...
... was abducted yesterday...
... while secretly attending
his daughter's wedding.
He was handed over
to U. S. authorities...
...arrested, and taken to a warship
in the Mediterranean.
Wire service intel reports.
None of the casualities answer
our description of Hassan.
No indication
he was even there.
He was there.
You called this one right.
Half the Middle East is backing Cyprus,
if only in principle.
We wanted him and now we got him.
And all the baggage that goes with him.
Until this is resolved,
Jaffa will remain in U. S. custody...
...an inglorious end to 15 years
of world terrorism.
Oceanic Flight 343, Athens
to Washington...
...now boarding at gate 13.
Welcome aboard.
Third seat on the right.
Is that who I think it is?
In the flesh.
Roger, Athens, cleared as filed.
2-8-0 after takeoff.
Would you like some champagne?
Here, let me help you.
There you go.
Stupid woman.
I'm sorry.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Have a pleasant flight.
Thank you for choosing Oceanic.
Flight attendants,
signal for departure.
Cabin crew, doors to automatic.
Here we go.
Excuse me, sir. May I help you?
Sir?
Excuse me, sir.
May I help you?
Listen to the sound of AI Tha'r!
This is your captain.
You may remove your seat belts.
Feel free to move about the cabin.
However, when you're seated,
do what we do:
Leave your seats belt on.
I see you've got the usual load.
Who is it this time?
It's my brother's twins.
It's their birthday next week.
Have a pleasant flight. Thank you.
And. . . .
Me?
Go on. Open it.
Oh, Jeannie.
It's for the ring.
I'm going in the pit. See you.
All right.
What was that?!
Maintain your course.
Reduce your airspeed
as indicated.
Careful.
I am a pilot.
American Embassy.
You've witnessed AI Tha 'r's conviction.
I have a message for the President.
I'm in control of flight 343.
Sit down!
Sit down! Sit! Sit!
Sit down! Nobody moves!
Nobody!
Quiet! Quiet!
Sit down!
Get up!
Take her.
Calm down!
It's over!
All right, it's over.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
You look like you could use this.
David Grant.
Michelle Thomas.
-You like hockey?
-Love it.
I've got two tickets--
Are you Dr. Grant?
You have an urgent phone call.
I'll be right back.
Come on!
Sit down! Sit! Sit!
Attention, everyone on board.
Listen carefully.
Remain in your seats
with your belts fastened.
Do as you're told. . .
. . .and there will be no need
for further violence.
Where's the passenger manifest?
I destroyed it.
You destroyed it?
To protect passengers?
Or someone else?
That was a very brave thing to do. . .
. . .and totally unnecessary.
Here's the data.
Sorry to spoil your evening.
That makes two of us.
It's him, no doubt.
One's a recording.
The one from the plane is live.
This doesn't make sense.
What the hell is he up to?
General Wood called.
Briefing at 6:00 in the Situation Room.
-Pentagon?
-Welcome to the big leagues.
White's running the show
in the President's absence.
-Got anything I can wear?
-T-shirt.
A jog bra and a pair of running shorts.
Thanks anyway.
Keep at it, guys.
This is a think tank.
They pay us to think.
By the way. . .
. . .who heads the anti-terrorist unit?
Colonel Austin Travis.
Special Forces Command.
You know him?
Jesus!
They said it was "come-as-you-are. "
-Excuse me.
-David Grant.
This was recorded from the plane...
. . .shortly after the bombing.
This is AI Tha 'r.
I have a message for the President.
The London bombing
indicates my resolve.
I am in control of Flight 343.
Its passengers
shall remain in my custody...
...until Abu Jaffa...
...is released from captivity.
Follow my instructions precisely.
No theater. No negotiation.
Jaffa will be taken
to Gatwick Airport...
... where a jet will land,
then leave with him.
On his release,
Flight 343 will go to Washington...
... where half the passengers
will be exchanged for fuel...
...and 50 million in gold bullion.
Jaffa must be in communication
with me by 6 a.m...
...or London will suffer
another punishment...
... that will make today's bombing
pale in comparison.
Mr. Grant.
This man. . .
. . .AI Tha'r, who is he?
Voice analysis confirms
it's Nagi Hassan. . .
. . .Jaffa's deputy director.
He's an extremist.
Take him at his word. He's not bluffing.
Thank you.
Any other comments?
It seems our posture must
be of containment.
Acquiesce to Nagi's demands?
I don't see any other choice.
London is demanding action.
I agree.
I hate the idea of conceding
to that bastard.
But if we get him on the ground,
we'll have options.
Travis' team will respond
once the plane is at Dulles.
It means shutting it down,
re-routing all traffic.
A full military control of the area.
Secretary White. . . .
Excuse me, gentlemen. . .
. . .I don't think we can allow
that plane to land. . .
. . .or even enter U.S. airspace.
What do you mean?
I don't think this is about hostages.
It's about one man planning
a major strike against the U.S.
You'd better explain yourself.
Our research leads me to believe. . .
. . .that due to his internal
political situation, Nagi Hassan. . .
. . .planned Jaffa's abduction.
Go on.
Six months ago,
a shipment of DZ-5 was hijacked. . .
. . .in transit to Germany.
We're certain
the Chechen Mafia was behind it.
But recent attempts to recover
the gas have failed.
Rumors surfaced that the DZ-5. . .
. . .was in the hands of Asmed Rhasjami.
This is the prick
who sent us on a wild goose chase.
. . .a supplier of arms and
explosives to Jaffa's group.
Mr. Grant. . .
. . .are you saying the nerve gas
is on board?
Yes, sir, I am.
In my opinion, Hassan plans to
use the DZ-5 and the plane as a weapon.
A sort of poor man's atomic bomb. . .
. . .to be detonated here,
over Washington.
How much DZ-5 might he have?
I can't be exact, sir.
But I can tell you this:
If this were DZ-5. . .
. . .that drop would be more than enough
to kill every man here.
The name he's using, "AI Tha'r" . . .
. . .in ancient Arabic means "revenge. "
Welcome aboard, Senator Mavros.
The press thinks you could be
the next President.
It's an honor to have you with us.
That plane will be here in 8 hours.
The President has two options:
Disregard Mr. Grant's theory. . .
. . .and let the plane proceed
to the U.S.
Or destroy it before it gets here. . .
. . .along with 406 passengers.
Even if we're right. . .
. . .how would we ever prove it?
Colonel, if you have an opinion,
let's hear it.
There is another possibility.
It's a Hail Mary pass, but. . . .
Colonel, tell him what you need.
There's a man named Dennis Cahill
who's an engineer for ARPA.
If we could get him on the line ASAP. . .
. . .he can tell you what I have in mind.
Remora was developed
for the space program...
...for low-orbit linkups
with the shuttle.
It has since been
modified by the Air Force...
... to study transferring
bomber crews at altitude...
...as well as other...
. . .contingencies.
We've had six hookups,
all successful.
This is a civilian airliner.
Mr. Cahill. . .
...do you mean Remora could work
with a 747?
This application was never
intended for a civilian airliner.
However, smooth-surface mating tests...
... were successful in a wind tunnel.
A wind tunnel.
I know you wrote the book on
assaulting hijacked aircraft.
But this is 5 miles above Earth.
Under the circumstances,
we don't have any other options.
It's your call.
We must be airborne in an hour,
six men. I'll need Mr. Cahill. . .
... to supervise the linkup.
Mr. Cahill...
... you and the Remora
be ready in an hour.
The press is in a feeding
frenzy about the hijacking.
Especially with Senator Mavros
on board.
Not a word of this operation
is to go beyond this room.
Anything you need, name it.
We'll need all the on-site intel
we can get.
I think Mr. Grant could
provide us with a great advantage.
And I'd just love to
have him come along.
You ready to take a plane ride. . .
. . .in the interest of national security?
Of course.
Check it out. It's the colonel.
Didn't have details on the op. . .
. . .so we brought everything,
even condoms!
Who's this? 007?
That's Mr. Grant, with lntelligence.
He'll travel with us partway.
Partway?
I'll explain on the bird.
Let's go!
So where's the 1 30?
Sergeant Baker. . .
. . .I reckon that's it.
You're joking, right?
Too much gear.
We won't get off the ground.
Break it down, boys.
Close-quarter weapons. . .
. . .com units, ordinance,
sleep agent. Dump the rest.
Andrews ground, Remora,
hangar three, taxi for takeoff.
It's all hooked up.
Oh, God.
Allison's been gone a long time.
They wouldn't leave her
there alone. Something's wrong.
Let's go through this.
Baker, set up the com link
with the plane and the Pentagon.
-Grant monitors.
-But I stay here?
That's correct.
The Remora will refuel in flight,
then trail the 747.
You'll be in video and
audio contact with us.
Your assessment
of Nagi's behavior is essential.
I'll do what I can.
Once we find the bad guys. . .
. . .we'll look for the DZ-5.
If we find it, you'll tap
into the oxygen supply. . .
. . .with the sleep agent.
Lights out. We take the bird.
Once we've taken control,
we'll divert.
Any problems, any questions?
Greenland's our best bet.
If the bomb has a short fuse. . .
. . .then my ass'll rain over Greenland?
I don't think so.
That's why I get the big bucks.
For what?
To save your ass.
That's what I want to hear.
The safehouse in Trieste. . .
. . .that was your intel.
The nerve gas was there, Colonel.
Operation was late.
If you say so.
I hope your averages improve.
If you don't believe me. . .
. . .why're you here?
Who else will do it?
You?
My men are hungry.
See to it.
The food's in the lower galley.
I must use the elevator.
All right.
What about the passengers?
They need something,
especially the children.
They may have beverages
and use the bathrooms.
You're responsible.
Anything suspicious will
bring about repercussions.
Understood?
Yes.
My God!
Satellite tracking indicates
our intercept here.
That'll give you 4 hours
to complete your mission.
Our target is the hatch near
the nose of the plane.
As soon as we lock on,
I'll raise the sleeve.
When it's pressurized,
I'll open the hatch of the 747.
When you're inside, I'll lock it.
Baker must go first.
The alarm on the hatch must be
neutralized. Tell him how.
I can't just do that.
It's not a B-52 with a docking collar.
It's a 747 without one.
Equalization process is delicate.
If the seal's not the proper vacuum. . .
. . .both planes could decompress.
Our mission's over.
This is what we'll do.
Baker follows right behind you.
When the hatch opens, get inside
so Baker can lock off the switch.
As soon as we're on board,
you go reseal the hatch.
I'll clip the circuit from the ladder.
I don't need to go on the plane.
That's how it's going to be.
I'm an engineer--
That's it!
Target sighted.
Initiating approach.
Climbing to flight level 3-8-5.
Activating Doppler imaging system.
Range: 1 ,000 meters and closing.
750.
500.
350.
We have heavy turbulence.
Only eight to ten seconds of this.
We're entering the slipstream.
In a moment it'll settle.
See that path?
That's the sweet spot!
We'll be on it in two seconds!
We're ready, Mr. Cahill.
Primary laser targeting.
Switch to master. And locked.
Switching to dorsal camera system.
Range to target:
Thirty meters.
Target point in sight.
Call the approach.
Steady.
Left 0.5.
Forward one.
Easy.
You're right on it.
You're on it.
Hold it right there.
Lock.
Prepare target for linkup.
Extending the sleeve.
-Activate.
-Roger.
Autopilot on.
We're engaged.
Primary tunnel pressurized and stable.
I'm going up.
Do it.
Seal looks good.
We got a stable vacuum.
I'm opening the outer hatch.
-What's that, a short?
-I don't know.
Move it.
Come on.
Move your ass.
Your turn.
A little bumpy.
What's that?
That's a warning light.
It's for an open hatch
in the avionics room.
That's impossible.
The plane is pressurized.
-Where is this room?
-Below.
It's under the first-class cabin.
Rat, you're next.
Doc, the bags.
Hope there's a good movie
on this flight.
Cappy.
Clear. Next.
Come on.
Where's the clip?
-You put it in?
-It was there!
You're on my shit list!
Hold up, we lost the clip.
Let's go! Let's go!
Got it!
Come on!
See, it went out.
It's a short.
Why aren't we climbing?
Come on, old man, move it.
What the hell?!
Wind shear!
Climb!
We are passing 330!
320!
What's going on?!
We have to break off now!
I can't hold the seal!
We got to pull him up.
What're you doing?
Let's move it!
Now! Now! Now!
He's unconscious!
Get above him!
Hold on.
Pull him up!
Get him out!
Move it!
Get above him!
We got him. Now get out of there.
Move.
Why is she so goddamn heavy?
Jesus, they're climbing!
I'm climbing with them.
Too much stress on the sleeve!
We're losing pressure.
The seals are going!
Listen to me!
Close the hatch now
or we'll lose both planes!
Come on!
Grab my hand!
I can't hold it! Close the hatch!
Lower the sleeve!
Listen to me! Close the hatch now
or we'll all die!
We're losing pressure!
We're not going to make it!
You are!
She's gone.
Castle Rock, Big Eye Six.
We lost contact with Hail Mary.
Big Eye Six, was delivery accomplished?
Can't say. Hail Mary was attempting
delivery when contact ended.
Did they make it onboard?
If they did, they'll establish
a link with us. Where's the fleet?
The carrier group's heading to
an intercept point in the Atlantic.
Have them go to alert.
I have to check the equipment
in the avionics room.
Show me this room.
There's a depression.
A deformity of C-7.
He's got a fractured vertebrae.
We have to immobilize him.
Can you move over here, please?
-Move!
-Sorry.
Hang on, Cappy, you old dog.
Buddy, you got some morphine here.
That'll help the pain.
Give me a break. You go down there.
Quiet!
Go.
It's a fried circuit.
It's an overload of some kind.
It happens.
Close it.
Everything okay?
Just a blown circuit.
Must've been the turbulence.
What'll we do?
Get me the Pentagon on sat-com.
The radio didn't make it.
We have no way to tell them
we're onboard. They'll think we're dead.
Shut up, Cahill.
He's right. As far as they know,
we went down with the plane.
The Pentagon is going to shoot us down.
We were their only option.
Listen to me.
We must negotiate.
Tell Hassan the Pentagon
knows his plan. . .
. . .and he'll never be allowed
to reach U.S. airspace.
-Calm down.
-I'm fine.
I know what I'm talking about.
We have to!
It's our only chance.
They've got to listen.
That won't stop them.
Get your hands off me!
You're not going anywhere!
I didn't sign up for this
G.I. Joe bullshit!
We don't need to do that.
He'll be all right.
Listen to me.
There is no negotiating
with Nagi Hassan. Understand?
If he knew we were here,
he'd kill us.
So let's calm down, everybody.
Just sit down and relax.
With no way to communicate, he's right.
They'll blow us out of the sky.
They don't know we're not onboard.
They'll wait until the last second,
hoping for a break.
We've got some time.
How much time
before we hit U.S. airspace?
Three hours, 50 minutes.
What's left of the gear?
We've lost the sat-com. . .
. . .scanners, sleep agent.
We've got half the weapons, probes,
mikes, bomb kit. That's it.
It's vital you find Hassan.
It all centers around him.
All right.
Mikes and probes first.
Hook up Grant to the com board.
See if he can locate Hassan.
Everything we need is here.
We locate their positions. . .
. . .blow the lights and go night optics.
We hit them hard while they're
still surprised. Let's go.
The bomb.
We don't know if there is one.
I'll take over the plane.
-That's what Travis would do.
-I'm not telling you what to do.
But if the DZ-5's on board,
there's a bomb attached. Find it.
Once this plane left, Hassan made
sure there was no turning back.
He's right.
It could be a pressure-switch timer;
if you land or change altitude. . .
. . .anything could set it off.
You must find it before they hit.
We'll look for it
while we're setting up.
Get the tools and bomb kits.
Let's get started.
Tell me what Hassan looks like.
I can't.
What do you mean?
You're the world's expert on him.
The only known photograph of him
was taken over 25 years ago.
Jesus.
But I'd recognize his voice.
I'd know him if I saw him.
I'm telling you, I saw them.
Americans.
Soldiers.
Baker, Station One.
First-class online.
Go ahead.
Okay, I've got one, first-class cabin.
Now another.
Skorpions on both of them.
Grant, do you copy?
I hear them.
Neither one is Hassan.
Four in the main cabin,
two in the galley.
Four with nine millimeter
skorpions, two AKM/FNC's.
Two more patrolling
the rear cabin.
Heavily armed.
Can you hear them in the galley?
Yeah. Yeah, I hear them.
None of them is our man.
This isn't working.
Meet me in the lower galley.
Put on Cappy's vest.
I'm on my way.
All right, clip the cable to your vest.
Put on your carabiner.
I'll winch you up.
Easy.
I got four probes and mikes down there.
It covers the main cabin.
If he's there,
you should find him.
Whatever you do. . .
. . .don't step on the panel
or you'll go through.
I'll try to remember that.
Hey, wait. Lose the shoes, pretty boy.
Hope the smell doesn't
give us away.
Go.
Senator, l--
Shut up!
Do you want to get us killed?
I think we're being presented with
an incredible opportunity here.
For what?
We always wanted to have
a war record for you.
Some edge with the media
that would put you over the top.
Remember the mileage
Jesse Jackson got. . .
. . .when he negotiated
that hostage release?
Yeah.
I'm at the last one.
He's not here.
Maybe he's in the cockpit.
Come on back.
Come on, I got you.
I got you, it's okay.
That's it.
Just keep tugging.
Good. You got it.
Get your arm in over there.
Maintain current course.
Shit.
Thanks.
Let's get down from here.
Stop.
What's going on?
I'm sorry, it fell. I was. . .
. . .getting coffee filters.
I don't understand.
How does threatening these people. . .
. . .have anything to do with your cause?
It's not your place to understand.
Just be patient.
It'll all be over very soon.
There's a change.
Maintain our course.
Excuse me.
I'm keeping you from your work.
Are you okay? What happened?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
And guess who I ran into?
Rat.
Forward baggage compartment.
Got something.
I'm on my way.
You wanted to talk to me.
I'm sure you're aware
the official U.S. policy is. . .
. . .no deals with terrorists.
Especially in hostage situations.
I can deal directly with the President.
If you allow me to conduct
the negotiation. . .
. . .I can guarantee your demands.
Money, media exposure,
safe passage to the Middle East.
I understand.
You want to be seen
as the savior of the hostages.
An image that won't hurt you
in the elections.
As powerful an image as you returning
to the Middle East, mission accomplished.
We are both men who truly understand. . .
. . .the importance of making
dramatic statements.
Rest assured, when the time comes,
I will call upon you.
Your theory was right.
Have a look.
You can forget Washington.
There's enough nerve agent here to
wipe out half the eastern seaboard.
Israeli intelligence has identified
the bomb-maker.
He's Jean-Paul Demou.
That's a recent photograph.
French-Algerian.
Former nuclear engineer
with the lraqis.
Lost his family in the Gulf War.
He's been with Jaffa's group since.
That's it?
That's it.
It's been over an hour
and no word from Travis.
We're running out of options.
There's still time.
Instruct the F-1 4's
to be ready to launch.
Issue the press release of
the President's decision to free Jaffa.
That bastard might be
our last avenue of hope.
We have no means
to communicate with him.
But he has arranged to contact you
as soon as you're airborne.
I can assure you, that plane
won't be allowed to reach the U.S.
If you can convince him. . .
. . .to divert the aircraft
to an isolated base. . .
. . .and release the passengers. . .
. . .he has the word of the President
of the United States. . .
. . .he and his men will be given
passage to any country.
I'll do everything I can. . .
. . .in the interests of peace.
Sorry, Cappy. We got a bad one here.
So. . .
. . .we know we've got DZ-5
in binary canisters. . .
. . .and 1 6 pounds of Semtex.
Let's take a look inside.
A computer trigger.
Microprocessor.
Dedicated drive. . .
. . .probably monitor a dozen sensors.
This ain't no pipe bomb
with a six-volt battery.
Take me closer.
Stop.
Take me in on that.
There.
What are you looking at?
That long, silver cylinder.
That's a barometric pressure switch.
Activated on takeoff, probably
set to airburst during landing. . .
. . .with an isolated trigger.
I tell you what. . .
. . .if I can. . .
. . .I mean. . .
. . .if you can disable the switch,
it'll buy you some time.
Then we got a chance.
We shut it down, take over
the plane, land it someplace safe.
Who gets to play
with the bomb?
What about Cahill?
He's a design engineer.
If he can build a computer. . .
. . .he can take one apart.
What do you think?
We're looking up the ass of a
dead dog, but it's worth a try.
But hurry, the morphine's kicking in.
Let's do it.
Get Cahill in here.
Overhead mid-cabin.
First class. I'll take the cockpit
and business class.
Use Channel B to Grant,
keep A open for assault.
I think you have problem.
I counted four in mid-cabin,
but there could be six.
Can you take them all?
I could take three or four,
but that's pushing it.
We need another gun.
What do you want me to do?
Jesus.
We're doing a simple
electronic bypass.
Ignore the rest of it.
Just ignore. . .
. . .the rest of it.
If you screw up, you'll never know it.
So. . .
. . .Iet's get to it.
Once more.
Push hard, up the ladder. . .
. . .Ieft in the companionway.
I'll surprise them.
That's it. You got it.
This isn't my thing.
With that, you can't miss.
Just aim for his chest and fire.
Whatever you do,
don't look into his eyes.
Then come back down the hall.
Okay, Cahill.
Meter reads 1 5 ohms.
That's good. That means
it's in parallel and isolated.
Let's complete the bypass.
Now take the red alligator clips
and set in the bypass.
Now take the red-handled dikes. . .
. . .and put the red wire on this side.
But don't touch anything else.
Ready, forward section.
Sit-rep.
Ready.
Baker up.
I'm ready.
Do it.
Tell them it's all theirs.
Thank God.
Cappy says the bomb is safe.
The dude's in my sights.
I'll blow the lights,
and we go on my signal.
Oh, Jesus!
Stop them.
Tell Rat to stop the attack!
Rat, stop the hit.
Cappy says to stop the attack.
Hold positions.
What's going on?
Someone ran a program test on the bomb.
Whoever it is. . .
. . .has an override switch
with his finger. . .
...on the damned trigger!
Can you override it?
I said, can you override it?
What's going on?
I think we might have lost Cappy.
Cappy's dead. I think Cappy's dead.
Calm down.
I'll be right there.
What happened?
Cappy's okay.
Just unconscious.
I am free and in flight.
The Americans wish me to tell you. . .
. . .they agree to all your demands.
You are victorious. Come home.
I rejoice in your freedom, Abu Jaffa.
Allah has blessed us.
A great destiny awaits us both.
You'll see I've achieved
a glorious victory on your behalf.
All of lslam will embrace you
as its chosen leader.
I am your flame.
The sword of Allah.
And with it I will strike deep
into the heart of the infidel.
Listen to me! They know!
They will destroy the plane!
Listen!
He cut him off.
Christ!
Jaffa's free.
Jaffa's free!
Anytime, guys. Anytime.
Tell Admiral Crosby to order
the F-1 4's to intercept the 747.
Make the plane divert.
Do it.
Call the President.
It's an executive decision now.
Now that Abu Jaffa's free,
shall I order the plane to Algeria?
Why?
-What's going on?
-Jaffa's been freed.
The second-in-command
is challenging Hassan.
He wants to know. . .
. . .why they're not diverting to Algeria. . .
. . .now that Jaffa's been released.
Allah has chosen for us a task
far greater than Jaffa's freedom.
We are the true soldiers of lslam.
Our destiny is to deliver
the vengence of Allah. . .
. . .into the belly of the infidel.
This has nothing to do with lslam.
It is not Allah's will.
You're blinded by hatred.
I'll have nothing to do with it.
Our mission was to free Abu Jaffa.
He is our leader, not you.
What happened?
He just killed one of his men.
Get back to your posts.
You son of a bitch!
What'd you get me into?
What did you get me into?
The others can't know about the bomb.
But somebody ran a test.
There must be a sleeper.
Triggerman. One of the passengers.
There're 400 passengers.
It could be anyone.
No way we'll find him.
We still have the element of surprise.
Let's hit them now,
forget the bomb and maybe get lucky.
Even if you kill them all,
the sleeper can destroy the plane.
But at least we'll save Washington.
We're out of time.
This is the best option we have.
Maybe not.
We still got an hour and 20 minutes.
Listen, we must give
that bomb another try.
You need Cappy for that.
-Maybe Cahill can.
-Forget it.
If he can neutralize it,
finding the sleeper won't matter.
And if he can't?
Then we must find the sleeper.
But I think. . .
. . .I know who it might be.
Can you hook up a probe. . .
. . .so I can see
into the cabin on this monitor?
We can't transmit between
the probe and the monitor.
Would a video camera work?
-You got one?
-No.
Shit.
Baggage.
We'll find one in baggage.
There are 400 faces up there.
You'll check each one?
Not without help.
Where's the weak link?
How do we pull
the teeth on this thing?
Come on, you're an engineer.
Go with your instincts.
Cappy said two power sources.
This is one.
I'm pretty sure this is the other.
If we had our own power supply. . .
. . .we could isolate
the bomb's power sources. . .
. . .Iike a heart bypass machine.
The bomb'll think it's online.
Along with the sleeper. With no power,
no detonation. Brilliant.
In theory.
That's all we've got.
Cahill, you're the man.
Go with your instincts.
I hope I'm right.
Whatever you do, don't cut that wire.
We found a camcorder in baggage.
We're ready to try this.
Be right there.
What? You can't leave now.
You've got Cappy.
What if he passes out again?
If things really get desperate. . .
. . .use your magic wand.
Okay. I got power.
Got the cable down the elevator shaft.
They won't see it.
Now for the hard part.
Let's try this.
Call light button.
I bypassed the buzzer.
Let's hope she sees it.
Wait. What makes you think
you can trust her?
When I was in the elevator. . .
. . .she saw me when Hassan walked in.
Wait!
She was cool, she covered me.
She'll do this.
I just hope you have better luck
with women than I do.
Come on, pick it up.
Pick it up.
I'm watching you on video.
Behind you. . .
...above the bulkhead.
There you go.
We met in the elevator.
American soldiers are onboard,
ready to take over the plane.
But there's a bomb,
and a passenger is in control of it.
We need your help to find him.
You're looking for a man
with an electronic device.
He's probably--
Sorry. I thought the phone rang.
Jesus.
Get on with it.
Come on, hang in there.
Hang in there.
She's had it. Forget it.
She's shaking.
She's not going to do it.
Wait a minute.
Lady's a player. She's with us.
Get in position.
Get upstairs. If she fingers somebody,
we must move fast.
They're here.
Oceanic Flight 343, approximately
120 miles from fail-safe line.
I've spoken to the President.
He concurs.
If we can't make them divert,
we have no other option.
The F-1 4's should intercept
in approximately 1 5 minutes.
We're not going to
shoot this plane down, are we?
Whatever evidence there is
will go to the bottom of the ocean.
The President would be finished.
He'd never recover.
Four hundred American lives.
We'd all be finished,
the whole administration.
Miss, may I have some water
for my medication?
My pleasure.
-Oh, dear.
-I'll get it for you.
What are you doing?
I was just getting her medication.
Can I go get her some water?
Go!
That's it. You got something, don't you?
Not long enough. One something.
-Did you get it?
-No, it was too quick.
She'll give it to us again. She must.
Here she comes.
-2, 1 --
-"K. "
21 -K!
Slap Flight, this is Lead.
Contact 0-3-9 at 125.
Come left 0- 1-5 for collision.
Three's contact and concur.
Angel's 44.
She found something.
21-K.
Midsection. . .
. . .starboard side.
Window seat.
Roger, I'm on my way.
I can't do it.
I can't. . .
. . .breathe.
Just relax.
I'm right here.
Close your eyes.
Why?
Just close your eyes.
Breathe deep.
Open your eyes and cut the blue wire.
It's a decoy!
It's a fake! The real works must
be down below under the plate.
What the hell happened?
What is going on?
I'm sorry.
It's just, the whole goddamn thing
could just blow up!
Speak English!
I screwed up.
We have to start over.
Grant, I'm there.
If it's Demou, he's about 50...
. . .olive skin, dark hair, balding.
It could be. I can't see him clearly.
I can't get a clean shot. Louie?
His back is to me.
But he fits the description.
Demou. It has to be.
Can you take him?
Not a chance.
There's passengers all around him.
-Where'd they come from?!
-I don't know.
Nagi, fighter planes!
Slap, Strike One Tally Ho.
Assuming position for escort.
Oceanic Flight 343, this is
flight leader, U. S. Navy aircraft.
You are approaching U. S. airspace.
You are to divert heading 0-2-0.
Fix vector for Thule Air Force Base.
Divert. Steer 0-2-0.
Squawk 7500 to acknowledge.
Oceanic Flight 343, this is
flight leader, U. S. Navy aircraft.
Son of a bitch.
Divert to Thule Air Force Base.
0-2-0.
Navy jets ordering us to divert.
-We must be close to fail-safe.
-We've had it.
They'll shoot us down.
No, no. We've got to
signal them somehow.
Got to be a way.
Come on, think. Think.
Vector 0-2-0. Thule Air Force Base.
Acknowledge.
Oceanic Flight 343.
On guard. Turn right.
Got to do something.
Look out your left window.
This is U. S. Navy flight lead.
Show me a sign you understand.
What the hell are they doing?
Getting ready to light us up.
-Take that left clip.
-I got it.
Okay. I got it.
That's 77.
Flight 343. It is imperative
that you acknowledge.
Divert now. Steer 0-2-0.
This is U. S. Navy flight lead.
We must respond.
You say nothing.
Stay on course.
Now.
It looks clear.
We need something non-metallic
to slip between those points.
I think we've got it licked,
but we need a few more minutes.
Great. Stay at it.
All right, listen. Pin 77's over here.
Slap Flight, this is Lead.
I'm going to pull out in front.
What are we missing?
I'm thinking the same thing.
The sphere is cold.
In my green bag,
there's a can of compressed air.
Give it a shot.
Shit.
In my kit, infrared goggles.
Jesus Christ.
We're finished.
One more time. Oceanic Flight 343.
Come right 0-2-0. Thule Air Force Base.
Give me Washington.
You must follow me.
Captain, please acknowledge.
This is AI Tha 'r.
Why are we being threatened?
I said my terms are absolute.
The hostages will be released...
... when we land in Washington.
No compromises.
This is Secretary of Defense
Charles White.
You must listen to me.
We know--
You know nothing!
Tell your President. . .
...he will comply or suffer
the blood of Americans on board.
It's time, Senator.
Hello? Are you there?
Can you hear me?
Hello, can you hear me?
This is Senator Mavros.
I'd like to speak to the President.
Senator, the President
is out of the country.
I'm speaking on his behalf.
I don't care.
I want to speak to him now.
Senator, I'm in charge
of the crisis team.
They have a gun to my head.
Please, just do what they want!
Please!
What was that?
What happened?
Jesus Christ.
This is the pilot.
They killed the senator.
Do what they ask.
He killed Mavros.
Whatever you're going to do,
do it now.
Listen to me.
The plane will continue on as planned.
Any further threats will result in
a passenger being killed every minute.
They're only 25 miles
to the fail-safe line.
We have to end this now.
Nav. Com. flash on the CRN-1 1 5.
National Command Authority.
We're ordered to destroy the target.
You're joking.
I confirmed it twice. It's for real.
Slap Two, Three and Four,
take high cover.
Follow on a one-mile trail.
Sparrow select.
Strike Slap One, stand by
for Fox One from Lead.
I'm going master arm on.
Do it.
Slap Flight, this is Lead.
We have full lock on the heavy.
Negative!
Go cold on the sparrow!
The taillights are flashing.
Hope I'm not going too fast.
Nobody uses Morse code now.
Except navy pilots.
Keep sending it.
Is that what I think?
You're damn right!
This is Slap One.
We have visual communication
from the target.
Seems to be Morse code coming
from the nav lights.
According to my supplement...
... the message appears
to be, " Hail Mary. . .
. . .Alpha One. . .
. . . 1 0 minutes. "
Message repeats.
Alpha One's the attack code.
You mean they made it?
They're onboard?
They'll try to take her.
It's too late.
They've crossed the line.
If they're on board,
we'll give them another 1 0 minutes.
Admiral Lewis.
Flight 343...
. . .this is Navy flight leader.
Alpha One, you have 10 minutes
to U. S. airspace.
Repeat. Alpha One...
... 10 minutes to U. S. airspace.
You have permission to land
at Dulles Airport. Good luck, sir.
They got it!
Really?
I should take back every
squid-hating thing I ever said.
Monitor the radio.
And no contact.
We got a break.
We have 10 minutes.
We'll take the sleeper first.
It must be by surprise.
Cappy's almost there on the bomb.
Wait a few minutes.
We're out of time.
We go, blow out the lights,
take our chances.
Five minutes, Rat.
They'll have the bomb diffused by then.
Now give it 5 minutes!
Give him 5 minutes.
I agree.
All right, Grant. . .
. . .5 minutes.
Baker, get into position.
Louie, stand by.
We have 5 minutes.
How you doing?
Where were you?
The sphere is filled
with photoelectric beams.
We need more than 5 minutes.
Grant, come in!
Just do the best you can.
Pick it up.
Jan...
. . .you've been fantastic.
But I need your help one more time.
Lower galley.
Turn around.
Get in the elevator right now. Go.
They'll start descending soon.
I know, Jack.
Radar confirmation. Oceanic Flight 343
now at 25-mile limit.
Keep going.
I'll blow the lights.
Two more minutes and then we go.
Grant, how are you?
Just keep walking.
It's Grant.
He's down below in mid-cabin.
When I push you down. . .
. . .hit the floor and stay down.
He's going for the sleeper!
That son of a bitch.
We go on your signal.
Go!
Something's wrong.
It's not him.
Everybody down!
Behind you!
He's got Demou! Blow the lights!
The sleeper!
The straw! The straw!
I can't hold it!
Come in, Dulles.
Dulles, this is Oceanic 343 heavy. . .
...requesting emergency landing.
We are low on fuel.
We have structural damage...
...but we are stable and in control.
This is Dulles.
You are cleared to land.
1-L north. Crash crew standing by.
Thank God.
They're in control.
The bomb! What about the bomb?!
Listen to this.
It's done!
Jesus!
You got anything else for us?
Got to tell Washington.
You okay?
It's over.
Over?
It's not over.
It's over.
Who are you?
No one.
You're very clever.
But you're too late.
You've stopped nothing!
Dulles lnternational. . .
. . .this is Flight 343.
The airplane is secure, but the
pilots are dead. Request help.
Flight 343, you're breaking up.
We don 't read you. You're cleared
to land on runway 1-L north.
I need help. I need instruction.
There's a bomb
that could detonate on impact.
You're breaking up.
They're not receiving.
Shit!
Get ahold of it now.
Get ahold of this plane.
It's all right.
It'll be okay.
All right, stick and rudder.
Stick and rudder. It's an airplane.
Straight and level. Hold it.
Oh, my God.
Are you a pilot?
You got to help me.
I've had a few lessons,
but I've never really soloed.
We're probably lined up for landing.
There it is! There's the airport.
There, see it?
Okay, I got it. I got it.
All right.
Pilot's Operating Handbook.
That's what I need. Over there.
I don't see it.
What's it look like?
It'll say, "Flight Manual. "
Back there! ln the back.
Okay, I got it, I got it.
Flight manual.
-What do I look for?
-The normal procedures.
Landing approach speeds.
Okay, here it is. I got it.
What's it say?
Final approach speeds. . .
" . . .over 600,000 pounds, 1 50 knots. . .
. . .under 400,000 pounds, 1 20 knots. "
Split it. 1 40 knots.
We're doing 220 knots.
Reduce power.
Nose down.
1 70 knots.
It's getting loose.
I'm losing control of the airplane.
What's wrong?
Flaps!
How much flaps can I put on?
Flaps, flaps, flaps. 1 70 knots--
any amount of flaps you want.
Goddamn it!
2, 3, 4.
There. 1 60.
There we go. 1 50.
1 40.
1 30.
What the hell? I'm going to stall!
I'm stalling!
Power!
Power up!
1 40.
There we go.
Wait a minute.
Landing gear!
Okay, we're going to land.
Oh, man. We're long.
What the hell?
He's way too high.
Come on!
I missed! I missed it!
I missed it. I'm over.
Power up.
Won't climb.
Come on, baby. Come on.
Gear up!
Now what do I do?
Turn around for another approach.
I can't turn it around.
Yes, you can!
No, wait. Wait a minute.
Let me think.
Hold it.
That's the interstate.
There's the ballpark.
Frederick Field must be ahead.
I know where I am!
I can do this. All right.
Line it up. . .
. . .for 2-6.
There it is. There it is!
Reduce power.
Here we go.
Power back.
Shit. Landing gear. . .
. . .down.
Airspeed. . .
. . . 1 40 knots.
Think.
What am I forgetting?
Who cares?
Just fly the plane!
You're right.
All right, I can do this.
"Fly the plane. "
I can do this.
Jesus, I'm down!
Shit. Hold on!
Things almost land themselves,
don't they?
I don't know how you did it,
but you did it.
No, you did it.
What do you mean?
What is this?
A little memento for you.
I'll tell you about it another time.
Right now. . .
. . .I need a drink. A big drink.
Marshal?
How you doing?
Getting better by the minute.
Where'd these commandos come from?
Good question.
You'll be okay.
Hold it.
Hey, guys.
It's Jean.
Hi.
What?
You called me Jan on the plane.
My name is Jean.
Who are you?
Dr. Grant. . .
. . .Agent Perry, FBl.
You're wanted at the Pentagon.
Sorry I asked.
Jean, wait!
Can I buy you some coffee?
As long as you're not flying.
No problem.
So, Jean, tell me something. . . .
Do you like hockey?
Hockey?
No, I only like baseball.
Subtitled by:
GELULA & CO., INC.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org