Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Blue, 18.
Set. Hit. Hit.
Zach. Zach. Crossbuck 30.
Crossbuck 30.
Crossbuck 30. Crossbuck 30.
- Ready?
- Ready.
The Eagles will have to go for it
on fourth down
with just 42 seconds left in the game
and no timeouts.
Coach Taylor can get his first winning
season for the Shiloh Christian Academy
if they can pull this play off.
Move it, team! Set, hit!
Zach Avery pitches back to Jacob Hall.
Jeremy Johnson's going down the field.
- Here come the Tigers.
- Throw it, Jacob!
Jacob's gonna try to tuck it and run,
and he's taken down at the 40-yard line,
stopped by Lewis Slaughter.
Jeremy Johnson was wide open.
If he'd had a few seconds more, this
game might have had a different outcome.
As it is, the Tigers will take over now
and will no doubt run out the clock,
ending Coach Grant Taylor's bid for
his first winning season in six years.
Now he'll have to wait until next season
for that all-elusive winning record.
That's if they let him
come back next year.
- Hi.
- Get 'em, Claire.
Hey, Grant. Come on, y'all.
Quit talking. Let's go, let's go. Hurry.
What?
What? You gotta be kidding me.
- This had better be a joke.
- No.
Mandy said he came in this morning,
got his papers.
A player can't just transfer to another
school. He's gotta change his address.
He did. He's moving in with his dad.
I can't believe that. This is
the third time this has happened.
Spend three years pouring into 'em
and when they get to their senior year,
they transfer to a rival school.
Why?
Well, 'cause at the end of the season,
nobody wants to be on TV
going, "We're number six, baby.
We're number six."
Well, you asked.
Just had to go there, didn't you?
- Did Darren switch to Tucker?
- We'll talk about it in a minute.
- So it's true?
Huddle up.
Coach, is it true
that Darren transferred to Tucker?
I got word this morning
that Darren did transfer to Tucker.
- There goes the season.
- The season will be whatever we make it.
Who's gonna take his place?
He scored a third of our points.
You let me worry about that.
We're not starting as if it's doomsday.
- Nobody's irreplaceable.
- Darren is.
Darren is not. There's more
to a good football team than a running back.
If anything, this ought to push you
to take up the slack.
Stop worrying about Darren.
Start your drills.
- We got a game to play this Friday night.
- Let's go, Shiloh. Come on. Let's go.
Why'd you park all the way out there?
Had to. It died again.
Why don't we get a new battery?
I'll get Brady to help me tomorrow.
I don't wanna think about it now.
- Do you want me to take a look at it for you?
- Stop it.
Oh, sweetheart...
I don't know what that smell is.
I've scrubbed everything I can.
- It's terrible.
- I know it is, but what else can I do?
I don't know where it's coming from.
This day stunk. Why shouldn't my house?
- What do you mean?
- Darren transferred to Tucker.
What? He did not.
Yep. Came by and got his papers,
didn't even say goodbye.
- Why?
- Why do you think?
Didn't see a chance of winning
at Shiloh.
But it ain't like Tucker's
gonna guarantee him a scholarship.
- I bet the boys are frustrated.
- More than you know.
I meant to throw that away.
Did you think you were pregnant?
I don't know. I just wanna be pregnant
so bad that my mind plays tricks on me.
You know, it's been four years
since we started trying.
Would you be opposed
to me going to see a specialist?
No.
I'd just like to know what she says.
OK.
I thought we were having
spaghetti tonight.
Stove's not working.
You are kidding me.
So we got a leak in the back room,
the dryer only works half the time,
the car's dying on us
and now the stove's broken.
That's about right.
No wonder I'm losing my hair.
I love you.
And now your Georgia Sports Break
with Alicia Houston.
The Richland Giants start football practice
as the new school year gets under way.
The team will be defending a three-year
GISA state championship run.
Now they prepare to fight for a fourth.
I'm here with head coach Bobby Lee Duke
of the Giants.
How does this year look for the team?
Alice, we've grown real fond
of the state title.
And we don't see any reason
to give it up this year.
I've got most of my starters coming back
and I've got a strong bench.
So I've only got one thing to say:
Get off the tracks,
'cause the freight train's coming.
I hope that's not a sign of the way
the rest of the season's gonna go, Coach.
- Why did he have to say that?
- Just let it go.
I hate this car.
Let's find somebody with jumper cables
and let's go home.
It's bad enough you lose your first game.
Now I can't even start my own car.
This happens to everybody.
Don't be embarrassed about it.
- Grant, I wasn't that embarrassed.
- Then why did you hide?
Why does this house
have to stink so bad?
You'll get used to it
after a couple of hours.
Honey, we gotta do something
about the car.
The only thing it does faithfully for us
is break down.
That's about right.
Would it not be better
just to get a small new car?
- You know we can't afford that.
- How do other people do it?
Other people make
more than 24,000 a year.
You make 6,000. That takes us to 30.
Enough to help us
with repairs occasionally,
not with a new car payment.
Besides, there's other bills
we don't normally have to pay.
- Like what?
- Like my doctor bill.
You saw her today?
- What did she say?
- She said that I'm fine.
My numbers are normal and she saw
nothing that gave her concern.
- That's good.
- It doesn't mean the problem is with you.
- What else could it mean?
- We just may not have given it enough time.
Four years?
Are you still hoping we'll have a baby?
- You know I am.
- Me too.
I catch myself thinking about it
more and more.
Don't you wanna know
if something's preventing it?
Are you afraid of getting checked out?
Yes.
Grant, I'm still clinging to a hope
that one day we'll have children.
I imagine 'em running in this house.
I hear 'em playing in the backyard
or running to our bed in a thunderstorm.
And I think about reading 'em stories
and teaching 'em songs.
And I just keep thinking
how can I miss someone so much
that I have never met?
I'll go.
Stanley.
Stanley, do you wanna tell me
what you're doing on the top of my desk?
No.
Do you have any idea
how you got on top of my desk?
No.
I suggest you get down immediately.
You two can tell Coach Taylor
that you're late for practice today
because you've been
sitting in detention.
Come on. That was some serious humor.
I'll get serious about your humor
when you get serious about your studies.
55?
Well, if you wanna announce your grade
to the entire class, you go right ahead.
57.
So basically we got
the toughest schedule we ever had
and less talent than we ever had.
At least we got Dewey County on Friday
night. That'll be a pretty easy win.
- I'm concerned it might be our only win.
- We'll pull three or four out.
That'll give us another average season.
I'm so sick of average seasons.
- I gotta go.
- Where are you going?
- Got a doctor's appointment.
- For what?
- I have a doctor's appointment.
Leave the man alone.
He don't have to tell you.
So what's wrong with you, man?
I'll be back in a couple of hours.
Now look what you did.
You done made him mad.
Me? You're the one that made him mad.
No, not me.
Besides, I know where he's going.
- Where?
- He's going to the hair doctor.
The man is going bald. You hadn't
noticed that underdeveloped region?
You're one to talk, Slick.
See, when a black man goes bald,
he still looks good.
Look at Michael Jordan,
George Foreman, Samuel L. Jackson.
Classy-looking brothers.
Who you got? Kojak?
Yeah, Coach gonna get him some plugs.
- Grant would not get plugs.
- Don't laugh. You next.
Your soccer skills
get better every year, son.
It doesn't matter. Shiloh doesn't have
a soccer team. They play football.
So? Why not kick for the football team?
They've already got a good kicker.
I'm sure they wouldn't mind
having two.
Dad, I'm too small. I really
just don't feel like getting killed.
Are you saying you're not interested
or you'd like to try out
but you're afraid?
What if I don't even make the team?
Well, you're already not on the team.
You can't get any more not on the team
than you are right now.
- OK, Dad.
- David, you can't be afraid of failure.
Everyone fails at some point.
So you think I should try out
for the football team?
Well, if you're waiting around
for soccer, it ain't gonna happen.
- Coach Owens, have you got a minute?
- Yeah.
Look, some of the men have been talking.
We wanna see this school succeed
with our football program.
I know you feel the same way, too.
But, frankly, we don't ever see that
happening while Coach Taylor is here.
You know we're in a rebuilding season.
Look, I know he's a fine man and all,
but he's had six years here
and nothing significant
to even show for it.
I honestly believe
you would make a better head coach.
Some of us have requested
a meeting with Mr. Ryker.
If you would just support us, I really
believe this could go a lot easier.
Mr. Pervis, I don't know.
Look, it's not like
we're trying to hurt the guy.
What we're doing
is for the benefit of the school.
You just think about it.
Good hustle, Casey.
- What was that about?
- What?
- Alvin Pervis.
- We were just talking.
Everything all right?
- Yeah.
- Mr. Taylor.
Yes.
I'm Larry Childers.
This is my son David. He's a junior.
- We're new to the school.
- Good to meet you. What can I do for you?
I just wanted to introduce myself to you
and David wanted to try out for the team.
- You a football player?
- I've always played soccer.
- I figured I could try out as a kicker.
- I've got a pretty good kicker,
but I don't mind letting you try out.
Jonathan, come here.
This is Jonathan. He holds
for our main kicker, Joshua Webster.
Jonathan, this is David Childers.
He wants to try out as a kicker.
- Why don't you two go and try a few kicks?
- All right, sure.
Thank you, sir. I'll just hang around
till practice is over.
No problem. Good to meet you.
Y'all just move here?
Yeah, from Athens. My dad got a job
teaching at the college.
That's cool.
I'm used to kicking soccer balls,
but I thought I could at least try out.
Josh is a pretty good kicker,
but he's also a receiver.
I think he likes that
better than kicking. Here you go.
I'm sorry.
- Sorry about that.
- It's all right.
- Hey, watch it.
- Sorry.
Matt.
- Let's go.
- I'm going with Brock for a while.
- Not tonight. You're coming home.
- Why?
- Don't argue with me. Let's go.
- No, Dad. I'll be home later.
Matt.
That old man still come every week
to pray in the hallway?
Mr. Bridges. Prays for the students
as he passes their locker.
- How long has he been doing that?
- Praying for revival since before I got here.
Lord knows we need it. Apathy in the
school's as bad as our football record.
That reminds me. I think you should go ahead
and let David Childers on the team.
- You see something there?
- He's just used to playing soccer.
He ain't that strong,
but he shows promise.
All right. I'll give him a shot.
One, two, hit!
What are you doing?
Let's stay in the game!
No! No!
Will someone tell me
how we lost to Dewey County 21 to 7?
21 to 7!
Dewey County hasn't beaten Shiloh
since you were in kindergarten!
I don't know what you call that junk
out there, but it sure wasn't football.
Nine dropped passes,
four fumbles, three interceptions.
Their defense
scored most of their points!
You gave the game away!
You can't win football games
if you don't play together as a team.
You can't win when you're more concerned
about what you're doing afterwards!
And you can't learn the plays when you miss
practice 'cause you're sittin' in detention.
I'm sick of the apathy on this team.
If we're not here to win football games,
then why are we here?
So, do you agree with him?
I don't know. I guess.
Only a few guys on the team
really seem to care.
So are you ready to play in the game?
I don't know why they would use me
when they've got Joshua Webster.
He can kick a 45-yard field goal.
I bet you could too.
Dad, I can barely kick
a 35-yard field goal.
At the end of the game,
kind of glad I didn't play.
That way, I can't mess up.
- That's fear, son.
- I just don't wanna embarrass the team.
David, I've asked God
since you were a baby
that he would show how strong he is
in your life
and that through you
people would see how good he is.
Then why would he make me
so small and weak?
To show how mighty he is.
Why don't we get washed up for dinner?
We can finish this later.
All right.
Dad.
OK. I'm OK.
- What were you doing?
- You missed a spot up there.
Thought I could get it for you.
I guess I got a little too ambitious.
I was just trying to take a swing at it.
So, what does that mean?
Is there a procedure?
What are my options?
Grant, first you need you realize
this is a fairly common problem for men.
Thousands of couples are unable
to have children. You do have options.
Although there's only
a 10% chance of success,
many couples have tried
in vitro fertilization.
- We can't afford that.
- The other option is to adopt a child.
But it's about as expensive either way.
If you're interested, I'll put you
in touch with the local agency.
I realize this is difficult
for you to hear,
but you and your wife can
make the best decision
now that you know where you are.
Sorry. I didn't realize
anybody was still here.
- Hey, Steve.
- Putting in late hours tonight?
Yeah, I guess so.
I can lock up. You can take off.
All right. Thanks, Coach.
It's about the boys.
I'm not asking you to throw him out.
If Shiloh can invest in a winning coach,
we don't need to settle for second best.
You can let him go
with as much class as you want to.
- Alvin, he's a good man.
- I'm not saying he's not a good man.
I'm saying he's not a good coach.
Come on, Dan. Just look at the facts.
His record speaks for itself.
- We need new leadership.
- I still think he deserves more time.
He's had six years. If he was capable
of winning, he'd have done it by now.
Grant Taylor is not capable of winning.
He doesn't have it in him.
That's the whole point.
I'm just saying I want my son to have
the best football program possible.
My son's got a chance
for a football scholarship
if he's taught by the right coach.
Matt's gonna be a senior next year.
I don't wanna see him
lose this opportunity.
Brady, you're awfully quiet.
What's your take on this?
Honestly, I don't know.
Sometimes I think Grant could do a better job
of building this football program.
But then other times I think he's doing
just as good as anyone else would.
You could do better.
- What we need is a change.
- Now.
We're losing booster support,
game attendance is down,
and from the looks of it
we've already lost this season.
Dan, we've got a weak program
because we've got a weak coach.
He's dead weight.
We need to cut him loose.
Have you been at school all this time?
Yes.
I tried to call you an hour ago.
Is everything all right?
Grant, talk to me.
I don't know where to start.
What's going on?
I was trying to lock up for Steve
and I overheard Dan
meeting with some fathers.
They didn't know I was there.
Brooke, they're pushing him
to get rid of me.
Neil Prater, Alvin Pervis, Luke Rae.
They said I wasn't capable of winning,
called me dead weight.
They can't make Dan fire you.
You've still got support.
You just go get JT and Brady
and see him tomorrow.
Brady was there.
They've just lost confidence in me.
I was so sure I could turn this program
around and I've just sunk it lower.
Brooke, I've tried so hard.
Why can't I win?
You can win.
Stop beating yourself up, Grant.
Brooke, I can't provide you
with a decent home.
I can't provide you with a decent car.
I'm a failing coach
with a losing record.
And I can't give you
the children you want.
What?
It's me.
Like everything else is me.
We can't have our own children
because of me.
What's God doing?
I mean, why is it so hard?
It's OK, Grant.
It's OK.
"I love you, O Lord, my strength."
"The Lord is my rock and my fortress,
my deliverer,
my God in whom I trust,
my shield and the horn of my salvation,
my stronghold."
"I will call upon the Lord
who is worthy to be praised."
"So shall I be saved from my enemies."
Lord Jesus, would you help me?
I need you.
Lord, I feel like
there's giants of fear and failure
just staring down at me
waiting to crush me.
And I don't know how to beat 'em, Lord.
I'm tired of being afraid.
Lord, if you want me
to do something else, show me.
If you don't want me to have children,
so be it.
But you're my guide.
You're on the throne.
You can have
my hopes and my dreams.
Lord, give me something.
Show me something.
If the Lord never gives us children,
will you still love him?
Field-goal unit.
Hold on, Joshua. I wanna give David
a shot at this one. David, come here.
This is your field goal.
Put us on the board.
Hit.
It's all right, man. It's hard.
You'll get it next time.
Dad, I don't even know
why they let me on the team.
Did you do your best, son?
I knew I was gonna miss it
before I kicked it.
Your actions will always
follow your beliefs, David.
Dad, I can't even kick it straight.
And I can't walk. Should I just
stay home and pout about it?
If you accept defeat, David,
then that's what you'll get.
Well, Brady, another fine example
of Grant Taylor's
wonderful coaching abilities.
Look, the kids don't deserve it.
The fans don't deserve it.
When you gonna get
a bellyful of this guy?
What's it gonna take?
You got a chance, man.
You got a chance to step in
and take over this program
and carry it up for a while.
When are you gonna get
sick and tired of it?
You got an opportunity here.
This program's going in the tank.
Ryker's gotta...
Grant, he came to me.
You're not doing anybody any favors
sitting on the fence.
You determine which side
you wanna be on and stay on it.
Mr. Bridges.
Revelation Chapter 3 says:
"We serve a God
that opens doors that no one can shut,
and he shuts doors
that no one can open."
"He says: 'Behold, I have placed before
you an open door that no one can shut.
'I know you have a little strength,
yet you have kept my word
and have not denied my name."'
Coach Taylor,
the Lord is not through with you yet.
You still have an open door here,
and until the Lord moves you, you're
to bloom right where you're planted.
I just felt led
to come and tell you that today.
Mr. Bridges.
Do you believe
God told you to come tell me that?
I do.
I admit to you I have been struggling.
But I've also been praying.
I just don't see him at work here.
Grant, I heard a story about two farmers
who desperately needed rain.
And both of them prayed for rain,
but only one of them went out
and prepared his fields to receive it.
Which one do you think trusted God
to send the rain?
The one who prepared his fields for it.
Which one are you?
God will send the rain when he's ready.
You need to prepare your field
to receive it.
So this is your new team philosophy?
What do you think?
I think this applies to all of life,
not just football.
Well, that's my point.
10 bucks to the person who can tell me who
won the state championship a decade ago.
- Walker Jennings.
- No.
- North Metro.
- Stop guessing.
You know it or you don't.
- How about five years ago?
- Richland?
That was three years ago.
You can't remember, can you?
Leads me to ask a couple of questions.
- What's the purpose of this team?
- Win ball games.
- Then what?
- We get a trophy. And people talk about us.
Maybe, for a while.
- Then what?
- I don't know.
Get a scholarship, play for college
and coach Little League.
What are you getting at?
You think we're just wasting our time?
If our main goal is to win games,
then yes.
- You don't want us to win games?
- No.
Not if that's our main goal.
Winning football games
is too small a thing to live for.
And I love football as much as anybody.
But even championship trophies will
one day collect dust and be forgotten.
It's just that so far
all this has been about us,
how we can look good,
how we can get the glory.
The more I read this book,
the more I realize life's not about us.
We're not here just to get glory,
make money and die.
The Bible says
that God put us here for him,
to honor him.
Jesus said the most important thing
you could do with your life
is to love God with everything you are
and love others as yourself.
So if we win every game
and we miss that, we've done nothing.
Football then means nothing.
So I'm here to present you
a new team philosophy.
I think that football is just
one of the tools we use to honor God.
So you think God
does care about football?
I think he cares about your faith.
He cares about where your heart is.
If you can live your faith on the football field,
then, yes, God cares
'cause he cares about you.
He sent his son Jesus to die for us
so we could live for him.
That's why we're here.
But, see,
it's not just on the football field.
We've gotta honor him
in our relationships,
in our respect for authority,
in the classroom,
and when you're at home alone
surfing the internet.
I want God to bless this team so much,
people talk about what he did.
But it means we gotta give him our best
in every area.
And if we win, we praise him.
And if we lose, we praise him.
Either way, we honor him
with our actions and our attitudes.
So I'm asking you,
what are you living for?
I've resolved to give God
everything I've got,
then I'll leave the results up to him.
I wanna know if you'll join me.
Your attitude's like the aroma
of your heart.
If your attitude stinks,
it means your heart's not right.
He sure is preachy today.
What?
- How's your attitude, Brock?
- It's fine.
Then you'll be OK
with the death crawl, right?
All right, everybody on the goal line.
Get your partner. Let's go.
All right, let's go. Show me something.
10 yards. Move it. Let's go.
Matt, let's go. Let's go, Jonathan.
Show me something. 10 yards.
Show me some power. No knees.
Keep your knees off the ground.
Show me something. Here we go.
10 yards. Show me some muscle.
Show me some power.
Give me some heart. Let's go.
Very good, boys. Very good.
Let's run it back.
- Man, that's not even funny, dude.
- Yeah, it is.
So, Coach,
how strong is Westview this year?
A lot stronger than we are.
You already written Friday night down
as a loss, Brock?
Well, not if I knew we could beat 'em.
Come here, Brock. You too, Jeremy.
- What? Am I in trouble now?
- Not yet.
I wanna see you do the death crawl again
except I wanna see your absolute best.
What? You want me to go the 30?
- I think you can go the 50.
- The 50?
I can go the 50 if nobody's on my back.
You can do it with Jeremy on your back,
but promise you're gonna do your best.
- All right.
- Your best.
- OK.
- You're gonna give me your best?
- I'm gonna give you my best.
- All right, one more thing.
- I want you to do it blindfolded.
- Why?
I don't want you giving up at a certain
point when you can go further. Get down.
Jeremy, get on his back.
Now, get a good tight hold, Jeremy.
All right. Let's go, Brock.
Keep your knees off the ground.
Just your hands and feet.
A little bit left. A little bit left.
There you go. Show me good effort.
Thataway, Brock. You keep coming.
- There you go.
- Come on, Brock.
- Come on.
- It's a good start. Little bit left.
Little bit left. There you go, Brock.
Good strength.
You gotta be kidding me.
- That's it, Brock. That's it.
- Am I at the 20 yet?
Forget the 20. You give me your best.
You keep going. That's it.
Don't stop.
You got more in you than that.
I ain't done. I'm resting a second.
You gotta keep moving. Let's go.
Don't quit till you got nothing left.
There you go. Keep moving. Keep moving.
Keep moving.
That's it. You keep driving.
Keep your knees off the ground.
Keep driving it. Your very best.
Your very best. Keep moving, Brock.
That's it. That's it. That's it.
Keep going.
Don't quit on me. Keep going.
Keep driving it. Keep your knees
off the ground. That's it.
Your very best.
Don't quit on me. Your very best.
Keep driving. Keep driving.
There you go. There you go.
That's it. You keep driving.
Keep your knees off the ground.
Don't quit till you got nothing left.
Keep moving, Brock.
That's it. That's it. That's it.
Keep going. I want everything you got.
Come on, keep going.
- It hurts.
- Don't quit on me. Your very best.
Keep driving. Keep driving.
There you go. There you go.
- He's heavy.
- I know.
- I'm about out of strength.
- Then find more strength.
Don't you give up on me, Brock.
You keep going, you hear me?
You're doing good. You keep going.
Do not quit on me. You keep going.
- It hurts.
- I know it hurts. You keep going.
It's all heart from here. 30 more steps.
You keep going, Brock. Come on.
- Keep going.
- It burns.
- Let it burn.
- My arms are burning.
It's all heart.
You keep going, Brock. Come on.
Come on. Keep going.
You promised me your best. Your best.
- Don't stop. Keep going.
- It's too hard.
It's not too hard.
You keep going. Come on, Brock.
Give me more. Give me more. Keep going.
20 more steps. 20 more.
Keep going, Brock.
Give me your best. Don't quit.
No. Keep going. Keep going.
Keep going. Don't quit. Don't quit.
Don't quit.
Brock Kelley, you don't quit.
Keep going. Keep going.
Go, Brock Kelley. You don't quit on me.
No, you keep going.
You keep going. Go, Brock.
10 more steps. 10 more.
10 more. 10 more.
Keep going. Don't quit.
Give me your heart.
- I can't do it.
- You can. You can.
Five more. Five more.
Come on, Brock. Come on.
Don't quit. Don't quit.
Come on. Two more. One more.
That's gotta be 50. That's gotta be 50.
I don't have any more.
Look up, Brock. You're in the end zone.
Brock, you are the most
influential player on this team.
If you walk around defeated, so will they.
Tell me you can't give me more
than what I've been seeing.
You just carried a 140-pound man
across this whole field on your arms.
Brock, I need you.
God's gifted you with the ability
of leadership. Don't waste it.
- Coach.
- Can I count on you?
Yes.
Coach.
- What is it, Jeremy?
- I weigh 160.
All right. Who's next?
Good practice, boys.
See you all tomorrow.
Hey, man, for the first time in a while,
I actually feel good about Friday night.
- Yeah? Why?
- I'm just on board with what you're doing.
If they get ahold of it,
it'll change their lives.
You count me in.
Grant, me too.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I feel like I owe you an apology.
I just want you to know
that I'm with you.
- Thank you.
- See you tomorrow.
- You need a ride, Matt?
- No, my dad's coming.
Or at least, he'd better be.
Can I shoot straight with you
for a minute?
- Sure.
- I feel like you owe your dad more respect.
- Why?
- 'Cause he's your father.
- You don't know him like I know him.
- I don't have to.
You need to respect him
because it's the right thing.
You know, Coach,
my dad doesn't even like you.
He thinks the school
needs to find somebody else.
That's beside the point.
Scripture says to honor your parents.
- And all you do is complain.
- All he does is boss me around.
He doesn't even try to understand me.
You can't judge your father by his
actions and yourself by your intentions.
It doesn't work that way.
You're not responsible for him.
You're responsible for you. You honor
God by honoring your authority.
You really believe in all that honoring
God and follow Jesus stuff?
Yes, I do.
Well, I ain't trying to be disrespectful,
but not everybody believes in that.
Religion works for some people, but I'm
just here 'cause I got kicked out of Westview.
Matt, nobody's forcing anything on you.
Following Jesus Christ is a decision
you're gonna have to make for yourself.
You may not wanna accept him.
'Cause he'll change your life.
You'll never be the same.
I do hope one day
you realize how much he loves you.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll get him. Give me the bag.
Bring that trash bag here. Set it down.
- Don't you let that touch me.
- I'm gonna get him out of here.
- Oh, man, he stinks.
- I can't believe that was in my house.
- Just make sure it's still dead.
- It's probably been dead for weeks.
You just get it out of here. Out. Out.
- Stop being a... Come here. Look at it.
- No.
It looks like a big hamster.
Come here, come here.
Don't be afraid. Just face your fear.
He's got a cute little tail there.
He's just got a big stink.
Look. See his cute little eyes there?
See his teeth? Look at his teeth.
Almost looks like he's mad.
You're terrible! I can't believe
you did that to me, Grant Taylor.
You are so bad.
David, right down the middle.
You got this.
Right, set it up. Run it again.
- Sorry, Coach.
- David, listen, son.
You act like you're gonna miss
before you even kick the ball.
We're gonna have to change
your kicking philosophy.
Now, see, you're kicking wide left
or wide right.
That ain't what's gonna get you home.
The ball has got to go
through the middle.
- I know, Coach.
- No, you don't.
Now, what does Scripture say about this?
Scripture says, "Wide is the gate
and broad is the way
that leads to destruction,
and many there be that find it."
Now, to us, that's wide left
and wide right.
"But narrow is the gate and straight
is the way that leads to life,
and few there be that find it."
Anybody can kick it
wide left or wide right.
My mama can kick it
wide left and wide right.
- But that ain't what's gonna get you home.
- Come on.
It don't have to look pretty.
It don't have to look smooth.
It can look like a dying duck.
But the ball has to go
through the middle.
Oh, my word.
Now, David, you gonna have to choose
the narrow way.
That's the only path
where you will get your reward.
Now send this ball through these pearly
posts. Set it up for me, Jonathan.
I've never heard it that way before, but
there's a lot of truth to what he's saying.
Let's see you kick it.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Grant, are you not aware
of what's going on outside on the field?
- What?
- You might wanna come check this out.
Mitch decided to bring
his Bible class outside today.
Matt Prater stood up
and accepted Christ as his Lord.
It was awesome. He started
confessing stuff from his life,
asking his friends for forgiveness.
Next thing we know, Bob Duke stands up
and does the same thing.
Kids break up into groups,
they begin to pray for each other,
they ask forgiveness for sins
they've committed.
This has been going on for three hours.
How did you not know what was going on?
Bless them in a special way.
Lord, I ask you to lift them up to you.
I ask you to bring up a generation
that has a heart for you, Lord.
Coach.
- I'm proud of you, Matt.
- I need to talk with my dad.
I'd like to go see him.
I'll take you right now.
So what we've done here
is we've gained these four lots
by moving the retention pond down here.
- We could try and do that through here.
- No. I like this. That's perfect.
Mr. Prater,
there's someone here to see you.
- Sarah, I'm in a meeting.
- It's your son.
- Would you like me to step out?
- No, it's OK.
Sarah, send him in.
- Matt, you OK?
- Sorry. I didn't know you were in a meeting.
What is it, son?
Dad, I just wanted to say
that I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for the way I've been acting.
I got right with God today
and I just needed to say
that from now on
I'll respect your authority.
Whatever you say goes.
That's it.
You know, I could come back tomorrow
if that would be better for you.
No. It's OK.
I'm sorry. I...
For what it's worth,
I'd give my right arm
to hear my son say that to me.
I feel like I'm standing
before a new team tonight.
It's a new day and a new game.
What you've experienced in your hearts
this week will be released on the field.
Stay humble but confident.
Why don't you take this one, Brock?
Lord, we know
our lives are not about football,
but we do thank you
for allowing us to play tonight.
We're gonna give you our best.
If we win, we'll praise you
and if we lose, we'll praise you.
We'll give you all the honor and the glory
for this night. Keep us safe.
- Amen.
All right, guys. Look at me.
Play hard, have fun.
Hit.
In the Old Testament,
Nehemiah had the task of
building a wall around his city
for protection.
But he didn't have enough people
or resources or time.
Because each person worked on the wall
in front of their house,
they got it done in record time.
That's what you're gonna do.
On defense you have to resolve
nothing gets by you as an individual,
nothing gets by us as a team.
I need you to build me a stone wall.
Let's go. Let's go.
Run through
like you're throwing yourself.
Come on. Hit somebody! I wanna see
some hitting. I wanna see some hitting.
Dig those feet. Come on, you ain't
on my team yet. You ain't on my defense.
You gotta dig those feet.
All right, Prater. Get in there, boy.
Hit him a little harder than that.
This ain't ballet practice.
This is football practice.
David.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org