Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Everywhere I see your faces...
Everywhere you sing
your smile and...
Every time you're not around...
It doesn't matter,
'Cause you're everywhere to me...
Everyone you've ever known...
Counts on you...
Waits for you...
To come through...
Don't you know...
That you're gonna
break through?
And everywhere
you came and left...
You came in the name
of love and...
Left a wake of happiness
and tenderness...
And sweet conflict...
Sweet conflict...
You hang around...
You come on down...
You come on
down...
And it's on...
And on and on and on...
It's on...
It goes on...
You're everywhere...
Everywhere everywhere...
To me...
Everywhere...
Calling...
I'm calling your number...
Calling your number...
Calling...
You're everywhere...
You're everywhere to me...
Everywhere to me...
Oops, sorry, Shaquan.
Again you go down.
Very easy for me.
That's very unfortunate.
Now got get me some Yoo-hoos
and some blunt wraps...
in honor of my victories.
I got next.
Nah, I don't play
no charity games.
What, are you afraid
of the Irish hand?
Look, dawg,
I don't play no octagons, all right?
There's no Geritols on the court.
50 bucks says
I'll kick your ass, salsa boy.
Let's go, fat man.
I'll even give you first serve.
Here comes the lightning.
Are you ready, boy?
Listen, you fat bitch,
don't call me boy.
It's very embarrassing.
You smell like moth balls.
- Serve it up.
- Bring it.
Serve it.
Come on, serve it.
That's what I'm doing.
You all right, pops?
Enough to kick your ass, Julio.
Paco.
My name is Paco.
Whatever.
You all right, pops?
(echoing)
Want to take it easy
for a second?
Serve 'em up.
Pops, you all right?
Yeah.
Hey, come on, come on, pops.
Cut it out. Get up.
Hey, pops?
Yo, call 911.
Somebody call the 911.
(people chattering)
(kettle whistling)
He loved the game.
I'm sure he's happy
he died on the court.
He never should have been
playing in this heat.
63 and 220 pounds...
he shouldn't have been playing at all.
(sighs)
[Man]: All right, quiet.
Come on, quiet.
All right, shut it!
Well, you'd better get out there
before your uncle breaks something.
[Man]: I'm gonna say something
about my brother.
John always talked about
having a wake like this, you know,
where family and friends came
and got stinking drunk...
and told stupid stories
about him.
I already talked
to a lot of you,
so the stupid part's
all taken care of, I guess.
But I loved my brother.
He- he was a lot of things
to a lot of people.
He was a husband...
to his beautiful Gracie.
He was a father...
to Henry and Cate.
He was a boss
in his own business.
He's probably raising a pint
right now...
and challenging
the Lord Christ himself...
in that big handball court
in the sky.
[Man]:
Here here. Yeah.
To John.
[All]: To John.
Is there someplace
you and Henry and I can talk?
Oh, sure.
Hey.
[Woman]: Jesus, Colin.
Doesn't anybody knock?
Sorry, Sheila.
(toilet flushes)
Why are we in my room?
It's not important
where we are, Hank,
only that we're here together,
which leads me to
why we're here together.
You're the head
of this household now.
You are, Hank,
not me.
I can't be, because...
I'm the head
of another household...
my household.
I'm Charlie Doyle, Henry.
This is Charlie Doyle, Henry.
I'm sorry we had to meet
under these circumstances.
I am your father's attorney.
There are some important
decisions...
Mr. Doyle has some important things
he needs to talk to you about.
There's no easy way
to put this, Henry,
so I'm just going
to be blunt.
The family's broke.
In fact, it's worse than that.
There are substantial debts.
Yeah, well, I figured my dad wasn't
too good with money,
but he did have
a life insurance policy, right?
Your father's life insurance company
expressly warned him...
about participating
in certain activities...
such as handball,
which they considered
a health risk.
He wasn't covered.
So there's no insurance money?
I'm afraid not.
Sorry.
What about the business?
Your father was the business.
There are no assets there.
Are you going to work?
I switched shifts
so I could be at the funeral.
(sighs)
Look,
at least the old man
went down swinging.
That's great, Uncle Colin.
I'm real proud.
Uh, Dean Swift.
Oh, hello, Henry.
I'm sorry to hear
about your father.
Thank you.
You know what?
I can come back.
Actually, I could use your help.
Come come.
I just have to fix this one model
for Miss Abel's class.
Can you hold the vagina
in place here...
Sure. I can do that.
...while I put the bladder in?
There you go.
Sorry to see you leave, Henry.
Your scores were beginning
to improve.
Well, it should just be
temporary.
Can you pass me the rectum?
(whispers)
The rectum.
Thank you.
Henry, this is an ovary.
You should be able to recognize
a rectum by now.
You're better than that.
You're right.
Is this it?
Mm-hmm, yes.
That's a rectum.
I want to complete my coursework
as soon as possible.
I just really need to make
some money right now.
I understand, Henry.
You have two years to make up
the remaining classes.
I hope to do it
as soon as I can.
Do you see the testicular
self-examination model?
Oh.
You take care
of yourself, Henry.
- Thank you.
- We'll all be pulling for you.
I can help you?
I'm here to see George.
Okay.
The name?
Uh, George...
George...
No, buddy, not his name.
I know his name.
He's writing my paycheck.
Your name.
Sorry. Henry O'Shea.
Mr. George, there's a Henry O'Shea
in the lobby.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
He's coming.
Great.
You like working here?
(elevator dings)
O'Shea?
Yeah.
Yeah, hi. What?
- What?
- What are you looking at?
Nothing.
- I'm Henry.
- Yeah, George.
Come on, we'll take this
down to my office.
The first thing you need to know is
you never go through that front door.
The only time you're in the front
is when you're in uniform.
- You got it?
- Got it.
Got it?
Look, kid, your Uncle Colin and I...
we go way back.
I'm doing him a solid
giving you a job.
Okay, thank you, sir.
No no no, you save the "sir" crap
for the tenants, all right?
Me- my name's George.
That's what you call me.
I know I look like a fighter,
but I'm a real pussycat.
Ask anybody.
Go ahead, sit down.
Yeah, just put that on the floor.
So what makes you think
you're doorman material?
Uh...
You Uncle Colin said that you
wanted to be a nurse...
- but you couldn't hack it, right?
- No, not exactly.
Look, I don't give a horse's tit
about your past.
Billy Donovan was a fruit.
He worked here for 15 years.
You know, your past
is your past.
Your Uncle Colin says
you're a good kid,
so you're a good kid
until you prove otherwise.
Okay, good, but...
Save it for the shrink.
Let's go over the rules.
The most important rule,
the golden rule is...
you want to guess?
Uh...
treat other people
like you want to be treated?
Wrong. Dead wrong.
The most important rule is...
you never ever let somebody
in the building...
- they're not supposed to be in.
- Okay. Of course.
Don't say, "of course". If it was
of course, you'd get it right, right?
Everybody- they think
being a doorman is easy.
It's not so easy.
The devil’s in the details, kid.
You know, you gotta learn
how to put out packages,
learn people's names,
you know?
And what's the most
important thing?
Don't let other people in
that aren't supposed to get in.
Yeah, good.
Don't forget that.
No eating or sleeping
in the lobby.
Don't fraternize
with the residents.
They got better things to do
than talk to you.
You keep it short, businesslike.
You want to write this down?
No, I'll remember.
Well, if you don't, you're out.
All right, tomorrow, 10:30 PM.
You'll talk to Raul.
He'll show you around.
And don't pick up
any of his bad habits.
- All right.
- Let's go.
(knocks on door)
[Mother]: with me
about every detail.
[Daughter]: I'm not arguing.
Scarlett, I don't understand
why you're being so ungrateful about this.
Because it's just not that big a deal.
It's a birthday party.
It's your birthday.
And it was a big for me
when I had you.
You were large and painful.
And since I happen to be financing...
this particular birthday party,
it's my simple wish...
that no hobos be allowed.
White shirts, two,
a little starch.
Afternoon, Mrs. Dowling,
Scarlett.
This is Hank.
Hank's the new doorman.
Hi, I'm Henry.
Welcome to the building, Hank.
George, you did get my message
about the caterer?
Yes, ma'am, sure did.
All taken care of, Mrs. D.
- Thank you.
Can I get those?
No, I'm okay.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
[Mrs. Dowling]: There are plenty
of people on the list...
- Okay, floor, please?
- Penthouse.
[Mrs. Dowling]: All right,
we'll discuss it later.
(jazz music playing)
(phone ringing)
Hello.
Honey, it's Gretchen.
Should I just leave these here?
Take them all to Scarlett's room-
down the hall, the last door at the end.
And this is for you, Harry.
Thank you.
See anything you like?
Oh, hey.
Your mom told me to put
your bags in here.
And snoop through my stuff?
No no, I wasn't snooping.
No? 'Cause it looked
a little like snooping.
I should probably go.
Nice to meet you.
"Classy ladies...
make 5000 dollars a week
without leaving your house.
No experience necessary".
I don't think you want
that one.
Why not?
'Cause they're looking
for hookers.
Oh.
Are you sure?
Because it sounds pretty good.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Look, maybe I could get you a shift
walking dogs,
but it's not exactly
a walk in the park.
Isn't it?
The fact that you think that
makes me know that you are not ready.
"Cashier...
good starting pay.
No experience necessary".
How hard could that be?
Yeah, you know what?
Call them.
And don't let them
jerk you around.
You've got to be ready
to play hardball, eh?
- (mumbling)
- (laughs)
You got a real knack
making oriental food.
Ha ha ha.
Wow, I'm gonna have a job.
I haven't had one
in 20 years.
They're gonna love you, Ma.
It's gonna be great.
Just don't tell your brother.
I don't want to argue with him.
I won't say anything.
Won't say anything about what?
What? Hey, how's school?
Great.
Won't say anything about what?
- I'm getting a job.
- She's getting a job.
No, you're not.
You listen to me.
I'm your mother.
And you can't tell me
what I can't do.
I'm not gonna just roll over
and give up my house...
that I lived in for 15 years.
We need money
and I'm getting a job.
No one's giving up
the house, Ma.
I left today
and Uncle Colin got me a job
as a doorman.
So you don't have to
go to work.
You quit
to take care of me?
I took a leave of absence.
You precious angel.
You're gonna be a doorman?
What the hell is wrong
with being a doorman?
You're gonna be able
to tell me pretty soon.
Have a nice evening,
Miss Janet, okay?
Hey, you, come here.
You must be the new kid.
Yeah, Henry O'Shea.
Raul.
You're on with me tonight.
Go get changed.
The locker room's on B1...
down the stairs, make a right.
Hurry up.
(man snoring loudly)
(coughs, exclaims)
What the hell are you doing?
I'm Henry.
I'm the new doorman.
- What's going on?
- I was sleeping.
This guy was touching me.
- Touching you?
- No, I wasn't touching him.
Was he touching you?
Okay, yes, I was touching him,
but I thought something was wrong
with his breathing.
I was listening to his chest.
I was on my way to get my uniform.
What's wrong with my chest?
Francisco, settle down, okay?
Look, buddy, I'm not gay.
Oh, who said anything
about being gay?
He said I was touching him.
I'm studying to be a nurse.
And you're not gay?
Look, Dr. Kildare,
you're not working here.
You're not on call, okay?
If anything is wrong with him,
you let him die.
Now get a uniform,
get dressed,
and no touching.
Don't touch anybody
that works here.
Don't touch anybody who lives here.
You got it?
Right.
What's wrong with me?
You've got obstructed breathing.
What's destructive breathing?
Forget it.
Do we really have to
wear the hat?
Nice fit.
Thanks.
It's hot, right?
Yeah.
That's 'cause it's made of wool...
one uniform for summer,
winter, spring and fall.
You ain't gonna find
no air conditioning nowhere...
that's gonna stop you
from sweating your nuts off.
Terrific.
You see Francisco downstairs?
Oh, yeah.
We had a nice conversation.
Yeah?
That's weird.
He's usually asleep.
Why didn't you eat early
when you had time?
Look, I couldn't
because I was waiting for you.
- Oh, waiting for me.
- Did you pack the Blackberry charger?
Yes, I packed the Blackberry charger.
How many times are you gonna ask me?
As many times as it takes
to know you did it, Debbie.
Don't Debbie me.
Good evening,
Mr. and Mrs. Silverman.
Hey, Bobby.
This is our new doorman Henry.
Hello, Henry.
- Pleased to meet you, Henry.
- Nice to meet you too, sir.
Here, take Hercules.
I need to take my Klonopin
before we leave for this nightmare...
I mean, our romantic
anniversary getaway.
The car's ready, Mr. Silverman.
Thank you, Raul.
We'll be back on Sunday.
If you can't get us on the cell,
you know you can always email.
Your father doesn't even have
a bowel movement without his Blackberry.
No parties, Bobby.
I'm not gonna have
any parties.
You listen to your father.
I love you, sweetie.
Me too, Mom.
(snaps fingers)
Keep an eye on him, okay, Henry?
I will, sir.
Thank you very much.
You hungry, man? I'm starving.
Let's get something to eat.
I thought we weren't
supposed to eat up here.
We ain't supposed to be seen eating.
That don't mean we gotta starve.
- Yeah, Mo's.
- Yeah, what's happening?
Let me get- hold on one second.
What you want on it?
It's my first night.
I'm all right.
Sausage, pepperoni... what?
Sure.
Let me get a large half-pepperoni
half-sausage.
1500 Fifth Avenue.
- [Man]: Raul?
- Yeah, what's up? It's Raul.
I'm just chilling.
You know what's happening.
- Be about 20 or 30 minutes.
- Mm-hmm, okay, thanks. For sure.
30 minutes or less.
Nurses' School, huh?
I guess that's cool.
You don't want to be
no doctor?
You know how much it costs
to go to med school?
- No.
- More than I got. Crazy money.
And I didn't have the scores
for a scholarship.
I'm gonna take off, buddy.
What do you mean, take off?
You don't need me here, man.
You got this job down pat.
Somebody comes-
open the door, let them in.
I mean, the night shift is dead.
It's easy.
It's easier
than being a nurse, right?
What if George comes?
George is asleep.
And if he do come, just cover for me.
Tell him I went to get some coffee.
Good looking, my brother.
Hey.
He's kind of cute.
A doorman.
(door buzzes)
- What's up?
- Hi, can I help you, ladies?
Yeah, we're here to see Roberto, 8B.
We're his cousins.
Uh, okay.
Hang on one second.
You said 8...
Yeah.
There.
One second.
- Bobby?
- Buenas noches.
Bobby, is that you?
[Bobby]: Bobby is not here.
Yo estoy Roberto.
Okay, Roberto, your cousins
are here to see you.
I'm sorry, what did you say
your names were?
Mercedes and Portia.
Mercedes
and Portia.
[Bobby]: Ah, yes,
cousin Mercedes.
Send them up, por favor.
You said you were his cousins?
Yeah, distant cousins,
removed a couple times.
Are you gonna let us go up
or what, baby?
Okay, go see your cousin.
I'm gonna regret that.
(knocks on door)
Sorry, didn't see you there.
Don't apologize.
Help me.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
- Henry, right?
- Yeah.
Scarlett, stop flirting
with the doorman...
and take Buck.
I want to go home.
Did somebody have a little
too much to drink?
Fuck you.
I had exactly the right amount.
Wow, he can puke
and be an asshole all at the same time.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
No, sweetie, I'm sure
you won't embarrass yourself.
Thanks, Gretch.
I'll take it from here.
- Isn't he precious?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna go.
Call you tomorrow.
[Buck]: Later, hot stuff.
Eat me.
Don't worry, I'll clean that up.
I'm gonna let you
clean up my boyfriend's puke.
He can clean up.
He's a doorman.
Buck, stop being such a jerk.
Listen, don't worry about it.
I clean up puke all the time...
at school.
I was studying to be a n...
don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
You're really sweet.
Thank you.
I owe you one.
Oh, fruit juice. Give him
some fruit juice and some aspirin.
It'll help his hangover.
Okay.
Great, thanks.
The night shift is dead, my ass.
(knocks)
Have you seen a couple of hos
come in here five seconds ago?
Sir, if I could please ask you
to wait outside...
Man, ring up the apartment
and tell them I'm here right this second,
or you'll need a tourniquet
where your dick used to be...
and a feeding tube
where your mouth used to be. Feel me?
Okay. Okay.
Just give me one second.
- Bobby.
- Buenas noches.
Bobby, you send those girls
back down here immediately.
Do it now
or I will tell your father everything.
[Bobby]: Fine, I'm coming.
He's coming. If I could just
have you wait outside...
No no, if they ain't
down here soon,
I'm going up.
Okay, you can just
stay there.
You Roberto?
Who got my money?
I don't have it. I thought
I could use a credit card.
Could I borrow a few bucks?
How much?
- 200 dollars.
- 200 dollars for...?
I'll totally pay you back.
200 dollars. Here.
Still short, man.
I want my money.
Look, there's 196 there. Are you
gonna hurt this kid over four bucks?
It's your lucky day, Roberto.
Are you nuts?
I'm sorry. I'll pay you back with interest.
Just don't tell my folks.
Don't tell... you...
go to bed.
You're gonna tell,
aren't you?
No, I'm gonna finish
mopping up this puke...
and you're gonna pay me back
tomorrow, okay?
I don't live on Fifth Avenue.
200 dollars is a lot of money to me.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
I owe you one.
You owe me 2 hundred and one.
Go to bed
before I change my mind.
Hey, George.
I was just adjusting my back.
Balls. You were sleeping.
- All right, I'm sorry.
- Kid, you can't sleep in the lobby.
You gotta get used
to the night shift.
Don't let it happen again.
All right.
Where is Raul?
He's here.
Where?
He was here.
Hey, I was just out getting coffee.
You want one?
No.
- This one's on me.
- Thanks. How did you-?
Look, man, I've been working here
for eight years.
I pick up on habits.
That man right there... George...
he's a creature of habit.
Ugh, what is that?
Aged coffee.
I keep it hid outside
behind the bushes.
Hey, partner.
Right on time, baby.
Yo, what's up?
(distant dogs barking)
[Caitlin]: Stella.
What?
[Caitlin]: Stella, shut up.
Don't look at me like that.
I know damn well you started it.
Here.
Get over yourself.
What's with the dogs, Cate?
They're normally really well-behaved,
but Stella can be a little bitch.
- No, I mean, why are they here?
- Oh, that?
I'm making some extra cash
doing overnight boarding.
So we're running a kennel now?
Mom is fine with it
as long as they keep quiet.
They're not quiet.
By dog standards,
they are church mice.
Forget it. You don't know
anything about dogs.
Okay, where's Ma?
I think she got a job.
Great.
So sensitive, that one.
Welcome back.
Thanks.
You have here
a letter or something.
One night, and he has
a secret admirer.
That's it for me.
I have sucked enough ass
for one day.
Have a good night, Henry.
All right, you too.
(door buzzes)
...jealous of the fact
that I can sing better than you.
I can sing better than you
and that's why you don't like it.
Okay, let me tell you something...
it's "heartache tonight,"
not "party tonight".
It's not a happy song, Ray.
[Ray]: Why can't you just admit
when you don't know something...
except talking
out of your hoop. Why?
Ring! Hello, clue phone.
It's for you.
It's The Eagles calling to say
you're an idiot.
Oh, like The Eagles would call you,
Mr. Wrapped-Up-Like-A-Douche.
Oh, please, everyone thinks
it's "douche" at nine years old.
[Ray]: I think you're a douche.
Can you help us?
- Do you know that song...?
- Let it go, Ray.
I'll buy you the CD
for Rosh Hashanah.
Oh, no. Your dog.
- No, it's The Eagles.
- No no no, your dog...
is going up in the elevator
with the leash.
- Oh my God, Cassius.
- Oh my God.
Oh my God.
[Jason]: Cassius.
[Ray]: He's not making noise.
[Jason]: Cassius,
everything's gonna be fine. Breathe.
This is all your fault. If you weren't
so in love with Glenn Frey...
[Ray]: Oh, shut up.
Shut up.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
(elevator dings)
Oh my God.
He's dead.
Oh my God, he's dead.
You killed him.
- What is he doing?
- I think he's reviving him.
Hang in there, Cassius.
Hang in, baby.
Hang in.
Don't go in the light.
[Jason]: What's he...?
What's he?
[Ray]: He's CPRing him.
Are you blind?
Oh, Cassius.
- Oh, Cassius.
- Oh, look at that.
Cassius, baby boy.
Baby boy.
Oh, my little angel.
You scared me.
Hey. Hi.
I am so sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
And you, mister...
who's amazing?
You are.
Thank you so much.
I don't know how we can ever repay you.
Don't worry.
I'm just doing my job, sort of.
- Come here.
- You don't need to...
Thank you so much.
On the mouth?
You just grossed him out.
- I was thanking him.
- Pick up that leash.
Hi, Scarlett.
Wow, I've never seen anyone
do that before.
Yeah, that was my first time
with a dog.
That didn't sound right.
No, it didn't.
What was that?
What?
What did I tell you about getting
too personal with the residents?
It wasn't a resident, sir.
It was a dog. And he was gonna die.
Not the dog, wise guy.
Miss Dowling.
Oh.
You don't listen
too good, do you?
What are you standing for?
Get to your station.
(elevator dings)
I didn't know you could
do that to a dog.
Yeah, right, 'cause you're always...
Yeah, like I was saying, you know,
I've been trying to do my thing.
- (door buzzes)
- Flowers for Scarlett Dowling.
I'll take those up.
Sorry, tenant's not home.
I'll sign for them.
(classical music playing)
(doorbell rings)
Someone get that.
[Mrs. Dowling]:
Could you get that?
(quietly) Nothing would give me
more pleasure.
Oh, hello.
Thank you so much.
Who is it, dear?
Flowers, darling.
Don't forget the tip.
Could you...?
Getting him a tip.
Those for me?
Yeah, I think so.
Right this way, please.
I think they're
from your friend Buck.
[Scarlett]: Yeah, I figured.
All done and dusted.
You can just move
some of that crap away.
Your room is great.
Isn't it?
I wish it didn't
make me so sick.
Why? What's wrong with it?
I didn't decorate it.
Mother.
You have a little
orange something on your nose.
Orange stuff?
Yeah, it's like powder
or something.
There you go.
Thanks.
Okay.
Henry.
Yeah?
How did you know how
to save that dog last night?
What, are you like a vet
or something?
Oh, no, I was never
in the military.
(laughs)
I'm a nurse.
I'm almost a nurse.
So you're almost
a nurse-slash-doorman?
Yeah. Well, I'm still in school.
- Oh.
- I had to take some time off...
to help... we... my...
Hey, there you are.
Buck, don't you have a phone?
Nice flowers, man.
Yeah.
I'm glad you approve.
What? Don't tell me
you're mad about last night.
I think those cocktail olives
were bad,
'cause I didn't have
that much to drink.
They're lucky I don't sue.
Listen, I'm gonna make a drink,
and you change,
put something nice on...
- and we'll go.
- Okay, you go do that.
Bye.
Hey, Grace, looking good.
I got your green tea
chai latte.
I took the liberty
of putting in...
a phytonutrient tablet.
It's got some powerful
antioxidants...
to give you a boost.
Well, that's very sweet.
Thank you, Laszlo.
Are you happy?
Very happy.
This chair is really comfortable.
It's one of our best sellers,
comes with a how-to video
that's amazing.
Well, I'm glad
that you're happy.
'Cause if you're happy,
the workplace is happy,
the customers are happy,
and then I'm happy.
I'm a people person.
At least I try very hard to be.
Well, I love people.
And I really like
working here already.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Well, jeez, I love to hear that.
And you're doing
a great job.
Keep it up.
Okay, you too.
I do.
All right.
Thank you for my, uh, phyto...
The last time we were in Japan
was in '95 and I...
No no, that was Hong Kong.
We were in Japan in '98.
Absolutely.
- We were in Hong Kong?
- Yes.
(groans)
We were invited to see
a Japanese production of "Cats,"
which, let me tell you,
was better than the original.
Can we go in, please?
- Dude, you killed it.
- Did I? Sorry, buddy.
Hey, thanks for doing your job.
I appreciate it.
- Sorry about that, guys.
- Whatever.
We went swimming in a lake
and I don't know if you know...
that these little fish...
I forgot the name of them,
but when you urinate
in water...
they fly up the stream
the other way.
- Hello, Mrs. Dowling.
- Hi, Buck.
- How are you?
- Thank you for coming.
I wouldn't miss it
for the world.
- Hey, you look great.
- Oh, thank you.
- I mean that.
- Thank you.
Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy.
- "You look great, I mean that"?
- I did mean that.
Your boyfriend's already
completely loaded.
Welcome to my life.
I don't know
why I put up with it.
Because good-looking and rich
is rare commodity.
God, I'm not that shallow, am I?
No, of course not.
A helicopter to the Hamptons
every weekend...
doesn't necessarily mean
you're shallow.
- No.
- I mean, who wants to do that drive,
especially in the summer?
Are you okay?
(glass dings)
Everybody, everybody,
can I have your attention? Thank you.
Now if the birthday girl
could join me?
You know,
I can hardly believe...
that this
whose diaper I changed,
whom I taught
to ride a bike...
and whom I can still hear...
reciting the lines of Puck...
from the immortal Bard
in fourth grade,
has transformed into...
this beautiful, graceful...
and sophisticated young woman.
Scarlett, I know that I speak...
on behalf of your mother
and myself...
when I say that we genuinely
could not have asked...
for a better child.
Thanks, Dad.
Happy birthday, sweetheart.
Happy 21st, Scarlett.
Oh, I nearly forgot.
A small token of our affection,
very small.
No.
Oh my God.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
- Hi.
- This is my buddy.
I need another drink...
a whisky and coke.
Could you get that for me, please?
- Happy birthday, baby.
- Give me that.
- Anyway, so...
- Hey hey hey.
We need to talk.
Jake, here.
This party sucks.
Do the right thing.
Gracias, amigo.
Dude, that's her baby picture.
Whatever.
Right.
Holy shit.
What?
That's a lot of witch, bro.
Would you stop
being such a pussy, Jake?
We'll split it.
(snorting)
- Oh!
- Yeah.
- (Buck snorting)
- You gonna do all mine too?
- Come on, man.
- Ahhh!
Hey!
Yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Thanks.
(exhaling)
So good.
(Jake giggles)
Mmm.
I want a white one, Mr. Dowling.
- A ribbon?
- A car, silly.
Oh oh oh, no problem.
When do you need it by?
It's Buck. He's passed out on
the floor in the bathroom.
- Oh my God.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
He just...
he fell and then...
Jake, tell me what happened!
We were doing some blow,
all right, Scarlett? He did too much.
Call 911.
Somebody call 911.
- What's going on?
- Isn't there a doctor here?
Dr. Rosenthal and his wife RSVP'd
but they never showed up.
Mother, call Henry downstairs.
He's a nurse.
- Henry the doorman?
- Yes, just do it!
(intercom buzzes)
Front desk. Raul.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, I'll send him up
right now.
Henry, 911 to the Dowling’s' apartment.
Somebody's hurt.
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
Come on!
- Get in there.
- Excuse me.
Excuse me.
- What happened?
- He was doing coke.
- I don't think he's breathing.
- Jesus. He must've done a lot.
- He did a ton.
- Okay.
Come on, you stupid prick.
Breathe. Breathe.
Is that CPR?
(Henry breathes)
- Come on, man. He's turning blue.
- Okay, this isn't working.
- Oh my God.
- [Henry]: Okay.
I'm gonna have to ask everybody to
back up. Could I have you guys back up?
I'm gonna try something.
(inhales)
(Buck grunts)
- Are you okay?
- Oh.
- Cocaine OD?
- Yeah.
I tried to give him CPR
but it didn't work.
So you hit him with
the pericardial thump?
- Uh-huh.
- Nice work.
- Thanks.
- We'll take it from here.
You're lucky you're not dead, kid.
Not too many people know
how to do a thump.
(elevator door opens)
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Are you sure, man?
'Cause you don't look okay.
I was so freaked out.
I just saved a guy's life.
- No shit? Who?
- Yeah, Scarlett's boyfriend.
- Wow.
- (door opens)
(indistinct EMT radio)
You saved my friend's life, man.
I wanna thank you.
I got 200 bucks on me.
I wish I had more, but...
200 dollars?
That's cool, baby.
No, I'll get...
I have a check.
Make it out to Henry O'Shea.
You do know how to spell O'Shea,
don't you?
- O'Shea?
- Yeah.
All right.
No no no. No no. I'm not taking a tip
for saving a guy's life.
If you'd like,
you can make it out to Raul.
- Raul?
- Yeah.
R~A~U...
Look, you already thanked me.
That's fine.
Are you... you serious?
Thank you.
Kid, let me explain
something to you...
you cannot turn down
a 200 dollar tip, man.
I'm not taking a tip for saving
a guy's life. It's not right.
Well, give it to your crew.
We didn't save nobody's life.
- Hi.
- Hey.
You were amazing.
I don't know how to thank you.
- You don't have to, really.
- You saved his life.
I mean, the paramedic said so.
I've never done that before.
I mean, we practiced
in school, but...
never on someone
who was about to die.
It's kinda scary.
You didn't look scared.
- No?
- No.
You looked like you were totally
in control of the situation,
kinda like when you had
that dog's head in your mouth.
It was kinda hot.
Very funny.
You're a sweet guy, Henry.
- I gotta go.
- 'Night, Miss Dowling.
(exhales)
You got a real problem
with keeping your hands to yourself.
Come on, George.
She was upset. I was comforting her.
This is your last warning.
Next time if I hear or see you
touching anybody in this building,
you hit the bricks.
And that goes for dogs too.
(exhales)
"You're a sweet guy, Henry".
(sighs)
What am I doing, man?
Do you have girl trouble often?
Raul is a love doctor.
Tchh! Then fix me, Doctor.
Fix me.
Let her go, papito.
[Caitlin]:
So how's the doorman business?
It's definitely been
a lesson in humility.
Any good stories yet?
None that don't make me
seem ridiculous.
What kind of stories
do you think I like?
- Can I ask you a question?
- Yeah, shoot.
Get. (clucks)
- Would you...
- Hey. Hey.
- Would you date a guy who was dirt poor?
- No.
Okay.
I'm just pulling your leash.
Of course.
Hey, get over yourself.
Girls don't care about money...
not the good ones, anyway.
Girls just want you
to be the alpha, you know?
You be strong and assertive,
you'll have to beat 'em off with a stick.
You want a guy to be the alpha?
Me? Hell no.
Wait a second.
Why are we talking about this?
Who's the girl?
No, I mean, there's no girl.
Hank, you're Lying to me.
You're a terrible liar.
What's her name?
When would I have had time
to meet a girl?
I don't know, may-
she lives in the building.
- (laughs)
- She lives in the building.
- What's her name?
- You're good.
- Uh, Scarlett- Scarlett Dowling.
- Scarlett Dowling?
- Mmm.
Oh, good luck.
What is she,
some kind of high-maintenance
trust-fund kid or something?
I don't know. Probably.
- You asked her out yet?
- No, of course not.
Why not?
Because rich girls from Fifth Avenue
don't date their doormen.
- Plus I would get fired.
- Mmm.
Yep, that would be bad.
- Hello, Miss Dowling.
- Henry, please don't call me that.
- It's Scarlett.
- Sorry, Scarlett.
How's Buck doing?
Rehab.
Well, I guess that's a good thing.
It is.
Listen, Henry,
I think I figured out
how I want to thank you.
- I want to take you somewhere.
- Oh, yeah?
Yeah, and it's a surprise.
I'm gonna bring those up
as soon as they arrive, Miss Dowling.
- Hi, George.
- Hello, Scarlett.
George, did you know
that Henry here...
is the best doorman
that we've ever had?
Oh, yeah.
Henry's, uh...
he's got a real way
with the residents.
You keep it up, Henry.
Keep it up.
- Okay, so what is with the tape?
- I don't know.
Yeah, it's been one of
the great mysteries of the building.
I don't think anyone's been
able to ask him.
I'm not asking him.
So you'll come?
Yeah, I don't think
that's such a good idea.
Um, they don't like us getting
too friendly with the residents...
and I'm pretty sure
George would fire me.
Uh, I can't afford that right now.
Okay, so we won't go out.
We'll have a meeting.
- A meeting?
- Yes, a meeting.
And it starts tomorrow at 7:00 PM,
Pier 83 on the Westside Highway.
- (elevator dings)
- Mum's the word.
- Scarlett, I can't.
- Yes, you can.
No, I can't. I really want to,
but I can't.
You... I'm...
- You said Pier 83?
- Mm-hmm.
- At 7:00?
- Yes.
Okay. Sounds like a good place
for a meeting.
Meeting.
It's just a meeting.
Hi.
I'm so sorry.
You weren't waiting long, were you?
- No no.
- I couldn't find a cab...
and I was just... I...
- What?
- No, nothing.
- Uh...
- Why are you looking at me like that?
You just- you look great.
Thank you.
I look like a Mormon missionary.
No, you look great.
- Well, maybe we should...
- Yeah.
- go in.
- I didn't know where we were going.
- How about a hint?
- A hint?
Well, let's see... it's bigger
than a breadbox...
and it floats.
Hi, two tickets, please.
[Henry]:
Oh no, I've got this.
No, don't be silly.
I asked you here.
No, I insist.
I wasn't raised like that.
- Two, please.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
- (beeps)
- Your card's declined.
- What?
- Got another one?
Uh, that can't be right.
You want me to try it again?
No, I have cash.
I was supposed to pay anyway.
Your machine must be broken.
Yeah, the machine's broken.
(scanning)
- Sorry about that.
- Here you go. Have a good time.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
How can I help you?
(upbeat music playing)
You should've listened
to what Mama said...
I walked away with
someone else instead...
You should've listened
to what Grandma said...
Married someone
more like Fred...
You should've listened
to your inner voice...
While you had time
to sell it short...
May I ask you something?
Sure.
Why be a doorman?
I thought you were studying
to be a nurse.
My uncle Colin,
he's been a doorman forever.
He got me the job.
But why a doorman?
I mean, no offense.
I just...
I thought you might do something
in the medical field.
It just seems...
What? Beneath me?
No, not that.
(helicopter passes)
I'm not really in nursing school.
I mean, I was, but...
my Dad died.
And his life insurance...
well, whatever.
It's complicated.
But my mom was left
with a lot of debt,
so I just had to
get a job fast.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't know that.
It's all right.
Wow.
She's amazing.
Are you trying to
make me jealous?
You two are so different.
You really shouldn't compare yourself.
I mean, she's so much bigger...
and greener.
[Scarlett]:
Maybe you're right.
"Give me your tired,
your poor"...
What is it?
"Give me your tired,
your poor,
your huddled masses
yearning to breathe free.
Send these...
homeless,
tempest-tossed to me.
I lift my lamp beside
the golden door".
Now you're just showing off.
Not really.
It's one of the only poems I remember.
Emma Lazarus. I had to memorize it in,
like, seventh grade.
Who sew the lions...
Hungry in the cage...
With the confidence
of a clown?
The little man...
Who rises on the stage...
As he falls without a safety net...
We have this story...
Of the impossible...
A tale...
- What?
- This is where I get off.
Oh, right.
I'll watch you go in from here.
- You don't have to.
- No, I want to.
Thanks for a great,
uh, meeting.
Thank you.
Whatever happened to
- The great escape...
- Good evening, Miss Dowling.
And all the plans we made?
Crafted with pride
by monsters on the train...
The world is great
to suckers...
We have this story...
Of the impossible...
A tale...
No, that's just it.
She wasn't wearing anything
under the dress.
Well, of course she's too old.
Mm-hmm.
Well, just because she left him,
I don't see why she has
to completely lose control.
(camera beeping)
Ellen?
Ellen, I have to call you back.
(dialing)
Yes, this is Mrs. Dowling.
I need to speak with George.
Hey, George.
You wanted to see me?
I'm gonna get right to the point.
Did you or did you not...
go on a date
with Scarlett Dowling?
I... I... no.
I didn't go on a date.
Don't lie to me, kid.
The mother is fit to be tied.
George, it wasn't a date.
All right? It was a meeting.
Don't sass me.
I hate to be sassed.
Okay, just listen to me for a sec.
I can totally explain.
Her boyfriend, or her ex-boyfriend
or whatever...
Buck OD'd in the apartment, right?
And they asked me up...
and I went up there and I saved
the kid... I saved him in the apartment.
And she asked me out
to thank me.
What?
You've got a tattoo
on your face.
- A face tattoo.
- All right, that's it, you're fired.
- Get out.
- Look, George, listen to me, please.
I really need this job.
Yeah, well, you should've thought
about that when you dated her, Romeo.
You knew the rules.
You broke the rules. You're out.
And don't use the front.
Use the service elevator.
(ringing)
Hi. Hi, is Scarlett there?
Um, it's the front desk calling.
Oh, what the hell
are you doing?
Get outta here!
I'm calling your uncle!
(door closes)
(door dings)
Hi, Raul.
Could I leave this with you?
It's for Henry.
- It's just a letter.
- Maybe I should call George.
No no, it's for Henry.
I think you should call George.
Okay.
I'll give it to him myself.
You got fired.
Yeah, I did.
Thanks for being discreet.
Sorry.
Why'd they can you?
Super found out that I went
on a date with Scarlett.
You got fired over a girl.
Do you have any idea how cool that is?
I wish somebody would get fired for me.
Yeah, well, it's not gonna be so cool
when we lose the house.
Dad's gone. No one's going to
take care of this for us.
Just...
What am I supposed to do
if I can't find another job?
Look, you're smart, okay?
You got all your teeth.
(man muttering)
Sorry.
Anyway, look,
forget about the job, all right?
Jobs grow on trees. What are you
gonna do about the girl?
I'm not gonna do anything
about the girl.
- It was her family that got me fired.
- Mmm.
(sighs)
Whatever.
I'm always gonna be
a doorman to those people.
Well, looks like you don't have to worry
about being the doorman anymore,
so that's solved.
And besides,
we're not gonna lose the house.
Mom got a great job.
- She did?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh my...
Is there something you
want to tell me?
Well, um...
apparently purple is
the color this season.
Damn it, Mother,
I am serious.
So am I. Look at these pictures.
I look awful in purple.
- What did you do to Henry?
- I had him fired.
Why would you do that?
You can't date the help, Scarlett.
It doesn't look good.
Henry is not the help, Mother.
He's a human being.
All right, fine.
But sweetheart, a doorman?
Why on earth would you date a doorman?
How do you think that
makes me feel?
Meredith Dowling's daughter
is going out with their doorman.
I just hope no one
saw you together.
I had no idea what
an elitist snob you are.
Don't talk to me that way.
And don't be so dramatic.
I just want what's best for you.
No, you just want
what's best for you.
I'm gonna date whoever I want.
Okay? Whether it's the doorman,
the trash man or the mayor.
And it's gonna have nothing to do
with their station in life,
but everything to do
with who they are.
George?
Oh, Miss Dowling.
- What a pleasant surprise.
- Yeah, can it, George.
Hire him back.
Oh, no no no, I'm sorry. There are
strict rules about fraternization.
Okay, well,
give me his number.
I'm sorry.
I can't do that either.
I really am sorry.
Fine. Fine, be a jerk.
I mean, I can get his number.
You don't think I can get his number?
I can get it.
76 Henry O'Sheas?
- You're kidding, right?
- [Operator]: No, ma'am. I don't kid.
No, I guess you don't.
Okay.
Okay, give 'em to me.
I can only give you
two numbers at a time.
If you want more,
you'll have to call back.
Forget it.
That's fine, forget it.
- Okay.
- Whoa whoa whoa whoa.
Can I help you?
- Yeah, I want to talk to Scarlett Dowling.
- You're gonna have to wait outside.
We cannot have all
these animals in our lobby.
Would you just get her down here?
These dogs crap on command and they
eat uncooperative doormen.
(barks)
Just get her down here.
- Are you a friend?
- What's your name?
Raul.
Raul, I'm Cate.
I'm Henry's sister.
So would you just be a sport
and call up for me?
Sit. I mean it.
(beeps)
Yeah, it's Raul
from downstairs.
- There's some lady down here saying...
- Not today. Not today.
Henry's sister.
Okay.
She'll be right down.
So you're Hank's sister?
Yeah.
He didn't tell me
he had a sister.
Hmm.
Listen, I think that's bullshit
what happened to Hank.
We kinda miss him.
That's cute.
But Hank needs to go back to school.
Maybe this will make that happen.
Why'd he leave anyway?
Our dad died.
Wow. Sorry to hear that.
I lost one of my dads too.
I'm sorry.
So yeah, that's why
Hank dropped out.
That's f- that's messed up.
(elevator dings)
- Hi, you're Henry's sister?
- Yeah, Cate.
- Scarlett.
- You want to take a walk?
- I would love to.
- Excellent.
- Nice to meet you.
- Do you need a hand?
I got it.
I feel really bad about
what happened to Henry.
I mean, he told me he was
going to get fired,
and I insisted.
It's- it's my fault.
Pardon me for saying,
but that is bullshit.
Hank got fired because of Hank,
not because of you,
not because of your mother,
although she sounds colorful.
I heard about that.
He got fired because of him,
whatever he did.
I still feel awful.
Hank will get another job.
I'm just happy to hear
that you feel awful.
You know, I think I can help him
get his job back.
Maybe you shouldn't.
You don't think
he wants my help?
No, it isn't that.
Ooh, easy.
Easy easy.
Okay okay.
It isn't that. It's just, you know,
Hank needs to be back in school.
You're right.
He's too smart to
be a doorman.
No, he's not. It's just that
he wants to be a nurse.
What's wrong with
being a doorman?
No- nothing.
Nothing's wrong with being a doorman.
I just think it's
a misuse of Henry's talents.
We agree about that.
Come on.
No.
No way.
This can't be it.
Young wo[Man on TV]:
She told me that I was going on a trip,
and that I was going to meet...
some tall dark stranger.
(girl and man moaning)
What you lookin' at?
Grace:
You need help finding something?
"Grand Theft Anal"?
Section 4, Male Erotic.
- Mom.
- Henry.
What a nice surprise.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm working.
No, you don't work here. This is
a sick sick place for sick perverted...
Shh! Hush.
It's a video store, honey,
for- for adults.
- [Girl on TV]: Yes, take me!
- Okay.
We need to talk.
Not here. Outside.
I'm working.
Don't you need to get to work?
- Hey, Gracie.
- Oh.
- Great job on the dildo display.
- Thank you, Lazlo.
- I would like you to meet my son Henry.
- Hey!
- It's a great pleasure.
- Yeah, it's- sure. Great.
Look, I'm sorry to tell you that
my mother needs to resign...
- from your store.
- Really?
But she's employee of the week.
Hey, Henry,
what do you do?
Uh, I'm a nurse.
Ooh. Well, to each his own.
You know, when the customers come
in here and they figure out that...
Gracie is working here,
well, it makes them
more relaxed.
They feel like they're at home,
'cause maybe their mothers...
didn't appreciate
these kinds of things.
So she's great for business.
- Isn't he sweet?
- [Girl on TV]: Yes! Yes!
- Yes! Ahh!
- I only wish that my mother...
were more like her...
hot and totally
non-judgmental.
Okay. That's great.
Thank you.
- We need to go.
- Henry, no.
I'm not quittin'. I'm treated
with respect here and I like it.
All right. How would you like
to be assistant manager?
Would you like that?
Two bucks more an hour?
- Yes.
- All right, you're assistant manager.
- Nice meeting you.
- [Girl on TV]: Ahh ahh ahh!
- Ahh! Oooh!
- Aw.
You cannot work here anymore.
You need to go and tell him that you quit.
You are really bothering me.
I'm working.
I'm serious.
You'll find another job. You can't...
- Henry?
- Oh, no.
No no no no.
Scarlett. Uh...
- you can't be here. Not here.
- [Girl on TV]: Oh, yeah, baby!
- Right there.
- Don't look at that.
[Man]:
Yeah, baby, look at it.
Mmm, yeah.
Now spit on it.
Need help finding
something, sweetie?
Uh, Scarlett,
this is my mother, Grace.
- Hi, it's nice to meet you.
- Very nice to meet you too.
[Man on TV]:
Do it like that for Daddy.
Are you looking for
an adult film?
No, I was looking for Henry.
Damn, it's hot in here.
[Girl on TV]:
Yeah yeah yeah!
(slow motion)
Nooooo!
What the hell are you doing?
I thought that... wh...
Forget it.
I'm not supposed to
wear this uniform in here.
I won't tell if you don't.
[Man on TV]:
Yeah, oh!
What are you doing here?
- Cate said you might be here.
- You talked to Cate?
Yeah, she came by the building,
which I'm glad she did...
because I was having a hell
of a time finding your number.
Were you?
I wanted to say
I was really sorry.
It's my fault that you got fired
and I really want to fix it.
You got fired?
Yeah. I'm sorry, Ma.
I was gonna tell you.
Sorry about what?
Everybody gets fired...
except here...
with Lazlo.
- Let's talk outside.
- Okay.
I can help you find
another job.
My father knows a lot of people.
Look, I'll find something, okay?
It's really not your problem.
But I want to help.
I mean, it's the least I can do.
- My dad has this friend...
- Just stop, all right?
I don't need your help
and I don't need your dad's help.
I can take care of myself
and my family.
Fine. You don't have to be
such a jerk about it.
- I'm not being a jerk about it.
- Yeah, you kind of are.
Okay, what are we doing here?
- Fighting about you being a jerk.
- Seriously.
Henry, I like you.
You know, I really want
to see you again.
I'm sure your mom
would love that.
Look, I don't know
what a guy like me
can possibly hope to offer
someone like you.
I mean, I can't put 100 bucks
on a credit card,
much less take you out to dinner
anywhere but a hot-dog stand.
I like hot dogs.
- I don't really care about that stuff.
- Yeah, well, I do.
And you can't possibly know
what that feels like.
I mean, you're Fifth Avenue
and I'm always gonna be Flatbush.
All right?
I couldn't keep up.
Okay.
You know, there's a reason that people
don't date their doormen.
Maybe you're right.
Have a nice life, Henry O'Shea.
(starts engine)
Shit.
All right, little guys,
it's a field trip.
Come on.
All right.
Hey eh eh!
She find you?
Hey.
Coma guy,
Scarlett find you?
Yeah, she just left.
- Hi, honey.
- Oh hey, Ma.
Hi. Hey, did your friend leave?
- Yeah, how'd it go?
- She's got beautiful bone structure.
Okay, I don't wanna talk about it.
Okay, you know what?
I didn't spend 14 dollars for a cab...
for "I don't wanna talk about it".
So start talking.
Why? What happened?
I don't wanna talk about it.
- Okay.
- (Grace laughing)
So Henry's really into this rich girl
at his building, right?
So finally she asks him out...
whatever...
and then he gets fired.
For dipping your penis
in the company ink.
Ma, don't talk about
my penis.
I just learned that expression.
I like it.
I don't think that
that's the exact saying.
So that was her in the store?
- Where'd she go?
- I don't know.
She's just gone.
It was never gonna work out.
They're millionaires.
I mean, they've got a car and a driver
and a house in the Hamptons.
They got a Jamaican lady who lives
in their apartment and cooks for them.
I thought she was the maid too, but it
turns out they got another lady for that.
I mean, I was in
their living room the other night...
and above their fireplace
they have a Cézanne...
not like a poster,
like a real Cézanne.
I mean, these people live
on a different planet.
They don't want me
dating their daughter.
You know? I mean, what?
At best, I'm gonna be a nurse?
My dad wasn't the master of the universe,
he was a plumber.
My mom works in a porn shop,
my sister's a dog walker.
These two worlds don't mix.
Are you done?
Yeah, I guess.
You're done insulting yourself
and your family?
You're done labeling
the entire world?
I don't care if you date
this girl or not,
but you don't define
your father as a plumber,
or your sister as a dog walker
or yourself as a nurse.
Your father...
loved people.
He loved his family.
Yeah, he loved handball
a little too much,
but he was a kind,
compassionate man...
who would have given the shirt off
this back to anybody.
There's no girl that's too good
for my Henry.
I don't care how rich or pretty she is,
she'd be lucky to be loved by you.
I'm gonna go.
Yeah, I'm gonna go sell
some lubricants.
I'll see you later.
Hank!
(dog barking)
Yo, Henry.
Yo, I don't want to sound
like a dick,
but George says you're not allowed
in this building no more.
Raul, I just need you
to call Scarlett.
- She's not here.
- Come on, Raul.
- Can't you just call her for me, please?
- I'm telling you, man,
she's not here, for real.
They just left, the whole family.
Do you know where
they were going?
I think they went to
the Gotham Club.
The Gotham Club?
Your sister was here too.
She told me about your dad.
Sorry, buddy.
If there's anything that we can,
you know...
Just, where is it? The Gotham place?
Do you know where it is?
It's on Park and 55th.
Park and 55th.
Thanks, man.
Hold on, man. You can't get in
wearing that bullshit.
So what's your rush?
Uh, I think I really like this girl
and I might have blown it.
Not so fast, hot shot.
Let me tell you something
about women...
never to be trusted
for a second.
I once had
a huge property...
swimming pool, tennis court,
waterfall.
It was like heaven on earth, man.
And this Svengali bitch
took me for everything.
Sorry to hear that, uh, Rajib.
Let me tell you something, kiddo:
"Run"!
Run like Seabiscuit, okay?
And don't look back.
Never look back.
Here we are, tiger.
That will be... nine-seventy-five.
- Thanks for the advice.
- Anytime.
Nine-seventy-five... 10 bucks.
25 cent tip. Now I can retire.
Cheap bastard.
- May I help you, sir?
- Yeah, I'm here to see Scarlett Dowling.
- I think she's here already.
- Sir, if you're meeting the Dowling’s,
you cannot come into the club
without the correct attire... coat and tie,
no jeans, no sneakers.
Look, I don't suppose you'd
just let me run up there...
- and give her a message quickly?
- I'm afraid not.
How about this?
I'll let you hold my ID.
Sir, this isn't a night club.
No, right.
I like your work.
Hey, boys.
Just another night on the job...
waitin', getting' food...
Takin' my break, guys.
[Meredith]:
I cannot believe he ordered...
You know, you're incorrigible.
- Henry?
- I need to talk to you.
Couldn't you have just called?
I'm sorry to barge in on you
like this, Mrs. Dowling,
but I really need to talk to Scarlett.
Can I borrow her for a second?
Did you get dressed as a chef
just to get in here?
Yes, sir, I did.
(laughs)
I like it.
You're the chap who
saved Buck, aren't you?
The doorman, Phillip.
Is there a problem, Mrs. Dowling?
Mother, don't.
I don't believe this man
belongs in the club.
I'm so sorry, Mrs. Dowling.
Sir, you need to leave.
Wait a second.
Scarlett, hear me out.
And if you don't ever want to
talk to me again, that's fine,
but what I said before
was bullshit.
I don't care that you're Fifth Avenue
and I'm Flatbush. It doesn't matter.
I haven't stopped
thinking about you...
since that first time I saw you
getting out of the elevator.
And you know what?
I don't care who knows it,
or what anybody else thinks.
And maybe I'll never be rich,
and maybe I'll never be a member
of a fancy club,
but none of that matters to me.
That's very touching.
Mmm. Come on, let's go.
Let go of him.
Mother, I'm leaving
with Henry.
Scarlett, you will do nothing of the sort.
Come back here and sit down.
Why, Mother? Because you're afraid
I'm going to embarrass you?
Look, everyone.
Meredith Dowling's daughter
is leaving with the doorman.
Don't worry. He's not
a doorman anymore.
Mother had him fired.
- Scarlett, come back here.
- Meredith...
be quiet.
Let them be.
Scarlett.
Henry.
How are you?
Not too bad.
How are you doing, Buck?
Just trying to stay sober.
Every day's a struggle.
Nice to see you, Buck.
We were just leaving.
Okay.
Gretchen?
You're a hooker.
Hey, you're not a hooker.
Come on.
- Promise?
- Yeah.
Well, that went well.
Gotta gift, hesitate...
Never make
the same mistakes...
If he could only see
the person...
If he could only stay
the same...
Sweetheart...
I could help you...
Open and unfurl.
[Raul]:
She sure is beautiful.
Oh, thanks, baby.
No, I was talking about
Lady Liberty.
Not that you're not
beautiful and all.
It's just, you know,
being up under her torch,
she sort of makes us
all feel equal.
Black or white,
rich or poor,
- Mets or Yankees.
- Jets or Giants.
- Nicks or Nets.
- Rangers or Islanders.
- Nice.
- Broadway or peep shows.
Broadway or peep shows?
Lower East
or Crown Heights.
- That's better.
- That's my baby.
- Queen of the Concrete...
- Cab or subway.
With heels on your small feet...
Your head at an angle...
Like you know
something... thing...
Like you know something...
And the car
takes a right turn...
It rolls to a slow burn...
And you start shaking...
Because it's just what
you do do...
It's just what you do...
Little hula girl...
Absorbing the world...
And you can swing
your round hips...
Make the grass skirt swirl...
Oh, little hula girl...
You're not a plastic pearl...
And it'll all spin around you...
On a tilted world...
Oh, you never even make
a sound sound...
You never make a sound...
Does it ever get you
down down?
Does it ever get you down?
You know it
when you wake up...
Put on your shirt
and go out...
You should know the way
by heart...
Now we hardly even know it
when it's gone...
The days, the nights,
truck in...
You hardly even guard
yourself to breathe...
He calls you in the morning...
And you would never
change it for the world...
Hard days keep moving in...
I'm a teenager...
I am anxious
in repose...
(vocalizing)
If somebody were gonna
lay down...
You wouldn't even try,
now would you?
We used to be
the fighters here...
We didn't want it anymore...
Since that
we're giving up now...
Didn't even try to support it...
No one ever reaches there...
No one ever reaches there
at all...
Hard days keep coming...
I'm tense...
I'm anxious in repose...
I changed,
I came home.
(vocalizing)
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org