Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
That was right behind me.
Did he have red hair?
Yes. Kind of reddish brown.
- Tall man?
- Six feet.
And a moustache?
Yes.
You mean me.
Remember? We talked at the hospital.
We were on the other side of the plane.
Sorry.
Since it happened, I get confused.
Anyone else remember that row?
21C was three rows ahead of me.
They were smashed flat.
Can anyone else help?
Go ahead, say something.
- Anyone else have information?
- Stop it.
Just let her go.
Why?
This isn't doing anybody any good.
She only wants to know what happened.
My son died.
Yes, but you know how he died.
You were with him.
When was the last time you saw your son?
His birthday, about a month before.
I don't remember kissing him good-bye.
I know I did, but I just can't remember.
You're very young.
I'm not young.
How old was your boy?
He was almost two.
I'm sorry.
He wasn't with you very long.
Jesus Christ!
This is sadistic.
And we're not accomplishing anything!
Do you remember me?
I'm Lisa. The flight attendant.
I really wanted to see you.
I came here mostly to see you.
I think about you and your baby a lot.
Do you remember how I tried to help you
with the seat belt?
Help me?
You told me everything would be okay.
You think you helped me?
Well, I tried.
Tried!
You told me to hold him. I couldn't.
You told me everything would be okay.
It wasn't!
Please, don't say that.
I didn't...
I didn't know!
You didn't know what?
Please.
You told me to hold him.
- You knew I couldn't!
- It's not my fault!
We're not here to blame each other.
You said everything would be okay...
...and it wasn't!
He died!
You want everybody to talk.
But only if it's nice things.
No, that's not true.
My son died!
And blaming her won't bring
your baby back.
Of course they think it's fair.
So what? What do you think?
I'm being fucked.
The big law firms are getting
much more for their clients.
I'll get another lawyer.
Mr. Brillstein, I heard a woman got
$2 million for her dead baby.
I think I should get at least that.
I'll call you. I'll call you every day.
Good-bye.
You have to understand...
...they owe us. They kill them
and they have to pay.
You don't understand a fucking thing!
I understand, Manny.
I understand that I'm alone.
So, pain and suffering are compensabLe.
Apart from the other compensable losses
such as...
...the $2-million Nutty Nick stores contract.
We didn't have a contract.
- Whose side are you on?
- Relax.
Don't tell me to relax. You have a husband
and a partnership insurance.
I have...
...a deposition from...
...Mr. Nutty Nick...
...that he had every intention...
...of hiring Mr. Gordon and Mr. Klein.
That's good enough.
He's lying.
It's nice, but he's lying.
All right.
Do me a favor.
Don't say that.
They don't have to know your opinion,
okay?
Work with me on this, Mr. Klein.
I'm sorry.
You promised to do your best
for Mrs. Gordon and her children.
You get a third of what we get?
I know. I'm terrible.
One-third is standard, Mr. Klein.
It's in my interest to get
as large a settlement as possible.
In fact, that's my job.
I don't apologize for it.
No, this is America in the '90s.
Nobody apologizes anymore.
They write a memoir.
This is the law. Not some trick I invented.
Each minute that you and Mr. Gordon
knew that you were going to die...
...is compensable as pain and suffering.
Testify...
...to the mental anguish...
...that you and Mr. Gordon experienced...
...and each minute is worth dollars.
Big dollars. Dollars to which
you and Mrs. Gordon are entitled.
What you really want me to say...
...is that Jeff wept at the prospect
of his wife widowed and kids orphaned.
It's a shame he died instantly.
If only he'd been mashed up and died...
...slowly in my arms, Nan...
Jesus, Max!
...could make out on this.
Fine. Good night.
Are you ashamed of me?
I'm trying to get money, so I don't meet
your standards of widowhood?
Let me ask you something.
If Jeff was here, what would he do?
Come on, Max, tell me.
I can't lie.
If you died and he had lived, what would
he say to help Laura and Jonah?
I know he ripped you off for the tickets.
Maybe!
Maybe he'd pay him back.
Are you punishing Jeff?
I'll say what you want.
Let it go.
I can Let it go.
I can't live as a coward.
Oh, fuck.
So I argued that it wasn't fair to us
and he agreed.
He just said, "Life is unfair."
So now the test's next week
and it's on Europe, not Central America.
I think he proved his own point.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
What'd you do today, Dad?
Go ahead.
Tell him.
What? What'd you do?
Talk to me.
Tell me what's going on.
Talk to me!
Each day you have to jump off a roof
or stand before a train to lose your fear?
Is that it?
What about me?
What about Jonah?
- You're like a crazy person.
- I'm not crazy.
I love you. We have lived together
for 16 years!
They've been great.
Oh, not always.
Yes. Always.
They've always been great for me.
Even when I hate you, I know love you.
I know you were happy too.
Remember?
Do you remember our marriage?
Even if I could remember, then what?
How can I live in a memory?
You see, that's cruel.
- Do you know that's cruel?
- That's the truth.
The truth?
You didn't tell Jonah the truth.
It was unfair to use him that way.
Fair?
Am I supposed to let you kill yourself?
I walked away from that crash alive.
That's what survived.
The taste and touch and beauty of life.
But I love that.
- I won't give that up!
- I don't want you to give it up!
Let me in.
Let me be part of it.
You can't.
- I wish I'd been on that plane.
- I'm grateful you weren't.
You don't make sense. You said
it was extraordinary, so beautiful.
You're right. I don't make sense
and I don't want to.
I know that what you found is...
...special, whatever it is,
and wherever it leads you, it's thrilling.
But there must be a way...
...to live with it so it does make sense.
I'm going to survive this.
I can't fight for you anymore. You want
to destroy yourself? I can't stop you.
I hope you make it.
You been dreaming a lot?
- You bet.
- Me too.
Were you alone on the plane?
No, I was with my best friend. My partner.
He was decapitated.
You saw him?
I should be going.
Thanks for coming.
You know, if...
If Manny has any interest
in doing carpentry full time...
...I could talk to some people.
They'd be happy to work
with somebody like him.
Don't talk about my husband.
Sorry.
No, it's all right.
I'm angry with him, that's all.
Don't look so scared.
I'm not scared.
I'm not scared of anything.
Scared to kiss me.
I just did kiss you.
I mean, for real.
I didn't want to offend you.
You're right.
I don't want to be kissed.
I don't want anything.
But I do want to go with you
next time you take a drive.
I'm missing it.
Look at this show!
It's beautiful.
Kate is so serious, isn't she?
Oh, look!
Adorable!
Bravo!
Beautiful!
Wonderful! Wonderful!
Wonderful!
FoLks, this is the captain here.
We're going to make an emergency Landing
at BakersfieLd Airport.
Fasten your seatbeLts before touchdown.
At that time...
...you'LL hear me say the words,
"Brace, brace, brace."
Hi, this is Nan. I'LL caLLyou back
as soon as possibLe.
Get into the crash positions
which your cabin attendants wiLL iLLustrate.
I'm not going to kid you,
it's going to be rough...
...maybe worse than that.
Pay attention to what
the cabin attendants say.
Good Luck to us aLL.
- May we be excused?
- Bring a bag of chips.
Let's play computer games.
Let them go.
It's a mistake to make them
anything but hamburgers.
Next time we'll have relish and ketchup.
What can you do? I don't mind,
as long as they're happy.
If we'll have Thanksgiving, let's do it right.
Max, don't play superdad.
Byron, honey, no.
Give me this. Give me this.
- This is garbage.
- What're you doing?
Go back to the table and finish!
- Max, calm down.
- I'm perfectly calm.
Listen to me. I'm throwing this out.
When you die, you don't get another life.
- Do you understand?
- It's not real dying. It's pretend.
- I know what dead bodies look like.
- Shut up!
It's going in the garbage.
- He's only a little boy.
- Lf it was up to you, he'd stay a boy.
I don't care!
Don't be cruel.
I don't want him to grow up
a frightened child in a man's body.
He's just fine, Max.
It's you who is in trouble!
Now give the game back.
Or keep on going,
but right out of our lives!
Our son is innocent.
Do you want to crash our marriage?
Okay, but don't hurt our son.
I'm not scared to end our marriage.
Neither am I.
Then I'll keep on going.
Good.
- Where to?
- Beautiful downtown Oakland.
Such a shame.
It was going to be gentrified and rebuilt.
Then the recession hit.
The country's falling apart.
The United States is finished.
But you and me...
...we're in peak condition.
You hungry?
In there?
Remember, we're ghosts.
They can't do anything to us.
You're really nuts. You are so crazy.
You should talk.
I can't believe you did that!
I'm not buying you another.
Look at this mess.
I've had it. We're going home.
So happy.
Maybe I am a ghost.
I was going to buy him a lot of presents.
Let's do it. Let's buy them.
What did he like?
How about a sword?
My son used to love swords.
He still does, but he's too old to admit it.
- What?
- What would your son like?
Does he play with Legos?
No, he's too young.
Bristle Blocks? Does he have those?
Babies can use them
and older kids like them.
You want me to buy a present for Bubble?
Bubble. Is that really his name?
It's Leonardo. I called him Bubble.
I can't buy him gifts. That's sick.
- Why?
- Because he's dead.
- Of course he's dead.
- You're not serious.
You wouldn't do this to me.
Would you buy a present
for your dead father?
My father?
I never bought him anything.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it. I just don't think
it's a good idea.
I made him something in school.
Carved his name in wood.
Made a little nameplate
that you put on your desk.
I was 13 when he died and...
...never had a chance to buy him
a real present.
Let's do it.
Let's buy presents for the dead.
Come on. Let's buy presents for the dead.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can.
Come on!
Who'll we give them to?
He liked to build things: Shelves, chairs.
He made our dining-room table.
Sometimes he'd give me a hammer,
let me do the easy stuff.
This is it. This is what he'd like.
Every time we came into a hardware store,
he'd stop in front of these.
It wasn't as magnificent as this one.
He'd be...
...totally silent...
...and then he'd say...
..."I'd like to have that"...
...and walk away.
Only thing I ever heard him say he wanted.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
I'd like to buy this for my father.
That's nice. I'll take care of that.
I've got to get him a monster.
He loves them.
I'll find him something.
Come here.
Look at this. This is great.
Do you mind?
Sorry.
Look what I have for us.
A beautiful bevy of desserts.
Now...
...this.
- Don't want any.
- We could use it as a paperweight.
I want that.
This is the only thing you can't have.
Now I have several other magical...
I have a magic mushroom for you.
Or better yet...
...the beautiful simplicity...
...of a ripe strawberry.
Let's dance.
Come on.
I don't dance.
Come on!
Pick up.
Hold on!
Oh, please, please, please.
Good night.
So I'll pick you up?
My goodness, it's night.
Where are we going?
We could disappear.
You all right?
What's wrong?
What?
There's something I have to tell you.
You got to promise
you'll never tell anyone.
All right.
All right, calm down now.
What is it?
What?
I want to tell you something
that nobody knows.
Do you remember...
...just when we touched ground and
it was like we were going to land okay?
What?
I let go of Bubble.
I had him in my lap.
I looked at the road and...
...I thought we were going to be safe,
and the wheels bumped.
I opened my arms.
I was safe in my belt, but he wasn't.
Oh, I see. It was your fault?
It wasn't the accident?
- I wasn't holding him!
- You killed your baby?
And the lawyer...
- Brillstein?
...I didn't tell him the truth.
I understand. So you're also a liar?
Yes, I lied! I lied to Father Conti.
I lied in the confessional.
I lied to the whole church!
- It wasn't your fault.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Carla, it's not your fault.
"Hail, Mary, full of grace...
"...the Lord is with Thee.
Blessed art Thou amongst women...
"...and blessed is the fruit
of Thy womb Jesus."
Carla, I didn't mean
that you killed your baby.
Carla, you're not to blame.
You couldn't have held on to your baby.
We were going hundreds of miles an hour!
Of course you think it's your fault.
God gave you a child.
It was your job to keep him safe.
But it's not your fault!
Stop it now! Come on, stop it!
That's enough!
Oh, shit.
Now what have I done?
Come on now.
I want you to get in the back.
Come on.
Come on now.
Just get in the back now.
This is your baby.
No, hold it upright, like this.
I know it doesn't look like a baby.
It looks like a toolbox.
It is a toolbox.
I want you to pretend
that this is your baby.
Pretend it's Bubble.
Now this is your chance to hold on tight...
...to save him.
Hold on to Bubble!
As tight as you can!
Pray to God to give you the strength
to save your baby.
Hold on to your baby!
Holy Mary, Mother of God!
Pray for us now
and at the hour of our death!
Right behind you. Careful, please.
Mrs. Rodrigo, how are you doing?
I'm okay.
It's whiplash. I was with Max.
I know. He's in intensive care.
He'll be all right.
Just between us...
...what happened?
He was showing me something.
What? That brick walls are hard?
How'd you get here so fast?
My beeper went off,
I was just two blocks away.
I don't know. I've been really lucky lately.
I mean, I know it's terrible...
...to talk about luck
when you've suffered so.
Have you seen a doctor yet?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
- What happened?
- Mr. Klein drove into a brick wall.
You don't understand.
The flight attendant told me
to hold Bubble.
I thought I didn't hold him tight enough.
I wasn't sure my hands were clasped
when we hit.
Be careful about what we're not sure of.
I thought I could save him.
Max showed me I couldn't.
- There was no way.
- He crashed the car on purpose?
Yes, to show me.
That's it.
That fucking nut ain't coming close to you!
- Let me talk to you.
- It's out of control.
Listen, our case is good. Actually,
we could improve our numbers here.
You must be Jonah.
I'm a friend of your daddy's.
Is your mom home?
Yeah, come in. Mom!
- A woman's here to see you.
- I know.
Go to your room.
Go to your room!
I'm Carla.
I know who you are.
This is a very nice house that you have.
Please sit down.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to bother you like this...
...but I thought that it would be good
if we talked.
I called the hospital.
They said that Max is doing okay.
I don't think he's doing okay.
How are you?
I'm okay.
I really wasn't hurt.
You know, I came by because I...
...I just wanted to say, you know...
...I can imagine what you must be feeling...
...about what has happened.
Really?
You can?
You have every right to be angry with me.
I'm not angry with you.
Why should I be? Wasn't it Max's idea?
- What he did was crazy.
- He must be very much in love with you...
...to risk his life for you.
- It's not like that.
Isn't that love?
No.
Look, I'm sorry.
I didn't come to argue with you.
I think I better go. I'm sorry.
Please stay.
I am very sorry about your little boy.
Thank you.
You know...
...when he died...
...I had nothing.
I couldn't feel anything.
Now I can feel something.
I can feel something inside
besides the pain for Bubble.
That's because of Max.
He would talk to me.
He'd talk to me like nobody else ever has.
We would have these great conversations...
...and they were weird,
but they were so exciting and...
It's not what you think.
He's my friend.
He's my best friend.
It's like God sent him to me.
It's like he sent me my own angel.
Let me be honest with you.
Maybe this wonderful friendship
that you have...
...might have helped you.
But it hasn't helped Max.
Maybe our marriage is over...
...but I have a son
and I want him to have a father.
Max is not an angel.
He's a man.
He cannot survive up there.
Hey, you.
How're you doing?
I got you these chocolates.
That's what they give patients.
Here.
- How's your head?
- Hurts!
I just...
I've really wanted to tell you how much...
I just wanted to say
how wonderful you are.
You look happy.
You know, it's probably
because Manny moved out.
I told him to.
Are you all right with that?
You know...
...I visited Bubble's grave.
For the first time, it was okay.
I'm glad.
But you know...
...things can't go back
to the way that they were.
You know what I mean?
I want you to go home, Max.
I want you to live again.
I'm not a ghost anymore.
I can't get back.
Yes, you can.
I don't want to.
I wish I could help you.
We could disappear, Carla.
I can't anymore.
I'm back.
I want to try living
on planet Earth for a while.
You can't save everybody, Max.
You got to try taking care of yourself.
Say good-bye, Max.
Good-bye? Why do we have
to say good-bye?
It has to be that way.
I don't want to say good-bye.
Just...
Just say it like it means nothing.
Good-bye, Max.
Please, Max.
Say it.
Good-bye, Carla.
"The soul comes to the end
of it's long journey...
"...and naked and alone...
"...draws near to the divine."
How're you feeling?
Okay.
101.4.
Let's see.
Are you going to stay?
I don't know. We'll see.
Sorry about the video game.
It's okay. You didn't break it.
Good.
What is it?
I want you to save me.
These are for you.
You're here! Great.
Listen, it may be premature.
I don't want to jinx it but I think
I'll have it all locked up tomorrow.
So, champagne, assorted goodies.
A little celebration.
It's an incredible story.
Because of your suicide attempt,
don't argue that...
That's how I presented it, that you were
suffering from post-traumatic stress...
...and that they were going to be
on the hook if you killed yourself.
I know, I'm terrible.
What a situation.
What am I going to do?
It's incredible!
Anyway, today I hondled with InterCity's
lawyer for two hours and we got close...
...really close, to big dollars for you,
Mrs. Gordon and Mrs. Rodrigo.
But I think we're going to make out
like bandits.
I know, I'm horrible, but listen to this:
An hour after the call...
...from the airline lawyer,
I get one from the insurance carrier.
What a situation!
I'm mean, I know.
I'm terrible to take advantage...
...but there's been a fuck up
in their communication.
They both think they're the one
who's been designated to deal with me.
So I played dumb.
Started doing numbers with
the insurance guy and his offer is higher!
Millions, we're talking millions!
Oh, shit!
This is it.
This is the moment of my death.
We'll make it, Max.
He's going to bring us in.
- He'll bring us in.
- There's a boy alone up there.
I'm going to sit with him.
It's going to be okay.
Everything's okay.
Now, put your head down.
Close your eyes.
It'll be over soon.
Everything's wonderful.
In the kitchen, there is a phone!
It's an emergency! It's an allergic reaction!
Stop it! What's happening? Dad!
No, Max! No!
I'm alive!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org