Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
~ To be lies ~
~ And all the joy ~
~ Within you dies ~
~ Don't you want
somebody to love ~
~ Don't you need
~ Wouldn't you love
somebody to love ~
~ You better find
~ Love ~
~
1965.
The great San Francisco acid wave.
~ When the garden flowers ~
I recall one night in a place
called the Matrix. There I was--
- ~
- Mother of God. There I am.
Holy fuck.
Uh, clearly I was a victim
of the drug explosion...
a natural street freak
just eating whatever came by.
Does anybody want some LSD ?
I got all the makin's...
right here !
All I need is a place to cook.
I decided to eat only
half of the acid at first...
but I spilled the rest on the sleeve
of my red woolen shirt.
What's the trouble ?
Well, all this white stuff...
on my sleeve...
is LSD.
With a bit of luck...
his life
was ruined forever...
always thinking that just behind some
narrow door in all his favorite bars...
men in red woolen shirts...
are getting incredible kicks
from things he'll never know.
~
Strange memories on
this nervous night in Las Vegas.
Has it been five years ? Six ?
It seems like a lifetime, the kind
of peak that never comes again.
~ Love is but
a song we're singin' ~
San Francisco
in the middle '60s...
was a very special time and place
to be a part of...
- but no explanation...
- ~ We can make the mountains ring ~
no mix of words
or music or memories...
can touch that sense of knowing
that you were there and alive...
in that corner of time in the world,
whatever it meant.
~ Though the bird
is on the wing ~
~ And you may not
know why ~
There was madness
in any direction...
- ~ Come on, people, now ~
- at any hour.
- ~ Smile on your brothers ~
- You could strike sparks anywhere.
~ Everybody get together ~
- ~ Try to love one another ~
- There was a fantastic
universal sense...
that whatever we were doing was right,
that we were winning.
And that, I think,
was the handle.
~ Some may come
and some may go ~
That sense
of inevitable victory...
over the forces
of old and evil.
Not in any mean or military sense--
we didn't need that.
Our energy
would simply prevail.
We had all the momentum.
We were riding the crest
of a high and beautiful wave.
- So now, less than five years later...
- ~
you can go up a steep hill
in Las Vegas and look west...
and with the right kind
of eyes...
you can almost see
the high-water mark...
that place where the wave
finally broke...
and rolled back.
- ~ Try to love one another right now ~
~
- ~ Want some whiskey in your water ~
- Room service !
- ~ Some sugar in your tea ~
~ What's all these crazy questions
they're askin' me ~
- Good morning, sir.
- ~ This is the craziest party
there could ever be ~
What do you want, man ?
What do you want ?
- Room service.
- Get out.
- ~ Mama told me not to come ~
- You're in the wrong room.
Get the fuck out !
- I've got a gun. It's not mine, really.
- ~ Mama told me not to come ~
- Uh, the-- the-- the bill.
- What ?
- Will you... s-sign for it ?
- Yeah, I'll get it. Hurry up.
Don't move, man.
Be very still.
There we go.
Say nothing
to no one, man.
~ Open up the window
Let some air into this room ~
The decision
to flee came suddenly. Or maybe not.
- ~ That cigarette you're smokin'
'bout scared me half to death ~
- Maybe I'd planned it all along,
subconsciously waiting
for the right moment.
- ~ Mama told me not to come ~
- The bill was a factor, I think...
- because I had no money to pay for it.
- ~ Mama told me not to come ~
Our room service tabs had been
running somewhere between
29 and 36 dollars per hour...
- ~ That ain't the way
to have fun, son ~
- for 48 consecutive hours.
- Incredible.
- ~ That ain't the way to have fun ~
How could it happen ?
But by the time I asked this question,
there was no one around to answer it.
That rotten attorney of mine,
Dr. Gonzo, was gone.
He must have sensed trouble.
Hmm ? Ohh.
A "Z" ?
Panic.
It crept up my spine like
first-rising vibes of an acid frenzy.
- All these horrible realities
began to dawn on me.
Oh, fuck.
Here I was...
alone in Las Vegas,
completely twisted on drugs.
No cash,
no story for the magazine...
and on top of everything else
I had a gigantic goddamn
hotel bill to deal with.
I didn't even know
who'd won the race.
- Maybe nobody.
How would Horatio Alger
have handled this situation ?
Stay calm.
I'm a relatively
respectable citizen.
- Multiple felon, perhaps,
but certainly not dangerous.
- Taxi !
Luckily I had taken the soap
and grapefruit and other luggage
out to the car earlier.
Now--
it was only a matter
of slipping the noose.
Hey ! Here, take this.
All right.
- Mr. Duke ! Mr. Duke !
- Oh, shit.
- We've been looking for you.
- The game was up. They had me.
Many fine books have been written
in prison, huh ?
- Sir ?
- What ?
Um, this telegram
came for you.
Actually, it's not for you.
It's for somebody named, uh, Thompson.
But it says, "Care of Raoul Duke."
Do you-- Do you--
- Does that mean anything ?
- Yes, yes, it means a lot. Thanks.
- Yeah, I checked the register
for this man Thompson.
We don't show him, but I figured
he might be part of your team.
-He is. Don't worry. I'll get it to him.
-Yeah.
Um, what confused us
was, uh...
Dr. Gonzo's signature
on the telegram from Los Angeles
when we knew he was right here.
Right.
You did the right thing.
Never try to understand a press message.
About half the time, we use codes.
Especially with Dr. Gonzo.
See ya.
- Um, tell me.
When will the doctor
be awake ?
- Awake ? What do you mean ?
- Well, um...
my manager, Mr. Heem,
would like to meet him.
It's nothing unusual, um--
Mr. Heem likes to meet
all of our large accounts...
put'em on a personal basis,
you know ?
Just a chat and a handshake.
You understand.
Of course,
but if I were you...
I would leave the doctor alone
until after he's eaten his breakfast...
because he's
a very crude man.
Jesus God !
- No !
But he will be available,
huh, maybe later this morning ?
Look, the telegram
is actually all scrambled.
It's actually from Thompson,
not to him.
All right ? Now, I've got to go.
I've gotta get to the race.
- B-But there's no hurry.
The race is over.
- Not for me.
Well, um--
Let's have lunch !
Righty-o, man.
Righty-o.
- ~ Now, the bricks
lay on Grand Street ~
- Jesus.
Bad waves of paranoia.
Madness. Fear and loathing.
Intolerable vibrations
in this place. Get out.
The weasels were closing in.
I could smell the ugly brutes.
Do me one last favor, Lord.
Just give me five more high-speed hours
before You bring the hammer down.
Just let me get rid of this goddamn car
and off this horrible desert.
~ Oh, Mama ~
~ Is this really the end ~
- ~ To be stuck inside of Mobile ~
- Oh, you evil bastard.
- ~ With the Memphis blues again ~
- This is Your work.
You better take care of me, Lord.
- If You don't, You're
gonna have me on Your hands.
- Pull over ! Pull over !
- Hey !
Good morning. How are you ?
All right, man. Doing very well.
Few people understand the psychology
of dealing with a highway traffic cop.
Your normal speeder will panic
and immediately pull over to the side.
This is wrong.
It arouses contempt in the cop heart.
Make the bastard chase you.
He will follow.
But he won't know what to make
of your blinker signal that says
you're about to turn right.
This is to let him know you're
pulling off for a proper place to talk.
It'll take him a moment
to realize he's about to make
a 180-degree turn, at speed.
It'll take him a moment
to realize he's about to make
a 180-degree turn, at speed.
But you will be ready.
Brace for the "G"s.
Fast heel-toe work.
Hi. How are you ?
Just what in the hell
did you think you were doing ?
I wanna know.
Let me see your license.
Oh, yeah, of course.
There you are.
Oh, my gosh.
It's me.
May I please have that ?
I knew I was fucked.
See you have two cases of beer,
a basket of grapefruit...
stack of T-shirts and towels,
light bulbs.
- You realize what you did
when you drive like that ?
- Yeah, I know. I'm guilty.
I understand that. I knew it
was a crime. I did it anyway.
Shit, why argue ?
I'm a fucking criminal. Look at me.
You have
a strange attitude.
Maybe.
You know, I have a feeling
you need to take a nap.
There's a rest area
just up ahead.
I'd like you to go up there,
pull over and get a few hours' sleep.
That's not gonna help me.
I've been awake for too long.
Three or four nights, maybe.
Can't even remember.
I go to sleep now,
I'm dead for 20 hours.
What are you carrying
two cases of soap for, son ?
I wanna stay clean.
No.
Here's how it is.
What I put in my book,
as of noon...
is that I apprehended you
for driving too fast.
- I advised you to proceed
to the next rest area.
- ~
Stop !
I advised you to proceed
to the next rest area--
your stated destination, right ?
And take a long nap.
Do I make myself clear ?
Well...
how far is Baker ?
I was sort of hoping to,
I don't know, stop there for lunch.
It's not my jurisdiction.
City limits end 2.2 miles
beyond the rest area.
Can you make it that far ?
I'll try.
I've been wanting to go to Baker for
a long time. Yeah. Heard a lot about it.
Excellent seafood.
You know, I'm thinkin',
a guy with your kind of mind...
ought to try
the land-crab.
- Excellent seafood.
- Land-crab.
All right. Why not ?
Thanks for the tip.
Look at me in the eyes.
Everything all right ?
May I have a little kiss
before you go ?
I'm very lonely here.
~ Oh, Mama ~
~ Can this really
be the end ~
I felt raped.
The pig had done me on all fronts.
And now he was going off to chuckle
about it on the west side of town...
waiting for me
to make a run for L.A.
Why, yes, Officer. Of course
I'll take advantage of that rest area.
And I can't tell you how grateful
I am for this break you wanna give me.
Get a grip, man.
If I boom straight for L.A.,
he'll bust me for sure.
No. This was not the time
for a showdown.
This was Death Valley.
Oh, fuck !
Sweet Jesus, it's him.
Oh, my God !
~
Shit !
Come on, you fucking bastard.
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
I've got to go. I've got to--
~
Well, they've nailed me,
goddamn it.
I'm trapped in some stinking
desert crossroads called Baker.
I don't have much time, man.
The fuckers are closing in.
- They'll hunt me down
like a fucking beast.
- You sound paranoid.
I need a fucking lawyer
immediately !
What are you doing in Baker ?
Didn't you get my telegram ?
What telegram, you worthless bastard ?
I'll cripple your ass for this.
You brainless scumbag,
you're supposed to be in Vegas.
I rented a suite
at the Flamingo.
You're supposed to be covering the
National District Attorney's conference.
- I made all the reservations.
Everything is arranged.
Now, what the fuck are you doing out
there in the middle of the desert ?
Nothing. Never mind.
It's all a big joke.
I'm actually, uh-- I'm poolside
at the Flamingo right now...
talking through a portable phone some
dwarf brought out from the casino.
Yeah, I have total credit here.
Don't come anywhere
near this place, you bastard.
Foreigners
aren't welcome here.
Well, this is how
the world works.
All energy flows according
to the whims of the Great Magnet.
What a fool I was
to defy him.
I was going back to Vegas.
I had no choice.
I had to get rid
of the Shark.
Too many people might recognize it,
especially the Vegas police.
Luckily, my credit card
was still technically valid.
Now this
was a superior machine.
Ten grand worth of gimmicks
and high-priced special effects.
The rear windows leapt up with a touch
like frogs in a dynamite pond.
The dashboard was full of esoteric
lights and dials and meters...
that I would never understand.
If the pigs
were gathering in Vegas...
I felt the drug culture
should be represented as well.
And there was a certain bent appeal in
the notion of running a savage burn...
on one Las Vegas hotel...
and then just wheeling across town
and checking into another.
Me and a thousand ranking cops
from all over America.
Why not move confidently
into their midst ?
- Welcome to the Flamingo Hotel, sir.
- Sir ?
Yeah, hi. Right. Okay.
~ Let me stay in your arms ~
~ I'm addicted to your charms ~
~ You're gettin' to be
a habit with me ~
~ I used to think your love
was something that I ~
~ Could take ~
- ~ Or leave alone ~
- My arrival was badly timed.
~ But now I couldn't do
without my supply ~
~ I need you for my own ~
~
This here model
is one that we had to use...
when we took on them little peckerheads
down there at Kent State.
This baby here--
I'm a police chief
from Michigan.
Look, fella, I have
explained to you.
I have this postcard which says that
I have a reservation in this hotel.
I'm very sorry, sir,
but you're on the late list.
- So your reservation
has been transferred to...
- It's okay.
the... Moonlight Motel...
which is just out
on Paradise Boulevard.
We've already paid
for our goddamn room !
It's actually a very fine
place of lodging, and it's
only 16 blocks from here.
It has a pool,
sauna, steam.
You listen to me,
you filthy little faggot !
I want a manager down here,
now, now !
Because I'm sick of listening
to your dog shit !
- I am... very sorry, sir.
- Get off of me ! Get away from me !
- Can I call you a cab ?
Sure, and I'll call you
a cocksucker !
Of course, I could hear what
the clerk was really saying.
Listen, you fuzzy
little shithead !
I've been fucked around
in my time...
by a fairly good
cross section...
of mean-tempered,
rule-crazy cops...
and now...
it's my turn.
So fuck you, Officer.
I'm in charge.
Hey, listen, I really hate
to interrupt, but I wonder
if I could slide on through.
The name is Raoul Duke. I think
my attorney made the reservations.
Duke, Raoul.
- Certainly, sir.
My bags-- My bags are out there in
that white Cadillac convertible there.
Maybe somebody could
bring it to the room for me.
Oh, yeah, uh, let me get
a quart of Wild Turkey...
- two-fifths of Bacardi...
- some ice for the room, and let's see--
- You just calm down !
Shit, let's try some lime chunks.
What do you think ?
I say okay.
- You don't worry about a thing.
- Now, calm down.
You don't hesitate
to call me-- Sven.
All right, Sven.
- Thank you very much.
- You-- You--
- I know, I know, I know.
It's hideous. You're gonna
be fine, though. You're doing well.
I'll see you later.
Wait. Don't touch it.
- Good night. Pardon me. Bye, Sven.
- Look what you did !
Look what you did !
Goddamn you, we wouldn't stay
in this hotel if you begged us !
~ Magic moments ~
~ When two hearts are caring ~
- ~ Magic moments ~
- ~ Memories we've been sharing ~
- Home, sweet home.
- Whoa. What kind of sick shit--
Oh, shit !
- Shit. What the fuck ?
Stop, stop, stop.
Ow ! She's biting my leg off !
You degenerate pig. Please !
- Can't be helped.
-My fucking leg !
-That's "Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds."
Lucy, be cool,
goddamn it.
Remember what happened
at the airport, okay ? Come on.
No more of that, okay ?
That's my client, Lucy.
That's Mr. Duke,
the famous journalist.
He's paying for this suite, Lucy.
He's on our side.
He loves artists.
Lucy paints portraits
of Barbra Streisand.
Yeah. Right ?
Um, I drew these from TV.
Really.
She came
all the way down--
- What's the name of that town ?
- Montana.
Montana. Just to give
these portraits to Barbra.
We're goin' over to the Americana
tonight to meet her backstage.
I desperately needed peace, rest...
sanctuary.
I hadn't counted on this:
finding my attorney on acid
and locked into some kind
of preternatural courtship.
Well...
they must have, uh,
brought the car around by now.
So...
why don't, uh...
ou-yay and... I-ay...
o-gay and, uh,
et-gay the...
uff-stay...
out of the unk-tray.
Absolutely. Yeah.
Let's get the stuff.
We'll be right back, Lucy.
- Give me a kiss ? One kiss, one kiss.
- No.
- No. No.
- One kiss. Why not ?
Okay.
Don't answer the phone.
God bless.
Well, what are your plans ?
Plans ?
- The child in the bedroom.
- Oh, Lucy.
I met her on the plane.
Yeah.
She's a religious freak.
I gave her a cap
before I realized--
Jesus, she's never
even had a drink.
Well, it'll probably work out.
We can keep her loaded, and then
peddle her ass at the drug convention.
Yeah, she's perfect
for this gig.
These cops'll go 50 bucks a head
to beat her into submission
and then gang-fuck her.
We can set her up in one
of these backstreet motels...
hang pictures of Jesus
all over the room, and then turn
these fucking pigs loose on her.
Hell, she's strong, man.
She'll hold her own.
Jesus Christ,
I knew you were sick...
but I never expected to hear
you actually say that kind of stuff.
- You filthy bastard.
- Straight economics, man.
This girl's a godsend.
Shit. She could
make us a grand a day.
That's ugly, man.
Stop talking like that.
Well, I figure she can do
about four at a time.
If we keep her full of acid, that's
more like two grand a day, maybe three.
Hold on, man.
What if I just jump on you
and beat the dog shit out of you ?
Would that make you feel any better,
you filthy bastard ?
All right,
listen to me.
In a few hours, she'll probably
be sane enough to work herself...
into some sort of towering Jesus-based
rage at the hazy recollection...
of being seduced by
some kind of cruel Samoan...
who fed her liquor and LSD,
dragged her to a Vegas hotel room...
and then savagely penetrated
every orifice in her little body...
with his throbbing,
uncircumcised member.
- That's so ugly, man.
- Well, truth hurts.
- That's-- Argh !
- Yeah.
- Argh ! That's argh !
- Argh !
- Argh ?
- Argh.
I wanted to help her, man.
Well, you'll go straight
to the gas chamber for this one.
Even if you manage to beat that,
they'll still send you back to Nevada...
for rape
and consensual sodomy.
No, she's gotta go.
Shit.
It doesn't pay to try to
help somebody these days, huh ?
Let's go.
Yeah. Americana Hotel ?
I need a reservation.
For my... niece.
Look, I want her treated very gently.
She's an artist and--
Fuck off. She might seem
a trifle high-strung.
She's doing her masters thesis
on, uh...
well, Barbra Streisand.
- It's time to meet Barbra.
- Last name ?
I'd rather not say. My brother's
in politics. Yeah, you understand.
I felt like a Nazi,
but it had to be done.
- Yeah, yeah, righto. Okay, yeah. Bye.
~ Yummy, yummy, yummy
I've got love in my tummy ~
- ~ And I feel like loving you ~
~ Love is such a sweet thing
Good enough to eat ~
~ And it's just
what I'm gonna do ~
Lucy was a potentially fatal
millstone on both our necks.
- Hurry the fuck up !
- There was absolutely no choice...
- but to cut her adrift...
- Jesus Christ. Take your time !
and hope her memory
was fucked.
Here's an extra ten bucks.
Make sure she gets there safely.
~
- That's that.
Hey, man, take off slowly.
Don't attract attention.
- ~ Yummy, yummy, yummy
I've got love in my tummy ~
- ~
Let's find a good seafood restaurant
and eat some red salmon.
I feel a powerful lust
for red salmon.
- Oh, no, man. We're gonna be late.
- We gotta go.
Goddamn mescaline.
Why the fuck can't they
make it a little less pure ?
I welcome you...
to the third National
D.A.'s Convention...
on Narcotics
and Dangerous Drugs.
And now,
without further ado...
the man who will define this cancer
eating at the heart of America...
Dr. L. Ron Bumquist.
I saw these bastards in Easy Rider,
but I didn't believe they were real.
Not like this, man,
not hundreds of them.
They're actually pretty nice people
once you get to know them.
Know them ? I know these people
in my goddamn blood.
Don't say that word around here.
You'll get them excited.
- You're right.
- The most efficient way
for us to do this...
is for each one of us...
to try and attempt...
to imagine
what it is like inside...
- of the possessed mind of the addict.
- Hmm ?
For example...
a dope fiend...
refers to the reefer butt...
as a "roach"...
because...
it resembles a cockroach.
What the fuck are these people
talking about ?
You've got to be crazy on acid to think
a joint looks like a goddamn cockroach.
You will notice
that I have distinguished...
four-- four distinct
states of being...
in the cannabis
or marijuana society.
They are cool, groovy...
hip and square.
Seldom, if ever--
- Too crazy, man. Too crazy.
We should get the hell out.
What a fucking nightmare.
If he figures out
what is happening...
then he can rise
one notch...
and become hip.
And then if he can
convince himself...
to approve
of what is happening...
then he becomes groovy.
Groovy.
And then, after that,
he can actually raise himself...
to the rank of cool.
He can become one
of those...
cool guys.
Dr. Bumquist.
You think the anthropologist Margaret
Mead's strange behavior of late...
could be explained
by a private marijuana addiction ?
Good question.
- I'm not really sure I can answer that.
But what I can tell you, sir,
is if Margaret Mead...
at her age...
smoked grass...
she'd have one hell
of a trip.
One more layer of deviance
to the woman.
This is fuckin' bullshit.
I'll be out
in the casino.
Shut up, man.
Go to hell !
Thank you very much. Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you for having me.
- Projector, please.
- Excuse me.
- All right.
~
Know your dope fiend.
Your life may depend on it.
You will not be able to see his eyes,
because of Tea-Shades...
but his knuckles will be white
from inner tension.
And his pants will be
crusted with semen...
from constantly jacking off
when he can't find a rape victim.
He will stagger and babble
when questioned.
- He will not respect your badge.
The dope fiend fears nothing.
He will attack for no reason,
with any weapon at his command...
- including yours.
- Excuse me.
- Beware: any officer apprehending
a suspected marijuana addict...
- Pardon me.
- should use all
necessary force immediately.
- Sorry. Pardon me.
One stitch in time on him
will usually save nine...
on you--
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
- Oh, God. Oh, God.
Yeah ?
Yes, Mr. Duke, hello.
You have one message.
- Call Lucy...
- at the Americana Hotel, room 1600.
- Oh, fuck.
- Hello ?
- Lucy called.
- What ?
- Lucy called, man.
Those two men in the dock,
they gave me the LSD.
They took me
to the hotel.
I don't know what they
done to me, but I remember...
it was horrible.
- They gave you what ?
LSD.
Castration !
Double castration !
- Where's my .357 ?
- Who the fuck knows, man ?
- You can't leave me alone
in this snake pit.
You bastard, what did you do
with my .357 ?
- This room is in my name.
- Well, tough titty.
Okay, goddamn it !
You're right.
She's my problem. I'll call her,
I'll get her off our backs.
- It's gone too fucking far.
- No, I'll take care of the situation.
- Relax.
- Relax !
Let me handle this.
- Where are my shoes ?
- The Americana Hotel.
-What did you do with my goddamn shoes ?
-Room 1600, please.
As your attorney, I advise you to take a
hit out of the little brown bottle...
in my shaving kit.
You won't need much.
Just a... tiny taste.
Let's have it.
Ah, there it is.
- What is this shit ?
- That stuff...
makes pure mescaline
seem like ginger beer, man.
- Adrenochrome.
- Adrenochrome ? Hmm.
Hello.
- Hi, Lucy. God bless.
- Hmm ?
Yeah, it's me.
Hell, no, I taught the bastard
a lesson he'll never forget.
What ? No, not dead.
But he won't be bothering
anybody for a while.
Yeah, I left him out there.
I stomped him.
I pulled all his teeth out.
I remember thinking, Jesus...
what a terrible thing to lay
on somebody with a head full of acid.
But we have a problem.
That bastard cashed a bad check
downstairs and gave you as a reference.
They'll be looking
for both of you.
Yeah, I know, Lucy, but you
can't judge a book by its cover.
Some people are
just basically rotten.
Anyway, the last thing in the world
you wanna do is call this hotel again.
- They'll trace the call,
put you behind bars.
No, I'm moving
to the Tropicana right away.
Hmm.
I'll use a different name.
I'll let you know what it is.
I gotta get off.
Probably have
this phone tapped, baby.
- Yeah, it was horrible,
but it's all over now.
Oh, my God.
There's someone at the door.
- There's someone at the door.
Christ ! Hey !
No ! I'm innocent !
It was Duke !
Lucy ! Lucy !
I love you ! I love you !
Don't put that thing on me.
Aaaah ! Aaaah !
Whoo. Oh.
Well--
That's that.
- That's the last we should
be hearing from Lucy, man.
She's probably stuffing herself
down the incinerator about now.
You know what we need ?
We need some opium.
I remember
slumping on the bed.
His performance
had given me a bad jolt.
For a moment,
I thought his mind had snapped...
that he actually believed he was being
attacked by invisible enemies.
But the room was quiet again.
Where'd you get this ?
Never mind.
It's absolutely pure.
What kind of monster client
have you hooked up with this time ?
Satanism freak.
I think there's only
one source for this stuff--
the, uh, adrenaline gland...
from a living human body.
- I know. The guy didn't
have any cash to pay me.
- ~
He offered me human blood,
said it would take me higher
than I'd ever been in my life.
- I thought he was kidding...
- Oh.
so I told him I'd just as soon have
an ounce or so of pure adrenochrome...
or maybe just a fresh
adrenaline gland...
to chew on.
I could already feel
the stuff working on me.
The first wave felt like a combination
of mescaline and methedrine.
Maybe I should take a swim,
I thought.
Yes, sir.
They nailed this guy
for child molesting.
He swore he didn't do it.
"Why should I fuck with children ?"
he said. "They're too small."
- Christ, what could I say ?
Even a goddamn werewolf
is entitled to legal counsel.
I didn't dare
to turn the creep down.
He might have picked up a letter opener
and gone after my...
pineal gland.
- You know ?
- Yeah.
- Crazy.
- Why not ?
Shit. We should
get some of that.
Just... eat a big handful
and see what happens.
Some of what ?
Extract of pineal.
Sure, that's a good idea.
One whiff of that stuff will turn you
into something out of a goddamn...
medical encyclopedia, man.
Beautiful
fucking tits.
Man, your head would
swell up like a watermelon.
- You'd gain about
a hundred pounds in two hours.
- Right !
Grow claws,
bleeding warts.
Yes.
And then you'd notice
about six huge, hairy tits...
swelling up on your back.
Fantastic !
You'd go blind.
Your body would turn to wax.
They'd have to put you
in a wheelbarrow.
And when you scream for help...
you'll sound
like a raccoon.
Man, I'll try
just about anything...
but I'd never in hell
touch a pineal gland.
Finish the fucking story, man !
What happened ?
What about the glands ?
Jesus, that stuff got right
on top of you, didn't it ?
Look at your face.
You're about to explode.
Maybe you could just...
shove me into the pool.
Man, if I put you in the pool right now,
you'll sink like a goddamn stone.
You took too much, man.
You took too much. Too much.
Don't try and fight it.
You'll get brain bubbles,
strokes, aneurysms.
You'll just wither up
and die.
- They continue
killing innocent people !
Allowing the hopes for peace and
freedom of millions of people...
to be suffocated.
So tonight, we do.
The great silent majority.
Sacrifice. Sacrifice.
Sacrifice.
Sacrifice. Sacrifice. Sacrifice.
Sacrifice. Sacrifice.
~
~ I feel the cottonwood
whispering above ~
~ Tammy, Tammy ~
- ~ Tammy's in love ~
~
What kind of rat-bastard
psychotic would play that song
right now, at this moment ?
~ Tammy, Tammy ~
When I came to...
the general back-alley ambience
of the suite was so rotten...
- so incredibly foul.
- ~
How long had I
been lying there ?
All these signs of violence.
- What had happened ?
There was evidence in this room
of excessive consumption...
of almost every type of drug
known to civilized man since 1544 A.D.
Oh, ah, Debbie.
Thank God.
Oh, Debbie. Hmm ? Look.
What kind of addict would need
all these coconut husks
and crushed honeydew rinds ?
Would the presence of junkies account
for all these uneaten french fries ?
These puddles of glazed ketchup
on the bureau ?
Maybe so...
but then why all this booze...
and these crude pornographic
photos smeared with mustard...
that had dried
to a hard, yellow crust ?
These were not the hoofprints
of your normal God-fearing junkie.
It was too savage,
too aggressive.
- Put your hands where I can see them.
- What ? What ?
Jesus God, man. Huh ?
Put your hands where I can see them.
Put your hands where I can see them !
Grim memories
and bad flashbacks.
Get a grip.
Maintain.
How many nights and weird mornings
had this shit been going on ?
- Something ugly had happened.
I was sure of it.
Who is that ? Oh.
Shit, that's me.
- Help me !
- What the fuck ?
- Oh, shit.
- You're under arrest !
- She must have used a pass key.
I was polishing my shoes
in the closet when I noticed
her sneaking in, so I took her.
- What made you do it ?
Who paid you off ?
- Nobody ! I'm the maid !
- You're just as much
a part of it as they are.
- Part of what ?
The goddamn dope ring. You must
know what's going on in this hotel.
Why do you think
we're here ?
I know you're the cops, but I thought
you were just here for the convention.
I swear. All I wanted to do
was clean up the room.
- I don't know anything about no dope.
- Come on, baby.
Don't try to tell us you never heard
of the Grange Gorman.
I swear to Jesus
I never heard of that stuff.
Maybe she's telling the truth.
Maybe she's not part of it.
I swear I'm not.
I swear.
In that case,
maybe she can help.
Oh, yes, I'll help you
all you want.
- I hate dope.
- So do we.
I think we should put her on the
payroll, see what she comes up with.
- You think you can handle it ?
- What ?
One phone call every day.
Don't worry if it doesn't add up.
That's our problem.
Y-You'd pay me for that ?
You're damn right
we would.
But the first time that you say anything
about this to anybody...
you will go straight to prison
for the rest of your life.
- What's your name ?
- Alice.
Prove it !
- Okay.
- Just ring Linen Service
and ask for Alice.
All right, Alice.
You'll be contacted
by Inspector Rock, Arthur Rock.
He'll be posing as a politician, but
you'll have no problem recognizing him.
That's right, Inspector Rock
will pay you in cash...
- $1,000 on the ninth of every month.
- Oh, Lord !
I'd do just about
anything for that.
- You and a lot of other people.
- Come here.
The password is:
"One hand washes the other."
The minute you hear that,
you say, "l fear nothing."
- Say it.
- I fear nothing.
- Say it again !
- I fear nothing !
Get the fuck out of here.
Oh, yeah, listen.
Nice meeting you.
Don't bother
to make up the room.
Just leave a pile of towels and soap
outside the door exactly at midnight.
That way we won't have to risk another
one of these little incidents, will we ?
- Whatever you say, gentlemen.
- Thank God for decent people.
- Say it again !
- I fear nothing !
Terrible gibberish. Splintered
memories looming up out of the time fog.
- Just press play.
This is it, the American Dream.
We're sitting
on the main nerve right now.
Yeah, don't get me started.
The owner always wanted to run away and
join the circus when he was a kid.
Now the son of a bitch
owns the circus.
Ah, man,
a real license to steal.
Oh, yeah. The American Dream
come true, man.
Pure Horatio Alger.
Yeah. Welcome
to the happy place.
Listen, let's get down
to brass tacks here.
How much for the ape ?
How much you got ?
How much do you think you'd take for the
ape ? Just wait here. I'll be back.
- Madness. It made no sense at all.
I desperately
needed the facts.
- ~
- What the fuck is going on ?
Where's the ape, man ?
Where's the ape ?
Forget about it.
He attacked an old man.
Bit off the head of the bartender,
then the cops came and took him away.
- Is that your car ?
- Somebody stop them !
- You poor fools don't understand.
This car is property of the World Bank.
That money goes to lately.
You can't put on a circus
without a tent.
- The top is completely jammed.
- You're right.
There's something wrong
with the motor.
All right,
who has the story ?
- Where are you, you fucking monkey ?
- You can't do that !
You people voted
for Hubert Humphrey.
And you killed Jesus.
There was every reason to believe
that we'd been heading for trouble...
that we'd pushed our luck
a bit too far.
Oh, gosh ! God.
Right. Uh--
The possibility...
of physical
and mental collapse...
is now very real.
No sympathy for the devil.
Keep that in mind.
Uh, buy the ticket...
uh, take the ride.
Hey, there. You folks want
to buy some heroin ?
Hey, honkies ! Goddamn it !
Pull ahead,
will you ?
I want to sell you
some pure fucking scag !
Cheap ! The real stuff.
I just got back
from Vietnam.
Scag.
I want to sell you
some pure fucking scag.
Shit ! Fuck !
Now hear me, you bastard !
Pull over ! I'll kill you !
- Pull over ! Come on !
Oh, shit. Oh, oh.
~
Okay.
Let's see here.
~
The mentality of Las Vegas
is so grossly atavistic...
that a really massive crime
often slips by unrecognized.
North Vegas is where you go when you've
fucked up once too often on the strip...
- and when you're not even welcome
in the cut-rate downtown places.
The North Star Coffee Lounge seemed like
a fairly safe haven from our storms.
No hassles, no talk.
Just a place to rest
and regroup.
I wasn't even hungry.
There was nothing in the atmosphere of
the North Star to put me on my guard.
Two glasses of ice water
with ice.
Two.
She looked line a burnt-out
caricature of Jane Russell.
She was definitely
in charge here.
He did it very casually...
but I knew that our peace
was about to be shattered.
What was that ?
What is this ?
- It's a napkin.
- Don't give me that bullshit.
I know what that means,
you fat goddamn pimp bastard !
That's the name of a horse
I used to own, ma'am.
- What's wrong with you ?
The question mark was emphasized.
You listen to me,
you son of a bitch.
I gotta take a lot of shit
in this place, but I don't have
to take it off no spic pimp !
Anybody that knows anything
knows that.
- Go on ! Pay your check
and get out of here !
You want me to call the cops ?
I'll call the fuck--
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
Want me to call the cops ?
How much is that
lemon meringue pie ?
Her eyes were turgid with fear,
but her brain was functioning...
- on some basic motor survival level.
- Thirty-five cents.
- How much is that lemon meringue pie ?
Whoo ! What a waste of talent.
No, honey,
I mean the whole pie.
The whole pie.
- Hmm ?
What, three ?
Three ? Four ?
Five ? Hmm ?
Five.
I'll be in the car.
The sight of the blade
had triggered bad memories.
The glazed look in her eyes
said her throat had been cut.
- She was still in the grip
of paralysis when we left.
It was all over now.
We'd abused every rule
that Vegas lived by.
Threatening the locals, abusing
the tourists, terrifying the help.
The only chance now,
I felt...
was the possibility that
we'd gone to such excess...
that nobody in the position to bring
the hammer down on us...
could possibly believe it.
Fifteen minutes to get
my attorney to the airport...
but we'll make it.
Christ !
No ! Oh, fuck !
- Fuck.
- Whoa, shit ! Whoa, shit !
Oh, God. Oh, God.
You son of a bitch !
Oh, God.
- You're going the wrong way.
- The next left.
Go ! Fuck !
Take a right here.
Goddamn it. We're lost.
What are we doing out here
on this godforsaken road ?
The airport's over there.
Goddamn it !
It's over there.
- I've never missed a plane yet.
Hold on !
All right. I'm gonna drop you
right next to the plane.
Fuck you. I'm gonna have to take
the blame. They'll crucify me.
- Right here, right here.
- Ridiculous, man.
Just say you were hitchhiking
to the airport, and I picked you up.
- You bastard.
- Get out.
Hey, hey !
Hey, listen.
Don't take any guff
from these swine.
If you have any trouble,
remember:
you can always send a telegram
to the right people.
Yeah, explaining my position. Some
asshole wrote a poem about that once.
Probably good advice,
if you have shit for brains.
There he goes...
one of God's own prototypes.
A high-powered mutant of some kind never
even considered for mass production.
-Too weird to live, and too rare to die.
-Ugh !
~ There you stood on
the edge of your feather ~
~ Expecting to fly ~
We're all wired
into a survival trip now.
No more of the speed
that fueled the '60s.
That was the fatal flaw
in Tim Leary's trip.
He crashed around America,
selling "consciousness expansion"...
without ever giving a thought
to the grim meat-hook realities
that were lying in wait...
for all those people
who took him seriously.
All those pathetically eager
acid freaks...
who thought they could buy peace and
understanding for three bucks a hit.
But their loss
and failure...
is ours too.
What Leary took down with him was the
central illusion of a whole lifestyle...
that he helped create.
A generation
of permanent cripples...
failed seekers...
who never understood the essential
old-mystic fallacy of the acid culture:
the desperate assumption
that somebody...
or at least some force...
is tending the light
at the end of the tunnel.
There was only one road
back to L.A.
U.S. Interstate 15.
Just a flat out high-speed burn
through Baker and Barstow and Berdoo.
Then onto the Hollywood Freeway,
straight into frantic oblivion...
safety, obscurity.
Just another freak...
in the freak kingdom.
~ I was born
in a cross-fire hurricane ~
~ But I howled at my ma
in the driving rain ~
~ But it's all right now ~
~ In fact, it's a gas ~
~ But it's all right ~
~ I'm Jumpin' Jack Flash
It's a gas, gas, gas ~
~ I was raised
by a toothless, bearded hag ~
~ I was schooled with a strap
right across my back ~
~ But it's all right now ~
~ In fact, it's a gas ~
~ But it's all right ~
~ I'm Jumpin' Jack Flash
It's a gas, gas, gas ~
~ I was drowned
I was washed up and left for dead ~
~ I fell down to my feet ~
~ And I saw they bled ~
~ Yeah, yeah
I frowned ~
~ At the crumbs
of a crust of bread ~
~ Yeah, yeah, yeah
I was crowned ~
~ With a spike
right through my head ~
~ Yeah, yeah, yeah ~
~ But it's all right now ~
~ In fact, it's a gas ~
~ But it's all right ~
~ I'm Jumpin' Jack Flash
It's a gas, gas, gas ~
~ Jumpin' Jack Flash
It's a gas ~
~ Bright light city
gonna set my soul ~
~ It's gonna set my soul
on fire ~
~ I got a whole lotta money
that's a-ready to burn ~
~ So get those stakes up high ~
~ There's a thousand
pretty women waitin' out there ~
~ They're all waitin'
The devil may care ~
~ And I'm just a devil
with love to spare ~
~ So Viva Las Vegas ~
~ Viva Las Vegas ~
~ How I wish
that there were more ~
~ Than the 24 hours
in the day ~
~ Even if I ran out of sleep ~
~ Boy, I wouldn't sleep
a minute away ~
~ Oh, there's blackjack and
poker and the roulette wheel ~
~ A fortune won and lost
on every deal ~
~ All you need's a strong heart
and nerves of steel ~
~ So Viva Las Vegas ~
~ Viva Las Vegas ~
~ Viva Las Vegas
where the neon signs are flashing ~
~ And the one-armed bandits
crashing ~
~ All those hopes
down the drain ~
~ Viva Las Vegas
turning day into nighttime ~
~ Turning night into daytime ~
~ lf you see it once
you'll never be the same again ~
~ I gotta keep on runnin'
Gonna have me some fun ~
~ lf it costs me
my very last dime ~
~ lf I wind up broke
then I'll always remember ~
~ That I had a swingin' time ~
~ Oh, I'm gonna give it
everything I've got ~
~ Lady Luck's with me
Dice, stay hot ~
~ Got coke up my nose
to dry away the snot ~
~ So Viva Las Vegas ~
~ Viva Las Vegas ~
~ Viva, Viva ~
~ Las Vegas ~
Whee !
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org