Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- made by TUDORICI -
- Asshole!
- Look out, Bozo!
Hey. Hey. Hey!
What?!
Shut up, fag.
The friggin´ maids took my laptop.
l´m talkin´ about everything.
l´ve got fourteen quality leads
waiting for me in that area.
Yeah.
No. They´re with Packard, bro.
Hewlett-Pack--
Wake up!
Ohh! Just get outta here.
Hey, uh, how much
for the whole night, Grandma?
You should be so lucky.
- Oooh....hot for teacher.
- Oh, you little--
God damn.
Dude you´re late.
l have to leave in a half hour.
Don´t dilly-dally, then.
Rack ´em.
Dilly-dally. l´ll just dilly-dally over
and grab that money from you.
Damn!
l mean, we´ve been
going out for years,
and all of a sudden--bang--she drops me.
No, l´m not saying l ever lad it,
but l´ve definitely lost it.
l mean, l used to be a model.
J.C. Penney. Springwear.
Yeah. See? See, look.
Look. See?
- That was one of my model things.
- Oh. Yeah.
lt might not look like it now--
that´s ´cause l´m wearing work clothes,
so it doesn´t really fit, you know,
but if l was wearing my modeling clothes,
trust me, l´d look like a model.
Yeah, yeah, you´re full of shit.
You know, Chach...
l take the rubble of man...
and l build superstars.
Come on, man.
Fuck that shit.
l don´t want no brochures
in here, man.
l mean, this guy,
he gets an open tab all the time here.
Watch. Watch. Watch.
Amen, Brother Ben.
Shot a rooster, killed a hen.
Now, that´s Hollywood talk.
That´s showbiz, brother.
lf you change your mind.
lf you´re gonna
hang around a while, that´s great.
- But you gotta move your truck.
- Yeah. No, l hear ya.
l keep forgettin´.
This place is hoppin´.
Oh, no. Listen, your money
can´t buy shit here, Sergeant.
- Well, thank you.
- Semper fi, man.
- Where you headed?
- l´m goin´ home.
- Yeah?
- l´m gonna go home,
kiss my wife,
be back on the front lines
as soon as they´ll have me.
- That´s truly righteous, man.
- You don´t know my wife.
Ohh.
- Evenin´.
Oh, l was--l was, uh--
l was just lookin´ for ya.
Zip it, shitbox.
You dropped off the beer.
Now take a hike.
Okay.
- Now! Now!
Ohh, man.
Goddamn dirt weed.
Rum and Coke...
without the Coke.
Keep it.
Not from around here, are ya?
- What gave me away?
- You have all your teeth.
Can l buy you a drink?
- Yeah.
l´m off in five.
Whisky shooter, please.
Which tab?
Mine.
- Hey, watch it there, buddy.
- Jeez, dude, l´m playing a game.
- Well, so am l.
- Yeah, mine´s for real money, though.
That´s all she wrote.
What the fuck!
Oh!
- That´s a rough one.
- That is fucking impossible!
Don´t get your panties in a bunch.
Want to go again?
- Goddamnit, no!
- Come on.
"Crap-ay" diem!
Fuckin´ pussy.
Anybody wanna go?
Mom, when are we going home?
After my meeting.
Come on. baby. let´s rock and roll.
Okay. You know the drill.
Keep these on.
Come on.
l can´t do this by myself. loney.
Now!
Come on. Take you to your car.
Not tonight.
l have an escort.
Eighteen bucks, pal.
l guess l´ll hold on to this.
Ah! Ah, shit!
Shit! Slit!
Ohh! Oll!
Damn, baby, act like you feel it!
Ahh!
Shit fine!
Hey, uh, you boys want to
try your luck with the loot?
Come on.
Hey, l´ll use one arm.
Nothing but a bunch of
limp dicks and pussies in here!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You shut the fuck up,
or get out.
No, you shut up, old man.
Come on!
Gime some action!
The fuck are you?
Unless you people want to die,
you´ll do what l say
and you´ll do it fast.
Mine´s bigger´n yours.
Listen to me.
A storm of hell´s comin´ down
on this place any second.
l don´t know what they are...
l don´t know where they came from.
All l do know is that these fuckers
are fast, nasty, and hungry.
And there´s four of ´em.
They got claws like Ginsu knives
and more teeth than a chainsaw.
They´re comin´.
Right now.
So we gotta lock this bar down.
That means doors, windows,
drains, and zippers,
and we gotta do it fast.
You. Get a phone, call the cops,
National Guard, townies--
anybody who kicks ass--
and get ´em out here.
- Any questions?
- Yeah.
Who the hell are you?
l´m the guy
that´s gonna save your ass.
Fuck.
Aah!!!
Aah!
Get down!
Where is he?
Where´s my husband?
Cody?
Come here.
l want you to stay...
right here.
l want you to stay in this closet
and do not move.
l don´t care what you hear,
don´t move!
Help me, somebody.
Aah! Aah!
Aaahh! Aaahh!
Aah!
ls it gone?
What the fuck?!
Fuck! Fuck!
Fuckin´...!
Where´s that little fucker?
l got it! l got it!
We´re okay.
- Scratch that.
- Close the motherfucking shutters!
God damn you!
Beer me.
- ls it clear?
- Unh! What the fuck?
ls it clear down there?
Yeah, l-l think--
l-l don´t know.
l don´t know, boss.
ls there a gun pointed at you?
No. No, l got--
l got the judge, see?
All right, nobody
moves down there. Nobody!
Shit.
All right, goddamnit! Who shot me?
Oww! Fuck!
Who did it?!
What are you idiots looking at?
My goddamn foot´s blown off here!
Who shot me?
Her fella.
My husband.
Where is the son of a bitch?
He´s dead.
What?
What the fuck happened down here?
What? What?
Look, it wasn´t me, all right?
lt was a f-fucking monster
or something!
l-l didn´t do nothin´.
One of their heads is over here.
Ow!
Yeah, that´s...
that´s definitely one for the wall.
Oh, my God.
What is that thing?
l have no--
l don´t know.
l don´t even know how l got here.
They were so fast.
That head used to be attached
to some huge, twisted body
like a rotting jackal or something,
like something out of a nightmare.
Of all the bars to be stuck in.
Anything else?
Yeah. We need to lock
this place down completely.
- ls everybody downstairs?
- My son--
- My son´s upstairs!
- Wait! Stop her!
Cody!
Cody?
- Oh, God, no!
- Momy?
Cody! l am never gonna
let you be alone again.
All right, look,
we gotta lock this place up.
Look, come here.
You okay?
Yeah?
l´m so sorry.
l am never gonna let you--
Aaaah!
Aah! Get it off me!
Aah! God!
No!!!
No!
No! No!
Fuck! Aw!
Aw, God!
Somebody help me, man!
God damn! Ow!
Burnin´, man! Shit!
Get this shit off me, man!
- Come on in--
- Fuck!
Come on, l got a sink in here.
Come on.
- Come on.
- Where´d he go, man?
All right. Ohh!
God! Aah!
Was that the only phone?
Yep.
What about cell phones?
This is canyon country, honey.
lt ain´t gonna happen.
Well, we´ve got to
have something here, right?
Just relax.
l´ve got a shortwave radio.
Except it´s...
upstairs there, somewhere.
This is bullshit.
What did you say to me?
l didn´t say anything, Flo.
How you doin´, buddy?
You holdin´ up?
Bad! l´m doin´ bad!
- Fuck!
- lt´s green.
Yeah, l know!
You got any more water pressure?
- No, that´s all it´s got.
- Aw, fuck!
God, your sink sucks!
Oh, fu--oww!
The stuff´s up my nose, man!
Can you--can you feel it?
Just calm down, you goddamn pussy.
You´re all right.
l gotta go to the hospital, man.
l gotta fuckin´ leave, man.
l need a doctor, man.
l´m outta here.
l´m goin´ to the hospital.
l´m gettin´ my truck. l´m goin´.
- Just calm down, okay?
- No, you calm down.
Now, you can risk your life,
but not mine.
My daughter is out there
waiting for me.
l have just as much reason
to get out of this place as you do.
But l also have
the comon fuckin´ sense to know
that staying alive means
being in here and not out there.
Do you understand?
Do you understand me?!
Yeah--yeah. Got--got ya. Got ya.
Pull that tough-guy shit again,
l will slice you from your neck
to your nuts.
This is bullshit, man.
You can´t keep me here.
You fuckers can´t keep me here, man!
This is bullshit.
This is fuckin´ bullshit!
This is bullshit, man!
Fuck this.
...this shit off of me myself!
Act like you´ve had some.
- Oh, l´ve had some, baby.
- l haven´t.
Oh, God.
That´s gonna stain.
We can´t risk letting them in.
Have they left? lt´s quiet.
No, they´re still out there.
They´re just listening to us.
We gotta start
clearin´ these bodies up.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, shit! Fuck!
- Come on! Come on!
- Easy, bud.
lt´s just a death rattle.
He´s gone, he just ain´t done
movin´ yet.
Let´s wrap ´em up in tablecloths
and dump ´em in the basement.
All right?
- All right?
- All right.
Let´s lock this place down.
- Boo!
- Shit.
lt´s hungry again!
lt´s gonna eat us!
Just calm down, okay?
We have to kill this thing.
Fire in the hole.
How you like that,
you little bastard?
Ow!
God bless guns.
Aaahh!
Get this fuckin´ thing off me!
Aah!
Okay.
Jeez...
it took all that?
- All those bullets?
- That´s the little one?!
We can´t kill these things!
No way!
Look, we lave to fight these things.
We just have to be clever
about this, okay?
Maybe we don´t need to
fight them at all.
Yeah. Why don´t we
just call them names?
Fuckin´ genius.
We´re stuck here--
l can see this.
But what we need to do
is think outside the box.
We don´t need to fight them.
We need to scane them.
We need to scare them back.
This...
...is a species stand-off.
We just need to show them
that we are not vulnerable.
That we...are fonmidable.
How?
l need a stick.
Open up that ice chest.
God damn.
Oh, shit.
All right,
give me some room.
lt´s gnoss.
How old do you think
that thing is?
- Take one of the planks off the window.
- No way.
Just one board. One minute.
lt´ll save your life. Just trust me.
- No.
- One board.
One minute. Home free.
Okay. Make it quick.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
- Wait. What are you doing?
- Showing superiority.
The scent of their dead
may drive them back.
- You see ´em?
- ls there like a call or something?
Come on, you
monkey motherfuckers!
Come on!!!
You can´t fuck with man!
Sweet.
Whoa.
There´s two of ´em.
lt´s like they´re wearing
dead animals or something.
Hey! lt´s working!
You´re a genius.
See? What did l tell ya?
Wait. There´s a third.
lt´s like a family.
lt´s a goddamn family.
And we just killed their baby.
Holy shit! She ate it!
She didn´t even chew it, man.
She just swallowed it.
Oh, dear.
What? What´s he doing?
They´re humpin´!
Oh, man.
The monsters are
doin´ it doggie-style.
Monster sex.
Where you goin´, boss?
You be careful, boss.
What is that?
Dude...took a dump.
No...it´s moving, stupid.
Ohh....spread out.
- God almighty!
lt´s one of the little bastards.
Any more ideas,
Animal Planet?
l was just bein´ proactive.
Hey, dipshit.
l didn´t see you workin´, did l?
Oh, go douche, Grandpa.
Well, what now? Huh?!
We´re stuck in here, that´s what.
lf you don´t mind me askin´...
how´d you run into these things?
We dnopped oun dauglten off
at my mom´s louse...
my little ginl Clanlie. My baby.
lt was only fon tle niglt.
Tlen suddenly... we lit it.
We lost contnol of tle can.
lt spun and flipped.
And l was tlnown fnom tle can.
lts lead was in tle noad.
Tlat´s wlen tley came.
lt´s road-kill revenge.
Well, l´d like to be the first
to thank you and your dead husband
for draggin´ this fuck fest
into my tavern.
The only thing we brought here
was a heads-up that saved your ass.
This is not my fault.
You pissed off the wrong clan, lady.
Maybe all they want´s you.
Maybe all they want´s the person that
ran over their old granddaddy in a car.
And maybe they can have you
on a silver platter,
apple in fuckin´ mouth.
You shoulda thought of that
before we killed their child
and stuck it outside on a pike.
No need to get menstrual.
That was a dumb fuckin´ idea, man.
Ow! Shit!
Fuck!
What the fuck´s happening, man?!
What the fuck is this shit?!
Just don´t touch it, okay?
Leave it alone.
- You´re making it worse.
- You tell me to leave it alone?
You get puked on by a monster
and you tell me
how that feels, huh?
l´m rottin´ here, and nobody
could give a shit!
l´m dying, all right?!
l´m fuckin´ dying!
l am upper-case fucked!
You don´t give a shit, man!
You don´t give a shit, either!
All you guys don´t fuckin´
care about me!
l don´t care.
Go suffer somewhere else.
Get the fuck away from me.
Ohh, God! Fuck, that hurts!
Look, somebody´s got
to know something about this.
This stuff doesn´t just
happen out of the blue.
You.
What?
- You know something.
- Huh?
- Yeah, you´re old. You´ve seen things.
- l don´t know anything.
- Easy, cowboy.
- Hey, back off me, Whitey!
l´m interrogating her.
She´s old.
Old people know things,
like legends and tall tales and shit.
No. No. Really,
l don´t know anything.
Come on, spill it.
- Spill it, or l´ll get rough.
- l don´t know anything!
Why don´t you ask him?
He´s old.
- Start diggin´.
- Ahh, sheesh.
Back off.
She doesn´t know anything.
Yeah, allegedly.
lt doesn´t matter where
they fucking came from.
They´re here. Either we kill them
or they kill us. That´s it.
Hey, no offense, Xena...
but by the way things are going,
looks like we need another chief,
somebody that knows
the lay of the land,
somebody with a little moxie.
Somebody like myself.
-Aah.
- Careful.
l think we´re gonna be all right.
l think we´re gonna be okay, guys.
Ohh!
Yeah. l think we´re
gonna be all right.
This is just some leaky barrel
radiation toxic dump waste
enviro-crap freak-beast accident
that crawled out of the sewer, man.
That´s all this is.
We´re gonna be all right.
l think the experts, they´re gonna be
showin´ up any minute to fix this up.
You know, some of those green guys?
Those guys with
the real can-do attitude and the tanks
and M-16s and torpedoes and--
Hey! Can you just give it a break?
Those guys are en noute.
You hear ´em?
They´re comin´.
- l wouldn´t do that if l were you.
- Yeah, be careful.
l don´t see a thing.
l can´t see a thing.
Aah! Aah!
Give me my eye back!!!
- Jeez!
- Ol.
Hm. Ahem.
Does everyone agree
that the monsters are still out there?
Huh, chief?
- Yeah, no slit. Sherlock.
l have some sweats
behind the bar in a...in a bag.
Tha-thank you.
- They coordinated that strike.
- Yeah, l know.
- l´m gonna need more shells.
- Yeah, tell me about it, missy.
A .45´s got six shots.
l got two refills.
- ln my locker in the basement l got--
...l got maybe some more shells.
Ah!
Jeez.
And...l got this.
Shhh...
...shit.
Honey, why don´t you just
leave the offense to us?
You need a whole lot more than that
to get out of here alive.
Oh, now you got
somethin´ to say.
You young´uns.
You worry about weapons.
- l´m thinkin´ strategy.
- Oh. And what´s that?
Sit still...
and look less like a meal.
That´s for bears and sharks,
Chunky Chew.
How do you tolerate him?
He´s an ass, but he´s my brother.
l´ve stood everywhere. Nothin´.
Didn´t you say you had a radio?
Upstairs, back of my closet.
Little slidin´ door.
- Channel 9´s the emergency frequency.
Have fun.
All right. l´m gonna go
to the basement for supplies.
And you--you´re going upstairs.
Heh.
Let´s not get carried away.
Step up, chief.
Ain´t you got a pair?
Watch it.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah. Shotgun.
All right, partner,
you´re comin´ with me.
Whoa. l don´t know about that, bub.
l mean, l ain´t exactly
no Billy the Kid.
Yeah, but you´re slow,
and that´s helpful.
Just stay close.
Who else is comin´?
l´ll go with ya.
What are you gonna do,
throw your teeth at ´em?
Just sit down, Cocoon.
You. You´re comin´ with me.
Keys.
- You´re locked in.
- What?
These two will be
on the other side waiting for you.
lf you become food,
l don´t want a set of keys in the belly
of one of those things.
Don´t get your hopes up.
Any volunteers
for the basement?
l´ll go.
All right. l don´t want to hear
any of this "Where is the key?"
"l dropped the key."
l want out. l want out.
You just find that fucking radio.
We´ll get you out.
We got your front, bro.
lt´s your "back."
"We got your back. "
Shit.
Okay.
You keep that handy.
- You wish me luck, girls.
- All right.
l´m okay. l´m okay.
l´m okay! l´m okay!
l´m okay...l´m okay.
Come on.
Just breathe....
just breathe.
Come on...come on.
Aah!
Come on...
just breathe.
Unh!
Easy. Easy.
Aah! Augh!
lt´s okay! lt´s just a bat.
lt´s just a bat.
Come on, hurry up.
Come on, you motherfucker.
Hello.
ls anyone out there?
Look, we need help. The Bear Tavern.
Send guns. And tanks.
Aaahhh!
l repeat! l repeat! S.O.S.!
S.O.S.! Calling all cars!
Okay! l´m ready to come out!
l´m neady to come out now!
Oh--
"Oh"?
What do you mean, "Oh"?!
Help! Help!
Cheese and crackers.
Goddamnit, open up!
Come on!
The goddamn key busted.
Old man! Help!
Goddamnit. lelp!!!
Help!!!
Old man!
The monster´s cock
is stuck in the door!
Aaahhh!
Fuck!
Help!
Shit!
l thought that was it
for a second there.
Hold me, brother.
What happened?
Papa Beast got neutered, missy.
Oh...good one.
lf they can´t reproduce,
then we´re one step closer.
A big step.
Now is the time
to band together.
We need to rise up
against these creatures of the night.
These monsters are no match
for the human spirit.
We can do it.
We just need to believe in each other,
believe in all of us.
We need to make a stand.
Right here, right now.
Dude...
are you gay?
Look....
those monsters were clawing
those nails out upstairs.
They´re like Mensa monsters.
They´re gonna need
a lot more than claws
to pop out these boards down here.
They´ll need a crowbar or somethin´.
- We gotta find a way out. Now.
- l have a really good idea.
We could all run outside
to our cars
and we could spread out
in different directions.
That´s a goddamn suicide trip.
- But if we all stick together--
- Hey, half of us can´t run,
and one of us
can´t even walk, hon.
Hanging out isn´t looking
too much better.
Even l can admit that.
Hey. Hey. Ow.
Hey, what about the basement
hatch door?
What about it?
We--we could trick ´em.
That could be our--our escape.
The--the--the monsters
don´t know about it.
lt´s a--it´s a--it´s a--
sh--sh--
shh--shh--
lt´s a sec--secret hatch.
Oh, crap. Ohh....
Has anyone got lip balm...
l can borrow?
- Fucked up and stupid.
- Look, it´s true.
lf we just go out there, no matter
how quiet or fast we are, we´re dead.
But if we can draw them away
to the other side of the bar,
we at least got a chance.
Do either of you have any--
a can of hairspray or anything?
Yeah, l do in my purse.
You put in some household cleaner
and some low-grade booze,
and you got yourself a distraction.
What about a car?
Whose car is close?
You gonna climb
through that hatch down there?
- Yeah.
- My truck´s the closest,
but there ain´t no way
it´s gonna haul the whole lot.
- ls it gassed?
- Fully.
- Four-door?
- Two.
- How many fit?
- Six.
- Max?
- Seven.
Ten. lt´s gonna fit ten.
Ten clowns couldn´t
fit in that truck.
Here´s a plan. Two of us go.
One to drive, one to defend.
We back up to the bar,
and tear ass out of here.
Not good odds, missy.
My daughter is waiting for me.
l don´t have a choice.
Okay, l´m in.
No, ma´am. lt would be an honor
to accompany you
on this dangerous journey.
- All right.
- You´re not gonna make it, hon.
l´m sorry.
Sooner or later
that wall is coming down.
lf we stay, we die.
What´s the distraction?
- Well, they want to eat us, right?
- Yeah.
- Let´s give ´em something to eat.
Uh-oh.
Turn on the light.
Which one?
The boy or the girl?
The girl.
Catch!
Ohh!
Oh, God.
All right.
Body bomb is good to go.
This is simple.
l plug in, and she goes boom.
We´re goin´ to hell.
Right to hell.
This chick is more useful dead
than you are alive. Will you shut up?
Yeah, we´ll just run this cord
upstairs there
where we been attacked
twice already...
then Fucko and l
drop her through a hole
without making a sound,
and trick the smartest creatures
l ever seen
into taking a bite out of her
instead of us.
That´s real simple.
Hey, l already had my moment.
How come l have to go upstairs again?
´Cause you´re lucky.
You see these peanut barrels?
We line up some planks,
when that wall comes down....
we roll ´em out.
Just like Donkey Kong.
Dipshit.
l don´t believe in guns.
This isn´t a time for
a political stance, hot shot.
This won´t run out of amo.
l want this back.
Hey.
Don´t monkey with my stereo.
Yeah.
How does it feel?
Uh, okay.
Good. Do you mind if l
take a look at it real quick?
- No.
- l´ll try not to hurt you.
How´s it look?
- Uh....
- ls it gettin´ better?
Maybe.
ls it healin´ up?
l´m just gonna
swish out my mouth.
ls it gettin´ better?
- Yeah, looks pretty good.
- Okay.
You should be a nurse.
Thanks.
Can you mend a broken heart?
l wouldn´t fuck you for practice.
- Tease.
- Asshole.
Ohh...ohh...
Bet this place is creepy
in the daytime, too.
Pull that chair down.
Hyah! Hyah!
Fuckin´ monster.
Hyah!!!
- Up and over.
- Okay.
You and l have
a lot of similarities.
Strong, resolute...
You need to be quiet.
l´m sorry.
l talk when l get nervous.
Quiet. Come on.
lt´s just that it´s been a while
since someone was horribly killed,
and it seems like the opportune time
for someone to get, l don´t know, offed.
What did l say?
- Quiet.
- Sorry. l´ll stop now.
We´re up.
Come on, you lazy bastard,
l can´t do it all.
Get on up there. Chop-chop.
ln you go.
Get up there!
Holy shit! She´s alive.
Help me.
No, she´s not.
- Okay, let´s do this.
Help me.
- No. No!
- Help me.
Hey!
Get the cord!
Get it, goddamn it!
Come on, grab it, you dumb-ass!
Grab it!
Get the goddamn thing!
Get it! Get the fuckin´ thing!
Put tle plug in. damnit! Now! Do it!
God almighty!
Come on. man!
Now!
Come on! Auggh--
Shit.
Great men will write
about my bravery.
Hey.
When we get downstairs...
...our story´s the same, right?
Hey.
l can stick this in your mouth,
get all dramatic, and ask again, but....
what about if l just say please?
Keep going for the truck!
l´ll draw them away!
Hey, over here!
Fucking monsters!
What the hell are you doing?
l think he´s going
for the truck. l couldn´t make it!
You gotta help me unlock it!
Stop! Stop!
- Stop!
- What are you doing?
They can´t get in here!
We agreed!
Just calm down.
Just take it easy.
Drop it!
- Okay.
- Drop it!
Please let me in. Hurry! They´re--
Ohh! Aaahhh!
Open the fucking thing!
l´m gonna fucking die!
- You´re killing her!
- Put the gun down, son.
Don´t let it in!
We´ll all die!
- They got her.
They got her.
Back off! Get away!
lf you could stop trying to
get people killed, that´d be great.
Fuck.
You motherfucken!
You ain´t got a chance
without me, dumb-ass--
Arrgghh!
Hold it!
Now we both got a secret,
don´t we?
Arrggh!
Hey, she´s outside.
We´ve got to get her
out of there. Come on.
- She ain´t comin´ back.
- What?
She´s gone.
What happened?
They got her, that´s all.
We tried.
That´s it.
That´s the fuckin´ end of it.
That´s the fucking...end of it.
Unh!
Ohh! Fuck.
Ah, fuck it.
Hey, you guys...
Our plan is--is--is good,
and--and that truck is coming.
lf we all just stick together, we--
Hey!
lf anyone has a right to have
a complete meltdown right now,
it´s me.
But right now,
l don´t have the time,
because right now
you morose motherfuckers
are gonna get off your ass
and get ready to roll.
´Cause if those things
are gonna fuck with us...
...we´re gonna fuck with ´em right back.
Now, who´s with me?
Yeah, y´all go ahead
and make a run for it.
Make it happen. Just...
you convoy out of here
and save the day.
Me, l´m gonna stay right here,
wait for help,
and, uh, limp out of here
to safety.
Y´all go ahead, though.
Storm out of here,
make a bunch of racket.
They won´t even notice me.
They like food that moves.
Aah!
- On the tables, now!
l´m not getting near it!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Aaaahhh!!!
Get off him! Get off him!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Calm down! Calm down!
- Calm--
- Stop it...
He didn´t make it.
- Yes, he did!
- No, he didn´t!
Yes, he did!
No, he didn´t.
No, he didn´t!
Bullshit!!!
Aah!
Those goddamn doors
aren´t gonna fucking hold!
Plan B?
Here. See this?
l want you to light
this motherfucker and throw it.
lf we get out of this shit,
l´ll personally take you to the hospital.
And don´t fuck it up.
Oh!
lt´s over.
We´re gonna die.
lt´s not gonna hold!
Comin´!
- l can´t--
- Look out!
lt´s stuck!
- l can´t--
- Get out of my way!
Okay, now!!!
Damn you, cocksucker!
Get out of the way!
- Ready?
- Ready? One...
Aah! Aah!
She made it!
- Piece of ass made it!
- Yes.
Come on.
Start it. Start it. Stant it!
Come on!!!
Come on. Come on...
Come on. Drive it like
you stole it, baby! Come on!
She´s...she--
she´s fucking leaving!
What?!
She´s leaving us?
Fuck!
Oh, God.
Hey, fuckface!
Whoa, fuck!
- No!
Oh, shi--
- Aah!
Come on, motherfucker!
Come on! Motherfuck--
Aaahhh!!!
Gime that!
Aah! Aah!
You´re having
a fuckin´ heart attack?
You kidding me?
Get the bottle!
Get the bottle, old man!
Aaaahhh!
Drink´s on me.
Aaahhh!!!
Good! Choke on it!
Aah!
- You got it?
- Yeah.
Come on.
Come on, open the door.
You know, her little girl´s
not far from here.
Wanna get her?
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Shut up.
Five, four
Three, two, run!
- made by TUDORICI -
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org