Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Zomcon presents...
A Bright New World.
From the darkest depths
of outer space
came an evil no man could predict.
A cloud of radiation engulfed
our great planet.
Scientists discovered
that these space particles
caused the reanimation
of dead bodies...
Zombies!
Creatures with but one
destructive need...
to devour the flesh of the living.
And so, we were forced
to defend our homeland.
The Zombie Wars...
mankind pitted against
legions of the undead.
But in our darkest hour,
a savior...
Zomcon, and our founder,
Dr. Reinhold Geiger.
Dr. Geiger discovered
that if the brain was destroyed,
the zombie was destroyed,
never to reanimate.
And so,
the Zombie Wars were won.
Zomcon built security systems
like the perimeter fence
that encloses our towns
in a wall of protective steel,
and surrounds other towns
right across this great land.
But even within the fence,
danger lurked.
Lingering radiation meant that anyone
who died became a zombie.
Be careful, Mrs. Smith.
He's not the man you married.
And then, a breakthrough...
the domestication collar.
With the collar in place,
a red light comes on,
telling us that the zombie's desire for
human flesh has been contained,
making the zombie as gentle
as a household pet.
But if the collar light
goes out, call Zomcon,
or push the nearest
safety button
and we'll be there
to handle any zombie problem,
large or small.
Thanks to Zomcon, we can all become
productive members of society,
even after we die.
Or, for those who can afford it,
a Zomcon funeral,
complete with head coffin,
guarantees you a burial
you won't come back from.
Your tax dollars
allow Zomcon new ways
to protect our homeland
from the zombie threat,
giving us more time to relax
and be with our families.
So thank you, Zomcon,
for winning the Zombie Wars
and building a company
for tomorrow
that gives us a safer
future today.
Zomcon, a better life
through containment.
Well, I think
that informative film
taught us all a little bit more
about how Zomcon
helps make our world
a better place,
isn't that right, children?
Yes, Miss Mills.
Our special guest is here.
Everyone straighten your desks.
Children, I would like to introduce
Willard's new head of security
at Zomcon,
who is not only a decorated hero of
the Zombie Wars,
but is also Zomcon's
official safety expert.
Mr. Bottoms is the father
of our newest,
and I suspect our brightest student, Cindy.
Well, good afternoon,
boys and girls.
So how many of you have ever had
to kill a zombie?
Ooh. Not too many,
and that's the way I'd like to keep it.
My job at Zomcon is to make things safe
for young people just like you.
That's why I'm building
a taller fence,
and there are going to be
new safety vans patrolling our streets.
And we're going to take
everybody's picture
just in case one of you...
gets lost.
What do you think of that?
Children, does anyone
have a question for Mr. Bottoms?
Yes, Roy.
Stan and me...
I mean, me and Stan,
have been Zomcon Cadets
for two years, sir.
We think Zomcon's great.
That's terrific. Thank you.
Does anyone have
an actual question?
Timmy Robinson has a question.
Timmy, go on.
Ask a good question.
Timmy?
Are zombies dead or alive?
- What a stupid question.
- Really stupid.
Now, now, now.
There's no such thing as a stupid question.
The truth is, to some people,
zombies might seem human.
But make no mistake,
these creatures have
only one goal,
and that is to eat your flesh.
So without Zomcon,
we'd all be dead.
And then where would we be?
- Dead?
That's right.
So does that answer
your question, Timmy?
I guess.
You guess?
Well, this isn't a world
where we guess, young man.
You either know
something or you don't.
I was just thinking
about the zombies
who were buried too deep
to get out of their coffins.
Well, that's impossible.
We always bury the heads separately.
I mean people buried
before the space dust.
Couldn't some of them
still be in the graveyard right now,
trying to claw their way out?
Yuck.
Well, children, look at that.
It's time for outdoor education.
Let's show Mr. Bottoms
how good we are, hmm?
# In the brain
and not the chest #
# Head shots are the very best #
# In the brain
and not the chest #
# Head shots are the very best #
# In the brain
and not the chest #
# Head shots are the very best #
Trying to make
Zomcon look stupid?
That wouldn't be hard.
What did you say?
Nothing.
- Okay, mister.
- But it's out of bullets!
It felt empty.
A good cadet always knows
how many bullets he has left, son.
- You idiot.
- That's it.
Detention, the pair of you.
That's not fair.
But he said Zomcon was stupid.
Did you say that?
No, no.
Pick up the box.
Don't drop...
That's Mr. Bottoms' lamp.
If that could go to the den.
It's just to your right...
It's very fragile.
Hey, Timmy!
Hi, Mr. Theopolis.
That's no way to treat a bicycle.
Sorry, Mrs. Henderson.
What have I told you about
leaving you bike on the lawn?
Now put it away properly.
Was that so hard?
Yes, Mrs. Henderson.
What did you say?
I mean, no, Mrs. Henderson.
What are you looking at,
Theopolis?
I'm going to take this apple pie
over to our new neighbors.
See if they actually
own all those zombies.
They probably do.
He's the new
head of security at Zomcon.
The new head of security
moved into the Johnsons' old place.
Well, that's good news.
What on earth, Timmy?
That is a new shirt.
It was those bullies
I told you about.
They pushed me down,
and Stan pointed his gun at me.
What?
Did people see you like this?
I don't know.
Come here.
There you go.
Everything's going to be fine.
Just go and clean up,
put on a new shirt,
and we won't even have to
talk about those bullies.
Oh, there's one other thing.
Hi, honey.
Made just the way you like it.
A three olive martini.
What did I do to deserve this?
Helen, what are you up to?
I've had a long day.
Oh, Bill, honestly.
Sometimes I wonder about you.
I really do.
If you must know,
I have a surprise for you.
Wow.
Hi, Dad.
Hiya, Tim.
- How's my boy?
- Fine.
- Are you ready?
- There's more?
Now, just relax.
Isn't it wonderful?
Now we're not the only ones
on the street without one.
Helen, could I speak to you
in the kitchen?
Of course, dear.
You're always so sensible.
Timmy, why don't you
go watch some television?
Yeah, but, Mom, I don't...
I'm sure there's
something wonderful on.
But, Bill, the neighbors.
Everybody has one except for us.
Well, Helen, in India
everyone has a tiger.
Why don't we just move there
and get a tiger?
Not everybody in India
has a tiger, Bill.
That's what I heard.
We can't afford a zombie.
I'm barely keeping up with
funeral payments as it is.
Funerals. Is that all you ever
think about, Bill?
I still can't believe you bought
a funeral savings plan for Timmy.
Come on, Helen.
The other kids hate him.
You said so yourself.
Bill!
I met our new neighbors today.
Did you know that he is the new head
of security for Zomcon?
Really?
That's who moved into
the old Johnson place?
Uh-huh. And did you know
that they have six zombies. Six!
And when his wife asked me
how many we had,
I didn't know what to say.
So I told her we had one.
You what?
What was I supposed to do?
Tell her that my husband
is afraid of zombies?
I'm not going to talk about this.
Hey.
Zombie?
The roast.
- Dad.
- Sorry.
I thought that was
a different button.
Whoops.
What are you doing?
It's hurting him.
Sorry. I...
You know,
I bet with our new neighbor,
we'll have the safest
street in Willard.
I can't argue with that.
And, obviously,
it will be chained up
in the backyard
when it's not doing chores.
Obviously.
It'll have to be.
Helen, propriety.
You're the boss, dear.
Afraid of zombies.
I'll tell you what
I'm afraid of, little lady.
Nothing, that's what.
Just stay right there.
Think I'm afraid of you?
Huh?
That what you think?
That's right.
Nicely done, Tammy.
No.
Grandpa's fallen
and he's getting up.
The elderly.
They seem friendly enough,
but can you really trust them?
No.
So don't get caught off guard.
Buy the Zomcon Zombie Alert
heart monitor.
When the heart stops, we start.
Aren't you going to
help me practice, Dad?
Oh, is that today?
You already changed it
from yesterday.
But I've already got
the driving range booked.
Don't other dads take their kids
to the driving range?
No.
No, they don't.
Honey, honey.
Please don't play
baseball by yourself.
It makes you look Ionely.
Now, I'm going over to meet
our new neighbors.
But you said you already
met the neighbors.
Timmy, I thought
you were on my side.
Give it here.
Come on, stupid. Throw it.
It's a baseball.
You throw it.
You throw like a girl.
Did it again.
It's so dumb.
Ow!
What are you doing?
It wasn't me.
You shot me with a B.B. Gun.
Get him!
So, where do you want
to get shot?
Head shot, Roy.
That's the first smart thing
you've said all day.
- Roy!
- Leave me alone!
Ow, my arm.
My arm.
Stay away from me.
Stop, zombie! Stop!
Let's get out of here.
And that loser Stan,
I thought he was
going to pee himself.
Crying like a sucky baby.
They sure won't
pick on me again...
at least not when you're around.
What?
Do you want to play?
Okay.
We should get a name for you
before Mom does.
I know.
How about Fido?
Nice catch, Fido.
Well, if you're not going to catch it,
you got to go fetch it.
Go get it, boy.
Come on, boy.
You're disgusting.
Why don't you go home
and get some clothes on?
If your mother could see you now.
Can't bear to look at you.
You rotten zombie!
You nearly scared me half to death.
Stop that!
You're spoiling my quiet time!
Fido?
Hello?
Oh, jeez.
Fido!
Stupid collar.
That's Mrs. Henderson.
What am I supposed
to tell Mom and Dad?
You're not supposed to
even be off your leash.
Dad's going to kill me.
Come on.
I got to get you cleaned up.
Hi, Cindy.
My mom and your mom
think we should be friends.
Oh.
Sorry.
That's okay. I don't mind.
Well, bye.
You're not allowed to have a zombie
without a leash.
You're a kid.
I don't care about
stupid Zomcon rules.
Here comes my dad,
and he sure cares.
- Hello, Tommy.
- It's Timmy.
Right you are, sweetheart.
Is that blood on your zombie?
Uh, it was a nosebleed.
Well, that's not a fresh zombie.
Only fresh zombies bleed, son.
I meant my nose.
How did blood from your nose
get on to your zombie, then?
I wiped it there.
Daddy, can we go now?
I can't be late for
my first ballet class.
All right, princess.
Get in. Come on.
Okay. Bye, Timmy.
I hate ballet.
I think we're in trouble, boy.
Hmm.
Heart attack, eh?
My grandpa had a heart attack.
You're not so bad, are you, boy?
Too bad you had to go
and eat Mrs. Henderson.
- I don't even want to ask.
- He got dirty.
And how on earth did he get dirty?
We were just in the park...
What were you doing
in the park with the zombie?
You stupid zombie.
Look at what you've done.
I'll never get it cleaned up in time,
and in your father's garage!
You're not allowed in here.
You know that, Timmy.
Mom, when we were
in the park...
Timmy, are you listening to me?
Your father is going to
send the zombie back.
No, Dad always does
what you say.
No, not this time.
Not with a zombie.
And then what are
people going to say?
They're going to say
that the Robinsons are strange,
and they're going to be right.
It's nothing, Mom.
We'll clean this mess up.
Dad won't even know.
I promise.
What was so important that
you needed to tell me, Timmy?
Um, it's Fido.
He protected me
from the bullies.
Fido? Who's Fido?
Fido.
What kind of
a stupid name is Fido?
Who names their zombie, anyway?
Lots of people name
their zombies.
Mr. Theopolis has a name for his.
I bet he does.
At any rate,
zombies don't have heart attacks.
No, I mean before,
when he was alive.
That's what killed him,
like Grandpa.
What...
You know you're not
supposed to talk about your grandfather.
Sorry.
I forgot.
Well, that's quite a thing to forget.
And she's missing since this morning?
Well, she's always
wandering off on her own.
I'm sure she'll turn up.
Mr. Henderson should have put her
in a retirement home years ago.
Really, Bill!
What would Francis do without her?
He'd be all alone.
Those homes are very comfortable
and... secure.
They're only secure because
they use the old prison.
Well... she is over 65, Helen,
and old people can't be trusted.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, we had a lot of trouble
with old people during the war.
Jonathan, please.
He never gets tired of talking about
that dreadful war.
You must have been, what, 10?
Uh... 11.
Any kills?
Just... one.
Someone close to home?
It was his father.
But you're fine now, aren't you, honey?
Yep.
Well, you did what
you had to, Robinson.
It's a terrible thing,
the Zombie War.
Families having to kill their own.
Never lose sight of that.
I'd take Dee Dee's head off
in a second if I had to.
He always says that.
Don't let 'em get too close.
It makes it harder to pull the trigger.
Well, that went well.
What is it, Timmy?
I just hope a zombie
didn't get Mrs. Henderson.
What a thing to say.
Well, what if somebody's
zombie did attack her?
What then?
Well, we all remember
what happened to the Johnsons
when their zombie
ate those Christmas carolers.
Did Zomcon really chuck them
into the Wild Zone?
That's probably how
the Bottoms got their house.
Bill.
Let's just say there's a very good reason
we don't have prisons anymore.
Bill.
Well, Helen,
he's gotta learn someday.
Can't keep denying it.
Timmy, I think it's nice that you're
caring so much about Mrs. Henderson.
But I think she's gonna be just fine.
Come here.
Come on! Come on!
Come on. No more mistakes
on Daddy's rug.
No, no, no. We're not going anywhere
until you do your business.
Spike, come here.
You're being a naughty boy
tonight, huh?
Why are you being such a naughty boy
Oh, no.
Stay away, Mrs. Henderson.
Sorry, Mrs. Henderson.
You weren't very nice,
Mrs. Henderson.
But I'm really sorry you're dead.
Now you're in a garden.
You always liked plants.
So I hope that's okay.
Shh. You'll wake up
Mom and Dad.
Fido?
Oh, no. Your collar.
Hey, Timmy?
Zombie troubles?
Okay.
Now, Tammy.
All right.
Okay.
It's okay, boy.
Hey!
You trying to get yourself killed?
No.
Let me tell you something.
I've had some pretty
close calls with my Tammy.
Lookee here.
You want that?
Not the teeth, Tammy.
Good girl.
She looks good for a zombie.
Same as the day I met her.
She was shopping in the grocery store
for candy corn with her mom.
Had some kind of
a brain aneurysm.
They slapped a collar on her before
she even hit the floor.
Got her before there was
any decomposition.
Where'd you get all this stuff?
Part of my severance package
when I quit Zomcon.
Hey!
Will you look at that?
Watch this.
Here you go, Sparky.
You used to be a smoker, boy?
Old habits die hard.
You wanna rip
my face off, don't you.
Oh, yes.
You wanna eat me for dinner.
How come zombies wanna eat people?
You know...
I don't know.
Geiger used to say it was their way
of trying to come back to life.
Would that work?
Not a chance.
He was a strange bird, Geiger.
I think that when
his wife went zombie,
he couldn't stand the thought
of losing her.
That's why he invented the collar
in the first place.
Okay.
Go ahead, Tammy.
Now...
not a word of this to anyone.
Not your mom, not your dad.
This will be our little secret...
or it's free lawn mowing for a year.
Yes, sir.
Much better. There you go.
Is that Dad's suit?
Yes.
And we don't need to
mention it to your father.
He won't even notice.
You look great, boy.
Not bad at all.
Hurry, your father's waiting.
Do we have to go?
These Sunday drives are
very important to your father.
How would it look if we didn't
go together as a family?
But it's weird.
We never know anybody.
Well, maybe this time we will.
Oh, I love this park.
It's so peaceful.
Come here, puppy.
Come on.
Come have some cheese.
Have some cheese.
They seem, in the view
of the foolish, to be dead.
And their passing away
was part of affliction,
and their going forth
from us utter destruction.
But they are in peace.
For if before men indeed
they be punished...
Is that zombie wearing my suit?
What would you suggest, Bill?
That I buy him a new one?
Why didn't you leave him
the way he was?
They way he was dressed?
Come on, Bill.
Head coffin, please.
Head coffin.
This guy's not coming back,
you can bet on that.
Shh.
Look. This is the best part.
Emmitt Mitchell,
from dust have you come
and to dust shall you return...
...and from dust shall
you not be resurrected.
So if a person dies
and becomes a zombie,
then they're not really dead.
No, not really.
Well...
it's like being in purgatory
before going to heaven.
What is your father doing?
So... zombies are sinners?
L... I suppose
we're all sinners, honey.
But God sees
the good in everyone.
God loves zombies, too?
Even when they kill?
Well, l... I think zombies kill
because it's their nature.
So then it's not their fault.
No, not really.
What are you so happy about?
I was just gonna
tell you something.
You know what Herman
the gravedigger just told me?
- Bill, Timmy was...
- Only 10% of people get funerals.
Most become zombies.
Can you believe that?
Well, they are expensive.
I'd rather be a zombie than dead.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on there!
Timmy is making observations
about the world.
I think it's healthy.
Observation about the world?
He's a kid.
What does he know?
He knows a lot.
At least he's not
obsessed with funerals.
Better than focusing
on walking corpses...
who should be buried...
without their heads.
Hey!
We're all getting funerals.
All three of us!
Bill, get your own funeral.
Timmy and I are going zombie.
Would you look at that?
Zomcon at the Hendersons'.
I wonder why they're
taking Francis away.
He probably gave her
an illegal funeral...
without a permit.
Is that bad?
Oh, yes.
Oh, dear!
This is how it always starts.
Oh, Bill.
One wild zombie, Helen.
That's all it takes.
Hey, that's the schoolteacher.
Any sign of the old lady?
God, I hate old people!
I'll be right back.
It's just water, boy.
Come on!
You missed a spot.
Hi, boys.
Hi, Mom.
I thought you two might be thirsty.
Timmy! Timmy!
Don't be cruel.
Timmy!
What's going on?
I was just bringing
the boys something to drink.
Zombies don't drink, Helen.
Yes, they can, Bill.
They just don't have to.
We can pretend, can't we?
It doesn't hurt anybody, does it?
Hey!
Give me that.
This is detail work.
It needs to be done delicately
if you're gonna protect the finish.
That's why they call it
"a man's job."
Flesh-eating maniacs
need not apply.
Hey, Helen.
Floyd.
Hey, get a move on, Robinson.
Um...
Why don't you...
stay with us today,
and we can be a family?
Besides, you don't even like Floyd.
You told me yourself.
I said Floyd cheats at golf.
I didn't say I didn't like him.
Bill...
I have a secret to tell you.
You... You're all wet, Helen.
I only had one rule.
Which rule was that?
Very funny, mister.
Get this zombie chained up.
Now!
Bye, honey!
Now what is that?
This is her walker... thingy, sir.
At least that's what our witnesses say.
We caught these two in the bushes
firing their.22s at the wild zombies.
The little one?
Shot Dougie in the leg.
Get that out of sight, will ya?
It's a boot. Put it back.
So let me get this straight.
You're saying that the Robinson zombie
tried to eat you
and then moved on
to Mrs. Henderson.
Is that right?
Yes, sir.
Well, I don't see any bite marks.
Well, he actually didn't
try to bite us.
Shut up, Stan!
He broke my arm.
Do you know what I think?
I think that you shot the old lady
just like, uh...
just like you shot
Dougie over there.
No way! It's all
Timmy Robinson's fault.
You got nothing
to worry about now, boy.
Dad loves ya!
Come on!
They'll never split us up, Fido! Ever!
Whoo!
Come on, boy!
That was fun, boy.
Did you like swimming?
You know,
I didn't even know you could swim.
We gotta get you back
before Dad comes home.
Don't do anything, boy.
"Boy"?
Let's just shoot him now, Roy.
Nah. Let's stick to the plan.
What are you doing?
We're gonna be heroes.
What... What are you
talking about?
We know your zombie
killed the old lady.
We told Bottoms, and he's gonna send
your whole family to the Wild Zone.
- What?
- Shut up, Stan!
He would have believed us, too,
if you'd let me do the talking.
- You're the one who blew it.
- Shut up! You're wrecking the fun.
- I'm just saying...
- Shut up!
- Roy, stop telling me...
Okay, Robinson...
I'm gonna shoot him dead
just before he gets to you.
I'm gonna save your life
from the zombie.
He's gonna pay for everything.
Do it, Roy!
Jeez, Roy! Blast him!
Oh, crap! You made me
shoot my stupid brother!
Oh, jeez!
Please don't eat me, Fido.
I knew you wouldn't eat me, boy.
I knew it.
Hurry and untie me.
You're right, boy.
It's not gonna work.
You gotta go for help.
You better clean up first.
Quick, Fido.
Please!
Good boy!
That'll hold him.
Now go get Mom.
Fido, wait!
You promise not to eat Mom, right?
I got it!
I got it! Stand aside.
- It's Joe Peterson.
- Not anymore he ain't.
Well...
Little rusty.
Okay.
Bull's-eye.
Hey.
Nice shot.
Goodness, Fido, you scared me.
What is it?
Where's Timmy?
What...
Is something wrong?
Is Timmy in trouble?
Please, someone help!
Which way, Fido?
Is this the right way?
Hold on.
Your collar!
Why aren't you eating me?
For goodness sake, Fido.
Help!
Which way now, Fido?
Help! Help!
Get away!
Mom!
Oh, Timmy!
Thank God you're all right.
God! Timmy!
You crazy wonderful zombie.
You never saw this.
They were zombies, and they
were going to kill you.
I know, Mom.
I did what I had to do.
I know.
And I don't want you thinking that what we did
is normal or okay in any way.
I don't.
- Nice shot.
- Thanks.
It's so nice to see
Cindy with a friend.
She doesn't have many?
We're always moving.
It's...
It's hard for any of us
to make friends.
Jonathan seems
to like it that way.
Bill's lived in Willard his entire life,
and he still doesn't have any friends.
And he definitely likes it that way.
He must be excited
about the new baby.
He hasn't even noticed.
How could he not notice?
You want another beer?
I wouldn't say no.
Dee Dee, get us a couple of
cold ones, will ya?
Coming right up, dear.
Hey. You're not actually gonna get him
another beer, are you?
Get your own beer, Bill.
Come on. Let me
show you the war room.
So that Helen of yours...
What a live wire.
"Get your own beer, Bill."
Makes you wonder what's going on
in that little head of hers.
You can say that again.
My first kill.
That is Uncle Bob.
Now, I gather it was
Helen's idea to get a zombie.
Yes, it was.
She seems pretty friendly with it.
What are you suggesting?
Look, Robinson, when people
get attached to their zombies,
it, uh... it only spells trouble.
Trouble for me,
trouble for you...
trouble for Mrs. Henderson.
Mrs... Mrs. Henderson?
Somebody's zombie got her.
Did they?
Well, I don't know, Robinson.
Why don't you tell me.
Chances are you know
a lot more than you think.
Well, that was fun.
Timmy, go to bed.
Helen, we have to talk.
Oh, lighten up, Bill.
Helen.
I am trying to have a serious discussion
with you, Helen.
Turn that off, Helen!
What is that damn zombie
doing in my E-Z Boy?
Bill.
We haven't danced
since our wedding night.
This is hardly the time.
Come on, Bill.
Dance with me.
I don't...
Helen.
That... is enough.
Well, if you're not
gonna dance with me,
I know someone who will.
Bill! Bill!
Nighty-night.
I'm sorry about Bill.
He's...
He's just...
I wish I would have known you before.
Before you died.
Do you remember that?
Can I see that?
"Timmy... R."
Fido?
Fido!
What are you doing with Fido?
Oh, I think we both know
what's gonna happen to Fido.
No! You can't!
He didn't do anything wrong!
Well, maybe he didn't,
but you did.
And because you made
friends with a zombie,
a lot of nice people
in this neighborhood got killed.
You didn't think of that, did you?
Timmy...
do you know that I could
send you and your whole family
to the Wild Zone
for what you've done?
How do you think
I got the Johnson place?
But I had a nice talk
with your parents,
and they assured me that nothing like this
would ever happen again.
Isn't that right, Helen?
Go to your room.
Now.
Yes, sir.
These little problems are
all about containment.
And Floyd hits this big slice into
the clubhouse,
and the ball hits old man Patterson
right between the eyes.
I thought we were gonna have
our first zombie golfer.
How come they blame the bullies
for Mrs. Henderson getting killed?
Well, we're just lucky to have a neighbor
like Mr. Bottoms.
Your mother is right, Tim.
But Fido had to die.
The bullies got blamed
for it anyways.
Mom killed the bullies
and didn't tell anyone.
How come she didn't
get in trouble?
Why... Why are we
talking about this?
I thought we agreed we weren't gonna have
to talk about this!
Bill, where are you going?
I loved Fido, too, you know.
- You did?
- Yeah.
Well...
in a way I did.
Like Mr. Theopolis loves Tammy?
No, he does not.
Like a friend, Timmy.
Just like that.
You see, Timmy, the thing
about your dad...
is that he is still
a part of this family.
He is?
Of course he is.
Why would you say
something like that?
I think he loves us.
I do.
I just think that
he's afraid to admit it.
Dad, you just
passed the school.
Oh.
So I did.
Bye, Dad.
Uh, Timmy...
uh...
Look, l... I know it's hard.
I understand.
You do?
Sure I do.
Look, son...
I know when you're a kid,
you feel things.
A lot of...
things.
But you have to get over that.
Get over what?
Feelings.
Not important, okay?
Being alive is what counts.
Wait a minute. I got something.
Go on. Open it.
- It's a gun.
- Take it out.
I know you're not supposed to have
a handgun...
until you're 12...
but it can come in real handy.
What do you say?
Thanks, Dad.
This will just be between us.
Keep it in your book bag.
Don't forget the bullets.
There you go.
Have a good day, Tim.
Bye, Dad.
Bill?
Do you think we did the right thing
sending Fido back?
I had a great chat with Tim today.
I think everything is
gonna be just fine.
Really?
Absolutely.
Bill, do you love me?
I'm pregnant.
Oh.
I'm sure it's nothing.
You're just gaining a little weight.
Helen.
I just don't think on my salary
I can afford another funeral.
- Are you sure?
- I heard Daddy on the phone.
He said he never wastes
a good zombie.
He's got him working the factory.
Can you get us in there?
Are you crazy?
My dad would kill me.
No, I mean he really would kill me.
But I know someone who can.
Not the teeth, baby.
Good girl.
Mr. Theopolis?
Yeah.
Is Tammy your girlfriend?
What do you mean?
Cindy says that she's your girlfriend,
and you got fired from Zomcon
for having a zombie girlfriend.
She said that?
Aren't you worried
they'll take her away?
Nah.
I'll just get me another one,
the same vintage.
Hey, I'm kidding.
I went and hurt her feelings.
So, you clear on the plan?
Yeah.
- Theopolis.
- Hi, Frank.
What are you doing back here?
Oh, you know, just bringing the old unit
in for a tune-up.
It's, um... Tammy.
- Right?
- That's right. Tammy.
So...
Okay, go ahead.
Thanks, Frank.
Timmy!
Bill!
If Timmy hadn't broken
the rules in the first place,
none of this would have happened.
He messed up, not me.
I suppose you think he got so attached
to the damned thing
because I'm a bad father.
I'd say I'm a pretty
darn good father.
My father tried to eat me.
I don't remember trying to eat Timmy.
Bill, just because your father
tried to eat you,
does that mean we all have to be
unhappy...
forever?
Welcome to Zomcon's
returns department.
Please... stay with your zombie
at all times,
maintain an orderly line
between the railings,
and use our conveniently
placed safety buttons...
Come on.
- Are you all right, Mr. Theopolis?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Now, the door into the factory
is right behind the clerk.
Are you ready?
All right.
Honey...
I'm gonna be gone
for a little while,
and then I'm gonna
come back, all right?
You stay here.
All right. Let's do this.
Wild zombie! Wild zombie!
That's my Tammy.
You... You knucklehead!
Fido?
All right, seal off the returns room...
and shut off that damned alarm.
You naughty little boy.
No, not you.
I'll call you back.
Fido?
Fido!
I'll be right down!
Hello, Timmy.
No!
Turn the car around.
We need to keep the road clear.
Of course, Frank.
- What's happening here?
- I'll call it in!
This way! This way!
Timmy!
Bill, give me that gun.
I'm going in.
You stay here
in case Timmy shows up.
No, l... I want to.
Bill, give me the shotgun.
I am a good father.
Bill!
Remember, Helen...
head coffin.
- I just wanna show you something.
- You can't make me go!
- Come on!
- No!
Now... take a look,
all right?
Out there is chaos.
And in here is safety.
People who don't understand that
end up on the wrong side
of the fence.
Now go on and make yourself
some friends.
No! No!
Let me out! Please!
Stay away from me.
Come on, Robinson.
All right. All right.
Fido, it's you.
Where's Timmy Boy?
They're not particularly fast,
are they?
Fido!
Dad!
Robinson?
I'd like you to let my son
back inside the gate now, please.
I don't think so.
Now you be quiet!
Help!
Leave him alone!
Dad!
Get him, boy!
Fido! Behind you!
Mom!
Where's your father?
Get in.
See you later, Frank.
My God.
Zomcon forces spent
Saturday afternoon
securing a Wild Zone breach
within Willard's own
Zomcon Containment Center.
Human casualties were low,
but the nation mourns one of its greatest
and most respected war heroes.
Zomcon Chief John Bottoms
died valiantly
while defending
the people of Willard
from a wild zombie outbreak
caused by this man...
Frank Murphy,
a once-trusted Zomcon
security guard,
who was caught accepting bribes
from a renegade group
of wild zombie poachers.
Are you ready, dear?
Head coffin, please.
Bill Robinson...
from dust have you come,
and to dust shall you return.
But from dust shall you not be
resurrected.
It's what he always wanted.
Okay, Tammy,
just what you ordered.
Now don't you move a muscle.
There's only one Tammy
in the world, right?
Nice catch!
Hi, Timmy. Hi, Fido.
Hi, Timmy.
Surprised?
Sort of.
It's okay.
He's so cool in a way.
And he's a lot nicer.
- Do you wanna play catch?
- Sure.
Does, uh, your zombie
wanna play?
What do you call him, anyways?
I don't know.
Right now I'm just calling him Daddy.
Sure. Okay.
Come on.
Come on, Daddy.
Subtitled By J.R. Media Services
Burbank, CA
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org