Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
His name is Martin McGartland,
and when I met him, he was an unemployed
Catholic hood selling stolen goods.
These are a guarantee for action,
all for a couple of quid, like.
- Take yourself off.
- Do you have a daughter?
I had you down for something
a wee bit silky. Oh, come on, it's sexy.
Martin helped support his family.
I liked that about him.
# OK, there's the trident in Bangor
# Then you walk back to the city
- We don't want any.
- Wait. Don't go.
Have you any Hugo Boss?
- Only the entire line at my fingertips.
- All right.
# An alternative Ulster
# Alternative Ulster #
No, there's no way, man. No way.
Please?
I'll do you nine
if you take the Hugo Boss for ten.
- Done. Do you wanna have a look, Lara?
- You know I'm not.
Thank God there's you and the Pope
looking after our souls.
You're under the wrong impression.
These goods are not stolen.
They're manufacturer overruns.
How about some shoes, Mrs Flaherty?
I can get you any shoes you like,
anything from this catalogue.
There's no point in me looking, love.
Well, not that I care
where it comes from.
Hmm. Hmm.
- Well, maybe next month.
- OK. Grand.
- Can I have another tenner?
- No, you cannot.
- Please.
- What did you do with that 20?
- I don't know.
- If there's anything you...
Jobs were generally controlled
by the Protestants,
which meant most of the young
Catholic men were unemployed,
...and angry about it.
Martin and his mate sean
had survived on the edge so long,
they didn't know any other way.
No way, man.
Who'd you kill for this, you wanker?
1800 twin cam.
Nought to 60 in seven seconds.
Outrun any peeler in the city.
The boot's a wee bit small,
but it'll do.
I can get you a deal anytime.
It's no use.
I can't afford the petrol.
And that's where I come in.
I was a peeler. That's what they call
the police in Belfast.
I was a handler with the special Branch.
My code name was Fergus.
Police made the first effort
to get marchers away from the area...
You see, by 1988, Belfast
had been a battleground for 20 years.
Irish Republican Army against
the Unionists' Ulster Defence Force.
Both were illegal armies.
It was about freedom.
Police barricaded all roads.
Unionists want Northern Ireland
to stay as part of the UK.
Catholic Republicans
want free of British rule.
Both sides were willing to kill
for their cause.
By 1969, violence had become so bad,
British troops were sent in
to keep the peace.
They've been there ever since.
To the IRA,
they were also an occupying army.
B-20.
We have a report of sniper fire.
Two officers down. send available
blue lights to Falls Road area.
This is B-20 out.
- This is B-21...
- Is everybody all right?
- Outcome?
- Result.
...six shots fired.
Two officers down. Two casualties.
Go on, you mad bastard.
Tell the boys to pull out.
Two officers down,
two casualties. send blue lights.
Over.
K-9 response to Falls Road.
six shots fired.
Trying to locate gunmen. Looks IRA.
We had real respect for the IRA
as a military force.
We sealed the communities,
Protestants on one side of the walll
Catholics on the other.
We couldn't stop what was happening...
...because we didn't have
the minds of the people.
In war, truth is the first casualty, and
information is as powerful as bullets.
Growing up an Irish Catholic lad
in a Republican community...
...where police and security forces were
not trustedl Martin had few choices.
You've never done a day's work
in your life.
But he was his own man, and so he had
real potential to work with us.
I don't think stealing cars
is employment.
Depends on how you look at it.
If the peelers catch you this time,
you're fucked.
- Tell me you didn't steal that car.
- I didn't steal that car.
He could make a difference.
All I had to do was convince him.
- Where you off to, lads?
- Just going to the shops.
- All right. Name?
- Mickey Mouse.
- What street are you from?
- Sesame Street.
- No, Mickey Mouse is Disneyland.
- Aye, right, Disneyland, eh?
- Yeah, yeah. Where are you going?
- Didn't you hear him?
We're going to the shops.
It's me sister's birthday.
- We're getting her a present.
- A wee bike.
- Name.
- You fucking hard of hearing?
Mickey Mouse.
Are you gonna shoot him, is that it?
Now you're gonna shoot me?
First you and now it's me.
Go ahead, man. Shoot.
Go on, man. Fire away.
Fuckin' shoot me, man.
Is someone gonna do something
about this psycho here?
It's all right. Put it down.
Wait! After them, lads!
Peelers!
Fuck!
After doing 90 on the Shankill,
your mate Sean spun out,
took off before the officers chasing him
could say "wanker".
I gather you're in sales.
A bloke like you gets around the area.
Not me, man.
I make it a point to see nothing.
How about easy cash,
the kind that doesn't see you
going to jail for selling stolen goods?
I show you some faces,
you tell us what you see them doing.
What makes you think
that I would be a tout for anybody?
The comings and goings
of a few neighbours...
...is not exactly being an informer,
or a "tout" as you call it.
A car. No record.
Not even on police files yet.
Martin didn't go
for any of our usual offers or threats.
He sold stolen goods in Catholic areas
against strict IRA rules...
...which were brutally enforced.
Are we done? Can I go now, please?
He wasn't afraid of them.
Which is why I also knew
I could trust him.
- Well?
- I'll take him out on a road test.
If he's useless, I'll give him to MI5,
tell them he's bloody brilliant.
Whoa, ho, ho, ho! Jeez, Paddy.
You watching your family videos again?
Ray came by
to make your acquaintance.
Marty's been working for me.
Like I say, he's a good lad.
- Is he?
- Fuck this.
Didn't have anything on you, did they?
Here you go, Paddy. Oh, Jesus.
How you doin', Ray?
So, Martin,
Sean here says you're a good man.
- Look, man, I didn't see nothin'.
- That's true, you didn't.
And you'd do well to remember that.
I know your ma.
She's a good woman.
- Thanks for what you did today.
- Aye, no problem.
We'll not forget it.
Aye.
Sean, man, how do you know him?
- He's IRA.
- Is he, now?
- He is.
- Where's me money?
Paddy, is there any chance of getting
a pair of these in black? Size eight?
Oh, please, God, no.
It's a pipe! It's just a pipe!
The bathroom's just upstairs.
Do I look like I shot anybody?
Hey, hey!
What reason could you have
to search my house for guns?
Two officers have just been shot.
You're Irish.
- Where were you two hours ago?
- Playing football.
- Bullshit!
- You're only gonna make it worse!
I didn't raise you
to be thick as a plank!
If you were anywhere near this trouble,
I'll drag you to the police!
- I had nothing to do with it!
- Evil can only do its work...
...if decent people turn a blind eye,
even if only for a moment.
Keep searching!
He's made an impression
on the IRA for sure, right up the line.
From here on, I'm out.
Can't figure out what you'd want
with a 10p hood like him.
What's this? Huh? What's this?
Heading round your ma's house
to do a wee bit of fixing?
Wouldn't be for stealing cars, would it?
Not our Frankie.
Breaking into people's houses? Yeah?
Yeah? Joyriding their cars?
Now I'm hearing about drugs.
These are crimes against the community,
my friend, and you've been found guilty.
It's not me. I swear.
What?
No! Help! Help!
- Fuck!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What the...
What the fuck are yous after?
Is that it?
You're one lucky wee fucker, Frankie.
If I'd have brought my. 357, your
football career would've been done for.
You want this lying down or standing up?
- Standing.
- Right.
No! No! Fuckin' leave him!
- Leave him!
- My jeans.
Fuck yourjeans. The peelers mightn't
give a shite about our community...
...and how wankers like you
fuck it up for everyone,
but we do, so thank God for the IRA.
- You bastard!
- Frankie!
- Fucking bastard!
- That's my brother!
That's my wee brother! Frankie!
Funny coincidence running into you, huh?
Frankie! Frankie!
That's for getting involved
in something that doesn't concern you.
I'm assuming you've no plans for
this evening. Someone wants to meet you.
Fucking bastards!
Fred. Fred.
You know that kid Martin McGartland?
Well, I've taken a special interest.
Goddamn it.
That's been less than ten minutes.
Who told you about the meeting
with Mickey Johnson?
Just lose the file.
And not a word to anyone, right?
Yeah, right.
Jesus Christ.
Sorry about the drama.
You've gotta be careful.
Would you get us some ice
and a tea towel there, love?
I hear the Brits
took your ma's house apart.
No warrant, no cause.
Picked you up for questioning.
Dogs have more rights.
Here. Thanks, love. Away and make
yourself a wee cup of tea there.
I can see
you don't partake in loose talk...
...or I'd be behind bars now.
Seems to me like we're on the same side.
You're a go-getter.
I've been asking around.
A kid like you deserves to work
at something, build a future.
Do you know why you can't get a job?
Because it makes you easier to beat.
The Brits underestimate us.
This war is being fought
on our own footpaths, in our gardens,
in our living rooms.
Makes for a special kind of man who's
defending his own home and community.
I'm thinking maybe
you'd wanna be part of something
that's bigger than your skinny wee arse.
Bigger than mine.
It's as big as a country.
Well? Do you want the job?
OK.
Paddy's nothing but a wheeler-dealer.
That's a sure way
of getting your legs broken.
A fence is just a tout in training,
so you're finished with him, OK?
You got a car?
Aye, I do.
Mickey Johnson ran a taxi
company and was high up in the IRA,
Drivers were a perfect way to recruit.
I knew Martin would be pissed off by
the IRA for taking out Frankie's knees.
Maybe he'd see Mickey's job as an
opportunity to get a car and to help us.
That was my hook.
In my world, timing is everything,
and occasionally we get lucky.
I've been asking around for you.
I'm glad you're OK.
I'm fine, no problem.
Come here, Frankie.
I'll get you in. You OK?
You'll be OK, man. Look at me, Frankie.
I'm sorry, mate, you know?
I wish I could have helped you, man.
There was nothing I could have done, OK?
Frankie's got an appointment
at the Royal. Bloody taxis. We're late.
I'm sure we've missed his doctor.
Next week
he goes on Tuesday and Thursday.
- Maybe I can give you a lift.
- You got a car?
Aye, definitely. Yeah.
That'd be brilliant,
wouldn't it, Frankie?
- Tuesday'd be grand.
- I'll pick you up on Tuesday, OK?
- Four o'clock?
- Aye, definitely.
There's a right way and a wrong way
to do this. He's not in our pocket yet.
Pick him up.
Let's see what he's made of.
Worst case, he ends up
another statistic in jail or the morgue.
I don't see a downside.
He doesn't listen. That's his problem.
- Fuckin' wanker.
- Hey.
What did you say?
- Take him.
- Come here, love.
- What did you say?
- Don't be starting anything.
- Did you say something to me?
- Marty, just walk away.
Move on. OK, move on. Good man.
OK, why would you do that?
You're gonna point that at me now?
- Oh, my God! Marty, what are you doing?
- Why'd you do that? Are you sick?
Sick in the head? Is that it?
Sick bastard!
I had a wee baby in my arms!
I had a wee baby!
- Get back there!
- Against the wall!
Ma!
- Marty!
- You're coming with us right now.
- Fuck off.
- I'm his mother!
- Stay back.
- I was just walking. He kicked me.
Ma, I swear to God
I didn't do anything! I swear!
He's assaulted an officer
and he's going down to the station.
Bloody idiots were supposed to
pick you up, not start a riot.
What the hell's going on?
Are you setting me up?
A desperate man
goes to desperate measures.
I'm Fergus.
That's a terrible thing
happened to your mate Frankie.
I'm sure the sister, Lara, forgot
to tell you, her mother got the shoes.
Thinks you're a rock star.
Hopefully I've impressed you
with our thoroughness because...
I need your help.
You met with Mickey Johnson.
- Never seen him.
- This is about lives and saving them.
They'll do to you what they did
to Frankie, only worse.
They're terrorists, killers who've found
a cause to kill for.
Terrorists? Is that what you think, huh?
Terrorists?
Well, I don't see anyone tearing up
your house 'cause you're Irish,
hauling your arse out, getting the shit
kicked out of you by soldiers for fun.
Huh?
The Brits have never been in Ireland
by invitation,
so who's the fucking terrorist?
I'm offering you a job
you can feel good about.
They'll offer you a job
that'll likely get you killed.
It's harder to live for your country
than die for it.
A car's expensive.
My gift to you. No strings.
You see,
I'm betting murder isn't in you.
Memorise this number,
then flush the card. Call me anytime.
Tell them your name's John Brown.
Ask for Fergus. They'll find me.
How do I know that's not bugged?
Well, why would we bother?
One phone call, I know where you are.
You wanna give me money
and a car for nothing?
That's fine by me.
Hop along, Frankie.
Give me those.
How'd you afford
a set of wheels?
Because I got a job.
- You? You got a real job?
- Aye, a real job. I'm a taxi driver.
- Where's your licence?
- You need a licence now, do you?
I thought we were in Belfast,
you wee shit.
This is brilliant.
Don't mind our Frankie.
He's fine.
Listen, I was just wondering
if maybe I could take you out.
Maybe see a film
or grab some dinner or something.
Sure. Dinner?
OK.
Look, I think I'm free on Thursday.
Is that OK?
- OK. You're on.
- OK.
Frankie, don't mind him.
He's got a real job.
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
- So where are we going?
- The Europa Hotel, man.
Oh, I need you to pick my daughter up
for school in the morning. Is that OK?
Aye, no problem.
- Nice shirt.
- What, this?
- Hmm.
- I can pick one up for you if you like.
Come on. It's not like that.
...so how do you like driving a taxi?
- It beats working for Paddy.
- No complaints about the hours?
- I like it.
- You're one of my best drivers.
You're reliable. That counts for
everything. Know who you remind me of?
I don't remind you of anybody.
I'm not like anybody else.
My ma always said
I'm like one in a million.
- A million. That's what my ma told me.
- Aye, you're full of shit.
- Who do I remind you of?
- Wee Aggie.
Who's Aggie?
I wouldn't trust him with my wife,
but I trust him with my life.
Ah! I've got
a bloody spring in me arse.
No wonder your aunt gave you
this shitbox for free.
Up yours, man.
I could have got you a deal
on a real car.
And end up with the peelers on my tail,
man? No, thank you.
You're a tube.
- There he is.
- Here he comes.
Sean, where are you going, man?
You'll catch up with Sean later.
If God is good and we're lucky.
We're going for a spin. Follow that car.
It's a nice day.
Go north to the M5.
Head for Larne.
Mate, I'm sorry,
but I was pretty much finished my shift.
I got a big, big night coming up.
You'll be finished
when I'm finished.
Fine. I'll just keep
my mouth shut, then, will I?
Turn left into that parking lot
there and park. Aye.
Just over there.
You stay here.
I'll look and be right back.
And then you can get on
with your big night.
Now, is there a problem?
- No problem.
- Good.
Good enough. Let's go.
Hello, yeah.
Can I speak to Fergus, please?
My name? John. John Brown.
So whatever you wanna do.
Just wear something slinky.
It's a really fancy place.
I'll pick you up at eight, OK?
All right, speak soon.
I'll be there at eight. All right, bye.
- Sounds like Marty's got a date.
- I do, I do.
I'm sorry, Ray. You're just not invited.
Listen, take her...
Take her somewhere nice. Yeah?
- Oh, my God. It's on fire.
- Is it meant to do that?
It's the chef's signature dish.
Of course.
- It looks smashing.
- Aye, it does. It really does.
- My pleasure.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- So you never answered my question.
- What question was that?
- Don't duck it. You have an opinion.
- I'm not ducking.
I'm not. I don't have an opinion.
You're Irish.
You were born with an opinion.
What are you thinking?
I was thinking whether your ma
liked them shoes that I got her.
- That's what I was thinking.
- Yes.
- She practically slept with them on.
- Did she?
You achieved sainthood.
So?
How did we get
from me being thrown out of school
to suddenly my belief in God, anyway?
Like, I wanna know about you.
Like, what's your favourite band?
OK, I'm not saying I don't believe
in God. I do believe in God.
But he's probably not a Catholic God.
I don't think God's sitting on a cloud
trying to figure out whether he's
Protestant or Catholic or Buddhist.
Everyone's got big opinions about how
you should live and who you should love.
The government, the peelers, the
Catholics, the Protestants, the Brits.
I mean, any of them is full of it...
...if they think that they know more about
you or me or God than anybody else.
They're more interested
in killing than living,
which is hard enough to do,
keep up with the everyday shit.
Morrissey, Guns N' Roses,
the Pogues and U2, of course.
Jimmy Page is probably
one of the finest guitar players alive,
and Prince is great for having sex.
# Up on the roof
No fear of falling
# With my girl at my beck and callin'
# I kiss her once and hold her tightly
# With a smile on my face
I know I could do this nightly
# Her warm embrace
Her face excites me
- Where are we, anyway?
- Near Larne.
You know, someone told me about
this pub. Do you wanna check it out?
What's going on there?
- Do you know him?
- I don't know him.
You, get back. Move it
out of here. Behind the line.
Go on, move it. Move it. Come on.
OK. We're moving.
- Move it back now.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Move back.
- Under there. Come on.
Did I ever tell you I wanted to
go to Disney World before I die?
Aye, you don't stop going on about it,
you and Minnie Mouse.
Tell you what, give us a lift home.
I always give you a lift.
You rode Lara, didn't you?
You keep track of her period or you'll
be shopping for nappies. Good man.
- Taking advice from the model da?
- My kids are beautiful.
Besides, being a da's not easy.
It's got its responsibilities...
Fuck me. How you doin'?
That's a nice bum. Aye.
We sickened 'em today.
It's one for our side.
Look, you gotta expect a bit of killing,
a bit of dying in a revolution.
That's the way things work.
Besides, you're not a man
unless you've got a cause.
Give us a lift.
Two soldiers died.
Two are critical.
- I didn't see anything.
- Why are you working for them?
I'm not working for them like that.
I've been driving Mickey around.
They asked me to pick up Quinn,
so I did.
- And they trust you?
- Like I said, it's not like that.
Why?
Well, you called me.
Why? What's different?
Everything.
You can move on the inside.
Dead men will be walking around
and becoming grandfathers...
...because of you.
That's my community.
Like, I know some of these people.
Memorise this.
Here's your petrol money.
Thanks for the tea.
Anytime.
Fuck! Stop him!
Hold it!
- Don't you fucking move!
- All right! Don't shoot!
OK, lads, make sure you're at
the Upland place by 12 noon tomorrow.
Mickey, you take the back roads,
dump the cars there and split.
Johnny will look after things here.
And, lads, make sure no one sees you.
OK, let's go!
- It's an odds thing.
- What is?
If the peelers get one of the cars,
the other two are more likely
to get through if we're in a pack.
Besides, with cargo like this,
it keeps us all honest.
Shit.
Sean, what are you doing, man?
Put that away.
I'm serious. Put it away. Put it away.
If this thing blows,
I'll be Jesse fucking James.
Sean, you put that away, man.
Fucking put it away. Put it away.
- That's quite a car.
- Yeah, it's my da's.
Uh-huh. Where are you off to today, son?
We're just picking him up
at the airport, like.
- You're a long way out of your way.
- Well, we had to go to my sister's.
She's moving,
so we're just on our way back round.
- Can I see your licence, please?
- Aye.
I told my da to keep it in there.
He must have forgot.
- Can I take a look in the boot, please?
- Aye, no problem.
You know what's happened?
This is a spare set of keys.
My da's got the main set.
It's not gonna work the boot.
Tell you what. If I give yous a number,
maybe you could speak to my sister.
Have you got a pen?
I can write it down for you.
My da'll beat my arse if I'm late.
If you could just tell my sister you're
calling about Martin McGartland, OK?
Just wait here, mate.
She says she has your keys.
OK. Thank you. That's great. Thank you.
Whoo!
They got nothing on us, they don't.
So who the fuck's your sister?
Uh, it was my ma. Fucking my ma!
Your ma? Bloody hell.
My ma would have let them have me.
Good work, man.
An RUC patrol
calling me like I was your sister?
- Come on. I was brilliant.
- stupid risks cost lives.
Including yours.
So you're my da now? Just get the guns.
Today in Belfast,
residents of...
Detectives said it was highly
significant and certainly curious,
the weapons ranging from...
A haul of nearly 100 guns,
including Kalashnikov rifles,
has been discovered by police...
Three men were arrested,
believed to be connected to the IRA.
Come on. Let's go.
- Who's that?
- He's a target.
And what are you asking questions for?
Listen, Marty,
it could just as easily be him
scouting you and your family. Go.
It's the Protestant church
up near North Road.
The target's got three wee girls.
What else?
Look, this guy's got a family as well.
He's just doing his job, you know?
OK, Ray O'Brien is the shooter.
That's it.
What about Sean?
Look, I don't know nothing about Sean.
I told you that.
You don't get to pick and choose.
This is all in.
Because I finger you, you're dead.
You finger me, I'm dead.
So... there we are.
I wanna show you something.
He has a kid. A ma, a da.
- Is he a tout?
- A tout?
He saved at least 30 lives,
probably more.
He's a goddamn hero.
Your mates tortured him for seven days,
168 hours, until we found him.
Sean doesn't get arrested.
A 400lb bomb was your mate's latest gift
to the city of Belfast,
seven people died,
and you don't want him arrested?
Look, he's my mate. He's got
two kids from two different women.
Aw! Give me a hanky.
No way. I can't do it.
There's no deal. No way.
Then there's no deal.
What if I give you every detail
of every move he makes?
You can shut him down, like.
Come on. I'm into saving my mates
as much as yours.
Look at him. Can't you just look at him?
It's a dirty war, and everyone seems
to think the end justifies the means,
which is why you and your mate
are even walking around.
How do you know I can do it?
You've got no choice.
Neither have I.
I'm not looking for a da.
Just... don't get yourself killed.
- Hello.
- How you doing?
Yeah, not bad.
It's a cold one, isn't it?
- Aye. That time of year, isn't it?
- Aye, definitely.
- Is this all your gang?
- Yeah.
- Hi. What's your name?
- Jane.
Jane, is it? Hello, Jane. I like
yourjacket, Jane. And what's your name?
- Catherine.
- Catherine. And what about you?
- You ready?
- You're cheeky, you are, aren't you?
Aye. Anyway, take it easy.
Have a good one.
Martin.
- What?
- I'm pregnant.
Are you sure?
I did a home pregnancy test,
and at the hospital... Yeah, I'm sure.
That's...
That's something, isn't it?
- It's brilliant. It's fantastic.
- Really?
Come on.
What did you think I was gonna say?
I don't know.
- What about my ma?
- Oh, shit, your ma.
Shit. My ma.
Marty! I have the washing,
but I couldn't find that blue shirt.
What were you doing with the blue...
Lara, love, you can come out now.
Look, the two of yous are adults,
but if you get yourself pregnant,
well, don't go expecting your parents
to treat you any different.
Oh, my. Well, then, I guess
a "congratulations" is in order.
Your father wasn't much of a man
to look to, but you're not him.
You'll do the right thing
or I'll kill you myself.
- Ma, for Christ's sake.
- Well, I'll leave you to make a plan.
- Sorry.
- There's lots to think about.
Oh, shit.
I was so worried.
Me too.
You OK?
I'm not gonna piss off
like my own da, man.
I'm gonna stick around, give the kid
a wee bit of advice here and there.
It's going down on Friday.
You gonna be ready?
I'll be ready.
You're worse than my own ma.
I just don't want you
to embarrass me, is all.
You wouldn't embarrass me, now,
would you?
Wanker.
So, lover boy, what are you gonna do...
...when Lara's ma finds out
that you knocked up her daughter?
Don't you worry about that one.
There's no way we're shacking up.
I've got it.
- Who is it?
- I don't know. I'm just getting it.
I've nowhere else to go.
My mummy, she found out.
Aw, jeez, look,
we can't live here really.
You want to shack up?
Aye. Oh, aye, definitely. Come here.
We'll be all right, huh, baby?
Marty McGartland,
you're full of surprises.
Aye, I know. Now, come on. Get inside.
- I've got school every day, so, like...
- Don't worry about that.
I'm fully employed.
You know that. You know that.
I love you.
Me, too.
At the Portsmouth ferry,
there's a boatload of soldiers
going to England on the 18th.
They're gonna hit the vans in the queue.
Too many civilians for the boat itself
makes for bad press.
Now, I know
they've got a shitload of Semtex,
a load of weapons,
make sure this really goes off.
- You know what Mickey said to me?
- What?
He said he was so pleased
with the Upland operation...
...that he's bumping me up to B Battalion.
- Yes!
- I thought you'd like that.
- I like that.
- You know what else he said?
- What?
- He's sending me to meet McFarlane.
He... Oh, come on. It's bloody
brilliant. That's bloody brilliant.
I'm here to prepare volunteers, in case
you get interrogated by the police.
They'll come in banging in the night,
screaming to confuse you.
Press this button
to get directly through to me.
Punch in a number, I call you.
OK. Appliance of science, that's
brilliant. I like that. Very James Bond.
Ask the duty sergeant to see the doctor
before they beat you.
The harder they hit,
the harder you hit back.
Curl up in a ball and protect your head.
You'll need it.
Unless, of course, they cuff you,
in which case you're fucked.
- I know what I'm doing.
- Oh, yeah?
You know, they'll hold your head
underwater till your eyes are spinning.
Again and again, for a couple of hours.
If they won't let you go to the toilet,
strip right down
in front of them and take a shit.
They'll squeeze your balls
with a pair of pliers,
twist your thumbs out their sockets.
OK, man, like, I get it.
You say one thing,
they'll have you for seven years.
You'll say whatever they want
to make it stop.
Think, outsmart them,
but never underestimate them.
You admit to anything, you'll end up in
a ditch with a cattle prod up your arse.
My car's marked, right? You bugged
my place. I've got this wee buzzer here.
Look, there's someone on my tail
24 hours a day.
Yeah, but it doesn't mean I don't worry.
I'd get up there if you would,
but there's no way I'm going on my own.
The British found out
about the Portsmouth operation.
No shit.
So, ladies,
what are we celebrating, then?
- We just passed our exams, a wee bit.
- Aye. This one got here two As.
- And a B.
- Two As and a B.
Well, cheers to that.
Cheers.
Mm. Don't you worry about this.
I'll go and get the next round.
- Give us a hand, Marty.
- Sean, I don't drink.
Give us a hand. I know you're not.
Sorry.
Two lagers, please.
There's a fucking leak.
They got everything.
Bloody waste of Semtex, it was.
- Brit blood would've spilled.
- Aye, Jesus Christ, what a waste.
If we didn't have bad luck,
we'd have no fucking luck at all.
Fucking peelers, man.
Peeler, yeah. It's times like this,
it makes you think about your family
and puts it all into perspective.
I wanna see my damn kids, you know.
Anyway...
- What's with him?
- He's just drunk.
- Feel that?
- Did it kick? Is it kicking?
- It's a ballerina in there.
- That is a footballer.
- Ballerina.
- Footballer.
- Let's go home and fight about it.
- OK.
Did you know
pregnant girls are extra horny?
- Let's definitely go home, then.
- Let's go.
You make me look brilliant.
I couldn't dodge this meeting.
Head of security'll be there.
- You don't think they're onto me?
- No, they're gonna test you.
Do whatever they ask. If they suspect
you're not 100%, you'll be out or dead,
and, well, we have no one
moving up the inside like you.
Aye. OK.
I'll meet you at five,
usual place. Good luck.
Cut him down.
Sean. Sean. Come on, let's get out.
- I wanna hear him say it.
- He'll say anything right about now.
- What are you gonna do with that?
- Relax, relax, relax.
You're a good lad.
I wanna know about the operation
on Portsmouth, what you told the cops.
I don't know anything
about the operation.
- What did you tell them?
- Nothing.
Both teams are being very
cautious. Nobody is taking the chance.
- What's the score, Sean?
- It's nil-nil.
No! No!
How'd the cops
get you to talk?
Money?
It's not much good to you now, is it?
What are you gonna do with those?
- You're a tout. What are you?
- I'm not! I'm not!
- What are you?
- Nothing!
- A tout.
A tout.
Sean, Sean, turn that off.
All right, lads, listen up.
Speak into that.
I'm a tout.
Just tell my mum I said sorry.
Just tell her I'm sorry.
Good man.
Marty. Marty, come here.
He's a tout.
Stiff him.
- Don't, please.
- Come on, brother. We haven't all day.
Do it! Just fucking do it!
No, don't! Don't kill me! Don't!
What the fuck was that about?
It's my operation.
He's my tout.
Get him out of here.
You... clean up this mess.
- You knew this was gonna happen.
- And you didn't?
- They completely trust you now.
- I had a gun at his head, like.
You said I couldn't do it,
I didn't have murder in me.
I was so scared, I swear to God,
I might have done it.
I lied.
We all have murder in us.
You?
The hunters become the hunted, yes.
Is that what you tell yourself
to make it all OK?
The price of a conscience is death.
None of us can afford it.
They're swearing me in.
I'm gonna be a full volunteer.
Do you have any idea what that means
to the next person you're going to save?
I've put a block on your house.
It means it's off limits to the peelers.
Store weapons for the IRA, we'll trace
'em every time they're moved.
89, Cutland Road, right?
There's an RUC officer
who's gonna be hit by Friday.
They're gonna blow him up
with a car bomb.
Now, is that it?
I'd like to get out now, please.
I don't blame the RUC
for turning my son into an informer.
I don't blame the IRA for killing him.
I blame me son for the choice he made...
...to go against his family
and his community.
It doesn't get any easier, son.
It's all about saving lives, isn't it?
It's gotta be done.
I dream that one day we'll walk
as free men in our own country.
The British have made us
into their poor, stupid cousins.
The IRA is here to show them
that an ounce of resistance...
...is worth a pound of votes.
Do you know who said that?
- No.
- Bobby Sands.
He was quoting Vladimir Lenin,
mastermind of the Russian revolution.
He changed the world and built a nation.
You've been through
the lectures and the books?
Aye.
- Have you been green-booked?
- Aye.
Then you know volunteers who engage
in loose talk shall be dismissed.
Volunteers found guilty of treason
face the death penalty.
I understand.
This is no picnic.
You'll end up dead or in jail.
There's no going back.
Once you're in, you're in.
You understand your responsibility
in the community?
People look up to you.
Behave accordingly.
You've already passed their security,
and Mickey says you're a good lad, so...
I, Martin McGartland,
promise to promote the objects
of the glaigh na hireann...
...to the best of my knowledge and ability,
to obey all orders and regulations...
...issued to me by the army authority
and by my superior officer.
Martin McGartland, you are now a full
volunteer of the Irish Republican Army.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Come on. Come on.
I'm proud of you, son.
The fuckin' Brits
took my son away from me.
I will never let that happen to you.
OK?
Sorry.
- Big things next year.
- Aye, OK.
- You'll be a hero.
- Yeah.
Don't mess this up, Marty.
Come on, man, give us my flag.
You'll have it when you're dead.
Marty, hang about.
There's someone I want you to meet.
Listen, one of our top operatives
needs a right-hand man, OK?
Hello, gents. This the Marty
you've all been talking about?
- They call me Grace.
- Hi. I'm Marty. It's a pleasure.
- Marty's gonna enjoy this assignment.
- Yeah, OK.
Grace Sterrin.
Oh, aye.
- What, you know her, do you?
- I know Grace, yeah.
Then you'll know
she's a nice, nice, nice-looking lady.
We've been trying to get her for years.
She's senior intelligence.
Uses her body like Mata Hari.
I mean, I would have to be forced.
I would consider...
I would definitely give her one.
- You and a few others.
- You would as well, would you?
- Wouldn't you like to know?
- I would, yeah.
Wouldn't you like to fucking know?
I don't wanna know
what's going on in your dirty mind.
She's a big fish,
which means she makes everyone nervous.
People are idiots when they're nervous.
That makes them easy.
- OK, stay outside.
- Mickey told me I could come in.
He's a worrier.
Nothing's gonna happen.
Mickey said, so I've got to do it, OK?
If I'm not out in ten minutes, go home,
'cause it means I'm dead, OK?
- Hiya.
- Hi.
Cheers.
You've reached the home of Lara
and Marty. Please leave a message.
Lara, it's me. Just letting yous know
I'm not gonna be too much longer.
I'll be home pretty soon, OK?
And I was also wondering if there was
any chance you could make me...
...that special apple crumble
that you make?
If you could get that going for dessert,
that would make a working man happy.
Apple crumble?
Listen, I gotta go. OK, bye.
You really shouldn't knock it
till you try it.
- I don't cook.
- What happened in there?
- Like, it didn't take very long.
- I got what I came for.
Want to meet me for a drink later?
Purely social.
I'd love to, but I just don't think
it's a very good idea.
Aye, apple crumble.
Apple crumble.
I really do have
a pretty serious girlfriend.
She's pregnant, and we're
living together and everything.
Just thought a wee drink would be fun.
Here.
Take this to Allan in Turf Lodge.
I told him you'd have it there by one.
If you're late, he'll be thinking
you're up to something.
Jesus Christ!
Man, were you following me?
They gave me this.
When you jumped the ladder,
a platoon started following you.
Next time, take your car.
I have about 12 minutes before
they think I stopped to copy that.
These are prison guards at Maze.
What's this schedule? Football?
I don't have time to talk. Can we just
move on? I've got to get out.
- Lara's water broke.
- What?
Don't worry.
Her ma's taking her to the hospital.
Shit. Shit, shit, shit. Her ma took her?
Yeah. Even mothers forgive
when it comes to grandchildren.
This is not good.
This is not, not good.
Oh, man, now I've gotta drop this off
before I can get up to the hospital.
Look, Fergus, will you come?
Shit!
It's about time you showed up.
Are you ready to be a da?
- Two sugars.
- That's perfect. Thank you. Brilliant.
Listen, Fergus, thank you so much
for coming. It means so much to me.
Thank you.
I'm telling you, it's just... It really
has just been amazing, you know?
Yeah. I remember
the day my Johnny was born.
Yeah, it's quite something.
We don't see too much of each other now.
Casualty of the business.
We've already moved the officers
off that list. But don't worry.
We've relocated all the officers,
making it look routine. You're covered.
OK.
Hey.
Oh, OK.
Well, we have to wet the baby's head.
Yes, we do. We absolutely do.
That is a very, very good plan.
Oh, I've got a few plans up me sleeve.
My God, I need that.
- What's his name?
- He's Patrick. Wee Patrick.
- Patrick.
- Aye.
Well, cheers, Patrick.
You've got one hell of a father.
So does Johnny.
- Hey, Marty.
- Jeez, Sean.
- Marty.
- Sean, what are you doing?
- How you doing, man?
- Check it out. I'm a da!
- Who the fuck is that?
- He's just some happy uncle.
Check him out. Come on.
- Look at that.
- What's his name?
- He's Patrick.
- Patrick.
He's got lovely eyes, just like mine.
- What are these?
- They're fucking shoes.
Well, they're, uh... they're lovely.
# Babylon's burning
# You'll burn the street
# You'll burn your houses
# With anxiety
But roughly a third
was intercepted by the police.
The device was primed and
booby-trapped, and police found it...
A bomb factory equipped for...
Nearly 100 guns
have been discovered...
Come on! Hand it over!
# Babylon's burning
Babylon is burning
# Babylon is burning
# Babylon's burning #
I didn't hear you come in.
Obviously.
It's not what it seems, OK?
Don't bullshit me.
You think I don't know what you do?
It's just for a few days, that's it.
It's the RA,
and if not them, the peelers.
Between the two, you'll end up either
dead or in jail, and then what about us?
What do you mean, what about us?
It's just for a few days, that's all.
You have to decide, because we're not
waiting around for the call...
...that they've found you in a ditch
with a bullet hole in your head.
Thank you.
We've got to go to Scotland?
For how long?
Three days. Grace is checking out
a Libyan shipment of weapons.
- We're her security.
- So we're meeting a Libyan gun dealer?
How do we know
if they're Libyans?
Usually they shave their heads.
And they're probably eating couscous.
- That's not true.
- You don't know what couscous is.
- They put curry sauce on it.
- The Libyans do?
Aye, they do. It's disgusting.
They've got awful breath, they do.
- Is that true?
- It's a fact.
He said that?
He actually said he wanted me to take
over the entire operation on me own?
- You're ready.
- Jeez.
What about Sean?
OK, fair point. Fair point.
Thank you for not making me say it.
And did you have something to do with
this as well? Did you speak to Mickey?
Maybe a wee bit.
Well, thank you for doing that.
It wasn't my decision.
It was his choice.
Well, thank you if you did.
This is just mad. I've never even been
out of Ireland before, and now all this.
- I know. I can tell.
- Oh, you can tell?
Mm-hm. It's cute.
Oh, great. Now I'm cute.
Don't be so sensitive.
Cute can be, um, a very good thing.
Well, then, I'm sensitive.
And cute.
Look, Grace, I'm sorry.
I just can't do that.
You turned her down, didn't you?
Mickey's good boy.
Sainthood.
Is that what you're going for?
- It's gonna be a fine trip.
- Sean!
Are you coming to Scotland or what?
Come on, man.
I'm hearing whispers MI5 are
gonna step in and poach your star boy.
He's a damn fine bargaining chip.
You could jump a few rungs.
Do you know
what the word "collusion" means?
It does have
a certain romantic ring to it,
but as words go,
it's extremely overrated.
We do the dirty work
while those brave souls in London...
...fight a battle
from their drawing rooms.
I'm telling you, I like it
here. It's peaceful. It's nice.
Look around, right? There's not one
chopper overhead, nothing. It's nice.
I guess you're nesting.
Come on. We're late.
You're not going in
on your own.
I'll do what I need to do.
Grace, good to see you.
Apologies about the cold boys, eh?
That why you're wearing
that naffjumper?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Bastard.
- I told you no guns.
- Are we going to do this deal?
Grace, you're not going in
on your own, OK?
For fuck's sake.
I'll be looking into you.
You can count on it.
Lara?
- Is she here?
- Three days and nights you disappear.
I know. Can I just speak to her,
Mrs Flaherty?
- Shame on you!
- I just need to speak to her.
Lara! Lara, are you in there?
Please, I was snagged by the RUC!
- That's a good one.
- They wouldn't let me near a telephone!
I swear, they wouldn't let me near a
telephone! There was nothing I could do!
If I could have spoken to you, I would!
Come on, please!
Will you just come to the window, Lara?
Please, I just wanna see your face!
Fuck!
Lara, please.
I'm so sorry. Lara, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I love you, OK? Look, look, I love you.
Look at me, please. Look at me, please.
Lara, look at me, please.
I love you. I do.
Do you love me? Do you love me?
- I thought you were dead!
- I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
That's it, eh? Come here.
I'm taking you to Scotland. That's it.
I'm just gonna take you and leave.
We're gonna get away
from all this political shit.
- You're never gonna leave the IRA.
- Oh, no?
I'll do whatever you want me to do
at this point. I'm yours.
Because you're captured by the anarchy
of it all, like the rest of them.
And you love it.
We're gonna hit the pub
afterwards, courtesy of Libya.
Don't go AWOL again.
It's not healthy.
I am in charge
of this entire operation.
Anyway, I've got to get back. Lara's not
exactly buying my excuses anymore.
Yeah, I was married to a nice girl until
I tried the alien abduction excuse.
Is this the
"take care of your family" speech?
You're so young, Martin,
you make me envious.
Life's full of mistakes. I lost
my family making all the obvious ones.
There, that was your speech.
Aye, very moving.
Are you saying that I should quit?
Is that it?
- We've had a good run.
- Aye, yeah, we have.
Look, there's gonna be a drop.
It's on Thursday night, on the docks.
My mate's wee brother's gonna
be there. He doesn't know anything.
He's just gonna be there,
so leave him alone.
Go in, get the guns and then get out.
OK, this is it.
What the fuck's going on?
Down on the ground!
What's going on?
Ah, Jesus Christ. Marty, they're Brits.
Get it started, Marty.
Get the fuck out of here. Come on.
What the fuck was that all about?
You said I'd save lives, and that
includes my people, you Brit bastard!
It's a set-up for a bigger fish. It was
out of my hands. It's big boys' rules.
Is that it? You're gonna hide
behind big boys' rules?
OK, well, how about this?
"Yes, sir! Consider it done, sir!"
"He's just another statistic, sir!
It didn't even happen, sir!"
Right? You think that shit's gonna
change the fact that you, yeah, you,
you killed an 18-year-old fella
that didn't know any better?
And you're innocent?
You and your mates are volunteers
in a volunteer organisation.
Who's making you do anything
you don't want to do?
Where does that leave you
and your mates?
Aye. Aye, my mates. That's exactly
what they are, they're my mates.
I know his ma. Do you understand that?
Is that getting through?
I know this guy's ma
and I know his brothers!
I told yous what I know
so you could save his arse, huh?
But, no, he's just another Paddy to you
and your big boys, isn't he?
You know what?
Get the fuck out of my country.
We all know the IRA aren't terrorists.
The IRA are freedom fighters.
Rise up for our help, oh, Lord!
strike down our enemies before us.
An eyewitness maintains
one of the men pleaded for his life...
...before he was shot.
This brings to eight
the number of IRA members...
...who have been killed
in the last three months.
Right, stop here. Remember,
lads, single shots to head and the body.
No fucking meddling, OK? Away yous go.
- Well, how's the kid?
- He's growing.
- They tend to do that.
- Yeah.
- Fuck it!
- Well?
- The fucker wouldn't go down.
- Drive.
- This wee girl was watching.
- Uh-huh?
We were wearing the balaclavas.
She wouldn't make us.
Right, here, get them shirts off.
I want you to take the car
up to Hightown Road. Burn it, OK?
- Did we actually get what we came for?
- Saturday 28th of March.
At least something went fucking right.
I've, uh, not really been sleeping.
That's why God invented sleeping pills.
I take it you've reconsidered.
- The hit on Park Street was...
- Ray.
Aye, and Johnny.
Oh, and a wee girl
saw the whole fucking thing.
Yeah. Seven years old.
She was right next to her daddy.
Got covered in his blood, I'm told.
I've got a son,
and there's nobody deserves to grow up
with that picture in their mind.
They didn't give me any warning.
I'm starting to, you know,
think that they're onto me.
You wouldn't be here
if they were onto you.
I've not got a good feeling about it.
- My car's definitely marked, right?
- Yeah, of course.
Go home. Hug your wife and baby.
The pub job's going on the 28th.
That's... That's all I've got.
Well, you did well.
Aye.
Make sure you check the timer. That way
it doesn't blow up in your face.
It's gonna blow up
the whole city, man.
It seems like whenever you're around,
nothing blows up.
- You wanna shut the door for me?
- Yeah, you give it a good kick. Good man.
There you go. What did we get Mummy?
We got her fish and chips, didn't we?
Straight out the deep fat fryer
we caught this, me and Patrick.
All right, let's get some food.
Your friends
Mickey and Grace dropped by.
Oh, they went on about the new house,
the fridge, the cooker.
They were extremely interested
in the new TV.
It's... It's fine, honestly.
It's nothing. They trust me. It's fine.
We have a child, Martin.
For his sake, I'd leave.
But I'm pregnant.
Where am I gonna go?
Look, let's get married.
I wanna get married. Do you?
- Let's get married, please. Come on.
- Why?
What do you mean, why?
Because I love you, that's why.
- Love?
- Aye.
Every time you leave, I wonder if
it's the last time I'll see you alive.
I have nightmares!
The neighbours are afraid of you.
You wear that like a medal.
I heard you were palling
with the RA nuthers!
Are you?! Are you?!
What exactly does the daddy
of our wee boy do for the cause?
Marty, see you
for a couple minutes, son?
- Mickey.
- Marty'll debrief you later.
Looks like we're all set.
Here's a present. It's from Mickey.
He wants you to keep it close by.
You know how he worries.
Aye. This is gonna make you famous.
By the way, it's only me and you
know the exact location.
Aye.
Info finally confirmed.
Every Saturday, the prison wardens
play a football match.
Locations are kept top secret.
Now, next Saturday, March 28th,
after the semis,
they'll be drinking in the Whale pub.
So we have a week.
This is the big one.
Did you give her the gun?
Yes.
Look, tonight we do a test run.
We check the place out,
we finalise details. No weapons.
If anything happens, they will know
that it was me who told.
Go on the recce. We won't
do anything till next saturday.
That's when we grab them, armed and
loaded, and when all the shit goes down,
you walk into
one of our secured vehicles.
We'll pull your family out.
Don't tell Lara anything.
A slip could be costly.
She's pregnant again.
Congratulations. I won't let
anything happen to you or your family.
- MI5 just called me.
- You told them to fuck off.
It's done.
- The pub job?
- They're running it now.
What about my source?
A good handler manages the source.
He doesn't let the source manage him.
He's not your source anymore.
It's shit like this that ends careers,
so walk away.
Right, lads, for security purposes,
most of you are hearing this
for the first time, so pay attention.
It's your lives that's at risk here, OK?
Martin, it's all yours.
We'll have two AKs in the getaway car.
Escape routes are on your maps.
- How many rounds we got?
- About 189.
Two mags for each of the AKs.
Spares are in the getaway car.
- Why, do you think that's enough?
- Aye.
Tonight is a dry run.
We make sure our plan is good to go.
Next saturday, on the 28th,
it's for real.
...sean, Kieren, go in the side door.
Grace, we'll go in the front.
Check all exits.
A wee bottle of Guinness.
Johnny, stay with the car.
I'll go inside, watch the front door.
Get a drink, do what you've got to do,
but don't leave any fingerprints.
Keep the change.
Hey. Ease up, man. For fuck's sake.
You got the time?
Code green. Code green.
Shit! You're a dead man!
You're a dead man!
You fucking bastard, you!
You're a fucking tout!
Fucking bastard! I'm gonna kill you!
We've got you now, bitch!
Hello?
- Lara, Lara, it's me.
- Oh, God. Martin!
Listen to me. Listen to me, OK?
I need you to kiss Patrick
good night for me, OK?
We're gonna be all right.
I'm gonna go to my mummy's.
I'm so sorry.
Martin?
- Aye.
- I got a question for you.
What's that?
- Will you marry me?
- Aye.
- You promise?
- Are we married?
- Yeah, we're married.
Great.
We are man and wife.
I love you.
I love you, too. I love you, and I love
Patrick, OK? But you've got to get out.
What's that?
- So where is he?
- How the fuck do I know?
Under the circumstances,
it's a fair question.
- Did you compromise the operation?
- So that's how this is gonna go down.
MI5 step in, screw up
and I get to eat the bullshit.
It's a big picture thing.
It was supposed to be
an easy bait and switch.
Your boy shouldn't have walked, but he
did and now there's a mess to clean up.
Don't be forgetting,
you're one of the good guys.
- A man of the law.
- Since when?
Since when did this become
about the law?
What the hell happened to you?
Me and Lara had a fight.
Marty...
Ma, no.
- Hello?
- Hello. Is Martin there?
- No, I haven't seen him.
- Tell him it's Fergus.
- Fergus?
- Give me the phone.
You set me up, man, you lying bastard!
It had nothing to do with me. I'll be
there in 20. I'm your only chance now.
Marty, what's going on?
- It's fine, Ma.
- Tell me.
Listen, it's all right.
- He's a tout, Mrs McGartland.
- There's no way that's true.
Marty.
Special Branch don't want him anymore.
- Connie!
- Connie, no!
No! No!
I'm going with you, OK.
You leave my family, please.
Ma. Ma, listen to me. I'll be fine. I'll
be back in two hours, OK? Two hours.
Let go of me! Get off of me!
Get off him! Get off him!
- Oh, Ma.
- Are you all right?
Christ. Christ. Oh, Christ!
Yeah.
Jesus. Fine. We're not going anywhere.
Just getting a bath.
They won't be here for another hour.
If it was up to me, you wouldn't be
seeing the end of that hour.
Piece of shit. Come on.
Oh, shit.
Ow! Fuck!
Where's Martin, then?
- You gonna let them kill your mate?
- He's not my mate.
Ever wonder why you're not behind bars?
We've been all over you for two years.
Your mate, Martin.
I hear that Special Branch
have lost interest in you.
Well, then, that makes me unofficial.
New rules. You get to live if he lives.
Broom Park.
Broom Park, you fucking bastard!
Yeah, this is a message
from John smith, IRA.
There's a bomb. A lot of samaritans
will die. Broom Park.
- Give us the password.
- Carry Gold.
Wait up. We need to be able
to question him. Bring him in here.
Come on.
Over there.
Fucking peelers like flies around shit.
You gonna tell me what you did?
I'm pretty sure the IRA
is holding my top boy in there.
Funny that we're looking for a bomb
in the same place your source is.
- Thomas...
- Great delay tactic.
Pretty much locked the place down.
- Move out!
- Who are you taking orders from?
- Just trying to make it to retirement.
- Oh, fuck it, then. Fuck it.
Some stunt.
Move out!
Aw, fuck, come on!
You're gonna talk, Marty. You know that.
You know that.
Keep it shut, big man, right?
Get it.
What are you doing here?
He was my mate.
I wanna hear him fucking say it!
- Sean, you're not authorised...
- Say it!
Get out, Sean! This is an army order.
I'm your senior officer. Get out!
Sean, are you deaf? Get out!
You'll bring the peelers
to the fucking door!
Shut up!
I wanna fucking hear him say it!
Get an ambulance, now!
He's a peeler.
We've no orders for this.
Jesus Christ.
OK, what happened?
Get him back.
- Take him to City Hospital!
- The Royal's closer.
He won't live if we take him there.
Take him to the City.
Get alongside him. Get alongside him!
Right up Jackson Street! Jackson Street!
Keep going and ram him.
Fuck it.
Shit! Shit!
Watch the door!
I hear the shit's going down
at Special Branch.
Bloody hell.
What is the matter with you?
Why is the kid still breathing?
Was it not a simple request?
- If it was, you'd have done it.
- Fuck off.
You asked.
Yeah, well, clean it up.
If the RUC don't protect him, MI5 will
leave him exposed, a gift to the IRA,
a bait and switch to deflect attention
from a plant higher up.
- What's your stake in this?
- He was my operative.
Shit.
There's no way
I can get involved in this.
How about I go to the press
and we debate this in public?
- You won't live long enough.
- Martin.
That's his name. Martin.
He saved, I'd guess, 50 soldiers,
RUC officers, prison wardens.
MI5 turns him into a bargaining chip.
He has a girlfriend, a son
and another baby on the way.
Look, we uphold the law and break
the law in the name of the law.
Is that why you signed up?
Not a bloody day goes by
when I don't serve this community.
I know.
Shit.
Why me?
You f...
You fuck...
- Where's Lara and the boy?
- They're at her mum's.
How long have I been... been out?
Long enough for the dust to settle.
You deserted me.
Well, like it or not,
I'm your only friend right now.
My real name's Dean.
But you can keep calling me Fergus.
The name's grown on me.
Is he OK?
He's OK, yeah.
- His wife's here to see him.
- He hasn't got a wife.
- Where's the RUC officer?
- I don't know where he is.
Did you tell her what room he's in?
- This is against my orders.
- He won't last the night here.
He has a deep internal cut,
a fractured jaw, severe concussion...
...and several broken ribs.
Just pray
this is a nine-lives situation.
- This is pretty cosy for a safe house.
- It's my house.
So, Dean... I hope you have a plan.
Well, Lara still doesn't know
you're alive.
I've negotiated a deal
with Scotland Yard.
Call Lara. See if she'll like the idea
of getting married in Scotland.
You look me in the eye, OK,
you tell me what kind of life
you think she'd have.
No hope, no friends, no community.
Always looking over our shoulder,
scared to death for them kids.
I can't do it.
I really can't do it. I won't do it.
I thought I was saving lives.
A superhero.
- Do you ever see your kid?
- He's, uh...
He's got a lot going on right now.
# And then my son
# He walked away
# I bowed my head
# In tearful shame
# son, you'll come to know
# Your sad smile is my blame
OK, let's go.
# It's the hero
# Puts down the gun
# In the name of daughters and our sons
# And now I pray
# Our war is done
# The dove flies free
# And we have won...
Oh, my God.
Help! Call an ambulance!
Stay awake.
Help is coming. Do you have family?
Who should I call?
Dean. Dean McTear. Dean McTear.
He's family?
Yeah. Dean McTear.
# We have won
# My son cried and said to me
# Why do young men kill what they love?
# The coward with a kiss
# The brave man with his sword
# Blood flows dripping from the dove
# You say it's for your daughters
and for your sons
# Father, it's time your war is done
# We'll be free
# We will have won
# Who in our hearts do we pray for?
# Who do we hold so very near?
# A cry from a lover
# A child's silent tear
# The might of God was on each side
# But nothing came of nothing
and war was my bride
# I heard of heroes
# Dreamed I'd be the same
# I'd even the score
# Be part of the game
# The dove flies free
# And we have won
# My son cried and said to me
# Why do young men kill what they love?
# The coward with a kiss
# The brave man with his sword
# Blood flows dripping from the dove
# You say it's for your daughters
and for your sons
# Father, it's time your war is done
# We'll be free
# We will have won
# The dove flies free
# And we have won...
# And we have won d
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org