Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
our gift to the world.
Look around. Look around.
I see a lot
of new faces.
- Ha ha!
Shut up!
Which means a lot of you
have been breaking
the first 2 rules of  Fight Club.
Man, I see in Fight Club
the strongest and smartest
men who've ever lived.
I see all this
potential.
And I see squandering.
God damn it.
An entire generation
pumping gas...
waiting tables...
slaves with white collars.
Advertising has its taste
in cars and clothes...
working jobs we hate so we can
buy shit we don't need.
We're the middle children
of history, man.
No purpose or place.
We have no Great War...
no Great Depression.
Our Great War's
a spiritual war.
Our Great Depression
is our lives.
We've all been raised
on television
to believe that one day
we'd all be millionaires
and movie gods
and rock stars.
But we won't.
We're slowly learning
that fact.
And we're very,
very pissed off.
- Yeah!
[The Men Murmur]
First rule of  Fight Club is
you do not talk about--
[Loud Banging]
Who are you?
Who am l?
Yeah.
There's a sign
in the front
that says
" Lou's Tavern."
I'm fuckin' Lou.
Who the fuck are you?
Tyler Durden.
Who told you motherfuckers
that you could use my place?
We have a deal
worked out with Irvin.
Irvin?
Irvin's at home with
a broken collarbone.
He don't own
this place.
I do.
How much money is he
gettin' for this?
There is no money.
- Really. Ain't that somethin'?
- Free to all.
It is, actually.
Look, stupid fuck...
I want everybody
outta here right now.
Hey. You should
join our club.
Did you hear
what I just said?
You and your friend.
Oomp!
Uhh!
You hear me now?!
No, I didn't quite
catch that, Lou.
Ooh!
Pfft!
Ohhh...
Still not gettin' it.
Aah! OK, OK, OK.
I got it.
I got it. I got it.
Shit, I lost it.
Ooh!
Back! All of you!
[Gun Cocks]
Everybody back.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Aw, Lou...
Come on, man.
We really like
this place.
Ohh!
[Tyler Half Sobs,
Half Laughs Hysterically]
Ohhh...
- That's right, Lou, get it--
- Shut the fuck up!
Oh, yeah!
Yeah! Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ho ho ho ha ha ha!
Think that's
fuckin' funny?!
Ho ho, ho!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha--
Ohh! Ho ho ho!
Fuckin' guys are loony,
I'm tellin' ya.
Unbelievable. Aah!
[Choking]
You don't know
where I've been, Lou.
- Oh, my God!
- Ha ha ha!
You don't know where
I've been! Ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Lou! Please let us
keep it, Lou!
Please, Lou!
Fuckin' use the basement!
Christ!
I want your word, Lou!
I want your word!
On my mother's honor.
Uhh!
Lou!
Aaahhh!
Thanks, Lou.
You, too, big guy.
See you next week.
This week...
each one of you...
has a homework
assignment.
You're gonna go out.
You're gonna start a fight
with a total stranger.
You're gonna
start a fight.
And you're
gonna lose.
Excellent choice,
sir.
Hey! Watch out,
jackass!
Come on!
Narrator: Now, this is not
as easy as it sounds.
I'm thinkin'
you really--What?!
Son of a bitch!
Narrator: Most people...
normal people...
do just about anything
to avoid a fight.
Excuse me.
You sprayed me with your hose.
Like that?
That's not necessary.
Dave!
Go call 91 1 !
Aaaahhh!
Stop it!
Sorry.
What did--
Come here!
Leave me alone!
You crazy?
Uhh!
Unhh! Uhh!
Bastard!
We need to talk.
OK.
[Door Closes]
Where to begin?
With your constant
absenteeism?
With your unpresentable
appearance?
You're up for review.
I am Jack’s...
complete lack of surprise.
What?
Let's pretend.
You're the Department
of Transportation.
OK?
Someone informs you
that this company
installs front seat
mounting brackets
that never pass
collision tests...
brake linings that fail
after a thousand miles,
and fuel injectors
that explode
and burn people alive.
What then?
Are you threatening me?
No...
Get the fuck outta here.
You're fired.
I have a better solution.
You keep me on the payroll
as an outside consultant.
And in exchange
for my salary,
my job will be never
to tell people
these things
that I know.
I don't even have to come
into the office.
I can do this job
from home.
Who--Who the fuck
do you think you are,
you crazy little shit?
Security?
Narrator: I am
Jack's smirking revenge.
Ohh!
Ahh...ahh...
What the hell
are you doing?
Ohh...that hurt.
Why would you do that?
Oh, my God.
No! Please stop!
[Making
Strangulation Sounds]
Uhh! Uh...uhh!
What are you doing?
Oh, God, no! Please! No!
Narrator: For some reason,
I thought of my first fight
with Tyler.
No!
Under and behind
and inside,
everything this man
took for granted...
something horrible
had been growing.
Now, look.
Give me the paychecks
like I asked,
and you won't
ever see me again.
And right then, at our most
excellent moment together...
Oh...thank God.
Please don't hit me
again. Please...
Telephone, computer,
fax machine,
52 weekly paychecks, and
48 airline flight coupons.
We now had
corporate sponsorship.
This is how Tyler and I were
able to have Fight Club
every night of the week.
[Crowd Cheering]
Now nobody was the center
of  Fight Club
except the 2 men fighting.
The leader walked through the crowd,
out in the darkness.
Tyler was now involved
in a class-action lawsuit
with the Pressman Hotel over
the urine content of their soup.
I am Jack’s wasted life.
Yeah! Yeah! Ha ha!
Yeah!
There you are, sir.
Tyler dreamed up
new homework assignments.
He handed them out
in sealed envelopes.
Did you know
there's a Fight Club
up in Delaware City?
Yeah, I heard.
[Car Alarm]
There's one
in Penn's Grove, too.
Bob even found one
up in Newcastle.
Yeah. Did you start
that one?
No. I thought you did.
Nah.
Pff!.
[Car Alarm]
Stop for a second.
Hey, what are we doing?
Turn around.
What are we doing?
Homework assignment.
What kind of
homework assignment?
Human sacrifice.
Hey, is that a gun?
Please. Please tell me
that's not a gun.
It's a gun.
What are you doing?
Meet me in the back.
Hey, don't fuck around.
Narrator: On a long enough
time line,
the survival rate
for everyone drops to zero.
What are you doing?
Come on.
Hands behind your back.
God.
Give me your wallet.
Raymond K. Hessel,
1 320 Southeast Banning,
apartment A.
Small, cramped basement
apartment, Raymond?
How did you know?
Because they give
shitty basement apartments
Letters instead of numbers.
Raymond...
you're going to die.
[Crying]
Oh, my God, no...
Is that your mom and dad?
Mom and dad are going
to have to call up
kindly Dr. So-And-So
to pick up
your dental records.
You want to know why?
Because there's going to be
nothing left of your face.
- Aw, come on.
- [Crying]
An expired community college
student I.D.
What'd you study, Raymond?
S-S-S-Stuff.
Stuff?
Were the midterms hard?
[Whimpering]
I asked you
what you studied.
Biology, mostly.
Why?
I--I don't know.
What did you want to be,
Raymond K. Hessel?
[Click]
The question, Raymond,
was what did you
want to be?
Answer him,
Raymond! Jesus!
Veterinarian!
Animals.
Yeah, animal s-s-s--
Stuff.
Yeah, I got that.
That means you have to
get more schooling.
Too much school.
Would you rather be dead?
No...
Would you
rather die, here,
on your knees,
in the back
of a convenience store?
[Whimpering]
No...No, please...
no...
[Releases Hammer]
I'm keeping your license.
Gonna check in on you.
I know where you live.
If you’re not on your way
to becoming a veterinarian
in 6 weeks,
you will be dead.
[Whimpering]
Now run on home.
Run, Forrest, run!
I feel ill.
Imagine how he feels.
Come on,
this isn't funny!
That wasn't funny.
What the fuck
was the point of that?
Tomorrow will be
the most beautiful day
of  Raymond K. Hessel's life.
His breakfast
will taste better
than any meal you and I
have ever tasted.
Narrator: You had to
give it to him.
Come on.
He had a plan.
And it started
to make sense
in a Tyler sort of way.
No fear.
No distractions.
The ability to let
that which does not matter
truly slide.
You're not your job.
You're not how much money
you have in the bank.
You're not
the car you drive.
You're not the contents
of your wallet.
You're not
your fuckin' khakis.
You're the all-singing,
all-dancing crap of the world.
I'll be out of your way
in a sec.
You don't have to go.
Whatever.
No, I mean, uh...
It's OK.
Are you still going
to groups?
Yeah.
Chloe's dead.
Ah, Chloe.
When did that happen?
do you care?
I don't know.
I haven't thought
about it in a while.
Yeah, well...
I think it was
a smart move on her part.
Hey, listen, uh...
what are you getting
out of all this?
What?
I mean, all this.
Why do you keep...
Is this
making you happy?
Yeah, well, sometimes.
I don't know.
I don't understand.
Why does
a weaker person
need to latch on to
a strong person?
What is that?
Well, what do you
get out of it?
No--It's--It's not
the same thing at all.
I mean, we're...It's
totally different with us.
We're--We're--
Us?
What do you mean by "us"?
I'm sorry,
do you hear this?
Hear what?
You're not hearing
all that noise?
Just--Hold on a second.
No, wait.
What were you saying?
Don't change the subject.
I want to talk about this.
You're not talking
about me, are you?
No. What?
That day you came over
to my place to play doctor--
what was going on there?
What are you
talking about?
Nothing. Nothing.
I don't think so.
Come on,
what do you want?
- Look at me.
- No. What?
Look at me.
What is that?
It's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, my God.
Who did this?
A person.
Guy or girl?
What do you care
if it’s a guy or a girl?
if I ask?
This is none of your
business. Leave me alone.
You're afraid to say it.
I am not afraid to say.
Let me go.
No! Talk to me.
- No!
- Let go of me. Leave me alone.
This conversation...
is over.
I just can't win
with you, can l?
Hey, this is getting
a little old.
[Doorbell]
What is--What is all this?
What do you think?
Hey, why do we need
bunk beds?
Hey.
Too young.
Sorry.
What's all that?
If the applicant is young,
tell him he's too young.
Old, too old.
Fat, too fat.
Applicant?
If the applicant
then waits for 3 days
without food, shelter
or encouragement,
he may then enter
and begin his training.
Training for what?
You think
this is a game?
You're too young
to train here.
End of story.
Quit wasting our time.
Get the fuck
out of here.
Bad news, friend.
It's not gonna happen.
I'm sorry if there was
a misunderstanding.
It's not the end
of the world.
Just go away.
Go.
You're trespassing,
and I will have to
call the police.
Don't you look at me.
do you think you're
ever getting in this house?
You're never getting in
this fucking house.
Never. Now get the fuck
off the porch.
Get off the porch!
Narrator: Sooner or later,
we all became what Tyler
wanted us to be.
I'm gonna go inside and
I'm gonna get a shovel.
You got 2 black shirts?
Sir.
2 pair of black pants?
Yes, sir.
One pair of black boots?
Sir.
2 pair of black socks?
One black jacket?
Sir.
$300 personal burial money?
Yes, sir.
All right.
[Snickers]
You're too old,
fat man.
Your tits
are too big.
Get the fuck
off my porch.
Bob. Bob.
Like a monkey
ready to be shot
into space.
Space monkey.
Ready to sacrifice himself
for the greater good.
You are too
fucking old, fatty!
And you.
You're too fucking...
blond!
Get out of here,
the both of you!
[Door Slams]
Narrator: And so it went.
Tyler:
Listen up, maggots.
You are not special.
You are not
a beautiful or unique snowflake.
You are the same
decaying organic matter
as everything else.
Narrator: Tyler
built himself an army.
Tyler: We are the all-singing,
all-dancing crap of the world.
We are all part of
the same compost heap.
Narrator: Why was Tyler Durden
building an army?
To what purpose?
For what greater good?
In Tyler we trusted.
No, when he was like, "You are
not your job," I was like...
Yeah!
Hey, what's all this?
[Laughing]
OK!
Go on in
and celebrate.
What are we celebrating?
Go on.
[TV Playing]
Hey.
Let me get that
for you.
[Belches]
Investigators are
on the scene right now.
Hold on. Police Commissioner
Jacobs has just arrived.
Commissioner, Commissioner,
could you please tell us
what you think
has happened here?
We believe
this is one of many
recent acts of vandalism
around the city
somehow related to
underground boxing clubs.
We'll be coordinating
a rigorous investigation.
That was Police Commissioner
Jacobs, who just arrived
on the scene here
of a 4-alarm fire
that broke out
about an hour ago.
She's hot.
Live from the Parker
Morris Building,
Lauren Sanchez.
Back to you in the studio.
- [Laughter]
- Yeah!
- Ha ha ha ha!
- Yeah.
Holy shit.
Yeah!
[News Anchor
Narrating Footage]
- Yeah!
- Ha ha ha!
Hoo hoo hoo!
What the fuck
did you guys do?
News Anchor:
...how the blaze started,
but arson investigators
are on the premises...
[Laughing]
Sir, the first rule
of  Project Mayhem
is you do not
ask questions, sir.
The victory
in the war against crime
will not come overnight.
It will take dedication
and commitment,
and most of all,
cooperation.
The streets are safer now.
There is hope
in the inner city.
However, this is only
the beginning.
I gotta take a piss.
These are the first steps
in a long journey.
That is why we have
created Project Hope...
Bob.
" Helping others with
prevention and enforcement."
Project Hope will be
a joint effort
between the police
and community leaders.
It will be
a powerful new weapon
in the war against crime.
[Applause]
[Strangled Scream]
Haahhhh!
Wrap it around the top of
his hacky sack, Bob.
Yeah. His balls
are ice cold.
Hi.
You're gonna call off
your rigorous investigation.
You're gonna publicly state
that there is no
underground group, or...
these guys are gonna
take your balls.
They're gonna send one
to the New York Times,
one to the L.A. Times
press release style.
Look...
the people you are after
are the people
you depend on.
We cook your meals.
We haul your trash.
We connect your calls.
We drive your ambulances.
We guard you
while you sleep.
Do not fuck with us.
[Muffled Screaming]
Fooled ya.
[Rumbling]
[Dialogue Drowned Out
By Noise]
Bob, you're on this one.
Let's go.
Narrator: I am Jack’s
inflamed sense of rejection.
Hey!
[Shouting]
Yeah!
Narrator: I felt like putting
a bullet between the eyes
of every panda that wouldn't
screw to save its species.
I wanted to open
the dump valves
on oil tankers and smother
all those French beaches
I'd never see.
I wanted to breathe smoke.
Where'd you go,
psycho boy?
I felt like destroying
something beautiful.
[Gagging]
Get him to
a fuckin' hospital.
Yeah.
Don't worry, Mr. Durden.
Airport parking,
long term.
After you, Mr. Durden.
After you.
Something on your mind,
dear?
No.
All right, yeah.
Why wasn't I told
about Project Mayhem?
[Together]
First rule of  Project Mayhem
is you do not ask questions.
What are you talking about?
Why didn't you include me
in the beginning?
Fight Club
was the beginning.
Now it's moved
out of the basement,
it's called
Project Mayhem.
You and I started
Fight Club together.
do you remember that?
It's as much mine
as it is yours, you know.
Is this about
you and me?
Yeah. I thought we were
doing this together.
You're missing the point.
This does not
belong to us.
We are not special.
Fuck that.
You should've told me.
Hey, Tyler!
[Horn Honking]
Goddamn it, Tyler!
What do you want?!
Statement of purpose?
Should I e-mail you?
Should I put this
on your action item list?
You decide your own
level of involvement!
I will! I want to know
certain things first.
The first rule
of  Project Mayhem--
Shut up!
I want to know
what you're thinking.
Fuck what you know.
You need to forget
about what you know.
That's your problem.
Forget about what
you think you know
about life,
about friendship,
and especially
about you and me.
What?
What is that supposed
to mean? What...
What are you doing?
Guys, what do you wish
you'd done before you die?
Paint a self-portrait.
Build a house.
And you?
I don't know.
Get in the right lane.
I have to know the answer
to this question.
If you were to die
right now,
how would you feel
about your life?
I don't know!
I wouldn't feel anything
good about my life.
Is that what you want
to hear me say? Fine.
- Come on!
- Not good enough.
- [Honking]
- Stop fucking around!
Tyler!
[Honking]
Jesus Christ!
Goddamn it!
Fuck you!
Fuck Fight Club.
Fuck Marla.
I'm sick of all your shit.
OK.
Quit screwing around.
Take the wheel.
Look at you.
Take the wheel!
Look at you!
You're fuckin' pathetic!
Why? Why?
What are you talking about?
Why do you think
I blew up your condo?
What?
Hitting bottom
isn't a weekend retreat.
It's not
a goddamn seminar.
Stop trying
to control everything
and just let go.
Let go!
All right. Fine.
Fine.
Narrator: I'd never been
in a car accident.
This must have been what
all those people felt like
before I filed them
as statistics in my reports.
Goddamn.
Huh?
Ha ha ha ha ha hahh!
We just had
a near-life experience.
In the world I see,
you're stalking elk through
the damp canyon forest,
around the ruins
of  Rockefeller Center.
You'll wear leather clothes
that will last you
the rest of your life.
You'll climb the vines
that wrap the Sears Tower.
And when you look down,
you'll see tiny figures
pounding corn,
Laying strips of venison
on the empty carpool lane
of some abandoned
superhighway.
Feel better, champ.
[Door Closes]
Narrator: And then...
Tyler?
Tyler was gone.
Was I asleep?
Had I slept?
You are not
a beautiful
unique snowflake,
do you understand me?
Narrator: The house had become
a living thing,
wet inside
from so many people
sweating and breathing.
We are all from
the same compost.
So many people moving,
the house moved.
Planet Tyler.
I had to hug the walls.
Trapped inside this
clock work of space monkeys.
You can't be
smoking in here.
do you know how much ether
we have in this fucking house?
Cooking, working,
and sleeping in teams.
Hang on a second.
It's under control, sir.
Where is Tyler?
Sir, the first rule of
Project Mayhem is you do not--
Right, uh...OK.
I'm all alone.
My father dumped me.
Tyler dumped me.
I am Jack’s broken heart.
What comes next
in Project Mayhem,
only Tyler knows.
The second rule is
you do not ask questions.
Get the fuck
away from me.
away from me!
Who are all these people?
Paper Street Soap Company.
Can I come in?
He's not here.
What?
Tyler isn't here.
Tyler went away.
Tyler's gone.
[Shouting]
Lay him down!
Gunshot wounds
comin' through!
Clear some fucking room!
What happened?!
We were on assignment.
We were supposed to kill
2 birds with one stone.
Destroy a piece
of corporate art...
Operation Latte Thunder,
go.
and trash a franchise
coffee bar.
We had it all
worked out, sir.
It went smooth
until...
Police! Freeze!
Until what?
They shot Bob.
They shot him
in the head.
Those fuckin' pigs!
- Ohh!
- Oh, God.
- Son of a--
Those motherfuckers!
You morons.
You're running around
in ski masks,
trying
to blow things up.
What did you think
was gonna happen?!
OK, quick,
we gotta get rid
of the evidence.
We gotta get rid
of this body!
Bury him.
What?
Take him
to the garden
and bury him.
Come on,
people!
Let's go!
Hey, get
the fuck off!
Get away from him!
What are you
talking about?
This isn't a fucking
piece of evidence,
this is a person!
He's a friend
of mine,
and you're not
gonna bury him
in the fucking garden.
He was killed serving
Project Mayhem, sir.
This is Bob.
But sir, in--in
Project Mayhem
we have no names.
No, you
listen to me.
This is a man,
and he has a name.
And it's
Robert Paulson, OK?
Robert
Paulson?
He's a man
and he's dead now
because of us,
all right?
do you understand that?
I understand.
In death,
a member of
Project Mayhem
has a name.
His name is
Robert Paulson.
Come on, guys,
please, stop it.
His name is
Robert Paulson.
[Chanting] His name
is Robert Paulson.
Shut up!
This is all
over with!
[Chanting] His name
is Robert Paulson.
His name is
Robert Paulson.
Robert Paulson...
[Telephone Rings]
Tyler?
No, this is
Detective Stern
at the Arson Unit.
I need to see you
in my office--
I went to
all the cities
on Tyler's
used ticket stubs,
barhopping.
I didn't know
how or why,
but I could look
at 50 different bars
and somehow
I just knew.
I'm looking
for Tyler Durden.
It's very important
that I talk to him.
I wish
I could help you.
Sir.
Every city
I went to...
as soon as I set foot
off the plane,
I knew a Fight Club
was close.
Hey! Hey!
Taxi!
Look at my face.
I'm a member.
Now, I just
need to know
if you’ve seen Tyler.
I'm not exposed
to...
speak any such
information to you,
nor would l, even if
I had said information
you want at this
juncture, be able.
You're a moron.
I'm afraid I'm gonna
have to ask you to leave.
Tyler had
been busy.
Setting up franchises
all over the country.
Was I asleep?
[Crowd Fighting]
Had I slept?
Is Tyler
my bad dream,
or am I Tyler's?
Man: We’ve just
heard the stories.
What kind
of stories?
Like, nobody knows
what he looks like.
He has facial
reconstructive
surgery
every 3 years.
That's the stupidest thing
I've ever heard.
Is it true about
Fight Club in Miami?
Is Mr. Durden
building an army?
I was living
in a state
of perpetual
déjà vu.
Everywhere I went,
I felt I'd already
been there.
It was like following
an invisible man.
The smell
of dried blood,
dirty, bare footprints
circling each other,
that aroma of old sweat,
like fried chicken.
The feel of a floor
still warm
from the fight
the night before.
I was always just
one step behind Tyler.
[Voices Murmuring]
Men: His name
is Robert Paulson.
His name is
Robert Paulson.
His--
Welcome back,
sir.
How have
you been?
do you know me?
Is this a test,
sir?
No, this
is not a test.
You were in here
last Thursday.
Thursday?
You were
standing
exactly where
you are now,
asking how good
security is.
It's tight
as a drum, sir.
Who do you
think I am?
Are you sure this
isn't a test?
No, this is
not a test.
You're Mr. Durden.
You're the one
who gave me this.
Please return
your seat backs
to their full, upright
and locked position.
[Telephone Rings]
[Rings]
Yeah?
Marla, it's me.
Have we ever
done it?
Done what?
Have we ever
had sex?
What kind of stupid
question is that?
Is it stupid because
the answer's yes,
or because
the answer's no?
Is this a trick?
No, Marla,
I need to know--
You mean you want
to know if I think
we were just having sex
or making love?
We did make love.
Is that what
you're calling it?
Just answer
the question,
Marla, please!
Did we do it
or not?
You fuck me,
then snub me.
You love me,
you hate me.
You show me
a sensitive side,
then you turn into
a total asshole.
Is that a pretty
accurate description
of our relationship,
Tyler?
We have just lost
cabin pressure.
What did you
just say?
What is wrong
with you?
What did you call
me? Say my name!
Tyler Durden.
Tyler Durden,
you fucking freak.
What's going on?
I'm coming over.
No, wait, Marla,
I'm not there--
[Dial Tone]
You broke
your promise.
Jesus, Tyler.
You fuckin' talked
to her about me.
Tyler, what the fuck
is going on here?
I asked you
for one thing,
one simple thing.
Why do people
think that I'm you?
Answer me!
Sit.
Now answer me.
Why do people think
that I'm you?
I think you know.
No, I don't.
Yes, you do.
Why would anyone possibly
confuse you with me?
Uh...l...
I don't know.
You got it.
No.
Do not
fuck with us.
Say it.
Because...
Because we're
the same person.
That's right.
We are the all-singing,
all dancing--
I don't
understand this.
You were looking
for a way
to change your life.
You could not do this
on your own.
All the ways you wish
you could be,
that's me.
I look like
you wanna look,
I fuck like
you wanna fuck,
I am smart,
capable,
and most importantly,
I am free
in all the ways
that you are not.
Oh, no.
Tyler's not here.
Tyler went away.
- Tyler's gone.
- What?
This is
impossible.
- No.
- This is crazy.
People do it
every day.
They talk
to themselves.
They see themselves
as they'd like to be.
They don't have
the courage you have,
to just
run with it.
Naturally, you're still
wrestling with it,
so sometimes
you're still you.
We should do this
again sometime.
Other times, you imagine
yourself watching me.
If this is your first
night at Fight Club,
you have to fight.
Little by little,
you’re just letting
yourself become...
Tyler Durden.
You are not
your job,
or how much money
you have in the bank!
No, you have
a house.
Rented in your name.
You have jobs, you
have a whole life.
You have night jobs
because you can't sleep.
Or you stay up
and make soap.
Marla--You're
fucking Marla, Tyler.
Uh, technically,
you're fucking Marla.
But it's
all the same to her.
Oh, my God.
Now you see
our dilemma.
She knows too much.
I think we're going
to have to talk
about how this might
compromise our goals.
Wh--What are
you saying?
This is--
This is bullshit.
I'm not listening
to this.
You are insane.
No, you're insane.
And we simply do not
have time for this crap.
It's called
a changeover.
The movie goes on,
and nobody
in the audience
has any idea.
Woman: Sir!
Are you checking out?
Yeah, uh,
b-bill me.
I need you to
initial this list
of phone calls,
please.
When were
these made?
It says
right there, sir,
between 2:00 and 3:30
this morning.
No, I w--
Have I been
going to bed
earlier
every night?
Have I been
sleeping later?
Have I been Tyler
longer and longer?
Is anybody here?
Déjà vu
all over again.
Yeah, with
enough soap,
we could blow up
just about anything.
Oh, my God.
Man On Telephone:
1 888.
I'm sorry,
who am I calling?
1 888 Franklin.
This is Maintenance.
Hello?
1 888 Franklin Street?
Yes.
Can I help you?
Hello?
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, I need to talk
to your supervisor
right away.
Speaking.
OK, listen to me.
I think something
really terrible
is about to happen
at your building.
You have got--
It's under
control, sir.
Excuse me?
Don't worry
about us, sir.
We're solid.
Man On Telephone:
21 60.
Marla!
Hey--Fuck!--Wait!
Wait, I gotta
talk to you!
Marla, Marla!
Your whacked-out
bald freaks
hit me with
a fucking broom!
They almost
broke my arm!
They were burning their
fingertips with lye,
the stink was
unbelievable.
Look--Look,
listen,
it's gonna take
a tremendous act
of faith
on your part,
but you've got
to hear me out.
Oh, here comes
an avalanche of bullshit.
A little more faith
than that.
No, listen,
I don't want to hear
anything
you have to say.
You have every
right to be...
Um, I'll just have
a coffee, thanks.
Sir, anything you order
is free of charge, sir.
Why is it
free of charge?
Don't--Don't ask.
Whatever.
I'll have the clam chowder,
the fried chicken
with the baked potato
with everything,
and a chocolate
chiffon pie.
Clean food, please.
In that case, sir,
may I advise against
the lady eating
the clam chowder?
No clam chowder,
thank you.
You've got
about 30 seconds.
Marla, I know that
I've been acting
very, very strange.
OK, I know that
it's got to seem
Like there's
2 sides to me--
2 sides?
You're Dr. Jekyll
and Mr. Jackass.
I deserve that,
but--
I've come
to realize something
very, very
important.
What?
The full extent
of our relationship
wasn't really clear
to me up until now,
for reasons I'm not
going to go into,
but the important
thing is, I know
that I haven't been
treating you so nice.
Yeah, whatever.
No, no--
1 5 seconds.
1 5 seconds,
please, please.
1 5 seconds, don't
open your mouth.
I'm trying to tell you
that I'm sorry.
Because what
I've come to realize
is that I really
like you, Marla.
You do?
I really do.
I care about you
and I don't want
anything bad
to happen to you
because of me.
Marla, your life
is in danger.
What?
You need to leave
town for a while.
Get out of
any major city
and just go camping
or something.
You're an insane person.
No, no,
I've involved you
in something terrible
that's about to happen.
No.
Shut up,
shut up!
Listen,
I tried, Tyler.
I really tried.
I know you did.
There are things
about you I like.
You're smart,
you're funny,
you're spectacular
in bed.
But you're
intolerable.
You have very serious
emotional problems.
Deep-seated problems
for which you should seek
professional help.
I know,
and I'm sorry.
Yeah, you're sorry,
I'm sorry,
everyone's sorry.
But...
I can't
do this anymore.
I can't.
And I won't.
I'm gone.
You can't leave,
Marla,
you're not safe!
No!
Leave me alone!
Marla, I'm trying
to protect you.
I don't ever want
to see you again!
That's fine, if
that's what it takes...
You wait.
Wait right here.
[Brakes Squealing]
Hold it
right there.
- [Honking]
- Shut up!
Shut up!
Take this money
and get on this bus.
And I promise you
I will never
bother you again
if that's
what you want.
- [Honks]
- Shut up!
Please get
on the bus.
on the bus!
Why are you
doing this?
Because they think you're
some kind of a threat.
I--I can't explain it
right now,
just trust me.
If I see
where you're going,
you will
not be safe.
I'm not paying
this back.
I consider it
asshole tax.
That's fine. Remember,
stay out of major cities
for at least
a couple of days, OK?
Tyler.
You're
the worst thing
that ever
happened to me.
[Honking]
Hello.
I need you
to arrest me.
I am the leader of
a terrorist organization
responsible for numerous
acts of vandalism,
and assault
all over this city.
...in the
metropolitan area,
with probably a couple
hundred members.
Chapters
have sprung up
in 5 or 6 other
major cities already.
This is a tightly
regimented organization,
with many cells
capable of operating
completely independent
of central leadership.
Look, look,
go to that house, OK?
1 537 Paper Street.
That's our headquarters.
In the back,
buried in the garden,
you'll find the body
of  Robert Paulson.
In the basement,
you're gonna find
some bathtubs
that have been used
very recently
to make large quantities
of nitroglycerin.
I believe the plan
is to blow up
the headquarters
of these credit card
companies,
and the T.R.W. building.
Why these buildings?
Why credit card
companies?
If you erase
the debt record,
then we all
go back to zero.
It'll create
total chaos.
Keep him talking.
I need to make
a phone call.
I really admire
what you're doing.
What?
You're a brave man
to order this.
You're a genius,
sir.
You said, if anyone
ever interferes
with Project Mayhem--
even you--
we gotta
get his balls.
It's useless
to fight.
This is really
a powerful gesture,
Mr. Durden.
It'll set quite
an example.
You're making
a big mistake, fellas.
You said
you'd say that.
I'm not
Tyler Durden!
You told us
you'd say that, too.
All right,
I am Tyler Durden.
Listen to me,
I'm giving you
a direct order.
We are aborting this
mission, right now.
You said you would
definitely say that.
Are you fucking
out of your minds?
You're
police officers!
Somebody
timing this?
No! No!
Keep your
mouth shut!
[Knock On Door]
Shit.
Yeah?
Hey, you know, some
of this information
checks out.
Let's go over
to that house
on Paper Street.
Be right there.
[Door Closes]
Hey! Wait!
I got him.
Sir, we have
to do this, sir.
Stop fighting.
Where's the rubber band?
Get away from me!
Drop that
fucking knife!
Drop it!
Back up.
Face down
on the floor,
both of you,
right now!
Get down
on the floor!
First person comes out
this fucking door
gets a--gets a lead salad,
you understand?
[Horns Blaring]
Get away!
I ran.
I ran until
my muscles burned
and my veins pumped
battery acid.
Then I ran
some more.
What the fuck
are you doing?
Running around
in your underpants.
Man, you look
like a crazy person.
No, I'm
onto you.
I know what's
going on here.
Well come on,
then.
I got us a great place
to watch from.
[Grunting]
It'll be like
pay-per-view.
Oh, Christ.
Now what
are you doing?
I'm stopping this.
Why? Greatest thing
you've ever done, man.
No, I can't
let this happen.
You know there
are 1 0 other bombs
in 1 0 other buildings.
God damn it, since when
is Project Mayhem
about murder?
The buildings
are empty.
Security and maintenance,
all our people.
We're not killing
anyone, man,
we're setting 'em free.
Bob is dead.
They shot him
in the head.
You wanna
make an omelet,
you gotta
break some eggs.
No, I'm not
listening to you.
You're not
even there.
Wouldn't do that.
Not unless I knew which
wires were what.
If you know,
then I know.
Or...
maybe I knew
you'd know,
so I spent
the whole day
thinking about
the wrong ones.
You think?
Oh, heavens no,
not the green one.
Pull any one
but the green one.
I asked you
not to do that!
Tyler, get away
from the van.
Tyler, I'm
not kidding!
Get away
from the van!
God damn it!
Whoa!
OK, you are now
firing a gun
at your imaginary
friend
near 400 gallons
of nitroglycerin!
Look, Tyler,
Tyler!
Ahh!
Aw, come on.
Don't go.
What?!
3 minutes.
This is it.
The beginning.
Ground zero.
I think this is about
where we came in.
Would you like
to say a few words
to mark the occasion?
[Mumbling]
I'm sorry?
I still can't think
of anything.
Ah, flashback humor.
It's getting
exciting now.
2 and 1 /2.
Think of everything
we've accomplished,
man.
Out these windows,
we will view
the collapse
of financial history.
One step closer to
economic equilibrium.
Why is she here?
Tying up loose ends.
Marla: Put me down,
you bald-headed fucks!
I'm begging you,
please don't
do this.
I'm not doing this.
We are doing this.
This is what we want.
No, I don't
want this.
Right, except you
is meaningless now.
We have to forget
about you.
Jesus, you're
a voice in my head.
You're a voice
in mine.
You're a fucking
hallucination,
why can't I
get rid of you?
You need me.
No, I don't,
I really don't anymore.
Hey, you created me.
I didn't create
some loser alter ego
to make myself
feel better.
Take some
responsibility.
I do.
I am responsible
for all of it,
and I
accept that.
So please,
I'm begging you,
please
call this off.
Have I ever
let us down?
How far have you come
because of me?
I will bring us
through this.
As always,
I will carry you,
kicking and screaming,
and in the end,
you will thank me.
Tyler.
Tyler, I'm
grateful to you
for everything
that you've
done for me.
But this
is too much.
I don't
want this.
What do you want?!
Want to go back
to the shit job,
fucking condo world,
watching sitcoms?
Fuck you.
I won't do it.
Oh, God, this
can't be happening.
It's already done,
so shut up.
60 seconds.
Can you see
alright?
I can figure this out.
I can figure this out,
this isn't even real.
You're not real,
that gun isn't--
That gun isn't
even in your hand.
The gun's in my hand.
Hey, good for you.
Doesn't change a thing.
Why do you want to put
a gun to your head?
Not my head, Tyler.
Our head.
Interesting.
Where are you going
with this, I KEA boy?
Hey, it's you
and me.
Friends.
Tyler...
I want you to
really listen to me.
OK.
My eyes are open.
What's that smell?
[Elevator Bell Dings]
Where is
everybody?
I don't know,
what's goin' on?
Mr. Durden!
Oh, my God.
Sir?
Are you, uh...
Are you
alright, sir?
Oh, yeah, I'm OK.
You look
terrible, sir.
What happened?
Oh, nothing.
It's no problem.
Oh, no, no, sir,
he's not kidding.
You look
really awful.
You need medical
assistance.
- I'm fine.
- Ugh.
Look, I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
[Marla Shouting]
Let--Let her go.
Christ
almighty!
You!
Hi, Marla.
Leave her
with me,
get your stuff,
I'll meet you
downstairs.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
You fucker!
What kind of sick
fucking game
are you
playing now,
putting me
on a fucking bu--
Oh, my God,
your face!
Yeah, I know.
What happened?
Don't ask.
You're shot.
Yes, I'm shot.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe
he's standing.
One tough
motherfucker.
Who did this?
I did, actually.
Find some gauze.
You shot
yourself?
Yes, but it's OK.
Marla, look at me.
I'm really OK.
Trust me.
Everything's
gonna be fine.
You met me at
a very strange time
in my life.
*With your feet
on the air*
*And your head
on the ground *
*Try this trick
and spin it, yeah *
*Your head'll
collapse *
* lf there's
nothing in it *
*And you'll ask
yourself*
*Where is my mind? *
*Way out in the water,
see it swimming *
* I was swimming
in the Caribbean *
*Animals were hiding
behind the rock*
* Except for little fish *
*When they told me
east is west *
*Trying to talk
to me, coy koi *
*Where is my mind? *
*Way out in the water,
see it swimming *
*With your feet
on the air*
*And your head
on the ground *
*Try this trick
and spin it, yeah *
*Your head'll collapse
if there's nothing in it *
*And you'll ask yourself*
*Where is my mind? *
*Way out in the water,
see it swimming *
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org