Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Look, or maybe it's not that literal.
All right, what's...
Could there be anything
in these prizes?
Oh, what, like he's gonna get
crushed by a giant Spongebob?
Hey, Spongebob lives underwater.
It's so sad that you know that.
All right. He won that tacky
mud-flap girl chain...
on this game, though, so...
aren't those usually
on those big 18 wheelers?
Yeah. Yeah.
God, I don't see it in
this picture anywhere though.
All right! God.
All right.
Uh, can I take your order?
Yeah. What do you want?
Are you OK?
Please tell me
there's a short in your wiring.
Whoa. Whoa. That guy's
way too close to my truck.
Hey, you're too fucking
close, man! Pull up!
Hey!
# There is someone #
Stop! Stop!
# Walking behind you #
Watch out! Shit!
- What the fuck?
- # Turn around #
- Oh, my God!
- # Look at me #
- Get out! Get out!
- What? What?
Behind us!
There's no one in that truck!
# Watching your footsteps #
Shit! Hey! Pull up, man!
Come on! Pull up!
- # Look at me #
- Unh! Shit!
- # There is someone #
- Back up!
Back up!
# Who really loves you #
# Here's my heart #
Watch your eyes!
Watch your eyes! Come here!
# In my hand #
# Turn around #
- # Look at me #
- Come on. Let's go!
Come on, come on, come on.
Unh!
- Oh!
- Unh!
We're all done here.
You need a ride?
Um, we can walk to my house...
and then I'll give you
a ride to yours.
No, thanks. We'll be OK.
Will we?
Yeah. We'll be all right.
I mean...
how Frank...
God, it... it's not only horrible...
but can you feel...
can you feel how vicious it was?
Easy.
OK? Easy.
Let's just...
let's just take a step back.
All right? He was behind
Ashley and Ashlyn on the ride...
but there was no ladder here.
You know, there was no rope.
Nothing in that picture pointed to this.
We were wrong about the photos.
I should've left town.
It's better not knowing.
No, it's never better
staying ignorant.
Willful ignorance
is surrendering control.
What, did you read that somewhere
in Mrs. Brooks' English class?
No. l... you know, I'm not...
I'm not the total idiot
you think I am.
OK, that's Lewis after Frank...
then lan and Erin.
There's a couple of kids behind them,
but I can't make them out...
because this guy's arm's
in the way. Can you?
No.
All right, you know what?
We'll ask Lewis, lan, and Erin
if they remember.
OK?
Are there any more pictures
from the roller coaster?
I guess...
that kind of thing
is gonna happen to us
for the rest of our lives.
Yeah.
You know, I was gonna...
I was gonna ask her to marry me.
Right after graduation.
Heh.
Oh.
No, wait.
Look, behind Stacy.
That's Frank.
This picture shows how he died.
All right, go back to Lewis.
OK, he's got that hammer.
And the weight looks like
it's coming down...
on his head.
No, no, no, check this out.
Right now Lewis is down at State
for football training camp.
State's team is called the Sultans.
That's it. That's the clue.
We have to tell him.
Show him these pictures.
Wouldn't you want to know?
Wait, there's pictures of us in there?
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Huh. No.
No. I don't want to see mine.
No. Huh.
What about willful ignorance?
Well, I'm full of shit, all right?!
I mean, I never thought
I could see my own death...
before it happened, Wendy.
No, you know what?
We can tell Lewis, but...
Seriously, if there's any way
to beat this thing...
I gotta stay focused...
and if I look at that picture,
all I'm gonna do is obsess.
So, you know what?
No, I don't want to see it.
I mean, unless we have to.
You mean until we have to.
One more thing.
Is it bad?
I mean, is it, like,
painful or embarrassing?
I mean, there's nothing, like,
up my ass or anything, right?
I'll see you tomorrow.
You on crack. Both of you.
Just listen, OK?
Ashley and Ashlyn were first.
Then Frankie Cheeks
and then you. This is the...
- Aw, come on, Kevin.
- Listen.
McKinley and Erin
were next, all right?
And there were two people in front of us.
Do you remember who they were?
Fuck no, and I don't care.
And you shouldn't care either, man...
'cause what you're tellin' me
right now is straight bullshit.
Just listen, Lewis.
Kevin, it's like those stories.
Like this guy was killed
by a car he sold 10 years ago.
Two sisters, right, were killed when
they were driving to visit each other.
You know, shit like that, man.
Fuck the Bruins!
Oh, yeah! Fuck the Bruins!
Bruin faggots!
Yeah! Fuck the Bruins!
Man, you're reading into this shit
like them damn urban legends.
Three people have died, Lewis.
I mean, if you think
this can be written off...
as a simple coincidence
and it ends there...
you're in serious denial.
Unh! What about you two, huh?
What?
You both lost people real close
to you in a fucked-up way.
And in order to feel
less guilty or whatever...
seeing signs and patterns, man.
I don't blame you.
But it's wrong, dawg.
Unh! It's wrong.
That's denial.
Unh!
- Unh!
- You got it!
OK, what about what happened
at the roller coaster? Huh?
Wendy saw it.
Man, she got a hunch.
Fuckin' intense, but she got a hunch.
Man, I'm here because I get
good hunches before every down.
No, you know
they're either gonna run or pass.
Hers came to her from nowhere.
You're here and alive because of her.
No, I'm alive because of me.
No, listen.
You don't get it, man.
Does that make sense to you?
There's nothing to get, Kevin!
It's bullshit.
No, just hear me out, all right?
Unh.
# Yeah #
Talk about a vision.
Man, I seen my whole life played out...
and it sure as hell
ain't gonna end now. Unh!
It's going just as I saw it.
35 high school games
without an injury.
- USA Today All-American.
- Second team.
- Free ride to play for the Sultans!
- The Bruins passed on you.
Man, fuck the Bruins!
- Fuck 'em!
- You goddamn right!
What the fuck is a Bruin anyway?
Aah!
Unh! Unh! Unh!
Four years from now...
Lewis Romero goin' in
the second round to Oakland.
Unh!
He's gonna romp and stomp.
15 seasons, with four Super Bowl
rings on his fingers.
Lewis ain't afraid of no death.
Fuck Death!
Death is a fuckin' Denver fan.
Death wear blue and orange.
Real men wear black.
Lewis ain't afraid of no Death.
Death is afraid of me!
Death fears me!
Kevin.
'Cause, baby, I just win.
I just win, Kevin!
That's all I know how to do!
I just win! Unh!
Fuck Death!
- Fuck the Bruins!
- Yeah!
Aah!
- Look out!
- Lewis!
Man, that was close, Lewis.
Hey, did you see that?
Whoo! What I tell you,
Kevin, huh?
Fuck Death! I just win!
That's all I know
how to do, Kevin.
Baby, I just win!
Aaaaah!
- Ooooh!
- God!
Did I do something...
to bring this on everybody?
Don't, Wendy.
But why me?
All those people out there
wanting to have a premonition...
or see a ghost or whatever,
and I don't.
I just want it to stop.
Just stop.
I don't know why, Wendy...
but you didn't do anything.
All right? This is just...
I don't know. I mean,
I wish I knew why, you know?
I wish I could... I could
come up with a guess even...
to make you feel OK, but...
You know, I can't.
Yeah.
There's nothing I can do.
Can you drive?
Heh.
Yeah.
You know, by the way,
that... that picture of me.
My, uh, my head's not, like,
through the windshield or anything?
You know,
crushed by a steering wheel?
lmpaled by a gear shift?
Right?
Zip, it's Pip.
Have you cut
those plywood orders yet?
Uh, that's a big no, Pip.
Osama bin Supervisor wants me
to get rid of these pigeons first.
They keep settin' off the alarms.
Hello, babies.
Ha ha ha!
Oh, ha ha ha! Heh.
Hey. After I, uh, restock
this stuff...
that these pinhead customers
can't manage...
to return to the shelves
themselves...
we can blow out of here, OK?
Righty-o, babe.
Aah!
Erin, it's Wendy and Kevin.
Shit!
You scared the shit out of me!
Yeah, wait till you hear
what we have to tell you.
Zip, it's Pip. Come over here.
You are gonna trip
when you hear this.
Well, paint me intrigued, Pip.
I'm on my way.
So let me get this straight.
I'm gonna O.D. on nail polish...
and lan is gonna be
embarrassed to death?
You saw what happened
to Wendy, right?
What's happened to the others?
I mean, you just saw their pictures.
Oh, my God, guys,
what's going on?
What's going on?
That's crazy! That's crazy!
Ha ha!
We need to know who was sitting
behind you on the roller coaster.
OK, who was sitting behind us
on the roller coaster?
Oh! Oh, wait! Wasn't it
that one guy who got voted...
most likely to become
manager at Red Lobster?
Oh, no. You know what?
God, I remember.
There was this guy,
uh, black cloak...
I didn't see his face, but, um...
the ride attendant
did take his sickle...
before the ride started
if that's helpful in any way.
Do you think we care
if you laugh at us?
This is our lives, OK?
What choice do we have?
Just give into it?
Oh, God. You know what?
There is no "it."
OK, wait, are you guys saying
that Death is, like, a person?
No. It's like... like a force.
Yeah. Well, you know what?
A force is just a force.
It's nothing else.
Just transferred energy.
I mean, it has no goals,
no awareness that is a force.
But there is awareness, McKinley.
In fact, in past cases,
if the next in line is saved...
it'd skip that person.
That's why we're here.
Oh, man,
what have you been smoking?
Ha ha!
- Top shelf.
- OK.
Kevin! Those banners.
They're in the picture.
lan, watch those boxes!
What the fuck, man?
You said those boxes were falling!
No, I said watch the boxes.
Really? What for?
They're not doing anything.
We're not gonna apologize
for trying to save you.
You haven't seen or been through
what we have... yet.
Oh. Yet.
OK, so who's next in this theory
you have, me or lan?
Well, we know the order of how
we were sitting on the roller coaster...
but not how it works
with people who sat together.
OK, we don't know
if Ashley or Ashlyn died first.
Hmm. God, Death is
fucking complicated.
Ha ha!
No, you know what?
It's not complicated.
It's simple. People die.
That's just part of life.
150,000 people a day, actually.
You know? I mean...
we're biological entities,
and death is just...
- Top shelf.
- the end of biological function.
It's as simple as that.
How can you explain
what happened to us as simple?
I mean, if Wendy never had
that premonition...
and none of us had gotten off that ride,
we'd all be dead right now.
- Does that not make sense to you?
- Oh, yeah.
Kevin, how come when a guy dies
of a plain heart attack...
no one goes, like...
"Oh, wow, he was
eating French toast...
"when Princess Diana
died in Paris...
"and then he saw her funeral on TV,
and now he's dead"?
You know why?
Because they'd sound crazy...
so guess how you two
sound right now? Crazy.
Zip, I'm done.
So finish cutting those orders...
- so we can get out of here.
- OK!
Unh!
Heh heh!
Ugh!
Sick.
OK.
Let's go with
what you guys are saying.
Let's just say, you know...
that Death does have
a conscious plan...
and that it's been
set into motion. Great.
So, Newton's third law of motion,
and, well, look...
I'm just guessing
that it goes for Death, too...
when he's working in our world.
Newton says that every action
has an equal and opposite reaction.
So, that means that...
if Death has taken action,
so can we.
And that that action
we take might have...
an opposite reaction
that thwarts Death's intent.
You're being a fucker, but go on.
OK. OK.
What if, for example...
the last in line were to make
the utilitarian choice...
Kill themselves.
Wow! Wow! That's pretty much
gonna ruin any plan...
that Death's put in motion.
And even better...
hey, it's gonna save
five skipped lives.
Any takers?
Nah, I didn't think so.
There! Those!
Ugh!
Aah!
Ooh!
Unh! Unh!
Unh!
Aah!
I didn't say anything.
I mean, I think...
they were trying to scare us
into saying something...
but they had nothing
to keep me there.
What'd you tell 'em?
Everything.
I didn't do anything.
I told them about
the pictures in the camera...
and Flight 180
and Frankie and Lewis...
and why we went to see
lan and Erin and...
Did they believe you?
Yeah, right.
Would you believe me?
No, they looked at me
like I was crazy.
10 hours they had us in there.
For all we know...
whoever was sitting
behind Erin is already dead.
And we're next.
Now.
lan almost died first,
but we intervened.
So it skipped lan.
That's... that's how we regain control.
If someone intercedes...
the life that was supposed
to be next is skipped.
All right, wait, wait, wait.
So, going by the way we sat
on the roller coaster...
Well, I'm next... and then you.
We can beat this.
We're so close.
We can't give up.
All right, my dad's here.
He's gonna give me a ride back.
But are you sure
we shouldn't stick together?
It's just for a couple of hours.
All right? A couple of hours.
Go back, look at the pictures,
see if you can find any more clues...
and I'll ask everybody I see if they know
if anyone else got off the ride.
OK?
Was there something
I should know about going?
No, it's just...
I'll just be freaking out
every second...
hoping you're OK.
Why?
I mean,
we don't even like each other.
Heh.
Come here.
OK?
All right, I got my cell.
OK.
Hey, Wen?
So we're meeting some guys
at that centennial thing...
and I could really use
my good-luck... bracelet.
Mmm.
Huh.
Hey, this is Julie.
Leave a message.
Call me on my cell right away.
Hello?
Do you remember Julie
being on the roller coaster?
What, your sister? No.
No, she would've said
something by now.
The person sitting
behind lan and Erin...
was wearing the exact same
charm bracelet...
our grandmother gave her.
Amber or Perry
were probably with her...
so they're next.
I gotta find Julie.
She went to
the tricentennial thing.
Well, l... I'm here now,
working security.
I'll start looking for her.
- I'm on my way.
- Wen, wait.
Look, after them, we're next.
So in case somethin'
happens to 'em...
before we meet up...
remember that time
we talked about?
When to look at our pictures?
It's now.
Great. Mine has no clue.
It's just me standing in front of
a blank background...
with Jason at
the amusement park.
Wait. McKinley.
lan? Is he in the picture?
No, but it... it feels like a clue.
And yours is the picture
that I took...
when I flashed the camera
in your face.
It's all out of focus
and overexposed, like...
Like a firework
went off in my face?
# There is someone #
# Walking behind you #
# Look at me #
# There is someone #
# Watching your footsteps #
# Look at me #
# There is someone #
# Who really loves you #
The British are coming!
- Whoo!
- Yay!
Get 'em while they're hot!
Take it to those Redcoats!
Column, advance!
The kite is aloft.
Now, let us hope
for some lightning.
Fuck you, Ben Franklin.
But he kept insisting.
"Get over here," right?
This is awesome, dude!
Heh heh.
Whoa. Hey!
Ha ha! Come on!
Hey, get out of here with those, man!
You're gonna set these off!
Hurry, dude.
Come on, man, let's go!
Hurry up!
Ladies and gentlemen,
to celebrate McKinley's tricentennial...
the fireworks extravaganza
will begin shortly.
Oh, my God. Julie.
- What?
- Look.
There's Kahlil.
Should we?
Hey, guys. I'm sorry,
but you can't be here, OK?
The viewing site is over there.
You too, sir. Come on.
They're not gonna
make us move, are they?
I don't fucking believe them.
- OK, we gotta clear out.
- Mm-hm.
Excuse me.
- Ladies.
- Boys.
What's going on?
Hey, Julie.
- You three need to come with me.
- What did we do?
Look, it's for your own safety,
Julie, all right?
I'll tell you about it as soon as
we get away from here, OK?
Let go of me!
Julie.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Julie!
Heh heh heh!
- Sweet.
- Ha ha!
Yeah!
Light it! Light it!
Go, go, go, man!
Julie!
Uh! Oh!
- Oh, shit!
- Dude, we gotta bail!
- Aah!
- Unh!
Unh! Hey!
Julie! No, wait, wait.
You're in danger, OK?
I'm trying to explain something.
Let me explain this to you.
Julie, look out!
- Aah!
- Unh!
Aah!
Julie!
Unh!
Aah! Unh!
Cut him off!
Unh!
Aah!
OK, OK.
Stay back! He's dangerous!
I got him.
- Just let me go.
- No, Julie.
You have to tell me,
you have to listen.
Tell me who was sitting next to you
on the roller coaster!
Oh, my God,
Julie, are you all right?
Listen to me!
You have to tell me...
who was sitting next to you
on the roller coaster!
Who? She's next!
Aah!
Kevin.
Fire!
You saved my life.
Thanks for that, McKinley.
- Shut up, McKinley!
- No!
We have to get out of here now.
What's the deal?
lan McKinley.
He causes my death.
In my picture I was wearing
the McKinley grad night shirt.
- He's the clue.
- What?
There's a first aid tent,
there should be security.
Get the fuck outta here, McKinley!
Hey, I'm just celebrating
our town's tricentennial.
You followed me!
Oh! You are paranoid.
But, hey, I saw what happened.
You're next, right?
You're the end of it, aren't you?
Man, I would be paranoid, too.
You didn't even believe me!
Yeah, well, seeing is believing.
Then you have
to stay away from me!
"Have to"?
Wow, that's extreme.
Oh, no way.
Do I cause your death?
Just like you caused Erin's?
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, what? What?
You have a vision? Was I in it?
Was I in a picture?
Just tell me how to start it off!
Let's get this over with!
You'll save me
if you just stay away!
Then it'll all be over!
What do I care? It skipped me.
For me, it is over.
I'm not dying.
I'm not dying!
Ha ha ha!
You see?
I'm not gonna die!
It's you, Wendy! You're dead!
# Came back down
from this fight #
- Hi!
- # Will get ya deeper #
# And make you right #
Thank you.
# Bruno's drops
threaten her... #
Wait, what about
that great curry place?
Don't we get off at Booth?
Oh, you mean Gupta's.
You get off at Oswald.
Oh, that's right.
You know, if I can't be home
for Thanksgiving...
I need some semblance
of a traditional dinner.
Turkey, stuffing, pie.
If you don't have turkey
for one Thanksgiving...
is that really gonna kill you?
# There is someone #
# Walking behind you #
# Turn around #
# Look at me #
# There is someone #
# Watching your footsteps #
# Turn around #
# There is someone #
# Who really needs you #
# Here's my heart #
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
This is Booth Street.
Next stop is Oswald.
End of the line.
The next stop
is the end of the line.
Wendy! Next stop after this.
- Let's just walk.
- It's freezing out.
Yeah, but the air'll feel good.
I could use some air.
Yeah!
Ha ha ha! Yeah, man!
All right, man. See ya.
Let's go, Bruins!
Bruins, yeah!
Hey, man, peace out!
- Come on.
- Excuse me.
- Watch out!
- Hey, Bruins!
You missed the beginning.
Did you see that?
This is it!
Yo, comin' through. Excuse me.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe this. Here.
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
I thought you weren't
coming till tonight.
Well, Dad's car just, like,
dies out of nowhere...
and he couldn't get it fixed
anywhere on a holiday...
so instead of sitting around
for a few hours...
I lucked out and caught
an early train.
I hope I'm not messing you up or...
No, no, it's just, um...
I think I had a sense
that you were coming now.
I was just...
I was feeling like I did that night.
No. No, it's over.
You, me, Kevin went over
a thousand scenarios.
lan was gonna cause your death...
you intervened,
and it skipped us.
Look, I'm not worried.
I ran into Kevin at home.
He's not worried.
And, if I were you...
until something happens
to me and then Kevin...
you've got nothing
to worry about.
You're right.
Uhh.
Hey, l... I want you to meet
my roommate and my friend, OK?
Yeah.
Hey, guys. This is Julie, my...
What are you doing here?
Wendy! Julie!
What are the chances?
How long have you been
on this train?
Uh, since home.
I was headin' up
to check out the game.
I was gonna look you up
afterwards.
You OK?
Is something wrong?
Aah!
- Aah!
- Unh!
- Julie, stay down!
- Aah!
Julie!
Aah!
- Kevin!
- Unh!
Aaaaaah!
Oh, God!
Aah!
Aah! Unh!
No!
I was gonna look you up
afterwards, but...
You OK?
Is somethin' wrong?
The train...
Oh, shit. Not again.
We gotta get out!
It's not working.
Somebody stop the train!
# People around the world #
# Join hands #
# Start a love train,
love train #
# People around the world #
# Join hands #
# Start a love train #
# Love train #
# The next stop that we make,
we'll make it soon #
# We'll make it soon #
# Don't tell anybody
what we're gonna do #
# We're gonna do #
# And climb on board
'cause you've got #
# Nothing to lose #
# If you miss this train #
# I feel sorry for you #
# People around the world #
# Join hands #
# Start a love train,
love train #
# People around the world #
# Join hands #
# Start a love train #
# Love train #
# People around the world #
# Join hands #
# Start a love train,
love train #
# People around the world #
# Join hands #
# Start a love train #
# Love train #
# All my friends,
I'm talking to you #
# Talking to you,
talking to you #
# And tell everybody
that you know, too #
# Don't be afraid
to try something new #
# If you missed this train #
# I feel sorry for you #
# People around the world #
# Join hands #
# Start a love train,
love train #
# People around the world #
# Join hands #
# Start a love train,
love train #
# People around the world #
# Join hands #
# Start a love train,
love train #
# People around the world #
# Join hands #
# Start a love train #
# Love train #
# People around the world #
# Join hands #
# Start a love train,
love train #
# People around the world #
# Join hands #
# Start a love train,
love train #
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org