Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Tomorrow marks
the one year anniversary
since Velez Air Flight 180
exploded and crashed
shortly after takeoff
from JFK Airport.
It's a disaster
that's affected many.
None more so than
Mt Abraham High School,
which lost 40 students and four
faculty members in the crash.
But it was the events
after the crash
that has turned this tragic story
into something even stranger.
The survivors who managed
to get off the plane before it crashed
died soon thereafter
in a series
of mysterious
and bizarre accidents.
Now, to some, these deaths
are just tragic coincidences,
but to others,
they're an indication
that there are more
sinister events taking place.
That's the contention
of tonight's guest.
Thank you for joining us
this evening.
Thank you for having me.
And I appreciate you using
the word sinister.
Most people say supernatural
because they think I'm talking
about ghosts and witches
and stuff like that.
Here's your chance
to set the record straight.
Great. Okay.
I believe that there's
a sort of force,
an unseen malevolent
presence...
that's all around us
every day.
And it determines
when we live and die.
And some people call
this force the devil,
but I think that
whole religious thing is...
so I prefer to call it
Death itself.
So I'm surrounded by Death?
Absolutely. Absolutely.
Every day, everywhere,
all the time.
And that's what I want people
to understand...
that Death
has this grand design
that we all fit into.
So when Alex Browning
got off that plane
and took the other
survivors with him,
he basically screwed up
Death's plan.
And that's what I'm trying
to warn people about.
And the fact that all
of the survivors have died
is your evidence of this?
Well, it's not so much
that the survivors died,
but it's the way
that they died.
I mean, there were
so many weird,
seemingly random things
about the way they died.
It just didn't
make sense.
And that's the proof
there's something out there...
Wait, that's not proof.
That is your interpretation
of events that can't be proven
in order to support your ideas.
Kimberly.
You should be more
open-minded...
What happened after that
was just coincidence.
May I finish?
Mere coincidence would have
one or two of these kids die.
But not all of them
including their teachers.
Yes, but people die
all the time,
so why should this be
any different?
It forced people
to question
these so-called
everyday coincidences.
What if they
were something more?
What if you could do
something about it?
Please, are you listening
to yourself? This is crazy.
You're saying we should be on guard
every morning when we leave the house?
That's exactly what
I'm saying.
Exactly it.
And in order
to survive...
the only way to survive
is to look beneath
the visible world.
Because in the end no one
can escape death.
And today may be
your day to die.
Okay, I'll call you.
Kimberly, are you sure
you've got everything?
Credit card,
cell phone, Triple-A card?
Dad, it's Daytona,
not Somalia.
Alright. Fix-a-flat, road flares,
sunblock, mace?
Condoms,
whips, chains.
Just kidding,
Mr Corman.
Don't worry,
I'll keep an eye on her.
That makes me feel
a lot better, thanks.
- Okay.
- Alrighty.
Can we go get the guys?
I'm getting horny.
Go on.
Okay, I'll call you.
Whips and chains.
That's nice.
Whatever,
your dad's cool.
Buckle up!
Watch it!
- Oh, easy, Kimmy. First year of driving?
- Sorry.
- Oh my God.
- Fucking freak.
Yo, Dano,
shouldn't we help your mum?
Good one, man.
You're hilarious.
You're not getting any of my weed.
Nothing.
Whatever.
What are we going to do
in Daytona?
We're going to see lots
of honeys there.
We're gonna get drunk, we're gonna smoke
this big 'El Gagerero,'
We're gonna have this
awesome party...
Pileup! Pileup!
A candlelight vigil to mark
the one year anniversary
of the crash of Flight 180
will be held at 8:00 P.M. Tonight
at the Mt Abraham
high school auditorium.
.' Highway to hell... .'
Oh my God.
- Hello?
- Hey, Kimberly, it's Dad.
- Hey, what's up?
- Your car's leaking transmission fluid.
- So I want you to get it checked right away.
- Okay, yeah.
I'll do that.
I mean it. Take care of it.
- Is that someone coughing?
- Yeah, okay.
I'll take care of it.
I'll talk to you later.
- I love you.
- Bye, honey.
- What did you do?
- Look at those titties!
- Shut up.
- You missed that?!
That's too bad.
Oh, shit!
Fuck man, there's a cop behind us!
Pull in the right lane now!
Shit.
Seriously, put it out.
- Put that thing out.
- Alright.
Wait, wait, wait!
- Get rid of it.
- Shit.
Hey, it's Kat.
Listen...
what the hell?!
Just wait. Not you.
I think we better pull over
and check the car, because...
Kimberly, the car
is going to be fine.
Your dad's going to be fine,
you're going to be fine.
Okay?
Look at that guy.
He's drinking a beer.
Oh, yeah,
that's real responsible.
You ever hear
of the ozone layer, arsehole?!
.' When it comes to this drug shit
I was made to play.'
.' Don't come around if
you ain't got no cocaine to bring... '
What? I'm wearing
my seatbelt.
You're gonna bust me,
bitch?!
Aaah!
Son of a...
bitch.
Fuck!
- Oh my God!
- Watch out!
- Stop!
- Oh my God!
Watch out!
Aaah!
Shaina?
I can't get out of here!
Help me!
Oh, easy, Kimmy.
First year of driving?
Yo, Dano,
shouldn't we help your mum?
Good one, man.
You're hilarious.
Pileup! Pileup!
- Oh my God.
- What?
There's going to be
a huge accident.
We're all gonna die!
I just saw it.
That's it.
My turn to drive.
- No, I'm serious.
- Kim, what's wrong?
- What are you doing?
- Oh my God.
...of Flight 180 will be held
at 8:00 P.M. Tonight
at the Mt Abraham
high school auditorium.
'Highway to hell.'
'Highway to hell... '
'Highway to hell'?
.' I'm on a highway to hell... '
Okay, Kimberly,
you're scaring me.
- Green means go, Kimmy.
- Yeah.
Are you out of your friggin' mind?
What the hell are you doing?
What the fuck, Kimberly?
What's this?
Kimberly, you just got
to breathe.
Oh, shit, shit.
Five-O's coming. Let's fucking roll.
- What?
- Oh my God.
Do you know how much
fucking weed I have on me? Huh?
Okay, Dano, just shut up!
Just stay cool.
Oh, fuck. I'm going to jail.
I'm fucking going to jail.
What's going on here?
I think there's going
to be a huge pileup.
I saw it.
There were bodies
everywhere.
There were logs...
I saw it.
It just happened.
Alright, miss, I'd like you to please
step out of the vehicle.
Just pull over!
I know,
Mummy's hungry, too.
Come on.
Come on!
Oh, fuck this.
I'm going to get this
and we're going to go.
Fuck.
What the hell
is going on up there?
Excuse me!
Is there any way
that we could drive around?
- I have a delivery...
- You need to get back into your vehicles.
- Just move it...
- Now!
That's it!
That's the truck
that's going to kill everybody.
You need to stop
that truck!
I told you again,
you have to calm down!
Why won't you listen to me?!
- Fuck!
- Oh my God.
This is unit 13 requesting
medical assistance
and backup for a major
traffic accident...
Kimberly, what's going on?
No!
Listen, sir,
this girl is really freaked out.
In fact, all of them are...
- scared as you can imagine.
- Scared?!
These people are the luckiest
sons of bitches on the planet.
Get this guy,
Evan Lewis...
yesterday the kid
wins the lotto.
Today, some loony bitch
blocks traffic
and he avoids the worst
pileup in years.
I should be
so damn 'unlucky.'
Go babysit the rest of them.
I'll be done with Lewis
in a minute.
Hey, excuse me...
We're trying to do
the best we can.
We're going to get you
out of here as soon as possible.
I just think it's a bunch
of bullshit.
Listen, I know
you've gone over all this
with Detective Suby...
but would you mind
telling me what happened?
It was like I was there.
I knew something bad was going
to happen even before it did.
- I just felt wrong, just like...
- Just like what?
Look, I know
this sounds crazy but...
you guys all heard
about Flight 180, right?
The kid who got off
the plane?
Well, it happened
a year ago, today.
My premonition
was just like his.
- What are you talking about?
- Come on.
You must have read
about the kid
who had a dream
about a plane blowing up,
so he got all his buddies
off the plane
and then the thing blew up
just like in his dream?
- Yeah.
- But did you hear what happened after?
So a month goes by, right?
Everything seems cool.
But then all the survivors
start to die one by one.
'Cause when your number's up,
your number's up, right?
You know, some people even say that
Death itself was stalking them,
hunting each one down
until they were all...
dead.
Please.
There was one survivor.
Clear Rivers is
in a padded room
at the Stonybrook Institution.
Well, that's encouraging.
Okay, you want me
to believe that this is true,
that this is happening
all over again?
I don't know why
we're even here.
What do you want from me?
But if I was never meant
to pull over,
we all should have died
in that pileup.
Which means Death
could be coming for us.
Yeah, like, what if
we're all getting that 'Different Strokes'
curse or something?
I think you're all
are certifiable.
I can't believe I've been listening
to this crap.
Let's go.
Let's go, Tim.
Mrs Carpenter, please.
Kimberly!
Oh baby!
- Are you okay?
- I'm so sorry.
Shh, shh.
You can all go now.
Thank you for your patience.
Could I ask you something?
Anything.
Did Mum ever have any...
I don't know,
weird feelings about anything?
What do you mean?
Like visions or premonitions.
Sweetie, are you sure
you're okay?
Dad, I know
this sounds crazy,
but I'm really scared
for the others.
I don't know,
I have this really bad feeling.
What?
It's not over yet.
Jesus Christ!
Shit!
Hey, Evan, it's Tawny.
Sorry I haven't called.
Hey, listen, I heard
about your lottery win.
Let's hook up.
Call me.
Yeah.
Hi, Evan, it's Nikki.
We met at Tucker's party
last year?
I know it's been awhile,
but I've been thinking about you.
I just wanted to say
congratulations.
So give me a call.
555-0123. Bye.
You little bastard.
Shit.
Come on.
Fuck. Fuck.
Come on!
Come on.
Fuck!
Jesus!
Oh!
Hey, this is Evan.
Leave a message.
If you're looking for Rick,
I don't know where he is,
and I don't know
when he's coming back. Thanks.
Evan, call me when you
get in, you lucky fuck!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Aah!
Jesus!
Come on.
Aah!
Shit, I'm lucky.
Jesus Christ!
No, Mother,
just turn on any station.
Well, I don't know how you missed it,
it's been on all day.
Yes, Mother,
Channel 4 is fine.
Okay... here it is!
I got to go, okay?
I got to go!
To recap our top story,
Route 23 was backed up
for almost nine hours today.
A record-breaking pileup
killed an estimated 18 people.
Emergency crews spent hours
sifting through the wreckage
hoping to recover any survivors
from this tragic collision.
So far police are refusing
to release the names of the victims
until the families
are notified.
The camera
of a highway patrol car
managed to catch
this shocking footage.
- A semi comes...
- Oh my God.
And smashes
into a red SUV.
- The driver of the SUV...
- No, um...
leave it.
...may have
saved her life.
He pulled her back
at the last second
just as the semi ploughed
into the vehicle.
The passengers inside
the SUV...
Oh, oh, oh! You guys see that?!
Shit, I was there, baby!
In other news, a freak accident took
the life of a lotto winner.
- Friends say Evan Lewis...
- Hey, shh.
Was on top of the world after
recently winning $250,000.
But in tragic turn of events,
Lewis died today
while trying to escape a fire
in his apartment.
He managed to make it out
of the building,
but somehow the ladder
on the fire escape
slipped and impaled him.
Investigators believe Lewis
died instantly.
Come in.
Hey, buddy.
I want you to take this
so you can get some sleep.
And then tomorrow it's off to the dentist,
which I know you love.
Now, get some rest.
- Mum.
- Yeah?
You think those guys
were BSing us today?
Yeah.
Some people just need
some rewiring, that's all.
Lights out.
At the request
of the patient,
you'll relinquish
any sharp objects
such as: 'nail files,
pencils, pens,
safety pins, bobby pins,
your necklace,
matches, lighters,
belts, belt buckles,
earrings, hair clips,
glasses, shoelaces,
paper clips, watches, money clip,
pocket knives,
food, drinks, keys,
cell phone... '
You have a cell phone
on you?
'... poisons, pills,
medications.'
Great. And let me see
your nails.
Good. Then I think
we're all done.
Wait.
Is she dangerous
or something?
No, honey,
she expects you are.
No, no, no.
Get him off me.
Get him off me!
How long are they gonna keep
her locked up like this?
Depends on her, I guess.
She's voluntary.
- Clear Rivers?
- Don't come any closer.
They told me you had something to do
with the crash on Route 23.
Look, I don't know how
to explain it,
but I saw the pileup
before it happened.
And I saved some people.
And now you think Death
is after you.
Nice work.
Maybe if you're real lucky,
you'll wind up in here with me.
Anything else?
One of the people died
in a freak accident last night.
What if the other people
are in danger, too?
If you put them on the list,
they're already dead.
List? What list?
Death's list.
The survivors of Flight 180
died in the exact order
they were originally meant
to die in the plane crash.
That was Death's original design.
The list.
I was supposed to die
in that crash with my friends.
So you're telling me
that I'm next?
You said someone else died
last night.
That means someone must
have intervened.
Officer Burke pulled me away
from the crash that killed my friends.
Congratulations.
You'll be the last to go.
But don't worry,
once the others are dead,
it'll come back for you.
It always does.
This doesn't make sense.
You said that you die in
the order you're originally meant to.
But my friends died last
in my premonition, not first.
Wait.
Died last?
Backwards.
Are you sure?
In my premonition
that Nora woman
and her kid died.
Then Evan,
then me and my friends.
Why is this even
happening to me?
That's what Alex used
to ask himself.
So, what am I
supposed to do?
Clear.
Watch out for the signs.
What?
Have you ever seen anything
creepy or ominous?
An in-your-face irony
kind of thing?
The songs on the radio.
Yeah, the guy in the beer truck,
everything on the road.
Well, don't ignore it.
Recognising those signs usually means
the difference between life and death.
You got to help me.
I don't have
to do anything.
But you beat it.
Take a look around.
What did I beat, Kimberly?
If you were smart, you'd save yourself
and just forget about the others.
How can you say that?
You have a responsibility.
My friends are dead.
That's how I can say that.
This is what happened to Alex
when I was responsible for him.
Get out.
Before you hurt me or yourself.
- Alright, you know what?
- What?
I think you're a coward.
You hide out in here
because you're
too damn bitter and selfish
to help any other person.
In my opinion,
you're already dead.
I tried calling you
last night,
but your father said
you were sleeping.
- Evan Lewis is dead.
- Yeah.
I've been getting calls all morning from
everyone who was on the on-ramp.
We're meeting tonight
at my apartment.
Wait, so...
you believe all this Death stuff?
Well, at first,
no, I didn't.
Until last year
when I was dispatched
to clean up one
of the Flight 180 survivors.
Clean up, I don't...
- Did you see that?
- See what?
- Pigeons.
- Pigeons?
- It's a sign.
- A sign of what?
If Clear's right
about the order,
then Nora and Tim are going
to be attacked by pigeons.
I'm not following you.
They're next
on Death's list.
If we don't find them,
they're going to die.
The doctor's ready
for you, now.
If he gives me the gas
and I wake up
with my pants unbuttoned...
- we ain't paying.
- Tim.
There you are.
What happened to you yesterday, Tim?
We missed you in here.
We got hung up by that accident on
Route 23.
Good Lord.
How lucky that you're okay.
Your mum says you've been
having some pain lately.
Not really.
I'm disappointed, Tim.
Does your mum know
you've been smoking?
Uh-huh.
Ow.
Yeah, that one's going
to have to be filled.
Damn those pigeons.
How many times am I going to have to
replace those goddamn windows?
We can't do it, boss,
we can't do it!
This will only sting for a moment.
Open big.
Little bit wider.
Wider.
Okay.
Oh God.
How do they
expect me to...
Would you rather just have
the laughing gas?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Jean, I'm going
to need you in here.
You'll have to speak up,
there's too much noise.
What?!
I can't hear you!
Excuse me, what?!
Yes, the sixth at 2:00 P.M.
Jean! Let me
get this started.
Tim, you'll be awake,
a little groggy,
but you're not going
to be able to move much.
Okay, great, thanks.
Alright, turn around.
The cleaning lady said they're at
the Ellis Medical Complex off of 14th.
God damn it anyway.
- Okay, I got it.
- I can't find a box!
Not again. Careful.
There we go.
Jean,
how's Tim doing in there?
What did he say
about your tooth?
- Did he say...
- I can't remember.
- Nora!
- The pigeons!
What? Pigeons?
Hey, whoa, whoa!
Kid, kid!
- No-oo!
- Tim!
Look out!
- Stay back, stay back!
- No! Please, no!
Nora's not coming.
She won't leave her son.
- No, but she's next...
- Right now I don't think she cares.
This is really
happening again, isn't it?
I hoped we'd get there
and they'd be fine,
and Clear Rivers
was just full of shit,
and Evan Lewis' death
was just some freak accident.
But we're all going to die,
aren't we?
I'm so scared.
I know you didn't ask
for any of this...
but I don't think you have it
in you to quit either.
A second one just died.
A 15-year-old kid.
I hope you're ready for this.
It's this way.
How is this guy going
to help us anyway?
He seemed to know
a hell of a lot more
about Death
than he ever told us.
Shouldn't we knock first?
He probably already knows
we're coming.
Hello, Clear.
I've been expecting you.
Oh my God.
- That's Evan Lewis.
- Come to pick my brain?
Just a simple question and we'll leave you
alone with your new friend.
Dead...
yet still fresh.
Look, we drove
a long way to get here,
so if you happen to know
how to stop Death,
it would be really great
if you told us.
You can't cheat Death.
- There are no escapes.
- Bullshit.
You told me Death
has a distinct design.
But Alex and I cheated Death,
not once but dozens of times.
The design is flawed,
it can be beaten.
Such fire in you now.
People are always
most alive
just before they die.
Don't you think?
Look, please...
if you know of anything
that could help us,
what harm could it do?
Only new life
can defeat Death.
What the hell
does that mean?
Some people say there's a balance
to everything.
For every life
there's a death,
and for every death
there is a life.
But the introduction of life
that was not meant to be,
that can
invalidate the list,
force Death
to start anew.
You have to follow
the signs...
Kimberly.
How do you know my name?
- Whoa!
- Wait a second.
'New life defeats death'?
'Follow the signs'?
Where did you
find that guy?
I thought he was supposed
to help us,
not freak us out.
What the fuck
are you thinking?!
I'm thinking suck on my junk,
bee-atch.
Little punk.
What is it?
What did you see?
You have to tell us,
what did you see?
Kimberly, look at me!
You have to tell us.
What did you see?!
I was driving a white van.
I don't know,
I must have lost control,
because I crashed
into a lake.
- And I drowned.
- You were there?
I can practically taste
the water in my mouth.
Wait, remember, the on-ramp?
There was a pregnant woman
in a white delivery van.
He said only new life
can defeat death.
If she gives birth
to a baby
that would've died
in that car crash...
a brand new soul that was never part
of Death's design...
It throws the whole list
out of whack
and we start over
with a clean slate.
- It seems like a reach, don't you think?
- What else could it mean?
We have to find
the pregnant lady's number.
I don't have it.
She never came to the station.
We have to warn her about the lake
so she can stay alive to have the baby.
- That'll be an easy conversation to have.
- How are we gonna find her?
There could be thousands
of white vans in the state.
Hey!
I'm a cop, remember?
Wait, that's it.
Got it.
With the plate number
I can put out an APB.
Here we go.
The vehicle
is a delivery van
registered to Marcus
and Isabella Hudson.
We should pick them up
pretty quickly.
Come on, let's get
to the meeting.
Hey, hold the door!
Hey, let go of my shoe!
Give me my shoe!
I wrote to management two weeks ago
about these friggin' bumpers.
Is that dogshit, dude?
Eww.
Oh, you got something
on your...
It's still there, bro'.
Here, I can get it for you.
No, it's alright.
I'll do it
if you want me to do it.
Just let... I'll...
Let me do it.
What?
Hey, man,
how you doing?
Listen, any word
on that white van yet?
Okay, keep checking.
Does anybody have a Valium?
Oh, yeah.
Here.
You're just going to want to take
half of that.
Keep 'em coming.
If what you're saying is true,
that means I'm next.
This is crazy, people, come on.
First Death
is stalking us,
and now premonitions?
What?
You're not next, Nora.
Nobody has to be next.
That's the point.
We need to help each other
in order to get through this.
This cannot be happening.
See, because my career
is at a peak
and I finally met
a quality guy.
I just bought a house.
Maybe if you shut the fuck up,
you'll live.
Like I'm going
to take advice from you.
Okay, look,
if you know what to look for,
you have a fighting chance.
If I call and say,
I don't know... subway...
Get to a high-rise fast.
A place where no subway
could ever possibly go.
Get it?
Okay, you guys, listen...
just because Kimberly
has these visions,
it doesn't mean
we're not all capable
of seeing signs
to some extent.
Okay, okay, look.
I gotta call bullshit.
I mean, I've sat here
and listened
to all your theories
and all your stories,
and I think it's just
all bullshit.
Call it what you want!
- It'll keep your arse alive.
- Darlin', my arse is alive!
Has been all day.
There is nobody after us
but you,
trying to make us all crazy.
I should have seen that coming.
Yeah.
If Death is out to get you,
why don't you get
the hell away from us?
She's the only one that's
dealt with this before.
We need to look out
for each other from now on.
Sleep in shifts.
We need to safe-proof
this death-trap.
Get you to step out
of the van, miss?
Are you kidding me?
- What did I do?
- This vehicle's been reported stolen.
Ohh!
Screw this.
I'm going for a smoke.
No, no, no,
it's not safe out there.
So, Nora's got
to bite it before me anyhow, huh?
Oh, you people have
no sense of humour.
Nora, you okay?
Four years ago
my husband died.
Now Tim.
There's nothing left for me.
Don't say that, okay?
If it is my time to go
and be in heaven...
with my family,
I can accept that.
You got to trust me.
We can fight this.
If we just stick
together long enough
for her
to have her baby...
If you'll excuse me,
I have a funeral to plan.
Nora.
What do you think
you're doing?
- I'm finished. I'm out.
- Don't leave, Eugene.
Look, look.
I control my life, alright?
Not some crazy list that
Death has put together.
I'll be sure to carve
that into your tombstone.
Whatever. You may be able
to scare these people,
- I'm not buying that shit.
- Be careful, man.
- Hey.
- What?
Even if you don't believe,
give this to Nora.
I'm just going
to put this in the...
closet.
Sorry.
Whoa.
Man with hooks?
Man with hooks.
Hey, I think I see
a man with hooks.
Is that...
- a sign?
- Oh my God.
- Do you guys see that?
- He's right.
- The phone.
- Shit.
What the fuck?
- Hello?
- Nora!
- Who is this?
- Can you hear me?!
Officer Burke,
I can't...
I can't hear you!
What?!
What does he...
A man with hooks
is going to kill you.
- What, what?
- Oh...
What is it, Nora?
No!
- Wait, wait!
- Let go!
Wait, wait, Nora!
- Get me out of here!
- Will you stop it?!
Let me help!
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Kat!
Help me!
- Wait!
- I don't want to die!
Aah!
Let me out of here.
I got it, thanks.
They found the van.
Isabella's being held at
the Greenwood Lake sheriff's station.
I'm in control of my life!
- Kiss my arse!
- Eugene, what is it?
- I control my life!
- What happened, Eugene?
- You hear me, you Reaper cocksucker?!
- Calm down.
- What happened? Where's Nora?
- Back the fuck up!
- Whoa, whoa, okay!
Eugene, what's wrong?
Just tell us what happened.
Alright, give me
the gun, Eugene.
- Give me the gun.
- No! Fuck no!
Eugene, you just got
to relax, bro', okay?
You just got
to calm down, man.
Give me the gun.
Give me the gun, Eugene!
- No, no, no, no!
- Don't do it! Don't do it!
- I ain't going out like that.
- Hey, Eugene, no!
- On my terms!
- Oh my God!
You hear me!
God!
Oh!
You don't keep it loaded?
- Maybe they're all duds.
- Six in a row?
Never.
That's impossible.
It wasn't his turn to die.
Can we find
the pregnant woman, now, please?
Is this safe, guys?
I mean, someone in this car
is about to get whacked.
Do the rest of us really feel
like sitting next to him?
Or her?
Hopefully her.
Okay, guys,
let's not panic.
- Isabella's safe.
- How do you know?
You said she was going
to drive into a lake.
How can she if she's
in protective custody?
Look at me.
Come on.
Does it look like
I'm in the condition
to commit grand theft auto?
This is insane.
Look, hopefully
the district judge
will have it all sorted out
by Monday morning, okay?
Marcus.
Marcus, Marcus.
When I get out of here,
I am going to sue his...
- Oh my God.
- What, what now?
My water just broke.
- What?
- My water, it just broke.
- I'm gonna have my baby.
- No, not here.
- No, you can't do this to me.
- Don't just stand there!
- Get me to a hospital!
- Give me a second to think!
I am not going to have my baby
in a jail cell!
Get me to the hospital!
Okay, okay!
Sheriff Perry,
this is Deputy Adams, come back.
God, I need the car!
Sheriff Perry, I need the car!
My van! My van!
Take my van!
Okay. Okay.
Yeah, we'll go.
We'll go.
Come on,
come on!
Y'all want to hear
something crazy?
It's not the first time
I cheated Death.
A kid came to school
with a knife...
killed his teacher.
Teacher would have
been me,
but I was transferred to another
school two days before.
That's fucking weird, man.
You want weird?
Last year my partner and I
were heading out
when a call came in
about a train wreck.
Frank decided
to let me handle it alone.
He died that night
in a shootout.
If that call had come in
just 10 seconds later,
I'd be dead, too.
Oh my God.
I'm sorry.
It's just I got one, too.
Okay, so last May
I'm supposed to go and stay
at this cheesy little
bed and breakfast in Pennsylvania.
Anyhow, there's this major gas leak
that no one knows about,
and all the guests suffocated
during the night.
So what happened?
I don't know.
I never made it.
The bus I was on splattered
some girl all over the road.
Was that in Mt Abraham?
Yes. How did you know?
That bus you were on killed
Terry Chaney.
She was supposed to die
on Flight 180.
Hey, do you guys remember
that theatre in Paris
that collapsed last year
and killed everybody inside?
Well, I had tickets to go.
But one night I'm in Paris
and I'm just
tripping on acid
and sipping lattes and such.
And then all of a sudden
this dude out of nowhere
just gets whacked
by this falling sign.
- Carter.
- Wait, wait, wait.
The teacher I replaced,
her name was Val Lewton.
She was from Mt Abraham.
She died in an explosion.
Shit. The call about
the train wreck
that saved my life...
that was the night
I scraped up Billy Hitchcock.
Wait a minute.
Who are these people?
The people who got off
of Flight 180.
They were my friends.
Kimberly,
tell us what happened.
About a year ago my mum and I
were at the mall.
I was supposed
to meet her outside,
but I got caught up watching
this news report
about some kid
that committed suicide.
I kept thinking,
'How can you strangle yourself
in the bathtub?
That's stupid.'
It felt wrong.
And yet...
I heard some gunshots
and I ran outside.
Some kids were trying
to steal my mum's car.
She tried to fight them off,
she was a fighter,
and they killed her.
After the funeral I kept thinking that
it should have been me.
I guess everyone must
think that.
But I guess I was right.
Get there.
Could you drive a little faster maybe?!
- I'm going as fast as I can.
- God!
When we got off
Flight 180,
it didn't just change
our lives.
It affected everyone
and everything
we've come
into contact with since.
I'm not sure
I'm understanding you.
Being alive after
we were supposed to die,
it caused an outward ripple.
A rift in Death's design.
So if you had never
gotten off the plane...
we wouldn't be alive
in the first place.
Yes, that's why Death
is working backwards!
It's tying up
all the loose ends,
Sealing the rift once
and for all.
Oh, shit!
Jesus Christ!
Hang on! Hang on!
- Is everybody alright?
- Oh God.
God, Eugene!
- He can't breathe.
- Oh, my legs!
No, please.
- It's not going to wait.
- I got to go help those people.
Do you want to deliver
this baby?
Those people can help.
Let's go.
Officer Adams reporting
a vehicle collision
off 9-A
at the 180 mile-marker.
Send all emergency vehicles
to the scene.
- We have to go. Go!
- Okay, okay, okay!
Just... okay, okay!
We're going! We're going!
- Easy, easy.
- Here, here, here.
I think he has
a collapsed lung.
- Everyone okay?
- Call an ambulance!
Stay with us.
Hey, hey you!
Hey! Come on.
Help me out.
You got to get me out of here before
this thing explodes or something, okay?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org