- Shanghai's a mess, don't go there
- My mother's sick, I must
Mitsuko, please wait here
Do you have any rooms?
Of course, please come in
They have a room, come on
No Japanese allowed here!
She's my wife.
Please give us a room
- Isn't that Chen Zhen?
- Yes, of Jingwu Mun
He's a lecher and a traitor
You'd better leave! You're ruining
my business, please go!
Chen Zhen, we'd better go
GRAVE OF HUO YUEN-JIA
- What's wrong?
- A mouse!
A mouse! In there!
A mouse?
- Where is it?
- It was over there, honestly!
Well, it's gone now
You should expect to find mice here
But this one was horrible,
it really upset me
They were here first,
it's probably us who upset them
I suppose you're right
I feel bad,
making you live in a place like this
It's a wonderful place
The view is lovely,
it's much better than any hotel
I wish I could take you
to a place where nobody knows us
And give up Jingwu Mun?
Jingwu Mun has given me up
It was a heavy burden.
I feel much happier
That's not like you
Why?
You're lying to yourself.
You feel empty without Jingwu Mun
You can't live without it!
Chen Zhen's lying to himself.
Mitsuko knows him better than that
Do you?
Tea, Uncle Nong
Thank you.
Have you eaten yet?
I've lost my appetite
Ting isn't home yet?
It can't be easy from him.
He's never lost a fight before
And what's worse,
he lost to Chen Zhen
He's a man of his word.
He'll never act as Head Master
If he doesn't, who will?
No outsider can run Jingwu Mun
If Ting resigns,
who will inherit the school?
Who's been teaching the others?
Cheung and Biu
If we were challenged now,
what would happen?
I got a letter from my mother.
She says Jingwu Mun offended the...
...Japanese and I should go back home
And? Are you leaving?
I don't know what to do
Well, it's still British territory
The Japs have to behave
You Chinese,
always stuffing yourselves...
...like pigs
What is it?
I want to see your Head Master
Who are you to summon him?
Speak to me instead
The Head Master of our clan,
Master Funakoshi,
is challenging your Head Master
What shall we do?
- We must find Master Ting
- Or Chen Zhen
Let a traitor fight a Japanese?
- Stop saying that, do you hear?
- He is a traitor, isn't he?
Stop it.
Arguing won't solve the problem
You, go and find Master Ting
Uncle Gun
Cheung
- Where is Master Ting?
- How would I know?
What is it?
Stop acting! How's my son?
We'll talk about it later
You promised to release my son
if I poisoned Huo
It's not that easy
Your son's a convicted murderer.
They can't just let him go
But you promised me!
I promised nothing,
the Japanese did
His wife says that...
...my son was killed in jail long ago
It's too late to regret it now,
anyway
Besides, you did get $1000.
You had no qualms...
...about taking the money
And as the Japanese promised
to release your son,
you can relax
You said the drug wouldn't kill him
Had I known, I'd have chosen
to let my son die instead
Help!
Uncle Gun has killed himself!
Help me, quick!
We must take him down, quickly!
We found this under his bed
What is it?
It's crocodile jerky,
brought in by a friend of Ting
It's a drug, a cure for asthma
Hey!
Listen!
Only Master Huo ate it
So we can assume that Gun
used it to administer the poison...
...and committed suicide
out of remorse
The deed's been done.
Let's keep this to ourselves
It could damage
Jingwu Mun's reputation
Your school is already doomed
Chen Zhen left, Ting's disappeared
I'd say you should put your school
in order quickly
To think it's come to this
Master Huo's memory
deserves better
Captain, what are we to do now?
You're on duty today.
Why ask me?
Couldn't you help me, captain?
Take the stuff for analysis
Please help me find Ting
I will, don't worry
Are you looking for someone, miss?
May I ask if Master Nong is here?
Yes, he's in.
Please follow us
Uncle,
this lady's looking for you
Who are you, miss?
Ting is staying with me
and won't leave
- You are the only person he'll listen to
- Where do you live?
- The Dizzy Star
- The brothel?
How long have you known Ting?
Two years
He must've spent a fortune on you
It isn't like that
Don't take it wrong.
Ting isn't as bad as you think
He cares deeply about
the good of Jingwu Mun
He even hopes to honour his
father by enhancing its name
He really does
You must help him!
Help Master!
Let go of me, I want to fight!
Let me fight!
Master
Sing, Biu, let's go home
Why have you all come here?
Is anything wrong at Jingwu Mun?
The Nijiguchi have challenged us.
I came to discuss it with you
What about Chen Zhen?
Letting Chen Zhen fight will
damage our name
You are the Head Master
Forget him!
Let's go back
Wait!
I'm coming with you
Are you up to it?
Even if I lose, I won't let anyone
look down on Jingwu Mun
Wait, hold on
What about this lady?
Are you going to leave her here?
Have you no shame?
- Sing, find the madam
- Yes
I want you to release this lady
Xian-hong,
won't you miss your lovely clothes?
I'm so grateful
you let me dress like you
This one's too small.
We'll get your size tomorrow
I've checked it out
Funakoshi is the top warrior
of the Black Dragon Clan
But he's getting old,
so don't worry
Uncle Nong, Ting...
She looks really nice
From now on we'll use
your real name, So-Ian, alright?
I wish you'd treated Mitsuko
the same way
It's not the same.
She's Japanese
Ting, it's only ten days to
the challenge. You must train hard
- Thanks. Come on, Biu
- Coming!
You really care for Ting
I treat them all the same
Is Ting the best in Kung Fu?
Yes
And Chen Zhen?
He's good too.
They're about the same
Are you alright?
- Are you feeling OK?
- I'm fine
Let's get on with it
What's wrong with him?
His heart isn't in it
Master Funakoshi, I've challenged
Jingwu Mun on your behalf
Let's be clear about one thing:
Whatever Funakoshi does
and whoever he challenges...
...is not the military's business
Let me remind you that
the Black Dragon Clan in China...
...is financed and supported
by the military
It makes no difference
Feel free to withdraw your support
I wonder whether your chairman
would agree with you
Don't use Mr. Oshima
to put pressure on me
I'm a martial arts master
Not a politician
- Up so early?
- Good morning
Uncle!
Hello, Uncle!
Mitsuko, why did you choose
to live out here?
I should've hired a horse
Did my father send you?
I haven't seen your father for ages
So why did you come?
Because of him
Chen Zhen?
Are you two married?
No...
But you're living together?
Married or not, neither the Chinese
nor the Japanese will accept us
It's lucky you're not married
If he dies...
you won't be a widow
What did you say?
If you die, I promise
to return your ashes to Japan
Young man...
You're very confident
You're going to fight?
Why didn't you tell me?
Men don't need to tell
women everything
Come on, Chen Zhen
How do you prepare
your most powerful attack?
I focus all my body's energy
on one point and then strike
Yes, that was very powerful
But I've rarely seen a stone fight back.
Your opponents are moving human beings
Theories are easy.
Shall we try action?
What is the most powerful defence?
Attack!
Why waste time on defence
when you can attack?
Attack as fast as possible
So that's the Huo secret:
simply attack?
Don't you know the basic rule?
Attack alone is wasted energy,
defence alone cannot strike back.
One is useless without the other
What kind of master are you?
Your teacher failed to
teach you another rule:
Anger is the fighter's
greatest failing
That's how you lose your advantage,
young man
My master didn't talk so much.
Ready to fight?
Stop!
Wait!
At my age, I need to warm up
- What fist is this?
- Don't ask. If it wins, it's a good one
Are your eyes alright?
I'm fine
I won't take advantage
Enough!
Are you alright?
It must be a great burden
to be young and so talented
You have a young man's energy
You Chinese have a saying:
"All fists fear the strength
of youth"
It makes a lot of sense
But I've lost!
I adapted myself to your style
Chinese martial arts put
the emphasis on personal fitness,
not on winning the fight
Actually, I was taken aback
by your performance
The goal is to defeat the opponent
Listen, the best way...
...to beat your opponent...
...is to use a gun
The aim of martial arts
is to teach you to maximise your energy
And to achieve that, you must be...
...at one with life and the universe
I must be off.
Take care
You're ending the fight?
Fights are for animals
Our match ended in a draw
But I can't vouch
for all Japanese warriors
Some are far more powerful than me
Aren't you the best in Japan,
Uncle?
To say Master Funakoshi's
the best is to speak of his wisdom,
not his killing skills
Master Huo Yuen, you've won
I didn't expect you to
have such a good disciple
The best Nijiguchi warrior,
the one they call Fujita Gou,
the Killing Machine, is waiting
Take care, young man
Check!
I've won!
You've improved your skills
in Chinese chess
Too bad one can't control life
as easily...
...as pieces on a board.
Sun Yat Sen was a loyal friend
of the Black Dragon Clan.
But our society has changed
Just like the military
Both want to conquer China
Conquer China?
Those idiots in the military
are dreaming
But they're not
The Japanese army in China
is almost as big
as the entire country's force
Then Japan's like a strong ant
Determined to consume
a sleeping elephant
As long as the elephant is asleep,
the ant has some advantage
But once the elephant awakens,
the ant doesn't have a chance in hell
True, but I think
that the elephant is still asleep
And there's more than
one ant ogling it
But it will wake up!
No doubt.
Too bad that most Japanese
wouldn't agree with you
For the past decades...
...Japan has benefited greatly
from winning wars
There are too many people who see
Japan's future as a great empire
People like General Fujita
If this is true...
...then war is unavoidable!
Chen, you're back!
How are you?
- Can I see Chen Zhen?
- He's out...
Please sit down
Some tea, perhaps?
Thank you
So you can speak Chinese now?
Yes, a little
You speak very well
Chen, Mr. Huo's here to see you
What have you been doing
with yourself?
I got a job in the village
- So you've abandoned Jingwu Mun?
- That's irrelevant
I may not live in Jingwu Mun,
but I can still be of use to you
Jingwu Mun needs you to come back
Even Xian-hong is there with me
The one from The Dizzy Star?
You must meet her
Congratulations!
You can bring Mitsuko with you
They may have accepted Xian-hong,
but never Mitsuko
She's Japanese
She's done so much for you.
She's a nice girl
What would outsiders think?
If she stays in Jingwu Mun,
its reputation will suffer
I can't be so selfish
I've learned a new fist
- What is it?
- Let me show you
- It's like the Huo Fist
- Yes
It's the Huo Minchung Fist
The Master said
only a Huo could learn it
The Minchung Fist is only
one of many altered by my father
Chen, promise me
I fight at Nijiguchi tomorrow.
If anything happens to me,
Swear you'll teach this
style to the others
Forgive me,
but I've decided to go home
Some things in life...
...are more important than love
With me out of the way,
you will achieve far more
When the Japanese forces
leave China and return to Japan,
I'll be waiting for you in Kyoto
I want only Lun with me
Ting, I'm worried
Shouldn't you take more people?
The Japanese will think we're afraid
if there're too many of us
Right
Wait for me here
Xiao-wei,
please look after So-Ian
Let's go
Ting
I speak Japanese.
May I go with you?
Let's go
They're together,
now nothing can go wrong!
General, Master Funakoshi
left Shanghai early this morning
That stubborn old fool!
By refusing to cooperate,
he's become an enemy of the army
- Notify Tokyo
- Yes, sir!
Should we cancel the match
between Nijiguchi and Jingwu Mun?
No, we don't need
to rely on the Black Dragon
I'll take care of this match myself
Yes, sir!
Great! You're both here
Master Huo, I've good news for you.
I've found your father's murderer
Enter!
Your man here has been bribed
He poisoned the food that
killed your father
He's a traitor
Don't get excited.
Take the body out!
Let no one in till I say so
Fall out!
SICK MAN OF ASIA
If you lose, you get this sign which
I've written especially for you
Catch!
- Can you walk?
- Yes
Stop!
Halt!
General Fujita has been killed
Don't move or I shoot!
Don't move!
- Are you alright?
- I'm fine
You have jurisdiction on British territory
only. You have no authority here
We're not here as policemen.
We're Chinese
We demand you hand Chen Zhen
and Ting over to us
What? You think you can
just walk out of here?
Let's see who hits the floor first
Stop!
Both sides, hold your fire!
I believe we can settle this matter
without a bloodbath
This man doesn't deserve to have
any more lives sacrificed for him
- Lieutenant!
- Yes, sir!
Take your patrol and retreat
But...
I'm the highest authority here
- Are you disobeying my order?
- No, sir!
Attention! Fall out!
Captain Jie
A Japanese General has been killed
I must inform my government
of the murderer's identity
Or the military will never rest
until it's satisfied
So, me escaping
would be their excuse to start a war
Right. I'll sacrifice myself
Good man, you're a true hero!
- Open up!
- Let us in!
Move Back!
There's nothing to see here!
Chen Zhen is dead!
By order
of Shanghai Municipal court
As of 28th October 1927,
Jingwu Mun will be closed down
Why do the British always let
the Japanese dictate everything?
They're in it together.
They join forces...
...to oppress us
All they do is oppress us!
Chen Zhen was a true hero
He thrashed all the Japanese
in the Nijiguchi School
It was fantastic!
Too bad he died so young
- What's wrong Uncle?
- Nothing, nothing. Let's keep talking...
It's hard to believe
Cheung was the traitor
At least in death,
he acted as Chen Zhen's corpse
- Chen Zhen, where to now?
- Which province has Japan taken?
- Tungshan
- Tungshan then!
Jingwu Mun did not vanish afterwards
Besides within the Chinese provinces,
Jingwu Mun even expanded to the Nang Yeung area