I'm gonna play it again.
You play that thing one more time,
I'm gonna melt it down into hair spray.
Let me play
the other side then.
No, Rayette,
it's not a question of sides.
It's a question
of musical integrity.
Then let me sing one for ya.
When there's a...
Hold it, hold it.
- Oh, Bobby!
- What?
Quit that now.
You said you're gonna help me
pick a song.
- I did?
- I'm gonna cut off your damn water.
I swear.
Selfish.
You can play on the piano.
Your whole damn family can play
some type of musical instrument.
All I'm askin' is for you
to help me improve my musical talent.
And you'd think you would.
Dipesto, why don't you
take that sign off your tit...
and you and me go out
and have us a real good time.
Where are we going?
I don't know, but I'll holler up
to Elton and Stoney.
Bobby, now listen a minute.
You know, I'II go out with you...
or I'll stay in with you...
or I'll do anything
that you'd like for me to do...
if you would tell me
that you love me.
You can sing the song.
You are never satisfied.
That's right.
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
All right, here it is.
They were all set up right for ya.
Get right in there, Dipesto.
- Just relax.
- Come on, Rayette.
Watch that left foot.
Left foot forward.
Not too much of a match,
is it, Elton?
In the gutter.
Isn't that wonderful?
Too heavy for me, honey.
The pins, you know. I can't see them.
I can't make 'em out.
Squint. I squint.
There they are at the end
of these little boards.
You notice 'em leading down,
just spot and follow through.
But there's so many.
- What's that for?
- That's for luck.
- Oh, you're crazy.
- Go show Ray how to do it.
- You slobbered on me.
- It ain't the first time.
Watch this.
There she is. She's doin'
a little variation on the Apache Shift.
I taught her that.
- Are you mad at me?
- No, I'm not mad at ya, honey.
It'll be all right.
- Look at me and tell me you're not mad.
- I'm not mad at you.
- Let's see you beat it.
- I'll show you how it gets done.
Don't talk about it. Do it.
Isn't he pretty?
Show me something.
Give me spirit. Give me something.
That stupid thing
just goes all cocky-wobbly, honey.
- Just do what I tell ya.
- I did, didn't I, EI?
You got another ball coming.
- Come on!
- Relax, Ray. That's all.
Attaboy!
That was real good, wasn't it?
I finally did it.
Great. You throw the big Zs
for 19 frames...
and then you throw a strike
on the last ball of a losin' game.
Just wonderful.
Wasn't that wonderful, ladies?
- Are you talking to us?
- Wonderful.
I guess I'll go wait in the car.
Why don't you go wait in the car?
I will.
I'll wait there right now.
One minute, honey,
and I'll go with you.
Me and Stoney got to get on home,
relieve the sitter.
Why don't you and Ray
just come on by the place?
All right, why don't you go on?
Here, I'll take care
of the beers.
And would you walk Rayette
with ya?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
- What do we owe you?
- Four dollars, sir.
Okay.
- Here's a five. Thanks very much.
- Thank you.
We've been wanting to ask you.
You're on the TV, aren't ya?
Am I?
She says you're the guy
that sells all the cars on TV.
I might have sold a few cars.
I told ya! My name's Shirley,
but they call me Betty.
Her name's Twinky.
- Twinky?
- Yeah, 'cause she's so Twinky.
Boy, oh, boy.
Well, Betty and Twinky...
it sure is nice
talking to you girls.
I wish I had some more time.
- That's a wig you wear, isn't it?
- Me?
Yeah, I told her it was you,
but that you're wearing a wig...
'cause on TV,
you're mostly all bald up there.
Your friend's real, real sharp.
I don't wear the wig on TV...
because if you're gonna be in front of
two and a half million people...
you've got to be sincere.
I mean, I like to wear it when I'm in
bowling alleys and slipping around.
I think it gives me a little class.
What do you think?
Yeah, but I can see
a little bit of the net up there.
That's what give it away.
A little net.
I wish I had more time
to talk to you girls...
but I have to...
I'Il...
Come on, Ray.
We're gonna go over to Elton's.
I'm not.
You're just gonna sit here?
Yes.
Okay, I hope
no one hits on you.
I hope they do.
Okay.
See you later.
No one would want to hit on you.
You look too pathetic.
Come on, Dipesto.
We can still have a good time.
You're the pathetic one,
not me.
I'm going over to Elton's.
I am not a piece of crap.
I'm sorry.
You treat me like I was.
Go slip around
right before my face...
in front of Elton and Stoney
that way.
What do you imagine they think
of somebody you treat like that?
Now, now, Ray.
Sweetheart, Elton and Stoney know
that I love you.
They're just gonna think that I'm not
too nice a guy, which I'm not...
and that you're a real hell of
a good person for puttin' up with me.
That's all.
Just find me dead one time.
You'll just kill me.
Come on, be a good girl.
If you ever really get up
and leave me...
you'll read about it
in the newsprint.
I'm not gonna get up
and leave you.
Now, come on.
Let's go over to Elton's
and have a good time.
You love me, Bobby?
What do you think?
Fuck.
You got banana on your face.
I do?
I still ain't figured out
how you got me workin' back out here.
I got you to work out here?
I ain't figured out how you let me
get you to work on these rigs.
I've never worked on these before.
You've worked on 'em before.
I can't figure out
how you let me get us out here.
Somebody had to look out for ya.
You're a mess.
You're crazy.
- I'm gonna bet two dollars right off.
- I'm in.
I think you're bullshitting me.
- What have you got?
- Pair of nines.
- Can you beat two pair?
- There's three aces right there.
I got me a hand.
It's time for me to go home.
See you in the mornin'.
See you in the morning.
I don't know if I'm goin' out there
tomorrow at all.
I got a lot of money
tied up in everything I've got.
I don't want no chains
going around and all this.
It's all right,
but I prefer cardplaying.
Where is it? What the hell is going on
in the middle of this game?
People talking and all.
We got money here or what?
Ride a cockhorse
to Banbury Cross
To Banbury Cross
we go
When I was four...
just four years old...
I went to my mother...
and I said,
"What's this hole in my chin?"
I saw this dimple in my chin
and didn't know what it was.
Get what my mother says.
She says, "When you're born,
you go on an assembly line past God.
If He likes you,
He says, 'You cute little thing'...
and you get dimples there.
If He doesn't like you,
He goes, 'Go away."'
So, about six months later,
my mother caught me saying my prayers.
I was going, "Now I lay me
down to sleep."
Mother says, "What are you
covering up your chin for?"
And I said, "Because if I cover up
the hole, maybe He'll listen to me."
I look unfit to you, Elton?
I'm fit!
If you haven't got your ticket yet
you'd better order it
He'll wet your carpet
and he'll fertilize your grass
He's got three white feet
and a hole in his ass
Don't you know no songs
about women or nothin'?
Yeah, but I'm just too loaded
to think of 'em now.
Watch out for all this traffic.
- Oh, God.
- I ain't in no hurry.
Believe starting off your day
like this, going to work?
Unbelievable.
Let me have a drink, will ya?
Thanks, EI.
Oh, boy, that's tough
in the morning.
What the hell
are these people doing here?
Isn't this some goddamn thing?
Jesus Christ!
I can't stand this goddamn freeway.
I heard ya! Why don't you
flash your lights...
so we can see
what else you got for Christmas?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where you going?
Why don't we all line up
like a goddamn bunch of ants...
in the most beautiful part
of the day!
Hey, get off my car.
0h, shit. What's he doing?
Play it!
Quit foolin' around!
Come on!
Bobby, he's turning!
Will you hold your horses?
I was with Elton
last night, Rayette.
It's the truth.
You son of a bitch.
Natalie, be quiet.
Come on, reach for it.
Come on. Good girl.
- Isn't he sweet?
- I can't see the set.
You take him for a while.
Go ahead now.
How ya doin'?
You ought to get yourself
one of them little things.
That's it. He crushed that one too.
Then I won't get any.
Bless my soul.
It's a new harmonica.
- That's for your birthday.
- My birthday?
How do you know when my birthday is?
I don't know myself.
The kitchen's on fire, Stoney.
Your mother's just died.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
- See ya, Elton.
So long.
Incidentally,
what's his name?
You just love that little baby,
don't you?
Well, what if she was?
I can't see nothing
so bad in that.
Well, what if I were to let you in
on a little secret that she is?
That's right.
She told me.
She's all torn up about it, too,
which I hate to see.
Isn't it something
you just have to face up to?
I'll tell ya, somewhere along the line,
you even get to likin' the whole idea.
When Stoney first give me the news,
I could've shit.
Well, isn't that nice?
It's ridiculous.
I'm listening to some cracker asshole
who lives in a trailer park...
compare his life to mine.
Keep on telling me about the good life,
because it makes me puke.
If you're saying you're something
better than I am, that's something else.
But I can't say much of someone...
who could leave a woman
in a situation like this...
and feel easy about it.
That's all I have to say.
I'm glad that's all
you got to say...
because I'm about
as goddamn tired of your mouth...
as I am working
on the goddamn job!
Shit ass!
Hey, Longcipher!
I'm quitting.
Do you hear me?
I said I'm quitting.
I don't give a damn
what you do.
I'm glad to get rid
of both of you dumb guys.
Hey, what's going on?
Don't do that, Bob.
Don't mix in.
They've got the right, Bob.
It's the law.
Don't you think
you could just leave him?
If he had known who you were,
he wouldn't have done that. Would you?
What the hell's going on?
All right, let him go.
What's going on?
I got accused of robbing
a filling station. Didn't I tell ya?
I just got wild
and jumped my bail.
They come runnin' at me a whole year
later. Isn't that something?
Tell Stoney for me, ya hear?
Hi. Miss Dupea?
- Upstairs. Up those stairs.
- Thank you.
There she goes again.
My one-year-old can carry a tune
better than that.
Miss Dupea.
- Miss Dupea.
- Yes?
I'd like to remind you again
that this is not an opera...
or a musical comedy.
Sorry. Was I singing again?
If you want to call it that.
Wait. You have simply to tell me.
That's all.
That's exactly
what I am doing again.
Must you let me get two thirds
of the way through the movement?
- This is tiring me.
- I have another suggestion.
- Why don't we take a break?
- For pity's sake.
- Is she gonna cry again?
- I don't wanna take a break.
Some coffee. What would you like
in your coffee, Miss Dupea?
- Tea.
- One tea.
Tell her Bobby's here.
Bobby's here.
Oh, my goodness!
Robert Eroica.
I can't look at you.
Well, don't, then.
You always do this to me.
I don't mean to.
Here's your tea, Tita.
Thank you.
Don't put it there.
Why? What's wrong?
This is a very special CB 275.
No kidding.
It has absolutely
no objectionable idiosyncrasies.
I have to talk seriously to you.
Everybody still living
up on the island?
Well, at the moment,
there's really just...
Daddy, Carl and myself,
and Van Oost.
- Who's Van Oost?
- Catherine.
She's a pianist.
She's working with Carl.
Carl's a fiddler.
What's he doing coaching piano?
Well, eleven months ago...
he was on his bicycle on his way
to the post office in the village...
and he ran straight into a jeep
and sprained his neck.
Strained his neck?
That's not funny.
He permanently sprained his neck.
Since then, it's been extremely painful
for him to tuck the violin...
Crashes into a jeep
and totals his neck.
I have to tell you.
Daddy's very ill.
- What?
- He's had two strokes.
He's not...
They feel, maybe,
he might not recover from it.
Don't tell me about this.
But don't you think it's right
that you should see him at least once?
- Miss Dupea.
- Just a minute, please.
Don't you think it's right
you should see him?
Yeah, I guess so.
I'm going back up tonight.
Will you come with me?
I'd rather drive up.
Maybe I'll go
into Canada after.
I'm not gonna stay long.
One week at the most.
I know.
Well...
Come on.
I'll walk you out.
I'll be back
in two minutes.
We've had our break, Miss Dupea.
- They hate me, I feel.
- Maybe you better stay.
I want to talk to you
about so many things.
I'll be seeing you
in a couple of days.
I'm so glad.
Me too.
Bye.
Hello?
You got the day off?
Are you sick?
Guess you heard
about Elton.
Okay, I got your point.
I hope you didn't strain yourself...
getting in here
before I hit the back door.
I have to go home.
My father's sick.
I'll be gone
for two or three weeks.
You'll be gone period.
I'll try and call you
from up there.
Come on, Dipesto.
I never told you
it would work out to anything.
Did I?
I'll send you some money.
That's all I can do.
I'II try and call you
from up there.
Bye, Ray.
You wanna go with me?
There's been hot spells
and cold spells ever since we've met
I've seen your big fires
your small fires
But I won't give up yet
Oh, someday you'll yearn
'Cause your heart's gonna burn
For that old familiar glow
You'll be first
- Like it?
- I love it.
You'll be burned out
or smoked out
And come back to me
I know
- What the hell are they doing?
- Is that an accident?
Who was driving?
You were driving!
What's going on?
Rotate, mack!
Look at my car.
I just bought it brand-new from a used
car lot, and the steering goes to pot.
- You're lucky nobody was hurt.
- Can you give us a lift?
Come on, Terry!
We got a ride!
You're gonna give those people
a lift?
- I can't just leave them here.
- I'd like to punch that son of a bitch.
Jesus. What a rude person.
- What's your name?
- Palm Apodaca.
- Terry Grouse.
What?
How far are you going?
Washington.
We'll get off in Washington.
We'll hook a ride.
- Where are you going?
- Alaska.
Alaska?
What, are you on vacation?
She wants to live there
because it's cleaner.
Cleaner?
Cleaner than what?
You don't have to tell everybody.
Soon, they'll all go,
and it won't be so clean.
What makes you think it's cleaner?
I saw a picture of it.
Alaska's very clean.
It appeared to look
very white to me.
Don't you think?
Yep. That was before
the big thaw.
Before the what?
I had to leave this place because
I got depressed seeing all the crap.
The thing is,
they're making more crap.
They got so many stores
and stuff and junk full of crap.
- I can't believe it.
- Who?
Who?
Man, that's who.
Pretty soon, there won't be
any room for man.
They're selling more crap that
people buy than you can imagine.
Crap.
I believe everybody should have
a big hole...
where they throw the stuff in
and burn it.
They'd never find a hole
big enough. Never.
Take me. Look at me.
When I was just one person,
before I was with Bobby...
I was collecting onto me more garbage
every day...
till I was gettin' to thinkin'
that I should get a disposal.
Disposal?
What's that, but more crap?
I've never seen such crap.
- Mass production is what does it.
- Mass? You're not that clean either.
Wait. I'm not that neat,
but I am clean.
You're not that bad.
But some people.
People's homes, just filth.
I've been in people's homes...
In my personal observation,
more people are neat than clean.
I don't see that.
I'm seeing more filth.
A lot of filth.
What they need to do every day,
no, once in a while...
is do a cockroach thing
where they spray the homes.
Imagine if their doors
were painted a pretty color...
and they had a pot outside.
- Yeah, could be adorable.
- And they picked up.
Then it wouldn't be filthy
with Coke bottles and whiskey and...
those signs everywhere,
they should be erased!
All those signs selling you crap
and more crap and more crap.
I don't know.
I don't even want to talk about it.
- Well...
- It's just filthy. People are filthy.
I think that's the biggest thing
that's wrong with people.
They'd be less violent
if they were clean...
because then they wouldn't have
anybody to pick on.
Dirt.
Not dirt. See, dirt isn't bad.
It's filth. Filth is bad.
That's what starts maggots
and riots.
Follow that truck.
They know the best places to stop.
- That's an old maid's tale.
- Bullshit.
0nly truck drivers know
the best places to stop.
Salesman and cops are.
If you'd ever waitressed, honey,
you'd know.
- Don't call me honey, mack.
- Don't call me mack, honey.
I wouldn't be a waitress.
They're nasty and full of crap.
You just hold on to your tongue.
Hold on to this.
If you think you can talk to me
like that...
Shut up, all of ya!
I'd like a plain omelet.
No potatoes.
Tomatoes instead.
A cup of coffee
and wheat toast.
No substitutions.
What do you mean?
You don't have any tomatoes?
Only what's on the menu. You can have
number two, a plain omelet.
It comes with fries and rolls.
I know, but it's not
what I want.
- Make up your mind.
- Wait.
I have made up my mind.
I'd like a plain omelet.
No potatoes on the plate.
A cup of coffee and a side order
of wheat toast.
I'm sorry, we don't have
any side orders of toast.
I'II give you an English muffin
or a coffee roll.
No side orders of toast?
You make sandwiches, don't you?
Would you like to talk
to the manager?
- Hey, mack.
- Shut up.
You've got bread
and a toaster of some kind?
I don't make the rules.
I'll make it
as easy for you as I can.
I'd like a plain omelet and
a chicken salad sandwich on wheat toast.
No mayonnaise, no butter, no lettuce,
and a cup of coffee.
A number two.
A chicken sal san.
Hold the butter, the lettuce
and the mayonnaise.
And a cup of coffee.
Anything else?
Yeah, now all you have to do is
hold the chicken, bring me the toast...
give me a check
for a chicken salad sandwich...
and you haven't broken
any rules.
You want me
to hold the chicken, huh?
I want you to hold it
between your knees.
See that sign?