Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I'm done discussing this.
Well, I'm not done.
Katy found Flicka.
She should decide.
Until you're running
this ranch,
I'll make the decisions
around here!
I don't want to run your ranch!
- NELL: Howard!
- No, I'm sick of this place!
You know what,
I've given it a lot of thought,
and guess what?
I'm never gonna be
a rancher. Never.
I want to go to college.
(Flicka kicking trailer)
Wh-Why didn't you say anything?
'Cause this is what
you wanted me to do.
Katy wants this ranch.
I don't want
any part of it.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
(kicking frantically)
(snorting)
Norbert... take your horse.
Hope to see you folks
at the fairground.
No! Please! No!
- Please!
- NORBERT: Let's move it.
Gus!
(Flicka snorting and kicking)
Flicka!
(neighing frantically)
No!
Stop! Stop!
(singing continues)
(ends)
(sniffles)
KATY:
The stories we hear
about how the West was won
are all lies.
The history of the West
was written by the horse.
Wherever a settler
left his footprint,
there was a hoofprint
beside it.
Men came further and further
west to stake their claim
in the great
American wilderness.
But they encountered a strength
that couldn"t be tamed.
Wild horses.
Mustangs.
The settlers
called them parasites
that would strip the land
and starve their own herds.
They couldn"t domesticate them,
so they destroyed them.
Isolated and hungry,
they were on their way
to disappearing
from the face of the earth.
Sometimes
when the light disappears,
an afterimage remains,
just for a moment.
Mustangs are an afterimage
of the West,
no better than ghosts,
hardly there at all.
No one really wants them,
not ranchers, not city people.
That"s their destiny.
Let them disappear
once and for all,
along with all
the other misfits, loners
and relics of a wilderness
no one cares about anymore.
Lucky for us,
a few mustangs survived,
hidden away in the mountains.
We need to protect them,
for they are the hope
for some kind ofliving memory
of what the promise of America
used to be...
and could be again.
Whoa.
Don't say anything.
Just get on.
Come on.
When the kids were little,
I'd tuck 'em in
and say, "I'll love you
till the mountains tumble down."
Right now, I feel like
they could blow away
at any second.
Before Dad died,
he asked me if I wanted
to sell the ranch and...
take the money.
I said, "Over my dead body.
No way, no how."
I thought that's what
he wanted me to say.
But, no, he... he seemed
almost disappointed.
He... he said he felt
like that he was giving me
something that didn't
make any sense anymore.
Maybe he's right.
But then I...
I see these kids,
they're hanging out
in the mall,
they're sullen,
they're lazy.
Got no ambition,
got no dreams.
This is the only
way that I know
how to save our children.
Honey, Howard
doesn't need saving.
He'll be fine
wherever he goes.
But Katy, honey,
we could lose her.
She's... smart and she's strong,
but she can't survive out there.
Our daughter lives
in a fantasyland.
So do you.
Look at you, sitting on top
of cowboy mountain
looking down at the world
passing by.
When are you gonna look
at your daughter
and realize that she's you?
And that's why
I love her so much.
They want to go
to the rodeo, you know?
She wants to see Flicka.
Yeah.
They expect me to say no.
Yep.
I bet I'd really blow
their minds if I said yes.
Then they'd see how diabolical
I can really be.
You are such a bad boy.
I love it.
Race me back?
Let's go. Come on.
Come on, Belle.
- Last one back's naked first.
- (Nell laughs)
Hyah!
(Nell whooping)
I'm gonna win!
Yeah, right!
Gotcha!
(Nell laughing)
(exhales)
Want to go swimming?
No, thanks.
It's a thousand degrees
in here.
I'm busy.
You really want to go swimming.
What's he gonna say?
Well, that's his problem.
I'm gonna go see
if the coast is clear.
Mom!
Nobody's home.
Let's go.
Are you sure about this?
Hey, we'll be back
before anybody even knows.
Come on.
I'm hot.
Are you hot?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah!
- (squealing)
- (woman singing alternative rock)
KATY:
Miranda?
Close your eyes, cowgirl!
(yelling and laughing)
(ends)
KATY:
What's going on?
Well, somebody tell me.
Miranda saw Flicka.
Where?
At the fairgrounds when I
was practicing the course.
How did she look?
What?
I've never, ever
been scared around horses,
not in my entire life,
but those horses
that she was with...
What?
Don't stop. Tell me.
You'd really have to work hard
to make horses that angry.
HOWARD:
Listen, I'm sorry, Katy.
I just thought
you'd want to hear.
MI RANDA:
The cowboys in that race are crazy.
But they say the purse
is over $8,000.
HOWARD:
Oh, money's no good if you're dead.
(gasps):
I can win that race.
My demented sister is even
more demented than I thought.
Riders get to choose
their horses, right?
MI RANDA:
Yeah.
I choose Flicka, I win.
If you can stay on her.
I can.
You're too young to enter.
You're not.
Bad idea.
Brilliant idea.
If I buy Flicka back
with the prize money,
she won't be Dad's horse anymore,
she'll be mine.
And if she wins,
someone'll want her foal.
That's money in my pocket.
And if he tries to sell
our land, I'll buy that, too.
Whoa, whoa, Katy, she is
way too dangerous to ride.
Maybe for you
but not for me.
I only have to stay on her
for a few seconds.
I've already done that.
Miranda?
Oh...
(laughs)
The people have spoken.
No, the inmates have
taken over the asylum.
Come on, let's see you
walk it like you talk it.
Drown me, please.
Hey! Hey!
Whoa! Whoa!
(girls laughing)
Oof! That aftershave'll
scare the livestock.
Oh. But the ladies
find it reassuring.
Yeah, it let's 'em know
I'm sensitive,
not just a... sexy beast.
(both laugh)
Can we get going?
(sniffs)
Oh, Jack, you stink.
Busted.
Let's go! Come on!
HOWARD:
I'm coming!
(engine starts)
Well, what'll it be
tonight, boys,
crazy eights or canasta?
(barks twice)
Canasta it is.
MAN (over P.A. System):
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome
to the Red Gulch Roundup!
(crowd cheering)
Now, for those of you
that may be visiting
our beautiful state
for the first time,
welcome to Wyoming!
In our grand entry today,
our flags are being carried
by Miss Rodeo America
and her lovely assistant.
And all of our beauty
a-horseback.
Now in the center
of the arena is the world
champion trick roper,
Mr. Gene McLaughlin!
They say in every cowboy's life,
he gets a...
good horse, a good woman
and a good loop.
All right, folks,
it's rodeo time,
but it seems that Miss Rodeo
America needs my assistance...
Aw, honey, how could you
eat that stuff?
It makes me sweeter.
You're already sweet.
There she is!
ANNOUNCER:
...the barrel race!
All right, ladies, cowgirl up.
Mm, mm, mm.
Introducing our next
barrel racer, Miranda Koop.
(cheering)
Come on, baby!
ANNOUNCER:
Here she comes around
the first barrel.
Quick.
Another great run.
Coming to the third barrel...
(crowd groans)
Out she goes.
That's okay.
(country music plays)
(man singing country)
Hyah, hyah!
(singing continues)
She's mine, boys.
(squeals)
(laughing)
(ends)
(cheering)
(slow country song begins)
(man singing)
Katy, I'm scared.
I'm not, not even a little.
What do you think?
I think I should be
the voice of reason.
We're runnin' out of time.
Hold on.
(distant music and cheering)
You need gum.
Yeah, okay.
(indistinct voices)
(country music playing)
Wait here.
Here's your receipt.
Good luck to you, partner.
- Thank you, sir.
- You bet.
How you doing, Norbert?
Oh, what you say, Wagner?
- Hey, sweetheart.
- Hiya, Norbert.
Can I help you?
Yeah, uh,
I want to register.
For an event.
(chuckles)
You gonna tell me which one,
or do I have to read your mind?
The wild horse race.
Wild horse race.
That takes a team of two.
Mm-hmm.
That's my partner.
Outside.
That little bitty feller?
(chuckles)
Good luck.
I need $50.
Yes, sir.
Fifty.
Gotta sign this waiver.
Right there.
Report to the corral.
Pick yourself out a hoss.
- WOMAN: Here you are, darling.
- Thank you.
The event rolls at 5:00 p.m. Sharp.
Here's your receipt.
Thank you.
And if you come to your senses
and want to back out...
you lose every penny.
(chuckles)
Good luck.
(horses whinnying)
(neighing)
(gasps)
It's okay, Flicka.
MAN:
Doggone, Billy!
Hey, get outta there,
you lunatic!
You choose your horse
like everybody else,
or you can take a hike!
Do the rules say you can put
a baby cradle on a horse?
- (laughing)
- Quiet down!
All right, gather 'round, boys.
Shout 'em out.
(overlapping shouts)
Fourth team takes
the black filly.
Son, you just lost a race.
That horse is truly loco.
Boys, next time
you see your horse,
it'll be in the ring,
trying to run you over.
MAN:
All right, now.
Good luck!
(neighing)
Ladies and gentlemen,
and cowboys...
the wild horse race
is about to start.
Now, if you've got
a weak heart...
Hey!
- Kick some cowboy ass.
- Thanks.
...or you just ate
a big meal, I suggest you...
Don't you dare get hurt.
Dang! Norbert.
You know what we say to our
first group of riders...
welcome to our...
Do you think he
recognized us?
- I don't know.
- ANNOUNCER: Let's bring 'em in!
Come on.
Now, direct your attention
to the chutes.
That ain't no earthquake
beneath your feet.
That's wild horses
coming at you.
Look at those crazy devils.
They've never been saddled,
never haltered.
Angrier than a cowboy
who just totaled his pickup.
Here's how it works.
In a few moments the horses...
- No way.
- What?
Are you freaking crazy?!
Just try and stop me.
...the boys have gotta grab
'em, saddle 'em,
then ride 'em
between a pair of barrels,
and any rider
that stays on that long...
Your group's up next.
...wins $8,000.
- I'm giving my number back.
- Go ahead.
So, let's bring in
the first set of victims.
(chuckling):
I mean, cowboys.
Team number one, this is
Jimmy Miles and John Bull.
Team number two, the Eggan boys.
Second generation,
Wade and Trace Eggan.
Team number three- Chris Fadey
and Big John Slim.
And this next team of kids,
they are so green,
they've got moss
oozing out of their pores...
- Hi, Norbert. How are you?
- Well, well, well.
Hi, how are you?
Guess you changed your mind
about mustangs, didn't you?
- (chuckles)
- Come again?
Well, you're here
to see your boy
ride that wild horse,
aren't you?
- My boy?
- Howard?
Yeah.
What are you
talking about?
Well, he's up now.
Where is he?
I'm gonna kill him.
- NORBERT: Follow me.
- Where's Miranda?
I don't believe this.
ANNOUNCER:
...the first four teams...
MAN:
Riders, get ready.
HOWARD:
Here we go.
Don't let anybody back out,
boys. Your life's on the line.
Let's go for it.
Ten...
(crowd joining in):
Nine...
eight...
seven...
six...
five... four...
three...
two...
one...
ANNOUNCER:
Aw, let her rip, boys!
Get back, Loretta.
Here they come.
Four of the toughest broncs
you're ever gonna see.
Remember,
one man's gonna give chase;
one's gonna try
to get him saddled.
You see this black filly,
number 14-
she is out of control.
- Get her! Get her!
- Whoa!
That's a bad old girl to have
to deal with in this dance.
Them boys got more
than they bargained for,
taking that horse.
Now this is the height
of insanity-
we've got a man on right here.
Almost on.
(groans)
Oh, my Lord, my mother
could've rode better than that.
Two riders up,
one still unsaddled.
- Heads up, boys!
- (man grunting)
Oh, that is not the recommended
way to dismount a wild horse.
NELL:
This is insane.
ANNOUNCER:
There it is, on the far side.
Take a chance,
put your life on the line.
Dropped him like a two-ton rock,
split him like a $2 suitcase.
He's wide open,
and he is all done.
Flicka!
Boy, I hope one of these guys
wins this thing...
(snorts)
(announcer's voice fades)
Easy, girl.
(whispers):
Hey.
(announcer continuing
indistinctly)
I see Howard.
(panting)
ANNOUNCER:
...the last time we see...
(sighs)
It's Katy.
Oh, my God.
Rob! Rob!
ANNOUNCER:
Lookee here!
Some lunatic just jumped
out of the VI P section.
He's here.
What's he doing
in the middle of the arena?!
- Look!
- I'm an idiot.
He's never gonna
let me keep her.
- Just win.
- It won't make any difference to him.
- He doesn't want either of us.
- Let go!
ANNOUNCER:
Look at that crazy fool, this guy is still at it.
Where is he going?!
What's going on?
Katy, let go.
Ya... come on.
Look a-here,
jumped on bareback.
What in the world is going on?
I'm gonna set you free, girl.
Hyah!
Ladies and gentlemen, number 14...
is gonna be the winner.
ROB:
Katy!
14, folks,
is not stopping at the barrels.
I've never seen anything
like this in my life.
I've been watching this
for 40 years.
So, call the state troopers
in Wyoming.
He's headed for Cheyenne.
I don't think he can stop
that black filly.
(thunder rumbles)
(sobbing gently)
I don't know what to do.
Where do we go, Flicka?
- Nothing you can do.
- (garbled radio transmission)
NELL:
What'd they say?
Can't get a helicopter
here till morning.
Boys lost the trail.
Probably won't be able to pick
it up again till daylight.
- Norbert, gimme a horse.
- Two horses.
Y'all need to calm down.
No, we're not gonna calm down
till we find our daughter.
She'll go home.
No, honey, she can't.
Not in the mountains,
not in the dark.
Not Katy- Flicka.
Hey, our mountains
are her home, too.
You're right.
Let's go.
When we get back to the ranch,
we're riding out.
Weather's coming in.
(thunder rumbling)
(Flicka huffs)
This is our creek, isn't it?
You brought us back.
(relieved sigh)
Thank you, girl.
Let's go home.
Come on.
What is it?
What is it, girl?
(snorts)
What is it, girl? Huh?
(neighing)
It's okay, girl.
It's okay.
Come on.
Come on, it's okay.
- (neighing)
- (yells)
(snarling)
(gasps)
No!
(neighing)
- (snarling)
- (neighing)
Get away from her!
No!
(sobbing):
Flicka!
Oh, my God.
(sobbing)
God! Get up.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Flicka, get up, please.
Get up!
Somebody help me!
(sobbing)
Get up!
Get up, please!
- Hyah! Hyah!
- Let's go.
Hyah!
(thunder rumbling)
JACK:
I'll search the ridge.
GUS:
I'll take the south meadow. Katy!
ROB:
I'm gonna check the creek.
You should go back.
Not a chance.
Katy!
Aah...
Oh!
(grunts):
Katy?
Oh, baby.
It's gonna be okay, baby.
Daddy's got you.
Come on.
Dad... the lion got her.
You're gonna be all right, baby.
(whispers):
It's all right.
(huffs quietly)
Flicka.
(crying)
Is she all right?
(shuddering)
Find Jack.
Go to the creek.
That horse is hurt bad.
NELL:
A hundred and two.
I don't know if it's accurate.
It's an old thermometer.
No.
The doctor can't land
in the storm.
So... no.
So, we'll wait.
(sniffles):
Okay.
What do I look for?
A hundred and five.
Can that be right?
Howard, get some more ice, son.
Flicka!
(neighing)
(singing lullaby)
(singing continues)
(snarling and neighing)
(ends)
Flicka!
What's Katy's shirt
doing around her neck?
She tried to stop
the bleeding.
Oh, she's cut deep.
We ought to take
away her pain.
(thunder rumbles)
You gonna shoot her?
What do you think?
How bad's the horse?
(thunder rumbles)
(sighs)
Go back and put her down.
She'll hear the shot.
She'll think it's thunder.
No, she won't.
Look, Katy's smart.
She sees things...
little details
most people ignore...
the ones that make
a difference.
She'll know it's Flicka.
I can't let that animal suffer.
I'll do it myself.
(thunder crashing)
- Dad?
- Don't.
(voice breaking):
I'm sorry.
I really screwed up.
Look at me.
You're a good man.
Yes, sir.
Now, you stay
with your mother.
Yes, sir.
Are you gonna kill Flicka?
I'm just gonna have
a look at her, baby.
(sobbing)
It's okay, Daddy.
You can shoot us.
(whispers):
Katy!
It's okay, baby.
It's okay.
(thunder rumbling)
Damn!
(echoing gunshot)
(murmured gasp)
Flicka!
(panting)
Shh!
It's okay.
Dang it.
(rain pattering outside)
(thunder rumbling)
(crickets chirping)
(door bangs)
Oh, dear God.
Oh...
Oh, look at her.
It was a lion.
There's no good reason
she's alive.
There's a very good reason
She's got
mustang blood in her.
She's a fighter...
just like our girl.
Don't worry.
The doctors will be
here in the morning.
Let's get her
to the barn.
Come on, sweetie.
Come on, Flicka.
Come on, honey.
(sighs)
The day you were born...
...and they gave you to me...
...I felt my hands were
too rough to hold you.
And you cried
no matter what we did...
...but your mom said
that that was a good sign.
You were strong.
That wasn't much comfort
when I was holding you
and pacing back and forth
all night.
All you did was look at me
with those big, beautiful eyes.
I made all kinds
of promises to you
if you would
just go to sleep.
Katy...
I forgot to keep
those promises...
...and I'm sorry.
Do you forgive me?
I'll tell you every day
how proud I am of you
and how proud I am
that you're my daughter.
Just stay with me...
please.
(kisses)
(sniffles)
(sighs)
(sniffs)
(sniffles)
(sighs)
(keys clacking)
(birds chirping)
(rooster crows)
(woman singing alternative country)
Daddy.
Her fever's broke.
I want to see Flicka.
NELL:
No, it's okay, sweetheart.
Oh, babe...
(sighs)
Katy, can you come downstairs
for a minute?
(crying)
It's my fault Flicka's dead.
(singing continues)
- I don't think so.
Come on outside.
(ends)
(gasps)
Flicka!
Baby!
(sighs)
(whinnies softly)
(whispering):
You're alive.
It's going
to be okay now, okay?
(whinnies)
Aw...
Your mother's been taking
good care of her...
but when you're better,
I expect you to take
care of her yourself.
But you said if I don't get
back into school...
Yes, that's what I said,
and I meant it.
So Dad sent them your essay.
I told them I didn't know much
about writing,
but I sure as heck
know about the West.
So does my daughter,
and it's right there
in her essay-
every opinionated,
ornery, hot-blooded
part of it.
(Flicka whinnies softly)
What did they say?
What does anyone say
to your father?
BOTH:
"Yes, sir."
(laughing)
I love you, Daddy.
I love you, sweetie.
(neighing)
KATY:
I believe there is a force
in this world that lives
beneath the surface...
something primitive and wild
that awakens
when you need an extra push
just to survive...
...like wildflowers that bloom
after a fire turns
the forest black.
Most people are afraid of it
and keep it buried
deep inside themselves.
But there will always be
a few people
who have the courage to love
what is untamed inside us.
One of those men...
...is my father.
(sighs)
KATY:
There was once a time
when Americans came west
to discover their destiny.
Today, they seem to move
around every which where,
restless and unsettled...
but I think they"re still
looking for the same thing-
a place where they can be
optimistic about the future,
a place that helps them to be
who they really want to be...
...where they can feel
that this life makes sense...
...a place where they can feel
what I feel
when I am riding Flicka.
"Cause when we"re riding,
all I feel...
...is free.
(man singing country)
(song fades out)
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org