Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
FLORES IN THE LOFT
the Grandmother's House
Although many years have passed,
since I saw it for it finishes time
I cannot forget
that my first impression
it was of fear and of admiration.
There it would lose my childhood...
...my innocence made serious pieces
...and all our dreams
destroyed...
...for what we would find
there inside.
My mother and father were for my
the center of the Universe when it was young
AND he/she dreamt of becoming bigger
to be the same as my mother.
we were a very united family.
I Remember like we received to Papá
when it returned home...
...after some of their frequent trips
of businesses.
Be already here!
- He/she Calls to Cori and Carrie
- If
- Let us go boys!
- Has dad arrived?
Quick, Already arrive!,
Let us go!
We go, we go.
Agachensen
Bend over Carrie that doesn't see you
Dad!
he/she loved Us to All, but it was
evident that I was their favorite one
Not I want them to become jealous
if he/she waited that they went to the bed.
You spoil me too much.
Tell me if you like.
Notice, it is also an alhajero.
As soon as I saw it I understood
that he/she had to bring it to you.
Mom
As you want him to place the candles?
I put 6 lines of 6
or 3 lines of 12?
Or the 36 candles
around the Cake?
And reason not two lines of 18?
Have not you been happened?
I want to prove the Cake of Papá!
I want to eat up one of the circles!
Allow me to take a bath the Mold!
They are very beautiful both,
but we have to wait...
...to sing him/her all to Papá
Happy Birthday.
And we cannot eat a piece now
tiny, tiny?
Please!
They want him to seem that they have come
the ratoncitos to nibble it?
It was very beautiful if I put
6 lines of 6.
It is Papá!.
Already this here. We go.
NO!
When dad died
He/she suckles it was very sad.
we Had to sell all that we had
to survive.
When we ran out of money
they removed us the house.
we were forced to abandon
the place in which we had been born.
Where all ntros were. memories
and the only home that he/she knew.
Mom said that alone we had
a place to where to go.
And like it is that there were never us
taken to know the Grandparents?.
Simply because there were not
ruined state.
Many years ago I made something
that it displeased the grandfather a lot.
And I punish myself disinheriting me.
Why we go now,
if they won't give us money?
They will give it,
the grandfather you this dying.
He has left very little time of life.
I go resolved to recover
my father's affection.
And then children, I will be able to inherit
a fortune that you/they had never imagined.
And through my, they will be able to carry out
all their dreams.
Mom had to have us prepared
for a thing this way.
For that say it?
It never allowed us to have a dog
or a cat.
And that that has to see?
Simply that the animals die,
Christopher.
And if has had a dog and you us
he/she had died, we would have learned something.
On that,
About the death?
If the death.
The death!
Taenia that to have us said them, taenia
that to tell us that the parents also die.
They die Christopher, although they are Young,
healthy and we need them.
Not I want Christopher to be here,
and neither I want to go to the grandparents' house.
I don't want to have a lot of money, and not
I care them not to be carried out my dreams.
Me alone he/she wanted to continue living at home
and to always have with me potato's memory.
Not I want to walk at night
he/she scares me.
Has not reason sent us a car?
Here there are witches mom Witches and Monsters.
Good Morning John.
Children introduce to John.
He has been with your
grandparents since I have memory.
They are Christopher and Kathy,
and the twins Cori and Carrie.
Charmed of Knowing you John.
Hello mother.
John was in charge of of his baggage Corine,
take you up to the children.
It is 6 in the morning my love,
mom will also sleep.
The children will sleep in one
room, Corine. The girls in another.
But I want domir with Cori mom.
He/she stops to protest Young boy
and listen to me well.
While they are it is this house
they will obey my you order.
Not they will scream, neither they will cry
neither they will form din.
And when their mother and I come out of here...
...we will lock the door.
Mom please understands that they are children!.
Not you can wait that...
The only thing that I wait is that...
...it is that they make what I am instructed.
Listen a moment children, comportensen
odebezcan to their grandmother.
And if they don't give him/her any, but any,
I motivate to punish them.
Please, portensen well
make that they obey, let us make them to think...
...that it is a game
or a wonderful adventure.
Why do you cry mom?
I will return inside a while.
Don't worry, we will be well.
Not it can be so bad, the grandmother not
it should be as bad as he/she wants to look.
Not forget that God the vé everything, God will see
all the bad one that they make to my backs.
And it will punish them.
- Do they know why their mother came?
- Yes to recover their father's affection...
...and that it puts it in the Testament.
And he/she has also told them for that reason
did the grandfather disinherit her?
I want many to go to the bathroom.
Silence!
He/she learns how to control you.
And I don't want you to speak never if I don't make you
a question.
- But it is alone a boy.
- That I have just said?
Their mother has come to this house after 17 years,
to regret their crimes and of all their sins.
Not alone against their grandfather or against my,
but against God.
Their mother's impious fué marriage.
A sacrilege.
An abomination before the eyes of God.
It has not counted them that it made
the but terrible of the sins?
You hurtles to the arms of a man that
it took their veins, the same blood that her.
Not he/she was a stranger, era their own Uncle
and you are the fruit of the Devil's seed.
- Damned from the moment of their conception
- I will look for my mother!
They come here
Sit down.
Don't move again until I leave.
I want that they know a thing, to their grandfather
he/she won't be said that they are here.
He/she will never be said.
The not even knows that they exist,
none of you.
Neither siequiera knows that they have been born.
While the grandfather lives, I swear them that I will avoid him/her
by all possible means that it suffers this shame.
I don't like this here Kathy
I want to return home.
Mom!
Where you have been?
Mom that has spent?
Coríne, I don't want screams
remain silent to your children immediately!
Not leave it!
Non Cori!
Mom tells him/her that she stops!
Corin, if you don't control your children, I will make them whip
until the blood runs for its backs.
They are very not well educated and they have to learn
to obey.
Any boy that alive under this roof
it will disobey me..
Neither he/she will scream, neither it will provoke me!
have they heard me?.
Have they heard me?
And you...
Now take off the blouse daughter.
I want them to see like they are the punishments
in this house.
If you are cruel with my children
I will take them to me this same night.
Take them to you Corín, take them to you right now
I don't care you to make it.
Take off the blouse Coríne.
Take off it!.
Fijensen well children...
...17 lashes one for every year
that he/she lived in sin with their father.
And I want them to know that will give them food
and I roof, but they will never have my affection.
Since it is impossible to feel another thing
that it is not disgust.
For what is not healthy.
- I feel already better.
- If he/she had an antiseptic one.
My young doctor.
The years of happiness that I shared
with their Papá, they are worth for 100 lashes.
The grandmother told us many things mom,
sew horrible
They have mistreated you and the hate hence.
The worst thing has already happened, starting from tomorrow
attempt you to go winning me my Father's affection.
And if you help me, all help me
behaving well as I have told them...
...I will get it.
To the right of the closet there is a secret door,
look for it tomorrow morning
Push it smoothly and he/she will open up,
they will see a narrow stairway that will take them
to such a big Loft that they will get lost there inside.
Make of him a place of games for the twins.
Make of him your special place.
- Will you go to the bathroom?
- No
Did you not even wash your teeth?
Not I have I encourage of making it.
That you say of all this?
That the uncles that marry their nieces.
That they have unsightly children with line.
Your you will be medical,
Do you believe that it can be certain?
We are the test.
In that think?
In Mom.
As soon as it has changed a lot since dad died.
Not it has changed...
this sad one.
We are also he Christopher,
and we are the same ones.
And if the grandmother enters before we wake up
and us vé in the same bed?
- You are not him/her afraid?
- No.
We have also always slept in the same bed.
I made a list of the norms that you/they should complete
while they live in this house.
Read them attentively and record them in their minds.
Take something of food, they won't want
to die there out from hunger.
It is necessary to look for the stairway.
- It is already.
- That you see Christopher?.
From here you don't leave anything.
Alone the stairway.
Are they prepared to ascend?
NOT EVEN!
To their mother he/she is authorized to tell them on the loft
but I want to remind them again...
...that they should never be seen.
My God!
the grandmother's norms were not norms
they were cruel punishments.
we were caught. The only way to feel the sun,
it was alone to travez of a put bars on window.
Our mother taenia that to be despaired to have returned.
we All will pay the price.
The weeks months, the memory were made
of our true house he/she began to vanish...
...however we continued grasped
to our dreams.
Chris dreamt of being medical,
and I wanted to be a dancer.
we were about behaving like a family.
it was the only form of surviving.
Mom was spacing her visits, and one day accent of coming.
we imagined that it had passed him/her something terrible.
OR that he/she had forgotten.
it Seemed that we didn't have any possibility to escape...
...but soon, very soon we would have to find the form...
...of deceiving the grandmother, to go in
it looks for and he/she helps of our mother...
...if we could.
- Do you like this snail?
- I find that this beautiful one, is very beautiful.
- I believe that it seems an orange
- Neither for I appear.
I have never done an orange with tentacles.
Your if?
They are antennas Kathy, non tentacles.
The snails pertecenen to the the family of the mollusks.
They have the soft body, they lack thorn number,
and their tubular intentinos finishes in the mouth
Dear Doctor Christopher,
when Cori and I want information...
...of the snails, we will send him/her a telegram
to wonder it.
That day we will leave out?
- As soon as mom says it.
- But he/she suckles he/she no longer comes but.
If we could leave to the garden we would have flowers
really, herbs really.
And snails really.
- God of it has taken them the whole herb to the sky.
- For that?.
For potato, or they maybe forgot that
did he/she always spend it cutting the grass?
Does reason always have to be in the loft?
Because the house of below it has disappeared.
That is not true Corí
- Mom doesn't come because she doesn't love us
- Not say foolishness.
Huy! It chops me...
He/she suckles it is very bad, we want to see the television...
...we want an ice cream, we want to play with our friends...
...we want to leave to the street.
- Do they want they want to go to the school?
- NO!
Look at me, look at me both, the Bible says
that there is a time for everything.
A time to grow, a time for
to sow a time to harvest...
...and to take an ice cream...
for sure there is also a time.
The time has arrived us of
to sacrifice us... for mom.
We have todala life for before
to live and to have a good time.
Can Kathy happen?
He/she closes the door door for not waking up the twins.
Something could pass mom...
...maybe this it makes sick.
Mom has always been strong
as a horse.
Where this whole time has been?
Why has he/she stopped to come?
I have had other thoughts...
...terrible thoughts.
- That?
- They can have contained it...
...in some place of this great house.
The same as to us.
- For what reason will they contain it?
- To punish her.
That you believe?. If they are totally crazy.
- You scare me...
- I die from fear...
...when I think a little.
- For sure not this contained.
- As these so sure one?
Does it care?
Not we will know the truth until...
...that he/she comes to see us.
Ah If?
- That it is supposed that that means?
- I have a plan.
- Christopher that you believe that these making?
- Don't worry.
Christopher!
You woke up the twins.
Carry, this it is not your bed.
I want to sleep with Cory.
Get up!
Leave the beds!
Not you don't play it!
No! it is dad's gift
NO!
Tell me Christopher, these thinking of the form
of escaping, without the grandfather finds out?
I have been thinking it for weeks, Kathy.
Not I have been able to think of another thing.
Will we be able to make it?.
Christopher, if he/she suckles this here,
we have to find it...
...we have to count him/her.
We will make it... tonight.
Help me Kathy
He/she throws with force.
He/she throws strong...
He/she throws, Kathy throws.
- I will lower with you.
- Neither you think it.
- IF!
Very well, but I will lower first.
Not I want you to put the hands in the rope
until I have arrived below.
Have you understood it?
Yes I have understood it
Have much care
Care!
That?
My God!
It ascends...
Kathy ascends!
Let us go, let us go!
Let us go!
Christopher!
Kathy!
Let Us Go, Christopher!
Date hurry, throw me the rope.
Your you can, single scale!
We Go Christopher.
Mommy...
Does he/she suckle?
He/she is mom
And I have a snail, Kathy has a
I siege to dance beside the window.
I am amazed of seeing them.
I am glad a lot to see the very happy ones that are.
We are happy of seeing you mom
but he are not be here
Why have you been so much time without coming?
We were concerned.
For that reason they did try to escape?
That they made, answer me.
Not we sought to escape mom
alone we wanted to be.
Were not they happened that they would ruin my plan?
Our plan..
Not they do understand what I told them?
- If they continue...
- The twins mom are not well.
They need to leave so that he/she gives them the air.
They need to play with their friends, they need space
free to run, and they need to return to the school.
Very well..
We will make what you/they want.
- We can leave now if they want..
- IF!..
...or we can wait a little
until they read the testament.
Is the grandfather dying?
The doctors say that not
he/she has neither a month of life.
If we leave now we won't have anything.
Not we will have to where to go.
If we stay, we will have
but of what we always wanted.
Forever.
We love you mom.
What is better...
...it is it we will make.
Would Kathy, like me to know that you say?
It will be better than he/she will see the twins.
Don't worry mom.
We will wait a little but.
We will be well.
Don't worry.
I already have it, I already have it!
Christopher has a mascot.
I am oppressed to fake before you Mr.,
because your ne hicistes to your image and likeness.
Christopher comes to see what has happened.
I believe that they have put but grills.
Chris regretted to have
consented to mom's desires...
I found a form of escaping...
...although alone he/she went to a bathroom in my fantasies.
Fantasies of a life full with parties,
friends, and perhaps even loves.
Fantasies that probably,
they would never be made reality.
- Kathy
- If!
Can I speak with you?
That it happens?
Not you will be bothersome with me to have
leaning to mom, truth?
- No, but because you always have
that to agree with her?..
Sinners!
- !Christopher
- That we have made so that he/she calls us sinners?
We are all in the same room,
week after week...
...and he/she doesn't want us to see each other.
You. it put us here. You. I close up us here.
He/she wants to be making
something that this bad.
He/she looks at your black dress, your wonderful jewels
and your face of bitter
We are not you afraid, we laugh at tí
you hear it we laugh, it was, it was, veto!
He/she suckles it didn't let him to happen to us anything.
We will have to block the door
or to hide in the loft.
Not it will ascend there.
So afraid Christopher am.
We will be well. He/she suckles he/she will be in charge of of it...
and me also.
Cori?
- That Christopher happens?
- Cori not you where it is..
Cori!
Where these?
Here it is not, your you look for it over there.
Cori
This here!
Cori, Cori, Awake!
He/she Wakes Up Affection
Fred escaped
I found difficult a lot to find it..
and where this fred?
This here with me.
It will be better than Fred he/she sleeps below.
Kathy!
Kathy
He/she opens the door
Kathy!
You are a sinner
Why does he/she make us this mom?
Mom doesn't know what happens, I am sure
And why doesn't he/she never come?
Kathy will already come..
soon, he/she will already come.
Reason the grandmother not us
has he/she brought the food, today?
Calm Cori will already come.
Perhaps no longer there is but eaten.
Maybe you finishes.
To my he/she gives me same because I am not hungry.
They will already bring it
- Good night John
- Good night Mr.
they didn't give us solar light, neither eaten.
Our faces became but pale
and our bodies but thin.
When the grandmother stopped to feed
small Cori became very sick.
AND you every day he/she left
weakening but and but.
Run him a little.
That you will make?
That you will make!
- Lift him/her the head
- Reason?, that you will make him/her?
There is what I tell you.
I have thought of another form of escaping,
I will attempt it tonight.
If you want to come with me, well.
If I won't leave alone..
See to see that door.
Kathy
It belongs to mom.
It is their room.
Vamonos cannot stay here,
all this will have an explanation.
When we see mom we will ask it to him
and she won't count them
We go, we cannot continue looking.
We go over there.
Is he?
This dead one, Christopher!
That it happens if you see us?
He/she cannot see us
if this dead.
You have always been my favorite Coríne.
Somewhere around.
- Do you continue him/her wanting I eat before?
- Not ask silly questions.
Where he/she wants that this, will be
thinking of us.
When he/she comes to look for us, him
we will understand and everything will make a sense.
- The twins sick Christopher are.
- They will become well.
- Chris...
- Not I don't want to speak but of it
That sick old lunatic won't live for
always Kathy. Pudistes to see that that night.
Not he/she knows who were who were.
Not we can forget the reason for which we came.
All the money of the world is not worth
the life that we are losing.
Non voucher for tí, but mom
without that money he/she doesn't have anything.
He/she has us, if he cared!
We take the twins and ourselves
we go, Christopher!
We have that buarcar an exit
before it is too much afternoon.
And that we will make later that go to
to make to feed them at the four?
Your you don't have any doubt, you don't realize
how much mom has it changed?
Not you realize where she is
taking their ambition for the money?
Non accent of thinking of their room...
He/she is our mother Kathy..
That quires that he/she says?
Alone the truth.
Cori?
I want to vomit Kathy.
- Because these removing the flowers Carrie?
- Because it is already time.
So that?
For the winter.
- Does it hurt your head cori?
- Today not, hurted me yesterday.
- And to the throat?
- A little.
Numbness in the fingers
of the hands and the feet?
That it is numbness?
It is when you don't feel the fingers and
we say that they have been slept.
Sometimes.
Become trained the hands.
- That these making?
- I examine you.
Children, I am already here!
Children, I am very happy...
Kathy that you have made? Very well daughter
these very pretty one with the short hair.
Are they angry with me?. Not they know
as I have missed them.
Wait to see the gifts that he/she buys them.
He/she wanted to warn them when it was leaving, but...
...but guess, guess the
that it has happened!
- Has the grandfather died?
- No.
Have they taken it to a hospital?
Not I am happy because you this dying.
I am happy because the he/she loves me.
Don't they understand it?
I made what I promised them, he has liked I so much
that he/she will give a party for me tonight.
A great party, to show up in society.
And tomorrow he/she has an interview
with their lawyer Wislow, is very nice...
...to include me in their Testament.
He/she has said that he/she will leave everything.
Even this house.
And that it passes with your children mom?
Does he/she know that they exist?
We know perfectly as
he/she feels regarding that.
And that it will belong to us mom?
As much as time will have to live in this prison?
Prison?
You have come with gifts for all us.
Do you believe that that compensates what we are suffering?
Christopher... if you no longer love me...
Not I have stopped to love you mom,
I put under an obligation to love you every day...
...in spite of that faces.
Not say a word but.
Look at us mom!
That aspect has compared with their
blushed cheeks and brilliant eyes!
You have seen as the twins are, to Cori him
the stomach almost hurts every day...
And to Carrie they are leaving him/her stains in the skin.
You have idea or at least you worry about the but
minimum that the grandmother accent of feeding...
...does he/she make but of one week?
- Already coarse!
Not you are entitled any of speaking to me in that way.
You accuse me of being well
when my children were bad.
You are unjust.
When they are able to be affectionate with me..
...I will return.
That these making?
I will lower, I want to see like it is the party.
Do you come with me?
Because they are not orderly and dresses?
They already know that during the day I don't like
that they are with the clothes of sleeping.
Cori this sick person
It is very bad
A Doctor Needs.
Because you stay there still?
Cori needs to go to a Hospital.
Not there is another decision that to take.
Can one know that devils spend, mother?
You stayed stop there...
...thinking of tí and in your money,
is seeing as Cori dying?
Is it that you don't care what happens him/her?
Have you forgotten that you are their Mother?
Always you...
Kathy!
That you rot in the hell but you take to the one
Hospital to Cori at this time.
You believe that you will be able to continue making that that
do want with us without nobody finds out?
If Cori dies Mother you will pay it very expensive.
You will pay it in a way or another
I will make you to pay it.
I promise you that you will pay it.
He/she enters.
It takes to the boy below and he/she brings the car to the door,
my daughter will take it to the hospital.
Hello John.
Don't worry Fred..
It will return
Cori had pneumonia
The doctors have made what you/they have been able to
Not there will be funeral
We have already buried him.
Nó!
Not I know that it passes Fred, Christopher.
He/she has not wakened up.
Poisoning for arsenic.
In the sugar of the cookies.
In small quantities he/she doesn't have flavor neither scent.
It is very difficult of detecting.
If they had made him/her the autopsy
has not discovered it.
Unless has suspicions.
That we will make?
Tonight I will lower...
...I will look for some money...
...or a couple of rings of brilliant of
those that the grandmother takes.
And later what?
Then we will leave Kathy
Not I know to where, but we will leave.
What happens later...
... it will depend on us...
...but in any event...
...we will be free.
- Is it really necessary to wait until tomorrow?
- Yes
- Not I know if I will be able to.
- You should.
Which the difference is in 12 hours?
The difference between a ring and two.
Damned you are!
That it has happened?
We will leave tomorrow.
- Have you found an exit?
- If!
- Where a window?
- Nó, a door. The main door.
That!
For tomorrow they are preparing another party.
I have seen as they fixed one of the living rooms.
They will probably have about 100 companies.
He/she can that but.
Not they will have to have the closed door
with that quantity of people entering.
That it has passed Christopher below?
That but you have seen?
Your you have told me that we are us
against them and that we are alone.
Don't lie me Christopher.
Not it is alone a party, Kathy.
It is a wedding.
Mom you vá to marry that man tomorrow.
Nó Chris!
I am afraid Christopher
Not you have reason to have it
already nobody will be able to make us I damage.
- Somewhere around
- Nó Chris
Not we can allow that you goes out with his.
We have to count the truth to the grandfather.
We can no longer care it. Vámonos
Mom cannot keep the heréncia later
of what has made with us.
We go, quick.
Not it is
Kathy has died.
That very now we can already be with Mom.
Non Carrie
Mom lied us
He/she said that he/she would come to look for us when
dies the grandfather...
...but it never returned.
Alone he/she worries about her, Carrie.
It will ruin it everything.
Not we can wait but.
But he/she is their mother.
And those they are their friends.
And it is my wedding.
We will begin the ceremony, now.
Today is April 23.
Christopher that that is?
Grandfather's Testament
For 2 months.
He/she says that if it is demonstrated that mom had children...
...of their previous marriage...
...still after their death...
...it will be disinherited.
Mom agreed for
that they never found us.
Not he/she planned to never take us out of the Loft.
My very Dear Relatives and friends...
...we are here gathered in this day
cheerful and jubilant...
...to gather Corine and Val in Sacred Marriage.
Let us pray...
Celestial Father..
In him Genesis is spoken of the Creation
Your dijistes that was not good that
the man is alone
and for it creastes to the woman...
...giving your blessing of the Sacred Marriage
It Protects Mister to Val and Corine...
...and grant them your grace.
Grant him/her the force and the serenity
so that they honor the votes that end up...
...of making before us.
We request you that in your infinite kindness
bless their home...
...fill them of healthy and happy children.
For our Christ Mr....
...Amen
Mother!
Do you like my dress?
I found appropriate for this occasion.
- Who you are?
- As they have entered?
Have you maybe forgotten that we exist?
Mom
Who children are?
We are the girlfriend's children.
That foolishness, you know very well that
I don't have children.
That they take them to him of here
Not I will allow that some
evil and cruel children...
...ruin my wedding.
Your you are the evil and cruel, mother!
Us tuvistes locked in the loft and dijistes
that you would come to look for us
when your father died.
But never vinistes.
Not you could leave that nobody
he/she found us...
...because but you would be disinherited.
Not it is certain
Nó
Can you prove what you say?
He/she died... eating the same cookies that Cori.
Who Cori is?
He/she was your son, our small brother
and the matastes.
In the same way that intentastes
to kill us.
You look at us Mother
As you have been able to make us this?!
Have Mother. The gift of your children's Weddings!
Leave
Eat up it
Cómete the Cookie!
we are Able to carry out our vengeance.
AND we are able to make it alone.
I found a work and I helped
to Christopher to pay their studies.
small Carrie became bigger...
...but their health always delicate fué.
With the time I danced again.
we Leave our past behind...
...but we could never forget to Mom...
...to the grandmother...
...and that Loft.
I sometimes wonder
if the grandmother will even live...
...I imagine it precidiendo the Mansion
and waiting our return.
SUBTITULADO FOR
JERG
Synchronized and corrected
by Federico Petit
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org