Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Oh. Hmm.
Oh. Oh.
I`m up!
- Ah.
- Phillip, it`s 7:00. Are you awake?
Up and ready for a new day.
- Oh!
- Oh what a beautiful morning
Oh what a beautiful day
- I can`t find my socks.
- They`re in your shoes.
- Where are my shoes?
- They`re on your feet.
Thank you.
Thank you, Weber.
Hi.
- Have you seen the paper this morning?
- Oh, yes, I did.
You know, if I could solve
this whole metastable compound business,
I could save the college.
A new energy source
would be worth a fortune.
You better hurry up. The loan`s due
at the end of the school year.
Not to worry, Weebo.
I`m very close.
May I see my schedule, please?
Ahhhh. After school
there`s something.
I know there is. What is it?
- This is your complete schedule.
- Hmm. Let`s see.
Unless you didn`t
tell me something.
What is it? There`s something.
There`s something there.
What is it? Oh.
It`s something to do with white.
Oh, what is it? I know it`s
something important. I know it!
Well, I don`t know. I`m sorry.
I know it`s so frustrating, isn`t it?
I just hate that.
I wish I could help you.
- But I can`t.
- Haircut!
Ha! Hmm!
They can`t just
close down the school.
Outside of the lvy League,
name me one private college...
or university that isn`t
in financial trouble.
Oh, all right. Name another.
- You don`t think it`s too much?
- No. It`s elegant.
And it`s a wonderful idea to go
with the big wedding this time.
It does put the pressure
on the professor to show up.
If he forgets this time,
that`s it.
Well, in his case,
once is justifiable...
and twice is understandable,
but three times--
Coming through!
Morning-- or afternoon,
whatever the case may be.
We have a lot to talk about today,
so let`s get into it without delay.
Oh! Oh, uh, thank you,
whoever gave me the plate of fruit...
and the dead pheasant,
but it does not count
as extra credit.
Last time we were talking about
Newton`s Law of Gravitation.
To review: We see this "G"
is like the "C" in E=MC squared.
It`s a constant, constant universe,
as much as anything
is constant in the universe.
It`s saying that the force of
attraction between two bodies...
is in direct proportion to
the product of their masses...
and in inverse proportion to the square
of the distance between them.
An example would be-- Let`s make, uh,
naked man, "M-1." Naked lady, "M-2."
Now, according to this formula,
their attractive forces...
would want to close
the distance to zero.
Why don`t they? Hmm?
The Earth! Ah.
So, in essence that is
gravity and this...
is "Dr Richards Life Drawing."
It`s not my class, is it?
Phillip! Over here!
Sara! Ooh! Very sorry.
And so, momentum.
May I sit here? Thank you.
Hello, Sara.
What a pleasant surprise.
- Hello, Ruthie.
- Martha.
- Martha what?
- Martha. Me Martha.
You Martha. Me professor.
- Yes, I know.
- I was just gonna, you know,
grade my lunch, eat a few tests
and hope for the best.
- How do you hold it in?
- Well, like everybody else, Ruthie.
I just cross my legs real tight.
No. I was talking
about your excitement.
- Excitement?
- The wedding.
Congratulations!
The wedding! Sara and l.
Oh, the wedding.
Oh, l`m looking forward to it.
Aren`t you, honey?
- It`s today.
- Are you sure?
- The wedding is today. Okay?
- I believe you.
6:30 at the Presbyterian Church
on Beach Street.
- I`ve been there.
- We had our rehearsal there last night.
That`s right, we did!
It went well?
- Yes, it did, but it doesn`t count.
- Good.
- No?
- The wedding counts,
and I want you to promise me...
on everything between us
that you`ll be there, okay?
I`d rather die
than disappoint you.
Well, this is going to be
the very last time I try to marry you.
I imagine so.
I know that I love you,
but l`m not sure
that you can love me.
That`s ridiculous.
I love you with all my heart.
With every cell, with every
molecule, with every atom.
I love you on a subatomic level.
Hmm! Prove it to me
tonight at 6:30.
Prove what, honey?
- That you love me.
- I love you.
- 6:30.
- Good luck.
Thank you, Betty.
I knew I shouldn`t
have come, but--
Oh, l`m very crazy about him,
you see, Miss French.
And this is the God`s truth:
I want him to have
what he wants,
even if it means
you instead of me.
No, no! You love him.
Don`t give him up.
Hey! l`m watching something!
- Weber!
- Why don`t you be quiet?
I`m watching TV.
Download some manners! Ohh!
Oh, but he ain`t in love
with me, Miss French.
Mmm. Tell me about it.
Hello, Phil.
What are you working on?
Can`t remember?
I understand.
It`s a damn shame they`re
shutting your college down.
I read about it in the paper.
- It`s not over yet.
- Oh, we`re doing fine at Rutland.
No such financial problems. Hey!
Are you still working on
that lighter-than-air compound?
It`s a, uh,
propulsive polymer and--
I don`t mean to be rude,
Wilson, but l-- I have to go.
You don`t seem too happy
to see me, Phil.
- I`m not.
- Well--
All the years we`ve known
each other, studying, working together.
- What happened between us, Phil?
- Well, I just got tired of you
stealing my ideas, Wilson.
And what would you have done with them?
You would have misplaced them,
forgotten them, lost them.
There`s no doubt you`re
the brighter of the two of us.
You have a genius for science.
I grant you that.
It`s just the science
of daily life that eludes you.
I`ve heard that copper psych
before. Excuse me. That`s very volatile.
I won`t deny that I hate you
for your brilliance.
I`m petty, corrupt.
I probably would have gone mad trying
to compete with you in pure thought.
But, uh, l`m not
an innovator like you, Phil.
I`m an adapter, and to that end,
I have profited from your ideas.
- Why are you here?
- Well, to be honest,
I`m here this weekend
to steal your fiancee...
and make her my wife.
Well, I think you`ll be
sadly disappointed.
I`ll see you
at the wedding then.
Eh, it`s a little crooked.
- Yeah. There you go.
- Weebo?
- Mm-hmm?
- The wedding was not on my schedule.
- Mm, no?
- Why was that information deleted?
Hmm. I don`t really know.
- Do you have another virus?
- You know, now that you mention it,
- I am feeling a little feverish.
- Really?
Mm-hmm.
You are a little hot. Say "ah."
- Ah.
Ah!
Oh, yes!
Hot. Cold. Hot. That`s it.
The hydrocarbons have been
inhibiting the cooper pairs.
But if you go from hot
to cold very quickly,
you get a conductive polymer
and you complete the metastable sphere.
Behold! There it is.
Now it`ll work. Yes!
But, uh, w-what about
your wedding?
Sorry, Sara.
Should I call the church
and tell them you`ll be late?
Very good. Right.
Very good. Ah.
Flowing from the condenser
to the pressure reactor.
Yes.
Yes! Oh! lt`s ready.
Organic catalyst.
The positive...
and the negative.
Little touch of electricity.
- Hmm.
Oh!
Wow. What a bang.
Yeah. Little touch
of electricity.
That`s not helpful.
Oh.
Mmm. Mmm.
- Oh, boy. This is not good.
- No, sir.
- Weebo?
- What?
- Get a broom.
- That`ll help.
Two years.
Wow.
Oh.
Oh, bless you. You have a cold.
You should.
It`s 77 degrees Kelvin.
That`s very cold.
Look. Come on.
All right, uh,
let`s try and describe you.
Uh, you`re an elastomer.
Yes, uh, um--
Ooh! You`re highly viscous.
But yet you can
phase-shift. Hoo!
Well, uh, let`s see.
You`re mouldable. Oh.
It`s a little ticklish.
Oh!
You`re foldable.
You`re gullible.
Oh. All right. Let`s see.
Oh, wait a minute. Okay. And--
Ooh. You`re ductile.
Oh! Oh. You`re elastic.
Let`s just see
how elastic you are. Okay.
I`m the hackeysack king.
Hoo!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey, hey!
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Bravo! Encore!
- Oh, boy. Uh, Weebo?
- Yes, sir?
- Take a picture.
- Okay. Look this way. Smile!
Yeow!
Ow!
- Weebo! lt`s amazing!
- Professor? Excuse me.
- It`s miraculous! lt`s--
- Professor, it`s gone!
It is! Oh! Oh!
Professor, I think you gave it
a little too much free will.
Oh, no.
There`s not a darn thing
to be afraid of, pal.
How can anything
get in your window?
It`s closed, okay?
Whoa!
Hey! Huh?
Oh! Huh!
- Whoa-oh!
- Yeah!
Ha!
Mmm! Whoa, Weebo! I got it!
Great. Now what are you
gonna do with it?
Oh! It has incredible inertia.
Mm, maybe it`s
just glad to see you.
- Weebo?
- Yes?
- Do you know what this is?
- Flying rubber?
Yes. That`s what it is.
It`s flying rubber.
It`s flubber!
Ouch.
- Thank you for waiting so long.
- Yes, ma`am.
I`m sorry, Sara.
Are you going to tell me,
"l told you so"?
No, no.
- I`m going to give you a ride home.
- Thank you.
There you are.
Careful. Watch your gown.
I`ve got it. Thank you.
It`s perfectly safe, Weebo. It`s just
an ordinary radioactive isotope...
that Weber is now removing
from the lead containment unit.
Very good, Weber.
Then you place
the radioactive isotope...
carefully behind
the sliding shutter.
You see, the sliding shutter
works just like a camera.
It regulates the flow
of gamma radiation.
Instead of billions of random particles,
you have a precise stream of energy.
Now we carefully place
the sliding shutter mechanism...
underneath the flubber.
And l`m burning up in here!
Weebo!
Over here.
The gamma radiation triggers a
metastable decay in the flubber itself.
- Right.
- Which releases enormous
quantities of energy,
- and that`s what propels the flubber.
- Of course.
Now doing it this way,
I believe, is a lot more scientific...
than dropping it
or kicking it...
or bombarding it
with light bulb photon flashes.
- Absolutely.
- I believe...
by controlling
the gamma radiation flux,
we can control the movement
of the flubber itself.
- Cross your fingers, Weebo.
- Here`s hoping!
- Good luck.
Oh, yes!
It works!
Descent, gradually.
Back up again. Yeah!
My wedding. Oh!
- I`ve gotta go, Weebo.
- But you haven`t finished
the experiment yet.
You`re just getting started.
You can`t just stop in the middle.
The wedding. Oh, I can`t
miss this one, Weebo.
I`m aware of the time.
Thank you.
But your days are wrong.
I`m getting married Friday, 6:30 p.m.
- No. No, you`re not.
- Why not?
Because you`re not
getting married, Phillip.
- Yes, I am.
- You missed the wedding.
It`s 6:30 in the morning.
No. No.
Yes. I`m sorry.
- It is?
- Yeah.
Sara.
Sara?
You have a lot of nerve
to show your face around here...
after what you did to me
last night.
Will you please let me explain?
No. There`s nothing to explain.
You weren`t there.
For the third time you left me
standing at the altar.
I`m sorry with all my heart.
But please listen to me, Sara.
Please. You know me.
You know how sometimes I can get
really fixated on an idea?
- I don`t want to hear it.
- Sara, you`ve got to hear it.
Sara, this is the reason
I didn`t make it last night.
It`s flubber.
Flubber! lt`s a metastable
compound, Sara.
In layman`s terms, if you apply
a small amount of energy,
it liberates an enormous
quantity of energy.
But the total effect
is transient, Sara.
The moment you stop applying energy,
it returns to a quasi-plasmoid state.
- Isn`t it remarkable, Sara?
- What`s remarkable, Phillip,
is that I ever fell
in love with you.
You broke my heart...
so that you could stay home
and make some green goo.
Sara, it`s much more than that.
Flubber could save this college.
Let me demonstrate.
- No, no, no.
- Just give me one minute, okay?
The flubber is placed
in my back pocket.
When I exit this window,
I will fall to the ground.
When I hit the ground, the flubber will
send me right back up unharmed. Watch.
- Ta-ta, my love.
- Are you nuts?
- I`ll be right back.
- Phillip!
Ah!
- Ouch.
- Phillip, are you hurt?
Just my pride.
Well, if you think that
you are going to get my sympathy,
you are wasting your time.
Ooh! We are finished!
Sara.
Oh!
Junior`s home.
Dad? Dad!
Dad?
Somebody in your organization
screwed up big time.
I got thrown off
the basketball team.
I flunked chemistry.
I`m on, uh, academic probation.
- How did this happen?
- I`m supposed to get A`s.
- At least, that`s what I was told.
- The only reason...
I loaned this "jerknut"
college money...
was so he could get straight A`s
and go to Harvard Business School.
- This isn`t supposed to happen.
- Yes, sir.
We talked to the, uh, that Brainard guy,
the chemistry professor.
Now, either he did not
understand us, or he forgot.
The-The boy knew we were having
persuasion problems, sir.
I have a science requirement,
you morons!
Quiet.
We`ll have to get the "F"
changed to an "A."
It won`t work. This guy? He
doesn`t live in the real world.
- He has principles.
- Get something on him...
that we can use to force him
to change the kid`s grade.
When a man says he has
principles, what he means is...
he can`t be bought cheap.
Hmm. Hmm.
Adding 500 milligrams...
crystallized flubber
to common hand cream.
Stirring in solution.
Hmm.
Hmm. I just need one
spherical test subject.
Mm. Perfect.
Yeah. Now, about two--
Applying flubber
in a solution...
externally to golf ball.
All right. Very good.
Evenly over the entire surface.
Kinetic test number one.
Oh. Oh! Oh!
Ooh! Ah!
Are you all right?
All right.
Applying light coating
of flubber...
to surface of bowling ball.
All right.
Oh. Very good.
- Right in the head.
- That golf ball was really moving.
- How`d he do that?
- I don`t know.
Commencing kinetic energy
test number two.
Controlling horizontal momentum.
Commencing now.
Hit the deck!
This definitely has applications
in the field of sports.
Ho, ho, ho! Yes!
Oh!
What?
Fluid flubber...
with a convenient
spray applicator.
It`s clogged. Hmm.
- You seen enough?
- Plenty.
All right, after the bowling
ball hits, we break for the car.
Oh, wait a minute.
You can adjust it.
Go!
Oh, damn! Oh!
- Yes! Weebo?
- Yes, sir?
- It`s gonna work.
- I hope so.
Now, let me show you how.
I connected the accelerator
to a sliding shutter.
If I press down on the accelerator,
it releases the gamma rays,
and that increases the thrust.
Ah. Listen to that baby chirp.
Now, the steering wheel
controls lateral motion.
- Mm-hmm.
- If you turn right,
- Okay.
- it`ll steer right.
- Ah! Turns right.
- Turn the wheel left, it steers left.
So, it functions a lot like
a normal automatic shift...
- with drive, park, neutral, reverse.
- Yes, yes, yes, yes.
- It`s that easy. See, Weebo?
- Professor!
- Weebo?
- Help! Let me out!
- Oh, Weebo!
- Professor!
- Oh!
- What were you doing in there?
- Flirting with the alternator.
- Hope you didn`t touch anything.
It`s not the time to play. We`re about
to make a major breakthrough.
Okay, here we go.
Yeah. I think we`re ready.
- Weebo?
- Yes?
What do you say
we take her for a ride?
- Fly me to the moon!
- That`s it. That`s the spirit.
We`ll fly over to Sara`s house,
park this baby on the roof,
and then maybe she`s
gonna change her tune.
You know, maybe you should
just go without me.
- Why?
- Because I get carsick.
- Oh, come on.
You`re not gonna blow chips.
- No?
- You don`t have a stomach.
- I have a queasy gyro.
Now get over it. This is not
about cars. This is about Sara.
- Now get in here.
- No!
- Now.
- All right.
Oh! We`re fine now.
- Ah! Out into the world.
- Okay, here we go.
Look at this! Let`s see
what this baby will do!
Oh! It works!
- Yes, it does.
- I`m psyched!
Oh, boy.
- You know what this means, Weebo?
- What?
I`ll never have
to buy tyres again.
Ah. Let`s see what`s
on the radio, Weebo.
Ho! Latin!
Bam ba-bum, ba-bum, ba-bum
Bum ba-bum ba-bum
Hey!
Bum-bum be-bum bum
Right turn.
Whoa! Yes!
Huh? Huh? Oh!
Ah! We`re fine.
Whoa! Oh.
- It`s all right. I saw it.
- I don`t think so.
Weebo, there is
nothing to worry about.
Oh-- Mayday!
Come on. Easy.
Oh! Sorry.
First-time flyer. Shh!
I`m very sorry!
Hang on, Weebo!
Oh! Ha, ha, ha! Oh!
Whoa! Oh! Oh, Weebo!
Oh, now, we`re cookin`!
Whoa!
Oh!
Oh! Yes!
Oh, Weebo. Come on up.
Please. You`ve gotta see this.
Wow! ls this
what you call heaven?
Almost. Look at it.
The whole world below
and beyond.
- It`s beautiful.
- The solitude up here.
The stillness.
- The silence.
- Uh-oh.
Silly me turned it off.
Turns right back on.
The shutter`s jammed probably,
Weebo. We`re okay.
Start right up.
Oh, please turn over!
For the love of Newton,
turn over!
Abandon ship!
Oh!
Yes!
It`s such a pleasure
to spend time with you...
without having Brainard
hovering above us.
Mmm.
- More wine?
- No. No, thank you.
I have to say good night.
I have a busy,
busy day tomorrow.
Mmm.
Rutland would die to have you.
We`d be together
with nothing but time.
Sara?
Mmm.
I`m sorry, Wilson.
Forget it. It`s okay.
We have lots of time.
Listen, l`m-l`m driving up
on Thursday to Rutland for the game.
- I`ll see you there.
- Should I make dinner reservations?
Since Rutland is going
to lose, l`ll pay.
All right. If your team wins,
you can buy me dinner.
If your team loses, we go up to
the mountains for the weekend.
- Mmm--
- Cad!
- Do we have a bet?
- I`ll think about it.
I can`t lose. She`s mine!
Sir lsaac.
Out!
All right.
One more time. What happened?
He took a golf ball,
he rubbed this cream on it,
and then the golf ball
took off and...
popped Smith in the head.
- Several times.
- Mm-hmm.
- I got hit with a bowling ball.
- Repeatedly.
- Were you drinking?
- No.
Two beers at dinner.
Wesson had a white wine.
- With dinner.
- Right.
It`s this stuff
he`s got, sir. It`s--
I don`t know what it is. I don`t
know where it comes from, but...
it will give you
one heck of a headache.
Oh, goodness.
I-l wish I could
make you feel better.
Hmm. So do l.
Well, maybe l`m old-fashioned,
but I believe...
a woman should love a man
for what he is,
and not for what
she wants him to be.
Thanks for the
sentiment, Weebo, but...
this is really not an area you`re
qualified to offer perspective on.
Well, I don`t have much of
a smile, but I do have a brain.
I have to deal with this alone.
It`s a human matter,
not for computers.
It`s for people.
- Good night, Weebo.
- Good night, Professor.
Hmm.
- I got it!
- Oh, no!
I gotta turn this thing off.
This is so embarrassing.
Weebo, I just had
this amazing dream!
- Weebo!
- Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry!
Weebo! Weebo!
- Weebo! Wake up!
- Mmm.
- I`ve solved all our problems.
- I`m all ears.
Flubber is going
to the basketball game.
- Basketball?
- Yes!
Testing, testing.
Applying a thin layer
of fluid flubber...
to synthetic leather surface
of basketball.
Application complete.
Wow!
Oops.
Two points.
Implementing plan "B."
Very tight. Tight.
And careful, careful,
careful, careful.
Secondary flubber experiment.
Control elements: bungee cord,
three-to-one elasticity ratio,
fifty-pound ballast.
Commencing now.
Wish me luck.
Oh! Whoa!
Yes!
Ha, ha!
Whoa! I got it!
Oh! Bungee! Bungee!
Oh! Oh!
Uh, help.
Uh, yeow!
It worked!
Yes!
End test.
Did you fully fix the flubber
on each tack before we painted?
Excuse me, Darth Vader,
but what did you say?
Did you fully fix a 15%
flubber solution to each tack
before Weber started painting?
- Yes, l`m positive.
- Excellent.
And how long does it take
the paint to wear off?
- Uh, 30 minutes.
- Be a little suspicious...
if the flubber started
working immediately.
- Uh, isn`t this cheating?
- No, it`s not cheating.
It`s equalizing.
You`ve seen the team. They
should have their own telethon.
Come on! We`ve got
to win this game.
I`ve gotta do it to prove to
Sara that flubber really works.
I`m gonna do it right under
Wilson Croft`s nose.
Don`t fail me.
- Weebo.
- Yes?
- While l`m out, you`re in charge, okay?
- Okay.
- No phone calls to Russia again.
- I think that was Weber.
Oh! Make sure the flubber
stays in the tank.
- Got it.
- Under no circumstances
are you to release it.
- Of course.
- Because you know what would happen.
- Ho, ho, ho.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, sir, I understand.
- Promise?
- Have no fear.
That`s my girl.
Go Medfield!
Okay.
Good evening, everybody,
and welcome to Rutland Arena...
for the 86th meeting of the Rutland
Rangers and the Medfield Squirrels.
Rutland, if they can just
stay awake, should be able...
to steamroll the Squirrels
here tonight at the--
All right, Squirrels,
Iisten up here now.
Okay, Rutland may have us
in height and reach,
weight and power,
agility, speed and talent.
They have the advantage
on offence...
and defence.
Sure, they`re-they`re
better coached,
better trained,
and their will to win is
unmatched in the conference.
They`re undefeated
in their last...
one hundred and eight games.
But that doesn`t mean we can`t
whip these guys. Right?
- Yeah!
- Ohh!
Rutland! Rangers!
Okay, flubber, it`s time
that you and l...
got to know each other.
Ow!
Another easy basket
for the Rutland Rangers.
They have built up a commanding
lead in the first half.
- Evening, Sara.
- Excuse me?
What a coincidence.
Dunk it! Dunk it!
Take it!
Come on, you guys!
You gotta do--
Not now, Ernie! Not now!
Go Medfield!
- Ow!
- Oh, sorry. Sorry, Wilson.
See if you can get me
another ten grand on Rutland.
- You got a problem, Bennett?
- You`re betting against my team?
It`s not your team. They
threw you off, remember that?
Ooh. Oh, baby.
That`s gotta hurt.
He fouled him!
He threw his hip into that!
Flubber? Flubber!
Where are you?
Mambo
Mambo!
Yeah!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Yeah!
Welcome back to Rutland Arena
for half number two.
The Medfield Squirrels tonight
are getting their nuts buried,
trailing by 51 at intermission.
If Coach Barker has any sense,
he has to be thinking forfeiture--
...for half number two.
Come on, boys.
Expect the unexpected.
Dale. Come on now, son.
You can do it.
Come on, Bruce. There we go.
Werner, be a flying squirrel!
Bart, the impossible`s possible.
Come on, Lawrence!
- Rodents rule!
- Loser!
Show time.
Keep going! Open!
Oh!
- Yeah! Get `em!
- Come on!
- Defence, defence!
- That`s pretty good.
Yeah!
Okay! Go! Beat them! Let`s go!
Oh!
- Yes! Yes!
- Gosh! We`ve never--
Yeah! Did you see that?
Did you see that, Dad? Yes!
What the--
We did it!
Wow! Wow!
Hey, are you blind? They`re doin`
something illegal out there.
Coach, nowhere in the rule book does
it say anything about jumpin` too high.
Now sit down!
Looks like a lonely weekend
in the mountains for you, Croft.
Come on, Squirrels!
Yea!
Did you see that, Croft?
Down, down!
Yes!
Yeah, yeah!
A tack.
Oh. Dale!
No!
Dale! Not the tacks!
- I don`t know.
- Okay, now, this game is not over yet.
You just wanna steal the ball
and then score!
Pardon me, boys.
Educator coming through.
Coach, I know very little about
basketball, but I do know chemistry.
And l-l believe that Dale is having
a problem, not with motivations,
but with some sort of adhesive buildup
on the bottom of his shoes.
- Do you have any ethyl alcohol?
- What?
- Excuse me. Hello, Dale.
- Coach.
- Oh, hello, Professor Brainard.
- May I see your sole?
- Wh--
- I mean, the bottom of your shoe.
- Oh, oh.
Now, the game`s not over yet. Keep your
chin up and your potential energy high.
`Cause you know why, Dale?
Son of a--
Get the ball.
Jump with all your soul.
B-- But l`m
on this end, sir. I--
Jump! Or l`ll flunk you.
- Uh-- What?
- You heard me.
Jump, or l`ll flunk you out
of my department for good.
Okay.
I think that`s
a little harsh, but--
- Jump!
- A-T-T-A-C-K!
The Medfield Squirrels are trying
to complete this astonishing comeback.
- Nice and patient, Rutland.
Plenty of time, baby.
- Rutland has the lead
with the clock winding down.
These rodents have fought
their little hearts out tonight,
but it looks like the Squirrels
are gonna come up a couple
of nuts short of a bushel.
Playing keep-away are the Rangers.
Here`s a wide-open "J" by Hatch.
Jump, Dale! Jump!
Jepner is soaring
into the air, makes the steal.
Look at him go! Jepner, with wings
on his shoes, soaring to the other end!
He`s all over it.
He dives. He`s through!
And Medfield upsets Rutland
on an incredible play by Dale Jepner!
- No!
- And the Squirrels are going nuts.
- Yeah!
- We won!
- Oh, we did it!
- Foul!
- We did it!
- Foul! Foul!
Since when is it within the
rules for a player to accompany
the ball through the hoop?
Oh, I don`t know. Come on.
I owe you dinner.
- Sara?
- Good night, Phillip.
Good night.
Brainard had something
to do with this.
It-lt`s the same stuff we saw
the other night over at his house.
Right.
I don`t know how, but l`m absolutely
certain your team cheated.
Oh, you`re just being
a sore loser.
Sara, m-m-may I speak
to you for a moment? Alone?
What you have to say to her,
you can say to both of us,
if you can remember.
Sara?
- Flubber.
- Flubber?
Sounds like baby shampoo.
Flubber is what won the game.
That amazing aerial ballet...
was because I flubberized
the boys` shoes.
A little on the bottom-- Whoo!
You are remarkable.
Sara?
Good night, Phillip.
Watch yourself.
Now what do we have to do
to get you to take a hint?
It`s over, Phillip. You lost.
Go home. Play with your rubber.
What kind of car does
that Brainard fellow drive?
Old T-Bird. Why?
- I just saw it.
- So?
It was flying.
You heard me. Flying.
- Hey, who won?
- We did.
Um, Professor,
why the long face?
- I think you know why.
- Would it be a Sara issue?
Wish I understood human beings.
Wish I understood women.
Wish I understood emotions and passions.
I wish I understood any of that.
If I did, I wouldn`t have had to spend
my entire life in a laboratory...
trying to figure out
how the world works.
I would`ve been out in the world
trying to figure out why it works.
I know I love her, Weebo.
Every neuron in my limbic system
is saturated with phenylethylamine.
That triggers euphoria,
elation, exhilaration.
Truth is, Weebo,
I`m not absent-minded because
l`m selfish or crazy or--
or inconsiderate.
I`m absent-minded because l`m
in love with Sara.
Oh, Professor.
That doesn`t matter any more,
`cause I don`t get
any more chances with her.
That`s not true. There`s always another
chance. I mean, you never know, right?
Probably just as well
that it`s over.
- Why?
- She has to move on.
- Oh.
- I`m not right for her.
- But you knew that, didn`t you, Weebo?
- Huh?
You never wanted me
to marry her.
Well, you were right.
I wasn`t right for her.
You`re the one for me, Weebo.
Just the two of us.
And flubber makes three.
- Good night, Weeb.
- Good night.
Uh, Professor--
And this is the God`s truth:
I want him to have
what he wants,
even if it means you
instead of me.
Ooh!
Sara? Sara, it`s me.
- Weebo?
- May I come in?
Oh, l`m sorry
to wake you like this,
but I can`t ring the doorbell.
- Is everything okay with Phillip?
- Oh, yeah.
It`s not
a conventional emergency.
Oh, Phillip would be very angry
if he knew I left,
but I have
to show you something.
Do you have a minute?
Listen.
I know I love her, Weebo.
Every neuron in my limbic system
is saturated with phenylethylamine.
That triggers euphoria,
elation, exhilaration.
Truth is, Weebo, l`m not absent-minded
because l`m selfish...
or crazy or-- or inconsiderate.
I`m absent-minded because l`m
in love with Sara.
Oh.
And this will be
our little secret.
Phillip.
Oh.
- Sara?
- Uh-huh.
This is it.
This is the solution.
This is how we save the school.
That`s what l`ve been saying.
Flubber.
- You saw what it did at the game.
- Yes.
Imagine the line of shoes
we could develop.
Oh, no, no, no, Phillip,
not shoes.
No. Look.
This. Flight.
- Flight?
- Yes.
- Oh, of course.
- A-Air travel.
Oh, Sara! Air travel.
- Yes.
- Oh.
- We`d better sell this
to a car company.
- Oh, Phillip.
- Hey!
- Dr Reynolds.
Professor. It`s a pleasure
to finally meet you.
I believe you know my son.
He used to play basketball
for Medfield.
Lovely old car.
Mind if I take a look
under the hood?
Yes, I do.
And I don`t appreciate you gentlemen
letting yourselves onto my property.
I expected something
more complex.
There`s a lot of money
in your discovery.
Perhaps we could make a deal.
Any discovery I make will belong
to Medfield College.
At the end of the term there isn`t
going to be a Medfield College.
- We`ll see about that.
- You could make a lot of money.
If we were interested in making money,
we wouldn`t have become teachers.
You think you`ll be able to sell
it for what you owe me...
by the end of the term?
We-- We will.
I`ll forget the debt right now.
No, l`m not selling.
When I leave,
I take my offer with me.
We understand.
Good luck.
Come on.
Watch your back, smart guy.
Bad move, Professor.
Good morning!
Pardon me, Mr Seldon.
Are you interested in seeing
a Phillip Brainard?
- Who?
- He`s the college professor
you spoke to on the sixth...
about a brand-new car design.
Tell him l`m busy.
Thank him for the interest.
- And send him a hat.
- Well, he`s here.
He`s right outside.
It`s one of the rarest looks
in watches you can actually own.
This watch we have here
is called the scarab.
It has Swiss--
Good night, Weber.
What?
One goon.
Two goons.
- Hey.
- What?
- I think I found it.
- You found it, all right!
- What was that?
- Take two.
Knock, knock!
Kiss me, big boy!
Did you get it?
Yeah.
Oh, l-l`ve never seen
so many zeroes.
When they saw us flying,
they couldn`t wait to write the cheque.
This will save the school,
Phillip.
Weebo?
They took the flubber.
- Weeb--
- Oh.
Um, sh-she`s leaking
battery fluid.
Weebo, it`s me.
Do you have signal?
Do you have audio signal?
Tracking. It`s me.
Professor Brainard.
Focus. Weebo?
Can you see me?
She sees me.
Weebo.
It`s all right. I`ve-l`ve-- I need
to get some sort of extension cord,
something so I can recharge her.
I`ve gotta-- I`ve gotta
download her, quick.
Weebo?
It`s all right. It`s okay.
Weebo, can you hear me?
It`s gonna be all right.
It`s like that time you ran into
the wall when I first made you.
We`ll get you upstairs,
onto AC and--
She`s-She`s losing--
She`s losing power.
It`s okay. It`s all right.
We just gotta get you
to the docking station...
till I can make repairs.
Weebo?
Goodbye, my friend.
Gone. I have no idea what--
Goodbye.
I don`t know what
to do with her.
What happens to the soul
of a machine, Sara?
Can you fix her?
I can make repairs,
but I can never bring back
the life it was she had.
That`s gone.
I never knew what it was to begin with.
It was some sort of glorious accident.
I kept trying to recreate it
and isolate it and find out what it was.
I never could.
What was that word
she was displaying...
on her screen at the end?
Probably a file name.
Why was she displaying it?
She was damaged-- It`s, you know--
download-- random piece of information.
- I don`t know.
- What was that word?
Oh, can you remember?
No, l--
- Try.
- I am.
It began with "S."
Hello, Phillip. It`s me. Weebo.
If I was human, that is.
If you`re watching this,
l`m no longer here.
I hope my demise didn`t
cause you any undue distress.
Phillip,
a full and complete design
of me is in this file.
You didn`t forget it.
I never showed it to you.
I`ve made a few changes.
I`ve removed a few
of my flaws...
and added a little of you.
I hope you that
you can love my daughter...
as much as I loved you.
Ooh.
Surprise, surprise.
Professor Brainard.
Dr Reynolds.
Good evening. Sit down.
You look, uh--
- Weary.
- Yes. Weary.
You came to repay your loan?
- No.
- I know you didn`t. I was
just having a little fun.
I`m here to sell you
the flubber.
You been to your house recently?
- Yes.
- Do I really need to buy it?
Flubber`s
a very quixotic substance.
It`s very difficult to handle.
Have you tried to do anything with it?
My man is working on it.
It won`t be a problem.
Well, I could make it
a lot easier for you.
If you give us a 30-day
extension on the loan,
I`ll tell you everything
I know...
and make you
a great deal of flubber.
I`ll give you the 30 days,
and after that
you give me two years.
Whatever you come up with
over the next two years is mine.
That`s not fair!
Shop somewhere else, lady.
Sara, Sara. I`ll do it.
- May I see the flubber?
- Would you like to show these
good people to the library?
You`re going to enjoy this.
Professor?
I got you a little help.
- The lovebirds.
- Wilson. Shame on you.
- Welcome.
- So you finally gave up teaching.
How could I pass up the opportunity
to transform the energy industry?
Flubber. Very interesting, Phil.
Too bad it`s so unstable.
I was just looking over the formula.
Dangerous mix.
You just have to know how to
deal with it, really. It just
takes a few simple precautions--
Hey, hey. Hang on, "Einsteen."
- Stein.
- Whatever.
- What`s this?
- Well, it-it`s a hand cream that
acts as a separating agent.
- Right.
- Um--
It`s so I can handle
the flubber.
- It`s okay.
- Thank you.
She needs to assist me.
Rub it on your hands.
It`s a, uh--
squirt gun.
- What`s it for?
- I use that to lower
the temperature of the tank.
Let him have it.
No, no. Give it to him.
N-No, no. Give it to him.
W-- Stop that
and give it to him.
Put-Put it in his hand
No, no, no, no, no.
Give the gun to him.
Oh.
- Thank you.
- You`re welcome.
You okay? lt`s me.
There you go.
Oh. Shh.
Do it for Weebo.
Look out!
Ooh.
Get him!
- Oh, dear.
- Sara? Going somewhere?
Wilson.
Ooh.
Left, left, left,
right, right, left.
- Sara!
- Huh?
- Grab her.
- What?
- Jump!
I`m coming, Sara!
Yo!
Ooh!
Hey, Lumpy. Hmm?
- Come on.
- Let`s go, smart guy.
- Ow.
- Phillip, look out!
Sara!
- Get him.
- This one`s for Weebo.
Ooh.
Oh, Mommy--
Wow.
Oh.
Beautiful.
For as much as these
two people have finally...
consented together
in holy wedlock...
and have witnessed the same
before God and this company,
I pronounce, believe it or not,
that they be
husband and wife together.
- You may now kiss the video screen.
- Oh.
Love you, Sara.
I love you.
I`ll meet you at the reception. I`m
almost done. It`s gonna be remarkable.
Phillip, please be careful.
Don`t worry. These chemicals
are completely compatible.
There`s no chance
that anything could go wrong!
Hey, pal. We`re 30,000 feet
up in the air.
There`s no monsters or bad guys
way up here, okay?
You can look out the window.
Mom. Mom!
Flubber`s gone. Get back here!
When we get to the hotel,
I don`t care what you say,
I`m not sharing a room with him.
Look at him. He`s gross.
He bounces all the time.
He squeaks. He phase-shifts.
I mean, he`s a quasi-plasmoid.
If it`s hot in Hawaii,
I hope he melts.
Ow
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org