[ Crowd Cheering ]
[ No Audio ]
[ Woman On P.A.] The captain has
turned on the "fasten seat belt" sign...
and we will be
departing shortly.
[ Man ] Your shoulder flaring? Nope.
- You winced.
- I didn't wince.
You grimaced.
My shoulder
doesn't hurt, Gus.
[ Beeping ]
How long has it
been hurting?
Perry wants me
to start tomorrow.
You gotta be kidding.
You're not doin' it.
No way.
It's the end
of a shitty season.
[ Sighs ]
I'm gonna go talk to Perry.
Sit down.
Sit down. Relax.
Sir, your drink.
Hi.
Thank you. It's a throwaway,
Billy. It means nothing.
Not to the Red Sox.
If I see you wince
even one time-
Oh, God!
[ Chuckles ]
I've-
I've got the ugliest wife
in the league.
That hurts.
It hurt my feeling.
[ Sighs ]
Buckle your seat belt.
Summer wind
Came blowin'in
From across the sea
[ Man ] Are we expecting
Miss Aubrey this evening?
[ Continues ]
We are.
What name am I registered
under? Mike Nelson.
The Sea Hunt fella, you know. All right.
Tell the desk that I don't wanna
talk to anybody except her, all right?
Mm-hmm.
And, Fitch, tonight,
everything
has to be perfect.
Have I ever let you down,
Mr. Chapel?
Two sweethearts
And the summer wind
Like painted kites
Those days and nights
They went flying by
The world was new
Beneath a blue
Umbrella sky
This is Mr. Chapel.
Have there been any messages?
No?
Thanks.
[ Woman On Phone ]
Hi, this is Jane.
Leave me a message after the
beep and I'll get back to you.
Thanks a lot. Bye-bye. [ Beeps ]
jane, it's Billy. I'm worried
now, so... please call.
Are you there?
[ TV Continues,
Indistinct ]
[ Groans ]
[ knocking On Door ]
[ knocking Continues ]
jesus. I've been
bangin' out here forever.
What the hell
happened to you?
You weren't at the gym.
Is Jane here?
No.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, Jesus.
Oh. Hmm.
[ knocking On Door ]
Chap, you know, a lot of little
bottles makes a big bottle.
Hey. Hey, that could be her.
You gotta throw today, chief.
Gus, do me a favor, huh?
Get the door!
All right.
Throw some water on your hair. It
might look like you took a shower.
[ Door Opens ]
No, not at all.
He's in the bathroom
back there.
Mr. Wheeler. Good mornin',
Billy. Got a minute?
Yeah, sure.
It's not easy
to get up here.
They treat me right. They
didn't have you on the register.
I can't remember all your
names. Price of fame, huh?
Can I
- Can I get you something? No, no, no, no.
Let's just sit.
Yeah.
It's been a rough season.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah.
Always next year.
Not for me.
It's one of those secrets
everybody knows.
What you don't know
is it's offiicial.
Billy, I sold the Tigers.
Well, that's, uh, great.
Is it?
Yeah.
Billy, you've been the
heart and soul of this team.
Like family.
All the negotiations,
the bastards never said a word.
Said what?
They want to trade you
to the Giants.
Wow.
Is-Is that why
you're here?
No.
I don't know how
to say this.
You know, I've been
watching you for 18 years.
[ Sighs ]
Nothing-
Nothing has given me
more pleasure.
You're like the old boys.
They were golden.
They had that special pride.
When they were done,
they were done.
Nobody had to show them
the door.
Are you saying
I should retire?
Why not? It wouldn't
hurt the negotiations,
and it would serve
those sons of bitches right.
I, uh-
I don't know.
I don't know what to say.
Well, you know, you can't tell
me you haven't thought about it.
And you've been smart with
money, right? Right? Yeah.
I've always been
a Tiger.
I know, son.
That's why
this is killing me.
You know, my dad bought
this team when I was seven.
I grew up
watching the Tigers.
I was gonna leave the team to my kids,
but they don't even like baseball.
Everything's changed,
Billy.
The players, the fans,
TV rights, arbitrations.
It isn't the same.
The game stinks.
And I-
I can't be
a part of it anymore.
[ Telephone Ringing ]
[ Ringing Continues ]
[ Sighs ]
Well-
Billy, you want me
to, um-
No.
Hello. Jane!
Where are you?
You're downstairs?
No! Just stay there,
all right?
just stay where you're at.
I'm on my way down.
[ Hangs Up Phone ] What do
you want me to tell 'em, Billy?
Look, I-
I need more time, all right?
The game doesn't stink,
Mr. Wheeler.
It's a great game.
Billy, what's up?
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
I tried to get her
in a cab, Mr. Chapel,
but she said she wanted to
- just go up and walk up in Central Park.
Go easy on our boys
today, Billy.
Jane?
jane?
Why didn't you wait?
[ Sniffles ]
Are you crying?
[ Sighs ]
What's the matter?
They didn't have any Kleenex in
the hotel bathroom. [ Sniffles ]
What's going on, Jane?
I've been sitting in the lobby
for the last two hours.
Doing what?
I'm sorry I didn't call
last night, you know.
I could tell that your voice
was worried enough that-
If something's wrong, just
say it, Jane. I mean, we don't-
We never had to fake it.
I'm leaving.
I'm going to London.
London?
There's a job, a good job.
An editor's position.
And-
I've been trying to fiigure out
a way to tell you,
but everything sounds so-
What can I say?
I mean, tell me what to say.
I can't tell you, Billy.
It's all right.
I knew it.
From the day I fiirst met
you fiive years ago, What?
I've always known... you
don't need me. Knew what?
You and the ball and the
diamond, you're perfect.
A perfectly beautiful thing.
You can win or lose the game
all by yourself.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Have dinner tonight with
me, Jane, after the game.
We'll go to Mario's.
I have a 6:00 plane.
They wanted me there
a week ago when you called,
and I wanted to see you.
I wanted to say good-bye.
Good-bye, Billy.
[ Rock ]
[ Male Announcer ] Welcome to
New York and to Yankee Stadium...
on a crisp and glorious
fall afternoon,
where the Yankees try to win the
divisional title against the Detroit Tigers.
Hi, everybody. I'm Vin
Scully along with Steve Lyons,
and welcome to our fiinal
telecast of the regular season.
You can smell the fall. The World Series
is just around the corner here in New York.
[ Lyons ] On paper, today's
game seems easy enough, Vin.
First place team takes an easy
game from the last place team.
But nothing's ever easy.
Mr. Chapel?
Hey. Ken Strout.
I was your batboy
a long time ago.
My dad was a Tiger.
joe Strout. I remember. [ Chuckles ]
How's he doin'?
Good. He and Ma are livin'
down in Florida now.
He doesn't move around too
easy, though. He's got bad knees.
You know,
a little arthritis.
What, are you playin' today?
No, I don't think so.
They just called me up.
Good. Well, good luck to you. Thanks.
And give your dad my best.
He was a... great player.
Oh, thanks.
I'll tell him.
[ Man On Radio ] Live from
Yankee Stadium in New York,
it's
New York Yankees baseball!
Today on the next
to last day of the year,
the Yankees have a chance
to clinch the pennant.
To do it, they'll have to beat
Billy Chapel and the Detroit Tigers.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Good afternoon,
everyone. It is a beautiful fall day...
Could you turn that off? at Yankee Stadium
as the Yankees are set to clinch the pennant.
No.
But standing in their way...
is the great veteran right-hander
of the Tigers, Billy Chapel.
Does anybody else know?
No. Nobody
knows nothin'.
Not even Perry. If they knew,
that's all they'd be talkin' about.
Well, what does Jane say?
[ Sighs ]
jane's movin' to London.
Movin'to London?
What the-
- How are you gonna manage that?
- We're not.
Billy...
this ain't your day.
[ Chuckles ]
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
That's
Wheeler's nephew.
He sent him down
to get your answer.
Guess he's gonna sit through
the whole game if he has to.
Poor kid.
Doesn't even know
what he's doin' here.
[ Sniffiing ]
just throw the ball to the
glove, son. just play catch.
Since you're throwin' bullets, I'm
not even gonna mention the fact...
that you were an hour late, and I've been
standin' here trying to fiigure out...
who my starting pitcher
would be if you didn't show up.
Have I ever not showed?
I mean, in 19 years
have I ever not showed?
Well, that's true of everyone till
the fiirst time they don't show.
Billy, I had an idea.
I've pretty much made up my mind,
but I wanted to run it by you fiirst.
I want Jimmy
to catch today.
I know how you feel about Gus, but he ain't
hittin', Billy. He ain't hit for a while now.
I haven't said anything,
but we need the left-handed bat.
I want Gus.
Yeah, I know,
and I'd love to take
one of these goddamn games.
We're not layin' down. We're not
gonna be a red carpet to the Series...
for these guys.
Gus catches,
or I don't pitch.
Me and Gus.
Nobody else.
I hope you hear me.
jesus, Billy, you tellin' me
how to run this team?
[ Grunting ]
No.
But today,
it's me and Gus.
I've never asked you
any other time, okay?
Good.
Glad you agree.
Can't argue about this
right now. Gotta warm up.
I'm sorry. We have
a bit of a delay.
We're correcting a bit
of a maintenance problem.
So we don't have a bit
of a crash?
Is there someplace I can stay? Yes.
The Premiere Lounge is just
down there on your right.
Thanks.
[ Lyons ] When the sun goes
down, it'll actually be...
an easier time to hit
for both teams.
[ Scully ] And now, talkin'about
shadows and sunlight,
that might very well sum up
Billy Chapel.
Long has he stood
in the brilliant sunshine...
in his great, 19-year career.
But now, battling back from
an 8 and 11 record this year,
trying to fiight his way out of
the shadows back into the sunlight.
He'll be facing Mike Robinson,
followed by Jonathan Warble...
and then Sam Tuttle.
Bottom of the fiirst inning, no
score, and the Yankees coming up.
What's he lookin' at?
He's lookin'...
at the clouds.
You okay, Chap?
Chappie!
You okay?
[ Man On P.A.]
Catching, number 27, Gus Sinski.
Number 27.
At shortstop, number 7,
Jose Garcia.
Trying to take my hand off? Sorry.
just let me set for that juice. Warn
me or something. Pitching, number 14,
Billy Chapel. I'm gonna throw a
little harder than usual today.
There's your warning.
Chap, don't throw it away
too early.
Today I'm throwin'
hard, Gus.
You and me?
One more time?
Why not?
[ Cheering ]
[ Man ] Hey, Chapel! We got
you, Chapel! You're done!
We're gonna stick a fork in
you, Chapel! You are finished!
You are complete! The Tigers are
done! You're done! You're finished!
Get outta town!
I can always tell
when I'm in New York.
[ Blowing Horn ]
Hey, Chapel!
Yo, Chapel!
You suck!
You stink on ice!
You couldn't pitch a tent!
[ Shouting, Cheering
Intensifies ]
[ Chapel's Voice ]
Clear the mechanism.
[ Shouting, Cheering
Continues, Muted ]
[ No Audio ]
Hello, Mike.
[ Umpire ]
Strike one!
[ Scully On TV ]
So, Chapel working on Robinson.
Bottom of the fiirst inning.
No score.
And there's a little looper
to Jose Garcia. One away.
Oh, this is-
This is my lucky day.
Hey, how are ya? How you
doin'? Fine. How you doin'?
Uh, the Bud
on the tap is good.
Okay. Oh, this is a beautiful day...
for the big ballpark
in the Bronx.
[ Scully Continues ] He was an
All-American shortstop there,
and he has certainly done
an outstanding job.
Two solid years, and now
a third with the Yankees.
Pretty good breaking ball.
Did get it up...
but got away with it. Lot of guys would
be upset about missin' their flight-
You know, delay, this and that
- but this works out beautiful for me.
[ Scully Continues ] So, Chapel
trying to derail the Yankees,
and the Yankees trying
to end a season...
that has long been finished
by Detroit.
[ Lyons ] Warble had a
game earlier this season...
where he had five hits,
nine R.B.I.s.
That's a week
for a lot of guys.
I don't know. They-They pushed
this guy up to pitch this game.
So, basically we clinch today
and I get to see it. Beautiful.
[ Scully ] They were 63 and
97. The Yankees, meanwhile-
Hi. What can I get for
you? Chivas and water.
[ Bar Patron ] Okay,
here we go. Everything is-
[ Scully ] Good sinker. Oh,
look at that. Ah, it's early.
You got, uh,
nuts, chips, somethin'?
- We got those pretzels.
- I can make do.
Thank you.
[ Scully ] Good fastball
with some movement on it.
And down goes Warble. jesus, he swung
at that? This guy, he's got nothin' now.
If I was Boston, I'd be worried. I'd be,
like, what, are they throwin' the game?
This guy used to be a monster,
to tell you the truth.
When he first came up,
he was unhittable.
Now, he's a junker.
30-30 three years in a row,
and in baseball circles we all know that
there's no love lost between these two guys.
They don't like
each other too much.
[ Cheering ]
[ Man On P.A.] At third
base, number 13, Sam Tuttle.
[ Chapel ]
Sam Tuttle.
I can't think of a better reason
not to be a Yankee.
[ Scully ]
Sam Tuttle hit. 625.
He went 5 for 8
against Chapel this year.
[ Lyons ] That would
make me not like a guy.
[ Scully ]
I would think so.
[ Chanting ]
Tuttle! Tuttle! Tuttle!
[ Chanting Continues ]
[ Scully ] Fastball on the
inside corner. Strike one.
Wasn't that inside?
You never do swing at the
fiirst pitch, do you, Sam?
No, no,
we're off the page now, Gus.
This is between me and ugly.
Straight heat.
That a boy.
- Strike two!
- Aw, that shit's outside.
No wonder nobody
likes you, Tuttle.
Everything's a goddamn
debate. [ Scully ] Fastball,
and it runs
right on that outside corner.
So 0 and 2 the count
to Sam Tuttle.
I saw that shitty little
Hollywood movie you did.
Ball! [ Lyons ] Gus
Sinski wanted that one.
So did Chappie. You see
the reaction on his face.
That's a pretty good pitch
on the outside corner.
Tuttle didn't like the first two calls, and
now he gets a break on that outside corner.
That's not the kind of pitch Chapel's
gonna like being called a ball all day long.
Don't crowd me, Sam.
I hate being crowded.
No.
So, 1 and 2 the count, and whoops,
Tuttle has really moved up on the plate.
He's all over the plate
right now.
Now you got the idea.
[ Scully ] Uh-oh! Down goes
Tuttle. [ Fans Protesting ]
What a knockdown pitch that was.
There's a message being delivered.
Yankee Stadium
is like a schoolyard,
and Bill Murdie looks like
a teacher who sees trouble.
You know, they say
in every great athlete...
there's a mean streak,
and Billy Chapel's no different.
[ Scully ] Bill Murdie
goes from umpire to referee.
[ Lyons ] Anytime I
played against this guy,
if he felt like he had his good
stuff, he'd flip you like this.
Throw a ball right up there over
your head just to let you know that,
"I can throw the ball
anywhere I want today-"
[ Bar Patron ] You know, I've
been a Yankee fan since 1958.
- I can name a Yankee for every number.
- Oh, God. Please don't.
Number one:
Billy Martin, Bobby Richardson.
Number two: Frank "The Crow"
Crosetti and Bobby Murcer.
Number three.. the Babe. Number
four.. Gehrig. Five.. DiMaggio.
Six.. Steve Boyer, Roy White.
Excuse me. Would you mind?
You can't smoke in a bar. What,
now you can't talk in a bar?
This ain't church, lady.
[ Scoffs ]
[ Scully ] Tuttle back up to
the plate. [ Umpire ] 2 and 2!
Same shit,
different day, huh?
I'd throw it at you again,
but I'm afraid
Murdie'd run me.
Strike three!
[ Scully ] Oh, good breaking
ball. Got him looking.
[ Lyons ] What a great job of settin'up
a hitter. Let's take another look.
Tuttle looks like a deer caught in the
headlights. Chapel just jelly-legged him.
[ Scully ] So at the end of one,
Tigers nothing, Yankees nothing.
All right, here we go now. Four,
fiive, six. Let's get something started.
jose, attababy.
It's all about
positioning, right?
You gotta wait on this guy,
all right?
Hey, Mike? Some water? [ Man ] Yeah?
Sure thing, Billy.
You all right?
You got it goin' good
out there.
Make sure
you save something.
Birch wants
to play golf tomorrow.
You know, I played golf with
Birch the day I met Jane.
You doin' all right?
Yeah.
I'm not hearin' 'em
at all out there.
[ Car Stereo ] Are you
gathering up the tears
Have you had enough of mine
Are you reelin'in
the years
Stowin'away the time
[ Yells ]
- Ooh. Hot.
- Stupid piece of crap!
Yeah, that'll fiix it.
[ Fades ]
[ Sets Parking Brake ]
[ Shuts Engine Off ]
[ Sighs ]
I don't need any help.
I can see that.
I can see you got your car...
kicked completely
into submission.
I mean it.
just go away.
[ Sighs ] You know, I can
always tell when I'm in New York.
Do you really know
anything about cars?
[ Chuckles ] You want
me to have a look at it?
Okay.
It's not mine.
It's just a trashy rental.
Yeah. Mine too.
Why don't you try the key?
See if we can't get it started.
[ Ignition Cranking ]
[ Chapel ] Should've paid
attention in auto shop.
Um-
[ Ignition Cranking ]
- [ Engine Starts ]
- [ Laughing ]
What did you do?
Well, I was-
I have no idea. I-
I don't- [ Chuckles ]
I don't know anything about cars.
I was just trying to be manly.
Well, that was great.
Thank you.
You saved my day.
Of course I did.
I said I would.
Where are you headed?
I'm not sure.
Bear Mountain, maybe.
I just threw my stuff in the car and
took off. Had to get out of the city.
How come? 'Cause summer's
over and I missed it.
You know, I work all the time.
Makes me feel old. I don't know.
Oh.
Well, thanks again.
So, what's the problem? My
problem seems to be solved.
Oh, no. Well, wait a
sec. No, the car's fiine.
But listen, honey, I gave up on four
calls haulin' my ass out to you, okay?
That's 100 bucks to me. So if there's
nothin' wrong with this car now,
there will be when I bring it
down to the city, okay? The car's-
- Everything all right?
- [ Man ] Everything's peaches, mac.
You're-
You're Billy Chapel.
I can't believe it.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I can't believe this.
Oh, I'm sorry.
[ Tow Truck Radio Chattering,
Indistinct ]
You know, you are the greatest
freakin' ballplayer out there.
I'm sor- I'm sorry.
But you really are.
I'm gonna go get that.
You stay right here, okay?
[ Car Door Opens ]
Billy Chapel.
Nice to meet you.
jane Aubrey.
You know, I-
I got this problem.
See, um, I'd like
to keep talkin' with you,
but I gotta go to work.
[ Chuckling ] just a second. Hey.
[ Whistles ]
I'll get there
when I get there.
Can you do me a favor?
Anything.
We got a bum deal
on this rental here,
so if you could
- if you could haul this back to town for us,
I'd really appreciate it.
I can't take that.
Wait a sec. Wait a sec.
What are you doing?
You like baseball?
What?
Baseball. [ Clattering
] No, not really. Hey!
- You ever been?
- No.
Would you like to go?
Would you like to go
to a baseball game with me?
Billy, if she don't
wanna go, I'll go.
Don't let that happen.
Lady, you can't just stand
in the middle like that.
Oh, sorry.
Let me see your ticket.
Oh, you're with the
players' wives. Follow me.
Go on.
Go on!
Thanks. Excuse me.
Sorry. Sorry.
Sure.
Hey.
Hey. Excuse me.
Who are you here with,
honey? Billy Chapel.
Oh, how nice.
[ Whispering ]
This week's blond.
No, no, stay. You're cool. Trust
me. I've been there, all right?
I'm Kisha Birch. Hi. Hi.
jane Aubrey. Nice to meet
you. [ Umpire ] Strike three!
[ Cheering, Shouting ]
You got a ball?
Yeah.
[ Jane ]
You don't lose much, do you?
I lose.
I've lost.
About 134 times.
Oh.
[ Chuckles ]
That's over, like, 15 years, okay? Oh.
All right?
You count them?
We count everything in baseball. I mean, that's
- God, that's all we do.
All right, quit stalling.
What?
You haven't told me
anything about you. Nothin'.
Well, I fiigured
if I kept my mouth shut,
I could pass for
elegant and mysterious.
You're forgetting I saw you
on the highway... [ Laughing ]
kicking the hell
out of your car.
Where are you from?
Oh, God.
Three questions.
Syracuse, New York.
That's one.
What are the pads for?
This one is my article on
lip gloss for Elle magazine,
this one is on skin peels,
and my grocery list.
Last question.
How do you liked
to be kissed?
You know, I always thought
that men and women...
should just
carry around signs.
If you're poor and you can't afford it, you
would make yours out of cardboard and string.
And if you're rich, you could
have it lettered in gold leaf...
or pounded out of tin by
Mexican craftsmen. [ Chuckling ]
It doesn't matter. But you
wear them around your neck, see?
And they say things,
like "shallow" or "horny. "
It just
- It just would be a hell of a lot easier.
What would yours say?
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
[ Moaning ]
Billy?
Billy, isn't this
your floor? I think so.
We've been here
twice before.
[ Siren Wailing ]
Good morning.
Gotta go.
Sleep as long as you want. You can
take a shower, anything you want.
Nobody'll bother you till
you take the sign off the door.
Okay, thanks.
What's this, a souvenir?
[ Chuckles ]
It's my number.
Billy, you don't have
to give me this.
I know I don't have to do this,
but, um, I wanted to.
When will you be back?
I already checked.
Four weeks from Thursday
I'll be back in New York.
So, uh...
that Thursday night?
Meet me in the bar
downstairs at 10:00, okay?
I'll be there
waitin' for you.
If you don't show up,
if you leave me standing in
that bar, it'll ruin this.
Well, then I guess
I'll just have to show up.
I'm serious.
I'll be there, Jane,
okay?
Okay, Billy Chapel.
[ Crowd Cheering ]
[ Chanting ] Birch! Birch!
Birch! Birch! Birch! Birch!
[ Chanting Continues ]
Birch, baby! Kiss that
bitch good-bye! Take it over!
Clear the mechanism.
[ Cheering, Shouting Fades ]
[ No Audio ]
You look old, Davis.
Are we that old?
[ Throwing Ball Into Glove ]
Strike one! [ Scully
] And the fastball...
sinks at the knees, picks up the
corner, and the count 0 and 1.
Don't smile at me, Davis.
I hate that.
[ Scully ] It was a sad day
in Detroit when Gary Wheeler,
the owner of the Tigers and a
somewhat beleaguered franchise,
was forced to trade Davis Birch,
who was a free agent.
Detroit could not come up
with his monetary demands,
and the Yankees were waiting
with open arms and an open wallet.
It was your team too.
I mean, how much money
we gotta make?
You want to see my team?
[ kisha ] You kids go and
play. That's my team over there.
You got it.
I'll be out in a second, okay?
Billy, are you
- are you gonna just sit there and mope or are you gonna help?
I ain't carrying no books.
Where's the pillows?
[ Chapel ]
You're the best, kiddo.
The best around.
The worthy opponent.
[ Scully ] The 0-1 pitch. And the
bottom just drops out of it. Strike two.
[ Lyons ] Look at Birch
starin' out at Billy Chapel.
They're sayin', "Where's
that curveball coming from?
He never had that curveball
when we played together. "
It don't happen that often,
but I got you mixed up, don't I?
You're guessin' now, aren't
you? [ Throwing Ball Into Glove ]
Well, here's your fastball...
right down the pipe,
just so you don't walk away thinking
I was afraid to give it to you.
Strike!
[ Scully ] Fastball runs on the
inside corner. Strike three called.
- Jesus, Birch, I could've hit that.
- So Billy Chapel, all business,
taking care of Birch
on three pitches.
Kenny Howell will follow.
[ Jane's Voice ]
If you don't show up,
if you leave me standing in
that bar, it'll ruin this.
[ Woman Singing,
Indistinct ]
[ Honking ]
[ Man ]
Cab, Mr. Chapel?
[ Whistle Blowing ]
You leaving?
Yeah, I was supposed to
meet someone, but they, uh-
I'm sorry.
I wasn't gonna come. I
actually sat in my apartment...
counting the hours to the time when
I was not gonna show up to meet you.
And then I-I just-
Oh, God.
Billy Chapel.
Why do you always use
both my names?
So I know
what I'm up against.
I
- I had a great time with you last month. It's not that.
Don't get me wrong.
It's just that...
I- I don't mean to sound
like anything or anything,
[ Man ] It's for our kid.
Thanks. but-but I don't do that.
And I'm not saying
anything about it. What?
I just don't do it, not since I
was in college. What don't you do?
I just
- You know what? I think I should go home.
Why? Because-Because I
just don't screw like that!
And-And-And
I hate that word.
[ Man ] You want that cab, Mr.
Chapel? Give it to somebody else.
I don't go to hotel rooms
with men I don't know.
Billy, I can't be a groupie.
You're not a groupie, Jane.
You don't look like one. You don't act
like one. I didn't treat you like one.
Wasn't-
Wasn't I a gentleman?
Yes, I know.
But you pull up out of
nowhere, you start my car.
You make me laugh, and the next thing I know
- No.
I'm at a baseball game
that you win!
I mean,
it's so surreal.
Little boys buy cards
with your picture on them.
They buy those for the gum.
[ Chuckles ]
Goddamn it!
God- What?
Goddamn what?
I like you.
So what's the problem?
I'm really not at all
the person you think I am,
and I think it would just be
more fair for both of us...
for-for me to just leave.
Well, forget it.
I mean,
what's the difference?
I mean-
What?
Just- No.
Here, give me the thing.
What's the difference
between the real you...
and this-this other you?
The-The real me is-is-
Here.
The real me is plain,
uninteresting and-and-
and hates sexy underwear because
it's really uncomfortable.
Oh.
All right, so the-
the real you's a bummer.
This can't be what you were
looking for from this evening.
I mean, be totally
honest with me. That-
That day I fiixed your car,
jane, I got lucky.
And maybe
you got lucky too.
I mean, I know we don't
know each other so well,
but that's-
that's what I was hoping.
I mean, we don't have to-
We could, like-
like, walk, you know?
We could walk like
- We could just walk. Walk?
I- I could walk.
I mean, we don't
- we don't have to talk so much either.
Okay.
You've got the look
of love light in your eyes
I was in crazy motion
Till you calmed me down
It took a little time
But you calmed me down
You know, border collies.
My dad loved
the blue heelers.
Is he still alive?
No, they're both gone.
Him fiirst,
and then her within a year.
He was a good man.
Very tall.
Very reserved.
Passionately in love
with two things:
my mother and baseball.
Then he was a lucky man.
Okay.
So, how do we do this?
How does this work, Billy?
I told you, I have to be here
next month for a couple of days.
I wanna see you.
Okay.
[ keys Jingling ]
So...
when you're away,
I'll live my life...
and-and you'll live yours.
And none of this stupid bullshit
why-didn't-you-call-me crap.
And what you do
when you're not with me...
has nothing to do with me,
and vice-versa.
No questions asked.
No worrying.
No obsessing.
That sounded perfect.
Good night.
My back keeps breaking out.
Candy says it's gross.
[ Imitating Austrian Accent ]
Use the loofah.
The what?
The loofah.
It exfoliates.
You're losing it
over this girl.
I met this woman
in New York.
I'm thinkin' of askin'
her down. Call her.
Nah, it's, you know,
it's not, uh- it's casual.
I've seen her a few times
over the winter in New York...
when I happen to be there.
Call her.
[ Telephone Ringing ]
Hello?
[ Chapel ] I'm having this
problem with my skin peel.
I was just thinking about you.
Yeah? What were you thinking?
I was wondering when you play your
fiirst series against the Yankees.
jane, come down here.
What?
Come see me. Come spend the
weekend. Meet my friends.
I don't know, Billy.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
Well, I-I've got a ton
of work to do, Okay.
and I can't really afford to be running off
- So, I'll pay.
No.
It's not that.
Look, we made the rules.
I think we should stick to them.
There's no rules about having
fun. I mean, that's bullshit.
Why is it bullshit?
Because if all you want to do
is have fun,
then you would come down here,
'cause this is fun.
You know who sat in the
bleachers last Sunday? Who?
Sandy Koufax.
You are such-
Sandy Koufax!
You are such a guy.
You are like the ultimate guy.
- What, you don't like guys?
- I need a regular guy.
Not the guy on
the Old Spice commercial.
It was Right Guard.
What?
It was Right Guard,
that commercial.
I was being
metaphorical, Billy.
Look, this is crazy.
What am I supposed to do? I'm
supposed to run down there...
and meet Sandy Koufax, get his
autograph and sleep with Mr. Right Guard?
What-What are you
so afraid of?
I'm not afraid.
[ Sighs ]
I can't be a groupie.
You know, that's the second time
you used that word to me, Jane,
and it didn't really go down
that well the fiirst time.
- Now you're mad.
- No, I'm not mad.
I'm just... pissed off.
Billy, that's not fair.
Look, I'm gonna hang up now, all
right? Let's start from the beginning.
- I'll call you some other time.
- Wait. No.
When will you call me? Like when
I don't feel like killin' you.
[ Sighs ]
[ Receiver Clicks ]
I told her.
[ Sniffles ]
So, I haven't seen you
around much lately.
I've been workin' hard.
Yeah, well, all work and no play
- [ Chuckles ]
[ knocking ]
All I've got is my toothbrush and a
bathing suit I bought at the airport.
[ Male Vocalist,
Indistinct ]
You're not smiling. You're annoyed. No.
- I'm an idiot.
- No, I'm an idiot.
jane, listen to me.
[ Chuckles ] No matter what
happens in the next fiive minutes,
I want you to know
that when I opened this door...
I was so happy to see you
that my heart leapt.
It leapt in my chest,
okay?
Okay.
Hey, Billy, can I borrow
your... blow dryer?
You'll find the words
still ring true
Some things
don't change
Some things do
[ Sighs ]
- Don't go.
- And you're the only one
With a broken heart
- The only one
- It's not your fault.
Who's afraid
of the dark
jane-
I have terrible timing.
I've always had it.
That's why I failed at acting
and skiing and table tennis. No.
I should've known when the
only flight to Lauderdale...
was at 6: 10 a. m.,
and the only rental car I could
get was this ridiculous Lincoln.
The car's perfect.
It's perfect.
That girl
- No, please. You don't have to do this.
I'm not angry or hurt. We're
not anything. You're fiine.
You can do whatever you want. I know I can. I ju
- I don't want her.
Well, then what is she
doing here?
Well, I like her.
She's my masseuse.
[ Laughs ]
It's never quite how
you play it in your head.
What about
the whole deal thing?
- What deal?
- You know. You do what you do, I do what I do.
You believed that? I was lying.
I was trying to be the man.
I was doing
a damn good job of it...
until you invited me
down here.
You were right.
I was afraid. I was afraid you
were gonna break my heart...
into a thousand pieces.
jane, I'm-
I've been thinking
about you, Jane.
I don't know what
I was- That was-
Look
- All right, tell me what I can say so you'll believe me.
I believe you.
Well, then- then stay.
Please, Jane,
I want you to stay.
This can only end
bloody for me, Billy.
I saved the sign.
You know, the "yes" sign?
I pinned it on the wall
in my locker. Goddamn it!
It was stupid!
[ Scully ] Strike three
called. On the corner.
I see a red door and I
want it painted black
Strike three!
Fastball got him.
[ Continues, Indistinct ] That's
strikeout number five for Billy Chapel.
He is really on a roll now.
I see the girls walk by [
Scully Continues, Indistinct ]
Dressed in their
summer clothes
I have to turn my head
Until my darkness goes
I see a line of cars
And they're all
painted black
With flowers
and my love
Both never to come back
I see the people
Turn their heads
and look away
Like a newborn baby
It just happens every
day You're in the zone.
[ Man On P.A.] Number 24, It feels good.
[ Scully ] Here's Mickey
Hart, 0 for 1. Mickey Hart.
[ Scully ]
No score, fourth inning.
Jack Spellman, doing well, has
allowed only two hits to the Tigers.
Meanwhile, Billy Chapel
in perfect control.
Mickey'll be gone
next year too.
Poor guy.
Never cold get a break.
What was that catch he missed?
The one that hit him?
They still play it on Diamond
Vision all the time. You know-
Whoops, there goes another rubber
tree plant [ Chuckles ] [ Chuckles ]
Fenway.
Uh, uh, uh
Uh, I remember wasn't so long ago, we had
a one-room shack and the livin' was low
And my mama by herself
raised me and my bro
Wasn't easy but we did it
with the little that flowed
She said Son, there'll be
times when the tides are high
And the boat may be rocky
You can cry [ Cheering ]
Just never give up
You can never give up
Everything's all right,
man.
Guess that looked pretty funny
out there today, huh?
Probably end up on ESPN
or somethin. '
A lot of shit ends up on ESPN I
don't think's very funny, Mick.
Phone call, Mr. Chapel.
There's a bunch of cameras out there right
now waitin' to make a joke of this, Mick.
So you can either stop, give 'em
the sound bite, do the dance...
or you can hold your head up and walk
by, and the next time we're in Boston...
we'll go out there
and work the wall together.
Don't help 'em make
a joke out of you.
Old school, baby.
He's right.
Chapel. It's Jane. I got your
number from the front offiice.
I hope that it's okay. That's
all right. Don't worry about it.
What's wrong? Something's
happened. It's my daughter.
She ran away.
Your daughter?
I'll tell you
- I don't have time know, but she's there in Boston.
Her father lives there. Oh,
God. We had a fiight. All right.
jane, just slow down,
all right? just slow down.
She climbed down the fiire escape and went to Penn
Station and got on a train to go to her father,
but he's not there.
What's the address?
8245 Clackton.
What's her name?
Freedom.
Freedom?
Scared you, didn't I?
Heather. It's Heather.
[ Rock, Muffled ]
Heather?
It's okay. I'm
- I'm the guy your mom said was coming to get you.
Let's get out of here before we get
our asses kicked twice in one night.
Heather?
- You're Heather.
- And you're the baseball player.
My mom can do
nothing normal.
[ Snickers ]
[ Whispers ]
Shut up, shut up.
You want somethin'?
I'll have a V8.
[ Scoffs ] What is it with
single men and V8 juice?
I mean, my dad's fridge has
nothing but mustard in it.
But when I come to visit it
has mustard, fiish sticks...
and this big jug
of V8 juice.
Like, if he makes me choke down a
glass he's being healthy and fatherly.
Well, I like V8.
Nutritious.
- So are you my mom's boyfriend?
- I'm not sure.
But you've slept with her.
V8. It's a refreshing blend of eight...
vegetable juices.
[ Exhales Sharply ]
What did you and your
mother fiight about?
[ Exhales Sharply ]
I didn't come home from school when I was
supposed to because I was with Mark Elton.
She freaked out because
he has facial hair...
and his parents
are never home.
I said, "We didn't do anything. "
She said, "Well, you could have. "
I said,
"Well, I might love him. "
She said, "Well, you
don't know what love is. "
I said, "I'm gonna do what I wanna do. "
She said, "Well,
not in this house. "
And-
So I went to my dad's,
because...
he doesn't care
what I do...
'cause he's stoned
90%% of the time.
She just-
She doesn't...
want me t
- to make the same mistakes that she did.
She had me
when she was 16.
You know, she never had...
a love story.
And now it's like...
she doesn't believe in it.
Honey, I'm so sorry. I'm
sorry too. I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
Billy...
Come up.
Don't ever do that again,
okay? [ Door Shuts ]
We can always work it out. just
talk to me. [ Cabbie ] Thanks.
Honey, you want some
spaghetti? No, I'm tired.
You sure?
I ate on the plane.
- How was it?
- It was fine. It was small.
[ Conversation Continues,
Indistinct ]
She's already asleep.
Thank you.
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't know. Uh, I
protect her maybe too much.
Some guys meet her, and they
don't come around anymore.
She thinks
it's her fault.
You want some tea or something?
Are you hungry? No. No, I'm good.
It's nice.
Good home.
Thanks.
[ Laughs ]
I like to hold it
in my hand...
'cause I know somewhere
you're doing the same thing.
I'm glad you called me.
I'm glad.
What are you doing
down there?
My foot's been kicking something
down here all night.
What is-
[ Clicks ]
[ Laughs ]
It's not mine.
Oh, you mean it doubles as
a flashlight? [ Giggling ]
It's really a flashlight. I wondered why
there were so many batteries in this room.
Shut up!
I'm hungry.
I'm starving.
To the kitchen.
About 20 hours of labor.
Nicky was so freaked out he didn't
even stick around for my sixth month.
There was this unbelievable nurse who
stayed double-shift to be with me...
and feed me ice chips
and tell me when to breathe...
and push and scream.
Then fiinally she came out.
They laid her on my stomach and I
could feel her little heart beat.
I just kept thinking
over and over,
"You and me.
You and me, little girl. "
And then I rigged out my backpack
like those baby slings they have now.
We walked out of there,
two kids together.
What are you thinking?
That you're heroic
and I admire you.
And you care a lot about me but
you can't afford to get involved.
Is that what's next?
No.
I was... thinking about
you and Heather.
And me.
I was really
thinking about...
how nice it would be
to spend time together.
Yeah.
[ All Shouting,
Indistinct ]
Oh! These are great.
We'll use 'em
in Central Park.
No, we can
use 'em out here.
You ever gotten
your heart broken?
Yeah, when we lost
the pennant in '87.
Would you still love me
if I got burned in a fiire?
Oh!
[ Laughs ]
Yes. If I ran into a
tree and got paralyzed?
[ Scoffs ]
Yes.
What If I were
totally disfiigured,
if my face were
all scraped away,
I had no arms, no legs,
no brain waves...
and I was being kept alive
on a heart-lung machine.
Would you love me?
No.
[ Laughing ]
But we could still
be friends though.
[ Chuckling ]
Do you believe in God?
[ Whispers ]
Yes.
How old do you think you're
gonna be when you die?
Do you like
white meat or dark?
Dark.
Dark?
The dark part's more fatty,
but it's cool to like that part.
You like it chopped up?
You know how people dice
it in the chef salad,
or you like it torn?
I personally
like it torn.
Not that you have to
like it how I like it.
No questions.
[ Chapel ] Why you
askin'me all this stuff?
[ Jane ]
Because I want to know you.
Breaking ball, a comeback right at
Billy Chapel to hold onto the line drive.
- [ Cheering ] - [ Lyons ] This is
one of those chuck-and-duck pitches.
When you throw a ball like that
and it comes back at you that quick,
it's almost like
the ball catches you.
[ Scully ] So far, Chapel
is gettin'away with it.
[ All Chanting ]
Go, Tigers, go, Tigers.
Hey, ho, hey, ho.
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
[ Scully ] We have one out here
in the top of the sixth inning.
No score. Spellman has allowed
two hits. Chapel has been perfect.
The batter is
Gus Sinski, 0 for 1.
[ Lyons ] Gus has had a tough
year this year at the plate,
but they really pay him for
what he does behind the plate.
He handles his pitching staff so well,
and any kind of hit that he gets...
is a bonus for this club.
- [ Crowd Cheering ]
- Yes!
- Simon Louis'a little slow in coming up with it.
- Get down! Get down!
Safe!
It wasn't close!
He beat the play!
Good call.
Attaboy!
In a game like this,
that could be a huge play.
The last leg double Sinski had was
during the Reagan administration.
The Yankees are now on the
phone talking to the bullpen...
and they get
a left-hander up.
Bobby Mack is ticked off
with the Yankees,
and he gives batter Jose Garcia
the intentional walk.
In a moment there'll be runners at first
and second, one out in the sixth, no score...
and a left-handed hitter coming
up- that would be Brian Whitt.
[ Whirring ]
[ Chapel ]
Jane.
I was just
lookin' for you.
Billy?
Oh, my God.
Can't feel
anything.
Hold this. Close your fiingers
around it. Hold it up. Hold it up.
[ Tires Screech ]
Hold on, Billy.
- [ Woman ] Occupation?
- Pitcher. He's hurt his hand.
- We need a doctor.
- Are you his wife?
No. No.
Are you a relative?
Then I'll have to ask you
to wait outside.
jane.
My friend cut his hand.
It's bleeding very deeply.
- Ma'am.
- Please, we need help.
Is this not America?
Is baseball not America's
favorite pastime?
- Can I help you?
- Are you a doctor?
- Yes.
- Thank you, God.
jane.
I'm right here.
- Jane, call Mike Udall.
- What?
The trainer in Detroit. Call
him. Tell him what happened.
I'm going with you. Sorry, there's
not enough room in the Medivac.
You're gonna need
to stay here.
jane!
Call Mike. He's the most
important person for me right now.
You need to clear out.
- [ Bat Cracks ]
- [ Scully ] There's a little flare just by Howell's glove...
- into right field.
- [ Players Shouting, Indistinct ]
Here comes Sinski.
Colborn waves him to the plate.
- The throw. He is... in there!
- Safe! Safe!
- [ Groans ] - The Tigers
take a 1-to-nothing lead.
[ Lyons ] What a great slide by Sinski,
sliding away from the play at the plate.
Jim Colborn, the third base
coach, didn't even hesitate.
Your catcher, the slowest guy
on your team, comin'around third,
trying to score in a scoreless ball game, had
no hesitation at all, sent him all the way-
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
[ Man ] It's all bullshit,
Billy. Don't listen to it.
You've done it all. You've won
every award there is to win.
You got a room reserved
at Cooperstown, Billy.
I just don't know how much more
you have to prove.
Even if you do come back, you're not gonna be
a hundred percent. You may not even be fifty.
- [ Chapel ] What'd you say?
- Nothin'. Let's knock off for the day. Jane's here.
What'd you say?
I didn't say anything.
You said "if. "
I didn't mean "if. "
But you said "if. "
I only meant-
Think I'm not comin' back? Billy.
Say it. You're tired. Let's quit.
Say it, chickenshit.
You got a job. That's to get
me strong and get me back.
All right?
You get me back...
I'll fiigure out how to win.
You wanna work with me tomorrow,
then get your mind right.
You get it right,
or you don't come around me.
[ Jane ]
You mad at me or at Mike?
[ Chapel ]
Why would I be mad at Mike?
You practically tore
his head off. Talk to me.
Talk?
You don't want to talk.
You just want to give me your
version of why I should quit.
- I want this shit outta here.
- What're you tryin' to do?
Are you trying to make me mad? Are you
gonna pack up my things and make me go...
so you can sit here in the dark
and feel sorry for yourself?
Well, forget it, Billy. You
can't cook, you can't drive-
I'll hire somebody
to drive me.
Someone who doesn't talk?
Doesn't think bad thoughts?
Billy, we are gonna get through
this. You just have to try-
Try! Goddamn it, jane, I'm the
only one who is trying here.
I got nobody in the front
offiice, nobody in the press...
and now I got nobody
in this house...
that thinks
I'm gonna make it back.
I have been nothing
but supportive of you.
I don't want you here,
jane! I mean-
Don't you get it?
You make
- You make me feel distracted.
You make me feel weak.
Billy,
you taught me something.
You taught me
how to believe again,
how good things can happen
and that they will happen.
But now you need to let me teach
you something about what I know-
about how sometimes life seems
like it's slamming you down,
but it's really
giving you a gift.
I had a baby
when I was 16.
That could've
wrecked me.
But it didn't. Instead, it was the
best thing that ever happened to me.
You mean if life gives you
lemons, you make lemonade?
- You are such an asshole. - If you're tellin'
me I'm never gonna hold that ball again-
I can't.
Haven't you ever loved
anything that much?
I'll call the airlines. See
what kind of flights I can make.
You do that.
[ Crowd Cheering ]
[ Indistinct Chanting ]
[ Grunts ]
- Strike!
- [ Scully ] Uh-oh.
Something happen
to Chapel?
Frank Perry is on the steps of the dugout
and apparently didn't like what he saw.
Gimme the ball.
What are you lookin'-
just stay there.
[ Crowd Cheering,
Whistling ]
[ Lyons ] There's something wrong with either
his arm, his elbow or his shoulder there.
He doesn't look
very comfortable.
- Bill, he's hurt.
- [ Scully ] Here he comes. He's goin'out to visit.
[ Booing ]
You just do somethin'there? No.
You hurtin'?
No.
Uh-huh.
How long?
- Ten years.
- [ Sighs ]
What do you wanna do? I'd
like you to smile at me,
pat me on the fanny, march your
butt to that dugout and sit down.
- That's what I'd like.
- I want this goddamn game, Billy.
Well, I want it too.
[ Exhales Sharply ]
If it gets any worse,
I'll sit down.
Ready to go?
Where's my pat?
[ Pats ]
Thank you.
You let me know. Yeah. He's all right.
[ Jane ]
He's flexing his hand.
What? He does that
when his arm's tingling.
Pretty soon he's not gonna be able
to feel anything. Do you know him?
Yeah, and I know
Mickey fuckin' Mantle.
[ Bartender ] Hey, watch the
language. There's people in here.
[ Patrons.. Mocking Laughter ] [ Man On
P.A.] This is a boarding announcement for...
flight number 12.
God, I hate Yankee fans.
Hey, you leavin'? How can you
leave when your guy's winnin'?
He's not gonna win.
How do you know?
Because he's hurting and he won't
tell anyone and he won't come out.
[ P.A. Continues,
Indistinct ] I don't know.
Honey,
I hope you're wrong.
[ Scully ]
As you mentioned earlier,
there's no love lost at all
between Tuttle and Chapel.
Tuttle would just love to break
up this perfecto right now.
[ Lyons ]
Yes, he would.
[ Scully ] He bunts up along third. Down
to get it. Backhanded by Chapel to first.
- You're out!
- And got him!
[ Groans ] What are you buntin' for,
Tuttle? We need a hit, you pansy!
[ Scully ]
For the third time today...
Sam Tuttle has boiled over,
arguing now with
first base umpire Richie Garcia.
[ Indistinct Arguing ]
- Take another look at it.
- [ Lyons ] The only guy that can fiield this ball is Chapel.
He's like a cat off the mound.
He slides, picks up the ball
and throws it.
That enabled him to get up
quicker than just bend over.
[ Scully ] What a mix we have
goin'on for the last two innings.
Sitting alone upstairs,
owner Gary Wheeler...
reportedly has already sold
his ball club, the Tigers,
to the corporate group
in the box to his left.
Now an unconfirmed report
beginning to ripple the water...
that the corporate's
first business...
would be to trade Billy Chapel
when the season is over.
So as so often happens in a ball game,
there are so many other undercurrents,
so many more things
than meet the eye.
And here we have it all.. [
Male Vocalist, Indistinct ]
a beleaguered owner selling
a ball club,
perhaps the new owners selling
the biggest star on the club,
and all the while,
Billy Chapel, perhaps,
trying to make
the decision of his life.
Does he remain a big leaguer, or
after 19 years will he call it quits?
[ Continues ]
See that? It just takes
off. I don't even know where-
Use the seams. I am using the
seams, but I can't feel the seams.
just-
And I remember
what she said to me
How she swore that it
never would end
I remember
how she held me
Oh, so tight
Wish I didn't know now
what I didn't know then
Against the wind
We were runnin'
against the wind
We were young
and strong
We were runnin'
against the wind
Well, I'm older now
and still runnin'
Against the wind
I'm still runnin'
against the wind
Against the wind
I'm still runnin'
I'm still runnin' against
the wind Against the wind
Tell her about the exhibition we
went to, the she-male paintings.
The portraits.
Tell 'em that one.
You tell them.
No, it's your story.
Please, will you excuse me? Sure.
What, I don't have enough
black on, or what? No.
No, it's just that you're
not on the list. Oh.
You need an invitation to get
in. Here comes my invitation.
It's all right.
[ Chuckles ]
I tried to tell him that...
baseball's America's favorite
pastime, but he wasn't-
I called your offiice. They told me
where you were. I hope you don't mind.
How's your hand?
Better?
You look beautiful.
jane? [ Whispering ]
Excuse me just one moment.
jane, what's the ma-
Billy Chapel?
Yeah. So nice to fiinally
meet you. I'm Ian.
Ian the editor?
Yes, I guess so.
jane's told me
so much about you.
- So you're in town with the team?
- Yeah.
I saw you play against the Padres in the
World Series in the '80s when I worked in L.A.
- It was fantastic.
- You like baseball?
Yeah, sure.
May I?
[ Clicks ] So, do you
like the paintings?
No?
[ Chuckles ]
Would you excuse us? We're gonna
have a drink. Sure. Go ahead.
[ Sniffs ]
You don't smoke.
I do sometimes.
Billy,
you surprised me here.
I didn't know-
I w-
I have to go.
Well, let me walk you. Let
me give you a ride. I can't.
Why not? Because I came with someone.
What?
I came with Ian.
Richard, thank you for
coming. My pleasure.
You mean, like a date?
Are ya seein' him?
Yes.
I haven't seen you in fiive
months. You haven't called.
I called. What do you
- Three times in fiive months.
You knew what I was doing.
What about what I've been doing?
You have no idea what I've been
doing for the last fiive months.
You come in here, you insult
my friends, you embarrass me-
I didn't insult anybody. The prick asked
me if I liked the painting. I said I didn't.
And I didn't... [ Lowers Voice
] come in here to embarrass you.
I mean, you could've told me.
You could've said something.
Said what? Goddamn it, you
never just lay it out there.
Lay what out there?
That you hurt me?
Is that what you want?
How on
the plane ride home...
the flight attendant
had to ask me how I was?
How in the cab, I couldn't tell
the cab driver where I lived?
Or how I had to beg Heather
to sleep with me?
Is that what you want? Is that what
you want me to tell you? I'm sorry.
I'll tell you all about it. I'm sorry. I'm
sorry about what I said to you in the condo.
[ Panting ]
It's all right.
It doesn't matter
anymore.
I think maybe
that you and I...
are just not
the same kind of people.
I'm pitchin' tomorrow night at
Yankee Stadium. I want you to come.
No. No.
You and Heather.
Please, it's my fiirst game back.
I want you to be there. [ Sighs ]
I'll be watching you.
You know I'll always
be watching you.
just not from
the friends' box.
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
I don't miss
the good old days
I've learned a lot
since then
I've changed my ways
I'm not bothered
by those things that
Used to get me down
Only when you come around
I wish you'd
come around
Don't you come around
[ Crowd Cheering ] [ Scully ] The
Tigers with a 1 to nothing lead,
but the story would be the inability of
the Yankees to do anything with Chapel.
No runs, no hits, no errors,
but more importantly,
no base runners
of any kind.
Billy Chapel is looking a possible
perfect game right in the eye.
Billy Chapel all alone,
his teammates staying away.
They don't want to intrude
upon the zone.
[ Rock ]
[ Chattering ]
Shh!
You guys, please.
[ Scully ]... and Wheeler
now seeing the fruition...
of the hope and the long work
in the 19 years...
with six outs away.
[ Crowd Chanting ]
Let's go, Yankees!
How ya doin', ace?
Anybody been on base?
Nobody.
Nobody?
This I ain't seen much of.
Huh.
Me neither.
Chappie, I never have.
What's the matter?
I don't know if
I have anything left.
Chappie, you just throw
whatever you got,
whatever's left.
The boys are all here for ya.
We'll back ya up.
We'll be there.
'Cause, Billy,
we don't stink right now.
We're the best team in baseball right
now, right this minute, 'cause of you.
You're the reason.
We're not gonna screw that up.
We're gonna be awesome
for you right now.
just throw.
[ Mouths Words ]
All right?
Come on! Come on.
[ Scully ] Billy Chapel has
retired 21 consecutive batters,
striking out eight.
And as the fates would have it, one of
his closest friends and a former teammate,
Davis Birch, will try to snatch
the diamond away from him,
leading off in the bottom
of the eighth inning.
I once held her in my arms
She said she would
always stay
[ Scully ] Ball one, and
now the question, of course,
how much petrol has
Billy Chapel got in the tank?
Remember, it was just two innings
ago that he started to hurt,
the arm tightened up.
Somehow or other he got through it,
but now he is in the eighth inning,
facing a most dangerous hitter.
Once I had mountains
[ Scully ]
Ball two.
In the palm of my hands
And rivers that
ran through every day
I must have been mad
jim, get Stafford up.
I never knew what I had
Until I threw it all away
Frank. Hey, I can see the scoreboard.
I know what's goin' on, okay?
just in case.
It makes the world go round
Love and only love
It can't be denied
No matter what
you think about it
You just won't be able
to do without it
Don't question me.
Get him up here.
Take a tip from
one who's tried
[ Man ]
Retire! Retire!
So if you find someone
That gives you all of
her love [ Man ] Billy?
Billy, you can do it.
just calm down. Throw the ball
to the glove. just play catch.
For one thing for certain
You will surely be a-hurtin'
If you throw it all away
So a moment of truth- and he's had
several along the way- for Billy Chapel.
[ Scully ] 3 and 0. If
you throw it all away
[ Cheering Fades ]
[ Cheering Ceases ]
Strike one!
[ Cheering Resumes ]
[ Lyons ] You want to
see a big-time pitch?
When you consider the noise, the situation,
this stadium, that's unbelievable.
[ Chanting ]
Birch! Birch! Birch!
[ Chanting Continues,
Fades ]
[ Cheering Continues ]
[ Scully ] They put the
handcuffs on him, 3 and 0.
But he's such an aggressive hitter, you
know they're gonna green light him 3 and 1.
- There it goes!
- [ Crowd Cheering ]
[ Scully ] There's a high
drive into deep right field!
Back goes Mickey Hart
to the track at the wall...
and leaps up and one hands it!
Yeah! Yeah!
[ Group Shouting ]
- I love you, Mickey Hart!
- [ Booing ]
[ Scully ] He took a home
run away from Davis Birch,
and the perfecto
is still alive!
[ Lyons ] What a play by
Mickey Hart right here.
This is a ball right out over the
middle, and Birch just hammers it.
You got lucky again, Chapel.
That was a great play.
I'll miss you
the most, Scarecrow.
Ma'am? Are you coming?
[ Scully ] That will be the
fourth save so far in seven.
I'm sorry.
You'll have to board now.
[ Scully ] Howell grounded
out, lost a base hit.
Ma'am? Ma'am?
[ Scully ] The crowd on its
feet, exhorting, well, whom?
Give my seat
to somebody else.
Twenty-two consecutive outs
retired by Billy Chapel,
and he goes head-to-head
with Lenny Howell.
Fastball pulled to the right side. A
sliding stop by Marcus Ransom to get him.
- You're out!
- That's the second time today...
that Ransom has taken a base hit
away from Lenny Howell.
And now four outs away.
[ Lyons ] We haven't seen Billy Chapel go
this far into a game for a lot of starts now.
He looks very, very tired.
[ Scully ] The batter will be Ted
Franklin, the local boy from New York.
You know he wants to atone
for two strikeouts.
Gus!
[ Scully ] High twisting foul,
off to the right of the plate.
Sinski comin' back
and makes the play.
Chapel has done it for eight,
retiring 24 consecutive batters.
Billy Chapel is certainly getting more
than a little help from his friends.
It don't matter to the sun
If you go or if you stay Thanks.
Billy Chapel, right?
Right.
I took my kids to see
you play your rookie year.
Long time ago. You
were great. Thank you.
keep it up.
I'll be there in one minute.
Shine down on me
Billy?
Do you remember me?
Heather, sweetheart.
Oh, God. How are you?
I mean, what are you doin'
here? I'm going to U.S.C.
Really?
Yeah.
That's great.
Are you playing
the Angels or-
Yeah, here for the Angels.
And how's your season going? Okay.
Well, not so good really,
but, uh, it's almost over now.
How's your mom? [ Girl
] Heather! Hurry up.
She's good.
She's really good.
Heather!
Go.
I miss you.
I miss you too.
Like you did the day before
You don't have plans, do
you? [ Jane ] No, I don't.
Well, I'm gonna be there, and
it's been a while. A long time.
just thought dinner at the
Waldorf might be nice. About 6:00?
How about 8:00, your room? Even better.
Great. I'll see you then.
Mmm-hmm-hmm
Oh, no, oh, yeah
What can I say
What can I do
I'm still in love
So why aren't you
It don't matter to the moon
If you're not in my life
I knew it the day I fiirst
met you fiive years ago.
What? I've always known
it. You don't need me.
You and the ball and
the diamond, you're perfect.
You're a perfectly
beautiful thing.
You can win or lose the game
all by yourself.
Oh, babe
But it matters
To me
[ Man ] You feelin'healthy?
You're lookin'good.
How are you feelin'?
Your shoulder? All right?
'Cause I'm gonna
keep ya in there.
[ Crowd Cheering ]
Mike.
You all right, Billy?
Yeah.
Got a pen?
Oh, yeah.
I want you
to do me a favor.
I want you to give this
to Wheeler's nephew.
His nephew? Yeah, that
kid in the clubhouse.
Oh.
All right. Let's go, guys. Come on!
Let's go!
Let's go, guys. Come on.
Come on now!
What do ya say?
Three more!
Come on!
Nothing but tops out there!
jesus Christ.
[ Scully ] Billy Chapel is 40 years old as
he sits in the dugout here at Yankee Stadium.
Forty years old,
arm weary and aching.
And don't let anybody tell you
or Billy that life begins at 40.
4, 100 innings Billy Chapel
has walked to the mound...
in a brilliant,
19-year career.
But never before, in all those
years and in all those innings,
has he ever had a date with
destiny as he has right now.
He will make the fateful walk to
the loneliest spot in the world,
the pitching mound at Yankee Stadium
in quest of the pitcher's dream,
the perfect game.
Billy Chapel, in quest
of the perfect game.
You also realize he may very well be
at the crossroads of a brilliant career.
He's a cinch to wind up
in the Hall of Fame.
However, after this game,
he has to make the big decision.
A: Will he continue to do
what has been his life,
maybe more important
than life itself, baseball?
Or will he hang it up,
and would a perfect game...
give him the logical
conclusion to the great career?
Strout.
You're hitting for Ruiz.
Grab a bat.
[ Scully ] At 40 years old,
Billy Chapel is flirting...
with perhaps the greatest
accomplishment in baseball.
Standing in his way will be Matt
Crane hitting for Babe Nardini.
Then Jesus Cabrillo.
And Ken Strout has a bat
in his hands in the dugout...
and might very well get
the call to bat for Jaime Ruiz.
And, you know, Steve, you get
the feeling that Billy Chapel...
isn't pitching
against left-handers.
He isn't pitching
against pinch hitters.
against the Yankees.
He's pitching against time. He's pitching
against the future, against age...
and, even when you think about
his career, against ending.
And tonight, I think he might be able to
use that aching old arm one more time...
to push the sun
back up in the sky...
and give us
one more day of summer.
Lord, I know that
I always said...
that I'd never involve You
in a baseball game.
It always seemed silly.
I mean, You got enough to do.
[ Exhales ]
But if there's any way You could make
this pain in my shoulder go away...
for about ten minutes.
Clear the mechanism.
[ Cheering Quiets ]
[ Cheering Increases ]
[ Feet Stomping ]
[ Cheering, Stomping
Continue ]
Clear the mechanism.
[ Cheering Increases ]
Okay, okay.
Three more...
like I done a million times.
[ Lyons ] That's tough to come off the bench
and sit and watch eight innings of play...
and then go up there cold and
have to try and swing the bat.
But if you don't get your pitch
and hack at it early,
you might not see one
for the rest of the at bat.
[ Scully ]
Matt Crane poses quite a threat,
especially now when Billy
has to be on the ropes.
No, Gus. A curve
would hurt too much.
[ Scully ] Ground ball to the right side,
smothered back at third base by Lee Giordano...
- He's out!
- and throws him out!
[ Scully ] That would
be another brilliant play.
No! He beat it!
[ Scully ] Two more outs to
go, and here's Jesus Cabrillo,
who struck out
and flied to center.
It's been over 40 years
that I sat at Yankee Stadium...
and broadcast the perfect game
by Don Larson in the World Series,
and now I never thought
I'd be able to see another one,
especially from a 40-year-old pitcher who
may very well be at the end of his career.
Gus, goddamn it.
Gus, just hold it
over the middle of the plate.
I'm just throwin'
straight shit right now.
[ Scully ]
Big swing and the count 0 and 1.
What are you swingin' at? That
was a ball. This guy's a bum!
[ Groans ]
[ Scully ]
There's a drive down the line.
Foul!
What a scramble up there.
What used to be
just a souvenir...
might very well turn out
to be a very valuable baseball.
[ Booing ]
Oh, God.
[ Chapel ]
Yeah, I know, I'm stallin'.
Everybody knows I'm stallin'.
[ Booing ]
Maybe you'd be stallin' too.
[ Scully ] And there's a
strike three call. Strike!
Billy Chapel, striking out Jesus
Cabrillo for his ninth strikeout,
and he is one out away...
Ken.
from the perfect game.
- Wreck it.
- All right, skip.
[ Scully ]
On deck is young ken Strout,
who will take
his swings for Jaime Ruiz.
[ Man On P.A.] Batting for
Ruiz, number 60, ken Strout.
Why not?
[ Lyons ] This is a great move
by Bobby Mack, the Yankee skipper,
sendin'a kid up, ken Strout,
his first major league at bat.
He's just young enough and just
cocky enough to not realize...
the magnitude of
the situation that he's in.
[ Scully ] There's a line
drive down the right field line,
hooking foul!
And that was too close for comfort
for the Tigers and for Billy Chapel.
Well, I don't scare you
at all, do I, Strout?
Guess you forgot who I am.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, God.
Think Billy.
Don't just throw.
Think.
No, a curveball's for shit.
He knows it. I know it.
He knows it.
This is gonna hurt
a little bit.
[ Groans ]
Strike two! [ Scully
] What's that old line?
"If you can keep your head when
all about you are losing theirs,
you don't understand
the situation. "
That's kenny Strout right now as he takes
another strike. The count is 0 and 2.
And with a weary body
and, no doubt, a sore arm,
now this big crowd, over 56,000,
rooting for Billy Chapel...
to do the near impossible.
It's either gonna be
your night, kid, or mine.
[ Scully ] Will this be
the last pitch of the game?
Will this be the last pitch
in Billy Chapel's life?
Will it be the end of his
brilliant major league career?
And if so, what a high note!
0 and 2, the count
to kenny Strout.
Come on, Billy.
[ Scully ] High bouncer
off the glove of Chapel!
- He's out!
- [ Scully ] He has done it.
Billy Chapel has
pitched a perfect game.
The cathedral that is Yankee
Stadium belongs to a Chapel.
He was safe!
Ah, geez.
Nice job, Chapel.
Got to give it to ya. Nice job.
Come on. Perfect game.
I told ya, Billy!
Didn't I tell ya?
History, man!
All right. All right.
All right.
Oh, geez. You're
the cream in my coffee.
Ow! That's okay.
That's okay. You didn't know.
This is good right here. I'll just
stay right here. Come on, come on.
This is a good spot. Wait.
I gotta make a phone call.
Well, this is
- Where are we? Oh, all right.
All right. Oh!
[ Grunts ]
You need anything?
Some water.
Thank you, Chappie.
No problem.
No, no, not for the water.
I know.
Okay.
[ Door Closes ]
[ Phone Beeps,
Line Rings ]
[ Woman ] Hello. You've reached
the hotel message center.
There are no new messages. Thank you
for using the hotel message center.
Good-bye.
[ Crying ]
Oh, God.
I thought you
had already gone.
I missed my plane. I had to
stay at the airport hotel.
You missed your plane?
There was
this ball game on.
You saw it?
With a bunch
of Yankee fans.
Grown men crying.
It was... perfect.
Heather saw it too.
I called her at school. We were
both so proud of you, Billy.
What are you doing here?
I was- I was
on my way to England.
Why?
Because you're there.
God, I thought
- I thought I was gonna have an ocean...
to think about what I wanted to
say to you, what I needed to say.
Billy, you don't need to. Yes, I-
[ Groans ]
jane, I used to believe-
I mean, I still do...
that if you give something
your all, everything you have,
it doesn't matter
if you win or lose...
as long as you risked everything,
put everything out there.
And I've done that.
I did it in my life.
I did it... with the game.
But not with you.
I never gave you that,
and I'm sorry.
Okay. Preboarding announcement
for Oceanic Airways,
flight number seven to
London. I have to go.
All ticketed passengers
please proceed-
jane. I've already missed my plane once.
jane, listen.
I know I'm-
I know I'm really
on thin ice here, but...
when you said
that I didn't need you,
well, last night-
that should have been
the biggest night of my life,
and it wasn't.
It wasn't because-
because you weren't there.
So I just wanted
to tell you, not-
not to change your mind
or keep you from goin'.
But just so that you know-
[ Whispers ]
that I know...
that I need you.
I love you, Jane.
Oh.
I never believed.
Believe it.
Loving you
Makes me a better man
There's things
I don't know how to do
But you make me think I can
I got a long way to go
but I know what I know
Like the back of my hand
Loving you
Makes me a better man
I've been wrong
More than I care to say
Time after time
I've been lost
Just couldn't find my way
You shed a light on
a path through the night
Leading right to the site
where I stand
Loving you
Makes me a better man
Boy, you blow my mind
You can make me crazy
You make me laugh You make me
cry keepin'my heart shook up
I'm so mesmerized, you're
the one who can save me
So say good-bye
Don't lead a lie
I think it's time
for the breakup
Baby, you're
my main attraction
Settin'off
this chain reaction
Just a little is enough Just
the thought of your touch
That's the fun of your love
I la love, baby
Oh, oh, oh, yeah
The feeling inside That's
the thrill of the ride
That's the fun of your love
I la love, baby
Oh, oh, oh
Let the days unwind
Let the dreams come true
Happy ever after, baby
In your heart you'll find
I'll be there for you
Just a little's enough Just
the thought of your touch
That's the fun of your love
I la love, baby
Oh, oh, oh, yeah
The feelin'inside That's
the thrill of the ride
That's the fun of your love
I la love, baby
Oh, oh
That's the fun of it, baby
To, to, to ya
Ooh
That's the fun of it, baby
Baby, baby, baby
I see you in
a different light
Candlelight, moonlight
I see you in a different way
through different eyes
You're so nice
I see you like
I never seen you before
The way I want
to see you much more
For tonight
Tonight
I see you in
a different light
When did your kisses
get so sweet, baby
Babe
It's such a sweet surprise
You made me
To look into your eyes
Oh, I see you
in a different light
In a different light
Candlelight, moonlight
I see you in a different way
In a different light
You're so nice
I see you like I never seen you
before Like I never seen you before
The way I want
to see you much more
Baby, tonight, for tonight
See you tonight
I see you in
a different light
Candlelight, moonlight
Moonlight, candlelight
In a different light
to see you in my eyes
Oh, baby, I see you
I see you
I see you, I see you
Like I never, never, never
seen you before
Oh, oh
I'm still seein'you, baby
I see you in
a different light
I see you, baby