Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
23.976
"4.5 inches by 4.0 inches."
And they got it in centimeters or whatever.
It's the same shit on the back. All right?
- Good night.
- Good night, Larry.
- Yeah.
- Thank you very much.
What are your friends like?
- I don't really have friends.
- Who do you hang out with?
Nobody.
Why do I think you're not exaggerating?
I just keep to myself.
I go about my business, you know.
Do my work.
A charming, loveable guy like yourself?
You should get out more.
I'm sure there's a ton of straight women
who you could make very happy.
Louis wants us to cut the kid's thumb off.
I'd like to give shouts to all my homies.
Mrs. Friedman. Lily.
Mr. Mossman
and the man he plays cards with.
Forgot his name.
And all my peeps at Wilshire Adult Care.
Everybody in the cafeteria. Big ups!
What's up to my man Larry. And Ricki.
Yo, yo, yo. Peace, G.
And the rec room.
I got neighbors, you know.
Dígame sabrosa.
- What's that?
- It's "español".
What does it mean?
I don't know.
See that?
Don't be a playa hater, G.
- Yeah?
- Who the fuck are you?
Who the fuck are you?
Excuse me.
What a shithole!
- Lady, I think you're in the wrong place.
- You are in the wrong place.
All right? You're in the wrong place.
You have no idea.
And who the fuck are you?
- You're the fuck are you.
- What?
What are you doing here?
- I'm stalking you.
- Wait, you know her?
First of all,
do not say my name in this room. All right?
Second of all, you're out of line.
This is a professional situation
and you have no right to intrude.
What kind of professional situation?
I can't believe this.
A fucking man?
Okay. I really thought
this was all about Sharon.
- Are you telling people where we are?
- Mind your own business.
- Shut the fuck up.
- Blow me.
Listen, both of you shut up.
Look, I haven't told anybody where we are.
And, Robin...
this is a professional situation.
Our problems
have nothing to do with Sharon...
and they have nothing to do with him.
- I want you to leave right now! Please.
- No!
I'm not leaving, he's leaving.
What? Who the fuck do you think you are?
- I fucking live here. I'm not going anywhere.
- Yeah?
Neither am I. Going to be all there is to that.
- Why are you doing this?
- What if I throw you out?
What if I roundhouse you upside
your fat head and collapse your skull.
- I don't know. Give it a shot.
- Don't. She knows how to do that stuff.
- Don't be macho.
- I don't give a fuck.
This isn't lesbian talk-circle time.
We got something to do.
- You're getting the fuck out. Got it?
- I mean, this? You need this?
You need a little freedom or something?
You want to dabble? We can all fuck.
We can all have sex together, that's fine.
What do you say, Hot Rocks?
- Would you like it?
- You're out of your mind.
- You know you want it.
- Our situation has nothing to do with him.
It's over.
- It's not him. It's us, honey.
- Right, it's not you, it's her. Get the...
Just shut up for one second! God! Fuck!
This has nothing to do with him.
- It's just, we're over.
- No, we're not over.
We'll set up together, the three of us,
till you get this out of your system.
- Baby, you're not hearing me.
- I'm fucking hearing you. Okay?
God damn it!
See, I'm going to kill myself right now
and you care...
- That's a nice girl.
- Shut the fuck up, all right!
- What the fuck is that?
- What did you...
No.
- What did you do?
- Is this hot enough for you?
- Get away.
- You want some?
Get away. What's wrong with you?
- Oh, my God.
- What the fuck is this?
Lady, you need some Band-Aids.
This must be Mental-fucking-lllness Week.
That woman is fucking beautiful.
Yes.
She's like the ones at the Baywatch.
They make my penis sneeze.
You got a good sense of humor,
you know that?
God bless you.
- Thank you.
- No, not you, stupid.
When my penis sneezes,
I say, "God bless you.
"God bless you, penis."
She's going to be okay.
What a relief.
Brian, would you excuse us?
I want to talk to Larry for a minute. Okay?
- You'll be all right in the car?
- Yeah.
Okay, good.
I just...
I got to tell you,
I'm not up for this thumb deal.
I say we don't do it.
You trying to test me?
Is that it? You wanna see
if I'm gonna do what I'm supposed to do?
No.
So, what are you,
a contractor with a conscience?
Look, I've done some bad things...
but I didn't sign on to this
to be a brutal street thug.
Because, as far as I'm concerned,
that's not the job I took.
How would you get around it?
I'd work it out.
But first I got to know, are you with me?
Sure.
Sure or yes?
- That's the same thing.
- No, it's not the same thing.
See, if I were to ask you to move my couch
for me you'd probably say, "Sure."
But if I were to ask you
to look deep into my eyes...
and tell me from the bottom of your heart...
if it would give you great pleasure
if I were to suck your cock for 12 hours...
if I may be presumptuous,
you'd probably say, "Yes."
See, it just implies
a different level of commitment.
Ask me the question again.
Okay. Are you with me?
Yes.
Yeah? Good.
Isn't this B level?
This is D level. You shouldn't be here.
I'm looking for B level.
This is a D level and no one is allowed here.
You need to go back to B level.
Hold on.
Because you're confusing me, okay?
You're confusing me.
Let's just start from the beginning.
If this isn't B...
Oh, my God.
- I am so sorry.
- That's okay.
Just soak that in cold water
and it'll come right out, okay?
I promise you. Yes. No, it will.
The thing is, the reason I'm here
is they told me to go around the corner...
- Close your eyes.
- What?
Close your eyes. Follow me.
Just walk in. Don't look.
Come on. Go. You're fine.
- Can I open them?
- No. Stand right here.
- It's cold in here.
- Don't look at nothing. All right?
- Can I open them?
- No.
Stay turned around.
Smells like my grandmother's.
- What was that?
- It's nothing.
I like big butts and I cannot lie
The other brothers can't deny
When the girls walk in
with an itty-bitty waist
And round things in your face
You get sprung, wanna pull up tough
'Cause you notice that butt was stuffed
'Cause I'm long, and I'm strong
And I'm down to get the friction on
So, ladies, yeah
Ladies, yeah
If you wanna roll in my Mercedes
Yeah
So turn around! Stick it out!
Even white boys got to shout
Baby got back!
That's an old-school song.
You're old-school, too, Larry.
We got an item that we want
to package ourselves and, you know...
- Mail out.
- Okay.
Could we just get an envelope from you?
What size would you like?
- Just the top, right...
- 6 by 9.
So all right.
We're done, right?
That's it.
Thanks.
Would you like your parcel insured?
No, that's all right.
I'll be right back.
Friend of yours?
Close, personal.
You know something?
You're right. It is sadness.
I'm fucking sad. You got me.
You're a genius.
You know why I'm fucking sad?
Because I got this fucking...
beautiful, sexy, gorgeous...
heartthrob-o-rama,
fucking smart, amazing bombshell...
17-on-a-fucking-10-scale girl...
sleeping in a bed, right next to me.
And you know what?
She's a stone-cold dyke.
A fucking untouchable...
unhaveable, unattainable brick wall...
fucking Dykeasaurus Rexi.
So it's sad, okay?
What do you want me to do?
I feel fucking sadness about that.
There's nothing I can fucking do.
And not only is she a major babe...
but I really like this girl a lot.
A lot.
She's not like anybody else
I ever knew before...
and that's a completely fucking new one
on me.
I don't even know her real fucking name.
So there you go.
And in case you're interested, my life sucks.
All right? Stick a fork in me, I'm done.
Clean the bar all you like.
I'm just going to puke on it again.
- Oh, you got me.
- Oh! I got you!
Do you think your fingernails
need trimming?
They're fine.
What? You don't like my fingernails now?
Look, I have no idea if this is true or not,
but I've heard it said...
that those who are balanced
more toward the masculine of either sex...
check their fingernails this way.
And those balanced more toward
the feminine check them that way.
I had a feeling that even though
you have this tough guy thing going on...
that you are wrestling
with some very strong feminine leanings.
That's fucking bullshit.
I can't see. I'm farsighted.
Nearsighted, whatever it is.
So I hold them out here
but I can't see them up close.
To find out how somebody's
balanced toward a masculine, look at me.
I can't see. That's why I hold them far away.
- All right.
- Yeah, it is all right.
No, all right.
I was gonna do this. That's what I wanna do.
But I know I can't see
so I hold them out there to look at them.
All right.
Don't give me that look.
I see you looking at me.
- Are you gay?
- What the fuck.
No. I'm not gay!
Why do you look at me and think I'm gay?
I'm not fucking gay!
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm fucking sure.
You know what, I bet you're right.
- Thank you.
- It wasn't a compliment.
Ricki, whatever your real name is,
all right, this is my eyes.
Look how I'm acting.
You're driving me crazy.
You give me a fucking headache.
I don't even know why I had a crush on you,
back a long time ago when I first met you...
that you really cured me of.
I don't know.
Maybe it's because you know
I can kick your ass.
Maybe that turns you on.
You cannot kick my ass.
What?
You need a woman.
I got one.
Stop.
Kiss me again.
I thought you wanted to be my bitch.
This is so fucked up.
- Where you going?
- It's turkey time.
Gobble, gobble.
What?
Now, you talk the talk...
you know I'm expecting
you to walk the walk. Come on.
Show me what I've been missing
my whole life.
Lay some of that sweet "heterolingus"
on me.
I think...
to be serious...
I just... You know, I think...
I was thinking, you know,
and you were right...
when you said probably,
actually a woman might know more...
about what feels better to another woman.
She's a woman herself.
A guy might be at a certain disadvantage.
You know, like...
It's like, you need a handicap.
You know, like golf.
Shut up and get over here.
God bless you, penis.
What'd you say?
Nothing.
Every relationship has a bull and a cow?
That's right.
Just to be up front about all this...
when this gig is over...
I want you to know
that I'm going to be leaving.
Listen...
you and Trixie over there,
meet me at Beverly and Lomitas.
Louis, what's going on?
And don't bring the thing.
- The what?
- The thing. Don't bring it.
What thing?
The thing. Don't bring... Don't bring it.
- You mean the...
- Yeah. Don't bring it.
You leave it somewhere safe
for the time being.
- All right.
- You understand?
- Yeah, I understand.
- And hurry up, jackass.
What?
It's Louis. Fucking pissed.
See this? Some cookies in there.
Be back.
- When are you coming back?
- Soon.
- Just relax, eat your breakfast. Okay?
- I'm not hungry, though.
Well, you can't skip breakfast.
It's a very important meal. All right?
Don't go nowhere. Don't touch nothing.
- Don't make phone calls. I'm not kidding.
- All right, Larry.
All right. See you later.
- Bye, Ricki.
- Bye, Brian.
- What?
- Nothing.
You know, I got this fantasy.
About making it with a guy?
No.
That's not it.
Going somewhere, you know,
like, somewhere really...
clean.
- Clean?
- Yeah.
No scumbags telling you what to do.
Nobody yelling at you all the time.
Someplace you could just be.
Be yourself.
No bad stuff.
That sounds good.
- What's up?
- We have a visitor from New York.
Follow me.
Hello.
- Welcome. Nice to meet you.
- Hello, sir.
Finally. Nice to meet you, too.
Come. Look at you. Beautiful.
Come on in. Here. Grab a couch.
Sit, sit.
I say everything twice. In, in. Sit, sit.
I'm so glad you could come...
on such a short notice, too.
Thank you, I really appreciate it.
I really... I thank you.
I appreciate it. Here, I've got some stuff.
I'm sorry if I'm a bit of a mess,
but I just got in a few hours ago.
I'm sure Louis told you,
you know, I'm having...
some little legal problems
out here right now.
What are you gonna do? It's a nuisance,
but what are you going to do?
I got to fight it, right?
I mean, I can't go to jail.
That just can't happen.
I'm used to the finer things.
- Louis, am I right?
- You are right.
It can't be. So I think we can say...
beyond a shadow of a doubt,
that it's not gonna happen.
Somewhere a mistake has been made.
Did you know...
that apparently some people...
do not regard the thumb,
technically, to be a finger?
Curious for myself, I turned to Louis here...
who with his newfound dictionary skills
looked it up for me.
- You know what it said?
- No.
Tell him what it said, Louis.
It said, quote:
"The short, thick, inner digit of the hand
next to the forefinger." Unquote.
Now it said, "digit," not "finger."
So I still don't really know, technically,
if it's considered a finger or not.
- Right?
- Right.
Right. Look at him. I love him.
I love this guy. He eats no matter what.
I love you, Louis.
What's this?
What is this? Louis.
I've been subpoenaed.
I can't be consorting with armed felons.
A little consideration, please.
Besides, you think something like this
is necessary...
anyway, to intimidate people?
I say intimidation comes from within.
There are a multitude of qualities
an individual can possess...
that make them intimidating.
Not only this, this is the outside.
Then there's the inside.
But you know
what's the most intimidating quality?
Not that you asked.
But the absolutely most intimidating
in my opinion?
When an individual just doesn't give a shit.
- Louis, you want to go to medical school?
- Medical school?
Yes!
Students there
can always use something to learn on.
I feel like I'm floating.
I feel...
released.
I don't give a shit.
I don't.
I have no compunctions...
none whatsoever.
And I am very concerned...
about the way things have turned out here.
How was the bleeding?
The bleeding?
No, not him.
The retard, when you cut his thumb off.
Louis told me you were concerned.
Bleeding was fine.
Fine?
It was all right.
Okay. Good.
I didn't need your help, you know.
I could have beaten these charges.
What were you thinking?
You were gonna extort a federal prosecutor.
You thought you could say:
"Kidnapped your little brother,
drop all charges," and the guy'd roll over?
You didn't think
all hell wouldn't break loose?
You didn't think every fucking fed...
wouldn't drop what they were doing...
and dive in to protect one of their own?
What do you morons think...
this is Little Italy?
Wake up!
This is the twenty-fucking-first century!
So now...
things are bad.
And whether you wanna call a thumb...
a finger or a digit...
for the sake of this discussion,
it doesn't really matter.
You know why?
Because whatever you choose to call it...
a thumb...
has a fingerprint...
and the one you sent...
had the wrong fucking one.
- Mr. Starkman...
- I know my fucking name...
you piece of shit!
You don't try to extort...
a federal fucking prosecutor!
And if you do...
you don't fuck around!
Fuck this.
Cutting off his thumb was a stupid order.
We would have been derelict
in our responsibilities if we had followed it.
Hello.
How long could we have kept below radar...
with a thumbless, bleeding half-wit?
You see, sometimes...
one has to use
their professional prerogative...
to override a dumb request.
With all due respect...
even at this point if you were to ask us...
to pursue a course of action that would be...
let's say, contrary to your best interests...
then as awkward as it might be...
we would have to take exception.
Aside from those of us in this room...
there's only one person, really,
that can link you to this fuckup.
And I feel that we should...
rectify that problem as soon as we can.
I think I'd much prefer just to...
you know...
end it right here.
And that would be
your professional prerogative.
If you think that having
that kid picked up by the authorities...
and telling them all about being kidnapped
in an attempt to save your ass makes sense.
If you think that's the best tactic
to keep you out of jail.
If you think that's any less dumb
than asking to have his finger cut off...
well, then that would be
the thing that you should do.
But if you don't...
then let us take the thorn out of your side.
Let us make sure that kid will never be
able to testify against anybody.
And if after that you're still not happy...
then we can all talk again.
- You were kidding, right?
- What do you think?
We'll take Brian back
to where you found him and get out of here.
Are we going to the Baywatch now?
No, we can't go to the Baywatch now.
Take you later.
Maybe this is it. Maybe this is the thing.
Maybe this is a sign coming from nowhere,
from out of the blue...
just telling me it's time. It's time to get out.
It's time to do it.
When I'm alone in my room
Sometimes I stare at the wall
and in the back of my mind
I hear my conscience call
telling me I need a girl
who's as sweet as a dove
For the first time in my life I see
I need love
So if you know who you are
why don't you make yourself seen
take a chance with my love
you'll find out what I mean
I need love
Let me ask you something.
You got a girlfriend?
No, I don't.
Let me do something for you.
You know, make up for all the problems
I caused you.
Because I see you're a little nervous
around women. Right?
Let me tell you something. You got
no reason to be shy. There's no magic to it.
Let me tell you this thing that I heard,
and I'm starting to believe that it's true.
You know?
It's that the thing
you're most afraid of in life...
if you do it, if you step up,
good things will happen.
You see a girl that you like
that you're scared to talk to...
bro, step up.
Go up to her and say:
"Hi, how are you today?
Nice weather we're having."
Take it from there,
wherever the conversation goes. You try it.
Try it with me. Practice. Go ahead.
Hello, how are you today?
Try it with me. Go ahead. Just say it.
Come on, Brian. Hello.
How are you today?
"How are you today?"
Nice weather we're having.
"Nice weather we're having."
There you go. You see how he did it?
It's because you stepped up, Brian.
If you're afraid, step up and good things
start to happen. Am I right?
- I stepped up.
- Step it up, pimp.
That's how you move. Step it up.
So, now that we're partners in crime...
how about telling me your real name.
The reason that I ask that...
is because I don't know
if you gave it any thought since last night...
but I've been thinking about it.
And seeing... You know, looks like
now we're both going to be leaving.
So I thought, you know...
All right, look.
I'm gonna lay it all out there for you
right now.
I'm just gonna say it,
because, you know, here I am.
- I think...
- Larry.
You know I haven't done
this kind of thing hardly ever.
The whole man thing...
doesn't really
hold that much for me, usually.
I know.
But somehow you got through.
Somehow.
But in the end...
I don't think
I could ever be what you really want.
- So where do you think you'll go?
- I don't know.
Somewhere clean.
You know, Northern California...
Oregon maybe.
You could just drop me off
near the Pacific Coast Highway...
- and I'll figure it out from there.
- Okay.
After that, Brian,
I think it's gonna be time to go home.
We just left there a little while ago, though.
I don't mean my apartment.
I mean, you know, the place where you live.
Where I got you.
What, you mean to stay?
Yeah, buddy. To stay.
Oh, my God.
- It's open. Oh, my God.
- What are you doing? Sit down.
- Oh, my God. I'm gonna go.
- Brian, what?
- What's he talking about?
- They're open.
They're open. Oh, my God. The Baywatch.
They're open!
- Cowabunga!
- Oh, my God.
That's the Baywatch?
It's open. It's the Baywatch.
Hello there!
I can't believe this.
- I can't believe. Stop.
- We can't stop now.
No, we have to stop!
No, Larry, no! They're here. We're here.
I know. We can't, though. I'm sorry.
We can't stop.
- We're here. Come on.
- We're here.
- We're right here.
- Brian.
Wait. That's it. We're right here.
Wait a second.
Wait. So turn around now, okay?
All right.
What do you think?
- Can I go down there?
- Brian, you can't go down there, no.
I mean, we're not allowed down there.
Plus, we got to go soon.
Please? Please, can I go down there?
You know, Brian, I don't even think...
This might not even be the Baywatch.
I think this is probably something else.
Larry, you promised me.
You promised me.
- It's right there.
- I know.
Just for five minutes?
Brian, what's your brother's name?
My brother's name is stinky Jimmy Dorf.
Want to know why?
Yeah, some other time, I do.
Yeah, Los Angeles. The U.S. Courthouse.
The office of a James Dorf.
- Because... Do you want to know why?
- Yeah.
Because sometimes he smells like fish.
No, I don't think so.
Yeah, I'll give you my name.
Give me a minute. Hold on. I forgot it.
Brian, look at me.
I think your brother and his friends
are gonna be here soon to pick you up.
Okay?
I want you to know something.
You're a good kid.
I'm sorry about all the...
I'm sorry for being...
I'm sorry.
I think you're wrong.
I think that is the Baywatch right there.
Who knows. Maybe it is.
I'm a genius, man. I knew it.
You take good care of yourself, Brian.
You take good care of yourself, Larry.
I'll do that.
Brian, let me ask you something.
How do your fingernails look?
- My fingernails?
- Your fingernails, how are they looking?
- Don't say nothing.
- They look very good.
I got A-plus nails.
- I give an A-plus for fingernails.
- Never mind. Okay. Good.
Go ahead.
Go on.
I don't know how you're thinking
about getting out of here or whatever...
what your plans are...
but I think you should take my car.
Go ahead, take it. Take it.
I couldn't do that, Larry.
I'd rather...
You know, I'd prefer if you had it.
It's a good car,
and I want you to be all right.
And I know that
it'll get you wherever you need to go.
So just, you know, take it.
I was thinking
about getting rid of it anyway.
I'm trying to change my image.
Go ahead, take it.
Please.
Okay.
- I will, thank you.
- Don't mention it.
Just do me one favor, though.
Name it.
As far as the lesbian thing goes...
Yeah?
...if you do ever think
about hopping the fence...
promise you'll give me a call first.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, listen up.
Camera is ready and picture is up.
I need all dancers to first position
as soon as possible.
All dancers to first position
as soon as possible. Let's go.
Okay, listen up, guys.
Can we please finish pairing up, everyone?
Come on, guys,
it's not like you're mating for life.
As the old song goes. ;
"just love the one you're with."
Find someone to love.
Come on, Brian. Dance with someone.
Nice weather we're having.
Yes, it's very nice.
It is?
Yes. But the weather's always very nice
around here, isn't it?
Yes.
And a 10% chance of precipitation
for low-lying coastal regions...
extending from New South Wales to Victoria.
And playback.
And action.
Rochelle.
What?
Rochelle. That's my real name.
So, Rochelle...
does this mean
you decided to hop the fence?
I wouldn't go that far.
But I figured
since I helped get you into all this...
the least I could do
is offer you a ride out of town.
Fair enough.
What?
You know,
I bet you'd look awesome in some mascara.
- I'm not sure how to take that.
- It's a compliment.
Yeah?
Like your mother said,
life's not always black-and-white.
Sometimes you just never know.
Are you driving or bullshitting?
I'm driving.
I like big butts and I cannot lie
The other brothers can't deny
When the girls walk in
with an itty-bitty waist
And round things in your face
You get sprung, wanna pull up tough
'Cause you noticed that butt was stuffed
'Cause I'm long, and I'm strong
And I'm down to get the friction on
So, ladies, yeah
Ladies, yeah
If you wanna roll in my Mercedes
Yeah
So turn around! Stick it out!
Even white boys got to shout
Baby got back!
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org