Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Sir.
- General.
Sir.
Lean and hungry.
- Still nothing?
- Not a sign.
- How long has he been gone?
- Nearly two hours.
- Will they fight, sir?
- We shall know soon enough.
Soldier, I ordered you
to move those catapults forward.
- They're out of range.
- Range is good.
- The danger to the cavalry...
- Is acceptable. Agreed?
They say no.
Steady! Steady!
People should know
when they're conquered.
Would you, Quintus?
Would I?
- Strength and honor.
At my signal,
unleash hell.
Load the catapults.
Infantry form up for advance.
- Archers ready.
- Archers!
Fratres!
Maximus!
Three weeks from now,
I will be harvesting my crops.
Imagine where you will be,
and it will be so.
Hold the line!
Stay with me!
If you find yourself alone...
riding in green fields
with the sun on your face...
do not be troubled.
For you are in Elysium,
and you're already dead!
Brothers...
what we do in life...
echoes in eternity.
Pull!
Pull! Pull!
Catapults ready, sir!
Archers, ignite!
- Ignite!
Archers, draw!
Loose!
All right, men, ready!
Hold the line!
Draw! Loose!
Loose! Loose!
Reload!
Hold the line!
Draw! Loose!
Stay with me!
Roma victor!
Do you think
he's really dying?
He's been dying
for ten years.
If he weren't really dying,
he wouldn't have sent for us.
Maybe he just misses us.
And the senators?
He wouldn't have summoned them if...
Peace, Commodus.
After two weeks on the road, your
incessant scheming is hurting my head.
He's made his decision.
He's going to announce it.
He will name me.
The first thing I shall do...
when...
is honor him with games
worthy of His Majesty.
For now, the first thing
I shall do is have a hot bath.
Your Highness?
We seem to be
almost there, sir.
- Sire.
- Where's the emperor?
He's at the front, sire.
They've been gone for 19 days.
The wounded are
still coming in.
My horse.
My lord.
Kiss?
You have proved your valor
yet again, Maximus.
Let us hope
for the last time.
There's no one
left to fight, sire.
There is always
someone left to fight.
How can I reward
Rome's greatest general?
Let me go home.
Ah. Home.
They honor you, Caesar.
It's for you, Maximus.
They honor you.
Have I missed it?
Have I missed the battle?
You have missed the war.
Father, congratulations.
I shall sacrifice a hundred bulls
to honor your triumph.
Save the bulls.
Honor Maximus.
He won the battle.
- General.
- Highness.
Rome salutes you,
and I embrace you as a brother.
It has been too long,
my old friend.
- Highness.
- Here, Father.
Take my arm.
I think it is time
for me to leave.
So much for
the glory of Rome.
Magnificent battle.
- General.
- Still alive?
- Still alive.
- The gods must have a sense of humor.
- The gods must love you.
- Valerius.
Back to barracks, General?
Or to Rome?
Home. My wife,
the son, the harvest.
Maximus the farmer.
I still have difficulty imagining that.
You know, dirt cleans off a lot
easier than blood, Quintus.
- Here he is.
- Highness.
Senator Gaius, Senator Falco.
Beware of Gaius. He'll pour
a honeyed potion in your ear...
and you'll wake up one day and all
you'll say is, "Republic, republic".
Well, why not?
Rome was founded as a republic.
Yes, and in a republic
the senate has the power.
But Senator Gaius isn't
influenced by that, of course.
Where do you stand, General?
Emperor or senate?
A soldier has the advantage
of being able...
to look his enemy
in the eye, Senator.
Well, with an army behind you,
you could be extremely political.
I warned you.
Now I shall save you. Senators.
Maximus.
I'm going to need
good men like you.
How may I be of service,
Highness?
You're a man who knows
what it is to command.
You give your orders, the orders
are obeyed and the battle is won.
But these senators scheme and squabble
and flatter and deceive.
Maximus, we must save Rome
from the politicians, my friend.
Can I count on you
when the time comes?
Highness, when your father releases me,
I intend to return home.
Home? Well, no one's earned it more.
Don't get too comfortable.
I may call on you before long.
Lucilla's here.
Did you know?
She's not forgotten you.
And now you're the great man.
If only you
had been born a man.
What a caesar
you would have made!
Father.
You would have been strong.
I wonder,
would you have been just?
I would have been
what you taught me to be.
How was your journey?
Long. Uncomfortable.
Why have I come?
I need your help.
With your brother.
Of course.
He loves you.
He always has.
And...
he will need you now
more than ever.
Enough of politics.
Let us pretend that
you are a loving daughter...
and I am a good father.
This is a pleasant fiction,
isn't it?
Good morning.
I need three more horses.
Two! Three!
Four!
One! Two!
You sent for me, Caesar?
- Caesar?
- Tell me again, Maximus.
Why are we here?
For the glory of the empire, sire.
Ah, yes.
Ah, yes, I remember.
Do you see that map, Maximus?
That is the world
which I created.
For 25 years...
I have conquered, spilt blood,
expanded the empire.
Since I became caesar,
I've known four years without war.
Four years of peace in 20.
And for what?
I brought the sword.
Nothing more.
Caesar, your life...
Please.
Please don't call me that.
Come. Please.
Come sit.
Let us talk together now...
very simply... as men.
Maximus, talk.
Five thousand of my men are
out there in the freezing mud.
Three thousand of them
are bloodied and cleaved.
Two thousand will never
leave this place.
I will not believe that they
fought and died for nothing.
And what would you believe?
They fought for you and for Rome.
And what is Rome?
I've seen much
of the rest of the world.
It is brutal and cruel and dark.
Rome is the light.
Yet you have
never been there.
You have not seen
what it has become.
I am dying, Maximus.
When a man sees his end...
he wants to know there was
some purpose to his life.
How will the world speak my name
in years to come?
Will I be known
as the philosopher?
The warrior?
The tyrant?
Or will I be the emperor who
gave Rome back her true self?
There was once a dream
that was Rome.
You could only whisper it.
Anything more than a whisper
and it would vanish...
it was so fragile.
And I fear that it will not
survive the winter.
Maximus...
let us whisper now...
together, you and I.
You have a son.
Tell me about your home.
My house is in the hills
above Trujillo. A very simple place.
Pink stones
that warm in the sun.
A kitchen garden that
smells of herbs in the day...
jasmine in the evening.
Through the gate
is a giant poplar.
Figs, apples, pears.
The soil, Marcus... black.
Black like my wife's hair.
Grapes on the south slopes,
olives on the north.
Wild ponies play near my house.
They tease my son. He wants to be one.
- Remember the last time you were home?
- Two years, 264 days and this morning.
I envy you, Maximus.
It's a good home.
Worth fighting for.
There is one more duty...
that I ask of you
before you go home.
What would you
have me do, Caesar?
I want you to become
the protector of Rome after I die.
I will empower you
to one end alone...
to give power back
to the people of Rome...
and end the corruption
that has crippled it.
Will you accept this great honor
that I have offered you?
With all my heart, no.
Maximus...
that is why it must be you.
But surely a prefect,
a senator...
somebody who knows the city,
who understands her politics.
But you have not been
corrupted by her politics.
- And Commodus?
- Commodus is not a moral man.
You have known that
since you were young.
Commodus cannot rule.
He must not rule.
You are the son
that I should have had.
Commodus will accept my decision.
He knows that you command
the loyalty of the army.
I need some time, sire.
Yes.
By sunset,
I hope you will have agreed.
Now embrace me as my son.
And bring an old man
another blanket.
- My father favors you now.
- My lady.
- It was not always so.
- Many things change.
Many things.
Not everything.
Maximus, stop.
Let me see your face.
- You seem upset.
- I lost many men.
What did my father
want with you?
To wish me well
before I leave for home.
You're lying.
I could always tell when you were lying
because you were never any good at it.
- I never acquired your comfort with it.
- True.
But then you never had to.
Life is more simple
for a soldier.
Or do you think me heartless?
I think you have
a talent for survival.
Maximus, stop.
Is it really so terrible
seeing me again?
No. I'm tired from battle.
It hurts you to see
my father so fragile.
Commodus expects that my father will
announce his succession within days.
Will you serve my brother
as you served his father?
I will always serve Rome.
Do you know...
I still remember you
in my prayers.
Oh, yes. I pray.
I was sad to hear
of your husband's death. I mourned him.
- Thank you.
- And I hear you have a son.
Yes. Lucius.
He'll be nearly
eight years old.
My son is also nearly eight.
I thank you for your prayers.
Ancestors, I ask
for your guidance.
Blessed Mother, come to me
with the gods' desire for my future.
Blessed Father, watch over
my wife and son with a ready sword.
Whisper to them I live
only to hold them again.
Ancestors, I honor you...
and will try to live with
the dignity you have taught me.
Cicero.
Sir.
You don't find it hard
to do your duty?
Sometimes I do
what I want to do.
The rest of the time
I do what I have to.
We may not be able
to go home after all.
Are you ready to do
your duty for Rome?
Yes, Father.
You will not be emperor.
Which wiser, older man
is to take my place?
My powers
will pass to Maximus...
to hold in trust...
until the senate
is ready to rule once more.
Rome is to be
a republic again.
- Maximus.
- Yes.
My decision disappoints you?
You wrote to me once...
listing the four chief virtues.
Wisdom, justice...
fortitude...
and temperance.
As I read the list,
I knew I had none of them.
But I have other virtues, Father.
Ambition.
That can be a virtue
when it drives us to excel.
Resourcefulness.
Courage.
Perhaps not on
the battlefield, but...
there are many forms of courage.
Devotion to my family...
and to you.
But none of my virtues
were on your list.
Even then it was as if
you didn't want me for your son.
You go too far.
I searched the faces
of the gods...
for ways to please you,
to make you proud.
One kind word...
one full hug...
where you pressed me
to your chest and held me tight...
would have been like the sun
on my heart for a thousand years.
What is it in me
you hate so much?
All I've ever wanted...
was to live up to you, Caesar.
- Father.
- Commodus.
Your fault as a son...
is my failure as a father.
Come.
Father.
I would butcher
the whole world...
if you would only have loved me!
Maximus, the emperor needs you.
It's urgent.
Lament with me, brother.
Our great father is dead.
How did he die?
The surgeons say
there was no pain.
His breath gave out as he slept.
Father.
Your emperor asks
for your loyalty, Maximus.
Take my hand.
I only offer it once.
Quintus.
Hail, Caesar.
I must talk to the senators.
I need their counsel.
Wake Gaius and Falco.
- Sword.
Maximus, please be careful.
That was not prudent.
Prudent?
The emperor has been slain.
The emperor died
of natural causes.
- Why are you armed, Quintus?
- Guards!
Please don't fight, Maximus.
I'm sorry.
Caesar has spoken.
Ride until dawn...
and then execute him.
Quintus, look at me.
Look at me!
Promise me that you will
look after my family.
Your family will meet you
in the afterlife.
Kneel.
Blessed Father,
watch over my wife and son.
Whisper to them that I live
only to hold them again.
At least give me a clean death.
A soldier's death.
The frost, sometimes
it makes the blade stick.
Praetorian!
- Remember the last time you were home?
- Two years, 264 days and this morning.
Blessed Father, watch over
my wife and son with a ready sword.
Whisper to them I live only to hold them
again, for all else is dust and air.
Whisper to them
I live only to hold them again...
for all else is dust and air.
Papa! Papa!
Don't die.
You'll meet them again.
Not yet.
No. They will clean it.
Wait and see.
Don't die.
They'll feed you to the lions.
They are worth more than we are.
Better now?
Clean. You see?
Proximo!
My old friend.
Every day is a great day
when you are here...
but today
is your most fortunate day.
Those giraffes you sold me...
they won't mate.
They just walk around eating...
and not mating.
You sold me...
queer giraffes.
- I want my money back.
- Not a chance.
I do special price for you.
On what?
Have you seen my new stock?
Come and see them.
Do any of them fight?
I've got a match coming up.
Some are good for fighting,
others for dying.
You need both, I think.
Get up.
What's your trade?
I was a hunter.
I bought him from a salt mine
in Carthage.
Sit down.
Mark of the legion.
- Deserter.
- Maybe so. But who cares?
- He's a Spaniard.
- I'll take six.
- For one thousand.
- One thousand?
The Numidian alone is worth 2,000.
These slaves are rotten.
It all adds to the flavor.
Wait, wait. Wait!
I can negotiate.
I'll give you 2,000...
and four for the beasts.
That's 5,000 for an old friend.
Come on! How long does it take
to get into my own house?
I am Proximo.
I shall be closer to you
for the next few days...
which will be the last
of your miserable lives...
than that bitch of a mother that
brought you screaming into this world.
I did not pay good money for you
for your company.
I paid it so that I could
profit from your death.
And as your mother was there
at your beginning...
so I shall be there at your end.
And when you die,
and die you shall...
your transition
shall be to the sound of...
Gladiators...
I salute you.
- Red.
Yellow.
Good.
- Red.
Spaniard.
That's enough for the moment!
His time will come.
Next.
Spaniard.
Why don't you fight?
We all have to fight.
Is that the sign of your gods?
Will that not anger them?
The gods favor you.
Red is the gods' color.
You will need their help today.
Some of you are thinking
you won't fight...
and some that you can't fight.
They all say that...
until they're out there.
Listen.
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Thrust this
into another man's flesh.
They will applaud
and love you for that.
And you...
you may begin to love them...
for that.
Ultimately...
we're all dead men.
Sadly, we cannot choose how, but...
we can decide
how we meet that end...
in order
that we are remembered...
as men.
On the left,
draw your shields!
On the right,
draw your swords!
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Pair them up...
red with yellow.
Next!
Move it!
- Go away!
- You'll never rule us, Commodus!
He enters Rome like a conquering hero.
But what has he conquered?
Give him time, Gracchus.
He's young.
I think he could do very well.
For Rome, or for you?
Go to your mother, Lucius.
It's what she'd like.
Lucius!
Mother!
Hail, Caesar.
Senators.
Rome greets her new emperor.
Your loyal subjects
bid you welcome, Highness.
Thank you, Falco.
And for the loyal subjects,
I trust they weren't too expensive.
- Caesar.
- Gracchus.
All Rome rejoices
in your return, Caesar.
There are many matters
that require your attention.
To order, please!
To order!
For your guidance, Caesar, the senate
has prepared a series of protocols...
to begin addressing
the many problems in the city...
beginning with basic sanitation
for the Greek quarter...
to combat the plague
which is already springing up there.
So, if Caesar...
Don't you see, Gracchus?
That's the very problem,
isn't it?
My father spent
all his time at study...
at books of learning
and philosophy.
He spent his twilight hours
reading scrolls from the senate.
And all the while
the people were forgotten.
But the senate
is the people, sire...
chosen from among the people
to speak for the people.
I doubt many of the people
eat so well as you do, Gracchus...
or have such
splendid mistresses, Gaius.
I think I understand my own people.
Then perhaps Caesar will be so good
as to teach us...
out of his own extensive experience.
I call it love.
I am their father.
The people are my children.
I shall hold them to my bosom
and embrace them tightly.
Have you ever embraced someone
dying of plague, sire?
No, but if you interrupt me again...
I assure you that you shall.
Senator,
my brother is very tired.
Leave your list with me.
Caesar shall do
all that Rome requires.
My lady, as always...
your lightest touch
commands obedience.
Who are they to lecture me?
Commodus, the senate has its uses.
What uses?
All they do is talk.
It should be just...
you and me...
and Rome.
Don't even think it.
There's always been a senate.
Rome has changed.
It takes an emperor
to rule an empire.
Of course,
but leave the people their...
Illusions?
Traditions.
My father's war
against the barbarians...
He said it himself: it achieved nothing.
But the people loved him.
The people always love victories.
Why?
They didn't see the battles.
What do they care about Germania?
They care about
the greatness of Rome.
The greatness of Rome.
Well, what is that?
It's an idea...
greatness.
Greatness is a vision.
Exactly. A vision.
Do you not see, Lucilla?
I will give the people a vision of Rome,
and they will love me for it.
And they'll soon forget the tedious
sermonizing of a few dry old men.
I will give the people
the greatest vision of their lives.
White and red wine
for your drinking pleasure!
Games.
One hundred and fifty days
of games.
He's cleverer than I thought.
Clever.
The whole of Rome
would be laughing at him...
if they weren't so afraid
of his praetorian.
Fear and wonder...
a powerful combination.
You really think the people
are going to be seduced by that?
I think he knows what Rome is.
Rome is the mob.
Conjure magic for them,
and they'll be distracted.
Take away their freedom,
and still they'll roar.
The beating heart of Rome...
is not the marble of the senate.
It's the sand of the Colosseum.
He'll bring them death...
and they will love him for it.
Spaniard.
Are you not entertained?
Is this not why you are here?
Spaniard! Spaniard!
What do you want?
Girl?
Boy?
You sent for me.
Yes, I did.
You're good, Spaniard,
but you're not that good.
You could be magnificent.
I'm required to kill, so I kill.
That is enough.
That's enough for the provinces,
but not for Rome.
The young emperor...
has arranged
a series of spectacles...
to commemorate his father...
Marcus Aurelius.
I find that amusing...
since it was Marcus Aurelius...
the wise,
the all-knowing Marcus Aurelius...
that closed us down.
So, finally, after five years
of scratching a living...
in flea-infested villages...
we're finally going back
to where we belong...
the Colosseum.
Oh, you should see
the Colosseum, Spaniard.
Fifty thousand Romans...
watching every movement
of your sword...
willing you to make
that killer blow.
The silence before you strike...
and the noise afterwards.
It rises.
It rises up like...
like a storm...
as if you were
the thunder god himself.
You were a gladiator?
Yes, I was.
You won your freedom?
A long time ago, the emperor...
presented me with a rudis.
It's just a wooden sword.
The symbol of your freedom.
He touched me on the shoulder,
and I was free.
You knew Marcus Aurelius?
I did not say I knew him. I said
he touched me on the shoulder once.
You asked me what I want.
I too, want to stand
in front of the emperor...
as you did.
Then listen to me.
Learn from me.
I wasn't the best
because I killed quickly.
I was the best
because the crowd loved me.
Win the crowd...
and you'll win your freedom.
I will win the crowd.
I will give them something
they've never seen before.
So, Spaniard,
we shall go to Rome together...
and have bloody adventures...
and the great whore
will suckle us...
until we are fat and happy
and can suckle no more.
And then...
when enough men have died...
perhaps you will have your freedom.
Here. Use this.
It's somewhere out there...
my country...
my home.
My wife is preparing food.
My daughters carry water
from the river.
Will I ever see them again?
I think no.
Do you believe you'll see them again
when you die?
I think so.
But then...
I will die soon.
They will not die for many years.
I'll have to wait.
But you would wait?
Of course.
You see...
my wife...
and my son...
are already waiting for me.
You'll meet them again.
But not yet.
Not yet, unless...
Not yet.
There.
There it is.
Out.
Go! Go! Out!
Good to see you again,
old friend.
Bring me fortune.
Have you ever seen anything
like that before?
I didn't know men
could build such things.
Win the crowd.
Get inside! Move!
Inside!
He sleeps so well
because he's loved.
Come, brother. It's late.
I will make Rome
the wonder of the ages.
That is what Gracchus and his friends
don't understand.
All my desires
are splitting my head to pieces.
Drink this tonic.
I think the time is almost right.
I could announce
the dissolution of the senate...
at the celebration
to honor our father.
Do you think I should?
Are the people ready?
I think you need your rest now.
Will you stay with me?
Still afraid of the dark,
brother?
Still.
Always.
- Stay with me tonight.
- You know I won't.
Then kiss me.
Sleep, brother.
Come on!
Take me.
All right, that's enough.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org