Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Go Paul there, we are here at the 3 hours,
and nor we know where was.
He/she has at least two meters and twenty.
I never saw a like this!
I don't leave of here without her
I am cold!
He/she closes the rattle.
Do go there mine, can we lean?
I have to give a mijadela.
- He/she urinates there in front of the boat.
- Go there!
She won't bite.
Shit!
Jesus Cristo.
- Go there mine, I am not like this capable.
- And because not?
Because it is eccentric
with you there seating.
He/she speaks quietly!
He/she doesn't import what I say.
It silences you Ainsley. You are maricas Ainsley.
Because you are not more similar
with your sister Ainsley?
- I said caluda, maricas!
- You see!?
Are you to see?
Stupid.
What did boy say?
Anything.
Don't make to throw you to me to the swamp.
He/she prays there is...
Jesus Cristo!!
- What did happen he/she?
- She wanted to eat me the balls!
You scared her, stupid!
What did want him to do?
Porra. We can lean for
I to finish my mijadela?
He/she dispatches you.
Cursed maricas,
he/she needs to urinate stooping.
Shit.
He/she is quiet, Ainsley.
I think she returned.
What should make?
Don't make noise, it is there.
Paul?
Did you pick her?
Paul?!
And if we went home now?
Father?
Paul?
Paul.
Do let us go?!
He/she walks to pick me, mijao.
I kill you.
God, helps me!!
VERSION NO CENSURED
I eat a bee.
He/she raises, mine.
That is Mardi Gras, is entertaining.
A madness!?
Here, here... look.
He/she looks at those mammas there.
Hi.
Something new, it is not?
Didn't you still see mammas that arrive?
I am not to feel this.
He/she should have stayed home.
What for? For you be in yours
room and to cry for Heather?
Kristine.
Mine, we came here to tan.
And you are to hinder the things.
There is amusement on the whole side.
Does he/she stop being cuts?
How is it that that is entertaining?
This ranch is disgusting.
Our room in the hotel
he/she smells to sweated tomatoes, mine.
All are drunk
and to madden. You...
...you vomited six times yesterday.
How is it that you managed to do that?
You can be to tan.
I will find something to do.
The something, alone?
Dewitt Robinson spoke to me in a
trip to the haunted swamp...
...that you/they did last year.
They said that was incredible.
Type lights to float
and other scenes in the water.
You want to leave this everything...
...for you will see lights in a swamp?
- You don't have to come with me, Marcus.
- We were at the hotel.
- Fasten.
Ben, waits, he waits for my...
- Marcus no, it goes there...
- No, I am going with you. Tásse well.
Thank you, mine.
Friend, you will see that it is worthwhile.
I think I prefer to skin
my sex.
- Certain, is official.
- It is here.
No longer there is small.
- They are closed.
- They cannot be closed.
But they are really.
He/she says closed... and you continue to beat.
Certain, that is a drought.
It is not dry none.
It will be fastens.
- For you, because you are a drought.
- He/she silences you.
What do want?
We want to do the trip
to the haunted swamp.
Me no longer I take trips at night.
It is not allowed me.
But it is that... our friends counted-
us that you/they made a here last year.
No longer I can take trips at night.
The insurance was very expensive...
...after what it happened.
- It is feather! Let us go.
- He/she waits...
What did happen he/she?
You don't want to know.
I do want.
There we go us.
I had a group,
outside in the swamp.
In the last halloween,
he/she was a become overcast night...
Yes?
And there was a...
...of your color.
He/she was afraid
with a thing in the margin.
He/she saw two eyes to challenge him/it
of the forests.
The children were fascinated.
He wanted to leave the boat to the hurry.
And the foot, to hang for the cliff.
- Did he fall?
- Did an aligátor pick him/it?
- What did happen he/she?
- He slipped...
...and it beat with the head
in the skull of the boat.
And it processed me for negligence.
- That maricas!
- Only that?
He/she tries in Marie Laveau.
How?
Two blocks above in the Rua Olive.
But she cannot know about me.
I have go give food
to my birds.
Care, walk in the walk!
- Go mine, wait there.
- The something?
Apposed what is the hell there, right?
Entertaining party... insane madness.
Wait Ben... that is grimace.
As it is that this is going you
to help to forget her?
Marcus, that scene there behind, it is...
All the sly ones good and nude middle that
I see, they make to remember Kristine.
He/she is probably to be hammered
by Bulkowski. In the room.
Bent in that beige sofa,
that my mother bought him/her.
What happened when dating
with a normal brute?
That brute has a neck
of the size of a carrinha.
And the colored flower in the ear,
it is strange.
The something? He will struggle with her
even á submission?
- He/she is well, it stops, it stops...!
- He/she is well.
I don't want to think in Bulkowski
to eat your girlfriend.
- Nor me.
- I already understood.
Go there mine, this will be entertaining.
If no there is small in the swamp,
I won't need this.
It will be entertaining.
- As entertaining as annoying.
- You there know.
- That that is sanded used...
- You went there.
I didn't know that her
he/she had insectos in the forest!
She started the night to scratch.
How is it that you didn't know?
You cannot eat any a, Marcus.
Everyone knows about that.
She said that was an allergy
in the fatty fabric, is it well?
- I saw and I asked.
- Fatty fabric!?
He/she looks at you shaver.
''Everyone knows about that.''
When it was the last time
what did make sex?
- I make sex the the whole hour...
- He/she silences you!
Ladies.
That is really entertaining.
That is good, good.
Give a kiss.
Yes, you adore.
You want, you necessary.
Rays. I have to change the battery.
God, brushes the teeth
a lot of times!?
It whips me, goat.
No thank you, I like the
my language without the syphilis.
Your syphilis... Sra. expensive words?
- That nor he/she makes sense.
- It whips me.
Misty, Jenna...
They can understand each other for more
one hours, they are not able to?
To tell the truth Doug.
I cannot work with this.
I am a professional actriz.
I walked in U.N.Y.
Which is the joke?
As if somebody already heard to speak of that.
- University of New York?
- I never heard to speak.
Girls...
Never nobody was discovered,
being done difficult.
I need that show me
the love, right?
Do I need the passion to feel, right?
We are to film.
I need to feel...
Certain, they are sensual.
Playful.
They are curious.
They are innocent.
Who is ready
for some terrors?
The night soon will fall on us.
The spirits of the cursed ones
they are to raise.
We will put our souls
in movement, my friends.
What can make for you?
Does he/she take the trip in the haunted swamp?
I am the only that he/she takes the trip
in the haunted swamp.
Live ghosts.
Stories of the macabre.
And ranches that are still
cursed for...
...curses voodu.
I don't like him!?
We will leave now.
40 bones each.
40 dollars?
- Yes.
- He/she is well.
- Do you sponsor me?
- Don't you have money?
No, I won't only pay this treta.
- Hello.
- Hi...
How are they?
How is it that go?!
He/she is well.
Do you care that he/she sits down here?
Comfortable.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Then me...
I think am here.
I am Ben.
Marybeth.
Marybeth?
Good name, because they are two names.
Most of the people
they only have a, and it is displeased type.
Ben.
But Marybeth, is...
Mary, and he/she is Beth.
Beautiful coat.
Then you have animals of
estimate, or...
Are you to like of Mardi Gras?
Yes.
You didn't find anybody courageous for
to do the trip of the ghosts with you?
No.
Tásse well.
I have somebody there home
and me in this trip...
He/she excuses, I didn't come
in this trip...
...because he/she waited,
that maybe, he/she will know you.
If you don't care, it liked
of being to look for this window...
...and to do to yield mine
30 dollars, is it well?
But that thing!
Very well personal.
I am your garçon.
Relax and get ready
for the doors...
Dog, you don't need that.
That is of the size of a Mini.
He/she says what have to say, stupid.
A limusina Mini, are they to see?
It was that I was to say
Me...
No, you...
We were so turns
when we make this.
- I am Marcus.
- Jenna.
Hello.
Jim Permatteo.
- And this is you, Janet.
- How is it?
Doug Shapiro, a lot of taste.
Beautiful camera.
Is he/she to do a film?
Because.
Who would say tiny.
- We have an enterprising one here.
- That exciting.
What film type?
- Did he/she already hear to speak of the beavers of the lake?
- Clear.
No.
Very well personal,
if they look on the right side...
...they can see the legendary
cemetery of Sant Louis, number 1.
Inaugurated 1789.
It is here that jaz the first black,
that is in the memorial of New Orleaes.
It is thinks also her
that is the grave...
...of the infamous voodu apprentice,
Marie Labeau.
Yes gentleman.
They know because it is that are
done bury below the ground?
It is because of the curses voodu,
that there is in the air for here.
They have the tendency
of raising of the ground.
Then we liked that
be stamped with cement.
Shawn excuses,
but we heard to say...
...that bury them below the ground
because of the levels of the water.
No!?
He/she is right, the level of the water
it is so loud, that sometimes...
...the things in the ground,
they give á surface.
It is not for that.
- But we heard...
- He/she already said not!
Certain, the time is to pass.
All on board.
Frightening Autocarro.
Frightening boat.
Certain, right.
There is no time, we have
that to hurry, therefore it is.
Certain, certain, to pass.
Well, we have to go.
Bacano...
Is that the boat?
Certain, we will see there something.
They are stupid.
They are duronas.
They are rotate.
They have a secret.
We are going tiny.
In Automatic Pilot.
Certain, here we go us.
You there.
Hello.
Sr. Shawn, think that man
he/she is to try to speak with itself.
No, no...
- Where do they think that go?
- What is he to say her?
That type, don't make case,
it is only a drugged.
Done drug?
Yes, yes, a local hunter
of aligátores.
He/she walks thereabout, the hell is bad.
He/she drinks the own urinate.
He is, you know.
A cretin one.
Go there.
This swamp is closed!
The swamp is...!
- Victor Crowley!
- What is him to say her.
Here we go, tell all good-bye,
all say good-bye.
If it was already here,
maintain is alerted.
They will die all.
Remember...
They don't need to have
your things on board.
Only those that don't want lose.
To the because it is, there is gigantic aligátores
in these waters.
Repair, it is not a thing...
...that you see
everyday, but I see.
Live cypresses.
What the Spaniards said
on the cypresses?
"What does care he/she is for here?"
Sometimes story this joke
in Spanish.
The cypress is not the tree
of the state of Louisiana?
- Apposed that is.
- Yes, since 1963.
- The cypresses baldness.
- There is only a tecto in this boat!?
We are going to a part of the swamp
with the most frightening show.
All want animated
or they go embroiders out.
Here in the lake of Mississípi,
hundreds of fishermen
and old pirates lost the life.
And if we have luck...
We can see their souls
to leave the water and to die.
- That is common.
- Go there mine, that is entertaining.
As entertaining as one
I take out full of pilas.
That is worse than the hell.
The only frightening thing
he/she is the uncle Limus vs Bruce Lee.
- Until it seems that am in the wave of the South.
- And that small one what vineyard with you?
She is fastens.
- But I won't eat her/it in this boat.
- Then in earth, it is for later.
How doesn't the Ian guy know about something?
It is a beautiful coat.
- This was classic.
- Yes!? No so classic...
No as classic as...
- I don't have anything.
- Exacto.
Now, to proceed, they will see one
old abandoned house.
That there is the house
of a legend of Louisiana.
Victor Crowley '' Axed.''
The legend counts that:
He was a deformed man,
the father went mad.
One night gave him/her one
axed in the face.
Probably because,
he was ugly or something.
He died.
And history prays that...
...who wants that is close
of the house of Crowley.
They still get to hear
Victor Crowley.
To cry for the father.
Did they hear?
I heard again.
- It is not like this.
- Be how it is, it is like this.
- Nor it is the house.
- Do they let to do me my work?
Did they already prove the piranha of here?
I am so excited
for having made this.
That habit that you had at the school.
Where?
- It is as classic as that habit...
- Too late.
- Reason?
- Are you still in the classic?
Prepared to see something frightening?
Are they ready?
Who is ready says "oh yeah."
He/she is well, I will do in the same.
Here we go.
Personal, I will turn off the lights.
When the eyes if they adjust,
they will get to see ghosts...
...to the summit of the water,
to the right in the margin.
- I am not to see anything.
- He/she waits until the eyes if they adjust.
They are adjusted, there is nothing there.
Can you tie the lights?
You are to destroy my filmings.
He/she looks at Jim, I think am to see something.
Because it is. Are they to see?
It is not only a, they are two ghosts.
I well told you.
That is not only one
chemical reacçao in the water?
No mine, they are ghost, he/she looks.
No bacano.
That is steams of the swamps,
I already saw this in television.
Do go there mine, because you don't align?
They are ghost.
Ah, are right...
But not.
Porra.
Now...
This is besiege where the
Captain John Donovan,
supposedly it buried
a trunk full of treasures.
The legend says that...
...he left two of yours
crew to keep.
But it cut him/her the legs
for them not to flee.
That is a stupid history.
He/she is well.
- Jim! Did you see that?
- I saw. What was?
It can be one of the spirits,
that he/she sometimes leaves after raining.
Is it frightening, it is not?
Perfect.
Who wants to enter
in the video of the halloween?
Go girls there.
- Your uh is out of time.
- Yes? Your nipples are manure.
That is fastens.
He/she is cold.
You are not very talkative?
I am not here to do friends.
Friends...
You should be of here.
He/she didn't know that you/they took this trip.
- We don't do.
- No, clear, yes, not.
Yes, I would not also make him/it.
They were some friends of the university
that you/they said that was fastens, for that...
I thought, that is sanded.
He/she looks at the swamp.
He/she takes advantage of the actividade.
I will be honest with you.
I have just taken with the feet of mine
girlfriend and we already dated 8 years ago.
My friends brought me for here
for to try to forget, but...
We were together
since the 7th year, and...
And he tells me that he/she needs space.
What wants that to say
in girl's language?
Space!?
As it is.
To turn off my mind.
Relax.
What did happen he/she?
Us...
Stagnated Ficámos.
Done stagnate? In the something?
Stones or some thing, I don't know.
Somebody that helps me.
Help me to push the boat.
- Is this part of the trip?
- He/she calms, it is everything well.
He/she is part of the trip...
Curse.
To who you will call?
To the father?
He/she silences you hideous.
I will call to the Police
and they order somebody.
- Who?
- The police, dah...
Will the Police order the police?
They are the same thing.
They are not anything, there is a difference.
Ladies, I remove the boat of here.
There is no need to call the men.
Marcus, help?
That is a drought.
My hair!
- Where do you go?
- He/she already has more than eighteen years...
He/she seats you already.
I am wet.
I know what am to do.
You are not still very familiarized
with your histories?
Shawn, how many trips
of these you did already do?
I already did plenty.
Jim, that is fantastic,
what do find?
My feet are to be wet!
- Are we to sink?
- No, we are not to sink.
Now it does seem, doesn't it seem?
Calm!
The tree where we are stagnated
he/she is going to the margin.
Maybe there be a highway
or a telephone or some thing.
- Here in the middle of the anything?
- We cannot be here.
No Jim, I think owed
to be here, and to wait for help.
Other boat should come
to do this trip, right?
Probably not.
He/she is to rain a lot.
Tiny, we can cross
for this tree to the margin.
No, it seems dangerous.
I could be at a Bar.
- You don't go, not!
- Here, it repairs.
Jim waits!
Everything is well,
don't worry.
It is a slippery mouthful,
they have to see where they put the feet.
But I think go...
Somebody that helps me!
He/she is arrested!
He/she is to pull my leg.
Take him/it for the margin.
When it has just rained,
this besieges will be a frenesim.
Move!
We go, all to leave the boat,
sink.
Nor to think.
I don't go there outside.
You go there outside.
- Jim, are you well, Jim?
- He is well.
It puts the weight on the left side.
It puts the weight in the person on the side.
No, don't cry. Don't worry
Everything is well, he/she walks, I help you.
Don't worry, he/she walks.
He/she goes for there.
- He/she walks, he/she lifts you.
- I am not capable.
You have to get up
and to arrive to the highest branch.
I don't want.
He/she walks, I pick you
- He/she lifts you!
- I don't get!
Misty, looks at me!
You will be well,
you only have to cross.
He/she walks, I help.
He/she walks, it crosses, there is no time.
He/she walks, fast!
- Leave the water!
Leave the water!
What was this?
He/she walks, I left give!
They go, vain!
- Good, stupid!
- He/she will sand you.
We needed to leave this mud.
The aligátores can return. Vain.
My hat...
Because you are of high jumps?
Slowly, don't hurt you
Are you well?
Care.
Here.
My God!
Somebody wants me to say
what is to pass been?
Somebody explains to me
because Jane has a weapon?
- Because you have a weapon?
- Because I should tell you, burlao?
He/she is well, he/she looks...
I will be honest.
Have just moved from Detroit.
My brother arranged me
this work.
And that could do
a carload of money.
Then I said, because not.
- How many trips did already take?
And how many boats did already drive?
He/she looks, I did to a trip last night,
and this today á night, is it well?
The boat didn't sink yesterday.
I don't believe in this.
And because he/she has her a weapon?
That is what I want to know.
Because I am to the search
of another boat, is it well?
Because my father and my brother,
they walked to the hunt in this river at 2 o'clock
nights behind and they didn't return.
The Police said that owe
to walk in the borga or something.
But I know that not
that that happened was.
Then, you come in a trip
on ghosts?
That doesn't make sense.
30 dollars for a boat are more
cheaply of what to arrange a boat.
He/she still doesn't explain the weapon.
Yes. Why is that her
did he/she only pay 30 dollars?
I have a weapon because
this forests are not safe.
Haul of that, it ended
of saving him/her the life.
Stop!
My husband needs help.
We needed go look for help,
and we needed to leave these forests.
- Who named you leader?
- We should ask for help and to be here.
- There are no Bars. I don't like you.
- I think should not move him/it.
We have.
He/she is to bleed a lot,
we cannot carry him/it until house.
If we don't leave these forests
now, we will die all.
Of the one what are to speak you?
- These forests belong to him.
- ?e who?
Victor Crowley.
Already enough of histories, is it well?
You nor they know where they are.
- I already told you...
- He/she is well, it silences you.
You nor you are of here.
Where are we?
It was a shameful secret.
Victor Crowley was born deformed.
His father maintained him/it closed home.
Where nobody could see him/it.
They lived like this years.
Only them, alone.
Victor died from fear
of the other small ones.
They enjoyed with him, they tortured him.
Just as the small ones they do.
It was cruel.
It is then one years later
in the night of the halloween.
Some adolescents went to the house.
They were to try to see him/it.
To try to scare him
for him to leave of house.
Mr. Crowley arrived
and he/she tried to enter, but...
The door was to burn.
He heard Victor to scream there inside
but it was not capable to enter.
He/she ran and it went to look for an axe,
and it began to cut the door.
But Victor was
of the other side to try to leave.
It was an accident...
But he got right him/her in the face
with that axe.
And the poor Victor Crowley died.
The old became
a hermit after that.
He/she never again left house.
He/she was there almost 10 years before
of dying of destroyed heart.
And from there that the people
they began to disappear in the swamp.
The places and the hunters say,
that if in the approximate-millstones
of the house of Crowley at night.
We still got to hear
Victor Crowley.
To cry for the father in the forests.
They say that he returned.
And it strolls for the swamp at night.
With that wound of the axe in the face.
In this part of the river
it is illegal to come for here.
It is like this to years, it is for that
that there are no other boats.
And it was for that that he brought us for here,
for not being picked in their outlines.
- It was for that that I came.
- For you find your father?
My brother.
He/she began to come to hunt aligátores
for here last week.
They thought that won more
because it was the only boat in the swamp.
They told him/her for us not to come!
Then you leaning that a ghost
did he/she pick your family?
That is stupid.
He/she looks to your turn, no there is nobody
in these forests.
There is yes.
They must have been
stagnated just as us.
And they had to walk to house.
Now they should be in Dennis or like this.
The moon on Miami!
Haul of that, we are not
close to the house of Crowley.
Is he/she well? He/she already told you.
It is on the other side of the river,
and to 3 distance quilómetros.
- It was not the house!
- How is it that you know?
Because it is that.
Look. Did I tell the truth, is it well?
I don't import myself if they don't believe.
You are to begin to get scared.
- I only want to go home.
- He/she tells me that this is part of the trip.
Oh yes, I sink the boat
all of the nights. It is hilarious.
- I want my money of turn.
- It should have a highway for here.
Shit.
I don't want to go over there.
I don't go over there.
If it is the fastest way,
then it is over there that we go.
Because you were not quiet?
We don't have surplus possessions,
you also had to blot us the pants.
I am to try to help,
you had to know the truth.
Rumors.
He/she is well, it is well...
Does it help me to lift him/it, is it well?
Go there.
It catches you to my shoulder.
Care, slowly.
Is he/she already safe, mine?
I am here Jim.
He/she will be everything well.
We will help him/it and we go
all home.
He/she is close to me.
Are you same afraid of that history?
It is only a myth.
Everyone knows a, Bigfoot...
- monster of Lockness...
- Please he/she stops speaking.
I don't believe that am here,
in a swamp.
Apposed that Julia Roberts
he/she didn't have to do this.
You believe in the history
of Victor I don't know about the how many?
Of course no.
I don't trust in anybody of here.
At least in people that only
they want to know of the own family.
Because it is that that brute was
with the dear and the 2 sisters...
...and I have to carry
with the agent?
I feel a lot, he/she didn't want
that this happened.
I only want to arrive to the highway
and later you take some lashes.
Jim, as you are wanted?
I am cold so much!
And it hurts... c'má porra.
The one that distance is the highway
after the house?
I don't know, some quilómetros.
Some quilómetros?
Are you to play?
You...
I want to go home.
All are a cobardes bunch.
Is anybody home?
Help us.
We needed help.
Please, stop.
We should not go thereabout,
we have to return back.
And to go where?
To return for the water?
Please, stop.
We have to be together,
they have to stop.
Go there, it cannot carry him/it alone.
Dear, it will be everything well.
We didn't need those mad ones.
Cobardes!
Stop! We have to stay together.
He/she will be everything well.
We have the Mister connosco, dear.
The Mister it protects us.
My God!
Walk!
Help me, help!
I am I, am me!
- Where are they whole?
- I don't know.
- Here. What did happen he/she?
- They are the two died.
- But I gave him/her a shot.
- Did you give him/her a shot?
But I thought that was a ghost.
You cannot kill a ghost.
- Can you kill a ghost?
- Did you kill him/it?
- I don't know, he fell.
- This is not to happen.
- Where is Marcus?
- Here on top.
- He/she goes down give.
- Nor to think, I am here.
- That is a treta, that is sanded.
- What do get to see you give?
I get to see that there none comes
elephant died to pick me.
You see a highway, lights,
some thing?
I think I see the drop,
but I don't know.
The one what distance?
In what direcçao?
Over there. But it is far,
too far.
You see a highway, cars,
some thing?
That stupid thing my. He/she is dark,
it is wet and I don't get to see pévias.
Wait. Where is Shapiro?
Doug? Shapiro, where are you?
- He/she speaks quietly.
- We have to go.
- We cannot leave him/it here.
- Then it disappears will see of him.
- That was bad.
- He/she tries your telephone.
- I dropped him.
- Did you lose him/it?
- Late!
- It silences you female dog.
Enough. He is not able to
to have gone far. Let us go.
Marcus walks, we leave.
Nor to think, I am here.
There is no panic need,
he/she calms you, we will arrange help.
He/she is well, tomorrow
we ordered somebody, we go.
He/she waits, it tolerates there.
I go. Curse.
Nor it was to be here, mine.
It was to be to see mammas, mine.
What does connosco happen?
Shit, as I will go down
of this cursed tree?
Damned! Even in the fruit.
That is a treta!
Shit!
If you killed him/it,
we already are not clear?
Maybe he is not a ghost.
Maybe it is a twisted marado,
that he/she likes to sleep a siesta
in the middle of a slaughter.
Yes, and now he is dead
because she gave him/her a shot.
He/she arranges your own theories.
Twisted Marado?
Who says that cannot be
a spoiled boy of the city,
that he/she went mad to do software
porn and did it go back to the parents' house?
For your information,
I am of Valley, not of the city.
Victor Crowley is real.
My mother always said
that sometimes,
if a person dies traumatized,
the spirit is arrested
in the night in that he/she died.
How a poltergeist?
As a ghost
what can move things?
No. As a ghost that can
to cut into pieces a person to your front.
I only want to leave of here.
You know that more Jackie Tucker.
You can smell me the rear.
- What did call me?
- You heard.
- He/she says again.
- I say the night all.
Jackie fake Chan,
Chris chupador.
I think a hemerroida
you can get confused.
Does he/she leave me alone, ass face?
It was an accident, for love of God.
Look. I will be honest
with you. I like...
What was?
Go there!
Go there! Shit.
- This is not my fault?
- Seriously?
Seriously. You think I believe
in these histories of ghosts?
Now I believe, you didn't see
that shit there behind?
Boys!
Apposed that this wants to say
that Shapiro was here.
That génio! You know that the vibrator is for
to put in your thing and not in the ear, right?
Because you don't suck him/it
your father again, goat?
I suck after you end.
- He/she is well.
- Fortunately.
Does anybody have a lighter?
What are to do?
In search of this.
What more we have here?
Samuel M Barret?
What is that?
Shapiro.
It is the transport letter
- The something?
- I don't know.
Credit card Samuel M Barret.
10 dollars, preservative.
Card of businesses, and they are two.
Samuel M Barret, diagnoses,
relationships of marketing sénior.
Doug Shapiro, Producer-Director.
That ass face!
I flew of New York here, and him...
Then he didn't work
in the lake of the beavers?
I am to think that not.
Him of having faked to be producing
to have a private colecçao.
- Good idea.
- Perverted.
Why is that the men
are some snotty ones?
I don't believe that
I already fell in this three times.
Does anybody have more secrets?
Because if I discover that is more somebody
to lie, I take oath that the bush me even.
I didn't walk in U.N.Y.
It was my first choice,
but I didn't get to enter.
- Then I went to Austra.
- We don't have time for this.
The films in Hollywood,
they should do me famous.
It is now will die here
with you idiots.
Us him matámo-lo?
Nobody will die.
What does anybody make to silence her?
He is still alive.
- No mine, he seems dead...
- It is not him.
Crowley.
Did he/she only take a shot, right?
Maybe have to take 4 or
6 shots, maybe six times!
I don't want him to return,
I don't want to die here.
We should go where sees her the river.
For us not to be more lost.
- Didn't you hear?
- The something?
It is of here.
What is that?
My telemóvel!
- We have net.
- No.
No, it is good.
We can ask for help.
No.
Shit, we walked in circles.
- I thought that you knew this.
- Monitor shit.
- I don't want to beat you, but you...
- He/she shuts up...
I will see on that Thursday.
To see if there is some weapon.
It should have some thing to struggle.
- You cannot return that house.
- I still have some shots.
- We needed some thing.
- And if he returns?
We don't have a long time.
- Be here.
- Fasten.
Do you have net?
Go there! He/she makes the connection.
We should not be here,
we have to go walking.
- It was been to play has to work.
- Scott Barnes calls me.
The something?
- Does he/she mark the numbers?
- Don't leave.
He/she works, damned.
I think he doesn't like
of these things.
The something?
He/she is my father and my brother.
- Are you the sure that the number and the 112?
- Which is that it could be, stupid?
As I can know, it is another area
it can be another code.
The something?
Don't move.
I said...
He/she dispatches you.
I think should run.
And if it goes a person
and to need of help?
We apologized later.
- I think is a kitten.
- You are crazy.
If it was the monster
we were already dead.
That this is sanded!
What is that?
- Nor to think, I don't go there.
- And if it goes anybody wounded?
If it is alive it is better than
certain people that we knew.
- You cannot leave a person to die.
- He/she looks to who increased a conscience.
He/she can need help.
- Reason me?
- Because you have a flashlight.
Certain, I already understood.
I already saw what happens.
Does he/she have the brother to be to do him/it?
I am man, I walk here,
I won't also move.
Because or else I graft you.
Shit!
Don't play me mine.
Porra. Certain...
We will see if it is a bebé
that is there inside.
Hello bebé.
Are you there inside?
Mine, is only a brute.
My God!
Please!
He/she waits, wait!
Leave!
I think already the despistámos.
Wait, I twisted the foot,
I cannot run.
- What is to do, he/she walks.
- He/she silences you erected.
He/she beat me.
It is been silence not you
I break you the teeth.
- Were you capable? Stupid, snail...
- We don't have time for this.
I only want that stops.
Please, I only want to wake up.
We have to move away us of that house.
Don't interest. It is his swamp,
it will kill us to all.
It should have some thing
that can do.
He is arrested in the night
in that was died.
It is gotten angry and afraid.
- He/she will mutilate who approaches.
- Is it if human being?
- And if he didn't die?
- That thing never human being.
Shit. The piles
no longer they last a lot.
- Right. we go, we go.
- So that side?
Over there.
Stop! Stop!
Personal! Stop!
That is useless. He will continue
to come until we be dead.
We cannot stop running.
What can make?
We can hurt him/it.
Ghost or not.
You saw like him fell
when I attacked him/it.
He/she fell when him of this the shot.
- I say for us to struggle.
- How?
Do Misty, still have the lighter?
You want to struggle with that monster
with my lighter?
There were a cans of gasoline
in the hut.
- Were they full?
- I don't know, maybe.
Do you want to return to the hut?
I thought that the plan was move away ourselves
of the hut the most possible.
If we don't kill him/it,
he kills us to all.
You are crazy!
Mine, nor you know if there is
gasoline in my cans.
I know that is better than to walk
to run for these forests...
...and one to be killed by one.
You are right.
Everything is so hot
and will we begin a fire?
If one of us to get to approximate
to throw him/her that gasoline...
We can set on fire him/it.
- All are passed, me no...
- Do you have an it idealizes better?
No.
We will make this. How?
Does it win me time, is it well?
He/she screams if you hear some thing.
- Do you see some thing?
- No.
I am well.
I am not to like of this.
He/she is too calm.
Go there, we will distract him/it.
Idiot, appears, we are here!
He/she appears, it comes to pick us.
Where are you?
Go there eccentric, it seems that
you were violated by wolves.
He/she shows you, ugly.
He/she walks to pick me Crowley.
What was? You are afraid that me
do feel a graft again?
Go there. One for a, you and me.
I bury you my shoe in the ass,
that will defecate attackers
for one week.
- Are you to see some thing?
- Anything.
He is here, it dispatches you. Now!
Yes! Burn.
Should they be to enjoy with me?
- Is it now?
- We leave, we go.
Ben. Ben!
He/she looks at me!
You only win us you time,
don't waste him/it. Let us go!
For here.
He/she should have a road
that he/she gives to leave the cemetery.
Here.
We will follow this even
find-millstones an opening.
- There it is.
- Thanks to God!
He comes there, vain!
There is a gate!
Shit!
He picked me.
Personal...
He will break to the middle!
It was the only gate.
My Porra, are
of turn to the forests.
Run!
He doesn't come.
Marcus!
No longer I can continue.
You can yes. Walk.
I already get to hear
the airplanes in the river. Walk.
Won't we die here, is it well?
Walk!
- No! He there kills us.
- Where do we go?
What wants!
We will push with the knee!
Walk.
I help you, I help you.
He/she is well, it is well.
It is my father's boat.
We go, we go!
Us him apanhámo-lo.
He/she uses this.
Thank you, for you be with me there.
No.
He/she is my father.
It is not easy.
Massacre...
We are alive.
We got.
I know.
No!
Marybeth!
Marybeth!!
Legendado for: @ sacred lma
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org