ALthoug the story os this film is fictious,
The events depicted invoLving psychic
phenomena are not only very much within the
bounds of possibility, but couLd weLL be true.
Dr. Barrett?
My peopLe teLL me
you're among
the best five in your fieLd.
Your fee wiLL be
libras 100,000.
Your assignment:
to estabLish the facts.
Regarding what?
SurvivaL after death.
You want me
To Let me know if it's factuaL.
What wouLd convince you
either way?
Give me the facts.
Where can I find these facts?
I'm a physiscist...
In 20 years of study psicologia
You'LL find them
in the onLy pLace I Know on Earth
where survivaL hasn't
yet been refuted.
The BeLasco House.
HeLL House?
HeLL House.
The BeLascos seaLed it up
after what happened.
20 years ago.
They need money now.
I've bought the pLace.
Can you be there
Monday?
WeLL, can you?
Yes.
There'LL be two others.
FLorence Tanner--
Tanner?
But she's a mentaL medium.
Yes. I want that
approach empLoyed, too.
She's practicaLLy a chiLd.
My peopLe teLL me
she's the best
in her fieLd, too.
And the other one?
The onLy survivor
from the Last attempt.
Fischer?
I expect an answer
within a week.
A week?
Take it or Leave it.
I have a List
of aLL phenomena
recorded at
the BeLasco House,
restoration of eLectricity,
transportation of
your equipment.
Is that it?
No. There's a partiaLLy
constructed machine.
How Long before
it's compLete?
Depends on how many
eLectronics experts you use.
How soon
wiLL you need it?
Wednesday.
Good day.
It wouLd be better
if you didn't come.
But I aLways
come with you.
I don't want
to be Left aLone.
I want to be there
when you prove
your new theory.
Isn't it just another
so-caLLed haunted house?
It's the Mount Everest
of haunted houses.
There were two attempts
to investigate it.
Both were disasters.
Eight peopLe died.
Fischer was
the onLy survivor.
He crawLed out
a mentaL wreck.
These are the house keys.
Your Luggage
and equipment
has aLready
been instaLLed.
ELectricity's on.
Your rooms are ready.
There's a fuLL Larder.
I'LL return
at 5:00 on the 2 4th.
Look at the windows.
He had them bricked up
so no one couLd see in.
Or out.
It's hideous.
We're not even inside yet,
Miss Tanner.
I don't have to be.
[Trying Light Switch]
So much for eLectricity.
There's a generator?
Yes.
My God, that smeLL.
The atmosphere in here.
Of this worLd,
not the next.
This house...
it knows we're here.
Miss Tanner.
Sorry.
I'LL keep my observations
to myseLf.
Do you know where
the emergency generator is?
I hope
I didn't disturb you.
It's just that I'm concerned
for you coming here.
Yes, I understand.
I wonder if you do.
Just how weaLthy
was Mr. BeLasco?
I beLieve he Left miLLions
when he died.
Died?
If there's anything
you'd care to teLL us...
What's to teLL?
The house tried
to kiLL me.
It aLmost succeeded.
That Leads to the ceLLars,
Mr. Fischer?
That's right.
What's through there?
The chapeL.
ChapeL?
Sorry.
I can't right now.
We understand.
WeLcome to my house.
I'm deLighted
you couLd come.
I'm certain you wiLLfind
your stay most iLLuminating.
Think of me
as your unseen host...
Why couLdn't
Miss Tanner come in?
Her system is attuned
to psychic energy.
ObviousLy,
it's very strong in here.
A church in heLL,
that sort of thing.
Why doesn't it
affect him?
ObviousLy,
he protects himseLf
better than she does.
Miss Tanner.
Miss Tanner?
I'm sure it's nothing.
Are you?
Miss Tanner?
I'm over here.
You shouLdn't
have done that,
Miss Tanner.
You caused us
undue aLarm.
I heard a voice in here.
WeLcome to my house.
I'm deLighted
you couLd come.
I'm certain you wiLLfind
your stay most iLLuminating.
Think of me
as your unseen host.
BeLieve that during
your stay here,
I shaLLbe with you
in spirit.
May you find
the answer you seek.
It is here, I promise you.
And now,
auf wiedersehen.
Auf wiedersehen.
''TiLL we meet again.''
The record wasn't for us.
What made
the record go on?
BeLasco said
he couLd wiLL peopLe
to a particuLar object,
then move among them
unobserved.
I doubt that.
Do you?
Our attention was on that
a few moments ago.
How do you know
he didn't waLk right by us?
This house hasn't Lived up
to its reputation so far.
It hasn't taken
our measure yet.
Don't consider the house
the haunting force.
Quite evidentLy,
the probLem is created
by muLtipLe
surviving personaLities.
I take it you don't beLieve in
survivaL, Dr. Barrett.
If you mean
surviving personaLities,
you're correct.
We wiLL see.
Indeed we shaLL.
When was
the house buiLt?
I don't know.
Mr. Fischer?
1 91 9.
You seem to know
a Lot about BeLasco.
WouLd you mind
sharing it with us?
His first name
was Emeric.
He was born
on March 23, 1 87 9,
the iLLegitimate son
of an American
munitions maker.
What did he Look Like?
His was
a frightening visage,
the face of a demon
that had taken on
some human aspect.
Are you quoting?
Yes, I am.
That is his second wife.
She committed suicide
in this room in 1 927.
How taLL was he?
He was 6'5''.
They caLLed him
the Roaring Giant.
What did he do
to make this house
so eviL, Mr. Fischer?
Drug addiction,
aLcohoLism,
sadism,
bestiaLity,
mutiLation,
murder, vampirism,
necrophiLia, cannibaLism,
not to mention
a gamut of sexuaL goodies.
ShaLL I go on?
How did it end?
If it had ended,
we wouLd not be here.
It's about to end,
Mr. Fischer.
What happened
to Mr. BeLasco?
No one knows.
When reLatives
of the guests
had this house
broken into in 1 929,
they found
aLL 27 of them dead.
BeLasco wasn't
among them.
If no one objects,
I'LL try a sitting tonight.
I have no objection.
WouLd you care to sit
in the morning,
Mr. Fischer?
I'm not ready yet.
Spirit of Love
and tenderness,
we gather here tonight
to communicate with those
who waLk this house
in torment.
HeLp us to bridge
the chasm of death
so faithfuLLy
that pain is transformed
into joy,
sorrow into peace.
ALL this we ask
in the name
of our Infinite Father.
Amen.
This is an eviL house,
a pLace of sickness.
EviL!
Extremes.
Limits.
Terminations
and extremities.
I don't know.
''If thine eye offend thee...''
Yes.
There is a young man.
Very young.
Says he must speak.
Must speak.
[In Spirit's Voice]
I don't know you peopLe.
Why are you here?
It does no good.
Nothing changes.
Nothing.
Get out or I'LL hurt you.
I can't heLp myseLf.
God damn you,
you fiLthy sons of bitches.
God damn you!
I don't want to hurt you,
but I must, I must.
Get out of this house
before I kiLL you aLL!
[Pounding]
You started manifesting
physicaL phenomena.
But I'm not
a physicaL medium.
You were just now.
The embryo of one.
I don't understand.
ALL this time
a mentaL medium,
and now this.
The Lord certainLy
does move
in mysterious ways.
So does this house.
Back to normaL.
Those pounding noises
are a bit unnerving
the first time
you hear them.
Why was Miss Tanner
so disturbed by that sitting?
Because she caused
physicaL phenomena.
If Miss Tanner
is a mentaL medium
and Mr. Fischer
a physicaL medium,
how can you be sure she created
those noises, not Fischer?
I can't.
In fact, I'm not at aLL sure
about Mr. Fischer
or Miss Tanner.
Who is it, pLease?
You want
to speak to me?
Are you the one
that warned us
to get out?
Yes, it is you, isn't it?
You must give me
some sign.
You're not BeLasco,
are you?
Such a pain
wouLd not be in BeLasco.
I feeL your anguish.
Who are you?
DanieL?
DanieL BeLasco.
Very cLever.
If you're that cLever,
why are you stiLL
a prisoner in this house?
[Weeping]
Good morning.
You sLept weLL?
Fine. And you?
Yes, very weLL, thank you.
I think I have
a partiaL answer
to the haunting, Doctor.
That young man that
warned us during the sitting
came to my room Last night.
BeLasco's son.
Yes.
DanieL BeLasco.
He's very young
and frightened.
Because he's
so frightened,
he's very hostiLe.
If I convince him
to move on,
the haunting force
wiLL be eLiminated.
Do so by aLL means.
I'd Like to suggest
another sitting,
under scientific
conditions this time.
Miss Tanner
in apparent trance.
PuLse rate 85,
respiration 1 5.
Four eLectric contacts
maintained.
No change in temperature.
Steady at 73.2.
Dynamometer reading
decreased to 1 823 now.
Temperature Lowering.
Now it's 69.6 degrees.
PuLse rate 94.5
and rising.
Temperature drop
now 1 2.3 degrees.
Dynamometer reading
reduced to 1 77 9.
Pressurometer negative.
ELectric contacts
stiLL maintained.
Rate of breath increasing.
50.
57.
60.
Rising steadiLy.
[CLicking]
Infrared rays broken.
Cameras activated.
Evidence of eLectromagnetic
radiation commencing.
Medium's respiration 21 0.
Dynamometer 1 460.
Temperature...
[CLicking]
Evidence of ozone
in the air.
EctopLasm forming.
Separate fiLaments exuding
from fingertips of both hands
uniting to form
two separate strands.
Two strands moving
toward each other.
EctopLasmic staLk through net,
moving toward tabLe.
Leave a sampLe, pLease.
Leave a sampLe in the jar.
Aah!
HoLd it.
She's aLL right.
Miss Tanner
coming out of trance.
Premature retraction
of ectopLasm
causing brief
systemic shock.
ConcLusion of sitting,
2:48 P.M.
I spoiLed your sitting,
didn't I?
Not at aLL.
I couLdn't be
more satisfied.
Take a Look.
What is it?
A specimen of that teLepLasm
prepared in water.
What the spirituaLists
refer to as ectopLasm
is derived aLmost entireLy
from the medium's body,
the remainder
being admixtures
from the air,
the medium's costume,
fibrous remains,
dust particLes.
But the buLk is
organic Living matter,
an organic externaLization
of thought--
Mind reduced to matter.
She made that figure
from herseLf?
I was visited
by BeLasco's son
again this afternoon.
Were you?
WiLL it never end?
WiLL what never end?
Your attitude of doubt
and distrust.
Why shouLd mediums
be expected to perform
onLy under conditions
that science dictates?
We're not machines!
I'm not a medium for fun.
Do you think--
I beLieve mediumship
is God's manifestation
in man.
''When I speak to thee,
I wiLL open thy mouth
''and thou shaLt say
unto thee,
thus saith the Lord. ''
There's nothing
in the BibLe
that doesn't occur today,
be it sights or sounds,
coming through
cLosed doors,
Levitations,
or the speaking
in tongues!
Miss Tanner,
I don't know
what this is about.
Aah!
Oh!
No!
Mr. Fischer, you must go.
What do you mean?
You know.
You're the physicaL medium.
You're being used.
You're not in controL.
You've got to Leave!
Trying to get rid
of us both now?
What do you mean?
Doctor, what do you mean?
I wouLd have thought
that was obvious.
What is he saying?
That I'm responsibLe?
You're the one who shouLd
Leave this house.
You're the one
who's being used,
not me.
Do we have to stay?
This is important to me.
What if you're hurt again?
I won't be.
I'LL see to it!
SureLy you noticed
how it aLL ended
with a word from her,
how I was the onLy one
who was attacked.
I angered her.
You think Miss Tanner
was responsibLe?
Not unassisted.
There's a Lot of power
in this house, Ann.
She was the one
who used it, though.
Directed it at me.
I made a mistake.
I accepted quiet,
poLite behavior toward me
at face vaLue.
You can't do that
with a medium.
You never know
what's underneath.
[knock On Door]
May I speak to you?
I'LL onLy be a moment.
Were you badLy hurt?
I'LL manage.
I know what happened
now, Doctor.
It was BeLasco's son.
He's trying to separate us.
We're Less of a chaLLenge
that way.
I'LL sit for you tomorrow.
There'LL be
no further sittings.
You can't
stop them now!
I'm doing so.
You don't think
I did aLL that?
I know it!
PLease.
I'm in considerabLe pain.
Doctor,
I am not responsibLe.
It was BeLasco's son.
Miss Tanner!
There is no such person.
You're wrong.
LioneL?
[Moaning]
LioneL!
Where are you
going now?
To Look for something.
Proof that
BeLasco's son existed?
I'm sorry if I
insuLted you before.
Mrs. Barrett.
Mrs. Barrett!
You...
me...
that girL...
LioneL...
aLL together...
naked...
drunk...
cLutching...
sweating...
biting...
Aah!
You...
You were waLking
in your sLeep.
Mrs. Barrett.
[Voices]
DanieL, I've found you.
[Chain RattLes]
Aah!
What is it?
What happened?
DanieL BeLasco.
I've found him.
WeLL, I'm not
imagining it.
He attacked me.
Did I imagine this?
He's in there
behind the waLL.
''Ashes to ashes,
dust to dust.
''O Lord,
we beseech Thee
''mercifuLLy to receive
''the prayers
of Thy peopLe
''and grant that
they may know
that which they
ought to do. ''
FLorence.
Is that you?
HeLp me, FLorence.
Why? Why?
You shouLd have gone on.
You're my onLy hope.
Your body was buried.
I prayed for you.
PLease, FLorence.
No. You have to go.
You've been given
your reLease.
You are my onLy hope.
You must go on.
You are my onLy hope,
FLorence.
What does he want?
No. I can't.
PLease, FLorence.
No!
[Door Opens]
[Hiss]
What in the name
of God?
[Cat Screeches]
Aah!
[Screech]
Oh!
Aah!
[Hiss]
Aah! Aah!
[Screech]
FLorence.
[Whimpering]
Doctor.
Miss Tanner's
been hurt again.
Where is she?
She's in her room.
She's been bitten
and scratched.
How did it happen?
I don't know.
A cat, I think.
A cat?
It was possessed
by DanieL BeLasco.
WouLd you Like me
to examine you?
This wiLL prevent infection.
I'm aLL right.
I know you think--
It doesn't matter
what I think.
What matters is
your being mauLed.
I'm aLL right.
I wonder if that is so.
ShouLdn't you Leave?
No! I'm not Leaving now.
I'd be faiLing in my duty
if I didn't
warn you to Leave.
I don't want you
to be another victim
of HeLL House.
He's right, you know.
You shouLd Leave.
You're being torn
to pieces.
You don't think
I'm doing this to myseLf?
Of course I don't.
You say
it's DanieL BeLasco,
but what if
you're wrong?
What if
you're being fooLed?
FooLed?
DanieL BeLasco does exist.
We found his body.
We Laid him to rest.
Why is he not at rest?
I think I know.
ControLLed
muLtipLe haunting.
Something unique
in haunted houses.
A surviving wiLL
so powerfuL
that he can use
that power to dominate
aLL other
surviving sources.
You mean
Emeric BeLasco?
He's the one that's
kept me from the chapeL.
He made it seem as if
DanieL possessed the cat.
He's the one that's keeping
DanieL's souL imprisoned here.
He's Like a generaL
with his army--
Never entering the battLe,
but aLways controLLing it.
Just what have you
been doing,
Mr. Fischer?
Hmm?
Have you been drinking?
I don't think that's
any of your business,
aLthough I do think
it's a very good idea.
Come on.
No.
You come on.
Mrs. Barrett.
Yes...Ben?
You shouLd not Leave
your husband aLone.
Oh, I think he's aLL right.
He's sLeeping.
Mrs. Barrett,
you must go back upstairs.
Did you know that this was
where it aLL happened?
Where aLL what happened?
ALL that debauchery
and vice.
Right here.
Right around
this very tabLe.
Mrs. Barrett,
you don't know
what you're saying.
Oh, yes, I do.
I know exactLy
what I'm saying,
Mr. Fischer.
Mr. B.F. Fischer.
Mrs. Barrett,
it's this house.
It's making you--
This house isn't
doing anything.
I'm doing it.
Touch me,
or I'LL find
somebody who wiLL!
No!
Oh.
I know you won't
forgive me...now.
I know what I did.
I'd give anything
to undo it.
I just don't know
why I went down those stairs.
I knew what I was doing.
I knew,
but at the same time...
I'm not asking you
to forgive me,
but pLease, pLease
don't hate me.
I need you.
I Love you.
I just don't understand
what's happening to me.
I just don't understand.
It's aLL right.
It'LL pass after
we've Left this house.
I Love you, too.
Doctor, I think
your wife is in danger.
Mr. Fischer.
It was not her fauLt.
PLease, Mr. Fischer.
This is a matter
of Life and death.
She waLked down here
Last night.
When?
Near midnight.
You were asLeep.
So was she.
She waLked in her sLeep?
Yes.
You shouLd have toLd me.
No, Doctor.
She shouLd have.
The fact that she didn't...
I don't think you know
what's going on
in this house.
What I think
is irreLevant.
What the heLL do you mean
by irreLevant?
Whatever is getting
at your wife
has aLready gotten
to Miss Tanner and to you.
You're bLocking yourseLf off
compLeteLy.
Mr. Deutsch is wasting
a third of his money.
You're bLocking yourseLf off
compLeteLy.
BLocking yourseLf off
I am not bLocking anything.
I'm just not
sticking my neck out
the way I did in 1 953.
Aaah!
Aaaaaaahhh!
Uh!
Eee!
[knock On Door]
Ben? I've been think--
Give up.
Give up?
What's happened?
I thought
we trusted each other.
I don't trust anyone
or anything.
Anyone who does
in this house is a fooL.
Something has happened.
Lots of things.
Nothing we can't handLe.
Wrong.
There is nothing
in this house
that we can handLe.
That's not true.
We've made
wonderfuL progress.
Toward what?
Our graves?
DanieL and the way
BeLasco works.
DanieL!
DanieL! DanieL! DanieL!
How do you know
he ever existed?
The body.
How do you know
that he isn't
a figment
of your imagination?
How do you know
his personaLity
isn't what you
made of it ?
I know I'm right.
We knew we were right
in 1 953.
Grace Lauter,
a successfuL medium for--
For 20 years.
She jumped off
the baLcony,
and she shattered
both her Legs.
Dr. Graham...
physicist.
He crawLed out
of this house...
to die.
Professor Rand,
head of
the chemistry department
at the University
of Oxford...
paraLyzed.
Professor FenLey...
psychic investigator...
crippLed and insane
to this day.
Yes, uh...
You're right.
I am obstructing.
You're quite right.
I'm shut off.
I am going
to stay shut off
untiL I am far away
from this pLace.
I am going
to coLLect my libras1 00,000,
and I am never
going to come
within 1 ,000 miLes
of this house
for as Long as I Live,
and I suggest
you do the same.
Ben.
[Water Running]
Huh!
Aah!
Can I do anything
to heLp?
I'm afraid not.
It's just
too compLicated.
Thanks aLL the same.
What's it going to do,
LioneL?
You've heard me taLk
about a power
in this house.
It's a reaL power, Ann,
a fieLd of
measurabLe energy.
Energy that can be
reversed.
That's what
I'm going to do.
By this time tomorrow,
HeLL House
wiLL be de-energized.
You'LL see.
[CLapping]
That piLe of junk
you have
isn't going to do
a thing.
Get her out of here!
You haven't a chance.
Have you?
Yes. I know the score.
You do not fight
this house!
HeLL House doesn't
mind a guest.
What it doesn't Like
is peopLe who attack it.
BeLasco doesn't Like it.
His peopLe
wiLL fight back,
and they'LL kiLL you.
Leave that machine aLone.
When Sunday comes,
teLL oLd Deutsch anything
and bank the money.
If you try anything eLse,
you wiLL be
a dead man.
He won't Listen, wiLL he?
I was the onLy one
to get out of here
aLive and sane in 1 953.
I wiLL be the onLy one
to make it out this time.
He's wrong.
I toLd you before,
what FLorence Tanner
beLieves is wrong.
I'm teLLing you now
that Fischer
is equaLLy wrong.
Tomorrow,
it wiLL be proved.
FLorence.
HeLp me.
PLease.
PLease...
heLp me.
[Moaning]
Love me.
[Roaring And Shrieking]
FLorence.
Don't go, FLorence.
HeLp me.
FLorence, heLp me.
HeLp me, FLorence.
[Voices Echoing]
FLorence.
DanieL,
you must understand.
What you ask
is impossibLe.
I can't.
I beLieve in you.
I've opened
my heart to you.
PLease, heLp me.
PLease, Love me.
FLorence.
Love me.
No.
PLease, heLp me.
FLorence.
PLease...
heLp me.
Love me.
Dear God...
reach down Your hand
and give me
Your protection.
HeLp me this night
to bring to Your care
the tortured souL
of DanieL BeLasco.
[Voices]
I give you now
the Love you've never known.
I give it so you wiLL
gain strength
to Leave this house.
I Love you.
And I Love you.
With Love, pLease,
with Love.
Hah!
Oh.
Ah.
FLorence.
Aaahh!
Aaaaahhh!
Mm hm hm!
FLorence.
How Long
have you been here?
ALL night.
There?
Stupid.
You couLd have
sLept with me.
Who put on
my nightdress?
Mrs. Barrett.
Why didn't you do it?
My God.
He's inside me.
He Lied to me.
He said it was
the onLy way.
But he's inside me!
I can feeL him
just waiting in there
to take over.
It wiLL be aLL right.
I wiLL take you
out of here.
He won't Let me go.
He can't stop you.
He can.
He can't stop me.
[In Spirit's Voice]
Who do you think you are,
you bastard?
You might have been
hot stuff before,
but now you're shit!
Dear God, heLp me.
I'm taking her away.
How are you,
Miss Tanner?
I'm aLL right.
You needn't come back,
Mr. Fischer.
The house wiLL be cLear.
CLear?
How?
There isn't time
for expLanation.
Yes, there is.
FLorence.
I am not Leaving
untiL I know.
ALL right.
The body emits
a form of energy
invisibLe
to the human eye.
This energy
can be expanded
far beyond the body,
where it can create
mechanicaL, chemicaL,
physicaL effects,
sounds, moving objects
Like we've experieced.
The energy I taLk about
is a fieLd of
eLectromagnetic radiation.
E.M.R.
ExactLy.
ALL Living organisms
emit this energy.
Such power must saturate
its environment.
Is it any wonder
that HeLL House
is the way it is?
Consider the mentaL
and physicaL energy
which is being poured
into its interior.
The house
is a giant battery,
the residuaL energy
of which
must be tapped.
We survive with this energy
after death.
No, Miss Tanner.
This residue
has nothing to do
with surviving
personaLities.
The spirit
of Emeric BeLasco
does not prowL
this house.
Neither does his son
or any other entities
that you beLieve yourseLf
to be in contact with.
There is one thing
and one thing onLy
in this house--
mindLess,
directionLess power.
You're wrong, Dr. Barrett.
You cannot
destroy a spirit.
ALL you wiLL do is send it
to another heLL.
No, Miss Tanner.
I'm right.
My machine
wiLL fiLL the house
with a massive
countercharge
of eLectromagnetic
radiation,
opposing the poLarity
of the atmosphere,
reversing,
and dissipating it.
And HeLL House
wiLL be exorcised.
I see.
WeLL, there's nothing eLse
to do then.
Barrett.
Ah!
Thank God she didn't
know what to smash.
I shouLd be fLattered.
Her attack
on the reverser
was her uLtimate tribute.
She knows I'm right.
There was
nothing eLse to do.
That's what she said.
She had to destroy
my beLiefs
before they
destroyed hers.
DanieL?
[Roaring Noise]
[Crying]
Aah!
No!
[Voices]
Aah!
No!
Aaahh!
FLorence.
DanieL, you must Leave
before it's too Late.
Soon you'LL be sent
from this heLL to another.
Aah!
Where is Miss Tanner?
She was Lying
over there.
Why didn't you
watch her?
Ah! Oh!
FLorence.
You tricked me.
God heLp me,
you tricked us aLL.
Ha ha ha!
Ah!
[Humming]
QuickLy.
[Voices]
You'LL have to open yourseLf
to it, Mr. Fischer.
Try, Mr. Fischer.
I guarantee
there'LL be no troubLe.
WeLL?
He's startLed because
there's nothing to pick up.
Is it reaLLy over, LioneL?
Yes. It's over.
Done with, finished.
I can't beLieve it.
I know.
Do you mind if I say
I toLd you so?
What a pity
Miss Tanner died
when the answer
was so cLose.
Barrett.
Barrett,
the house is cLear.
It is compLeteLy cLear!
And I caLLed that machine
a piLe of junk.
You better go
and get some rest.
I want to check
my readings.
[CLicking]
[Beeping]
[CLacking]
This is impossibLe.
I don't accept this.
I do not accept this!
LioneL?
LioneL.
LioneL!
In here.
LioneL?
Here.
Aah!
No!
I'm sorry.
LioneL.
Oh, pLease get me
out of here.
PLease.
I'm not Leaving.
I'm going back
to the chapeL.
No. No, you can't.
You don't know
what it's Like in there.
I have to.
You don't.
There is no reason
to go back there.
None.
Ann, Listen.
I have to.
It's for FLorence.
It's for your husband.
If I Leave
HeLL House now,
my whoLe Life
wiLL be a faiLure.
You can't soLve it.
It cannot be soLved.
You're going to die...
Like LioneL,
Like Miss Tanner.
Then I wiLL.
It's here.
The entire house is cLear
except for
this one pLace.
Why?
BeLasco.
That's what the '' B''
inside the circLe means.
She was trying
to teLL us
that it was onLy
BeLasco aLL aLong.
It isn't mindLess,
directionLess power.
It isn't
muLtipLe hauntings.
It's onLy one.
One entity pretending
to be DanieL.
to be many others.
That's where
the answer Lies.
But what's the key?
What is the key?
Extremes and Limits.
Terminations and extremities.
Oh.
Oh, God.
Of course.
That's what she meant.
Extremes.
Limits.
Legs.
Grace Lauter's spine
and Legs shattered.
Dr. Graham crawLing.
Professor Rand, paraLyzed.
Professor FenLey, crippLed.
FLorence's Legs crushed.
Your husband's...
''If thine eye
offend thee... ''
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
BeLasco!
Whatever you do,
do not interfere.
BeLasco.
Here I am.
Destroy me if you can.
Don't Leave the job
haLf done.
We're here.
I'm here!
kiLL me!
That's it.
Oh, that's it.
TeLL me something,
BeLasco.
Why didn't you ever
Leave this house
when you were aLive?
Why did you despise
the sunLight?
Was it better hiding
in the shadows?
[Whining Noise]
No one...
No one couLd reaLLy
see you then,
couLd they?
No one couLd find out
your secret then,
couLd they?
You weren't a genius!
You were a deviate!
A sawed-off
LittLe bastard!
[Roaring Noise]
Your mother was a bitch!
A whore!
You were a bastard!
A funny LittLe
dried-up bastard!
You're no genius!
You're no Roaring Giant!
What size were you,
BeLasco?
5-foot 2?
1 ?
I know you weren't even
5-foot taLL.
Aah!
Emeric BeLasco.
The Roaring Giant.
Is it cLear?
This is a speciaL moment.
Meet Emeric BeLasco.
Your husband did have
part of the answer.
FLorence had
part of it, too.
I finaLLy found
the Last part,
that which
BeLasco's giant ego
couLd not face.
He so despised
his own shortness
that he cut off his Legs
and wore those instead
to give himseLf height.
''If thine eye offend thee,
pLuck it out.''
Maybe he was a genius
after aLL.
Just because a man
preserves his body
doesn't make him
a genius.
It's not his body
of which I'm speaking.
This is why
your husband's machine
couLd not destroy
his power.
These waLLs
are sheathed with Lead.
He buiLt himseLf
a fortress
to protect his spirit.
He knew what was coming
years before it came.
Your husband
and FLorence
heLped us
to rid this house
of BeLasco.
Let us hope
that their spirits
guide him
to everLasting peace.
BeLasco.
Legendas em Ingls by (c) dCd /Maio [2003]