Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
You got it.
He's in the bar right there.
Be careful. Cops.
Right there.
Out.
Yeah, just give us one more.
All right, time to go home, pal.
You've been sitting here
over two hours,
and all you've ordered is one shot.
l got paying customers
looking for a seat here.
One shot's all l need.
l'm a resourceful kind of guy.
All right, get the fuck
out of here, man.
Just go feel sorry for yourself
someplace else, okay?
Get the--!
Jesus!
Shit.
What?
l'm gonna kick
your fucking ass, that's what.
Well, go ahead and do it, then.
I reaIIy wish we hadn't started here.
It's too easy to get
the wrong idea about me.
That's Dawn, my wife.
A Car aCCident ended
that happiness,
Ieaving me with an empty home
and an empty Iife.
There you go.
Stace, can we get a couple
of Millers, please?
You sure?
You know we have
Miller Lite on special.
Yeah, well, if l was on a diet
l wouldn't order beer.
All right, Swain.
Two Millers coming up for you guys.
Thanks, honey.
l gotta get out of this town.
Go somewhere nice...
like a beach somewhere,
you know what l mean?
Become a Rastafarian.
You all right, buddy?
Yeah.
What about you?
Surely you don't want to stay
in this shithole forever.
l don't know.
Next time can we get a puppy?
l'm just waiting
for my ship to come in,
then l'm bye-bye.
l don't know.
Somebody please help me!
Help me! Oh, my God!
Please help me!
Help me!
Give me your coat!
Call 91 1 . Call right now! Go!
Help!
Hi. l'm here to help you, okay?
Don't worry.
Don't worry, l got you.
Please, help me!
Somebody help me!
lt's gonna be all right.
Just keep your head down, okay?
Take her. Take her!
You all right, man?
Can't believe
you just fucking did that.
You're a fucking hero, man.
Get a fucking ambulance over here!
l'll call 91 1 right now.
Mom, l love you.
You're okay.
For the first time
sinCe Dawn had died,
I'd done something worth doing.
That day I saved a Iife.
But not today.
The road to heII is paved
with good intentions.
Everybody's heard the saying
''Never get Caught
with your pants down.''
Everybody but LynCh MCGraw.
Yeah, that's right, baby.
Oh, shit!
You dropped your fucking gun!
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
You like that, you punk bitch?
Hello. How are you this morning?
Good.
So, what can l do for you?
l'd like to cash this, please.
Hey, l know you.
You're the guy
that saved that little girl
from that car a couple years ago.
Yeah, you saw that?
l saw the whole thing on ''Dateline.''
That was a really
brave thing you did.
Anybody else would have done
the same thing, l think.
l don't know, you know.
Tell me you're not high.
l'm cool. God damn!
You fucking better be.
Security guard's right on time.
Well, girls, no turning back now.
Fuck turning back.
We're doing this shit.
Swain, you sure
you don't want in on this?
- l think l'm in this enough, right?
- You sure?
Come on, can't you feel
my heart beating?
This is gonna be one hell of a rush,
don't you think?
- Are we ready?
- Sure.
- Everything's in the bag?
- Yeah.
- Masks, everything?
You fucking behave.
Ready, big boy?
What are we waiting for?
Let's do this!
Nobody fucking moves,
nobody fucking dies.
l guarantee it.
Yeah, so, lover boy.
That's enough from you.
Tellers, back away
from that counter.
Put your hands
on top of your heads.
Everybody else on the floor now!
What are you doing
standing there?
Open the drawer now.
You think about
doing some dumb shit,
l'll put a bullet
in your face, Comprende?
That's right, folks,
this is not a reenactment,
so for your own comfort and joy,
could you please keep
your legs and your arms
within the vehicle!
Otherwise, you may lose them.
Thank you.
Why the fuck are you standing?
On the floor!
- Move, bitch.
- l'm going as fast as l can.
No doubt, G,
she's a fine piece of ass.
l'd wax this shit
till midnight next Thursday!
- Holy shit!
- Jesus Christ!
Shit was an accident.
Shit just went off, man.
Get the fucking money.
What is this? This is a bank?
No, no, no, no, no.
Get his black ass
back out of there!
Get the fuck back over here!
What did you do?
lf you don't get back over here,
l'm gonna do it again.
- Fill it up!
- Let's go, let's go!
Hey, what did l tell you?
This is what happens
when you people move!
Jesus, this wasn't
supposed to happen!
- We shouldn't even be here!
- Shut the fuck up, bitch!
- And grow up!
- Kill him.
Kill him!
We gotta move. Kill him.
Come on, come on, come on!
Let's go! Cops are coming.
- Come on.
- Go. Go, go, go, go!
Can l help you?
You're the man
who tried to save her.
- lt's Liam, right?
- Yes, hi.
l'm so glad you came!
And so would Kayla be,
if she knew you were here.
l brought her these.
Thank you. Those are beautiful.
l guess now we know
who to thank
for all these other
beautiful red roses.
Her father
passed away last year.
l'm sorry, l don't know
why l mentioned that.
Oh, no, that's all right.
l'm just...
so thankful
for what you tried to do.
l just reacted.
Real heroes like you, Liam,
are always humble.
They always say they just reacted.
I feIt Iost, I feIt...
Confused.
I feIt I had no ChoiCes,
no options.
When a man is pushed,
he wiII Commit aCts of vioIenCe
he normaIIy CouId not imagine.
Cause of death...
Take your pick.
But...
l'm betting it's the frying pan
with the brains smeared all over it.
Maybe he was cookin' up
a freaky lunch.
lf he was, he would've, l'm sure,
used somebody else's brain
rather than his own.
Yeah, right.
We get an lD on this guy?
Yeah, Lynch McGraw.
He had a rap sheet
longer than Florida.
The way he lived,
never any question
about the way he would die.
He's still somebody's son, right?
Well...
somebody's dead son, yeah.
l'm sure his family
didn't even like him.
Somebody's son.
lt's quite a mess, ain't it, sir.
Nothing l ain't seen before...
like Beirut.
Don't you want to know
about the perp, sir?
What'd you say?
The perp, sir.
Let's pretend for a second
that l'm not a complete idiot
after 30 years, okay?
And assume, if you will,
l've been around this place
one or two times already
ahead of you.
- You got it?
- Yes, sir.
And that l got
a long day ahead of me
because of some
pan-happy nut job
who likes to whack people
about the head!
- Can you pretend that for me?
- Yes, sir.
How dare you ask me
something like that!
Now, stop pretending it
and go get me a coffee.
lt's unbeliev--
These uniforms, they're idiots!
You're scaring people.
Scarin' peo--
Well, you're ogling a dead body.
ls that business or personal?
You notice the puncture wound
to the groin?
Yeah, l saw that,
but that was personal.
- You're a sick man.
- l'm hungry.
Hey, where's my coffee?
Lieutenant CoIoneI
WaIter ''Cosmo'' JaCkson.
Did two tours in 'Nam with my dad.
When Dad died, Cosmo beCame
my obIigatory father figure.
You can't be fucking serious.
They tried to kill me.
So?
Well, you think there's
some kind of divine justice
around here, is that it?
You think you're
God's own avenging angel?
Well, l got news for you, kid.
lt don't work like that.
And don't talk to me about death
like l'm some dancer
that's never hit the floor.
Now, l understand you got
your grievances with these fools,
but you need to talk
to the police and air this shit.
Tell 'em you found out
who the cocksuckers are.
lt's complicated.
Christ, Liam, killin' a man
ain't never easy.
Now you just--
you just take a second here...
and think.
No. No police.
Maybe l did something
l shouldn't have, but...
what's done is done.
Yeah, well, maybe you're right.
You go to the cops now,
they'll lock you up for life.
Maybe that's what you get--
what you deserve.
And then how true
would be my word?
l made your dad a promise
l'd do everything l could
to keep you safe and clean,
same as he did to me.
l need your help.
Revenge.
It's an airborne disease,
and it traveIs fast.
We need to talk.
Why, man?
l said we got to talk!
l'm trying to get some.
Take it easy.
Get up.
Beat it!
Let's go.
What's up?
Someone killed Skinner's brother.
l'm sorry, man.
What happened?
He was beat to death.
With a wok.
A what?
A wok. Chinese skillet.
Doesn't make any sense, though.
l mean, Lynch, he was...
Who do you guys think it was?
Do the math. lt was Liam.
l ain't buying that shit.
Not on his fucking
best day of his life
is he gonna kill your brother.
No, l'm telling you,
he's unbalanced.
lf ''unbalanced'' means ''drunk''...
You know what, hero boy
was in the news for one minute,
and he hasn't seen
a single one of us since he came to.
Yeah, there's a reason
for that, too.
'Cause he thinks one of you
are gonna hurt the girl.
You're a clever fucking boy.
Give yourself a round of applause.
'Course he knows we're gonna
hurt the girl, but l'm tellin' you,
freak show does not have
the juice to fuck your brother.
l sit here and l listen
to you guys chatter,
no facts coming out
of either one of you.
Only fact is
my little brother's dead.
Yeah, we'll fix it. We'll do it.
Yeah, we will.
Let's say we go
to Liam Case's place.
That's what you want?
That's a done deal.
Shit. Shit.
- Hi.
lt's just me.
Are you busy?
- Mind if l come in a minute?
- Sure.
Thanks.
l'm sorry about the mess.
Please, don't apologize.
l'm the one who should
be saying l'm sorry.
- For what?
- For just... dropping by like this.
l hate it when people come
to my house unannounced.
l don't mind.
How is she doing today?
Oh, you know...
What's it been, three months now?
Three months without a change.
l'm sorry.
Oh, don't.
Please, Liam.
You didn't shoot her.
Hey, come here.
Have a seat.
l don't want to talk
about my daughter tonight.
Seems like all l do
is talk about my daughter,
think about my daughter.
lt's like l don't... have a life,
you know,
of my own, you know?
lt's like sometimes l...
think that l just wish she'd die
so that l could just carry on.
Don't say that.
Sorry.
Most of the time l'm...
l wish it was me that was dead.
l know how you feel, Melanie.
How could you?
This is kind of embarrassing.
Would it be all right
if l spent the night here,
you know, just for a little while?
Oh, yes.
Please, l really can't go back
to that empty house.
l can't.
MeIanie feeIs she's got
nothing Ieft to Iive for.
It's a feeIing I know aII too weII.
Oh, man, do we have work to do.
Yeah.
Now, first thing, turn off
the movie in your head.
Support the bottom of your gun
with the left hand.
Stop it from kicking you
in the face.
Now, you won't always
have time to use the sights,
but whenever you can,
you use it.
You drop a line down that bastard
and you squeeze.
Never pull it. Just squeeze.
Go ahead.
Give me that thing.
That's how it's done.
Yeah.
You know, the cops'll be looking
for whoever killed that guy.
He was a wannabe gangbanger
who lived in a grease pit.
There's probably 100 guys
wanting to kill him,
including the police.
Yeah?
Load.
Squeeze.
Better.
No doubt, G,
she's a fine piece of ass.
l'd wax this shit
till midnight next Thursday!
You like that, you punk bitch?
Just 'cause you can't shoot
don't mean l can't, motherfucker.
Stay off the court if you don't
own ball for the bizounce!
Fuck! Fuck.
Come on, answer the fucking phone.
Answer the phone, man!
You motherfucker!
Fuck your fucking head!
Don't you ever fucking die,
you motherfucker?
You want to die, motherfucker?
You're gonna fucking die!
Can't breathe, huh?
Oh, my dick!
Hey, buddy, long time no see.
What do you want?
Where's the love?
Ain't you gonna invite us
into your little shithole?
l don't like people
stopping by unannounced.
Cut the shit.
You know why we're here.
- Refresh my memory.
- Come on.
Fuck this.
- lt was you, wasn't it, boy?
- l don't know what you talking about.
- You don't know?
- Liam, is everything okay?
Hey, the dude's got company.
Liam?
Yeah, l'm fine.
Okay, okay, you know
what we're gonna do here?
We're gonna talk tomorrow night.
We're gonna go to the Razor Room.
Should feel safe there.
lt's not my kind of place.
lt's gonna be your kind of place.
You know why?
'Cause if you don't show,
l am gonna drive to the hospital
and l'm gonna go to Room 248
and l'm gonna give my regards
to Kayla McQueen.
Got that?
Haven't you caused her
enough pain?
Hey, save it, save it.
Come on, man.
l haven't even started.
Haven't even started.
Good night.
Tomorrow, you crazy fuck.
Check out that chick over there.
Look who's comin'.
Your cousins.
You're fucked.
- Fucking hell.
- What do you got?
Nothing. Fucking nothing.
What's this?
Why, it's good to see you too.
Things have changed.
Didn't we talk about this already?
We did. He's family, he's my cousin--
he's also Lynch's cousin too.
Fine, fuck it.
You don't need me, then.
Where are you goin'?
To find Liam.
And then what, tough guy?
You're in as deep as l am,
as deep as these guys are,
understand what l'm saying?
Let him go, Derek,
just let him go.
Yeah, go bye-byes.
Bye bye bye bye!
When it's over,
l'm gonna kill him.
Fine.
What's up?
What?
What's not convincing you?
Derek, how many fucking times
do l have to tell you?
lt was fucking Liam.
You were with me in his apartment.
That boy was laughing at us.
He was fucking laughing at us.
Lynch tried to kill him.
What would you do
if someone tried to kill you?
l'm tellin' you,
he's not got the fucking juice.
- l gotta take a piss.
- You go piss, yeah.
Give me a smoke.
- Listen.
- What?
lf l tell you to fuck up Swain,
you fuck up Swain.
Don't you ever threaten him
in front of me again,
'cause he's one of ours.
Your brother died
with his dick in his hands too.
You're dead!
Get up!
Fucker!
Cocksucker!
You sick fuck.
You sick fuck!
Hey, did Case show?
What do you think?
Where's Skinner, man?
Fuck Skinner.
Lynch, the guy that got
whacked with the pan?
They just found
his brother dead too.
Marley, what are you doing here?
l came to see you.
Where have you been?
A friend's.
Same friend who beat you up?
What, are you writing a report?
What's your problem?
l'm sorry, it's just...
lt's just kind of a bad time right now.
What are you doing out
so late, anyway?
- Mom's on a date.
- Yeah?
Well, maybe you should get home
before she gets back.
You don't want me here?
No, Marley, it's not that.
lt's just... l got a lot of stuff
l'm sorting out right now.
You don't like me anymore?
You know that l do.
You're like a little sister
to me, Marley.
A sister?
Yeah.
l don't think of you like a brother.
You don't?
Back up.
Marley...
if you were older,
you wouldn't think like that.
Yes, l would.
l'm old enough to know what l think.
Marley, you're a pretty little girl,
and l'm sure all the boys
are chasing you in school--
l don't like the boys at school.
Listen, Marley,
this really isn't the time for this.
Screw you, Liam.
Yep, that went well.
When I saved MarIey,
I did it without knowing,
without seIfish motivations.
I just reaCted.
I saw someone in need.
The worId had written me off,
and yet I aCCompIished
something good in spite of it aII.
Liam!
l got this for you.
It's hard not to bask in it,
not to Iove every seCond of it.
And so today,
on behaIf of this great City,
I'm proud to present to Liam Case
the highest honor we Can bestow.
Endangering yourself
to save the life of another
has more than earned our respect.
So, Liam, please accept
this medal and plaque
in recognition
of your selfless valor.
Thank you.
l just want to say thank you for this
to all the firefighters and policemen
who do this on a regular basis,
things far more courageous
or heroic than l could have...
l just want to say thank you.
Thank you.
Come on in.
Shut the door.
- What are you doing?
- Shut the fucking door.
Look, l know you got a gun,
so put it on the table.
This has got nothing
to do with her.
Relax, man, l'm just here to talk.
Have a seat.
You been to any clubs lately?
You want to stop this
before this goes too far?
l trusted you.
Look at you, sitting there
all fucking righteous.
You're a hypocrite!
Yeah, l screwed up,
l made a mistake-- l got that!
l have to live with it,
but that's what l'm gonna do.
l'm gonna live with it.
Then why are you still here?
Thirty-five divided by five
doesn't make me Donald Trump!
Where the fuck am l gonna go?
Was it worth it?
You didn't even
fucking know that girl.
Who?
Fuck.
Go ahead. Tell her.
What? What girl?
Go ahead! Tell her.
- You're gonna have to shoot me.
- What?
No!
Fuck you.
Guess we're all
going to hell, right?
What's going on, Liam?
Put the gun down, Melanie.
- Who was that?
- Nobody.
Tell me.
Just put the gun down.
You tell me.
He was involved in Kayla's shooting.
How?
He was with those guys
at the bank that day.
And how is it that you know him?
That's a long story.
l've got lots of time.
My daughter's in a coma,
remember?
We used to work together.
And?
And l know those guys
at the bank too.
Two of them are already dead.
Please make me understand.
lt's complicated.
Don't touch me.
You stay away... from me,
and you keep away
from my daughter.
Whatever you say.
You kill those bastards.
Look, l didn't hear shit, man.
lf l did, l probably thought it was
them backbeats we were tossing.
You're telling me you didn't
hear or see anything.
Aside from the dead guy
in the bathroom?
Yes, aside from the dead guy
in the bathroom.
No, nothing out of the ordinary.
This is a club restroom.
Everybody's got a number one
or a two in them somewhere.
He's got a point.
No, l'm serious.
Listen, ever since Bush bunny
let that ban on assault rifles expire,
it's like the ''Realm of Chaos''
in here, without all the tentacles.
l was probably just in the next room
when it all went down.
Go ahead and go do
whatever you do.
You sure?
l'm sure. Go.
Cool, bro. l hope you guys
catch your man, all right?
McGraw family's dropping like flies
around here, Sub.
lt's quite a coincidence,
two dead brothers.
Yeah, right.
What are you thinking?
That robbery at Star Financial.
l mean, we found
that burnt-out car in the river.
FBl ended up blaming those kids
that were passing through
on a cross-country binge.
They pinned it on
those guys from Parkers--
l don't--
l don't know.
l never really bought it.
You know, l'm a pretty smart guy,
but l don't have a clue
where you're going with this.
Right now l'm going to Brett's.
We'll have a few drinks
and meditate on this.
Brett's.
You ain't that smart.
l didn't leave you much.
You left me enough.
Six in the corner.
What, are you scopin'
for a date or something?
No, no, it's Liam Case.
Doesn't ring a bell. Should it?
He saved that little girl
and he helped that bank teller
over there at the bank.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, l remember.
Ace in the side.
lt's just funny.
One minute he's a hero
all over the news,
next he's inside a bottle
with no exit.
He's looking like Oedipus
right after someone told him
he fucked his mother.
Yeah, it's too late in the day
for Roman mythology, Sub.
No such thing as Roman mythology.
lt's a Greek tragedy, is what it is.
Take you, for example.
You're like a chimera.
You're half man, half pool shark.
Miss one already!
Give a guy a shot.
Get the fuck out of here.
- Look.
- l know. l'm running him.
Shit. Come on, Brett,
what's the matter?
Come on, man,
you see this mess?
You okay?
Come on, come on.
- You sure you're all right?
- Yeah, yeah.
l just think happy hour
is over for me. That's it.
From the looks of things,
l'd say you're right.
Okay.
You're not driving, are you?
Want us to give you a ride home?
No, no, l'm just around the corner.
Yeah, where's my keys?
- l'm just bullshitting.
- You're not driving?
l'm right around the corner.
Thank you!
Thank you, boys.
You see the way he looked?
He was in a fight,
and it wasn't just this guy.
He was in a brawl with somebody.
You're right.
Could be a coincidence, but...
l'll have one of those.
Liam Case.
Want to try to put me
on your bitch list?
There is no list.
Yeah? So how come
two of my buddies
are fucking in the morgue,
toe-tagged?
Oh, man,
we've been through this shit.
We been through this shit?
You want me to go
talk to your buddies,
the guys with the badges,
tell them a little story?
l got a pretty good one to tell.
You know what?
You impress me.
You shock and stun me.
l mean, you did fucking Skinner,
which is very impressive,
but tell me something:
how the fuck did
you do my buddy Lynch?
'Cause he can fuck
with the best of them.
- What do you want, Derek?
- What do l want?
Well, you know what,
you're a big hero,
and in every hero's story,
there's always
a little damsel in distress.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Marley. Think you can
save her again?
- l'll kill you.
- Yeah?
With the fucking cops in there?
Go ahead, motherfucker.
You stay away from her.
Too fucking late.
Where is she?
Don't let me go,
you'll never fucking know.
What are you doing, man?
What am l doing?
Tell you what l'm doing.
Tomorrow, the factory
just off the highway,
Andrew Street,
me and you there.
High noon.
Do some western stuff.
We'll go boom boom
and see who walks away.
Marley, she's not in this, man.
lt's between us.
She's a means to an end,
and if you're a second late,
she ain't blowing no more
birthday candles out. Feel me?
Oh, fuck.
I wish I wouIdn't've survived
in the bank that day.
I wish they wouId have kiIIed me.
He knew.
He knew aII aIong, probabIy.
He knew I hadn't toId him
the whoIe story.
l thought we were finished.
l don't have anywhere else to go.
You know, l can't tell if there's
any good left in you, or...
if you're just
plain rotten to the core.
Sometimes l don't
even know myself anymore.
There's still time, Liam.
There's still time to put up the deck
before you play the final hand.
Don't let this go any further.
They got a little girl, Cosmo...
and they're gonna kill her.
l fucked up.
Now, you listen to me, kid.
l've already been
in one war that was a lie,
and l don't want to make it two...
so you better
start leveling with me now.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
I went to the Cemetery to see Dawn.
I wanted to be with her again,
one more time.
But something happened.
I Iooked, and there was this girI.
Just her very essenCe
reminded me of Dawn.
I beCame obsessed.
She represented something to me,
something good,
something that I had
that I had Iost.
I needed it, I needed her,
I needed...
I needed whatever
she represented baCk in my Iife.
But there's more.
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
Can l help you, sir?
No, no, thanks. l'm fine.
Window number three is open
if you'd like to make a transaction.
Nope. No, l was just
actually leaving. Thanks.
- Okay. Have a good day, then.
- Yeah.
Fuck.
You hear what you're saying, man?
You're talking like a crazy person.
Crazy people,
they talk like that.
She's just a chick
you want to bone, man.
No, man, no.
No, it's more than that.
More than that...
lt's insane, what you're
fucking talking about, man.
Just talk to the girl.
Come on, what've you got to lose?
Everything.
Right now l ain't got shit
to offer her.
You got your job.
l'm a garbage man, man!
So what?
Pays the fucking bills, right?
lt's gotta be right--
the moment, me, everything.
She's gotta know
that l can be more than this, man.
That sounds
all romantic and shit, but...
lt's the only way.
That's the only way.
l think your brain got burnt up
in that fire, that's what l think.
You gonna help me or not?
Could get in a lot of shit
for something like this, man.
Five grand.
l'll give you $5,000.
Five grand, that's it?
Come on, man,
l've known you a long time.
Dude, l hang with you every day.
l don't know you at all.
l'm asking you as a friend.
As a friend.
Dude, if you had a friend,
which you don't,
they would not let you
go through with this.
l'm asking, man.
You know, America was built on labor.
Look at this shit now.
Yeah, it's real fucked up.
My uncle, Sweet Dick Willy,
used to work in this factory here.
Now that nigga's on crack.
Oh, shut up!
Shut up!
Shut your mouth!
- No!
- Get out!
- No, you can't!
- l said get out!
Get away!
How's this work, again?
Come here.
Listen, listen.
You're just gonna scare
the hell out of everybody,
all right, but in the end,
nobody's gonna get hurt.
How do we not get caught?
Come on, man, listen.
l did my research already,
all right?
There's only one security guard
on Saturdays,
and he's an ex-traffic cop, all right?
The cat takes a lunch break
same time every shift,
and he's always gone
at least 40 minutes.
So, wait...
l break in, you intervene,
l get scared and run off,
that's it?
The cops'll be on their way already.
You won't have no choice
but to get the hell on.
Why me?
Why you think you?
You're the only one l trust.
Wait, wait...
Shut the fuck up, man.
l can't understand your stupid ass.
Speak English.
You're gonna tell me fuck off
and speak English, you dumb prick?
l'm Scottish for a start,
you fag-looking motherfucker.
Can l talk to you for a second, man?
l'm a little busy.
lt involves money.
lt always does.
Not like this.
You gotta go, you gotta go.
l'm listening.
That place we used to work--
can l meet you there tomorrow?
Are you the pope
of Greenwich Village?
Why can't we talk right here?
l just don't want him to hear.
What the fuck's your problem?
You still pissed 'cause my cousin
got you arrested?
No, dick,
it's 'cause l don't trust him.
That matters?
Look, man, no Gordy, no job.
He's too fucking volatile.
What the fuck
you gonna do about it!
You know what,
he is a bit of a caveman.
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow.
l don't get it.
Why doesn't he just talk to her?
l said the same thing,
man, l don't know.
What, is he fucking pussy-whipped?
Shit, if a nigger
really wanted pussy that bad,
wouldn't he just pay some ho,
say some dope?
Swain, what are you
bringing me this shit for?
l ain't gonna take a fucking risk
like that by myself.
$5,000 in a fake bank heist?
Give me a break.
l get it. This is about
the Caribbean for you, isn't it?
Hula-hula, right?
This is your chance
to put your Speedos on, hang out.
This is your chance to own up.
Liam did all this fucking homework.
He knows all the security,
all that shit.
l don't know about this, man.
A bank job? Come on.
That's fucking crazy.
We could do
some serious time for that shit.
Hang on a second.
l'm still lost.
lf he's expecting you to do this
and we show up instead,
he's gonna know that you sent us.
What's stopping him
from going to the cops?
He becomes an even bigger hero.
Well, then we tell on him.
l don't fucking know.
The last thing he wants
is for this to come back to him.
- Fuck it.
- We're doing it.
- Let's do this.
- You want to do this?
- Let's fucking do this.
- Are you serious?
- Abso-fucking-lutely.
You fellas complain about
the liquor stores, dollar stores.
With this, we won't get caught.
The penalties are the same.
- Exactly.
- The payout's huge.
You know how much money's
in that fucking bank?
You want to make nickels and dimes
or fucking dollars?
You can spend the rest
of your anorexic life on your pipe.
Screw you, all right?
l was just fucking sayin'.
All right, if l have to,
l'll take care of Case.
What are you going to do
when it's over?
Soon as we get the money,
l'm off on a fucking beach
somewhere.
Get going.
Don't forget your suntan lotion.
Come on. Hey, come on now.
Come on now. Hippity-scop.
Are you serious about this shit?
It was a simpIe pIan:
Swain wouId make me
out to be the hero,
I'd impress the girI,
and he'd make a IittIe money.
It's obvious how stupid I was.
Yeah, so, lover boy.
Think your nigga was gonna rob
a bank and not take any loot?
Find someone else to feed
your heroic addiction, fucking faggot!
And forgive us our sins
as we forgive
those who sin against us.
Lead us not into temptation;
deliver us from evil.
For thine is the kingdom
and the power and the glory forever.
Amen.
Turning away isn't an option.
It is now up to me
to make things right...
whatever the Cost.
He's been in and out of trouble
since he was a kid.
Dad got killed in Vietnam,
Mom was a junkie,
and then somehow
he gets his life together,
gets married, has a good job.
Listen to this.
He's driving along with his wife,
bus driver has a heart attack,
hits the car,
they end up in the pond.
She drowns while
he's trying to save her,
and on top of it, she was pregnant.
Jesus Christ,
this guy's had a shitty life.
lt doesn't change the fact
that we got two dead guys,
he looks like hell...
You see that mark around his neck?
Matches the wire
from Lynch's garage.
l know. We gotta bring him in.
l know.
Everything's gonna be
all right, okay? l promise.
You just got caught up
in the middle of some shit.
lt'll be over really soon, okay?
What you doing there, stud muffin?
Trying to make her
your little girlfriend?
l'm just talking to her.
There's 900 numbers
for that kind of shit.
You cryin'?
'Cause you become a liability,
and l'll kill you myself.
Don't worry about him.
lt's gonna be okay.
Okay, don't worry.
lt's all right.
Okay?
l'm gonna make sure
l get you out of here.
Don't worry, all right?
lt's gonna be okay. 'Kay?
When we're done with Liam,
what do we do with the little girl?
What do you think
we're gonna do with her?
Christ, we can't kill her.
Aye, so you have
a better suggestion?
Yeah, l can fucking think
of 50 of them.
Swain, you're the one who brought
us this shit in the first place.
No, l never told you to take the girl.
l never said that.
What are you lacking?
ls it brain cells or is it Cojones,
because the only people who seem
to have any is me and Gordy.
Shit.
Tighten up, boys, he's here!
Here we go!
Look who we have!
The frickin' hero.
Throw the gun to the floor,
please. Do you mind?
Tough guy, the hero.
Thank you.
You okay, Marley?
Marley's fine.
We're looking after her.
We were waiting for you to get here
so we could fuck her up.
You said you'd let her go.
Let her go.
Case, listen, she saw my face,
she saw my boys' faces.
What do you want me to do,
let her walk out of here?
l'm not gonna let you
kill a fucking kid, man.
Hey, Swain!
We've been
through this shit already.
We've discussed this.
lt's all been discussed.
What's wrong with you?
Fuck you, asshole.
- Gordy!
- Yo!
Do me a favor.
Can you put your gun
on this prick
and show him
the error of his ways?
Otherwise, l'm gonna
have to climb up there
and bitch-slap that little faggot.
Hey, Liam, fuck you.
Derek!
Who the fuck was that?
Liam, l told you
to come on your own!
Fuck!
Gordy! Cover Case!
Somebody find the bitch
who shot me in the shoulder.
Fuck. Do something,
you fucking pussy!
Motherfucker!
Fuck!
Hey, if you don't stop
fucking with me,
l'll kill this little bitch right now,
l swear to Christ!
No!
l'm gonna get you
out of here right now.
Where are you,
you son of a bitch?
Stop firing at me!
Then fucking kill somebody!
Get away from her!
Enough! Enough!
No!
No, Gill, no!
Cosmo!
Fuck.
lt's okay.
Come on, over here.
Drop your weapon!
Put your hands in the air now!
Put the weapon down!
Drop the damn weapon!
Now!
Come on!
Come and fucking get me!
They're inside!
lnside there.
Oh, man, these guys need help.
l'll call the paramedic.
- l'm going after them.
- All right.
Listen, l need you
to stay here, okay?
l need you to stay right here.
Damn, boy!
l thought you had me there!
l love America...
but l fucking hate cops!
What you gonna do with that,
throw it?
l'll deal with you in a minute.
Don't move, Liam.
Don't twitch a muscle.
How long have you known?
l've had my suspicions.
My intuition told me.
l'm not going with you.
You might've just saved my ass,
but if you think
you're going someplace,
you've got another think coming.
l have to see her.
l thought you were
one of the good guys, Liam.
So did l.
- Jesus.
- Marley.
l want you to go, Liam.
Hey, Marley, give me the gun.
Give me the gun, sweetheart.
Take it easy, easy, easy!
Easy! Easy.
Just give me the gun.
Not until Liam's gone.
Liam's not going anywhere,
okay, sweetheart?
Put the gun down.
He's not going anywhere.
Tell her.
- Marley.
- Tell her.
You saved my life, Liam.
You saved my life!
And this is your chance.
Do whatever it is you have to,
but this is it.
l'm giving it to you,
same as you did for me.
You're like a little sister
to me, Marley.
Always.
Come here.
No!
Give me the gun.
l'm sorry.
l didn't want you to hurt him.
l wanted him to be safe.
lt's okay. lt's okay.
Security, there's a man
with a gun in the lobby.
Liam, oh! Oh, my God!
No, no!
She's awake.
She's awake, Liam!
She's awake!
l'm sorry. l'm so sorry.
Liam.
lt's over.
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
God! Help!
Hey! Help me! Help!
Redemption. It's a funny thing.
Sometimes you have
to go through heII to get it.
Thank you.
For what?
For saving my life.
This is only the beginning.
Sometimes...
things worth dying for
are worth Iiving for.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org