Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Want a hot dog?
No, thanks.
Just ketchup, please.
Thanks.
Listen, I've got
an errand to run.
Kind of skimpy
on the ketchup.
Duncan, I've got to do this alone.
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
You called me in Paris,
and you said,
"We have to meet."
Now suddenly you've
got an errand to run?
What's going on?
I don't know.
It's...
nothing.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Really.
I know you better
than that, Connor.
Haven't seen you like this.
People change, Duncan.
You'll learn that.
Fine.
You can tell me
all about it tonight.
8:00 at the bar.
And you're buying.
Right.
8:00, and I'm buying.
Mm-hmm.
You sure you gonna be
all right, Connor?
Of course.
Duncan...
watch your back.
Connor?
Okay.
What is it, Connor?
Open it.
Oh, a ballerina.
Wow. She's beautiful.
Thank you.
Mmm, my angel.
Oh, my God,
I'm so proud of you.
I love you, Connor.
I love you, my Rachel.
Oh, God,
I'm proud of you.
Thank you.
Hello?
Rachel!
Rachel.
My beloved Rachel.
How long has it been
since she died?
A year?
A century? More?
My mind keeps slipping,
but some things I know.
I am Connor MacLeod
of the Clan MacLeod,
and once,
a very long time ago,
I was a Highlander.
Born of this land,
and like this land, immortal.
Witch!
You brought
this plague on us.
You damned us all,
Connor MacLeod.
You sold your soul!
You're a witch!
You child of Satan!
They drove you from your home,
cut you off
from your own people.
What else do they want?
Someone to blame.
Your mother will burn!
Connor.
Rot in hell!
Get in the house.
Get off my land!
Leave us in peace!
Connor, please.
You're not going back
to Glenfinnan.
I have no choice.
Connor, please.
They can't hurt me,
and they know it,
but they can still
hurt the ones I love.
I'm afraid.
I love you, Heather.
More than anything in this world.
Do you believe me?
Yes.
Then don't be afraid.
Nothing can keep me from you.
Nothing.
Connor.
I thought you might be
the water horse...
come to take me on his back
and drown me in the loch.
No one comes
to take care of you?
Not in years.
They think I bedevil
their children...
because my own was banished.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Tiny mites...
and soured dispositions.
I've no need of them, Connor,
any of them.
Then it's settled.
You're coming with me.
Aah!
Connor!
Connor, what is it?
I'm not sure.
It happened once before.
Aah!
Aah! Connor!
In the name
of the Holy See...
and the rule of law,
you are hereby charged,
Connor MacLeod,
with heresy...
and the practice
of black magic.
We were friends, remember, Jacob?
I stood at your ordination.
I vouched for you.
You shouldn't have
come back, Connor.
Take him.
Aah!
The ties of blood...
cannot be severed
by word or deed.
Mother.
Due to
the infinite compassion...
you are entitled
to one final opportunity...
to renounce all that is unholy,
and declare Connor MacLeod
not of your loins.
How say you,
Caiolin MacLeod?
If your God...
should persecute me
into the next world,
then I shall simply have
to find myself another.
Burn her!
No! No! No!
He is your son.
I am silent for you.
Black powder.
It will ease your suffering.
Mother!
No!
You're next, you demon!
Aah!
My water horse.
Unh!
The Devil's come back to life!
Let her be, Connor.
Aah!
Father?
Please.
Do not leave me.
Father.
Aah!
Connor--
My endless days...
are filled with memories
of the past...
and the death of my mother
by Jacob Kell.
Boy, you people are
extremely difficult to find.
We like it that way.
Go ahead, man.
Take your pick.
Unh!
Uhh!
Aah!
Aah.
Take their heads.
They might be Immortals.
Yes, they might be.
Aah!
Don't be long.
The Sanctuary.
So it's true.
What sacrifices
they have made of you,
warehoused like
rotting pieces of meat.
Tell me,
is this... the better way?
I'm sure you've had
time to reflect upon it.
What you need to understand...
is that I don't care
about the game.
I don't care about the rules.
I don't even care about
these pathetic souls...
you keep locked away
as a barrier to the prize.
Which one is
Connor MacLeod?
Well, what do we do now?
What we always do.
We're Watchers, not cops.
We'll find another volunteer.
Whatever you fear
about Connor MacLeod,
fear the worst.
Who is this?
A friend.
Don't bother looking for me, Duncan.
He's on the move.
Duncan MacLeod
of the Clan MacLeod.
Hello, Methos.
What brings you
to my humble abode?
Need your help.
Why me?
You've been around for 5,000 years.
I want the benefit
of your experience.
And I thought
it was a social call.
You ever had nightmares?
What kind of nightmares?
Bloody images...
powerful enough to even
break your meditation.
We live violent lives, MacLeod.
Some of that's
bound to stay with us.
These ones came
10 years to the day...
that Connor MacLeod disappeared.
Connor had good reason to go.
He told me how much
Rachel meant to him.
There was more to it than that.
I was with him that day.
The day Rachel was killed?
Something wasn't right.
Connor, you okay?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Really.
I know you better
than that, Connor.
I've never seen you like this.
People change, Duncan.
You'll learn that.
I need to know
if he's still alive, Methos.
You know a little
about Buddhist monks.
Some of them come
to cherish life so much...
that to step on an insect
or harm a blade of grass...
becomes a violation
of their creed,
so they place themselves
under an extreme form...
of protective custody--
A Sanctuary of sorts.
Well, for an Immortal...
who comes to abhor
the bloodshed,
there's a similar solution--
Away to be removed
from the game forever.
The price
is unimaginably high,
but you are, for
all practical purposes,
protected from
the violence within you.
And it's called The Sanctuary.
Connor would never do that.
Are you sure?
It's been around since
before you were born.
At least until last night.
What happened last night?
It was annihilated.
Hey, Duncan, what's the matter?
The British...
destroyed the clans, Connor.
Scotland's finished.
Scotland will always be Scotland,
and someday you'll go back.
You can bet on it.
How much?
Aw, come on.
Does everything have
to be a wager with you?
Well, you're the one
that keeps telling me...
our lives are nothing
but a boundless game.
Good morning, gentlemen.
What seems to be
the problem here?
They refuses to pay her toll, sir.
Really? How dare they.
These men are rogues.
These men are
liars and scoundrels, sir.
They've done nothing but
prey upon us 3 years running,
right at this very spot.
And by whose authority
do you act?
By Deed of the King.
There is a little "X" down here.
Does the King always
sign his name with an "X"?
Excuse me. Sorry. Ha ha.
I think these gentlemen
should be paid.
That deed is a fake.
That's a matter of opinion.
You, sir, are
no better than they.
That is also a matter of opinion.
Here you go.
Ladies.
It's gold!
Why not--
It's gold.
First man: Ha ha!
Hey, wait a minute.
They took my money!
Oh, it's here.
Let's go get 'em!
Shall we?
Aye.
Aah!
- Ooh.
Heh heh.
Not bad.
Uh-oh.
Mmm.
All right boys, time to go.
Let's go!
Come on!
Ohh. Cuckoo.
Oh, looks heavy, huh?
Looks like
you lost your edge, lad.
Really heavy.
Or could he be lass?
Could be.
Hyah!
Come on!
Hyah! Hyah!
Hyah!
Corporal Duncan MacLeod, sir.
I've come to pick up
the wounded.
You've improved greatly.
Ah, you really think so?
No.
I'm just being gracious.
Hmm.
Now, remember.
You are only immortal...
as long as you
can keep your head...
on your shoulders.
Gahh.
Duncan, what you give up
to your adversary...
in defeat...
is everything.
I know.
And at that point,
I'm very, very dead.
Come on!
Heh heh heh.
Not just dead, Duncan--
Empty!
Aye, Connor, I know.
It's called the Quickening.
Our strength and knowledge,
our life essence,
flows into the victor, feeds him,
and makes him stronger, yes?
It's what drives
the other Immortals...
to kill us,
and what forces us...
to be smarter,
better than the rest.
I understand.
Ooh.
You do?
Ohh.
Good.
I slipped.
Listen, soon you and I
will have to part.
There is one more thing
I want to give to you.
Va via. Va via!
Ho ho ho.
Oh, aye!
Oh, aye. This is
much more to my liking.
Good.
Bah! Heh heh heh.
Heh heh heh.
Attack me.
But you've got your back to me.
It's not always
about strength, Duncan.
Attack me!
Aah!
It's about manipulation
of the mind...
as well as the body.
Aye, but now I'm in control.
Heh heh heh. Are you?
Remember well, my friend.
Properly executed,
this move is unstoppable.
we'll nae have this talk again.
Who are you?
A friend... or a lover.
Or a wife.
Kate?
Attaboy.
Except I'm Faith now.
Part of the makeover.
What are you doing here?
Remember our wedding day,
Duncan?
I do.
The way we danced.
I felt like we were flying.
Of course,
we did come down...
didn't we?
Crashing.
Oh, shit.
It's time to show
our Immortal brother...
a thing or two.
Somebody order
a club sandwich?
He's funny.
Nice outfit, too.
Faith, I told you I look
like a fuckin' orange!
I'm not dressing you black, Bob.
Trust me.
Who are they?
Friends.
What, it's a team sport now?
What, you didn't know?
It's a whole new ball game.
Aah!
Hey!
Nice bat.
Aargh!
Told you I was gonna cut you.
Aaah!
Let my man Jin Ke
deal with him.
Jin Ke...
who served with
the Emperor Chin.
The same man.
Some people say
you're a man of honor.
What do you know about honor?
Oh, great.
Yaah!
Honor's not in a weapon.
It's in the man.
Enough!
Boys, boys.
I do apologize.
When it comes to discipline,
the first hundred years
are the hardest.
Ohh!
Guess I'm not much
of a swords guy.
I thought I told you to stop.
Yeah, well,
I stopped.
Tell me, Carlos.
How much is your life worth?
Don't start this bullshit, man.
'Cause the only way
to win your freedom...
is to kill me.
You're crazy.
Am I?
Then go ahead.
Stop the madness.
Can you live with the fear?
Can you live
with the weakness?
Weakness, Carlos.
I call this...
decap with a twist--
No sugar.
Watchers?
Huh?
Watchers observe Immortals.
They're not supposed
to interfere.
Unfortunately, our role
has changed somewhat.
Why?
Because the rules
have been broken.
One of your kind
has gone renegade.
In doing so, he's gained
himself a sizable advantage.
One that'll be
impossible to overcome.
Nobody's unbeatable.
Oh, yes, Duncan. He is.
Unbeatable.
No.
Ahh.
Sorry about that.
There must always be
two of your kind.
As long as there are two,
and you're kept from fighting,
then the prize is safe.
The Sanctuary must not fail again.
You're insane.
Get yourself another volunteer.
We had a number of volunteers!
Sadly, that's
no longer the case.
You'll be warehoused,
hidden away.
Go to hell.
Don't worry.
The drugs'll kick in momentarily.
Get up.
Get up!
You have better things to do
than lie there on your ass.
Who are you?
Someone who knows
more about you...
than you know about yourself.
Are you a demon?
Heh, heh heh.
I've been called that...
and worse.
I'm Connor MacLeod
of the Clan MacLeod.
Connor MacLeod?
And like you, my friend,
I have a hard time dying.
Dawson?
Heh, you look like shit.
Thanks.
How long have I--
We'll talk about it later.
We gotta get outta here.
Come on, can you walk?
Yeah.
Uhh.
Go. Go!
What are you doing here?
Keeping tabs on you.
Yeah?
Well...
someone should keep tabs...
on that psychotic asshole
back there.
Didn't you get it
back in London?
These guys don't play by the rules.
You don't know what
you're up against, Mac.
So people keep telling me.
Stop the car.
I managed to liberate that
from their lost and found.
There's blood on it.
I didn't say it was easy.
Pull over.
What?
MacLeod, tell me something.
Mac, hear him out!
Mac! Will you
tell me something?
Now, how many Quickenings
have you had?
How many heads
have you taken?
I don't keep score.
Well, we do.
MacLeod, Connor.
What's that?
The Watchers' version
of a resumé.
It's a bit like
handicapping horses, I know,
but it's part
of the gig, all right?
174 confirmed Immortal kills.
Sound about right?
So, what's your point?
Here's the gentleman
you met in Connor's loft.
661 confirmed Immortal kills.
Welcome to your worst nightmare.
Sanctuary wasn't shit, pal.
This guy is way
out of your league.
I want to see
Connor MacLeod's body.
Why?
Something
doesn't make sense.
What are you saying?
I think he's saying
he wants to see the body.
Well, it's gonna be a rough I.D.
They're all missing their heads!
We gave 'em
a Christian burial, MacLeod.
It was decent, you know.
Said all the right words.
Can't begin to tell you
how reassuring that is.
With all these
unexplained corpses,
well, we had to take it
off the beaten track.
End of the road, Joe.
Thanks.
You watch your ass, MacLeod.
It's not my ass
I'm worried about.
Did I happen to mention
about all this...
coming to a bad end?
No, Methos.
I don't believe you did.
You were gonna stay and dig.
Dig? Oh, yeah!
I need to know
if he's still alive, Professor.
I want to see
Connor MacLeod's body.
One of your kind
has gone renegade.
People change, Duncan.
You'll learn that.
No.
What are you doing here?
You walked out
on your life, Connor.
Why?
I had my reasons.
Reasons?
Every life I touch ends...
brutally...
and for no reason.
It's a curse...
that's followed me for centuries.
I can't outrun it,
and I can't outlive it.
Rachel's death made you
the last soul on this planet...
that means a damn to me.
I thought there was a way out.
The Sanctuary?
Yes.
The Sanctuary.
So, how did you escape?
I didn't escape.
I was let go.
I couldn't see the slaughter,
only heard it...
and felt it.
Jacob Kell.
So, here we are--
Both immortal.
Missed the signs,
didn't we?
But we were both
so new at the game.
Connor.
What a glorious sight.
Just look, Connor.
Look back at the endless
travesties of your life,
and you'll see me,
always there
waiting in the shadows.
When friends and lovers...
are wiped from your sight--
I'm there.
When those you cherish...
die abruptly and for no reason--
I'm there for you.
And when your cellmates...
in their so-called Sanctuary...
are left twitching
like headless chickens--
Guess who?
Connor.
Stay out of it, Duncan.
Would you kill
an unarmed man...
again, Connor?
Oh!
You didn't know, Duncan?
Because you didn't tell him.
Would that finally
put the agony...
in your soul to rest?
Then go ahead.
Send me home.
What's stopping you?
Honor?
Guilt?
The nagging sense that maybe you,
more than I, deserve to die?
Or somewhere along the way...
did you just lose your nerve?
It's holy ground, Connor.
Ooh.
Yes.
Take your shot.
What better chance than now?
Do it.
Do it for your sweet mother.
Aah!
Or the sweet little war orphan...
Rachel Ellenstein...
who, if I'm not mistaken,
you raised
as your own daughter.
Tell me, do they even begin...
to equal for the murder
of a man of God...
who raised me as his own son?
Aah!
Slow...
close--
Feels good, doesn't it?
But look at you.
Even now, you're afraid--
Afraid you'll lose.
That's your true fear, isn't it?
The thought of giving up
your essence to me,
making me
even stronger by it.
What's wrong?
Don't you want
to be inside me?
I want you to think back
to this moment, Connor!
In the endless nights ahead!
Aah!
And know...
every time
you close your eyes...
from now to eternity,
I'll be there!
Ripping apart the ones
you care about most!
Aah!
It's never over,
Connor MacLeod.
Living is what matters.
And you will live with this.
Count on it.
One far-off day,
you and I will be
the only two remaining.
You will look back on this...
and know you had
one chance to stop me.
You failed.
But until that day,
I will take my vengeance...
on those you love.
Your living...
has been my prize.
For old times' sake.
He is your son.
You, on the other hand...
are on borrowed time.
Call you.
Is what he said true?
Is it?
Believe only what your heart...
and conscience tell you.
Connor...
with time, anything
can be forgiven.
You taught me that.
Did I?
Oh, look at Dave. Dave!
Behave yourself, Duncan!
No more talking!
May all your hardships fade away.
Till night becomes morn,
let love remain
to guide your way.
Till the day we are reborn.
Kiss her, won't you?
Connor?
I thought you'd never get here.
Connor!
You know
Kate is like us, immortal.
Aye. I sensed something
the day we met,
but I wasn't sure.
Well, now you know.
And you know as well as I do...
that her Immortality
can only be triggered...
by the shock of a violent death.
Yes, I do.
And without such a death,
she will simply
grow old and die.
Yes, I know, Connor.
Is that what you came
to tell me on my wedding day?
Come on.
Drink up, man.
No.
I was wondering.
Does she know?
Why?
Many years
after I was married,
one night...
I found Heather
in front of the house.
She had a knife in one hand...
and her hair in the other.
When I asked her...
why she had done such
a thing to herself,
she said it was
the one part of her...
that would never age.
It would forever
remain the same...
as when I first
fell in love with her.
That's how she wanted me
to remember her.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I once loved a woman...
more than life itself--
and I watched her die.
Unlike me, you have a choice.
What would you have me tell her?
I'd tell her nothing.
She wouldn't believe you anyway.
Then I can do nothing.
She's in the flower of her youth.
Enjoy the moment,
and let it pass.
And if it were you in my place?
I was in your place!
But I thank God
I never had the choice.
I love Kate,
and I will hold on to her
as long as I can.
And that is all I can do!
Forever, my love.
Until the day we are reborn.
You haven't lost your touch.
What do you want?
To talk.
Oh, that's a first.
I've tried to talk to you
a thousand times--
Get to the point.
I was wrong.
Oh, no, no.
Stealing's wrong.
Lying's wrong.
Killing's wrong.
What you did
goes well beyond wrong.
Fine.
I deserve that,
but I want a chance
to make it right.
You want to make it right?
Then give me back the ability...
to have children,
to grow old
with the man I love.
How about anything that
resembles a normal life?
And you took it all
away from me.
Those things I can't give you.
Oh, something else
you forgot to tell me.
Good-bye, Duncan.
Kell can't give you
those things, either,
so tell me, Kate, why him?
Because I've never
known anybody...
with such a capacity for hate--
Except me.
That's what's kept you
going all these years?
Hmm?
Fine.
Go home, Faith.
Take care of what's important.
You were with him.
A woman is a temple...
built on a sewer.
Remember what you were
when I first found you.
A whore.
Now, look at you.
A liberated whore.
Fuck you.
Oh, we'll get to that, blossom.
But in the interim, be grateful...
I don't take
your pretty little face off.
Hurts, doesn't it...
that there is something
you actually can't have?
Hmm. I can have...
anything I want.
Except me.
I've already had you.
Not really.
Close enough.
Forever.
May love remain
to guide our way...
till the day we are reborn.
Forgive me.
Uhh!
I'm sorry.
You had no right.
Uhh!
Kate?
No. Don't be frightened.
You're immortal.
We both are.
Aah!
Uhh!
I did it for you--
For us.
- Uhh!
- Kate.
Kate?
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
What have I done?
Kate!
You wanted this.
You forced it on me.
I never asked for eternity.
I never wanted us to be apart.
Would you have really understood?
Which part?
The endless, numbing
sameness of it all?
Or never bothering
to love someone...
because whole lifetimes
tick by so fast...
they don't even count anymore?
Then why did you come?
To see if I could feel again--
Anything.
You're missing the point, Kate.
The difference
between Connor and I...
is that as long
as you're still alive,
there's a chance that one day...
I might be forgiven.
It may take years--
Centuries, even.
But at least I can
carry that hope inside me.
That's one blessing
of immortality--
There's always tomorrow.
Even for us.
What are you doing, Jin?
Just thinking.
Men, for the most part,
can mend their ways...
only after they have made
a mistake.
One day soon,
we will all...
serve very little purpose to Kell,
except dead.
A toast.
I see tonight...
as a celebration of the spirit.
To all of you...
who continue to stand by me--
even those who might waver...
at times--
You are my flock.
You...
nourish my soul.
You are all a part...
of a great journey--
a 400-year quest--
for justice.
And here, my friends,
is the instrument
of that justice--
The giver...
and taker of creation...
baptized in blood.
It is the living...
that matters...
after all.
It sings like an angel.
Just listen.
Uhh!
Till the day we are reborn.
Ohh!
Aah!
Uhh!
Kell.
Jacob Kell.
Connor?
We've lived many lives,
you and I.
We've seen things...
that most people
could never understand.
But now what do you see?
I see someone who would
never kill an unarmed man.
I also see someone
who has lost hope.
Life brings hope and pain...
but revenge
never brings redemption.
The path and choice are ours.
Connor, what the hell's going on?
I have chosen mine.
Aah!
What are you doing?
Kell's too strong,
and he's getting stronger.
Neither one of us can beat him alone.
Are you out of your mind?
Aah! If we let him win,
it could mean the end.
Connor, no!
Kell is going
to kill you, Duncan,
just to torment me,
and there is nothing
you can do about it--
Nothing!
I don't believe that, Connor.
Neither should you.
Alone, neither one of us
can beat him.
Together, we can.
You know the rules.
Only one Immortal
can challenge another.
And only one will.
This isn't the answer.
Listen to me.
In the end,
there can be only one,
and that has to be you.
No.
We can beat him together.
Then we are in agreement.
Enough, Connor!
I won't fight you.
I will never fight you, Connor.
Then you die!
Uhh.
No! You're not
doing this, Connor.
Oh, yes, we're doing this.
Every day,
every breath we took
was for this end.
Look inside
and tell me I'm wrong.
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Do it!
I can't.
Remember how
you first found me?
Sitting in that bloody bog,
scared out of my mind?
You taught me
how to live, Connor.
You taught me why we live.
Have you forgotten all of that?
No.
Our bonds...
are all that hold us
in this world.
Don't break this one.
Please, Connor.
I'm begging you.
It's too late.
This has to be done.
Haah!
No, Connor!
Not like this!
Come on, stop!
Connor, stop!
Duncan!
One of us has to die now,
old friend.
No.
And you know it.
Good-bye, Duncan,
my true brother.
I love you, Connor.
Aah!
No!
Duncan.
Well done.
I ever thought
you had him in you.
What does it feel like
to kill a brother?
Feels good,
doesn't it?
You'll never know, will you?
Now you'll never have
Connor MacLeod's head.
Are you going to run?
Are you going to hide?
Run?
Uhh!
Aah!
Brother, come on!
- Aah!
How bad do you
want it, Duncan?
You'll pay!
Ahh!
Ohh!
Duncan!
Okay, Kell. Come on.
Let's do this.
Just watch.
Merry Christmas.
A valiant effort, Duncan.
Too bad.
And this is
just the beginning.
You see, when
you absorbed Connor's spirit,
you inherited his curse.
Revenge...
is so sweet.
I wonder who we'll start with?
Oh, Kate.
Forever.
Oh, God.
Kell!
Jacob Kell!
Revenge...
will never bring you redemption,
so I'm going to do it for you.
Aah!
Is that all you've got?
Dunc,
I'd thought
I'd be home for dinner...
an hour ago, but
this is very impressive.
Come on.
Come on.What are you
waiting for?
I'd be delighted.
Yaah!
Impressive...
isn't it?
Uhh!
Duncan!
You see at last your fate!
Yes!
Because this game is done!
Uhh!
Well, look on the bright side.
At least
you went down swinging.
Jacob Kell.
Time for redemption.
The game isn't over yet.
What's the matter?
Don't you want to be inside me?
In the end--
...there can be only one.
And you're not it.
Uhh!
Call ya.
No!
Aah!
Hope you found peace,
my friend.
So, why are you here?
You hoping you'd find me?
For whatever reason,
Kell made his choice.
So, um,
what now?
Trust.
You can always trust me, Faith.
Faith is dead.
I thought we'd give
Kate another chance.
Not yet.
Till the day we are reborn.
You hold onto it for me.
We've got plenty of time.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org