We said we'd do something
I wanted to do.
- We did. Camel riding.
- I hated camel riding.
I really want to do
some real stuff.
What do you mean real stuff?
It's for losers! Ruth?
OK... We'll miss the
Rajasthani buffet!
Ruth!
Ruth, wait!
Is she out of money?
No, it's quite simple.
I have to tell you the truth.
For the sake of Ruth's
and our old friendship.
Oh, what's that taken on?
That's very exotic. Hmm?
- On my Olympus.
- That's interesting.
Mine's a Minolta.
Is yours an auto flash job?
What am I looking at here, Prue?
Who are these people
in the photo?
Ruth.
That's Ruth.
My God, I didn't realise.
Gilbert, it's Ruth!
Yeah, I can see that now. She's
wearing the national costume.
I'd never have recognised her.
I know.
Is something wrong?
Tell me, I want to know.
We were just like everyone else
travelling in India.
We wanted to visit a live guru.
We weren't serious about it.
She thought it would
be a good laugh.
Oh, it was so scary. Some sort
of freaky hypnotism happened.
I think they were on drugs.
She even burnt her airline
ticket in front of me.
That's when I asked her,
"Is it true what they said?"
"That Baba might marry you?"
No, thank you, mate. No,
thank you. No, mate. Thank you.
No, no. Say no, Ruth! Say no!
Say no, Ruth. Stop him!
Ruthy, stop him!
No, no, Ruthy! Stop!
Please, no! Say no!
Ruthy! Ruthy!
Somebody help!
This is serious.
Tim, please. It's serious.
Come on.
We were waiting for you.
OK, seriously, what's happening?
- Who's he?
- He's the top man on the subject.
He's been very very helpful.
Hi, Tim. Isn't it terrible?
But don't worry, Miriam's gonna
get her back. She's going to India.
- Are you?
- I will if I need to.
I'm determined to fight.
G'day, Tim.
Stop Robbie drinking too much.
That's right, Mom, we'll fight.
Don't. Don't come here and mock.
I'm close to the edge, Tim.
Sophie, sterilised at 23
to focus on her spiritual growth...
...wanted a reversal at 34.
It can't be done.
- So how do we get her back?
- Lure... You lure her.
Couldn't we contact the
embassy to send her home?
No, you can't.
If she were under 18, yes, under
the International Convention.
But you got nothing on your sister other
than declare her mentally incompetent.
And that's almost impossible to do.
What we often do is steal. These cults
use coercive and deceptive methods.
Steal 'em.
Turn the deception around.
They make up their little
stories, we make up ours.
But we get her back.
The next step
is the difficult one.
You'll have captured
your daughter's body...
...but not her mind.
So what do we do, Stan?
We hire the man I believe to be...
...the number one exit
counsellor in America.
For legal reasons, it's best
if he's in and out. Untraceable.
- Could it be dangerous?
- Yeah, it's delicate.
The mind's a damn mystery.
Why do people believe in God?
Why do people believe
they're in love?
Why do I tell myself every day,
"You're fat, mate. "
"Today I won't eat
cake, butter or bread"...
...and by lunch time,
I've done the lot?
So what did Mr Hot Dog
American cost?
$10,000 Australian,
plus expenses.
Shit! And what's wrong with
Number Two? How much did he cost?
Forget it, Gilly. We're doing
it. She's our golden girl.
My plane's leaving in
three hours, everybody!
Delhi's hot.
95 to 105 degrees.
- Oh, God!
- What if she doesn't come back?
When she knows you're
dying, she'll come.
Sure!
What's bitten his old bum?
He doesn't like
pretending to die.
Do you speak English?
Do you know where that is? That
restaurant? Shiva's Restaurant?
It's a... fair way,
I suppose, is it?
Ah... goodness,
this is busy, isn't it?
Hello. Give me your money, please?
Give me a rupee, please?
I'm sorry, I'm from Australia.
I haven't got any...
...any Indian money.
Are you sure this is it?
Mum!
Oh, where's your sari?
- You've got this on.
- I was looking for a sari.
Oh, you're so hot!
Who's that?
The restaurant's fake holy man.
This is my friend Rahi.
- Who?
- Rahi.
It's my Sanyasin name.
Hello, Miriam.
Hello.
You need a cold drink.
Have you ever tried a lassi?
- A who?
- A lassi. It's a yoghurt drink.
Is it from a bottle?
Mum, it's clean here.
Yes, only a few dozen flies.
Is there a toilet
or a hole here?
It's a hole.
"All your father and I want... "
Oh, no...
Calmie, calm... Calmie, calm.
Ventolin.
Oogh!
Mum, I've got no idea
what Prue told you.
She got really scared.
Something amazing
happened to me.
So powerful and so gentle.
It's... hard for me to describe.
You've got to
experience Baba, Mum.
When he looks at you,
just looks at you...
...all your pretensions
and fears just vanish!
Suddenly, it's so obvious
how to live your life.
That it's really possible
to be happy...
...and truthful and do good.
How would you feel if I
were to become enlightened?
Come to a meeting tonight.
It's a beautiful opportunity.
Baba's going to be
taking questions.
Just come and see!
He is so full of love.
Your father and I are pleased
you've found fulfilment.
Are you?
How is Dad?
Like I wrote to you,
he is very ill.
He had a stroke at Bill and
Puss's farm and won't be moved.
Is he going to die?
Yes, he could.
He wants to see you.
He's paid for your ticket home.
See? I cry!
I couldn't cry before.
I didn't know you didn't cry!
Will Daddy...?
Maybe next time.
- What do you mean next time?
- You know, next time.
In another life.
- Oh, never mind.
- He's dying, Ruth!
- Is he scared?
- Of course he is.
He wants to see you!
We've got a ticket for you.
It's really the timing.
Isn't it, Nazni?
Who is Nazni?
It's Ruth.
That's her apprentice name.
Ruth, can you speak for you?
Would you mind calling me Nazni?
It's my name now.
Look, they only initiate
new Sanyisans once a year...
Fine, fine! You're doing
just as you should.
You're pleasing yourself which
is exactly what we taught you.
Just please yourself. Don't let
our deaths inconvenience you.
You've got great hair.
Oh, goodness.
That's really kind of you.
No, it's fantastic.
- She's a bit nervous.
- Of course.
- How's the hair? Any scent?
- Ah, it's good.
Great.
The kitchen will be
open for supper...
...after the evening
programme...
No.
- Please.
- I'm sorry, no.
I can't be sniffed.
I feel sick, I want to go back.
- Don't be...
- I can't. I feel like an animal.
- Yes you can. You'll be fine, just...
- No, NO! Don't touch me!
- Mum...
- No!
- Mum. Don't be silly. Mum!
- Excuse me.
Mum, stop it.
You're embarrassing me!
- No!
- MUM!
No! No!
I can't breathe!
My spray! My spray!
No! No drink! No drink!
Oh, thank God it's QANTAS.
We're here, it's fine.
- Hello!
- Oh, my God!
Why is Miriam so freaked out?
Oh, she thinks
I'm gonna live in India...
...marry Buba and
commit group suicide.
She and Dad hate Indians.
You know? Dark people.
They're just the main points.
Well...?
Are you going to marry him?
- I wish.
- You wish?!
Well, yeah.
He's an absolute love.
There's, um...
just three problems.
He's not cute, Ruth.
Look at him. He's like, old!
It's about love. It's not that
literal. Marriage is symbolic.
He's marrying everyone.
Sydney, Australia.
Case 190.
Fabio's an extra body
if needs be, and Robbie, too.
- Hi, there.
- Yep, whatever's necessary.
Mr Waters, my name's Yvonne,
with a 'Y'. I'm Robert's wife.
It's such a relief
you've arrived...
...because we've all
been so worried.
I'm here to be of assistance
to you. I'm on supplies.
Do you find it hard to get
polite help in America?
- Polite?
- People with lovely manners.
Don't look at Robbie.
He hasn't got any.
Where's the guy with
the exiting experience?
Ah... Colin, where's he?
He's had a family misfortune.
His mother died.
Oh, God, Stan! Was it expected?
Excuse me. This is not looking
good, Stan. I needed Colin.
I can't begin this work without a
properly experienced assistant.
- Those are the rules.
- That's where Robbie comes in.
Stan, come here a moment.
I'm a little aggravated.
I could've got my Carol to come...
...and she is good.
Now instead, you've
given me two fruitcakes -
One's a ponytail and
the other is a clown!
Now, exiting is a...
precision exercise.
I'm taking a leap with
this girl into the sky.
We put everything at risk.
And when we get to the bottom,
I need her parachute to open.
I need mine to open.
Now, which of these men would
you trust to pack your chute?
Ah... Fabio?
I think he'd do a neat job.
He'd do a neat job
with his toilet bag.
If he hasn't packed one before,
would you trust him?
Hey! Don't splash!
No, no, no, no!
- Yvonne! Yvonne!
- What?
OK, cop you later.
That was Tim, my older brother.
He's a gay man. They've arrived.
She's visited Dad once,
but she's restless.
So, where do we go from here?
I'll take a look at her when I
arrive, then we'll start talking.
Mm-hmm.
She's not that easy to
chat to. Is she, Robbie?
This isn't a chat. This is a
conversation that takes 3 days.
It's a very intuitive thing,
very concentrated.
So, what is it that you do?
I work a basic
three-step system...
...where I steer the subject
toward a breakthrough.
Breakdown, whatever
you prefer to call it.
Step one - isolate her,
get her attention and respect.
When she's listening, I start
to push her. The heat goes on.
- The heat?
- It's very traumatic for her...
...which it's supposed to be.
- You want some? It's hot.
- No, thank you.
Step two -
I remove all her props...
...her books, her sari,
if she wears one.
- Is she wearing one?
- Yeah.
Actually, she looks quite feminine
for a change. Doesn't she, Robbie?
What?!
Finally, the clouds of
her unreason burst -
there's tears, sobs,
hugs with the family and...
...it's over for me.
But, just beginning for you.
I've successfully exited
189 subjects...
...with a recidivist rate of 3.5%.
There's no one in the US or UK
who can match those statistics.
I've rejected three cases when
I've judged the subject too...
...psychologically unstable.
Do you have a wife or
lady friend, Mr Waters?
Why do you ask?
I bet she wouldn't
stand a chance.
What do you mean?
You're very persuasive.
I imagine you could persuade
any woman to do anything.
- Hi, Mummy.
- Hi, baby.
- Hi, Aunt Puss.
- Good morning, early bird.
Where are the boys?
Back at the motel,
cuddled up asleep.
I thought I'd just... drive out
and say bye to Dad.
Oh, he's sleeping, Ruth,
I think he should be left.
Don't worry.
I'll sneak in. I won't wake him.
Wait, Ruth. We'll come, too.
Ok, race you.
Come on!
Oh, God.
Om...
Om mani padme om...
Dad, you're up!
My God, that's great!
That's great!
What's the matter?
What's going on?
You're not sick at all, are you?
We're all sick from
worrying about you, Ruth.
What?!
There's someone visiting
we want you to talk to.
You're bullshitting me.
We want to be sure
you're on the right track.
Look, you'll bloody well stay
here... Get this sheet...!
How dare you?!
- Hey! Hey!
- Liar! You lied to me.
I fucking came home! Made me
think you were dying. You liar!
- We did it cos we all love you.
- Yeah, we all love you. I love you.
You know we love you.
Yeah, Ruth.
We all love you.
We love you, sis.
- Where's Mum?
- Give it time.
- Come on. I'll take you to meet him.
- It's for your own good.
No, thanks. Where's Mum?
You want your mummy now,
do you? Not so tough, eh?
You've met your match in him,
girlie. He's kinda strike you out.
He's a great guy, sis. He's really
experienced in religion and stuff.
Just three days, just listen to him.
Get round her, get round her.
You fucking lying shit!
You lying shit! I hate you!
- Let go. Let go.
- Behave yourself.
Tim. Timmy.
Timmy, let me talk to you
and Mum, please.
Tim, please, Tim.
Please! Please, Timmy, please!
Please! Please! Timmy!
Come on, walk over.
Oh, God!
He's not there?
No other back-ups,
nobody else?
Phone's out of range.
It doesn't work.
Look at this.
It's a gift, see?
She's coming towards me.
We're on step one.
This could be over in 12 hours.
- What about your lady friend, Carol?
- I need someone now.
But there isn't anyone.
I've tried the Rabbi, I've left
several messages, no response.
- What do we do? Just let her go?
- Yeah, we let her go.
Three little steps, Stan.
But you don't want to fall.
Well...
you're the expert.
I wanna talk to my mother.
Sure.
You're in.
So, are you gonna do it?
Ah... there.
Why?
Why? Why?
Because I think you've
been manipulated...
...maybe even drugged.
No... No, Mum.
Mum, I'm the only one of my
friends who doesn't do drugs.
Tell her!
I'm sorry, Ruth,
that's what I believe.
I believe you're
manipulating me right now.
Mum, Mum, Mum...
why are you here?
To save you.
No. I mean on Earth. Why are you
here? What's the point of your life?
- This is a trick.
- No, no Mum.
It's a real question. Why are you here?
Did you ever think about that?
Yes, I think about
a lot of things.
I think about the...
magnetic draw of the planets...
...their ever-shifting
relationship...
...the healing power of crystals...
Look. Mum and Dad have spent
a small fortune on this guy...
...who by the way has a very good reputation.
- According to who?
No. According to who?
So why don't you just
do the three days?
According to who?
Excuse me, according to who?
Ok, to a friend of mine,
a doctor, a psychiatrist, ok?
May I?
Come on.
Come on, big jump. Coming! Ooh!
Oh! That was a good one.
My turn.
What do you believe in?
Safe sex.
- Sex?
- Hey, I'm an anarchist.
My parents subscribe
to their magazine.
The Lord's Prayer is muttered
by traumatised, paranoid worms...
...grovelling for a
meagre existence.
- Traumatised worms?
- Traumatised paranoid worms.
So what's happening?
Have they finished?
No. The good news is
she's shaken hands on it.
She's going to do the three days.
He finally promised her a ticket
back to India. Excuse me, Robbie!
He wants to leave
as soon as possible.
Where are they going?
I think he should have told me about it.
I'm supposed to be security.
A halfway hut. Says he can't
work anywhere near the family.
Look, we're very lucky to
have him in the circumstances.
His personal assistant's coming
from America. And she's experienced.
I'm not gonna think costs.
We HAVE to do it.
But what about
the security operation?
What about Fabio?
Do we send him home?
- Well done, dear.
- Fuck off all of you.
You, madam, watch yourself
with your mother.
Hey, come on, Ruth.
You can talk, you hypocrite.
Where's your little love bomb?
- I don't know what you mean.
- Don't engage with her.
Yes, you do. Where's my
half-sister then, Dad?
You know, your secretary's
secret little love bomb?
What love bomb?
If this cure works, I'll be
as fucked a liar as you!
Keep up with her. Go!
- To the rescue!
- It's my go.
Batman!
Shoes, please, Ruth.
Day one -
Isolate her. Get her attention.
Win her respect.
I feel for these kids,
every one of them.
They're lost and they
don't know it yet.
This is, um...
a complete waste of time.
You're never gonna break me.
That's fine.
I didn't expect it to be easy.
You're a young, intelligent lady
with strong convictions.
It would be disappointing
if it were too quick.
There's no way I can even listen to
someone like you, who dyes their hair.
- I've made up my mind.
- You grew up your mind?
Yes, that's right.
And how may I ask,
did that happen?
- What?
- How did you do it?
Did you make your mind
hard and solid like a brick...
...always the same, rain or shine,
nothing gets through?
If I say to you "don't think
of pink butterflies"...
...you don't, right? Or do you?
I'm not thinking
of pink butterflies.
You just mentioned them.
You see, the mind is
a rebel, not a servant.
I'm not the one who will
break you. Your own mind will.
"It will seek the truth and
the truth will set you free. "
John Vlll, 32.
It's already heard the truth.
The truth about your saintdom?
Baba and Mrs Baba.
Not everything's a posture.
Not everything's a joke.
You're right. It's not a joke.
We're talking about your soul here.
Have you thought about the damage
that could be done to your soul...
...to your very centre...
...if you hand it over
to someone else?
To the wrong someone else?
"I feel within me that spark...
..."that atom emanation of the
divine spirit. " Giuseppe Verdi.
The soul is the match.
The spark.
The flame that
can light your path.
I wanna ask you a question.
What in your opinion is the most
important task of a human life?
Any idea?
Is this multiple choice,
or a fake question?
It's an oratory technique.
Have you heard of Socrates?
Yeah.
"The soul takes nothing
with her to the other world...
..."but her education and culture. "
So, let's get to the facts.
What are you doing
with your soul?
What does Chidaatma Baba
teach you?
What's the point
of my telling you?
You already have an opinion.
I wanna know what you know.
Something has
touched you, hasn't it?
To find out that, you'd have
to look into my heart.
Way beyond something
you can read in a book and quote.
It is. It is. It is.
That's his teaching.
And that's what he said?
His words? It is.
His words.
"He alone attains unto it
who exclaims 'It is! It is!'
"Thus may it be perceived and
apprehended in its essence. "
The Upanishad.
The Upanishad, Ruth.
An ancient Hindu text.
Feel with your heart,
but check your facts.
I want my shoes back.
No. You agreed to stay...
...and I'm going to
make it easy for you.
You can't stand the fact
that I've got faith, can you?
Cos you're so frightened
and dried up.
But feeling... just trusting
your heart... is beyond you.
I get strength like... like you
can't imagine from my choice.
That's what we're
really here to examine.
The meaning of the word "choice",
and whether you had one or not.
Hello?
Listen, I need clothes for Ruth.
- Oh, yes.
- Can you meet me at the yards?
Ok, but... two changes?
Do you think dresses or pants?
- You decide.
- Dresses?
- Have you got the clothes?
- Yeah, clothes and the coffee.
So, has she started
talking yet?
A little.
She's so lucky
to have you to talk to.
I've got problems,
too, you know?
Robbie thinks
I've been having an affair.
- Yeah, he found my letters...
- So, you are?
Robbie's so mad.
He just wants
to beat the guy up.
He has no idea who it is,
and he'll never ever guess.
Shall I tell you?
Ok...
Me.
I wrote them...
and they're so beautiful.
And they're so romantic.
You wrote the letters?
I don't have sex with Robbie.
I have sex with film stars.
I cut out their picture and I
stick them on my bedside drawer.
And when we make love...
...I pretend it's Brad Pitt
or Tom Cruise.
- I like Sly, too. Do you?
- Mmm.
In the dark...
.. I imagine that Robbie's
arms and legs are theirs.
Oh, that's lovely, Robbie.
Oh, yeah! Yeah!
Oh, Tom, Tom!
Oh, God, Matt! Matt!
Sometimes I get
a little confused...
...because I can't
remember who it is...
.. who is making love to me.
But... but I think
that Yvonne is cheap!
Take it easy.
Breathe... into the diaphragm.
- Yeah.
- Keep breathing.
I mean, who's
gonna want me...
...when they know how
many guys I've slept with?
- Keep breathing.
- Yes, thank you, the breathing.
Down here.
The breathing.
Do you have a web site?
Keep breathing.
Oh!
Day Two -
A painful day for the client.
Remove her props,
upset her and provoke her.
So I put the sari up the tree.
No more Mr Nice Guy.
I want my clothes back.
Juice?
I thought I was gonna have
to wait for the longest time...
...for the real you
to break through.
You think a sari
is going to change that?
Ten hundred saris
won't hide that.
And you'll only succeed in tying
a big knot around yourself.
Hello? Would you share
what you're thinking, please?
Hello?
Meditating.
I was just meditating on the
difference between you and Baba.
He wears a dress.
He lives the way he teaches.
And what specifically
has he taught you?
To do good. To be
a good person!
And how is that
manifesting itself?
Are you out there doing
good deeds, paying taxes?
- You're a cynic.
- Yes.
Yes, I am a cynic.
Because I investigate crap.
What about the
crap in you, Ruth?
Did you take that to the guru?
You're a shit.
You don't care about me!
You don't even know me.
And I didn't go to Baba to get
my fucked-upness fixed.
- You'd be the first.
- Allright!
So I hoped it would
help me grow!
- I know I'm not perfect.
- Good, Ruth.
Yeah.
So what do you
believe in, then?
Why do you want to know?
Because I'm just curious to
know what you worked out.
So you can follow me? Sorry,
honey, that's not my ticket.
I told you. Don't you ever touch me!
My body is mine... honey.
You're a prick!
You know, you'd be
better off crying.
FUCK YOU!
I don't want to
disempower you.
Oh, yeah?
If you want disempowerment,
go right back to Mother India!
See how they treat women there!
Or didn't you notice those
little ultrasounds blipping away...
...so people say,
"Oh, my God, it's a girl"...
...and flush her out and abort her.
- They're more honest.
- Excuse me?
They're more honest
in their hatred of women!
I don't hate women.
I love ladies.
"Ladies".
You wouldn't know any.
I bet you date little
Barbie dolls, don't you?
"Oh, you're so brainy,
you're so big!"
"Can I suck your dick?"
Can I be alone now?
So, was it the ultimate revenge?
What was?
Taking your beauty
off to an ashram?
Beauty has its own price.
You wouldn't know.
It attracts the shit.
Can do.
I've dated some beautiful
ladies. My ex-wife was a model.
Wow!
A bit paranoid - always
going on about fat people.
She looked good, though.
Oh, right.
- Excuse me?
- "She looked good, though. "
Yes, well, it didn't
work that well.
There was a kind of a...
hostility between us.
She was always mixing about -
very flirty with the friends -
...suggesting open marriage,
which we... did.
We both slept around.
Um... I slept around.
Then we went to India.
There were six of us.
Next thing, she's off
with my best friend.
I punched him out...
left the bus and wanted to die.
That's when I met Singh,
the so-called God.
I shook all over. I totally...
relinquished myself then.
If I saw any crap, wich I did on
occasion, I put it down to a test.
You know, Singh was testing me.
Then one starred day...
...he took me to his private
rooms and hugged me.
I thought, "I'm special,
he's chosen me".