Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
He said good morning and
asked how is your hand?
It's, uh...
... it's better
What's left of it?
sorry...
We wanted to speak with you
if you feel well
yeah, yes, it's alright
Coffee?
No, thank you
Tell us of that place you mentioned
in Slovakia
It is...
... some kind of factory
There are very very rich people
They pay to torture and
to kill kids
It seems one it manufactures
They killed my friends
They take you from this hostel
They take you to this factory and...
I went there...
... looking for Josh who's one of my friend,
they, they took  him there.
... and...
They killed him
It is horrible
he asked how you survived?
I...
... escaped
Who organizes this place?
I dont know, it is some type of...
... hunting club, they...
... they all have the same tattoo,
it is a dog...
... it's a bloodhound dog.
It is strange that you mention
this tattoo
Why?
Because someone was found dead
in a stationbath in Vienna.
With this same tattoo of
dog bloodhound that you describe
The security tape
of the station...
... shows him entering from
the platform...
... of the train arrived earlier
that day from Slovakia.
It came through the same station in Vienna
you were on that tape
Did his tattoo looks something like this?
What's going on?
Help! Somebody help me!
Jesus!
Are you hungry?
It's 3:15 in the morning
I'm supposed to take these
food , I just wanted to know if you wanted anything
Yea, I want you to talk
with someone
When you gonna tell Josh's
mother what happened?
I won't make it
She still thinks that her son
is in Europe
What the fuck I supposed
to tell her?
She'd go straight to the police
-Yea, Exactly, someone should
-No, noone should
You dont get it , these people
ared tided with everyone
Somebody will start asking questions
and they will come after me...
... and they will find me
...at my grandmother's house.
I've been coming here since
I was a kid
I can barely find
the place
-Ask to my sister as arriving
-You told your sister that we are here?
-If, and?
-Who but he/she knows it?
Nobody
I make this for your protection
do you know it, certain?
Oh Paxton
He/she looks
I brought you of return because
it felt bad
But you these returning crazy
You wake up screaming all
the nights and I cannot sleep
That will no longer be problem
Paxton, is not it that...
Good morning
Paxton
I will warn you
I sit down it
Single intent to be
in the moment
Absorverlo
You believe that you came out
of classes?
If he/she made it, it should be
in another part
Oh God, if he/she listened to it to speak...
of that moment
once but
I swear for heaven's sake that me
I give a shot
Until Tuesday
Not there is treatment
You can make it and
one doesn't eat the you make
I can become trained if your you want
The hands in their pencils
boys
It excuses
Can I see?
-It should break it
-Not be shy
In a word, it is beautiful
-Thank you
-To as much as you offer it?
I don't blindfold it, you can
to stay it
-Deveras?
-If
Oh my God, mchas thank you
-Of anything
-Do I invite you a swig or something?
In fact, we will train
but...
-... not you, in another mamoento
-This well
-If
-Ok
-Then I see you
-This well
Good-bye
Non potato, we will be well...
No, potato, you already know
that the fourth season comes
-You look at it, you look at it, porfavor...
-Because...
... no student stays
the fourth semester
It is for the whole people
so...
Thank you, ero porfavor not
If, if we have
Ok, I love you, good-bye
God, I should call him/her ago
some minutes
-Vamonos
-No, we have to wait somebody
Who?
-You already know
-No
He/she requested it to me in my department
this sick person...
... I felt bad that is supposed
that debei to tell him/her?
That he/she leaves to Baltimore
For that here'
Not it is so bad
Do you have a newspaper?
If, it is a newspaper of trips
For memories
Porsupuesto
I go for a swig
do they want to go?
I am well, thank you
Ok, we will see each other to sleep
That you are comfortable, friend
-It is enormous
-Idiot
It is as the strange twin
As it is, it is happy inside
-I want one of those
-They finished
Your girlfriend harasses us
They convinced me to
to take a trip
He/she looks at this
As you call yourself?
You know where I can get
a swig?
That you need?
Not you, something eats...
PCP, the priority
Ok that are two
Clear
We return... to my boxcar
... and do we take something?
If?
Does Chingado, know that?
I attempt it but...
... I don't find it
but wait
Do they want a swig?
No, thank you
This well, but we will request it
in another side
Did I find it, ok?
You smell well
We have to leave, Lora
us this waiting
-If, we have a friend
-Do they have a friend?
1, 2, 3, perfect we won't have
that to share hey
-We have to leave, don't worry
-To where they go?
And your you get dressed this way
damned cow
As chingados you did call me?
I told you American stupid cow!
That you cr...?
The train is too much
small dog
We will see them
For that told this way you?
My God Loren that I happen?
Somebody enters...
... there is a policeman in the train
or something like that?
If, I will revise
You takes everything
It is horrible, I regret it
They are the idiotic scullions
They are those idiotic scullions
Alone stays quiet
Hello... excuse some of
you this lost?
Oh my God
As you knew that mine was?
I saw a type leave of here
and I am about being taken my handbag
I found it in their pocket
I worry about if he/she returns
Do you want to stay with us?
-Deveras?
-If, we have another seat
-If, they come
-If totally
Thank you
I believe...
.. that we all need this
That well
Non thank you, I don't drink
Thank you
As always he/she says
my potato...
... "nasdrovje"
to serve them
Nazd - ro - vje
So you're going to  angers to french?
Look I dont wanna go home...
I don't blame you, I drop twice
at the overnight train
There is some place left
in erurope?
So where are you going?
On a lil a Spa vacation
Where?
Slovakia
Wait, what's that with some boring in Slovakia?
You hasnt been bored  in Slovakia
for fifty years
It is Bosnia, lover
As if you knew it your
That other places are?
This the best place in the world
I go twice to the anus
It is grandiose to escape to
the Italian
Haya is many but
Hot-Springs?
Is something of beauty?
-I want to go
-It is easy
Alone you have to give
turn in Prague
That well
You know, I have had demaisado
this weekend
This well, we will make it
You know some place
to stay?
Can I help them?
I need a room
for my friends
If, clear, their passports
porfavor
American, well
If that well, stay
the whole night
No, I want this
No, it is for my
Here their keys are
This is a steering wheel for
the tonight festival
They will have a good time, we go
I know it, they have it
cacda anus
-If
-A lot of music, dances and suits
Oh my God, we can go
Half Gay is heard
Excuse
We will be there
We go, here
-Thank you
BiemdiedoP
GIVE that I refer!
That it happens?
If, anything... alone it finished
my breakfast
devera?
These sure one?
If, if, I can go to the moment
Alone I will tell him/her that I have
an appointment
God, religious and heathen
Lorna, do you have a newspaper?
In fact if
I have to write Preposition
of the beautiful thing that it is this village
And I have to write Preposition
of you
That was good
-Something late
-Grafccuas
Do they have a dollar?
-I have
-No, no, not
No, I have
I have ments
Do they like mints?
Welcome to Slovakia
Both have a suite
Here they are their you kill
Perfect, thank you
-Clever to make this?
-If, I am clever
Deveras?
Because you see yourself as
if you didn't like
If I like it, I will take a bath
and I will feel better
Thank you
If?
I go to the department
This well
Not I have chosen anything
I cannot also pay it
No, esque is not able to
to listen anything
We go, I don't have that
to speak of everything
He/she says that their father
it doesn't allow it to him
If
She would want to be
in Slovakia,
Very bad
You are a pro
I believe that I will pass with this
of the tattoo
-We go man, let us make it
-Tatu, I am not me...
... it is not my style and me...
I don't like needles
No, I don't like needles
Compa that you make?
That is the problem man
Linda...
... that he/she will say when he/she sees the...
my wife won't understand it...
... but friend, is
some other one...
... option
All take tattoos
This in the contract
Steve, we go
Sit down, these types
they have their plan
The tattoo is something
very difficult of explaining
Not you had to explain a lot
for the weapon that you brought of Thailand
-For heaven's sake
-Not I can believe that every time...
Is there some problnema?
No, non wise esque that this
it was it leaves of this
Stuart
This is not as everything
the rest, you cannot retract
Sit down
Which is the problem
Before they say something...
... it is not alcoholic
And those children of there me
they gave them
-Does Oh God know them?
-No
I have go to thank
Not much English hblan
This is probably
the drink but alcoholic that has proven
Thank you
-Health, Nestrovia
-Nestrovia
It is my song, we go
They come, let us see what you have
There they are... at 3 o'clock on the dot
-Is a madness not?
-It is this way
-To where you go?
-Forget something
Do you want to dance?
With me
No, thank you, me...
... I have not taken enough
We go, I will teach you
No, deveras, is easy
No, deveras thank you, but...
... I feel tired
I could have helped you
Does it excuse?
That type, you have
some problem?
No, this well
That he/she said?
Anything, alone he/she wanted to dance
Non temolestes
These bothering me?
He/she takes a swig
-Thank you
-Of anything
-I sit down it a lot
-Don't worry
-Allow me to buy him/her a swig
-No, it is not necessary
I insist
Oh my God, wants to take me
in their boat
Not he/she speaks English, but
do we understand each other, do you know?
Alone he/she promises that non angers
to any side with the, ok?
For that not?
Which is the problem
Alone I am dancing with the one
Alone because it is very comely?
No, alone I want you to stay here
that we don't separate...
... alone you promise me that
we will leave meetings
Lorna
rometeme that non angers
anywhere with the one
This well
Dois porfavor
Here you have, I regret it a lot
-This well
Greetings
That he/she brings you to
this bank of the world?
Her, she brought us
And your?
Hinestamente, not you
I sit down it, this is...
probably.
... they should have a
I exercise taking care of them
For that to travel this way alone
to say that they are American
You already know
Deveras?
Health for that reason?
It seems that your friend, is been
If, I believe that they will have sex
but late
I could tell him/her...
Neither 3 centuries ago they had
sex there
Perhaps your table is there
It is a long history
We will have to listen to it
in another moment
It is a small village, and seugo
we will see each other of nuevoMuy vueno
Good night
Good night Beth
Did I tell you my name?
No, listen that he/she said it
your friend
But I have to tell you
mine, is Stuart
I like in knowing you Stuart
Good night
Lorna!
I sit down it!
You promised it
Him you
I sit down it
That distant
Roman that you make?
They come with me
He/she closes the eyes
I have to see him to return
Beth!
He/she hardly knows it
You know, it continues ahead and me
I will go for Lorna
This well, thank you
-Sure
-Thank you
Do you come?
Good night
No, we will sleep
-Ah if?
-If
The this well, but we can
go to rest, we go
-Not it is very sweet for the one
-This well, I take care of it
I am sure that you will make it
but non tonight
Good night
I sit down it, I sit down
very embarrassed
I will go direct
to the prostitute bed
You that you will make it
You are the first type
that I arrive late in the prepa?
Not but perhaps to the I finish
Me if
This small Greg, returned
of certain place
There was something in the one
it had changed
Not he/she said anything, there was something
different, simply the wise thing
If, you seem...
... technically it is as
the animals foresee it
Exactly, as an animal
But you sometimes know somebody
that it is very awful
Something makes you think that
this type has killed somebody
Nobody says it
But as an animal
you can feel it
You know that this type has
the balls to make...
... what wants
Now that you know it,
... people aben will be
Linda will fear you
That makes it will be of payment
for the rest of our lives
It depends on you
Single mante ites hreore
You s the qye pasatan in seghunos aqi
-No, no, n me diensto friend
It is as we make it
For the following level
co eioente in those goings
Does something know strange in the agura?
If
You faith like the girl
that we met hot
That the game begins
But strong, but strong...
Return?
No, I have just revised
I believe that I am the only one
that he/she didn't have action last night
I attempt it
If, this place is magestuoso
Perhaps this having breakfast
No, God willing this in coma
It is something about
their letter...
Please, please
Please...
No
God, please help me!
-Veto
-Porfavor helps me
-Alone you take away from my
-No, no, help me
-Somebody pursues me
-Be about helping but you don't listen
Go away
The police arrived soon
They are looking for your friends
Thank you
But you?
Porfavor
Thank you
Then, your and Sasha...
-.. you are...
-Oh not
God, not
It is as old as for
to be my potato
To that is devoted?
It cares and it exports
They come, we go for clothes
Porfavor doesn't harm me!
-I will make what is
-I won't harm you
This well
Porfavor helps me
That that is?
I will make you beautiful
Beautiful so that?
For the client
It aids!
I am procupada for Whitney
Withney is a rude girl
She will be well
You have a scratch
If
-It hurts
-I sit down it
You have a very beautiful skin
thank you
Who the one is?
Alone some friends
They come, you should rest
I will wake up you when
arrive the police
Do you believe that we are some sick persons?
Chingado, not!
Friend, aims some part
of the world where there are not laws
Where there are damned characters
Those are the shits
We are the normal ones
Some idea of that that
will we make now?
Nisiquiera would want to know it
He/she listens
I am me
I Am Stuart
Not say anything, ok
If they hear us speak
They killed us at both
Did you listen to me?
I need to know if these listening
That chingados faces?
That it is this place?
Where chingados is?
Stuart!
You remember when...
... I said that not wise
that that toward here?
This is it I make here
That it is this place?
This place
People come here...
... people come here to
to kill people
That?
To the one who you/they kill?
Oh my God! Will they kill us?
Not us
Oh my God
Oh my God, will you kill me?
-Will you kill me?
-No, no, not!
No, God, not!
Then that chingados makes here?
That chingados brings position?
Somebody brought me here
The same q1ue to you
Somebody that I know
He/she wants that me...
... make this
With the one
That?
Stuart, porfavor...
... porfavor allows me to go, porfavor
help me to leave this seat
Take off of this seat porfavor!
Where you want the first
That was very good!
You should have seen
your expensive scullion
We have to leave of here
Not we can
Do they believe that you killed me?
Your you are not a mounstro
Not I am this way
No, him you
-You are good person
-Not I am this way
Him you, of course that not
Not I am this way
We have to leave of here
Do you have family, not?
A wife, my wife
Nisiquiera me gustsa my wife
-Did you finish?
-If
Hey, you have not made anything
You have to finish
Do you know that? Let us already gorge, if you don't like
finish it your same one
Not you can leave to less
that you complete, it is the contract
I renounce!
They have my money and
they can stay it!
Not I will return to that room!
Finish!
Hello, it is their it kills...
... it won't be available
in at least 20 minutes
Does he/she want it?
Allow to revise
Thank you, we will warn him/her
If?
Apologize to interrupt it
But we have a special one
available at this time
My good price
Where this Stuart?
Their problematic friend
Can I stay it a moment porfavor?
That you believe?
Should he/she make it?
I say, he/she would not pay but of thousand
for this shit
You look at it
Not it lasted a lot
That you made to my friend?
The volume
Soon you will meet with
your friend
That you think of my?
Comely that if
Lousy dog
Now you respected me
I will make you to believe me
Tell me that I am a shit
Never me jodas
You look at yourself
That?
Do you have something to say?
If? Dog?
Well, but it is worth that it is good
Do let us listen that?
I know your wife
I know your wife Stuart
She doesn't understand each other
-As me I see it, your you are strong
-I am strong
-That sees
-I am the scullion hercules!
Him you, that sees, I see it
He/she hoped you kissed me
I want you to kiss me
I thought of you the whole night
Throw you to the floor
These afraid one?
Do you love me to my?
I like it
You look at me
Dog
Damned prostitute
Go up you to the seat!
Go up you to the prostitute seat!
-Which the code is?
-Chinga your...!
Which is the puto code!?
-That?
-December 12?
That chingados!
Not he/she opens up!
Already the truth!
Shoot him/her!
this behind you!
Prostitute's son!
Shoot him/her!
Not shoot! Care!
Not shoot!
Porfavor doesn't shoot!
-Wait!
-I want to buy my exit of here
Not you can pay it
Not say that I cannot pay it
there is not anything that he/she cannot pay...
... he/she would buy to each one
of those of this room
Angers with your parents
for money?
No! Dog son!
it is my money
Alone brings me a PDA,
an I number of bill and a beneficiary
I have bills in Zuiza,
Luxemburg and Ireland
Alone I gave your puto price!
Trust, I have it!
Negocioemos
This is a shit!
This is business
I will pay but
Not you have but
that your house
Or the school priovada
of your daughter
It is for that reason that you paid
Which is the I number?
The money is not the one
only problem
We have a contract, lover
That contract type?
Anyone that comes
to this place...
... it cannot leave...
... without killing
I should kill you, damned dog
That you told me?
You are an idiot...
lousy p...!
Wait!
Damned shit! Wait!
I judge you
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org