Downloaded From www.mysubtitles.com
Astonishing truth?
The people think about me as something environmental.
And when I go down to see them, they say:
Mother Nature, you are a female dog
destructive.
Ok, which you see is disaster.
While I see the growth for the
following generation.
You want to grow without food, without
animal.
And from the small ones, until the humans,
that be very grateful.
And everything worked well.
Until that a generation arrived.
The spoiled babies
and these dwarfs of diapers.
They thought could make everything that you/they wanted
when quizessem.
For instance:
When he/she enters her in war
that is to demonstrate his/her force.
However these boys say:
I don't like this war.
I believe that will stay home.
The hour that you/they stop looking doesn't arrive
in turn and have.
They say, our careers come first.
The babies can wait.
They want to be happy with money and
to accumulate ownerships without serventia.
And they think that can pick the resources
natural.
And to contaminate the water.
And to build buildings until the sky.
However I have the power.
Yes, yes, because now
They will age.
And they won't like.
And they will say: Oh, I don't want a double chin!
They will remove them a piece of the behind for
to put him/it in the face.
That is not natural.
It is not natural.
And they will say, no, we don't want to age.
I want to be young forever.
For always and forever.
And they know what think.
Pure shit.
IT COULD NEVER BE HIS/HER
Hello mom, where were they?
We went to see Sara in his/her house
and soon we were Beverly Hills.
However they said that you/they wanted their own children.
I forgot of who was each son.
That such he/she sees himself each boy with each dad, that
it is good.
What did in his/her head pass?
They turned me a little
because my hair grew inside of my head.
Instead of out.
What does make with that?
What?
That is mine, I bought him/it
in the again.
And he/she didn't have his/her wallet, as always.
As soon as I bought him/it.
Because he/she didn't have my pants, for that.
Although he/she never trains. He/she always walks with
sweater.
If at least it, he/she would stay in
form.
He/she believes that to use creams me he/she will make to seem as
adolescent.
And you think that to use his/her cap behind
will he/she do him/her riper?
He/she thinks that to use that shirt does to seem him/her
more serious.
In other words, that he/she has state writing the whole end
of week
without encounters?
Didn't any handout arrive?
No.
He/she will want to jump on me.
Only human being.
Does he/she know about a thing?
Deberia to leave.
I will mark him/her an encounter with somebody.
You have luck.
What did mom, happen with the good arrivals?
Lindsay, love you.
Thank you, Orlando.
Ei, you said that he/she loved me.
He/she never said that. Still dressed of bride no
he/she would change of idea.
However you love me, I know that yes.
Orlando, we go!
Go, he is mine!
And you have an ugly body.
It is igualzinho to yours.
And that dress is so out!
What does mean he/she?
When in the school something is old-fashioned
we called him/it out.
However affection, that is to deceive somebody.
As the one that uses the ugliest clothes of the
neighborhood.
I will already reward him.
Leave my man or he/she dies.
Do I believe that you are very beautiful, does he/she want to swim?
Why suddenly is happy?
It is maniac depressive.
Mom, and as he/she knows when true love is?
He/she usually listens the highest music and
sometimes seedling with him, sometimes included space
higher.
Not in television, but in the real life.
Real life?
Of where removes that?
He/she knows, no longer they import me so much Barbie.
However they newly are beginning.
He/she has a jeep,
a horse, a fourth of recordings.
Yes, but no longer it satisfies me.
God!
The people still God says?
Clear, nowadays it is said, God, I am dying from hunger.
Dog, don't behave as if he/she didn't know.
He/she should know how to hold.
He/she knows that he/she only wants to annoy him/her.
I believe that he/she needs to stand back of that.
Only remember every time to see a tree!
He/she won't have this man of the trees that
have.
Wait!
He/she is right, I went dizzy.
No there is other tree that quizesse to see.
Cut!
Did I go too emotional?
He/she enchanted me that of the trees.
You were well, he/she gave me a lot.
You were well, he/she gave him/her a lot.
It was emotional, so brilliant!
That is beautiful, of where removed him/it?
Ei Rosie, there is a meeting.
Good-bye!
Let us find the mom!
And these balls are so weighed!
Where?
The balls are very weighed!
The one of the bowling.
It is an organ!
They seem the man's testicles.
And that is stupid.
Only play her.
It is Gena!
My secretary.
That is enough for me.
He made a lot of games for will Grace.
It is besides you never support him.
Everything is a game.
Is he/she making another show of talents?
Where?
What has of 2006.
He/she makes my plastic surgery show.
It is astonishing what do.
Fact is had the eyes.
He/she seems a 28 year-old man.
He/she thinks that suddenly can if for in a
young picture.
Unless it maintains his/her form, mute.
He/she can run, to jump from top to bottom.
However inside it continues envelhencendo.
Ei, there is something new to redo.
Internal organs.
Now he/she can make him/it.
A reduction of the stomach or
a piling of straight.
If he/she does them baby, it will seem younger than yours
former-wife.
He/she is with that of Cameron Diaz and Justin
Timbarlake.
I am the one that is behind that and who me
pay.
I don't want that his/her wife if it completes, nor the
whole people.
I call soon, mom.
Did anybody call?
See what did Rhiana!
He/she already made that to Tom.
It is so comic!
We have to do some changes in the episode.
The part that left in the bowling was cut.
He/she has to do what is better for the show.
He/she was the censor, they thought was very sexy.
Do I feel a lot of tá?  Forget!
If somebody needs of me, I am alone.
Clear!
Speak to me girl!
Is Rosie?
No, has just left.
He/she had to do an emergency botox.
You are bad!
No, no sobreatue, be only nice.
Quite so, speak to the girls.
Female dogs!
Good-bye Dilan!
Hello!
Hello mom!
What does the one know happened today?
What?
I went to the bathroom
and he/she had blood and I was not nervous.
Wanted, that is his/her period.
Happinesses, you are a woman!
That the game begins!
Mom, which is better? Maxi with brims or
these super absorbent?
I like these other ones.
Wanted, he/she doesn't need these whole ones.
Can I use these? Yes.
Ops, had a career
moving my trazeiro
and to do me the good.
Oh, baby, baby!
Ops will see more
and to dance as prostitute.
It is that I don't have talent.
Ei, see what found!
They gave me in the sixth year.
Is he/she seeing?
It is my period!
Kaki is cleaning.
He/she is eating well.
And that is having here?
It is protected, nobody knows what happens
enter their feet.
When can I have sex?
When you...
He/she obtains his/her title.
No, we go, really!
When it goes for the University to the 18.
Mom, to the 15!
In way none!
Maybe to the 17.
Mom, 15 are the new ones 17.
The adolescents should see this with yours
parents.
Brilliant, call his/her mother!
That!
This sound is leaving me crazy!
Mom, I should play to have something in common.
He/she seems as a good relationship.
Now go home!
I have to sleep here.
My father was today the some prizes.
Only make something in silence, to finish mine
task.
How devils only obtained two points?
From now on, anything of problems.
No clubs, no adolescent pregnancy.
Anything of homosexuals.
What does have if he dances with the promotion?
Maybe a lesbian kiss.
However, without nutritious disorders.
Anything of problems racists.
We go, anything of shows yankis.
Did they never listen to her, not?
We always used her/it in the 80.
Ok, removed the dance, when the boy kisses
the other.
No, that was only a badly itinerary.
The reconstructions are big.
The reconstructions are in the fashion.
They want them if they make them, we want
also.
Everything is said on that.
He/she can make him/it.
Let us make this show well.
And the part, I want that incorporates this in the
show.
He/she knows that cannot supply the show of cellular.
They are new, the boys sent more
messages than...
He/she seems very clear that yes.
Oh, and put that thing of I and it is like this how they say
then.
I never saw so many men in only one place.
It is for it that you/they wrote last.
Maybe what gave me did me badly and clear
My head is not prepared for the baths.
Worse than one day
I will be like this.
And I hurt.
And my head is not ready for the baths of the
third floor.
Thank you very much, it was brilliant.
I don't see none!
And that there is of this boy Shan?
Maybe if we call him/it again...
Let to try me a thing.
He is Adan.
No, wait, feel one second.
How did he/she make that?
I hope are proud of you.
I hope you/they have a real feeling of
success.
Because one day they know, no longer I will be in the
school.
And in a close future.
However one day they will open the newspaper or they will attend
the tv
and they will see me
or the some other magician
that he/she makes something spectacular.
And they will remember that you/they treated him badly.
Drian, would like to be so good
like you, boy.
Because now ríem.
Because they say that we have something that us
contaminate.
Ok, have of that now in my pants.
However you have something very worser
in their souls.
It is what want.
Was I well?
Thank you very much. He/she was brilliant.
He/she was brilliant, thank you very much.
Very well, thank you.
It is something good.
Not even he/she thinks him.
Ready? Yes!
What Dilan does the one know did yesterday?
It used his/her mug of milk in his/her mouth and the
he/she bounced for yours.
Actually I underestimated them.
I will do better.
In mathematics the one what is pi?
3.
3.14. Last night he/she knew him/it.
Ok, see each other.
3.14, don't forget.
I take out, because I think that was very sexy, already
he/she waited for him.
Yes, is it that?
Of the money what is there?
I call in a little while.
Is Rosie?
He/she is changing his/her hair.
He/she told me that collected my schedule.
Wait!
It is that there, direct in the eye.
The larger boys write down without that.
We already lost the lunch.
And it continues with that.
I feel, but no longer I kiss his/her trazeiro never
plus.
In English he/she would say, no longer I carry their things.
We go, she has a perfect body.
With those thighs!
When it was the last time that obtained one
magazine?
Lindasy, Paris, the girls of TV.
It is what I say.
Tired, it is what say.
We go, he/she has to have attitude!
No, I don't want him to get dressed as the other ones
boys.
He/she has to dress something to whitewash him/her well.
A shirt that enhances the green of their eyes and...
Maintain the jacket for if maybe...
That light it doesn't seat.
That their emphasis eyes!
It is not what seek.
Oh, by God!
Oh, I am beautiful!
I am beautiful!
Actually I am very well.
It is not for so much.
We go, I never saw myself with un good look.
Why not?
Because they never saw me beautiful, I make to laugh them
to call his/her attention.
Wait one second!
It uses the comedy to hide their feelings.
I believe that he/she has something here.
Wait one minute!
What?
You are very beautiful!
What did the one find?
Not even he/she needs to arrest the hair!
How does it get that look?
Hurried!
I cannot make miracles!
Excuse.
He is Adam yes, hello!
Hello!
I see you soon.
Ok.
I know that you/they said things on me.
I cannot get up to 7:00 a.m for the
make-up,
to do exercise.
Therefore when arresting my lines
and to shine at 16 o'clock.
I cannot make him/it.
He/she is well.
All want something of me.
There is much more than can offer.
I promise him/her that we will make something more
so that it can be better.
Thank you.
It is that when I am tired
I don't make my best work.
Nobody wants that.
He/she is only tired. Yes.
Fortune-teller? What?
The life is good.
I know what wants to say.
Do I pose to eat these?
They are delicious magicamente.
Tecnicamnte is not magic.
It is sugar.
What does the one know happened today?
My friend and I invited Zack and Dilan to the
movies on Wednesday.
We asked the zack wants to go and he/she said ok.
And Zack said, I will be with Melanie.
And Dilan with Izi.
And what Dilan does the one know said? What?
He/she said, I suppose.
Serious?
He/she still has shampoo.
However this is soft.
And I have to seem better.
I cannot believe that goes the an encounter in group
with the boy that you like.
Don't worry mom, their parents will be there.
Ei, see how I was!
And that finds of this itinerary?
Yes, it would be better.
Take one.
Did Quiem put this ketchup there?
Action!
I need to know that will do for the festival of
talents.
You like.
That he/she is speaking?
What does make he/she?
Something of surprise?
I already read my lines.
It is exactly the same.
I won't make this of all the forms.
I know that doesn't fall him/her well.
He/she seems shit!
However this boy could be next Ben
Stiller.
It is never known.
And it could be good for you to have
a good relationship.
Ok, return.
Thank you.
Moni said that we will work to the 8.
Probably yes, until that he/she leaves.
His/her husband allows to work him/her
until so late?
I AM NOT MARRIED!
And his/her boyfriend?
I don't have.
Will there be a musical one for the show, not?
He/she will be in the supervision yes.
He/she looks, there is a boy among my companions of
room that
he/she plays in a band, and equal will tell him/her.
Maybe you can.
Do let to wonder a thing? Clear!
Most of the students in this show
he/she has wives, children...
Ok, are not exactly adolescents.
And you got the work.
However how many years he/she has
in the reality?
In the reality?
Well, 32.
For qué? How old are you?
He/she is super!
Then, what says?
Ok.
On Friday?
He/she is well.
We will make something to kill the diet.
Something type Lindsay or Hillary.
I don't know. It is something like that.
He/she seems beautiful.
We will meet in the palm trees.
Oh yes!
You know where it is that.
However I can catch him/her.
Brilliant.
Ok, about the 9?
Well, ok.
See through where goes.
He/she is well.
Oh for God, as he/she should love this!
We see each other.
Ok, is a little younger.
Estaría well if I went a man.
Because he/she doesn't notice in the intelligent things,
instead of the brutes?
What did talk him/her about jumping in this?
Only in the kati house.
He/she is well.
Speak to me about the school.
Moli had an idea today.
Since she goes out with the best friend
of Dylan
and he/she will tell him/her that he/she speaks to Dylan that I like him.
And to know that said.
No, don't allow him to know that likes him.
Act as if it didn't exist.
Seem busy the whole time.
He/she has to act as if he/she didn't care.
Hello?
It is happy with his/her service of long
distance?
I am learning a lot on acting
normal.
What such? I like.
However see that happens when I make this.
Don't make that!
Oh it goes!
He/she already comes.
Is it brilliant, not?
Can he/she give me his/her shelter?
Oh thank you!
Who is?
He/she is a prisoner.
Very functional.
Ei, his/her mother uses the same medicine.
He/she seems as a great relationship.
I am in the middle of a dance game, if
he/she wants to go...
Ei, knows the secret to arrive to the
following level?
Is there a secret?
Can it become trained?
He/she is well.
Izzi, please, lowers that!
I cannot ponder with that stupid music.
Mom, see how I moved forward!
Devils!
Thank you.
Is he/she with cold?
No, I am well.
Take!
Feel his/her identification.
He/she will be the largest there inside.
I can handle him/it.
It is not better to return to the house
and to do something calm?
Ok, you are ridiculous.
He/she seems that the old wants to call the attention.
What does make that lady?
Something of drinking?
Ok.
I will look for a beer. Does some want thing?
No, thank you.
It seems that he/she needs a drag.
Serious?
Let to guess me. A martini, not?
I feel, I cannot listen to him/it.
What such?
Does he/she want to dance?
I don't know who is you.
I will try, but he/she doesn't make to stop her.
He/she is crazy!
It is Friday night!
I have to do him/it.
Thank you for this.
I believe that was everything.
I will be good.
I want him to listen a thing.
Greenday!
They lent me.
Ricky Martin?
It is not mine.
Actually I don't have 37.
What age does he/she have?
Actually I have 31.
Ok.
I need my keys.
He/she is well.
I am well, I already have them.
I need my wallet.
What is making he/she?
It is the form of finding him/it.
What do happen with that de30?
He/she wanted to say 39. I thought that he/she had something as 30.
Either you.
Because he/she knows what say: Never trust in
nobody with more than 30.
Then it can trust me.
Ei, you are super.
Thank you.
What has been making he/she?
Anything.
Yes, clear!
See, he/she obtained his/her money of turn.
He/she worked well.
See the tests.
Boys give him/her 30.
In girls, 22%.
We saw the same numbers when Scritch
he/she left in the...
Those were the safe number for the
campaign.
It is like this, see the new boy.
Ei, taste of these numbers.
The rest of the writers approves him/it.
Why does want to continue with him?
Because he is amusing,
it is nice
and it can act.
The girls will love him.
I don't need more words.
I believe that this boy should continue.
Ok, but we lowered a point and he/she leaves.
He/she won't pass.
I promise!
Ei, cut her!
She is a girl!
It insulted me and he/she will do again.
Why was all this?
He/she said that my mother makes a show of three points.
Ei, didn't listen that Brad Pit
he/she dismissed his/her father.
They already gorged and they leave.
And they will go well.
Oh, what is happening?
They are without clothes, in the pure skin. We have that
to dress them.
That is depressing!
What did happen in the films?
Did Dilan put his/her arm in turn of you?
No.
Did they join their arms when they were close?
First I put him/it in him.
And I put his/her hand with mine.
And he removed her.
And if it put like this.
He/she is not ready for relationships.
He/she had bride last year.
Then he/she doesn't have good taste.
Mom, I love him!
Ok, feel a lot.
Is it safe what wants to undo of them?
Yes!
It is so sad when it finishes the season.
Everything leaves.
Does he/she want to play a last one?
Mom, I am big for Barbie!
Yes, but me not.
Ok, will be the last episode.
Let us see.
Is he/she without admission or the one what?
He/she wants Adam to leave.
I am not badly.
I am redrafting.
This is good.
Encounters.
And not to act as idiot.
I consulted and it means penises.
If he/she allows to tell us penises.
Yes, they can see penises, but...
This ó the bad penises.
As violation.
And that is exactly the good penises?
See him/it!
Why only tell ourselves, that is well.
It is an interrogation type.
However all understand him/it.
Ok all, hour of eating lunch.
They go and don't throw me this.
I see him/it.
He/she is an actor.
Ei, retreat young lady bulimia.
Hello Scritch!
He/she knows, I believe that should take care.
Why?
They speak that is very white.
Me?
I caught you!
However with Rhiana it only falls him/her well the pesssoas that
say
the as she is beautiful.
Rose wants actually that
feel well with her.
Is it it what wants, not?
He/she cannot tell him/her. Go and he/she catches Rhiana.
Unless he/she has something sexual in that.
Ei, should not smoke that thing.
It is not marijuana.
It is Shiton, oh it goes!
Oh, as it got that work?
What is that?
In case they feel well, both can be better.
I like the quality of the volume.
He/she seems that Adam likes.
This is not well.
I am fed up with reading on Misha.
Mindsay and Katy.
Now all have better papers.
Therefore, all will be there.
And that kills me.
I went a young girl a lot before them.
They are seeking him/her for the scene of the beach.
I will put my biquine.
He/she already told him/her that you have
a body of a girl of 29?
Serious?
It is besides has that big one...
I have to go.
I cannot let to go her.
However he/she should make him/it.
However I cannot make him/it
But he/she has to go.
However I cannot leave him/her.
However, he/she should make him/it.
His/her work is larger than we.
After all those episodes that there is
produced.
I have to go.
We will go to the movies later.
Should he/she move actually?
My car is not still ready.
He/she takes mine.
I will bring him/it before he/she leaves.
We are going girl!
You are auspicious. He/she goes out with a boy.
It causes many problems for you.
It is an accelerated thing.
Can I help them?
We looked to scenery.
Ok, is something new at this time.
Ok.
He/she walks and averigüa that seek.
Y is same to C and C equal to V.
I had my first writer work
and he was born.
Oh, by God!
In 1977, they made this show,
dark Amdona appeared.
However now it is the new.
He/she thought that I was born with the old age.
As he/she does that a positive number
do turn negative?
It removes him/her the positive remaining him/her
larger numbers.
This won't work.
Yes, because it is a maxim.
No, I want to say this.
You and me.
Why? What did I make?
No, anything.
You are wonderful.
Did we pass the sixth well?
Yes, Friday was brilliant.
Then the one what?
He/she remembers when we spoke on that he/she had him/it...
I don't stop thinking in as...
Young.
Quite so.
I plan to be old.
Well, I don't plan to be young.
That is yours.
What does think he/she am a dizzy boy, not?
No.
Of course no!
You are what is. Young.
Youth is superior to be old.
And that?
And everything.
Oh yes?
And who is like this?
That is a fear example.
He/she knows that in our society,
youth is better than old age.
To be high is better than lower.
Beautiful it is better than smart.
I only want...
If we commit ourselves,
somebody will result wounded and
Because I am older
I have to be the responsible.
However we can be friends.
Can we be friends, not?
Yes, he/she knows that will be here for you.
He/she doesn't have sense of humor.
Ok, now this!
Hello!
An is not little low, hey?
He/she is so punished!
Oh for God!
I already arrived.
What are making?
Anything.
How did it arrive so early?
Where is Adam?
We decided not to leave more.
Why, liked him.
I tried to be ripens.
It is not his/her style.
I know.
Why does still have encounters?
Be not stupid!
The oldest people don't have encounters.
Good night.
I told the truth.
Where is Rosie?
He/she is with academical.
What hour does the one return?
I don't know.
He/she had to seem well.
He/she told me that he/she caught Glo of his/her office
However no havía nobody there.
That allowed to remove me this
when there was not anybody.
And you come everyday.
It is so hard.
It is for you.
He/she decided to give him/her this.
What is?
It is what obtains sleeping
with the producer.
Did she write?
Yes.
He/she has three more episodes.
It seems that will continue a time.
Maybe we can go for a coffee.
And which his/her opinion? Can we use this in the show?
No.
He/she thinks about these cellular ones.
Hello.
I see that he/she already has the new episodes.
Yes.
And?
I have good news.
Serious?
After doing a lot of investigation,
I will give him/her other opportunity.
That is a sample.
I believe that is good for the show.
It is what you think.
However his/her subconciente is finding
ways of
to stay to my side.
Surprisingly they want him/her here.
This is not anything!
However I need that says him/it.
I don't believe that Michi sees go-girls.
Maybe yes.
I believe that likes a lot.
Why does that find?
Because he/she gave him/her a musical cd.
His/her voice saying what speaks his/her heart.
That is not a good lesson.
Only listen to him/it.
Where is his/her car?
Oh, I sold him/it. I am in the bankruptcy.
He/she knows that
he/she wanted to see him/her.
Thank you.
Ei, are here.
Do see?
He/she seems younger.
I know.
I don't see in that way.
Actually it seems his/her nephew.
Nephew? He/she is wanting brother to say.
How many years he/she has?
And do how many think I have?
49?
Yes.
However do I seem to have how many?
Well, he/she would say...
Give 32 or he/she will never stop.
Thank you.
I operated the eyes.
No, this is not allowed.
And go down then!
After this whole time,
Y and Zack came.
As soon as don't stop them.
Did he/she make you to laugh?
I have faith that yes.
Is it brilliant, not?
Did Rhiana already arrive? Not yet.
However does it come?
Probably.
Let us go!
Men!
Continuing, go-girls comes.
Silence all, my part comes.
Can I remove an extra mechanical pencil?
Cwow, see that skate board!
I am me that swallow them.
Nathan!
Leave that!
Well done!
Thank you.
Good I work there.
Serious?
And you?
I see you soon.
I thought that would go my house.
I already have a, thank you.
Excuse me one second.
Stupid!
And that seeks now?
I am writing a reality on mine
life.
On that.
How reality can be if you write him/it?
You are adorable. Good show and good night.
Thank you, Rosie.
Thank you for having come.
Brena, excellent episode.
Am I concerned for qué?
I believe that that humor has a great writer.
Think about that.
Pleasure in knowing him/her.
Big!
He/she is Joe.
Now,
remove this.
I feel nude.
He/she shows some skin alí inside.
Not to me, show to him.
Good luck.
He/she takes mom.
I didn't feel bill.
Did Jena already leave?
All already left.
He/she has one "that" of my grandmother's house.
Does he/she want berber some thing?
Ok.
It is strange, in one moment it is trying
to lose weight
and later,
very heavy things.
He/she seems that Izi is busy.
He/she is not here. He/she went to see his/her father.
And when does it return?
On Sunday.
Then we are alone.
Only you and me.
It seems that is trying to seduce me.
Would it like that seduced him/her?
Yes.
I felt his/her lack.
And me her yours.
Don't answer. He/she is my mother.
I feel... hello mom.
Can I tie him/her in a little while?
Oh shit, I left my condones in the car.
Wait here.
He/she seems that the boy doesn't want to make pregnant him/her.
And?
When it arrives the time,
he/she cannot have
those children.
He/she would love to have a baby.
He/she is only using you.
That is not true.
He/she already has the work.
He/she opens, I forgot my keys.
It would lose his/her head if it was not arrested.
Give this to Adam.
What is?
It was collected by an extra. I feel a lot.
Ok, calm.
Ok, have an evaluation of 22.
However on Thursday we had twice more.
Yes, but he/she has to look the balance.
He/she sees, still knowing
that the numbers seem high,
we should go up some.
Does he/she understand that should see now?
Yes, all understood.
He/she forgot of that.
Independent of we go up the points,
we should be happy for that.
What is the one what more loves in me?
He/she never said that he/she loved her.
Let us go!
He/she never said.
First...
Oh, by God!
Didn't he/she leave in go-giris this week?
He/she was so amusing.
That of hiding was so amusing.
Thank you.
I want to say, I hardly ever see him/it.
Because he/she upsets me.
He/she didn't know about that.
However that episode was the best in months.
Does he/she have card?
Can I give him/her this?
Yes, clear!
She is well.
Does he/she know Martin Green? The one of the comedy?
Yes, I know who is.
He/she wants that goes with him in the Friday night
to his/her show.
I don't know...
It was so brilliant to know him/it.
I hope he/she doesn't think badly of me.
However it would enchant me to give him/her my picture.
He/she also has my number.
I had some small papers.
Maybe it can take him/it with us of the go-girls.
Maybe not.
Thank you.
Now he/she will see what can obtain with his/her fame.
He/she is not interested.
Let to show him/her to me a thing.
His/her note great curve here.
It is not his/her type.
This is the style of all wants if he/she gives bill or not.
This point
He/she gives him/her more something.
Without mentioning his/her hair and his/her face.
She can die from hunger.
She can disappear here, but he sees the
signs.
He/she sees the signs that his/her body is eliminating.
Without importing him/it as it preserves him/it.
That is for animals, not for us.
He/she doesn't have medicine.
Is a good thing?
The coffee came fast.
It is had 10 dollars, as it would be yours
porcentajem?
I don't know not even as he/she treats him.
Sr. Mir said that won't get him/it in the way
correct.
I hate the mathematics.
It is eaten three cookies
and 50 lost calories
and he/she has 140 calories,
in each cookie how much is there?
And why do make him/it so difficult?
Adam called. Creo that will come.
I believe that he/she forgot.
His/her telephone!
That hot!
It is the new go-girl poster.
No, and Briana in the room.
With somebody.
I won't leave that is upset.
Somebody sent her.
If somebody had sent her,
he/she would not be in a place of messages.
Because he/she has to be there when does he/she arrest him?
Because Tivo knows that likes.
How will they know him/it what that does there?
I won't reach conclusions. I will speak to him first.
Mami?
It is a smile without expression.
Like her
in this house,
after some long vacations
My telephone!
I was seeking.
When did they make this?
He/she is right, he/she doesn't deceive me.
What did he/she/you tell him/her?
He/she is not such good actor.
Boys, can we continue?
Boys, can we finish this?
So that?
We can improve like this the show.
We gave some ideas.
Nobody appreciates the band of it Draws and he knows.
Where are they?
Mail.
I have an encounter later.
Oh, see!
It seems that you/they gave one of these pictures of the
show.
Are Ei, you and Adam if sells?
No.
Is it it what uses?
Yes.
Not even they are going as friends to places,
or they leave.
Rosie,
is he/she safe?
I am a lot of things but no liar.
He/she takes one.
Never in mi life he/she would smoke.
Cut! Ok, see!
He/she will see in one minute.
Sharon Stone?
Busy.
Alice Davis? Hung.
River? Hung.
Kim Basinger? Hung.
Emma Thompson? Broken hand.
Susan Sarandon? He/she is super operated.
Meg Ryan? Too much plastic surgery.
Naomi Griphit?
A lot of plastic surgery.
Cher?
She is the queen of the surgeries.
Listen, small pervert.
How does he/she dare to insult these women?
How many oscar does he/she have?
Does he/she see her well on them or to Tom Hampson?
Not even he/she would see himself well beside yours
trazeiros.
He/she will see her now.
Ei, is brilliant.
How is Izzi?
He/she didn't call me to ask for my children.
Ok, will be honest.
After the transcriptions of the show
and many presupostos,
to anybody it matters.
Two and Half Man?
Nor all the ones that have children want to see them.
We want to change.
That means, to include music.
He/she continues cutting our projects.
You face him/it. Go-giris is occupying
too much.
I was advised by some friends and...
As soon as it substitutes me for a show reality.
Actually we have a comedy to pass.
Two writers wrote an itinerary
for a very amusing boy.
Wait for him, you know him/it.
Adam Prole
He/she calls himself Shizol.
Shizol?
Shizol.
That means the new thing cool.
No, it doesn't mean that.
He/she means shit.
Anything and you cannot say
he/she substitutes with shit.
Does he/she like that?
Good luck. I hope he/she understands the name.
Thank you for his/her support.
Rosie!
Hello!
Happinesses in his/her show. It is very amusing.
Thank you, and the other also.
Oh, if he/she spoke about his/her boy.
I believe that we gave him/her some calls
did he/she know?
Yes, and it doesn't import me.
Ero calls herself the executive. He doesn't have
sense of humor.
I feel so much, Ian.
No, it will happen again.
I understand, but it is already in their 20.
Happinesses to you also.
He/she seems brilliant. Thank you.
I cannot believe that you/they have made that.
Did they think the one what?
Anything.
To who more they called?
To anybody more.
To who more?
Angie Jake, Jason Papen,
Heather Grant.
Don't forget the other.
Jhony Noxver.
Noi, believe that should go home now.
I feel a lot.
This makes to resemble as an idiot.
If they give me his/her telephone number is because
they trust
in protecting his/her privacy.
Now I seem antiprofissional totally.
I feel a lot.
What do make with you?
I can punish myself.
As escever an excuse to all
the ones what called?
And not to use the telephone for one week.
One month.
It is too much.
Two weeks.
Ok.
All the one that entrusted were disappointed.
Forces of the darkness, listen to us.
What are making girls?
Using magic.
We are witches.
That sad!
Don't worry, we don't make sacrifices
human.
Or with blood.
As in the graph.
This proven that the adolescents only
they owe
to be anorexic or
witches.
How do they make this?
One want to show true love,
light some candles and ask for him/it.
And does the love come?
It can use him/it.
I am hungry.
I think I have some here cookies.
He/she should join. Leave that the fire...
What does make he/she? I call him/it, I write...
I believe that should tell him/her something that in it owes him/it
to wait.
Marti?
Yes?
What?
Am I upsetting myself because the show finished?
I don't know.
Incredible!
Ei, listen!
They want him to make a pilot.
And because he/she has to tell me?
Everything is.
It is what want to tell him/her.
And that there is of Briana?
What?
Don't make to resemble as idiot.
I know what is having.
If you have some thing,
don't stand back for my cause.
What? Why does tell me this?
This arrived for email.
It is madness, somebody wants to play with you.
It was what thought.
Somebody tried to upset me, playing with
his/her cellular one.
It is also tried to leave me disgusted with this.
And when it was coqueteando with Briana...
Coqueteando, that is saying?
He/she flirted with her.
Tell me that he/she made him/it.
Why would make that?
Because he/she said that all should make her to think
that are crazy for her.
He/she never said that.
It was not what listened.
I already know what listened.
Voce is a star. Of these of TV,
he/she wants to have all of the girls that it can.
As soon as he/she can have all.
I don't want beautiful girls jóvens.
I want you.
Ok, understood.
I am very old for these school things.
Listen!
What such what make?
Please, tell me that uses shorts under that.
Yes, healthy very small.
They make to resemble to have a great trazeiro.
If it is what all say.
What such trazeiro?
Don't let to interrupt me them.
He already left.
No, it didn't go.
Leave!
It is the end of the discussion.
When it is very displeased, his/her voice is sharp.
I will see what happens, I was never in a car with
Briana.
Actually he/she has problems in trusting.
Exact, I agree.
What does have to do with this?
Everything!
He/she is the first boy with el that I have been leaving
in 10 years.
And he/she can go out with me.
And I don't want that commits the same mistake
with me.
Then I will be like Ashton.
And she would be like Demi.
And he/she wants to know, we could leave.
She is beautiful.
That devils are speaking?
I am not Demi.
You are not Ashton and you are not Bruce.
Is he/she seeing as it is upset?
In my bachelor party nobody can come.
That is crazy ok?
Only calm down and leave.
No.
Ok, have to leave.
However, when he/she knows, I will call him/it.
Ei, not!
You are well of all the forms.
Ok.
Izzi, go!
I don't have boyfriend, I don't work.
I will only be with a boy.
Is he/she happy now?
I am looking at the show.
This does very sense.
She is refined and beautiful.
He/she gave for that boy the best sex of his/her life.
Without waiting anything.
And she thinks is an I show.
He/she cannot leave crumbs in all of the sides.
What?
It is not that he/she leaves them the a side of the bed.
What is having he/she?
Why does always something have to be badly?
Ok.
Kati is a prostitute.
It ordered a card for Dilan.
And he/she said all that he/she knew what did.
And he/she knows that the master because they told him/her.
I know that he/she said that the fact of Izzi to like of him, not
it turns them a couple.
Can he/she believe?
Not even it likes him. He/she only wants to upset me.
He/she wants is to make fun of.
And it criticized his/her show.
Did he/she say for kati as he/she sits down?
No.
And if it changed my name for Drew?
What does have of badly, Izzi?
Anything, only that can call myself
Drew from now on?
I hate this place. Because we have to come?
Because it cannot use the
same jeans every day.
Because we didn't buy him/it only?
Because they are not him/her badly.
I seem with a cow.
Is he/she well?
I only want to see.
If it presses him/her...
Mom, is not me...
I like that.
He/she seems well.
They don't close.
Which is the mark?
They are tight mamçae, forget.
I am so fat!
I am ugly and he/she doesn't understand me
He/she has flat stomach and it is beautiful.
No, wanted. My face is falling.
And everything is also falling.
Little by little I get older.
You are young.
It is as a new peach.
Izzi, are you beautiful, doesn't he/she see?
I am not beautiful, not even beautiful.
And I am not a peach.
See!
Can I be with her?
Yes.
Adam ordered them.
Ok, that is having? In the set what is there?
That is shit!
He/she told me that he/she would feel the writers
of go-girls.
However he/she didn't give me Rosie.
That is a producing extra, he/she doesn't need her.
When he/she gave me this show promised me.
To the whole group.
He/she already has two writers.
Yes, but it is not the whole group.
It is that don't feel complete.
Ei boy, it is ignoring one
enormous opportunity.
It thinks should be loyal and that group.
It is not what wants to say.
In effect, gentleman.
It is what I want to do.
I will return when he/she obtains her.
Ei, let to feel him/her a piece of advice.
He/she has to leave of that,
or else he/she won't be a real man.
I don't need to be it.
I am an actor.
Mom?
Ei, doesn't want to do me
a birthday breakfast?
When did we eat that?
Hello?
That good to know that is there.
Of the one what is speaking he/she?
That boy Adam wants the writers.
He/she told me that doesn't trust in anybody more than you.
He/she knows that I was thinking
that was able to supevisionar this boy.
Leaning that maybe not.
What does think he/she maybe not?
Maybe not?
Because I think about shit.
As soon as it is that there.
The most powerful man gets the woman.
He/she is right.
And that there is if he/she has a beautiful man or a...
A girl that shows sign of leading him/it?
He/she looks, there is an agreement
for this.
Why cannot change the things?
He/she is not able to, it is not natural.
And that is brilliant of the natural?
What?
Think!
The alluvia are natural, the hurricanes
also.
The earthquakes are natural.
The natural stinks.
It is not for a test.
His/her task arrives late.
His/her language is horrible.
Besides talking a lot with the ones that they are in turn.
I know that he/she is a woman that works.
However I wait for a more little of discipline home.
See, the thing is...
Izi newly had his/her period
and he/she had strange things.
He/she enters in the puberty.
A girl can obtain better notes
for his/her cycle.
Without mentioning that still teachers
they begin to see them different,
As they grow.
That is another thing.
Why would the teachers make that?
You tell me!
Why did obtain this?
And these other questions badly
when are the answers well?
Why didn't show his/her work correctly.
However he/she was right.
I need the solution to arrive
to a good answer.
However she works in a different way.
My work is that these students
make him/it well
and demonstrate him/it in exams.
And it would not be better to support the girls
for they feel
mathematical,
in the place of doing them to believe that are stupid?
I have an idéa!
Why don't you teach as to be better
and does he/she let to become trained my class?
I have a better idea!
Why doesn't catch the exams
and does it put them in the trazeiro?
I already know from where that language comes.
Affection!
You are the best mother of the world.
Let us leave of here.
Izi, when he/she sang that part in the car,
actually he/she surrendered.
Yes, it is the part of screaming.
However I thought about singing her/it to regulate.
Why?
Because all will be in the show.
Dilan will be there.
And?
I don't sometimes do well.
And I don't want to run any risk.
Which is the problem if he/she notices him/it or not?
Make him/it well.
While it shows what has,
nobody will care.
The key? Yes.
He/she takes risks.
He/she was brilliant.
Ei Rosie, feel not to have given him/her
before the sad news.
However I obtained work in Shizzle.
Hello?
They offered him/her a good agreement.
I don't want to do this!
We are not able to is to return soon.
When somebody beats in a weak boy, I will be
lá.í
Every time that somebody is badly, I will be lá.í
Ok, can use that.
Can I see the videos of the beach?
I feel a lot, I can make him/it again.
You told me that he/she wanted that Briana
he/she thought that he/she cared.
And she is aggressive.
It is when it doesn't please the people and he/she does
jokes,
as Jena.
I already made one of Briana and John.
It is so comic!
Ei, raisin!
And that is it what has with this boy?
I have faith in him and I know him/it.
Yes, I like that.
You are an idiot!
However it is wanted him to make him/it,
he/she has to do something first.
Any thing!
Give up Jena, my old secretary.
That will be something hard!
I don't like to dismiss the people.
From when does he/she care with the secretaries?
I am me or her!
Ok.
What?
Listen, I will count everything to his/her wife.
Oh we go!
I will show what does with the fotografías.
You imagined all this, female dog.
Because he/she doesn't tell him/her as if it holds
with talents jóvens?
And from when it seduces the
are producers a talent?
See!
Don't say anything!
Where will I work?
It could get a corner in Hollywood.
We will speak!
That was entertaining.
He/she always knew that Jan was psychotic.
Actually it should like me.
I cannot blame her.
Poor.
I feel a lot.
I acted as an immature child.
It is good to see that.
Only that he/she didn't want that me
he/she left for being older.
I am not so superficial.
It doesn't import me his/her age!
Serious? It only imports me his/her weight.
Oh that beautiful!
What is that?
Ladies and gentlemen, the winner of an Emy!
Benvindos to the fair of talents.
The spring is jóvens time.
All are family.
Without more the than to say, I present them Dylan
Nicolson!
I am Dilan and I have things for saying.
He/she would like to present to the adorable ones
Melani, Izi and Kati!
It was brilliant!
What such the voice?
It removed her/it of me.
What did with his/her face happen?
I made a chin implant.
They can make him/it to seem better.
Where is she?
I will congratulate her!
No, leave her alone!
Does he/she see him/it what is happening?
Does Izi, want to walk?
Ok.
We see each other.
How did he/she know that that will happen?
I am his/her mother.
Be not moved a lot for him.
Now which his/her problem is?
Remember that is very young.
Therefore it will be substituted.
In addition it can like any other.
Besides he/she was not looking at him.
Only taste of you.
Serious?
Yes.
I like his/her beginning.
Would he/she like to play a vídeogame?
Clear!
Some time played Face Scape?
Na, but maybe it can become trained.
Oh for God! Look at her!
It is a thing that never happened with me.
He/she kissed him and it still continues happy.
Hello?
How does it think the things are like this?
His/her body is brilliant!
And he/she has style!
See what got!
Ok, when it puts him/it of that sorts things out...
That is good.
Now it can be calm and to ripen.
However what does mean that?
To change the shoes or to continue like this?
They don't seem good things.
I don't want to do that.
I want to stay passionate.
I want to scream in rock concerts.
And to upset me with the news.
I want to use minifraldas.
He/she will seem ridiculous!
Ok, a lot of people seem ridiculous.
He/she begins to seem normal.
Downloaded From www.mysubtitles.com
www.moviesubtitles.org