Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Honey, you got the baby?
Yeah, yeah, I got the...
I'll get the baby.
I thought you had him.
Coming. Coming.
Oh!
Daddy's got you.
Where's my kiss?
Come on. Come on.
You're doing it wrong.
What are you talking about?
You don't even know what I'm doing.
I can tell by the cry.
Come on, take Kelly.
I got this.
Go ahead.
Hey, my big boy... Hi.
Aw...
That's my big boy.
Oh, yes...
Hi, I'm Richard Cooper.
And that's my wife Brenda.
We have two incredible
children, Brian and Kelly.
We've been married
close to seven years.
My wife is beautiful,
intelligent
and a great mother.
It's the perfect life.
There's just one problem:
I'm bored out of my fucking mind.
Now, I'm sure I'd have
a much rosier outlook on life
if my wife and I
actually had sex,
but there always
seems to be something wrong.
No, my face hurts.
It's not your birthday.
We both work, we're both tired,
but that's no excuse.
To be honest, I don't know
how much more of this I can take.
Richard, do you think
perhaps you work too much?
Oh, no, no, no.
I- I work, too. I do.
But I come home from work, and
I have to take care of the kids,
and I have to take care of you.
And frankly, I'm tired.
I'm tired.
Too tired to wear
a nice pair of panties?
What's wrong with my panties?
They're huge!
You know, the biggest thing
on a pair of panties
should be the tag.
That's all I want to see:
tag and ass.
Tag and ass!
You see? You see?
- This is what I'm talking about.
- Mm-hmm.
You see how insensitive he is?
You know, Brenda,
maybe I'd be more sensitive
if you'd have sex with me.
It seems like the only time
she wants to have sex with me
is to make a baby.
The only time you want
to make a baby with me
is to have sex.
That doesn't make any sense!
Well, that's because I'm tired!
Now we're making progress.
I hated that therapist.
She wasn't married
and didn't have any kids.
You know,
when you're on a plane,
you kind of want a pilot
with more experience than you.
But maybe that's just me.
Now, what I can't figure out
is how can my wife
not have sex with me,
and then send me out
into a world with so many
beautiful women?
That's like dropping me
into the ocean
and expecting me to not get wet.
I mean, every single woman
that I see
I have an imaginary
relationship with.
Like this one.
Ah, she's got beautiful lips.
But if we got married,
how long would it be
before I got tired of those lips?
How long would it be
before those lips
called me an asshole?
And look at her.
What a smile.
She looks happy now,
but if I was married to her
for eight years,
I'djust be thinking about
that phone bill.
I don't know.
And look at her.
Look at those eyes,
those cheekbones.
She's like a painting...
a painting I'd love to mount.
No matter where my head is,
when I get to Manhattan, I'm fine.
I love the city, rats and all.
I love myjob.
I'm an investment banker
at a mid-size firm.
I'm one of the only blacks
at the company.
As a matter of fact,
there are so few blacks here,
I think I know every black
person that works for the firm.
Morning, Pam.
Howdy, Mr. Cooper.
Morning, Ron.
Good morning, Richard.
#Yo, fuck the cracker #
#That's what I say #
#And fuck these bitches
that always want to play #
# I'm the type of nigga
that is never gay #
# If you fuck with me, I'll
put your head in cake #
shoot your moms at your wake #
# If you fuck with me,
you made a big mistake. #
Okay.
Tracy...
this is what we're
doing today, all right?
Seen George?
I'm right here.
See you later, Mary.
George, your wife is on
the phone, and Veronica called.
Wife? I don't want to talk to her.
Find out what she wants.
Call back Veronica.
Rich, you want to
go over that stuff
before Landis gets in?
Sure,just,
uh, take off your coat...
Good morning, everyone.
Cooper, how's the Coleman account?
Incredible. The Narco funds are up.
All right.
Let's get to work, people.
Pupkin & Langford. Please hold.
Pupkin & Langford.
Lunch?
Well, I got to ask.
Come on, you know I hate the crowds.
By the time you get your
food, you got to come back.
Well, have fun all by yourself.
I'm gonna get a quick bite and
then get on the Coleman account.
See ya.
Hey, I got nothing against George,
but I just hate going to lunch
at the same time
everybody else does.
It's just way too crowded.
Look at this mess.
It's just not the New York
that I like.
Now, at 2:00,
it's a different story.
Things slow down.
That's when I like to go out.
I can eat,
or I can go shopping,
or I can just clear my head.
And I can also watch women
and get a good look.
'Cause I know I will never
see them again.
Now,you can't look
at a woman in the suburbs.
You stare at a soccer mom
too long,
and they'll post your name
on the Internet.
Can I help you find something?
Just looking.
Have you seen the new Prada suits?
No, that's okay, that's okay.
Excuse me, sir, would you like to try
a new fragrance today?
Nah, that's okay.
Oh.
Hey! Don't spray that shit on me.
It's really good.
Hi, I'm Candy.
Can I help you with something?
Do you have this in blue?
You know, I think you
should try this green one.
Uh, I-I don't really wear green.
Okay, but this green is hot.
Come on. Trust me.
Let's go try it on.
I'm telling you, I don't like green.
That looks great on you.
You think so?
Absolutely.
It's sexy.
I love it.
I just don't like wearing green.
Yeah, but you should
start wearing green.
I mean, you look
really handsome in it.
Hey, Lisa.
Will you tell him
how this shirt looks.
Oh, I love it on you!
I'm-I'm not just saying that.
I think it looks great on you.
Daddy's home.
Daddy!
Yeah!
Daddy's home.
Hey, Daddy.
How's it going?
Pretty good.
Where's Brian?
Oh, he's upstairs napping.
Oh, hey, I've got
all these tests to grade,
so can you do the dishes tonight?
- Yeah, yeah, no problem.
- Great.
Hey, Kelly.
Hi, Daddy.
How big is Kelly?
This big.
Yeah. Where's Kelly's ear?
Here.
- Where's Kelly's nose?
- Here.
Where's Kelly's esophagus?
Give the kid a break;
she's only three.
Hey, there's white
kids that are three
taking the bar right now.
W- H-I-T-E, please.
Okay, okay.
Hey, Kelly, I got you.
Daddy got you.
- Right upside the head.
- You went shopping? Huh.
Daddy got you.
I thought you didn't like green.
Figured I'd get something new.
It's different.
Pretty.
There were days
when Brenda and I got along great.
But we still weren't having sex.
When a married couple
stops having sex,
at first, they complain about it.
But after a while,
they get used to it.
She walks out of the shower,
you don't even look.
'Cause you know there's
nothing there for you.
The most dangerous time
in a marriage
is when the couple accepts
that they're not having sex.
Speak up; I'm in an elevator.
Richard, there's someone here to see you.
Uh, a client?
She didn't say.
Nikki?
Wow, Nikki Tru.
I haven't seen her in eight years.
She was my best friend's girl.
I was crazy about her.
What's wrong?
You didn't think you'd see me again?
No, it's not that;
I'm just surprised.
Wow, you look good, Nikki.
Thanks.
You know, people don't really
smoke in offices anymore.
I'm not really a smoker.
I'm just trying to lose some weight.
So what's that, a diet cigarette?
I'll put it out.
You look good, Richie.
That's a nice shirt.
Thanks.
So, wh-what brings
you around, Nikki?
I was in the neighborhood,
heard you worked in the area,
thought I'd stop by and say hi.
That's allowed, right?
Yeah. Hi.
Hi.
You want to show me
your office or something?
Come on.
Okay.
It's good to see you.
Yeah, you, too.
- Which way?
- This way.
NI KKI
Are these your kids?
Yeah, that's
my son Brian
and that's my daughter Kelly.
Same mother?
Same mother, my wife, seven years.
No side kids?
No side kids.
I know, it's very white of me.
Richard Marcus Cooper is married.
Tied the knot, till
death do you part.
Mm-hmm.
Something strange about that?
No. Just...
not the Richie I knew.
- People change.
- Hmm.
You happily married?
Yeah, I'm-I'm happily married.
No, you're not.
You didn't say it right.
Okay, how was I supposed to say it?
Oh, I don't know.
But you're not supposed
to think about it.
I hear ice cracking.
What?
You ever walk across
a frozen river
and hear ice cracking?
It's the scariest sound
in the world.
Hey, hey.
My ice is fine.
My-my marriage is frozen solid.
You could do a triple axel
on my marriage.
One second.
Hello.
They're ready to start the meeting.
Yeah, yeah, I'll come right now.
So, to be
completely honest,
I do need a favor.
Ah. I knew Nikki didn't
come over here for nothing.
Well, I just got back in town,
and I'm trying to get a job,
but I need a reference.
Okay, well,
write up a letter,
bring it by, and I'll sign it.
No problem. Whoa!
Magic.
So you just knew
I would sign this, huh?
I figured a friend in
need, couldn't resist.
Okay.
Good luck.
Thank you...
Mr. Married Man.
Even though I hadn't seen Nikki
- in eight years, I got to say,
- Richard.
she looked even better
than I remembered.
Gonna put these right
on top of the block.
Do I have to eat this, Mommy?
Kelly...
- Hey.
- Hey, Daddy.
- Hey, honey.
Mm.
I'm almost
done with them,
and dinner will be ready
in a few minutes, okay?
Is baked chicken okay?
Ah, you know chicken's great.
All right.
Where's my kiss?
Ooh, that's a good kiss.
What's up, Bri?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So how was school?
You know that test I was giving?
I had to give it again.
They all got A's.
Oh, um, Allison wants
to have a playdate
this weekend at her house.
Any B-L-A-C-K kids gonna be there?
A few. Not enough.
You know, I'm thinking of
joining a Mocha Moms group
in New Rochelle.
That'll be good.
I got to do something.
Hey, how was, um, work today?
Anything happen?
Ah, nothing much,just work.
I'm not crazy.
Would you tell your wife
about Nikki?
But I got to admit, seeing
Nikki got me to thinking.
What would it be like
to be single again?
I mean, if I were single,
I wouldn't do all that
romance-and-flowers crap.
If I were single again,
I would get right to the point.
Excuse me, would you
like to have sex with me?
- Of course I would.
- Well, come on!
When you're single,you're
never at a loss for words.
Excuse me, can I bite your ass?
For $1,000.
Come on, let's get biting, bitch!
When you're single,
you have nothing to lose.
Come with me to a hotel right now.
But I have an appointment.
Yeah, a pussy appointment.
When you're single,
you're invincible.
Excuse me...
Get the fuck out of here!
When you're single,you're alone.
I'll fuck you.
And that's why I got married.
When I went to work
the next day,
being single was
the last thing on my mind.
I had a lot to do,
there was a big client
I wanted to bring in,
and I needed to be focused.
You know what I always say,
valuation's an art not a science.
Hey, want to go to lunch?
I got a plan how we can
reel in EuroTech.
I'm gonna pass on the lunch,
but let's talk about it
when you get back.
Have fun with yourself.
Walter, listen,
I know you're in bed
with Cross and Lubitsch,
but I'm telling you right now,
you're gonna see
some things in the...
There's a Nikki Tru on line one.
Tell her to hold.
Well, I just
want you to know
that our doors are always open.
All right, take care, Walter.
Nikki.
Hey.
I got the job.
Good.
So as a thank you,
I was thinking you should
let me take you to lunch.
You know, I don't normally
do lunch till late.
Well, that's okay,
'cause I'm still in bed,
but I could get in the shower
and be to you in about an hour.
You know, I got
a lot of work to do, Nikki.
But you are gonna eat lunch, right?
So I'll be there at 2:00.
Okay?
Okay.
Good.
Bye.
Excuse me, miss, there's no smoking.
Okay, I'm putting it out.
I live on the West Side with Teddy.
He has a place here
and in D.C.,
although most of my stuff is in D.C.
So how'd you meet Teddy from D.C.?
He's a club promoter.
I met him out.
You know how it goes.
Yeah.
So do I know your wife?
I don't think so.
Is she white?
No.
Why-why would you ask that?
Don't get offended.
Remember that girl you brought
to Andre's party?
It was one girl at one party.
I- I go out with
one white girl,
all of a sudden, I'm Prince?
No, it was just a question.
I didn't mean anything by it.
So do you and your black wife
still fuck?
And what's it to you?
Mmm,just curious.
Most of the people I know
who are still married
say that after a while,
they don't fuck.
So do you love Teddy?
You didn't answer my question.
'Cause it's none
of your fucking business.
I'll take that as a no.
So, Mr. Married Man,
how did you meet
this black wife of yours?
You don't want to know.
No, I do.
Sort of.
I was...
coming from a meeting,
I was walking by the park,
and she was there
with her class,
this beautiful woman
with these kids.
I don't know-
there was just something
really calm about her.
And I was like, "I got to meet her. "
Wow.
I guess I was wrong.
You do love your wife.
I've thought about it.
Doing the whole wife thing,
having kids.
I'm getting a little old
for the club scene.
I don't even know how you do it.
Hanging out late,
- eating cheeseburgers at 4:00 in the morning.
- God...
Come on.
You used to love this shit.
You just let yourself get old.
I just let myself get bored.
This was fun.
We should do this again.
Yeah. Maybe.
Okay.
Saturday is the one day
I like to sit in my house and relax.
Unfortunately,
it's also the same day
that Brenda likes to go
into Manhattan and shop.
Brenda didn't like
living in the city,
but she sure liked
buying her clothes there.
Honey, why don't you get these?
I like them.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, well, let's
find your size
so that you can wear them.
Ah, come on, we drove
all the way to the city.
You could've got those
at the Panty Depot.
Oh, come on.
No, I like these.
- And they're comfortable, and they're cute.
- Richard?
Richard.
I thought you lived in Westchester.
- What are you doing here?
- Hey.
Nikki, Brenda.
Brenda, Nikki.
- Hi.
Nikki's an old friend.
Uh, what's it been,
like, seven, eight years?
At least.
Uh, Nikki used to date
Nelson, remember?
Yes. Yes!
Right.
And who is this handsome guy?
Oh, well, that's my Brian.
And that's Kelly.
Hi.
She's gorgeous.
Of course, like her mom.
Thank you.
Say, "thank you," Kelly.
These are great.
Where did you get these?
Is this the Heavenly Collection?
No, they're from
the Latifah Collection.
Okay.
Stop.
Um, actually,
I don't know what they are.
But I got them downstairs.
Well, I should go pay for these.
Um, it was really nice to meet you.
Yes.
And it was great
seeing you, Richard.
Oh, great to see you.
Guys.
Bye-bye.
So she's the
one that, uh,
Nelson tried to kill himself over?
Yeah, he-he was going
through a lot back then.
Huh.
Yeah, guess he was.
I'm gonna take these back.
Okay, that was a lie.
But big deal.
I mean, nothing happened.
Nikki's a friend.
An old friend.
I mean, I've known Nikki
longer than I've known Brenda.
She used to date Nelson.
We had a lot of fun together.
I mean, sh-she makes me laugh.
Th-There's nothing
wrong with that, right?
Nikki's an old friend,
a good friend.
A friend I can't tell my wife about.
Morning, Richard.
- Nikki called.
- Five minutes ago.
She said she'll be by at 6:00.
Is there something wrong?
No.
- Nothing.
- Nothing at all.
Wall sconces?
Well, they're not expensive
and we can get an electrician
to put them in.
What do you think of art deco?
Art deco's fine.
Hey.
Okay, if we go with art deco,
we might have to reupholster
the couch.
I thought we were
talking about wall sconces.
Well, they have to match, honey.
If they don't match,
then I got to change the rug.
- If I have to change the rug...
- I guess you're right.
Uh, honey, could we talk
about this later?
Yes. Look, I have to go-
it's parent-teacher night.
I fixed you a plate, so just
heat it up when you get home.
Okay. So I'll-I'll
talk to you later.
Wall sconces.
Sounds fun.
When exactly do you start
getting calls at work
about wall sconces?
Right after you get married.
I mean, before you get married,
you get calls like...
I can't wait to suck your dick.
Then, after you get married,
you get calls like...
I can't wait for you
to come home
and see these drapes.
Poor Mr. Married Man.
I hope you don't mind me
stopping by like this,
but I bought something
for your kids.
I haven't been able to stop
thinking about you guys.
Hey, you didn't have
to get me anything.
I know.
Thanks.
This stuff's expensive.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I put it on Teddy's credit card.
So now I owe Teddy some money.
So you're the expert-
what do you think?
Would I make a good wife?
Nikki, you don't want to be a wife.
Why?
You want a wedding.
You want the show.
Mm-hmm.
What are you looking at?
You have any singles?
Yeah, I should have
about seven, eight bucks.
What do you need?
Just give me all of it.
All right, I'm gonna have
to break into my stripper stash.
What are you doing?
Feeding the fish.
Come here.
Look.
Okay, who is gonna get it?
Oh, look at this guy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoo...!
Shh!
It's just a dollar.
It's just a buck.
- This is decadent.
- Try it.
All right.
All right, here we go.
Whoo!
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Yeah!
You're going to cause a riot.
Well done!
Yes!
Oh, wow!
Ooh, look at the homeless guy.
Oh, get the mon...
Oh, he needs it.
Never gonna get it.
Nope. Going too slow.
Come on, homeless guy.
You need that money.
Get it.
- Nope.
- Oh!
White man wins again.
That was fun.
That was too much fun.
You know what?
I better take my wife
out to dinner
and get the stench of fun
with another woman off of me.
I don't even want to go that way,:
you can't go down the FDR.
Oh, God, no.
- It's insane.
Okay, this is safe.
Dinner with Allan and Jennifer.
Once you get married,
you only hang out
with other married people.
Why?
'Cause no single person
could stand to be around you.
It wasn't always like this.
We all used to talk
about sex, politics, art.
But now, all we ever
talk about is our kids.
Of course, I had
to miss the end,
because I had a little
exploding diaper problem.
And when it's not our kids,
it's always the same conversation.
First, there's the rap conversation.
...hos, hos, hos
in different area codes.
I'm kind of wondering,
did anybody have a nice mama?
Was it a situation
where their mama
smacked them
upside their head,
and they said, "Bitch!"
Then there's the conversation
about theJews.
They had it just as bad as us.
Black folks need
to take care of themselves
just as well as theJews
take care of themselves.
Except we can't stick together-
that's the problem.
We're too busy buying
spinning rims and gold teeth.
You think Steven Spielberg
got spinning rims?
And no group of people
are too sophisticated to have
a conversation
about Michael Jackson.
I blameJoe.
Please, what grown-ass man
sleeps in a bed with kids?
MichaelJackson
just didn't have a childhood.
Hey, man, childhood's only
12, 15 years.
Michael's, like, 50.
How many sliding boards
does this nigga need?
You know good and well you would not
let that man babysit your kids.
I wouldn't let MichaelJackson
watch my kids on TV.
Amen.
Maybe he thought
the little boy was 18.
You can't confuse the little boy.
Give me a break.
Just yesterday, little Sharon
came into the room
singing "Magic Stick. "
I said, "Magic Stick"? Little
girl, you're four years old.
What do you know
about a magic stick?"
Can I take your drink orders?
Honey?
Uh, you know what?
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Honey, can you just
get me some water?
Think I'll take a ginger ale.
I'll have a Chardonnay.
Okay.
Excuse me, can I talk
to you for a second?
Is there a problem, sir?
Yes, there's a problem.
See, I came here
for a lovely dinner
with my wife
and some friends,
and next thing I know
is I got these big tits
asking me if I want a drink.
Do you mean your waitperson?
Listen, man, I'm with my wife.
I don't need this shit.
I don't need some girl, with
her big-ass village feeders,
asking me if I need some help.
Is this Hooters?
No, sir.
- Is it Hooters?
- No, sir.
I know this ain't Hooters,
'cause-'cause if it is,
you owe me some
fucking buffalo wings.
Sir, what can I do to make this better?
See that guy right there?
Yes, I do.
That's my waiter.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
You okay?
So he just got up
and said, "It's over"?
No, you don't understand.
If we're fucking and I
fall asleep, that's fine.
If we're fucking
and we both fall asleep,
that's okay, too,
but if we're fucking
and you fall asleep,
it's-it's fucked up!
He didn't say it's over,
but I know it's over.
You-you got to excuse her;
she's upset.
The fuck are you looking at?!
Our stop's coming up.
When Nikki came by to see me in the afternoon,
it wasn't really a big deal.
But when we walked through
the office at 9:00 a. m...
Good morning.
...people looked at me
like I was crazy.
I mean crazy.
It's like we've been
breaking up for months,
and I'm just finding out
about it now.
Well, that's how relationships are.
You add how long
you been together,
and then you divide it by two,
and that's how long
you been breaking up.
So if you get a divorce
after 20 years,
you been breaking up for ten.
That's right.
So can I stay with you
for a couple days?
Nikki, my wife...
Oh...
I'm just playing with you.
You should see the look
on your face right now.
Okay, I'm not trying to get rid
of you, Nikki, but I really...
iPod.
You got some nigga ears.
Nigga what?
Some old-ass nigga ears.
Look at this, Levert, Patti
LaBelle, Luther Vandross.
You know, white people
make music, too.
I got George Michael.
Doesn't count.
Okay, I'm gonna
give you my iPod,
and you are gonna give me yours.
Okay.
When you get a chance,
I want you to listen to that song.
Can I get back to work now?
# Fuck the cracker,
that's what I say #
#And fuck these bitches
that always want to play #
# I'm the type of nigga
that's never gay #
# If you fuck with me, I'll
put your head in cake... #
I think he might be off the phone.
Richard.
That girl is here to see you.
Well,just send her in.
Richard...
...can I ask you something?
Hi.
It can wait.
I don't think your
secretaries like me.
Hey, they don't like me, either.
You know, if you keep
showing up like this,
we're gonna have
to get you a job here.
People are gonna start talking.
Oh, let them talk.
I need you to do me a favor.
Can you come uptown with
me to look at a place?
You know, I-I got
a lot of work to do.
I got to get
out ofTeddy's,
and... he's supposed
to be out of town.
I'd like to be out by
the time he gets back.
Are you okay?
Can you come with me?
Yeah, yeah.
- Let me just check.
- Okay.
Tracy, what's my rest
of the day look like?
You and George have a
conference call at 3:00.
Damn. George!
Yeah?
You need me for that call at 3:00?
I do. Why?
I got to do something.
I mean, I-I should be back,
but if I'm not,
you can handle it, right?
Yeah, I got it, don't worry.
Hi, I'm George.
- Nikki.
- Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
So, I'll see you later?
You tell me.
You sure this is what you want?
It's what I can afford.
So, where do you work?
I'm a hostess at a place downtown
called The White Bar.
Oh, that's nice.
Well, here you go.
Washer and dryer
on the third floor,
pay phone on the second floor.
Don't knock on my door for change.
Get your own damn quarters.
Um, there was something
in the ad about cable.
I got jumper cables,
if you need 'em.
Okay.
And don't blame me
if the bed's
not big enough for both of you.
This place is really for students.
Oh, we are not a couple.
Yeah, yeah, I-I'm just a friend.
Oh.
I guess that's a Super Bowl
ring, huh?
You a Jet or a Packer?
Uh-huh.
Which one of you friends
is paying the rent?
I am.
Sure you are, baby.
I never thought I'd be
back in one of these.
This is where everybody ends up.
WOMAN... a wooden Barton hutch
made of pine in Al's backyard.
This is a project an experienced
do-it-yourselfer could tackle,
since this shed is pre-cut
and ready to assemble.
- Hey, fellas.
Hi!
- How are you guys?
- Very well, thanks.
That doesn't look so hard;
we can do that out back.
I'm getting splinters
just watching this.
I got to hand it to you-
you knocked it out the park.
It looks like EuroTech
may come aboard.
Hey, it's not a done deal,
and when it gets done,
I couldn't have done it without you.
What do you say we go grab
some lunch and celebrate?
I- I'd love to... but
I got other plans.
Hey, guys. You ready?
Can I talk to you for a second?
Yeah, sure.
Inside.
- Be right back.
- Okay.
I'm sorry. I won't keep him long.
No problem.
Okay, what is it?
Are you aware of what
you're getting yourself into?
What are you talking about?
Nikki- she's here every day.
George, she's just a friend.
A friend? Come on.
I've had friends before- they
don't fucking look like Nikki.
Look, you got a good situation
at home, you got two kids...
I'm not fucking her.
No, she's fucking you;
you just don't know it.
I can't believe I'm hearing this shit from you,
of all people.
You cheat on your wife all the time.
Last year, you were
fucking Tracy and Mary.
I didn't say shit to you.
That's different.
I don't give a fuck.
I can fuck a girl, go home,
kiss my wife good night
and sleep like a baby.
You, on the other hand,
got emotions.
You're like Captain
Save-A-Ho, all right?
You like to be needed,
and that bitch knows it.
Are we done?
I'm not getting
in your shit, all right?
I just...
Be careful, okay?
Hey.
What's wrong?
You look upset.
We can't do this anymore.
Do what?
What are you talking about?
This whole... lunch in
the afternoon thing.
It doesn't look good;
we really should stop.
We're not doing anything.
It's not like we're fucking.
It is like
we're fucking,
only thing, we're
not fucking,
and I feel all the guilt
as if I'm fucking you
without any of the pleasure
of actually fucking you.
I don't want things to
get any more complicated.
I'm not trying
to complicate anything.
I like you, Richard.
I don't like a lot of people.
I like you 'cause you're safe.
You don't want anything from me.
Okay?
Okay.
So, you want to get
something to eat?
No.
I have something else planned.
Wow.
I've been thinking
about coming here.
I knew you'd like it.
You should have one of these.
Wanted one of these
since I was a kid.
That I don't know.
What I know is that
I'm gonna get me
a little Porsche one day.
You're going down!
I'm going down, all right.
- Oh!
- Yeah, yeah.
You dirty, dirty...!
What is that?!
Richard!
Richard, Brian's asleep ups...!
What is that?
You-You don't like it?
No, no, I don't.
And you're making the kids deaf.
Ah, come on, it's not that loud.
Yes, it is.
And you know what?
I was in my car
the other day, and...
Where did my CDs go?
Wh-Where's my,
where's my Peabo Bryson?
Where's my Usher?
Where's my Beyonc?
You know, you really got some nigga ears, honey.
Nigga ears?
How many times do I
have to ask you
not to talk in front
of the kids like that?
You know what?
You just keep doing
what you're doing.
'Cause one of these days,
they won't be asking
where my daddy is,
they'll be asking,
"Where's my nigga?"
Then what are you gonna do?
You know, I tried
calling you yesterday,
and no one could find you.
Was probably at lunch.
No, it was almost 4:00.
Aren't you usually back by then?
I mean, I tried
calling you on your cell,
I tried texting you,
you didn't text me back.
What did you want?
What difference
does it make
what I wanted?
That was yesterday.
You have to tell people
where you are.
What if something
happened to the kids?
What if I got hit by a car?
Ah, come on, why do you always
have to take it to,
"What if I got hit by a car?"
I- I went to the deli,
I wanted a chicken salad sandwich.
I- I stood on line.
Uh, when I got to
the front of the line,
I realized I didn't
have a ticket,
so I had to get back on the line.
That's it.
You make it sound like an alibi.
All you have to do
is answer the phone.
I didn't hear it.
All right.
Tomorrow.
Have you thought
about what you want to do?
Do you want to see a movie?
Do you want to have brunch
with Jennifer and Allan?
Nah, nah, nah, we do
that all the time.
Let's try something different.
Different?
Okay.
Honey, let's go look
at the new Porsches.
Wh... Why?
No. No, no, no, no.
In here, it says that
there's something over there
that you're really gonna like.
Oh, yeah. Come on.
Let's go.
Bye-bye.
Come on, baby.
Going to the car show
and looking at the minivans
was like going to a strip club
and looking at the DJ.
Mr. Cooper,
what sectors have the most
growth potential for our company?
Well, Mr. Yuni, what
we're finding now
is that most advertising dollars
are migrating online.
Is that you?
It's me.
- I probably should, uh...
- Mm-hmm.
Richard, I have an emergency.
I need to ask you something,
but I'm afraid
you're gonna get mad at me.
I have to take this.
Um, if you'll
excuse me,
I'll be, I'll be right back.
H- Hey, what's up?
I can't really talk right now;
I'm in a meeting.
Okay, really quick.
Just promise you won't
get mad at me.
I won't get mad.
You didn't promise.
Okay, I promise.
Will you come with me to get my
stuff out ofTeddy's apartment?
Didn't you hear me tell you
I'm in a meeting?
Not today,
tomorrow.
Fine.
Okay? I got to go now.
Have a good meeting.
Oh, and what were your plans?
Three kids?
Yeah, could be better.
Small family emergency.
It's under control.
All right, so where's this guy live?
'Cause I got things to do.
Shuttle's in, like, 45 minutes.
Shuttle?
Wh-What are you
talking about, shuttle?
To D.C.
Remember I told you,
we have a place there,
and he's out of town, so
now I can get my shit.
I'm not going with you to D.C.
You promised.
I didn't promise to go
with you to another state.
It's not a state, it's a district.
It's, like, a 30-minute flight.
You must be
out of your fucking mind
if you think I'm getting
on a plane to Washington D.C.
to go to some guy's house
to get your shit!
Richard?
Richard, yeah.
Uh, I have one question for you:
Where the fuck are you?
No, no, no, don't worry.
I'll be there.
Yeah, something just came up.
Look,just get here, okay?
I told you I need you on this one.
Tell Mary that
if Nikki calls,
I'll call her tomorrow.
Tell her yourself when you get here.
You're a good liar.
Listen, we're getting
on the 1:00 shuttle,
not a moment later, okay?
'Cause I got a meeting at 3:00.
Okay.
Right here.
- Here?
- Uh-huh.
What are all these cops doing here?
Oh, it's kind of
a crazy neighborhood.
Something's always going down.
- We'll be right back.
- Okay.
So how many cities
have you lived in
- with this Teddy guy?
- Hey, police! Open up in there!
- Uh, here, and New York.
- Open up in there!
In Miami, I lived with his brother.
That's where I met him.
Wait a minute,
you lived with a guy,
then you left him for his brother?
How'd you pull that off?
I got a hard enough time
telling my wife I want pancakes.
We're in.
All right,
now that we're in,
I want you to
get your shit
and let's get out of here.
I'm just gonna grab
a few dresses, some shoes,
and then we'll go.
Okay.
Thank you.
Forget "Thank you,"just hurry up.
Teddy's doing pretty good.
Mm-hmm.
You were on the math team
in high school?
For two years. Why?
I don't know.
Just can't imagine you
solving a problem.
My Ferretti sweater.
I had no idea where this was.
Richard Cooper's office.
Hi, Brenda.
Hey, somebody
around here's
got some nigga ears.
Excuse me?
Biz Markie's Greatest Hits.
That man is a genius.
The genius that wrote
"Pickin' Boogers. "
"Pickin' Boogers," "The Vapors"
and of course, my favorite...
#You #
#You got what I need #
# But you say he's just a friend #
# But you say
he's just a friend #
# Oh, baby, you #
#You got what I need. #
Okay, Teddy, calm down.
You know you got two strikes.
There's cops all over the place.
How the fuck y'all get in here, man?
Huh?
Who the fuck are you?
What, this the new nigga?
You fucking him now? Huh?
You the new nigga, man?
No, no, I'm-I'm not the new nigga.
I've n-never been the nigga,
I'm just a... friend.
How's it going?
Richard Cooper.
Oh!
- Teddy!
- Motherfucker!
Teddy, what the fuck's
wrong with you?!
- You bring this stupid-ass nigga
- Stop it!
- in my fucking crib?!
- Teddy!
Help!
- Fuck you!
- Somebody help!
- Take the boot! Take the boot!
- Somebody help us!
Take the motherfucking boot!
Hi, Mr. Landis, it's Tracy.
You like the taste, huh?!
You like the taste?!
- Everybody freeze!
- You like the fucking taste?!
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org