I'm really gonna miss you, you know that?
- Sam, it's just a couple of weeks.
Which is gonna seem like an eternity.
- An eternity, and then some.
That's better, you bloody Englishman.
- Say it again.
Say what?
- I love hearing...
you use English swear words. Say "bloody".
- Hm, bloody.
Now, say "bugger".
- Bugger. You bugger,
you bloody bugger.
- That's the one.
Crap! I have to get dressed, run through
my notes, rehearse my presentation.
Have a nervous breakdown,
ignore your half-naked girlfriend.
Give me two seconds. Stay right there,
and don't move your cute British butt.
Don't tell me, there's a gift.
There's always a gift.
It makes me feel very guilty.
- Well, that is the general idea.
I have a present, too. I'll give it
to you later. It's a surprise.
Great. I love surprises.
Wow. It's perfect.
- I know.
Vintage, Portobello Road. It was only
ten pounds. And it does come with this.
Nice lining. Silk.
What?
- I have to get ready.
This meeting is very important. If it
goes well, you know what that could mean.
Ian...
- Sam.
Please. Have mercy.
- You know, that's what I was thinking...
that after you close the deal
and knock them dead...
it would be a perfect time to step back,
relax, and go to Ohio.
Sam.
- I want you...
to go to my mom's wedding with me.
You can meet everyone.
You're not coming?
- I tried to free things up,
but, you know...
you know how hectic work's been.
I'm really sorry.
That's okay.
I really am sorry to let you down
about Indiana. - Ohio.
Bugger! I'm sorry. Again.
I'm just going to have to meet your mom...
at the next wedding.
- What wedding?
Ours. Next year.
- Me? Marry you? A guy who confuses...
the Buckeye state with the Hoosier state?
I don't think so.
I'm gonna take a shower now.
- Be my guest.
London Bridge is falling down,
my fair lady.
Sam?
- London Bridge is falling down...
Sam!
- ... my fair lady.
I am cool.
Ready for breakfast? Bon appétit.
Hey, I don't care how big this meeting is.
- Sorry, there's no time.
Oh! Oh...
- Ow, I'm such a klutz.
Show me.
Better?
- Much.
Good.
One day
accessing one's genetic make-up...
will be as easy as running a credit check.
That knowledge gives us the power...
to alter our destiny.
- Alter destiny? You believe that?
Of course I do. In the next 50 years...
- People are still going to die.
It'll still rain right after you
wash your car, and the Stones...
will still be touring.
That stuff's out of your control.
All you can control are your own choices.
Ok. That would be the other point of view.
But I really don't have time...
to debate destiny.
I'm just practicing my speech. Oh.
Dinner tonight, Tantra, seven o'clock.
- Tonight, seven o'clock?
You're kidding, right?
- Kidding? Not that I'm aware of.
My concert. The one I've been preparing
for three years.
ring a bell?
- Yeah. Your graduation concert.
I didn't forget that. That's...
- Tonight. Seven o'clock.
I'm an ass.
I'm so sorry, Sam.
I can't believe I did that.
Good luck. In your meeting. Not that you
need it. You're gonna be great.
I'm sorry.
You've gotta be kidding me. Uh!
Oh, no... the stupid jerk.
You know, don't be late.
I'll take care of this. I'll see you...
tonight at the concert.
- Concert? What concert?
I was kidding. Because it turns out
I forgot the thing and...
This must be that British sense of humor
I keep hearing so much about.
Ok. Well. I'll see you tonight.
Gentlemen, we at AGS are not only
at the forefront of biotech...
Not the forefront, the vanguard!
Bollocks!
I cracked it this morning.
But it says eleven o'clock.
- Well, the hands must have moved.
At least it'll be right twice a day.
- Do me a favor?
Call Tantra, push my reservation to nine.
Have someone dash over to Harvey Nicks.
I need a present for Samantha...
- For Samantha's graduation concert.
How did you remember that?
- Not sure. Could be because she told me,
she sent you an invitation,
which is on your desk.
We programmed the date into your...
- Ok. Got it. Got it. Thank you.
Anyway, I promised her a surprise.
So, how about a sweater?
Something cashmere. Red.
- She's already got one.
A red cashmere sweater. She was wearing it
last time she was here. She went on and on
about how much she loved it.
- Really? Where was I?
right next to her.
You have no idea...
what I feel inside.
Hold me, babe...
Sorry to make you pick me up
all the way over here. Pick up.
Cute hair. Shit. Voicemail.
Hi. Um, I just found your blue folder.
The one with all the notes in it.
I'm on the way to the hotel, right now.
Sorry. Sorry.
Ladies, Gentlemen,
today we are given an opportunity...
to help mankind.
Excuse me. Sir?
Hi, could you please take this folder
into the conference room for me?
My... Mr Wyndham's expecting it.
- I'm sorry, Miss,
but that's against hotel policy.
- But he could lose his job.
Oh, that's tragic.
But, alas, not my problem.
God. Even when you guys are nasty,
it sounds polite.
Now, in terms of your investments...
- Shit. Briefcase is open. I've to go in.
Excuse me for interrupting, Mr Wyndham.
This is for you.
I just thought that you might need...
the exact same folder...
you already have. I see. Ok. Well.
False alarm. Terribly sorry.
I just thought... I just wanted...
to make sure you...
he had everything he needed.
Because he worked so hard on it.
I mean, really...
dedicated, and he deserves for this
to all go perfectly.
Not like this.
This is my fault. Me.
So, anyway, really nice
to meet all of you.
You were right.
They really are a serious-looking bunch.
In in a good way.
So, in conclusion Ian's good.
Give him the money. See you later.
So, shall we move on?
I forgot my purse.
He already had the folder. Take this.
I never want to see it again.
I think that went well.
- Did it?
Yeah, the glaring, the awkwardness,
the cold stare from Ian.
Just what I was hoping for.
I think I talked too much.
You? Come on, let's go to work.
There's a guy there who loves...
your delightfully impulsive nature.
I can't do it. I'm bad.
- No, come here.
You are not bad. Do you know why?
Because if you were bad
that would mean I was a bad teacher.
In fact, I am a fabulous teacher, right?
Hence, you couldn't...
possibly be bad.
- You've got a point.
Come on. Let's all play together.
You ready?
1 , 2, 3.
Did you land the money then?
- I had them in the palm of my hand.
I can't believe Samantha pulled that stunt
right after she spent all morning...
being peeved at me for "not being
in the moment" or some such bollocks.
All birds are like that.
- Yeah, especially the Yanks.
Oprah.
- Oh, right.
You're up, guys.
- Excuse me, Miss.
I couldn't help, but notice that you
work here. I was just wondering...
what time you knock off?
- Oh, just piss off, will you?
Oh, shit. Sorry, mate.
- That's all right, Mate. Sorry.
I should be heading off anyway.
Samantha. right. See you later, boys.
- Bye, Romeo.
I think she liked you.
- Definitely liked you, mate.
I just need an objective person
to tell me if the surrealist nudes...
should go on the east wall or if I
should put the phallus sculptures there.
They look pretty amazing
when the sun hits them.
I bet they do. Is that Ian?
What's he doing?
The surprise.
Clifton Hall, please.
That's a music school, isn't it?
- There's a concert there tonight.
Your girlfriend's a musician?
- That's right.
And you're having problems
with your love life?
How in the world did you know that?
- Taxi drivers are second...
only to barmen
in knowing the problems of the heart.
So, what's the trouble?
I don't want to talk about it.
- That's a good idea.
The thing'll probably just fix itself.
I can't seem to make her happy.
How can you love someone so much...
and not know... how to love 'em?
So you do love her?
- Yes. Very much.
Well, that's all that matters.
- She's going away tomorrow for two weeks.
And she wants me to go with her.
- What if she never came back?
What sort of a question is that?
- Well, go on, picture it.
You wave goodbye at the airport, she gets
on an airplane, you never see her again.
Could you live with that?
No.
No. I couldn't.
Well, you know what to do.
Appreciate her.
And what you have.
Just love her.
It's not for another two blocks.
- You can't show up empty-handed.
If Ian bought a ticket, if he's going
home with me, it's really sweet.
Maybe he's coming around.
- I hope so. You deserve it.
And if Ian doesn't know that,
he's nothing but a fuckwit.
Oh, you always know exactly what to say.
- Now remember, you are the bee's knees.
It's a good thing.
Have a great time tonight.
- Thank you. Bye.
Next, Melvina Walters will sing
Juliet's Waltz by Gounod.
Hey. Thanks.
You ready?
- Yeah. I'll see you later.
You two have a great trip.
Oh, hey, Oliver. Oh, you made it! Hi!
Are you kidding?
He wouldn't have missed it for the world.
She was the best one. I love Miss Andrews.
Everyone does.
If I was just a few years older...
Oh, you little...
This is for you.
- Oh, well... Thank you.
Ian, is this not the cutest card?
- Yeah.
Yeah. We should go.
- Well, I...
That's okay. We need to go, too.
It was a disaster. Dunbar passed.
Trahern is pissed, and I'm screwed.
- God, Ian, I'm so sorry.
Forget it.
So... what else is going on?
Lottie has an exhibit tomorrow.
Some big shot gallery, The Zinc.
I went down there to help her.
- Sounds like fun.
Wanna dance?
When have you ever seen me dance?
- So, where'd you go this afternoon,
after your meeting?
I called your cell like a zillion times.
I turned it off. I didn't want to hear
from anyone. I spent the rest of the day
walking around the city, thinking.
- About?
About us,
and whether we were going to make it.
No, I didn't mean that.
You don't understand.
You have to admit our morning was not
the greatest, and the meeting was...
Well, I was wondering what to do,
and then I met this cab driver,
and we talked.
Cab driver? You talked to...
- It was good. He made me realize...
that even though you and I have problems,
we share a lot, too.
We enjoy each other,
and I should appreciate that.
Because underneath everything,
and despite this awful day,
I adore you.
I guess what I'm saying is, I...
I want to soldier on. I really do.
Ok?
No.
- No, what?
I don't wanna "soldier on".
Ian, if I were to stay in London now,
it would only be for you. For us.
And I would do that
in a heartbeat if I thought...
that we were really special.
- We are.
Really? You never tell me how you feel,
or talk about yourself.
You don't want to meet my family.
You forgot my graduation.
We ran into my favorite student,
and you act as if he...
has something contagious. Ian,
I know you have the best intentions...
but I just feel
like I'm a very high second priority...
for you.
That hurts.
And the worst part is,
I'm starting to get used to it.
I don't understand.
- I know.
That's what kills me.
If there had been just one day, Ian.
One day where nothing else mattered,
but us.
- I adore you.
I don't want to be adored.
I want to be loved.
Where are you going?
- To spend the night at Lottie's,
to the airport tomorrow, and then...
I can't do this anymore.
I saw you at the travel agency today.
Where are you going?
- Johannesburg. Business.
Samantha! Samantha, wait!
Please! Will you, please?
You can't do this to me.
You can't leave me.
What are you saying?
That I'll never see you again?
In or out, my friend?
It's your choice.
Samantha!
No, Samantha!
I'm so sorry.
I wanted to be with her.
I really did.
How can this have happened?
How can she be gone?
I've been working on this song about me
& Ian. I want to give it to him...
before I go away,
but I'm afraid I'll scare him,
so I bought him a jacket instead.
They say there's always someone...
in a relationship who loves more.
Oh God, I wish it wasn't me.
Read one word and I'll kill you.
I was just kidding.
- You, you, you're, you're here?
Yes, and you're scaring me.
- I...
I... I...
- You...
I...
Ok. I'm gonna approach you.
And now I'm going to hug you.
It's ok. Everything's gonna be ok.
I'm really going to miss you.
- Me, too. I really will miss you, Sam.
I hope you know that.
It's important that you believe me.
I believe you. And I'd hate for you
to go through so much pain.
So, instead of missing me,
why don't you come with me to Ohio?
Samantha.
- You're definitely not coming.
I can't.
- Of course you can't. Work, I know.
Big meeting.
- My meeting. I had a meeting.
And you, you...
- Ok, Ian, calm down.
Calm down.
Look, you're very prepared for today.
And you're gonna be great.
Don't go anywhere. What are you doing?
- Sit. Don't move your cute...
British butt. Don't look.
- There's a gift.
There's a gift.
- This can't be happening.
It can. I like buying things for you.
And I wanted to say goodbye properly.
Portobello Road. Ten pounds. Plus...
Look at this.
Oh, my God!
- Ok.
Not the reaction I was looking for.
- I'm sorry. I've just...
I had a terrible nightmare,
and I can't seem, um...
I can't seem to, to get rid of it.
I...
and you...
We...
- We...
... should eat?
Yes. Yes.
We should have breakfast.
Let's have breakfast. Together.
Ok.
Oh, I am the coolest.
Samantha? Samantha...
Watch out, the coffee pot!
I see it,
crazy Yelling Man.
I... I know. I just...
You might hurt yourself.
Sam?
Oh, I'm sorry. Am I too loud?
- No. I was actually hoping...
that you'd sing.
- Oh, you need to get out more.
You are a great songwriter.
And you need...
to let people see that.
It's an amazing gift.
You're biased.
- That's true.
Oh. Ow! God... I am such a klutz.
You burned yourself on the hand.
- Keen powers of observation.
Ow... Ow!
Ian, what's wrong with you? I burn myself
with that damn thing every other day.
You do?
- Yes, I do.
What are you doing?
- We always go that way.
And do you know why?
- Why?
Because that's where you work
and I teach.
Let's try a new way.
Loop around. It might be fun!
I like this route better, don't you?
Whoa!
Care to explain?
- Yeah, I just thought...
the scooter seemed a little... speedy.
Watch where you're going!
- You've gotta be kidding me.
It wasn't a dream.
- What?
All these things that are happening today.
I already knew they would happen.
What do you mean?
- The leather jacket. The burn.
The Coca Cola spilled on your sweater.
I... already saw or dreamt those things.
Some happened a little differently, but...
- Ok, calm down. You know, sometimes...
I've had déjà vu, and it...
- But it's not déjà vu. In a déjà vu,
it feels like it's already happened.
You don't know what's gonna happen.
What happened in the dream
that freaked you out so badly?
It was...
It was awful.
- Ok.
Let's be logical about this.
In your dream or vision,
or whatever, what happens next?
You go back to the apartment
to wash your sweater,
and I go to my meeting.
- That is awful.
Oh, on the way to my meeting
my watch cracks.
Ok. So here's what we're gonna do.
We will walk to your office together.
And if your watch cracks,
we'll know that something is going on,
and we'll deal with it. Ok?
Almost there.
We're holding hands.
I like holding hands.
Me, too.
- Oh!
Do you have the time?
Sorry. Watch. Sore subject.
It's fine.
- You're just nervous.
You're right. I'm sure you're right.
- So, you ok?
You ready for the meeting?
- Yes.
Good luck. Not that you need it.
You're gonna be great.
I'll see you tonight at the concert.
- Concert? What concert?
I was kidding.
That was me kidding.
You know, the British sense of...
Never mind.
Bye.
- Yeah, see ya tonight.
Do me a favor. Call Tantra,
and push my reservation to nine.
And I need a present for...
- For Samantha's graduation concert?
You forgot.
I reminded you twice.
Yes, no, I don't know
if I did or didn't forget.
I forgot yesterday,
but I don't think I forgot today.
Did you wear that yesterday?
- Quite possibly.
On the pittance you pay me,
I've only got a few things.
Claire, can I ask you a question?
- If you must.
Did you ever have a dream and the next day
everything feels familiar,
like it's from the dream?
- Yes. I have.
For example, last night I dreamt that you
would bore me to death first thing...
this morning, and lo and behold...
- Come on. Seriously.
Seriously?
- Yes.
Ian, I believe
dreams are very important.
They should be listened to.
- You really think so?
Yes.
And I also believe that you should
get your ass over to that meeting,
or you'll be sacked,
and I'll be on the dole.
And those are AGS's main objectives.
To design new ways to treat, cure,
or prevent the countless illnesses...
that inflict humankind.
I'm happy and more than a little proud
to report that AGS...
is way ahead
of the competition in this area.
Now.
In terms of your investments...
These 7-year projections will document
everything we've discussed so far.
We've amortized the cost of the research
over a 10-year period. And...
I knew it!
I knew you'd be here!
Ok. You've heard my pitch,
and I can tell by the unbridled excitement
on your faces...
Oh, come on, guys.
Settle down. This is not a party.
This research isn't about perfect
projections or amortized costs,
or about beating the competition.
It's about giving people...
the most precious gift possible: time.
This is a great opportunity,
and I say grab it.
What do you think?
Did you land the money?
- I did.
It was strange because the other time
when Samantha walked into the meeting,
I thought she messed everything up.
Oh, I didn't tell you guys...
about the dream I had. Of course not,
because that would be tonight.
Ok, then. Tell us about the dream.
- It's more of a déjà vu.
Ah, déjà vu. It's sometimes dismissed
as a random neurological event,
but is often a message from deep
within the soul. And when the soul...
comes tapping at the door,
it's time to let her in.
Oprah.
- No,
Dr Phil.
- You're up, guys.
No, no. That's not what I'm talking about.
There are certain things...
that I know are going to happen.
- Excuse me?
But haven't we met before?
In my dreams.
Oh, just piss off, will you?
- You see? I knew that would happen.
Ian, we all knew that was gonna happen.
Can you remember anything useful?
Like the 3:30 winner at Newmarket?
No, I'm afraid not.
But everything is the same.
It's just in a slightly different order.
Slightly different order.
I... I've gotta go.
Mackenzie Street, please.
- Yes, sir.
You've got to be kidding me.
- Excuse me, sir?
You're the driver from yesterday.
- Anything's possible.
Yesterday you knew certain things
about me. - About your love life?
Yes.
- People in my profession are second only
to barmen in knowing about problems
of the heart. - You said that exactly.
So if you're the same,
if this cab ride is the same...
then everything else today will be
the same. At the end of the day,
my girlfriend gets into this taxi...
It stops at a light,
it's hit, and she...
Is that gonna happen?
Is it?
What if she doesn't get in the cab?
What if I take her out of London?
Maybe if we stay in the apartment.
Tell me, what can I do?
There must be something I can do!
Just one thing. Appreciate her.
And what you have.
Just love her.
Let me out right now!
- Certainly, sir.
No, that's alright, sir.
Why not?
- You paid me yesterday.
Better hurry up.
You haven't got much time.
Samantha Andrews, where is she?
- I have no idea. Are you alright?
Oliver?
There's three next door, as well.
Samantha!
I'm sorry.
Sam! Sam?
Lottie!
Oh, come on.
Can I help you?
- Hi. I know you don't know me.
I'm a friend of Lottie's.
This will sound really strange,
but I need to get into her apartment.
- Never seen you around before.
Actually, I'm her best friend's boyfriend.
Do you know Samantha Andrews?
Of course. I love Miss Andrews.
Everyone does.
If I was just a few years younger...
Zinc!
Hey, can we eat at some point?
- Don't be such a big girl's blouse.
A wimp. A wuss. Cry-baby.
Samantha, thank God, I found you.
- What are you doing here?
I've to get Samantha out of here at once.
- What is with you today?
You have to trust me.
Things are happening from yesterday.
Ok, we already went through this.
- I know, and maybe you're right.
Maybe it's stress. But all I know is
that we have to leave London. Immediately!
I promised Lottie.
- You've helped loads.
You're right. The fallacies
will look great in the garden.
Ian, I have my concert tonight. Remember?
- I'll have you back in time. I swear.
Come on, let's go. I have to get you
out of London now. Just trust me on this.
Ok, let's go.
- Now, will you tell me where we're going?
You said anywhere I want to.
So stop asking. Just enjoy not knowing...
what's gonna happen.
Hang on a minute.
- What do you think? If you don't want...
to stop here, we can just keep going.
- How did you know that this was my...
You told me where you were from.
I've never met your family.
They've been busy.
- I really want to see...
where you grew up. I want to see
where little Ian went to school...
and played soccer.
Sorry, football, American.
I want to see
where you became the man I love.
If you've something to hide, you shouldn't
have said, "Anywhere you want to".
Was that thunder? I think I heard thunder.
It's gonna pour. I mean, you do know...
that it's raining, right?
- You're just trying to get out of this.
This was a lot steeper when I was a kid.
They must have come in here...
with heavy machinery and flattened it out.
- Yeah, unless you've changed.
Me? Not possible.
- Hey, are we going to that shack?
No. We need to get to the top.
- Yes, chief. So what's at the top of...
"Ian's Magical Hill"?
- Nothing, really.
Except the solitude.
Being away from everything.
I'd go up there to read or think.
I felt safe there, at peace.
It's definitely gonna pour.
Pouring rain in England? Not likely.
- Come on.
No wonder you never took me home
to meet your family.
They have a very small house.
Hey, why didn't you tell me about 'em?
I'm always yapping about my friends
and family, but you never...
talk about yours.
- Sam, let's just forget about everything.
You know, I just want to...
I just wanna be here. With you.
You really don't want to talk
about your past, do you?
Ian?
- The past doesn't matter.
What matters is now. Only now.
You really are acting funny today.
Keep it up, ok?
Can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
If for some reason you thought
you didn't have a lot of time left...
You mean today?
No, I...
I mean in life.
If you had one day left.
What would you do?
That's an odd question.
- I'd just like to know.
Well, let's see... my last day on Earth.
Shoe shopping.
And eating ten hot fudge sundaes.
And there's that Calvin Klein
underwear model. Might be fun...
to get to know him better.
It's an easy answer. A no-brainer.
I'd spend it with you.
- Really?
Yeah. Of course.
Just being together.
Kind of like now. Doing nothing.
And that's it? I mean...
nothing else?
A closeness.
An intense closeness.
Really sharing things with each other.
Silly things.
Difficult things.
That's what I've always wanted for us,
and if we could have that,
nothing could hurt us.
I love you.
Good.
The rain's letting up.
Do you want to go to the top of your hill?
No.
I want to take you somewhere else.
Do I have to climb?
Maybe we should wait another minute.
Good idea.
Your dad was a very handsome guy.
So I guess you took...
after your mom, right?
He spent a lot of time here?
- Yeah, he did.
After he got laid off in '93.
Here all the time.
When I was a kid, my dad was my hero.
I thought he was the strongest man...
in the world. He was so proud.
His job at the factory
wasn't just any job to him, you know?
Everyone loved him, though.
And his family, well,
we all worshiped him.
- He sounds wonderful.
He is.
Well, he was.
Then the owner decided to relocate,
and they all lost their jobs.
He never found another.
This became his second home.
>From the age of 15 on,
I don't think I ever saw him sober.
And I've been determined
not to let that happen to me.
To live my life at the whim of others.
You don't have to.
- I know. I know that now.
I just wish I could have helped him.
- You were only a kid.
I know. But to watch your father,
your hero, just dissolve...
right before your eyes...
You really loved your dad.
Yeah.
I hope he knew how much.
Wherever he is,
I bet he knows how you feel.
Ian, death doesn't put an end to love.
You think so?
I know it.
Why didn't you ever tell me
any of this?
I guess...
I guess I just...
I just didn't want to feel...
any of it.
I'm so glad we're here.
Me, too.
I kind of wish we didn't have to go.
- Go where?
Back to London. My graduation concert.
- Let's not go back.
Let's just get on a train
and ride off somewhere.
Let's see.
I've been playing violin for 16 years.
I've been studying for 3 years.
I'm about to graduate from one of...
the finest music schools in London.
I think we should go home.
You coming?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
- Just a small surprise.
Something you're gonna love.
- Ok.
I don't think there's enough time.
- Don't be silly.
You said you've always wanted to do this.
- Yeah, and you know why I haven't?
Because I'm scared of heights.
- Baby, there's nothing to be afraid of.
I'll be with you.
- The doors.
Ah, it's beautiful.
Still scared?
Oh, that's weird. I guess I forgot.
Hey, I'm sorry for being
such a big girl's blouse.
What?
- Where did you get that from?
Lottie. Did I use it right?
- Yeah, it couldn't have been better.
Thank you.
- What for?
The perfect day.
I think I'll wear this to dinner.
You're going to love the singing tonight.
Oh, is it that opera business
that I'm so fond of?
I'd rather stay here and listen
to you sing. - Be serious.
I am. I don't understand
why you don't let people hear your songs.
What are you afraid of?
Success or failure?
Yes.
- Sam.
I will sing them. I will.
- When?
One day. Someday.
Have you seen my keys?
Keys. I just had 'em.
Oh, it's alright. I've got 'em.
I've gotta run by the office.
What? The office? Now?
Yeah, I wasn't there all afternoon.
The place could just crumble without me.
It'll just take a second.
- See ya there.
Yeah.
Hi, I need 75 copies,
and I'll be back in a couple of minutes.
One day... Someday is here!
Ladies and gentlemen, that was
to have been the last performance...
but we have a very special treat
for you.
Samantha Andrews, a visiting artist
from America has agreed to grace us
with one of her own compositions.
Samantha.
You don't want to let down
your future fans.
You are in big trouble.
Whoo!
I can't believe you did that!
I mean, what an amazing feeling.
Do you have any idea how terrified I was?
- You didn't show it. You were great.
In the beginning, I couldn't even breathe,
and then this, this calm came over me.
My God, what an amazing feeling.
- You were so incredible.
You're biased.
- Guilty as charged.
Hey, I'm starved. Where are we gonna eat?
- Anywhere you want to.
Ok.
You like this place?
I thought you'd hate it. Cozy, intimate...
It's exactly my style.
You looked really cute today
in your meeting.
I mean strong and manly.
What are you saying?
- You, strong...
like bull.
- But you didn't come to work today.
I mean, I didn't see you.
- I came to bring you the blue folder,
but you already had it,
so I slipped away.
You did look really cute, by the way.
Close your eyes.
Happy graduation.
- Oh my God...
Some of the charms are old,
and some are new.
That's a musical note. A violin.
This one's a flower.
But there's no sense in that at all,
except it was exquisite, like you.
Let's see.
The train that we took today.
That's the Eiffel Tower
that you've always wanted to see.
And there's a frying pan.
You are the only person that I know
that can actually do the flipping thing.
This one's a heart.
My heart.
It's yours now.
Are you ready?
- You sure we can't walk?
It's pouring rain, silly.
Here we go.
Wait, wait!
What?
I love you.
- Oh, I love you, too.
I wanna tell you why I love you.
- It's... it's raining.
You know that, right?
I have to tell you this,
and you need to hear it.
I've loved you since I met you,
but I wouldn't allow myself...
to truly feel it until today.
I was always thinking ahead.
Making decisions out of fear.
Today, because of what I learned from you,
every choice I made was different...
and my life has completely changed.
And I've learned...
that if you do that,
you're living your life fully.
It doesn't matter
if you have five minutes or fifty years.
Samantha, if not for today,
if not for you,
I would never have known love at all.
So thank you for being the person
who taught me to love.
And to be loved.
I don't know what to say.
You don't have to say anything.
I just wanted to tell you.
Thank you. Let's go home.
Are you coming?
Of course.
Ludgate Square, please.
- Yes, Ma'am.
You haven't got much time.
Anything's possible.
I'm so sorry.
I can't believe he's gone.
I mean, why am I here and he isn't?
Some things are just
out of our control, sweetie.
Ian, he had...
a premonition or a dream, or whatever.
He knew.
And he kept trying to tell me,
but I didn't believe him.
right before we got into the cab,
he told me about how I taught him to love.
Loving him was so easy for me.
He just wanted to say everything.
Subtitles: VIVOMEDIA 04/2005
www.moviesubtitles.org