There are some things
you should wish for...
and some things you shouldn't.
That's what my little brother
Frankie told me.
He told me I only had just three wishes.
And I looked in his eyes.
And I don't know why I believed him.
-Remember, we're on holiday, all right?
-Knock it off, Christy, love.
All those with U.S. passports,
use the two left lanes.
-Passports, please.
-We're on holidays!
-Are you, little girl?
-Yes. And my dad's not working.
What are your purposes
in visiting the U.S.?
We're on holidays.
-How long have you been in Canada?
-Just visiting.
Listening to my mom and dad...
We got the car in Canada.
...l was scared we weren't gonna
get across the border.
And if I didn't talk to Frankie,
how were we going to get into America?
'"Please, Frankie. Please.
'"Please help us, '"l said.
-How many children do you have?
-Three.
Two.
-it says three here.
-We lost one.
-What's your name, little girl?
-Ariel.
And who are you?
She's Christy.
-What age are you, Christy?
-She's 10.
-Welcome to America.
-Thanks very much.
And that was my first wish used up.
But I still had two left.
We heard Manhattan
before we ever saw it.
A thousand strange voices coming
from everywhere.
And you're not going to believe this...
but we had to go under the water
to get to the city.
No,I swear it. it was a real alien.
And we lost contact with everything.
it was like we were on another planet.
...classics from the '60s, '70s,
'80s, and '90s....
We looked all over Manhattan
for a place to live...
until finally we found the house
of the man who screams.
What are you doing
with the camera, little girl?
-You the police?
-What?
Fingers.
-Are you the police?
-No, we're Irish.
-All Irish are police.
-We're not.
Are we going to live here now?
-You're gonna live in here in this building?
-Yeah.
All right. Keep an eye on the car.
Papo's gonna keep you safe now.
All right? Come on in.
Welcome to your new mansion.
Come on.
Look, a lift!
That hasn't worked forever. Come on.
-Are we going to live here now?
-Yeah.
-Why?
-Nowhere else will take us.
-They don't want kids in Manhattan.
-Why?
-Why do you think it's called ''Man''hattan?
Papo, don't come any further, man.
Relax, Tony. it's just me.
I know who it is.
Go back downstairs to your apartment.
I’m clean, man. I’m showing this family
the empty apartment.
-No way, Papo.
-All right.
All right, Papo. We'll take over from here.
-Why does he scream?
-Maybe he sees ghosts.
Is this a haunted house?
-it's like Fort Knox.
-Cool.
-Where did you learn that?
-What?
-''Cool.''
-I just heard it.
You're American already. it's disgusting.
-Race you in, Christy.
-it's huge!
I know. it's enormous.
-This is my room.
-it's big, girls.
-I get top bunk.
Look, Dad. There's a bath
in the middle of the room.
There's pigeons! Ariel, look at this.
-it's a bit of a hole.
-it'll be fine when we do it up.
it'll cost us, Sarah.
How are we gonna pay for this place?
We'll sell the car.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, good.
-Are you?
-I’m great.
Are you?
-Dad?
-What?
Can we keep the pigeons?
Dad, can we keep the pigeons?
No, we have to leave them go.
it seemed like all our problems
were flying away.
-Dad, can I help?
-Go and ask your mom.
-Mom, can I help?
-Why don't you go on your skates?
I'll fast forward through this bit.
Ariel got to know everybody
in the neighbourhood.
My mom couldn't get a job teaching.
So she got a job in the ice-cream parlor
so Dad could go to auditions.
I really like the character.
I’m glad you asked me back.
I just wanna say
I'm real pleased about that.
Has he looked at the part of Vinny?
The New York guy?
He's a bit of a stereotype.
But if you want him, you got him.
Can you do a London accent?
You having a laugh?
He's only got two lines.
Do you want me to come up there
and sort you out?
-Do you like him?
-Yeah.
But acting's about more than just accents.
I wanted to cast you.
But you've got to give me much more.
Don't you understand?
Get it out of your head.
it's from here and from here.
Just give me one more chance.
But he didn't get another chance.
And then summer came.
And with it, the heat.
And a new word.; humidity.
-Dad, it's still not working.
-Wait.
it's too hot.
-it's still not coming through the holes.
-Hang on there.
Wait.
it's coming.
it's working.
-Well done, Dad. it's lovely and cold.
-I love you.
Ariel, Dad has an audition.
-Dad!
-What?
-What are you doing?
-I’m reading my scripts.
-Why?
-Because I’m learning my lines.
Dad, can we stay here all day?
-Dad, America's okay.
-Great.
-Dad?
-What?
Nothing.
What are we doing here?
Dad, Ariel's upset.
-She's been too long in the bath.
-What's wrong with you?
-My feet are like prunes.
-What?
They're like prunes.
Oh, Jesus. Where's your ma?
Are you okay?
it's too hot.
Dad, how are you gonna get that
air conditioner up and down the path?
Dad, how are you gonna....
Come on!
Dad, they're gonna shoot you.
-Dad, look out!
-Asshole!
Look, it's Dad.
-You're using, Papo.
-No.
Don't you walk....
Can I have some of whatever he's on?
Crazy, fucking Irishman.
Christy, open the door.
Mom, Dad's got an air conditioner!
He's coming!
-Walk away from me! Go on.
-Jesus! You'll have a heart attack.
-Open the window.
-Open the window, Mom !
What's wrong?
Wrong plug.
25cents short.
That's no use to me.
I got to make a living. $1 .99.
I’ll give it to you tomorrow.
-You're from the junkies' building, right?
-So?
Look at that.
That's from holding the knife of a junkie.
I got 25 stitches. He got probation.
Do I look like a junkie to you?
$1 .99.
-What's that?
-There's 5cents on each of those.
-Where's the $100Igave you?
-I put it in the bank like you insisted.
And 25 cents.
And $2. Mr. American Dream.
And one plug.
And 1 cent.
Dad, don't worry. Mom’s breathing's okay.
Is it okay?
it's the lemon drops. They're magic.
You take them,
and you forget about your breathing.
Say your prayers.
it's all right.
Go on, get your head in there.
Is that good?
Is that lovely? Yeah?
-Get a load of that!
-Get Christy!
Come on, get your face in there.
Look at that.
You're a genius, Dad.
Hey, gringo!
Gringo, what the hell's going on up there?
We got out of there as fast as we could.
We went to the bank,
took out our money...
and went to the movies
where it was lovely and cool.
Listen, don't be upset.
E.T.'s gone to Heaven.
-But they said he went home.
-Well, that's the same thing.
it's not.
I miss things.
What do you miss?
Things.I have no one to play with.
-You have your sister to play with.
-No. She plays with her camcorder.
And I have no one to tell my secrets to.
Christy telis them to her camcorder.
And she won't let me hear what she says.
And you don't play with us anymore.
-I do play with you.
-Not like you used to.
Here you go!
Step right up,
pop the balloon to win a prize.
-Pick a number.
-Dad!
Dad, you can win E.T.!
it's a game of chance. it's as simple as pie.
Just throw the ball
through the hoop seven times...
-and you win E.T.
-Seven times? Is that all?
-Can adults play?
-Sure.
-Simple as pie.
-That's $2.
Keep throwing as long as
you double up your dollars.
lf you win, you get the money back
and any prize you like.
-You get all your money back if you win?
-Yes. And any doll you like.
Yes!
-That's one.
-Come on, Johnny.
-Two down. Five to go. $4.
-Come on, we'll get there.
Come on, Dad. You're excellent.
You're brilliant.
All right, don't worry. I’ll get it in.
-Mom, is Dad going to win?
-Of course he is, darling.
Come on, Dad.
Yes!
Three, four, five. Very good.
Only two to go.
$8.
Game of chance. Simple as pie.
You can keep throwing
as long as you double up your dollars.
Shit!
-Number five, two to go. $16.
-Let's go for it.
-Come on, Dad. Only two more to go.
-All right. I’ll get this. Don't worry.
$32. We got $32 over here.
-I don't need a crowd.
-Well, you're the main attraction.
Game of chance. Simple as pie.
$64. Are we finished, sir?
Angela. Over here.
I got $55.
-Here,I have another $5.
-Just need $4 more.
-Dad, it doesn't matter.
-No.
Just take it, Johnny.
And $1 change for the big girl.
Only one to go.
One ball to go for the big doll
for the little girl.
Don't let him break your
concentration, Johnny.
-Give me the rent money.
-What?
-Please don't do this to me tonight.
I can't lose
in front of the kids again, Sarah.
Wait a minute. We got $128 over here.
Go on, Dad.
-We're finished now, sir.
-Leave it, please.
Go for it, man!
We can't blow all our money.
I believe in you, the kids believe in you,
and you can win that doll.
-Go on.
-You're gonna win.I just know it.
And then I used all my willpower
to quieten the crowd.
But it didn't work.
Every cent of every penny we owned...
was down for an E. T. doll worth $30.
So I said.;
'"Frankie,I have to ask you
for a second wish. '"
And to this day, my dad still believes
it was him who won the E. T. doll.
Fee, fie, foe...
fum !
I smell the blood of an Irishwoman!
Give me a bite of you!
Come on, Christy. Come on.
Run, E.T.!
Help! Ariel!
Fee, fie, foe, fum !
I smell the blood of an Irishwoman!
Run, E.T., it's the monster!
Fee, fie, foe, fum !
I smell the blood of an Irishman!
-Johnny, what's wrong?
-I was looking for him.
I was looking for Frankie.
Just play with the kids, Johnny.
I couldn't find him.
Am I going insane?
Just act, Johnny. Just act.
Go on, love.
Fee, fie, foe, fum !
I still smell the blood...
of an Irishwoman!
Come on, give me your finger.
Christy, I’ll save you!
No, get off her now, Dad!
You didn't find me.
I wasn't looking for you.
Exactly. You weren't looking for me.
There's nowhere you could hide
I wouldn't find you.
Fee, fie, foe, fum !
-Girls.
-I still smell the blood of an Irishwoman.
Take the bag. Take the money.
Go to Heaven. Marina will look after you.
I smell the blood of an Irishwoman.
-Hi, you two.
-How are you doing, girls?
You're a little later than usual.
Where's your mom?
My mom is playing with Dad on her own.
Fee, fie...
foe, fum !
I smell the blood of an Irishwoman.
Fee, fie...
foe, fum !
I still smell the blood...
of an Irishwoman.
-Where are the kids?
-Leave it on.
it's all right. it's okay.
-Where are the kids?
-They're fine.
They're in Heaven.
Marina's looking after them.
-Come on to me. Come on.
-No!
And that was the moment
the baby was conceived.
What's wrong?
Was it that good?
Was it that bad?
Look at me, Sarah.
Are you all right?
What's wrong?
Come here to me.
I can't.
Look at me and tell me the truth.
Frankie had your eyes, Johnny.
Say something.
You blame me.
I should have been there to catch him
when he fell down the stairs.
it's my fault.
I don't blame you.
We had to go to a Catholic school.
So my dad took a night job.
Ariel was worried about a blind man
called José.
Everybody smile and say ''cheese.''
Cheese!
Christy, why can José not see?
it's not José, it's:
O say can you see
I helped, too.
Fill the bag with these, like that.
Yellow ones.
Okay.
Statue of Liberty.
Nation, friends, and caring.
So now we're all together.
I’m hungry!
Keep your eye on the meter.
And get in the cab
and keep your ear on the radio.
I won't be long. And lock the doors.
401 to Base. lf you can hear me, come in.
Hello, Base here. Where's your dad, girls?
He's in his audition.
-Where are you?
-I’m not positive.
Christy, do you know where you are?
No.
Are you on Broadway?
-Yeah.
-I think so.
Near where?
-Near the audition.
-Yeah. Very good.
Is my baby all right?
How are you feeling?
Fine. A little bit tired.
But other than that, I’m okay.
Mom, do you think
Dad will know who I am?
You look great. You'll knock them out.
-Can you guess what they are?
-Ariel's an angel.
Christy's a forest.
-She's autumn.
-No, fall.
That's what they call it here in America.
Fall. Like leaves fall.
You guys look great. They look great.
-Irish. Spare a quarter, please?
-I got a quarter.
You're the best.
He gave me a quarter, Angela.
He gave me a quarter.
-There you go.
-Thank you, sir.
-Who are they?
-That's the Irish.
What's wrong?
Everyone else has bought their costumes.
-We look stupid.
-No, you don't.
And last but not least,
a special prize this year...
for the best homemade costume
goes to the Sullivan sisters.
You can't throw away your prize.
-Best homemade costume.
-They made it up because they pity us.
-You got it 'cause you're different.
-We don't want to be.
We want to be the same
as everybody else.
Why would you wanna be the same
as everybody else?
-Everybody else goes trick-or-treating.
-What's that?
it's what they do here for Halloween.
Like ''Help-the-Halloween'' party?
No, not ''Help-the-Halloween'' party.
You don't ask for help in America.
You demand it.
Trick or treat. You don't ask. You threaten.
-You can't do that on our street.
-Why not?
Because you can't threaten
drug addicts and transvestites, that's why.
What are transvestites?
A man who dresses up as a woman.
-For Halloween?
-No, all the time.
Come on.
-Why?
-it's just what they do here, okay?
We were allowed to go trick-or-treating
in our stupid building.
Trick or treat!
-Dad, get out of here!
-Trick or treat!
Come on, let's try another door.
Answer the fucking door.
-Why won't they answer?
-Maybe they're afraid.
We're nice kids, so let us in.
-How many doors is that?
-Four.
Why am I so anxious?
it's the stairs, Johnny.
-it says ''keep away.''
-I don't care. Come on, Christy.
Trick or treat!
Trick or treat.
Who's there?
-Someone's in there.
-Oh, my God!
No drugs here! Other door.
Knock again.I dare you.
-Trick or treat!
-Who....
Go away!
What?
Hello.
-Are you the kids from upstairs?
-Yeah.
-Is this Halloween?
-Where are you from?
-Ireland.
You came all the way to America
to trick-or-treat?
Yeah.
Come in.
-Are there only two of you?
-Two girls.
Are they all right in there?
They'll be fine.
-What's your name?
-Mateo.
- What's yours?
- Ariel. Hello.
- My name's Christy.
- Hi, Christy.
- Is that our building?
- Yes, it is.
Looks like a haunted house.
It is haunted. But it's not scary.
- It's a magic house.
- Frankie believed in magic.
- Who's that?
- Frankie. Our brother. He died.
He fell down the stairs when he was two.
We thought he was okay.
But there was something in his brain.
A brain tumour.
And for three years
it got bigger and bigger.
It was malignant.
Are you crying?
Are you?
It's okay. He's in Heaven now.
Is that your hand?
- Yes.
- Is that blood?
Spaghetti sauce.
Come here.
I better treat you or you'll trick me,
am I right?
- Yeah.
- Okay, let's find something.
Let's see. So, what's in the fridge?
Nothing.
How about this?
- How much is in it?
- A lot. Mateo's fortune.
- It's too much.
- No, it's not.
When luck comes knocking on your door,
you can't turn it away.
- Happy Halloween.
- Okay, happy Halloween. Bye.
Hi, Dad!
We're going to show Mam
what we got, okay?
Happy Halloween.
Happy Halloween, Mateo.
He was really nice,
and he gave us lots of money.
How much does it add up to, Christy?
Two hundred and forty pennies,
twelve nickels, and two dimes.
- How much is that all together?
- $3.20.
- And he had nothing in his fridge?
- Just medicine.
We should invite him over.
No way.
He gives me the heebie-jeebies.
- What is it?
- It's called colcannon.
It's potatoes mixed with curly kale.
Right. Plates, please.
Thank you.
Wow! That means you're gonna be rich.
Halloween is called the Day of Ancestors.
When the dead come back,
you hear their voices.
How do you hear them?
You hear their voices
through the men dancing.
What do they say?
They complain.
"You don't pay attention to me.
"You don't feed me.
"I'm hungry."
Are they ever happy?
When they're happy,
you never hear from them.
You're magic. You're winning everything.
That means you're gonna get married.
Christy!
Who's that?
You see that?
Do you not think I'm bad,
or are you just saying I'm good 'cause...
You are.
- Am I doing the wings nice?
- You're doing great.
- Really?
- Yes.
I thought I was bad.
You're doing great.
- Is that you in the pictures?
- Yeah.
So you were rich?
Is that why the angel has blue blood?
You know, in the Irish language,
the word for "black man" is fear gorm.
But that really means "blue man."
The word for "black man" is fear dub.
And that means "the Devil."
You have us figured out?
They can't wipe us out, they can't lick us.
We'll go on forever, Pa,
'cause we're the people.
"I said in mine heart, go to now...
"prove thee with mirth,
therefore enjoy pleasure." Awesome.
Johnny, come to bed. It's late, come on.
Put the script down now.
- You're happy.
- I am. It's something Mateo said.
What's he say?
He said everything's gonna be all right.
And the baby will bring its own luck.
The baby will bring its own luck.
That's it there. You see?
I could be wrong...
but I haven't felt the baby move
for a couple of weeks.
It's serious.
This baby will not go full term.
And if it did, it would be
extremely dangerous to your health.
If you decide to go ahead with this,
you'll have to be a very brave woman.
But I thought the doctor said
you couldn't have any more babies.
Sometimes, Ariel, doctors are wrong.
There. It just kicked.
Oh, my God!
Johnny, feel it.
I remember the first time
you kicked, Christy.
It was in one of your dad's plays.
Every time he spoke, you kicked.
Like you were applauding him.
- Did I ever kick?
- You kicked like a mule, night and day.
There it is again.
Johnny, did you feel it?
I can't feel anything.
Do you want me to lie?
You're the only actor in the world
who can't lie, Johnny.
- Not even for the sake of your kids?
- What does that mean?
If you can't touch somebody you created...
how can you create somebody
that'll touch anybody?
- What are you going on about?
- Acting, Johnny.
And bringing something to life.
It's the same thing.
That's why you can't get a job acting,
because you can't feel anything.
This baby's not Frankie, Sarah.
Look at me. Why don't you look at me?
You've gotten over him.
I had to get over him, Johnny,
for the sake of the kids.
So you're gonna put your life on the line
for the sake of the kids?
- And that's protecting them?
- Yes.
- That's a total contradiction.
- How?
You know what the doctor said.
I don't care what they said.
What do they know about us?
And my baby?
I gotta fucking get out of here.
Where are you going?
- This is real.
- No!
This is real. It's not a fucking play!
What are you talking about?
Where are you going?
- Let me get out.
- No.
You'll upset the kids!
I'll be back in a minute.
Johnny, come back.
Johnny, where are you going?
Johnny, you're scaring me. Come back.
Just come back. Johnny, please.
All right? Everything all right?
The baby will bring its own luck, will it?
I'll tell you the luck the baby will bring.
The baby could infect her...
and two giris will be left without their ma.
So keep your trap shut.
You don't believe.
In what?
God?
You know, I asked him a favour.
I asked him to take me instead of him.
And he took the both of us.
And look what he put in my place.
I'm a fucking ghost. I don't exist.
I can't think. I can't laugh. I can't cry.
I can't fucking feel!
Do you wanna be me?
- Do you wanna be in my place?
- I wish.
Are you in love with her?
- Are you in love with her?
- No.
I'm in love with you.
And I'm in love
with your beautiful woman.
And I'm in love with your kids.
And I'm even in love
with your unborn child.
I'm even in love with your anger!
I'm in love with anything that lives!
You're dying.
I'm sorry.
That's Frankie.
I'm just scared.
It's gone. I can't make-believe anymore.
Sometimes, I think our entire lives
are make-believe.
This is make-believe.
The air I breathe is make-believe.
Just make believe you're happy, Johnny.
Please, for the kids.
"Now is the winter of our discontent
"Made glorious summer
by this sun of York
"And all the clouds that there are around
"dance to the lascivious pleasings of a lute
"Now is the winter of our discontent
"Made glorious summer
by this sun of York"
So I'm a little high...
Sometimes, it seemed like everyone
in New York was an actor.
Even the stockbrokers.
You might not think it to look at me...
and I know I'm white and everything,
but I can rap.
Help, somebody!
Somebody call an ambulance!
Come on, man. Somebody, help!
He's fallen down the stairs!
I think someone's fallen down the stairs.
I think it's Mateo. Get your coat.
It's Mateo. Will I get the lemon drops?
- Yeah, and a pillow.
- Okay.
Mateo! Did anyone call for help?
He just fainted.
Keep the dog away, man, keep him away.
- Go downstairs.
- Stevie doesn't let me. He'll lock me out.
That's because you're a junkie, Papo.
Go and get an ambulance.
Don't do that.
- I did this to my brother.
- No. It's different.
Come on, come on.
Are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Can't seem to catch my breath.
- Just relax.
- Here.
- What are they?
- They're lemon drops. They're magic.
If you suck on some,
they'll make you better.
- Is that right, Christy?
- Yeah.
My mom takes them to help the baby.
I think you saved my life, Ariel.
All right, that's it.
Get out of the fucking cab!
What are you talking about?
I was right in the middle of a flow.
Come on, what the hell
is the matter with you, you freak?
Where's the Bill of Rights?
- Get the fuck off me, you piece of shit.
- Take your fucking handbag!
Night, E.T.
Are you awake, Ariel?
- Yeah. Are you, Christy?
- Yeah.
- What's wrong with Mateo?
- Some disease.
- Will you get it?
- What?
Mateo's disease.
- Why?
- Because you kissed him.
No.
- Night, Christy.
- Night.
There's Dad.
Get him, Frankie, get him.
You okay?
I was just out of breath.
What was Frankie like?
A warrior.
What does that mean?
A warrior who's not afraid
to go to the other side.
The other side of what?
This.
Hi, Dad.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are not alone.
Here on this little ball we call the Earth...
we have friends among us.
Don't be scared. He's not too well now.
Did he not take the lemon drops?
I don't think they agree with him anymore.
Why do you have sores?
If I tell you a secret,
will you tell nobody else?
No, I won't.
I'm an alien. Like E.T.
From a different planet.
My skin is too sensitive for this Earth.
Right?
The air is too hot for me.
Are you going home like E.T.?
I suppose I'm going home.
When are you going?
Soon.
Will you say goodbye to me?
- I will.
- Promise?
Yes, I promise.
Mom’s having a baby.
What do you think we should call it?
We're going to call it after you.
I think he's asleep.
My mom had to go into hospital...
so I thought about using my third wish.
But I had to be careful.
If the baby came too soon,
the baby might die.
And if the baby came too late,
my mom might die.
You have to be careful what you wish for.
Come on, kids, time to go.
See you later, all right?
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
- Take it easy, love.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
- Love you.
Excuse me, Mr. Sullivan?
We'll need that check by Friday.
- For how much?
- $5,000.
All right, okay. That's great. Thanks.
You know the situation.
You know I'm in trouble.
- Come on.
- "Shut up.
"Look into my eyes.
What are they telling you?
"They're telling you no.
"You either do the job
or you get out of town. Understand?"
- I understand.
- That was good, Dad.
Yeah, it wasn't so bad from you.
You're gonna get it, Dad.
- Do you think so?
- Yeah.
Will we sell the camcorder?
No.
Don't be worrying, girl.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Hey, Irish. Irish!
Hey, Johnny.
Haven't seen you for seven days.
- That means you owe me $7.
- Jesus, not again.
A dollar a day keeps Frank away.
Hey, I'm joking.
I've no money.
No, no. I got something for you.
Here, here.
- What are they?
- They're food stamps.
- I'm all right, thanks.
- Come on, you helped me out.
I'm just trying to help you out for once.
Come on, take them.
You can't take something from me?
Take the stamps.
Come on, take the stamps.
- Thanks.
- No problem, Irish.
Come on then. Tuck you in.
Dad? Who's gonna iron
our school uniforms?
Daddo the baddo.
- Dad?
- What?
- I need money for school.
- I have that sorted. It's all right.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Night, Dad.
- Good night.
Dad. You forgot to say Christy's prayer.
- I don't know it.
- I'll say it.
- All right.
- Kneel.
- What?
- Will you kneel?
No. I'm not kneeling, no.
- Mom always kneels.
- But dads are different.
- I want Mom.
- Christy, do the prayer, would you?
No monsters, no ghosts.
No nightmares, no witches.
No people coming into the kitchen,
smashing the dishes.
No deviis coming out of the mirror,
no dolis coming alive.
Mateo going home, Frankie in Heaven.
The baby not coming too early or too late.
Mom, Dad, Christy, and Ariel,
all together in one happy family...
and all well with the world. Amen.
You're great girls.
I'll see you in the morning.
- Night, Dad.
- How much does it cost in the hospital?
- Thousands and thousands.
Good night.
"To be, or not to be..."
Blah, blah, fucking blah.
"Whether it be nobler in the mind"...
to stick my head in the fucking oven
and end it all?
Where's Dad?
I want my dad.
- I am your dad.
- You're not my dad.
I want my real dad.
- Come here.
- Stay away from me.
- Come here to me.
- Where's Mom?
- What did you do with Mom?
- I'll get Mom. Come here, baby.
No! Mom!
Come here to me.
Look at me, look at me.
- Am I your dad?
- No.
Here, look. Look at me.
Am I your dad?
Maybe.
So spring came. And with it, the baby.
It had come too soon.
Can you get Karen for me?
Please don't let my baby come.
I don't want my baby to come.
No, it's too early. It's too early!
Coming through, stat.
I need a morphine drip.
Nurse, morphine.
Johnny, why is my baby not crying?
- Just go with the baby, go with the baby.
- I'm going.
We've stabilized her for now...
but she will need a blood transfusion
in the next couple of hours.
All right?
Everything's gonna be okay.
The baby needs a blood transfusion.
We have to sign this consent form.
The pair of us.
Is that okay?
All the blood is bad.
Mateo said all the blood is bad.
You're not giving my baby bad blood.
You gave my baby bad blood.
And that's why he died.
That's why he fell down the stairs.
This is the new baby, Sarah.
He tried to climb the gate. And he fell.
Why did you put it up?
- Where is he?
- Who?
Frankie.
Frankie's not with us, Sarah.
You should have taken the gate down.
It's your fault.
You should have taken the gate down!
- You're hiding him.
- No, I'm not.
- I want to get Frankie. I want my baby!
- Calm down, all right?
- Where is he? I want Frankie.
- Easy. Easy, now. Doctor!
It's your fault he fell down the stairs.
Could you ring your bell there? Doctor!
Why didn't you take the gate down?
- It's all right.
- No, please.
Please, I'm begging you, please.
Johnny, please.
No, no, please. I want to see my baby.
- Please don't take my new baby.
- I'm not taking her.
- Save my baby, Johnny, please.
- I promise.
I will.
If the baby dies, just don't wake me up.
- There's only one other solution.
- What's that?
- Are you O-negative?
- I am.
Christy's O-negative.
- What if I have it?
- Have what?
Mateo's disease.
That's not possible, Christy.
How do you know, Dad?
God won't let that happen to you.
You don't believe in God.
- I'm scared.
- Don't be scared.
Everyone's dying.
- Will she survive it?
- She can't survive without it.
That's what the doctors said
before they opened Frankie.
- What do we do?
- I'll give her the blood.
Is that a decision?
Christy will give her the blood.
Are you okay, little girl?
Don't "little girl" me.
I've been carrying this family
on my back for over a year.
Ever since Frankie died.
He was my brother, too.
It's not my fault that he's dead.
It's not my fault that I'm still alive.
Christy.
Mom was always crying
because he was her son.
But he was my brother, too.
I cried, too, when no one was looking.
- And I talked to him every night.
- She did, Dad.
- I talked to him every night until...
- Until when?
Until I realized I was talking to myself.
Listen, I'll take her home, okay?
- All right. Thanks very much.
- No problem.
Your check bounced.
I sat there with my dad, and all the noises
of New York disappeared.
All I could hear
was the blood thumping in my ear.
But for some reason, I felt happy.
I wondered if Frankie
had felt like this. ; special.
Everybody looking at you
like they were looking in a mirror.
And smiling. Except in their eyes.
Did Frankie know he was going to die?
Is that why he kept nodding
and smiling at us?
When he died, I cursed God.
I told him,
"You're not gonna see these snotty tears...
"running down my cheeks ever again."
So now, I can't cry.
I thought I'd come in here...
and you'd wake up, you'd hold my hand.
I'd cry, and the kid would be all right.
Everything would be okay.
We need a miracle, Mateo.
Hey, Irish, whoa.
You can't say hello?
What? What's up?
- I'm sorry, man.
- A bad day?
- You could say that.
- Yeah, the whole world had a bad day.
Joe, come on, give me a few bucks.
- Come on.
- I don't have any money to give you.
I'm sorry. I'm stupid.
I shouldn't be bothering you.
Come on, lighten up, Joe.
It's gonna get better.
Come on, Irish. Fighting Irish.
I'm coming to get you.
Just give me some money.
I'm not doing this for me. It's for Angela.
Come on, put your hand in your pocket.
- Take it easy.
- Your other pocket.
Your other pocket. Faster, Irish.
Let me see it.
Get it out.
- I don't know what it is.
- Take it out.
I'm taking it out. Okay, there you go.
I just needed money.
I'm sorry, okay?
Okay, that's enough.
Stop it. I'm sorry. Joe, I'm sorry.
- Hey, Joe. We're still friends?
- Go to hell.
We were waiting for the baby
to show some sign of life.
She just lay there and lay there.
The hospital bill arrived. It came to. ;
$30,420.20.
Look, just get me in the door
for the audition.
I'll give them whatever they want.
Sir. Your bill is ready.
All right.
- Bill's been paid.
- What do you mean?
A Mateo Kuamey paid it.
There's no balance.
See, see my playmate
Come back
Finally, my dad got a part in a play.
And he came to tell us the good news.
Since 1982
Got some good news, girls.
Sarah Mateo Sullivan is coming home
from the hospital.
Cool, yeah!
- Look who it is.
- How are you doing there?
- You want a look?
- Yeah.
- Mom, can I?
- Yeah, grand.
Okay, see you later.
Big yawn.
What's wrong?
- He never said goodbye.
- What?
He never said goodbye.
The baby's asleep.
Christy.
Come here to me.
Look up there and tell me what you see.
A full moon.
And what else do you see?
Stars.
Can you not see Mateo?
He's going past the moon on his bike.
I think he's waving goodbye to Ariel.
- Will we tell her?
- Yeah.
Look up there.
That's Mateo riding past the moon
on his bike.
- Where?
- There, look.
- Can you not see him waving to you?
- No.
- He's right there.
- He's there, flying past the moon.
- Can you see him?
- No.
Can you not see him waving to you?
He's waving goodbye.
Just like he promised.
Oh, yeah. Bye, Mateo.
- Bye, Mateo.
Bye, Mateo. Look after Frankie.
- Look after Frankie.
- Look after...
And then I asked for my third wish.
Say goodbye to Frankie, Dad.
What?
Say goodbye to Frankie.
- Bye, Frankie.
- He can't hear you, Dad.
Goodbye, Frankie.
Get out of here.
Dad wants you.
It was as hard for Frankie to smile,
when the tumour was malignant...
as it was for my dad to cry after.
But they both managed it.
I'm going to switch this off now.
It's not the way
I want to see Frankie anymore.
Do you still have a picture of me
in your head?
Well, that's like the picture
I want to have of Frankie.
One that you can keep
in your head forever.
So when you go back to reality...
I'll ask Frankie...
to please, please, let me go.