Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
[crickets chirping]
[Glass Concrete & Stone
by David Byrne playing]
Now I'm wakin' at the crack of dawn
To send a little money home
From here to the moon
Is risin' like a discotheque
And now my bags are down and packed
For traveling
(anchor woman) After
months of speculation
analysts expect an
announcement this week
that GlobeCom International
will acquire Waterman Publishing
and its flagship
magazine, Sports America.
The man at the helm of GlobeCom,
billionaire media magnate Teddy K.
has been on a spending spree recently,
acquiring a food service
company, a cable operator
and two telecommunications providers
in deals totaling more than $13 billion.
And how did one lucky
ferret owner come to own
the largest dog treat
manufacturer on the East Coast?
Skin, that covers me from head to toe
Except a couple tiny holes
And openings
Where, the city's blowin' in and out
This is what it's all about
Delightfully
Everything's possible
When you're an animal, not inconceivable
How things can change
I know
So I'm puttin' on aftershave
Nothin' is out of place
Gonna be on my way
Try to pretend
It's not only
Glass and concrete and stone
That it's just a house, not a home
(Dan) Mr. Kalb.
Dan.
Thanks for the Lakers tickets.
You bet.
Seats were terrific.
But I'm still not going to
advertise in the magazine.
My son-in-law tells me that
people don't read much anymore.
Too much effort moving
the eyes back and forth.
So we're gonna put most of our budget
into television, radio, Internet.
Okay.
''Okay''? What does that mean?
I'm not gonna try to sell you.
Why the hell not? You're a salesman.
Yeah. Just not a very
good one, that's all.
I'll say.
But I am gonna ask you one favor.
Oh, yeah?
I'm gonna leave you an
issue of the magazine.
And I'm personally gonna
send you a new one every week.
Now, I'll call you in a few weeks,
and if you want to, we'll talk.
There's a great article in there
comparing today's quarterbacks
with Johnny Unitas.
[scoffing]
Unitas would kick their butts.
[chuckles]
So, this is your sales pitch?
I've been with the magazine
for 20 years. I believe in it.
Well, good for you.
So, are you worried
about all these rumors
that your parent company
is about to be sold?
No, not really.
I don't see how it would affect us.
Well, hopefully it won't.
You know, that Teddy K. character
offered to buy my
business a few years ago.
I told him to go screw himself.
[chuckling]
My son-in-law says
I'm a dinosaur.
Don't knock dinosaurs. They ruled
the earth for millions of years.
They must've been doing something right
Simply put, we are never
gonna be able to reach
this significant, untapped market,
until we learn to think like them.
In point of fact,
less than .05 percent
of all cell phone users
are under the age of 5 years old.
That's why we have the T-Rex phone
and the Triceratops phone,
and the Pterodactyl phone.
'Cause it's gonna change all of that
and each one of these phones
has its own unique ring.
[roaring]
[mimicking child]
Mommy, Mommy, I want one.
Buy me one for Christmas.
P.F.G., Carter. P.F.G.
What's P.F.G.?
Pretty fricking good.
Gentlemen, ladies. I have
an announcement to make
It's on.
Teddy K. has busted his move
and we are taking over
Waterman Publishing.
Ow!
Let's give it up for Teddy K.
[hooting]
The man has vision. He's a maniac.
And, I guess it's okay
to tell you Teddy K.
has personally asked me to go over there
and turn around marketing
in the magazine division.
So, if you'll excuse me...
Carry on.
Waterman! That's incredible.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mark. Mark, you're taking me with you.
Tell me you are taking me with you.
Carter, I'm gonna take that place
and whip its fat ass into shape.
And... And?
I want you to come run ad
sales at Sports America.
I knew it. I knew it.
The magazine's a cash cow.
It's the cornerstone.
I mentioned your name to Teddy K.
He liked what you did with cell phones.
Oh, hold up, hold up. I'm...
I'm sorry. Teddy K. knows my name?
I'm gonna tell you something.
And I don't want it to go to your head.
You're being groomed.
I'm being groomed? Yeah.
Mark. Thank you.
Thank you. I am going to
kick so much ass for you.
I'm gonna take no prisoners.
I'll be your ninja assassin.
Wow. You're the new me.
No, I'm the new me.
Congratulations.
[chuckling]
What's up?
[engine starting]
[knocking on door]
Hey, Dad.
Hey, button.
What are you still doing awake?
Couldn't sleep.
Can't sleep?
What, were you worried about something?
No, not really.
[sighing]
'Cause, uh,
you know if--if--if you
are worried about something
you can always talk
to me about anything.
Remember? You know
when you were a little
girl we crossed our hearts
and said we'd always tell
each other everything.
Be honest with one another.
[chuckling]
Yeah.
I'm kind of tired.
Hmm. Okay.
We still gonna hit tomorrow?
Yeah, sure.
All right. I'll see
you then. I love you.
I love you, too.
[Ann grunting]
[sighing]
Hmm.
Uh, what time is it?
It's after 3:00. Go
back to sleep, honey.
Sorry I woke you up.
Hi, sweetheart.
Hi.
Honey,
does Alex have a new boyfriend?
Uh, no.
W-What about that Myron kid?
I think that they're just friends.
Yeah.
[whispering] I'm pregnant.
What?
[sighing]
I'm sorry. I thought you
said that you were pregnant.
Yeah.
You can't be pregnant.
Yeah, I can. I'm... I am.
Now, how could that happen?
Well, I think that you were there, too.
No, honey.
You know you're done with all that.
That's what Dr. Steinberg
said, but he was wrong.
You're pregnant? Yep.
Holy crap.
Holy crap!
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Does it feel like a boy?
Right now it feels like a stomach flu.
You can't be serious. Are you serious?
[whispering] I am serious.
[moaning]
This is fine. This is fine.
This is... This is fine.
Yeah.
That means when he's 21,
I'll be 72.
Three.
Two. Three.
Holy crap.
I'm just so excited. I'm so excited.
ls excitement contagious or what?
Um, no.
I'm being groomed. I'm being groomed.
Do you have any idea what this means?
That you're a chimpanzee?
It means that we're on the road.
You know, things are fallin' into place.
We can buy a bigger house.
We can have kids. You know?
[chuckling]
I'm sorry. We got a life going on here!
Carter, it's 3:00 a.m.
How much more enthusiasm
are we looking at here?
15 minutes? An hour?
Honey, I'm sorry.
It's just, Teddy K. knows my name.
Are you even qualified for this job?
What? Yes. Sure.
Selling cell phones, selling ad space.
You know, it's all the same crap.
Anyway, it's just a stepping-stone.
Love you.
Love you, too.
The light. Yep.
[dog barking]
We're all gonna get fired.
Well, anything's possible.
No, it's not possible. It's probable.
Did you hear about this Teddy K. guy?
Hear about him?
Everybody's heard about him.
I heard he's an albino, but
he covers it with makeup.
Alicia. Yes. What?
Are you fired?
What? No! What? Why?
You haven't heard anything.
Why? Are you fired?
Uh, I'm sorry.
Are--are you
saying I'm fired?
No, no, not yet. I mean not yet, Dan.
I'm... I can't predict the future. Um,
the thing is, Dan,
you're not head of ad sales anymore.
Carter Duryea is.
Who is Carter Duryea?
Some hotshot from GlobeCom.
This a bummer, Dan. It's a real bummer.
But you're lucky. A lot of people
are getting canned immediately
across the company.
Are you getting fired?
Me? No.
This is a joke. This is a joke.
We have had our biggest
year ever this year.
My sales team works incredibly hard.
I'm not gonna put up with this.
Well, you have to put up with it.
What are you gonna do,
start somewhere new?
You're not a kid anymore.
You know how tough it is out there.
People are cutting back.
They're not looking for guys
like you who make a decent salary.
Hey, buddy, I am as pissed
off about this as you are.
So then why are you smiling?
I'm not smiling.
Yeah, your lips are curling up.
They do that naturally, Dan.
[sighing]
[cars honking]
[elevator bell dings]
Hold up! Hold up! Thank you. Thanks.
[Alex clearing throat]
47. Are you going to
Sports America offices?
Yeah.
You an intern or something?
Uh, no, my dad works there.
Oh.
Are you interning there?
No, I'm starting a job there today.
That's cool. Congratulations.
Oh, thank you.
I'm totally scared shitless.
I have no idea what I'm doing.
Don't tell anyone, okay?
Okay.
[elevator bell dinging]
Please.
Thank you.
[sighing]
Dan, your daughter's here. She is?
Hey, boss, what's this gonna
do to our stock options?
I have no idea. Don't call me ''boss.''
Now, look. I insist. Let me take that.
No, that's okay. I'll hold
onto it. Oh, no, really.
Dan, you hear anything? Are we fired?
Mr. Colon is so
excited to work with--
Oh, God. I'm sorry. Christ.
(Carter) No, I'm sorry. You okay?
I'm fine. It was all my fault.
Uh, you okay?
Yeah, uh, no broken bones.
No harm, no foul. Terrific.
(receptionist) Okay, terrific.
Hey, champ.
Hi, what are you doing here?
Tennis.
Oh, sorry. Yeah. Yeah.
Why? ls today a bad day?
Ah, no.
No, no, it's--it's fine.
It's just... To hell with it.
Let's...
Let's go. Come on.
Okay.
[grunting]
You all right?
Man, you sort of sucked today.
[snorting]
I was just holding back to
give you some confidence.
Yeah, right. Yeah.
You're an old man.
[grunting]
Hey, Dad.
Yeah?
Remember when I said I might
want to transfer to NYU?
Yeah.
Well, I got in.
What, to NYU?
Yeah.
Sweetheart, that's fantastic.
I'm so proud of you.
Thank you.
You'd--you'd have to live
here in the city, though.
Yeah. And, uh, I want to
study creative writing.
And NYU has such a great program.
But what about SUNY and the tennis team?
Dad, I'm not gonna be a
professional tennis player.
Well, look, sweetheart, being
a writer is just as tough.
You're living in the city and I don't--
I don't-- I don't like that idea.
This is a lonely place.
You got to have street smarts.
I don't think that's such a good idea.
Dad,
I want to try living in the city.
And
I know that NYU is more expensive,
but it would be such a
great experience for me.
Yeah. It is more expensive.
Yeah.
But
it's your education.
Yeah.
That's the most important thing, right?
We could manage it.
[exclaiming]
Dad!
What?
You're drenched.
Oh. Oh.
I think you're gonna be very happy here.
You're really stepping
into an all-star team.
Oh, uh, this is Morty Wexler.
Morty, Carter Duryea.
Duryea. You're on the
Ford account, right?
Correct.
Well, it's a pleasure to meet you.
You, too. I'm really looking
forward to working with you.
Oh, terrific. Thanks.
Okay.
''l really look forward
to working with you.''
[sucking]
Bite me.
Uh, we have a terrific office for you.
Great view. Um, It's not
cleared out yet. But, uh...
Not bad, huh?
Uh, excuse me a second? I'm going
to use the little boys' room.
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Tasty.
[elevator bell dinging]
[door opening]
May I help you?
Oh, I'm sorry. This is your office.
Yeah.
You're the guy I bumped into.
Dan Foreman. Carter Duryea.
You're Carter Duryea?
Yes, and, uh, it's a
pleasure to meet you.
The Carter Duryea that's
come in to run ad sales?
That's correct.
How old are you?
I'm 26 years old.
Twenty-six
and you're my new boss.
[chuckling] Uh, I guess so.
That's, uh, that's quite a...
That's quite a kung-fu
grip you got there, Dan.
Oh, well. So,
what kind of experience
do you have in ad sales?
Uh, well, I'll be honest with you, Dan.
Not much.
How much?
Um...
None.
None. That's not much.
But I'm a fast learner, Dan.
Hey, now that you know how old I am,
how old are you?
I'm 51 .
Fif... Wow!
[both chuckling]
Wow. That's crazy. Yeah.
That's like a year older
than my dad, so that's weird.
Oh, well, this is... This is great.
You two have met.
Are you kidding me? We
are old buddies by now.
Dan, it was a pleasure to meet you.
Pleasure.
Um, Dan, you want
this door closed? Or...
Yeah, you can go, um,
go ahead and close it.
[door closing]
[metallic clanking]
So it was pretty unexpected.
But it's--it's like a
pretty big promotion.
That's fantastic! Way to go.
So, uh, the Boxster S has more guts.
You'll sure feel the extra horsepower.
But if you really wanna go,
I'd say take the 91 1 Carrera.
I'm gonna go with the 91 1 .
[Sister Surround by Soundtrack
of Our Lives playing]
[sighing]
You're a rhyme without reason
And you know it so well
Well, who's the king of the season
Well, you never can tell
Go ahead.
Though it's so plain to see
Carter.
Surround sister
'Cause I'm not afraid to fall
Yeah.
No, I'm not afraid to fall
[engine revving]
[glass shattering]
[whooshing]
Jackass!
[clanking]
[crickets chirping]
[door closes]
Hey.
Hi.
Uh, I hurt my arm. But l-I'm okay.
I'm glad you're okay.
Carter.
Kimmy.
Kimmy, again?
[chuckling]
Seven months? We've been married...
Come on.
Okay, I know things
have been a little off.
I've been swamped at work.
I mean, God, I should have
taken you on a real honeymoon.
Well, I should have just shut
that cell phone off. It was...
It was ringing off the hook.
That's--that's
my bad.
You know, this whole thing is my fault.
Okay, here's the good news.
I can change. I'm gonna change.
This--this has actually been a
very good lesson for me. Thank you.
Don't try to sell me, Carter.
I love you, Kim.
Kim, I want to have kids with you.
But I don't want to have kids with you.
I don't even know if
I want to have kids.
I told you that.
I told you that on our second date.
Wow, I thought you were kidding.
Carter, is this really
such a surprise to you?
Are you sleeping with somebody else?
I was, but I broke up with him.
Well, it must have been
really rough on him.
Well,
I'll be at my parents'.
They're really excited to have me back.
[heart beating]
[door closing]
We're gonna hear two heartbeats now.
(Ann) Mmm-hmm.
That strong, slower one is yours, mom.
[heart beating fast]
And that... that's
your baby's heartbeat.
[gasping]
Oh, my God!
Nice, strong heartbeat.
That's your new baby, Dan.
[heart beating rapidly]
Dan?
[panting] Yeah?
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah.
That's fantastic.
Uh, I'm feeling a little, uh...
[chuckling]
You are having a little
bit of arrhythmia.
Have you been drinking
a lot of caffeine lately?
No.
You under a lot of stress?
Well, l...
I did sort of get demoted at work.
Ah.
You what?
Yeah.
l, uh... We'll talk.
[dog barking]
[crickets chirping]
[car seat whirring]
[cars honking]
[gulping]
Another?
Yeah, just keep them coming.
You don't even have to ask.
[sighs]
How was everyone's weekend? Fun?
I'm sorry. That was, uh...
[sighing]
[exhales]
[clearing throat]
Um, I'd like to thank
everyone for joining me here.
Teddy K. has an... has a thing
that what makes GlobeCom
great is the men and women
of GlobeCom.
ls it like a thousand
degrees in here or is it me?
[chuckling] It's like...
It's me.
I have an agenda.
And you're gonna learn this
about me. I'm a machine.
What was I saying about the...
(Alicia) An agenda.
An agenda, I have an agenda.
[sighing]
Which is that I have to immediately, um,
increase the ad pages
here by 20 percent.
20 percent? Carter, only a
startup magazine can do that.
Yeah, well, I think
this team can do it, Dan.
Um, how?
Well, Morty,
basically what we--
God, that's an awesome question.
''How?''
And the answer
is synergy.
We need to team up here.
Yeah, we need to synchronize
and we need to synergize.
We're not alone. We're not alone.
We're part of one of
the biggest multimedia
and brand name companies
in the known universe, okay?
Let's--let's take advantage
of that, like, uh...
Like...
Krispity Krunch.
Did anyone know that, uh,
one of our sister companies
is Krispity Krunch?
So?
So we talk to our brothers and
sisters over at Krispity Krunch.
We make a deal where we supply
sports factoids to their boxes.
So that when Joe Couch
Potato is sitting there,
he's, uh, snacking, he looks
down, and what does he see?
Sports America, Krispity
Krunch sports factoids.
He's definitely buying
more Krispity Krunch
and not Krunch 'n Krackle
which, by the way, looks
and tastes exactly the same.
But guess what? No sports factoids.
And Krispity Krunch is so happy
they guarantee us 28 pages a year.
Besides which, they know if they don't,
Teddy K. is gonna be pissed.
What is that? What am l
talking about here, people?
Synergy.
lsn't that cheating?
No, no. Hell, no.
And, uh, Techline cell phones.
We own Techline cell phones.
Guess what we put on their browser?
Factoids.
Yes! Factoids! Synergy!
And what else? Uh, box scores. And ads!
We make a deal like a
100,000 hits on the Internet
has the equivalent value of
one ad page of our hard copy.
Are you getting it, people?
The magazine has become just a portal
to a synergized world
of cross-promotion.
We're gonna bust things wide open.
We are gonna take
things to the next level.
Who's with me? Who's with
me? Who-- who's psyched?
Lou, are you psyched?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm psyched.
Okay.
Alicia, are you psyched?
Absolutely.
Better. This guy. I'm sorry,
I don't know your name yet.
Hector. I'm in maintenance.
That's cool. Hector...
Hector, I know you're psyched.
I'm psyched!
[all laughing]
Yes, Hector's psyched!
And if Hector's psyched,
then you know I'm psyched.
I am psyched for this team.
Now who else is with me? Who's psyched?
(all) I'm psyched!
(Carter) Excellent. Who else? Come on.
Who do you think will be
the first to get canned?
My money's on Dan. He's prehistoric.
Sorry, Dan.
Thanks for joining me for lunch.
You like sushi?
I'll just stick with the teriyaki.
You should try some.
The spicy tuna here is money.
Come here. Get that.
Get that.
Yeah, go fishing, man.
Yeah.
[grunting]
Yeah. So I wanted to talk to you,
because, uh,
This is raw.
...an increase in ad pages is...
Well, it's really only
part of the equation
in terms of achieving the bottom line
my bosses want me to hit.
Understand, Teddy K. is making
cuts across the board here.
In point of fact, I have to cut
$300,000 salary from the
sales team immediately.
[grunting]
I don't make that much money, Carter.
I know how much you make, Dan.
Well,
I wish you'd told me that I was fired
before I ate the goddamn fish.
Oh, Dan! Dan! Dan!
[clearing throat]
I'm--I'm not
letting you go here.
You're not?
No.
You are an excellent salesman.
You ran a good team.
I think that you have the potential
to be an awesome wingman here.
An awesome wingman?
[laughing]
B-But, Carter, I definitely
see the benefit for you
in having an awesome wingman.
But what is the benefit for
me at this point in my career
of being an awesome wingman?
Well,
one benefit at this point in your career
is that you get to keep your job.
That's a pretty good
benefit, don't you think?
Really? Really! Are you smiling?
You're smiling! This is funny to you.
Guess what? You have no idea
what a nightmare you're
about to step into, my friend.
[door opening]
A-hole!
We'll see how soon this place goes
down the poop chute without me.
Maybe there is justice in the world.
You enjoying yourselves? Great.
[phone ringing]
[Gone For Good by The Shins playing]
Untie me, I've said no vows
The train is getting way too loud
Carter is ready for you.
I gotta leave here my girl
Get on with my lonely life
Dan, uh, I'd like you to take a
look at one of these forms for me.
It's a 360 evaluation. Mmm-hmm.
It's basically an
evaluation from every angle.
That's why it's called a 360.
It's corporate policy.
But it would be great
if I had it by Monday.
If you really want to get aggressive,
to penetrate that
core demographic--
I believe that--
Dan, not now.
Sports America is the number one
magazine, boys 13 to 18 in the country.
I spent 12 long months on the lam
That's enough sitting on the fence
Hi, leave me a message or don't.
[machine beeping]
Hi, it's me.
I mean, you know it's me.
Uh, just filling up the old
mailbox. So give me a call
or don't.
And go out of my head
You love a sinking stone
Here, boy.
That'll never elope
So get used to the lonesome
Oh, hi, Mrs. Cherneski.
No, I didn't know he moved out.
Well, tell him Carter says hi.
Here, boy!
Hey.
And he is dropped
right on the goal line.
Tackled by Bob Colder,
Leahey held on to the ball...
Hello? Hey, Dan.
It's Carter.
Who?
Carter Duryea.
[chuckling]
Thought we'd get the
group together tomorrow.
Maybe go over some
business development ideas.
Tomorrow's Sunday.
I know. It'll be great. We'll
get a great jump on the week.
Not the whole day, just a
couple of hours in the afternoon.
I'll tell you what, I
will see you there at noon.
Uh, I'll bring some sushi.
It'll be a lot of fun.
Okay? Great. All right.
You love a sinking stone
That'll never elope
So get used to the lonesome
Girl, you must atone some
Don't leave me no phone number there
[footsteps approaching]
What are you doing?
What?
[clearing throat]
Um, nothing.
I was just, uh, seeing stars.
Ever do that?
Yeah, when I was three.
Hey, what are you
doing here on a Sunday?
Sunday is a fun day to kick some ass.
Absolutely.
Guess what? I have my
whole team coming in today.
Hey, Dan Foreman's here.
You should really meet him.
Yeah, I'd rather not
get personally involved.
Didn't we decide to let him go?
Uh, no, we let Enrique
Colon go instead. Remember?
Yeah. That's right.
Did a little colon cleansing.
Get it?
[both laughing]
Hey, you want to grab
some dinner tonight?
Ooh, wish I could.
I got to fly to Berlin to meet
with some of our satellite guys.
Ha, too bad.
Somethin' wrong?
Um...
My wife and I are having some
problems and, uh, I was just--
Okay, I got to go.
Listen, uh, you're gonna have
to riff some more people, man.
Okay. Riff them?
Reduction in forces. Shitcan them.
Right. Um, but I think we're
gonna get ad pages up here.
So I don't think we
need to riff anybody yet.
Well, sooner or later everybody
has to deal with reality.
Thanks for coming in.
You, great job today.
Louie, great job. You want to,
uh, grab a drink or something?
You know, I'd love to, but
I'm a recovering alcoholic.
Well, better not, then.
How about you, Morty. Drink?
Uh, I'd better get home for dinner.
My wife is slowly poisoning me to death
and she gets very angry if I'm late.
Okay. Alicia?
Uh, you know what, I got
to go home and do my hair.
Oh, shut up.
[chuckling]
How about you, Dan? You want to,
uh, grab a drink or something?
[grunting] It's Sunday.
I have to go home and
have dinner with my family.
You want to have dinner with my family?
Oh, yeah! Are you... Let me,
uh, let me just grab my stuff.
Wait.
[tires squealing]
Who taught you how to drive?
No one.
No kidding.
I'm home.
Yes.
Oh, this is what I'm talking about.
This is like a real home-type home.
Hey, sweetheart. This is
Carter Duryea from the office.
Hello, it's nice to meet
you. Hey, Mrs. Foreman.
What a pleasure to meet you.
Thank you so much for
having me into your home.
[clearing throat] You're very welcome.
I hope you like baked ziti.
Baked ziti! Uh, this
is... This is so perfect.
That baked ziti. That's
so... This is what I need.
Like a-- Like a real,
home-cooked thing.
This is great.
ls there something wrong with him?
Clearly.
Let's just feed him and get
him the hell outta here, okay?
He's really young.
He's a lot younger than you.
Yeah. Thank you for that. Thank you.
[chuckling]
So, um, I did the numbers on NYU.
Do you know how expensive that place is?
Hmm. Plus living expenses.
Plus Jana's orthodonture.
Plus baby costs.
Don't worry about it.
Well, that's not actually a solution
to a problem. ''Don't worry about it.''
I think we may have to
take out a second mortgage.
Why don't I just go into the living
room and ask my boss for a raise?
Oh, hey.
I was, uh, just looking at you and...
And you've...
We never got to...
That day in the elevator.
My name's Carter Duryea.
Yeah, I know who you are.
Does my dad know you're here?
Uh, your dad invited me over for dinner.
Technically.
Uh, who's that?
Uh, it's Dad's new boss.
You can't be Dad's new
boss. You're too young.
Yeah, and he's also scared shitless.
Wow, good memory.
And you're too cute to be Dad's boss.
Oh, well, thank you.
[phone ringing]
I got it!
[sighing]
So, uh, how's it going?
Okay.
So what are you doing here, really?
Uh, my wife left me, and today's
the anniversary of our first date.
I found the idea of going
home to be so depressing
that I kind of leeched onto your dad
and invited myself over for dinner.
[snickering]
Wow, you're sort of a
bizarrely honest guy. Huh?
No.
No. Honestly, I'm...
[chuckling]
I'm not.
Just around you, for some reason.
People would probably say
that I'm an emotionally guarded
anal-retentive asshole.
You wanna play foosball? Okay.
Cool, I'll just change.
Okay. Good. Yeah.
Do you think Alex could cope with
living in the city on her own?
[sighing]
Well, I'm less worried about her
coping with it than I am about you.
Yeah, well, frankly, I'd rather
keep her under house arrest
with a homing device around her ankle.
Then why did you agree to it
without even talking to me?
[grunting]
And why is your teenage boss here?
And why am I so nauseous?
I hardly had any morning
sickness the first two times.
Hey, hey, hey!
and I'm so sick of it!
Calm down. Let me have that.
[gasping]
[sighing]
[retching]
I'm not really that into tennis anymore.
What I'm really not
into is being the jock.
You know, it's like people don't
even invite me to their parties
because they think I'm
in training or something.
Also, there's this rumor going
around that I'm a lesbian.
[Carter chuckling] Man, that sucks.
Or not. I don't... Not being a lesbian.
Yeah, well, I'm not.
It'd be one thing if I wanted to
go pro and make a ton of money,
but I'm not at that level.
I've played girls at
that level and I'm not.
I mean, not that I'd want that, really.
Their lives have peaked by
the time they're like 21 .
Oh, nice.
I wonder that about
myself sometimes, too.
Like maybe my life has peaked at 26.
Maybe it's all downhill from here.
Well, it probably is.
[chuckling] Yeah.
Here you go. Keep the change.
Dinner's ready!
I'm on an important call!
With who?
My boyfriend.
Your what?
Hi, this is Mr. Foreman. Who
is this and how old are you?
All right. Well, I just wanted to say
if you ever give my daughter an
alcoholic beverage or a joint,
I will hunt you down and neuter you.
(Jana) Dad!
Dinner's ready!
[door squeaking]
There you are.
You kids ready to come in for dinner?
[crickets chirping]
[sighing]
[whispering] God.
(Carter) I lived in
the same town as my mom.
And I mean... You know what I mean?
The entire... The
whole family thing was--
Right. Yes, I'm...
No, no, it's really not
a good time right now.
(Jana) I know, but l
really like him a lot.
Oh, my God, this pizza's
amazing. Where'd you get this?
It's from a wonderful little
Italian restaurant called Domino's.
So, are you really Dad's new boss?
We're not, uh, we're
really more colleagues.
No, that's not true. He's
the boss man. I'm the wingman.
(Jana) Are you married?
You're wearing a wedding ring.
Um, yes, I am, sort of.
Um, or... Yes, no. I'm married.
So you're like prematurely old.
Jana, would you pass the pizza?
I got it. Oh, my God, Dan. My bad.
I'm sorry. I mean, I got it. I got it.
Carter, Carter, C-Carter.
Only my wife is allowed
to touch me there.
[sighing]
Excuse me. I'm gonna go upstairs.
I'm gonna change my pants again.
Good job.
[chuckling]
Thank you.
Thank you so much. Terrific
pepperoni, by the way.
You're very welcome. Goodbye. Go home.
Okay.
Good night.
Thanks again.
[Naked As We Came by
lron And Wine playing]
She says, ''Wake up,
it's no use pretending''
I'll keep stealing, breathing her
[engine starts]
Birds are leaving over autumn's ending
One of us will die inside these arms
Eyes wide open
Naked as we came
One will spread our
ashes around the yard
She says, ''If I leave
before you, darling
Don't you waste me in the ground''
I lay smiling like our sleeping children
One of us will die inside these arms
(Dan) Oh, here.
I got you some pepper spray.
Eyes wide open, naked as we came
Oh, how sweet. Yeah.
And I've installed surveillance
equipment throughout the dorm.
So I'll know if you're
getting into trouble.
Okay.
One will spread our
ashes around the yard
Be careful.
Okay.
I love you, Dad.
Love you, too.
[grunting]
See you later.
Bye.
Sign here, here, and here.
And you've got your second mortgage.
Sign, uh, there, there, and there.
And it's official.
You're divorced.
[cars honking]
(Carter) Okay, two things.
First, Steckle is organizing
a company basketball league.
I'm gonna be sales team captain.
You are my new power forward.
And second, I heard you're
taking the guys from Rums Jamaica
to the Knicks game on Wednesday night?
Yeah.
You have to run that stuff by me, man.
Run it by you? They're my clients.
No, they're not, Dan.
They're GlobeCom clients.
That's why we're gonna be takin'
'em to the GlobeCom luxury suite.
Well, these aren't
luxury suite type of guys.
Dan, everyone's a
luxury suite type of guy.
[chuckling]
Uh, we can't go there on
Wednesday, because Teddy K.
is hosting Bill Clinton,
Jay-Z, and Kofi Annan.
We're gonna do it Thursday.
I'll bring them to a concert.
Look, I gotta get these guys
to up their buy by 18 pages.
We gotta start kicking some ass here.
[sighing]
I'm gonna have to let some people go.
Why do you say ''let them go''?
They don't want to go.
Why don't you just say, ''fire them''?
Because it sounds better.
Not to the person
getting fired, it doesn't.
You wanna get with me? Put 'em up
Take long trips with me Yeah
This guy was shot 1 2 times
and pronounced legally dead.
Hence the name.
Someone should tell him
it's spelled D-E-A-D.
[laughing]
They're afraid to.
He's got the number one
hit single right now.
He's a protege of 50 Cent.
Why don't they just call him ''NickeI''?
[laughing] What?
20 years, your jokes
still haven't improved.
(Carter) Want you guys
to meet my colleague.
This is Petey from K-Jam Sneakers.
Hey, hey.
Hmm.
Cross-promotional idea.
You buy a certain amount
of Jamaican rum, boom.
You get a discount on
running shoes. Done.
Yeah, sounds like a great fit.
Get a lot of drunk
people running around.
[laughing]
Dan. You want to go get some air?
Yeah.
Be back in a bit.
Word. Hey, not too long. We
got chimichangas on the way.
You wanna get with me?
Take long trips with me
Sorry about the concert.
They wouldn't let me just get
regular seats for the Knicks game.
No, it's okay.
Look, Dan. I've been
instructed not to advertise
with Sports America anymore.
What?
We were bought out last year by this
company called Continental Brands.
Apparently, the company that bought us
and the company that bought you
are having a feud over wireless
communications in Europe.
Wireless communications?
What--what the hell does that
have to do with our business?
Nothing. But we have
this corporate policy now.
Look, I'm sorry, Dan.
[music playing]
[sighing]
Dan, I have to
fire Louie and Morty.
No, you don't.
I do.
We're gonna get those ad pages back.
We'll get those...
Oh, my God! It's like you
don't get it or something.
That was a huge client.
Steckle gave me a bottom line here.
I have to increase pages.
We already got Harry, Pete,
and Alicia on the Ford account.
Morty's the logical choice.
Oh, and the new woman at Pepsi
thinks that Louie's a sexist.
Guess why. He called her ''sugar tits.''
He's an idiot.
Come on, you can't fire these guys.
These are my guys.
They've been with me for eight years.
I hired them at the same time.
Yeah, I know, Dan.
That's why they have
huge, bloated salaries.
And they're not pulling their weight.
I'm sorry.
Well, I've been here for 23 years.
My salary's bigger than theirs.
Why don't you just fire me?
Do you want me to fire you?
Because I could, Dan.
You have a family that loves you.
You have a kid on the way.
I look at you sometimes and it's like...
You have people who need you.
Do you really wanna put them
in jeopardy for Louie and Morty?
[Sunset Soon Forgotten
by lron And Wine playing]
Be this sunset soon forgotten
And what's worth keepin'
Sun still sinkin'
[sighing]
Down and down
Once again
Gone again
What, are you living here now?
[sniffing]
What... We, uh... What time is it?
7:00 a.m.
Look, I've been thinking all night.
[breathing deeply]
And, uh, if it has to be done,
I should be the one to do it.
[phone ringing]
[Dan sighing]
[sighing]
Guys, I feel really terrible
about what I'm about to say.
But I'm afraid you're both being let go.
Let go? What does that mean?
It means you're being fired, Louie.
Believe me, if I had any
choice in this, I would...
[sighing]
Anyway, I thought you
should hear it from me
because I'm the one who hired you.
Oh. Wait a minute. Are
you being fired, too?
No, no. Uh...
[clearing throat]
This isn't my decision.
Oh, so it's not your decision, so
therefore it's not your fault, right?
I didn't say that.
You know, this is bullshit.
Louie. No, no, Morty.
You know something? I
look at you like a brother.
I would've stood in front of a
bus for you, you piece of shit!
You've turned into a real corporate
asshole, you know that, Dan?
Louie.
Do me a favor. If you see my friend
Dan, tell him I'm looking for him.
Louie!
Dan, what the hell am
l gonna tell my wife?
I mean, she already wears the pants.
Now she's gonna wear
the tie and jacket, too.
Morty, I am so very sorry.
I know this must have
been hard for you, Dan.
You were a good boss.
I mean it. You always treated
everyone with respect. And l...
Look, I appreciate it.
What's this?
My 360 evaluation.
Uh, you rated yourself,
''Does not meet expectations.''
Yeah.
I'm gonna cry.
Don't. I'll call you.
Take care, Morty.
[whispering] Okay, good luck.
(Alicia) Morty. Oh.
I can't believe this.
Me neither.
You gonna be okay?
I'll be okay.
Take care.
No way! What are...
What are you doing here?
Hey! Um,
just reading. l-I've--
I go to NYU now.
No way! Yeah.
You did it! That's... That's awesome.
Yeah, yeah. What about you?
I'm renting an apartment in TriBeCa.
Oh, yeah? Yeah.
Wow, that's awesome.
Do you drink coffee?
No! Uh, normally I just
hook up to an lV, actually.
[both laugh]
[car honking]
My, you sure can pound
back the caffeine, huh?
ls that why your leg
is shaking like that?
I think it is. Yeah.
You're not wearing your wedding band.
Oh. Yeah. I'm now officially
the first person in my high school class
to get divorced.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
When I think about it honestly,
it was pretty much coming
since our second date.
How's... How are you?
How's school going?
It's pretty good.
It's pretty good. I mean,
you know, it's, it's, uh...
it's hard to meet new
people as a transfer.
Everybody's got their own little cliques
and they're not sure if
they want to admit one more.
But, uh, my creative writing
classes are really great.
Oh, yeah, creative writing?
Yeah. I've just, uh...
I've always been interested in stories
and escaping into other people's lives.
I guess 'cause mine
always seems so boring.
I'm cursed with a functional family.
But writing isn't exactly practical.
So I think I might
double major in business.
Oh, no. Don't do that.
Stick with the creative writing.
Strange, you know,
sometimes you seem sort of
bummed out about your career,
but you're so successful.
No, I'm not bummed. Uh...
God, my career is pretty
much what I have in my life.
That and a dented Porsche, right?
[laughs]
Your family must be really proud of you.
My mom is.
You know, she's... She's
this kind of hippie.
So she's not really
into the corporate thing.
And my dad left home when I was 4,
so, you know, I never
really got to know him.
His family had money,
but, uh, he was this kind of artist
you know, in quotes, slash druggy.
Uh, he was in this cult for a while.
Do you, do you... Let's get out of here.
Do you want to, like,
take a walk or something?
I'm like, uh... Now that I've
told you my entire life story.
Sure.
Although, uh, there isn't
much left to talk about.
[Cannonball by Damien Rice playing]
Really?
Still a little bit of your taste
In my mouth
Still a little bit of you laced
With my doubt
Still a little hard to say
...wear these giant muumuus
that were see-through.
What's going on They were see-through?
Yeah. That's cool.
Stones taught me to fly
Love taught me to lie
Thank you.
So...
Life taught me to die
So it's not hard to fall
Right.
When you float like a cannonball
You want to see my dorm room, maybe?
Hey, don't get the wrong idea.
l--l don't invite
guys to my room often.
Or ever, actually.
Okay.
Oh.
I'm having a major
college flashback here.
Aw, come on, old man.
My roommate's out for the night.
Really? She's, oh...
I was really looking
forward to meeting her.
Yeah, she's only mildly
chemically imbalanced.
Ta-da!
Oh.
[door closes]
Yeah, this is awesome.
Yeah, it's okay.
Uh, I heard this rumor
that alcohol impairs your judgment.
I wish you weren't so beautiful.
I'm not.
No, Alex. You are.
Thank you.
[sighs]
[Spanish song playing]
[lighter clicking]
Well, it looks like
everything's perfect.
So why are you still talking?
What?
Oh, nothing.
I was just thinking
about how my dad said
he put surveillance
cameras in the building.
[chuckles] That's...
That's hilarious.
[phone ringing]
Where to now?
You're all going to the 29th floor.
Oh, great. I hear there's, uh,
fantastic air-conditioning
on that floor.
[phone ringing]
Hey, Dan, how's your commute?
Can you believe we're
moving offices already?
By the way, first b-ball game
against the 51st floor corporate VPs.
So, uh... Oh, weird. I
guess that's this floor now.
What's wrong with you?
Me? Um... Are you...
Nothing. Um, nothing.
You're acting jumpy.
Did you switch from mocha to crack?
Whoa, Dan. That's, uh...
You're coming off really
paranoid right now.
[chuckles]
You're weirding me out, buddy.
Crack. That's...
[phone ringing]
[Ten Years Ahead by Soundtrack
of Our Lives playing]
Well, it's so good
I didn't have to make it
It's so good Hey, Alex.
Haven't talked to you in a few days.
It's your dad, by the way.
Give us a call.
'Cause I'm ten years ahead
And you're the echo of the things I say
Yes, I'm ten years ahead
You understand this is totally
demoralizing for me, so...
[laughing]
Sorry.
I don't think you
should force it, honey.
[grunts] Don't force it.
Don't say it.
Well, it's no good
Revolving around me
Hey, Alex.
Uh, left a message for you
at the dorm and on your phone.
Guess you have your
cell phone turned off.
Give us a call.
When you cannot reach me
I'm fired?
'Cause I'm ten years ahead
And you're the echo of the words I say
[sighs] I'm sorry.
Yes, I'm ten years ahead
But I've worked here for 5 years.
[sniffs]
It's been an honor.
[phone ringing]
(Carter) Okay, you ready?
Will you be okay with that thing?
Oh, yeah, fine.
Hey, uh, what's that big guy doing here?
He's one of the moving men.
Uh, I guess, uh, Steckle
recruited him for his VP team.
Oh, that's fair.
Wonder if I can still dunk.
You could dunk?
Oh, yeah. Can't you? You're 26.
[chuckles]
Heads up!
Whoa! Hey.
What's up?
Word on the street is,
Teddy K.'s on the prowl.
Soon as he gets back from his
around-the-world balloon trip,
he's gonna go munch
on Continental Brands.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Hey, great.
Maybe they'll advertise
in the magazine again.
I'm sorry, who are you?
Mark, this is Dan Foreman.
He's the one I was telling you about,
helped us close that Toys 'R' Us deal.
Oh, Carter's being modest.
He did most of the work. Aw.
That's beautiful.
Maybe you two should get a room.
You pussies ready to get schooled?
[chuckles]
[whistle blows]
[people cheering]
[man whooping]
[crowd cheers]
[crowd cheering]
[laughing]
[Steckle laughing]
(Steckle) Oh!
Not in my house! No, no, no.
(Steckle) Do it, baby. Do
it, baby. It's for me. For me.
(Steckle) Go ahead, donkey!
You can't guard me.
(Theo) Get down. Get down there!
(Steckle) Mine. He's mine. Help. Help.
Yes!
[all cheering]
Let's go! Get down, Jimmy.
Yo, Krouse! Fist! Fist!
That's right! Move! Come on. Come on.
I'll take the big man.
Hey, ease up, my man.
You're gonna have a heart attack.
What's the matter?
Can't take a little D?
(Steckle) Open! Get open!
(Alicia) Let's go, Dan! Yes!
Yeah, yeah! Throw it down!
(Theo) Dunk it!
[all groaning]
Oh, shit.
[ball bouncing]
[grunts]
I'm okay. I'm okay.
[exclaims]
I'll be right back.
Just give me a second.
[Dan groans] Damn.
[moans]
[phone ringing]
(Alex) This is Alex's cell phone.
Please leave a message. Thanks.
[phone beeps]
[Those to Come by The Shins playing]
Eyeless in the morning sun
You were pale and mild, a modern girl
Taken with thought, still prone to care
Makin' tea in your underwear
You went out in the yard to find
What's her name?
Who? What? Who?
The fish.
Oh. Uh, it's a he. And,
uh, his name is Buddy.
Ah.
Does Buddy want a friend?
Buddy had a friend.
Um, he ate him. So...
[chuckles]
You mind if
l, uh--uh...
Sure. Yeah. You... Yeah.
I want to, I want to ask you something.
Okay.
[clears throat] When, uh...
When you were 18,
did you ever return your
parents' phone calls?
Uh, well, they never called.
But, uh, yeah, I'm sure I would've.
Well, my oldest daughter,
she won't call me back.
And I feel like going down
to NYU and kidnapping her
so I can stop worrying about her.
[stammering]
That sounds like a really bad idea.
Uh, look, Alex seems, um,
from the very brief time that I met her,
to be pretty savvy.
I don't think you have to
worry about her too much.
She's a smart, terrific woman.
Girl. Or smart young lady. Whatever.
What I'm trying to say is that, uh,
I think she can probably
take care of herself.
Dan, you seem to have
the perfect marriage.
How do you do it?
You just pick the right one
to be in the foxhole with
and then when you're
outside of the foxhole,
you keep your dick in your pants.
[Carter laughing]
Well, that's poetic.
(Alicia) Oh, my God. Did
she outdo herself or what?
(Alicia) All right. Oh, yeah. Make way.
Coming through with the cake here.
[all chattering]
[music playing]
Oh, hey, Theo. How's...
[all chattering]
Hey, uh, where do I put this?
All right.
It's a rager, huh?
Okay.
Are you still glad you decided
not to have a birthday party?
Yep, not in the mood this year.
Well, Mom says you
could use a little fun.
She says you should lighten
up for the sake of your health.
She does, does she?
They're here. Everybody hide.
You go ahead, sweetheart.
I'm going to check the mailbox.
Okay. Cool.
[dog barking]
Quiet, he's going to
be here in a second.
[door opening]
[door closes]
(all) Surprise!
Surprise?
[all screaming]
Dad!
Hey, Morty.
Hey, nice party.
Thanks for coming. Sure.
How are you?
Not so good, not so good.
I mean psychologically.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's okay.
Anyway, my wife got a promotion.
I'm hoping she'll raise my allowance.
But this is good punch.
Happy birthday. Good party.
[dog barking]
You look-- you look
really beautiful.
Thank you.
And, um...
This is really not a
big deal. But l, uh...
I got something for you.
It's not my birthday.
Go on.
Holy shit.
[laughs]
Wow! Are these real diamonds?
It's too expensive.
No. No, don't. No.
I feel funny.
I'm sorry. I don't... I
mean, it's not... l--l...
It just felt good to...
It's sweet.
It's very sweet. Thank you.
You're the kind of person
that's it's good to
be in a foxhole with.
We're not in a foxhole.
We're in a Porsche.
(Dan) A sling.
(woman) Yes.
(Dan) Betsy, I wish you well, too.
[all laughing]
Let's see, what.... Wow.
And this could be what?
[all laughing]
That's good. Epsom salts.
[all laugh]
(Alicia) Do you like them?
(Theo) lmported from Jersey.
[people laughing]
(Alicia) Don't tell me
you already have some.
[all laughing]
[chuckles]
It's got that easy--easy-pour
spout on it, too.
[all laughing]
(Alicia) Special for you.
[all chattering]
[car honks]
[car honking]
Thanks.
She waits.
Okay.
(Carter) Hey.
Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
Work has been just nuts.
That's okay. I have a class at 3:00.
[car honking]
Oh, you're... You're
wearing the necklace.
Yeah. Yeah. I feel like an impostor.
But it's nice. An impostor?
No, you look...
Hey. Doesn't she look beautiful?
She does.
(waiter) Now, we have
three specials today.
Avocado soup with awapuhi oil,
bluefin tuna with Awapuhi
and jalapeno sashimi.
(waiter) We have calamari fritti
with Awapuhi oil on the side.
We also have, uh,
sicafreed lobster tail.
Can I get that with
a side of Awapuhi oil?
Welcome. May I help you?
Oh, shit.
Hi, is there going to be a third?
I have just one question.
Are you sleeping with him?
I'm going to get you folks some bread.
Uh, Dan, this isn't what it looks like.
Oh, yeah? What does it look like?
Tell me. What do you
think it looks like?
Well, I'm sure it looks like
some kind of sleazy, tawdry...
Alex, I asked you a question.
Are you sleeping with him?
What do you want me to say, Dad?
[sighs]
Get up.
What?
Dad!
Pardon me, sir, but I don't
think you should treat--
Back off, before I drop-kick
you across this restaurant.
You are a piece of shit!
Dan, I love her.
You what?
I love her.
[Carter panting]
I love you.
You love her? She's my daughter.
She's in college.
She's a college student.
I took out a fricking second
mortgage so she could go.
Three years ago she was in braces.
I'm sorry.
This guy.
You had to sleep with him?
Dad, l...
Dad...
(Alex) Dad.
[groans]
Dad! Wait, I'm sorry.
This had nothing to do with you.
He's my boss, Alex.
I know. But it just happened.
We made a deal, remember?
We made a deal we'd always
be honest with one another.
Dad, I was like 5 years
old when we made that deal.
Yeah. I liked you better then.
That's awful.
That's an awful thing to say.
Dad, please don't walk
away. I want to talk to you.
Why? You don't need my
advice about anything.
[door opening]
Hey, you.
Hey.
Hey, Carter. Wow, that's some shiner.
Thanks.
Maya, could we have
some privacy, please?
Sure. Absolutely.
[growls]
Sit down.
Hey, can I get you some ice for that?
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
[clears throat]
Um, there's no ice.
But the soda's cold.
Oh, thanks.
Look, I wanted to apologize,
uh, for my timing when...
Uh, with the ''I'' word.
It just kind of slipped out.
But I've been thinking
about it a lot lately,
and it's how I feel. It's
really important to me--
Oh, that's really sweet.
Well, I mean it.
I know you probably think you do.
But l-I've been doing
a lot of thinking, too,
and I'm
taking anthropology classes.
And I'm doing a double major.
Yeah.
And I'm just... I'm really busy.
Yeah. Uh, I'm just not...
I'm not ready for a big commitment.
Yes, that's...
[chuckles] That's what I'm saying.
[sighs]
Look, when I said I loved you,
I didn't mean that I wanted
to interfere in your classes
or, you know, whatever.
I'm not talking about
marriage or anything yet.
Carter. Look.
I've had an amazing time with you,
and I think you're a great guy.
But you are on the rebound.
No, I'm not.
Carter, you are.
I mean, it was not that long
ago that your wife left you.
Best thing that ever happened to me.
Well, that's great.
But then that's a good thing
whether you're with me or not.
I think we should
stop seeing each other.
Alex.
[laughs] Alex, come on.
I just want you to know
I enjoyed talking to you more than
maybe anyone in my entire life.
Thank you.
Me, too.
[door opening]
Dad, where have you been?
Your cell phone was off.
I tried to call you
like a thousand times.
What happened? Where's your mom?
(Ann) There you are.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Yes, I'm fine.
The baby's fine.
I had a little scare.
There was some bleeding.
What? What is it?
A placenta previa.
It sounds bad, but, uh, it's okay.
[chuckles]
I just need some rest.
If anything ever happened to
you, I'd just have to pack it in.
Oh, I'm afraid you're going to
be stuck with me for a while.
[door opening]
[sniffs]
How's she doing?
She's okay.
You know, I broke up with Carter.
Because of me?
No. Because of me.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
But, you know, I think you should know
that Carter didn't try
to seduce me or anything.
If anything, it was
the other way around.
I really don't want to hear the details.
[grunts]
I mean, unless you
want to tell me, and...
No. No, not particularly.
Good.
[sighs]
You must think I'm disgusting.
Disgusting?
Why on earth would I think that?
I didn't know that you
took out a second mortgage.
I don't need to go to NYU.
SUNY's fine. It's fine.
No, no, you are staying at NYU.
Look, Alex.
You're a really smart woman.
And you can take care of yourself.
And I'm going to try
and adjust.
You don't have to change, Dad.
Yeah. I do.
[computer beeps]
It's going to be okay. Muchachos!
(Teddy K.) Good. Hello,
how are you? I know.
(Teddy K.) Tell him not
to be late this time.
(Teddy K.) Hi, how you
doing? Good to see you.
Hi. Oh, nice brooch.
Thank you, sir.
Must be paying her too much money.
Mark Steckle. Hi.
Ah, Mark Steckle, how are you?
Very psyched. How's it going?
Very good. Good, good.
Right this way. Hi.
How you doing? Nice to see you.
How are you? Good to see you.
(Teddy K.) Thank you.
Carter Duryea.
Oh, yes. Cell phones.
Yes. Thank you.
I'm at Sports America now.
Well, that's the flagship.
What happened to your eye?
Yeah, what happened there?
I fell-- I fell
asleep at my computer.
Just kind of banged
right into the monitor.
Those things can be dangerous.
[all laughing]
(Teddy K.) Keep up the good work.
I wouldn't be surprised
if he announces another
big takeover today.
Teddy K.!
(Teddy K.) Great to see you. Thank you.
(Teddy K.) Thank you.
Synergy. What does it mean?
(Teddy K.) Why does a
business swim with it
and sink without it,
in this new ocean of megabytes,
streaming video and satellites?
Every day,
the world becomes more complex.
And to survive in a complex world,
we need complex bonds
to interface with it.
In this room,
I see this.
What we're trying to get to, is this.
(Teddy K.) This is unbreakable.
This is inevitable.
(Teddy K.) What are we
building here? ls it a company?
Or are we building a new country
with no national boundaries?
A new democracy for the consumer.
A new democracy with a new electorate.
24-hour music videos in Kuala Lumpur.
Computers with parts
manufactured in Japan,
Greenland, ldaho, India.
A soft drink ad going out simultaneously
to seven different continents.
The Dalai Llama eating
his Krispity Krunch
while uploading prayers onto the Net.
Woman's World magazine.
Well, why not Woman's World
Channel across the world?
Computers.
Why not a computer section
in Sports America magazine?
[chuckles]
(Dan) Uh, excuse me. Excuse me.
Yes?
Uh, uh...
Uh, my name is, uh,
uh, Dan Foreman. l...
I work for Sports
America and I'm not sure
l--l understand what
you're talking about.
(Dan) W-what
I mean is--is
what do computers
have to do with sports?
Are you... Are--are
you literally saying
that there should be a
section in the magazine
about computers?
Who's going to want to read that?
Um...
[clears throat] And, uh...
[sighs]
l-I'm not sure I understand
how the way the world is changing
is actually going to
change how we do business.
We're still selling a product, right?
Which hopefully someone needs.
We're human beings with other
human beings for customers.
So I don't see how this
company is like its own country.
I mean, just because we sell
different kinds of things,
that doesn't mean we should
operate by our own laws, does it?
Besides which, countries,
at least democratic ones,
they have some obligation to
their citizens, don't they?
(Dan) So how do layoffs
and bottom line thinking fit into that?
Dan Foreman.
Sports America.
You ask some excellent questions.
Excellent, excellent questions.
I'm glad you asked them.
And I'm leaving it to you,
to all of you, to answer them.
Hmm.
Teddy K.!
(Steckle) Teddy K.! Teddy K.!
(Carter) Oh, my God, Dan. Oh, my God.
(Steckle) Good, you're both in here.
You, I'll talk to in a second.
You, have you lost your frigging mind?
Well, he said they were
excellent questions.
Okay, you think this is funny.
You think it's funny to
disrespect a great man.
Do you know who you were
just talking to in there?
That was Teddy K.!
Teddy K., God damn it!
Look, we've been carrying
your fat, bloated
salary for way too long.
(Steckle) I want you
out of this building
within the next 10 minutes.
I'm going to my office.
I'm going to smoke a nice Cuban cigar
and try to forget that you ever existed.
You, in my office now.
Mark, don't do that.
Excuse me?
Look.
The guy busts
his ass and--
And what?
Nothing. I'm sorry.
(Carter) I just... If you fire him,
you're going to have to fire me, too.
Wait.
Let me get something straight here.
You're throwing yourself in with him?
With this useless,
over-the-hill loser?
Think here. Think
about what you're doing,
because if you're not careful,
you could end up like him.
I guess that that would be okay.
All right.
Then you're fired, too, you little shit.
Well, that's too bad,
'cause, uh, you're gonna lose a huge
account that Dan and I've been working on.
It was gonna save the year for us.
Without it, the magazine's
pretty deep in the red.
Really? What account is that?
You think we'd actually tell you?
You're bluffing.
I don't bluff.
I'm not that good of a salesman.
Yeah, well, I don't give a crap.
I think Teddy K. will.
See, I'm gonna call him
and I'm gonna tell him
that you single-handedly drove
his most profitable magazine,
his flagship, right into the ground.
And he'll remember my name.
He likes what I did with cell phones.
You've got 24 hours,
or you're both gone.
[sighs]
Any ideas?
One.
You got all your research?
Yep.
Follow my lead.
(Kalb) So, um, how are your daughters?
They're great. Thanks.
How about your grandkids?
Uh, they're fine.
My son-in-law has just
enrolled our oldest, Ralphy,
in a computer camp,
whatever the hell that is.
Uh, this is my boss, Carter Duryea.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Mr. Kalb.
You have a really awesome company here.
You... It's a really
awesome, awesome--
Your boss? He looks
more like your nephew.
Well, I've, uh, certainly
been learning a lot from Dan.
So what happened to your eye?
That's one of the things
he learned from me.
Are you saying that you
punched him in the eye? Why?
Well, it's... We don't have
to really go into it here.
No, no, no, please, please.
I'm--I'm--I'm rather curious.
Why did I hit you?
He called me a dinosaur.
He said I was out of date.
That I'd better step in line.
So you slugged him?
It was a fair fight. Hmm?
Right.
Mr. Kalb, we have a sister
company, Krispity Krunch,
that I think we could do a really
exciting cross-promotion with here,
all in the GlobeCom
family. Carter, Carter.
I think that we
could achieve--
Carter, it's ok. Mr. Kalb,
I don't want get into facts and figures
with you today. You know them already.
(Dan) I just want to
ask you one question.
What is your hesitation
about advertising with
Sports America magazine?
My hesitation is that our ad
budget is already overextended.
My son-in-law has put a lot
of money into cable and online.
And now he wants to plow even
more money back into it. But...
But what?
But he is such an asshole!
I mean, I built this business.
I know more about running
this than he ever will.
So, yeah. I'm gonna make a
major ad buy in your magazine.
And then I'm gonna restructure
the whole damn ad campaign.
That is great news. Thank you, Mr. Kalb.
Oh. Thank... Yes.
Thank you so much, sir.
You know, I don't give a
shit about Krispity Krunch.
Let's just stick with
the magazine, okay?
You really slugged him?
Yeah. Carter.
Oh, my God. Oh, my
God, that was amazing.
That was unbelievable!
God, that was actually fun.
What Kalb really needed to see
was an old fart who beat the crap
out of a young punk half his age.
And you know what the best thing is?
It's the right thing to do.
It will improve his business.
Wow, you actually, uh...
You actually believe in this stuff, huh?
Of course I do.
Why else would I do it? Hmm?
[elevator bell dings]
Hey, Dan. Where you been?
Los Angeles.
We made a huge sale.
Congratulations. So did Teddy K.
He sold the company to
CalCor Communications.
(Carter) Mark! What happened?
I thought you said Teddy K.
was buying another company.
That's what they told
me, but he sold us.
I'm out.
Wait, you're out?
Yeah. They're reorganizing
the whole company.
You're out, too. I think you're in.
I'm in what?
Your old job.
What? Running the department?
That's the rumor.
The whole thing seems so arbitrary.
I feel used.
Yeah.
Kind of tough to know
you're replaceable, huh?
[clears throat] I'm--I'm
sorry you lost your jobs.
[Solsbury Hill by Peter Gabriel playing]
Came in close, I heard a voice
Standing stretching every nerve
I had to listen, had no choice
I did not believe the information
Just had to trust imagination
My heart was going boom, boom, boom
Son, he said
Grab your things, I've
come to take you home
[elevator bell dings]
Yeah, back home
[phone ringing]
Hey, Dan.
Hey, Carter. Come on in.
Have a seat.
Nice office.
Yeah.
[door closes]
[sighs]
So.
How have you been the last month?
I've been good. Really good.
It's a little weird,
uh, not having to get up,
go to work in the morning.
That's why I want to talk to you.
I want to offer you a job.
I know we definitely had our moments.
But I think you're a good
manager and a good salesman.
And I want you to come here
and be my second-in-command.
Wow, Dan.
Uh, l... I really appreciate that.
Uh, more than you know. And l...
I think if I really want
to do this for a living,
there's no one I could learn
from more than you. But l...
Look, I don't know what
I want to do with my life.
I know that I want it
to mean something to me
the way that this
means something to you.
[sighs] Oh.
God, do you think I'm being stupid?
No. No. l...
I think that sounds right.
So how's the family?
Uh, Ann's fine.
Uh, the baby's coming
Tuesday after next Tuesday.
Oh. It's a... It's a cesarean.
Dan, that's amazing.
Yeah, it is.
And, uh, both girls are...
They're doing well.
Good.
Please, uh, give them all my best.
Yeah.
[sighs]
Dan.
Thank you.
For what?
For...
I guess for showing me a few things.
No one ever really took the time to
give me a hard time before.
Or teach me anything that was
actually worth learning.
[clears throat]
All right.
[sighs] Now listen, Carter.
I want to tell you something.
You're going to be okay.
You think so?
Yeah. I know it.
You're a good man.
[sighs]
[sniffs]
Don't be a stranger.
[elevator bell dings]
Morty?
Hey! You're back!
Yeah, back in the saddle.
And look at you.
You're--you're...
You look like a delivery guy.
Oh, do you know Dan's daughter Alex?
Yeah. What are you doing here?
I'm surprising my dad. Tennis.
(Morty) Alex is a
fantastic tennis player.
She was a junior champ, right?
Really? Oh, you're into...
You're into tennis, huh?
Yeah.
How is everything?
Good. Really...
Really good.
Um, I'm leaving town, actually.
I think I'm going to try teaching
or, um, maybe open an Awapuhi store.
[chuckles] I don't know. Uh...
How are you doing?
(Alex) Good. Very good.
I've been working on some short stories.
Oh. That's awesome.
Well, I got a raise. Dan got me a raise.
Which is a good thing, because
my wife just got laid off.
Timing's everything in life, right?
[elevator bell dings] Right.
Well, good seeing
you. Take care, Carter.
Yeah. Look, it was really
great seeing both you guys.
You, too, Carter. It was...
It was really good to see you.
Bye.
Hi, guys.
Well?
Yes?
Wel, I'm delighted to say
that you have a baby sister.
[chuckles]
Are you happy, Dad?
Yeah, I'm psyched.
[cell phone rings]
Hello. Dan! Hey.
Oh, my God. Congratulations.
It's amazing.
Do you have a name yet?
Oh, no, that's terrific.
Uh, probably because I'm jogging.
No, I'm outside.
Yes. I'm actually jogging outside.
Please Playa del Rey. Don't laugh.
Remember me
I'm thinking about getting into...
Happily
By the rose bush
Laughing with roses on my chin
The time when
we counted every black car
passing your house beneath the hill
and up until
someone caught us in the kitchen
with knives
A mountain range
A piggy bank
A vision to removed to mention
But, please, remember me
fondly
I heard from someone you're still pretty
And then
they went on to say
that the pearly gates
are so eloquently repeated
Like words I've lost and found
And don't look down
And someone save temptation
And, please
remember me silently
In the car behind the corner
you hold my hand
between your knees
You turn from me
Said the trapeze, it was wonderful
But never meant to last
The clouds have passed
So we just come up with anger
And then
The circus moved
The parking lot
Hiding out, a hint of danger
So, please, remember me
fondly
You're my uphill crawl, my dear
But if I make
the pearly gates
Do my best to make a drawing of God
And Lucifer
A boy and girl
An angel kissin' on a silkscreen of Mars
The aftermath
A marching band
All around the fray
just trapeze swinging
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org