Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I was one of you.
I believed in control.
Some control is necessary.
Is it?
The gorillas, they let you
stay with them, even at night.
You were becoming one of them.
- Are you listening?
Are you listening to me?
Yes.
Not one of them.
Not a gorilla.
Don't you see?
They accepted a man.
They reached across.
They took me in
as family.
They welcomed a human being
among them.
That's the miracle.
What about the family
you left behind?
What about Lyn?
We leave her
outside of this.
- Why?
- And my wife. Leave them out.
You think I don't know. I know what
I was, what I lost, what I killed.
- She's not dead. She wants to see you.
- She saw me at the airport.
She saw what I am now.
You let me
be dead to her.
You change
the subject, "Juha",
or walk away from this.
Which do you want?
For now, I want the forest.
Take me there.
In the forest
for all that time.
Did you ever miss
the contact with any humans?
No. They were there.
I may not have seen them,
but I always knew they were there.
If you were
learning their ease...
Their peace.
Then why does this all end in murder?
There were many murders.
- Many?
- Yeah.
There's a zoo not far from here
where I studied...
and many years ago...
and, uh...
they needed
a male gorilla,
a wild capture.
And I did that.
I helped capture him.
I didn't even know what murder
was when I was you, "Juha".
You know what murder
I'm talking about.
If you don't talk to me about this,
I can't help you.
- I don't want you to help me.
- What "do" you want?
I want you to listen.
- And then what?
- Share it.
- With?
- Whoever you share with,
the people you're close to.
Are there any?
Why don't you tell others?
'Cause I'm not
for this world,
not any more.
What world, then?
In your memories, locked away
in your mind for the rest of your life?
- Is that all you want?
- No, I want to finish this.
- Finish what?
- Telling you what I know.
What makes you think
what you know is any different
than what other people know?
I had different teachers.
Okay, okay.
So I'm supposed to...
pass on your work.
Yeah, for all it's worth.
- What made you pick me?
- A look in your eye.
- You seemed to have half a brain.
- Thank you. What look?
That look...
curious, searching,
unsatisfied,
slightly pissed off.
Why didn't you pick
your daughter?
Leave it alone.
- Why do you refuse to talk about her?
- Leave it.
She wants to see you.
I say we talk about it.
Hmm.
I was wrong
about you, "Juha".
- Explain that.
- Tell them to open this door.
You're not the one, "Juha".
- I'm not the one?
- No.
I'm not the one
who cut your medication?
I'm not the one to say if
you're competent for a hearing,
a chance of getting outta here?
- I'm the one, Ethan.
- Are you?
I'm the one.
- The one in control, huh?
- Yes.
- Who's in control?
So who is in control, huh?
Are you?
Am I?
The guards outside?
The warden in his office?
Yeah?
Who's in control?
Testing, testing, testing.
One, two, three, four.
Dr Ethan Powell,
interviewing Dr Theo Caulder.
Now, this will be a very simple test.
Pass or fail, life or death.
Ready, "Juha"? Now, you write on
this paper what I have taken from you.
What have you lost?
Write it! Write it!
Wrong. You never had control.
You only thought you had it.
An illusion, "Tabibu Juha"!
And what do you control
for sure, huh?
The volume on your stereo, the air
conditioning in your car? What else?
What else?
All right.
Another chance. You were nervous.
Too much pressure. Try again.
What have you lost?
What did I take?
Write it. Write it!
You're a fool, "Juha".
- Ha!
Did you think
you were free?
Where were you going at 2:00 today?
Into the gym, right?
In the morning,
your wake-up call.
In the middle of the night when you wake
up sweating, with your heart pounding.
What is it that has you all tied up,
"Juha", tied up in little knots?
Is it ambition?
Yeah.
You're no mystery
to me, boy.
I used to be you.
Okay. One last chance.
You think I won't do it?
What's one psychiatrist
less to the world?
I'm already deep in the pit.
So what can they do to me?
Last try.
Get it right.
What have you lost?
What did I take from you?
Write it.
Yeah.
Congratulations.
You're a student,
after all.
And you've lost nothing
but your illusions...
and a little bit
of skin.
- Hi.
What happened
to your face?
Gets a little rough
in there sometimes.
Well, what happened
to it?
Duct tape.
Oh.
- My father did this to you?
- Yes.
- What did he do?
- He was teaching me.
Looks like
a pretty tough class.
Are you gonna quit now?
No. I never quit.
Even when I'm doing something
really stupid, I never quit.
- Are you like that?
- No.
I once played solitaire for 48 games
straight until I won.
Solitaire, huh?
That figures.
I don't have time
for a lot of people.
Do you have time
for one?
Don't get nervous.
I didn't mean me.
Uh, want a drink?
- Yes.
- Let's go out.
Two cars.
No date.
You know, it's all right if you need
to hold on to somebody for a minute.
It's all right
if you don't.
- Doc, you won't believe this.
- What is it?
Just see for yourself, Doc.
You got to see it for yourself.
Doc, what you doing?
Hey, Doc,
what do you make of it?
What is this?
Not finished.
- Ethan...
- Take your time, Doc.
- What are you making here?
- The true history of mankind.
It's a true history.
No fiction, no lie.
Africa,
two million years ago.
Humans. Then they moved.
Migrated.
Ten thousand years ago,
civilization. You.
This is me?
Yeah, and me too. Us.
Takers. Who are
the blue people?
They're tribal societies...
hunters, gatherers, planters.
They never killed more animals
than they could use.
They never ploughed more land
than they needed.
They fought, but they never waged war.
Never exterminated.
They had a place in the world.
And in the world, they were part of it.
And they shared it.
We changed all that.
Now, what, are we supposed to change it
back? What are we supposed to do?
Move.
- Move where?
- Out of my way.
What, are we supposed to unbuild
the cities, wander off into the jungle?
A stupid, specious argument.
You figure it out.
- I'm busy.
- You're a pain in the neck, Ethan.
I know.
Now get out.
Dominion.
What?
We have only one thing
to give up... our dominion.
We don't own the world.
We're not kings here,
not gods.
Can we give that up?
Too precious,
all that control?
Too tempting,
being a god?
Where's my card?
I still don't have my card.
My card! Where...
Show me my... That's not mine.
- I want my card. Do you have my card?
- I got a box here!
I have a box here
with everybody's name in it!
It is mine! Give me that!
Show me the card!
I want to see
my ace of diamonds.
- Can you hit that?
- Ace of diamonds! Show it to me!
- Bang that hard. Bang, bang, bang!
- I didn't do it.
I have a box here
with everyone's name in it!
All of you
are in this box.
I have picked one name.
This is the name of the person
that will go outside today.
We're not using the ace any more.
Understand?
Each day I will pick
one name from this box,
and that person
will go outside.
Then I will set his name aside,
and the next day I'll pick a new name.
Everybody will have
their equal turn.
And today
it's Lester Rodman.
Where are you?
Lester Rodman.
Lester Rodman?
Lester Rodman,
where are you?
- Lester Rodman, today
you get to go outside.
- All right!
Let's find that ace.
Come on. Who's got that ace?
- Who the hell's got it?
- 'Cause I want it!
- We're not using the ace any more.
- Today Lester Rodman goes out...
- Come on. Let's see the cards.
Let's see your card.
Come on.
You got the ace, Pete?
How about you, Ethan?
You got the ace?
Come on, now.
Let me see that card.
Don't be shy.
Let's see your card.
- Dacks.
- Let me see it.
What was that?
Was that a look?
Dacks, damn it, don't.
The cards are finished.
The cards are garbage.
Do you understand?
You throw 'em away.
We're not using the ace any more.
Everybody goes outside.
Everybody goes.
Everybody goes!
Everybody goes outside!
- Everybody goes!
- Everybody goes outside!
Everybody goes outside!
- Everybody goes.
- Outside, everybody!
Pick up those pieces!
Everybody goes outside!
Dacks, damn it, you hit him again,
I'll have you up on charges.
Pick 'em up.
Son of a bitch.
Lester Rodman goes today.
Maybe you go tomorrow.
No cards. No ace.
No fighting.
Let's go, Lester.
- Haven't you learned anything yet?
- I guess not.
That coffee's been burning
for nine hours.
After ten,
use the instant.
It's in the top cupboard.
Well, how's
the medical staff today?
Fine, sir. Fine.
Splendid.
You fine, too,
Dr Caulder?
Doing okay. Can I get you
some coffee, Warden?
I'm not here for coffee.
- Okay.
- I'm here to talk about...
that little episode
in the gymnasium today.
We worked out
a different system.
You think you can walk into
my institution, start changing
rules and causing riots?
- There was no riot.
- The prisoners refused orders,
and my guards had to use
force because of you.
The force wasn't necessary.
All the violence came from Mr Dacks.
He was trying
to provoke Powell.
Powell is dangerous, and he was
dealt with as a dangerous psychotic.
No, no, no.
He offered no danger, none.
Dr Murray, did Powell
behave in a threatening way...
at any time?
No.
- I'll have a talk with Mr Dacks.
- Splendid.
Meanwhile, your little game
compromised my authority...
and the authority
of my guards.
Do you know what that means
at a maximum security prison?
You put everyone at risk.
The safety of every man here rests with
me, Caulder, and I can't trust you.
And I want you out.
You have ten days.
And I'm being generous.
I have 15 days left in my evaluation.
I'll leave when I'm finished.
Now you have seven days.
- How does he have the...
- Hang on a second.
How does he have the right
to cut my evaluation time?
He doesn't,
but he has the power
to kick you out...
whenever he wants to
and bring in somebody else.
So write your conclusion.
Wrap it up.
If I have more time, I think I can
get him out of there.
What are you
talking about?
The hearing. I think
when the judge hears the man...
who he is, what he has to say...
I think he'll walk out of there.
You're not his defence attorney.
You're not his pal.
What are you after?
- Big time ending for the book?
- Not about a book.
- It's not about my career...
- It should be.
Theo, you walked
into this case...
under my guarantee,
with an opportunity
to further yourself.
Now, are you willing to put
all that at risk possibly,
damage your career
possibly,
embarrass me?
Sorry, yes.
Then stop complaining about the time
you have left and use it.
Push the man.
Shake him.
- Where does the violence come from?
- I'm not sure...
- The gorillas?
- I'm not sure of the connection.
Well, find it.
The only way he is ever going
to get out of that place...
is for you to make that judge
feel that Powell is sane and safe.
You show where
the violence came from,
and you show
that the violence has gone.
- Can you do that?
- Yes.
Good.
You're on your own.
Thanks.
- See you later.
- I'll call you later.
Okay.
Hello.
This is a surprise.
Sorry. I, uh...
- The message said you'd be home
after 7:00, so...
- So you came by to check?
Were you hall monitor
in school?
Yes, I was.
Funny, I never got a sense
of you in your parents' house.
- This is definitely more...
- Messy?
More you.
So...
what did he do to you
this time?
I don't see
any cuts or bruises.
This time
it wasn't him.
I only have seven days left
with your father. That's it.
Are they going to take
the case away from you?
Case.
It's not a...
not a case any more.
It's not a book either.
He may break my neck tomorrow, but I
think I'm becoming a friend of his...
and his student.
His "Tabibu Juha".
He calls you that?
I think "Tabibu"
means "doctor".
Yes, it does.
What does "Juha" mean?
"Juha" means...
"idiot".
Yeah.
Well, I must be, because
I can't figure this one out.
He knows I can't bring
a gorilla into his cell and...
What?
- Where are we going?
- Fresh air, a ride in the country.
You'll like it. It's wilderness
all the way. They're waiting for us.
Who? What are you
planning, "Juha"?
I'm not your idiot any more.
- You finally looked it up.
- No.
Your daughter told me.
Watch your step.
The gorillas are
in the cage room now.
- Whoa!
Jesus Christ.
The old silverback's
been with us the longest.
You remember him, Dr Powell.
He's the one you...
I'm sorry. We need
to be alone in here.
The restraints?
I'll put them back on him
before we leave.
You understand if he comes out of
that door without them on...
I thought you'd feel
safer here.
I thought if you were around them,
you'd talk to me.
Tell me about the violence,
about the killing.
These are shadows
of gorillas.
Born in cages.
Only the old male...
he was free once.
Still alive.
Goliath.
I named him that.
I brought him here.
This cage has broken him.
Broken his heart,
broken his mind.
Made him insane.
I did that.
I understand that, Ethan.
I do.
But I need to know
about the killing.
There's a female
just like that one.
Was there ever
any violence among them?
Was there any violence
towards you?
There were warnings.
Warnings.
She was a good mother
and a good teacher.
The baby was always protected,
always instructed.
Always groomed,
always...
touched,
safe.
She used to watch
over him,
the way the old silverback
used to watch over...
all of us,
even me.
It's an amazing...
feeling, Theo,
to be watched over.
I discovered
in that look of his...
more than watchfulness...
tolerance,
acceptance.
- In fact, he was...
Ethan?
Ethan, what is it?
- What is it?
What's wrong?
- Shh. Shh.
- Shh.
It was me.
They'd found my things.
Been tracking me.
So I brought them.
I brought the... takers...
and death.
Still he looks at me
without blame.
Because you're
not to blame,
not for any of it.
You were just defending
your family.
- Ethan, close it.
- He won't come out.
You see?
Even if he can.
Not far from here is a fence, and on
the other side of that fence is freedom,
and he can smell it.
He'll never try
to get there,
'cause he's given up.
By now he thinks freedom
is something he dreamed.
And you?
Have you given up?
Because we have a chance to get you
out of here now, a good chance.
This is all I need...
what you've told me.
It's not just something
you dreamed.
It's real.
- I'd like you to wear this
to the hearing today.
- Where'd you get that?
Lyn brought it.
She's still here.
- Ethan, you can do this.
- Leave it alone.
What are you so afraid of?
I don't want to hurt her.
You've already done that.
Remember the first thing you said
to me? The first word? Remember?
You told me to tell
your daughter goodbye.
Tell her yourself.
I don't know what to say.
How are you?
That sounds stupid,
I guess.
I miss you.
Your father is a fool.
If you were just born, I would
pick you up and hold you...
and take you everywhere with me
and never walk away from you.
You're such
a treasure, Lyn.
You're so much better
than your father. You don't hate.
You don't even hate me.
You know that
when I went away from you,
I always took you
with me, inside.
I would love
to believe that.
Well, this is all
I have left for you.
It's the only possession
I kept.
You'll wait in your cell
till I come and get you.
The van'll be here in 25 minutes.
The hearing starts at 4:00. Understand?
You'll change out of
that pretty blue suit...
and turn it over
for storage.
- Any questions?
- Sorry, Ethan.
Ethan, there was
nothing we could do.
Inside.
I said, "Inside"!
Stop hitting him!
- You think that's funny, Nicko?
- Just stop hitting him!
Ow!
- I got Dacks!
- Oh, you wanna play, Pete?
- No, no! Sorry, Mr Dacks.
- You think that's funny, Pete?
- Huh? You think that's funny?
- It was an accident.
- You want to play? Come here.
- No, you can't come in here.
You can't come in, Mr Dacks.
You can't come in.
No, Mr Dacks.
No, don't be bad, Mr Dacks.
You wanna play "Can't Come In"?
We'll play.
- No! Mr Dacks!
- Let's play, Pete.
- No!
- You wanna play, Pete?
- Well, let's play!
- Ow! No! Ow!
You want to play?
Think this is for fun?
Huh?
- Aah!
Damn it! Lock this place down!
- I want this place locked down!
Anderson, secure the block
and cuff that son of a bitch!
Get back in there!
Settle down!
- Shut up! Shut up!
I heard. You want
to stay for supper?
- I blew it. I lost him.
He's silent again.
It's over.
Let it go.
He was protecting
his family... again.
I should have been with him
every minute.
Let it go.
And don't worry...
about anything.
I'll speak to Josephson,
smooth things over.
I'll help you cut
your losses.
And his losses?
It's true, isn't it?
He'll never get out
of there.
It was never your job
to get him out of there.
Theo, there is nothing
to be done.
Know when to walk away.
You help the ones you can.
I'm sorry. I've let you down,
and I barged in here...
Theo.
If you don't let this end,
you'll do yourself damage.
You got involved...
emotionally. It happens.
Now you have to get
your focus back.
You're losing control.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Mealtime!
Line 'em up!
- You heard him. Let's go.
- Single file!
I'm ready,
I'm ready, I'm ready.
Dr Caulder,
what's wrong with him?
- Nicko, back in line.
- Dr Caulder...
Any change?
Not a word in three days.
- Sorry.
- Hey, ape man!
He said mealtime!
Can you leave him there,
Dacks?
Keep your hands
at your side!
I'm sorry, Ethan.
I don't know if you can hear me,
but this is my last day, so...
I put Dacks up on charges.
I still might be able to get you
that hearing, if you would just speak.
If you would just come back.
Okay, Ethan.
You asked me
a question once.
"What has you
all tied up in knots...
when you wake up sweating
in the middle of the night?"
You still wanna know?
I've been thinking about it.
I've been thinking about it a lot.
It's not the work.
I love the work.
I've always loved the work.
It's the game.
The game, Ethan.
And I was so good at it.
I made sure all
the right people liked me.
At night, I'd do
the checklist in my mind.
Am I cool with Ben Hillard?
Am I cool with Dr Josephson?
Am I cool with all the people
who can help me?
who can hurt me?
Nobody thought I was weak
or a loser.
There was nobody
I was offending,
nobody I loved.
"That" game, Ethan.
But guess what?
You taught me how
to live outside of the game.
You taught me how to live.
And you know what
scares me even more?
That I'm going back in.
"Forgive me, Ben.
Put me back in the game."
"I'll make you like me again!
I'll do the work."
"I'll do all the work,
just put me back in the game!"
And do you wanna know...
You wanna know the psychology
behind this?
Now, pay attention,
because I'm good at this.
I'm trying not to say
goodbye to you.
I'll miss you.
I'm trying to forget you.
Ethan Powell, case closed.
Case closed!
Look at me.
- Come on!
Oh, come on!
- Take the bat
off your shoulders, you bum!
- Calm down, Dacks!
Hey, on a three-two count you gotta
protect the plate, you moron!
- Three and one,
Dacks, not three and two.
- First base.
- I would protect the plate.
- We're on first base.
- You gotta protect the plate.
- Right, the plate.
- Protect the plate.
- You see? You see? You see?
You take the lumber off
the shelf and you get a hit.
- Peter! Hey, come on!
- Pete, put it back in! Pete, please!
- Put it back in, Pete!
- Hey, Pete!
Give me the plug, Pete!
Give me the plug!
- Give me the plug now!
- Stop! Stop it!
Peter, give Guard Anderson
the plug. It's his birthday.
That's right, Pete.
It's my birthday.
You wanna give me
a present?
Come on, buddy.
Let me have it.
- That's it. Let go.
- All right, all right.
- Plug it in. Come on.
- There you go.
Are you gonna leave it alone now?
- For you.
- Okay. For me.
Hey, Dr Caulder's here!
Glad to see you, Doc.
Hey! Caulder's back!
Welcome back, Doctor!
Anything he does out there
is gonna come down on my head,
and I'm gonna come down
on yours!
Heard you were long gone
back to the city. I thought
you were all through here.
- I came back to talk to Powell.
- Well, your highflier's
gone out the window!
Went through a hole
in the fence.
We think he scaled the other one.
He must have had some help!
And he even wrote
a little note... to you!
Can you make heads or tails
of that? I sure can't.
What?
- You're never gonna find him.
- You know where he is?
You're never
gonna find him.
- If you got any idea where...
- If you're holding out on me,
you could be aiding an escapee.
That is a felony, and I could
have you arrested for that!
I'm beginning
to like it here.
"Dear Theo."
"I'm sorry I'm not there
to say goodbye."
"You were right.
Freedom is not just a dream."
"It's there on the other side of those
fences we build all by ourselves."
"Thank you for giving me hope and for
giving me back my daughter."
"And I thank you, Theo, for sharing
this journey with me."
"Your friend, Ethan."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org