Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Commencing data uplink,
establishing connection.
Okay.
Beam me to Burma, Scotty.
Satellite online, sir.
Snowman to Reindeer,
pick a visual on the target.
Roger, Snowman. Target picked.
Roger that. We have video confirmation,
and you're coming in 4 by 4.
Locking complete.
Reindeer, transpo is on.
Look at all those poppies.
Travis, I'm almost liking you now.
Copy that. Stand by.
Don't move. We got company.
No, sir. Don't go.
Shit!
Snowman, this is Reindeer. Hot evac.
Get out of here.
Get them out of there.
Gray smoke in sight,
approaching extraction point.
Go.
Come on! Don't run!
The package is in the box. Let's go.
You'll be all right.
We live right...
and we die right.
You're not dying, man. You'll be all right.
- You're a lying motherfucker.
- Come on, now.
You're not dying, man.
I gotta lie down, man.
Shit!
I will continue working to give Tokyo
and Japan a better future.
Vote for me, vote for Takayama.
In order to secure our cities and ports,
I intend to enact the legislation...
...concerning the deportation of immigrants
with questionable origins.
These countries need to understand
that it is necessary to protect our borders.
How would you handle foreign residents'
opposition to the new legislation?
All questions should be directed
to my press secretary.
To all my brothers,
today we stand in front of
Quang Quang, the God of War.
We swear with blood our loyalty to him.
When we shed our blood,
we will become family
Whether for good or bad,
we must stick together.
Gentlemen.
Good afternoon.
Well done.
I want to toast you on a job well done.
- Cheers to the Governor.
- Cheers.
He's in a better place now.
...we live together and we die together...
I am Chinese,
I do not want to serve the Japanese.
I refuse to work for you, so I will not swear.
Time to go.
- Block.
- Hi. John Davidson, FBI.
Listen, I'm calling
regarding the governor's assassination.
- What about it?
- Well, we need your help.
Johnny, it's local. It's not my party.
We're thinking it's a Yakuza hit...
and we're hoping that you have someone
that has some knowledge in that field.
Yakuza?
Yeah, I've got someone.
You're gonna owe me big for this one.
How have you been?
Things are good. How about you?
I've been working very hard.
So have I.
So here it is, swords of this caliber
don't come up for sale anymore.
I would pay twice this amount
for instruction from you.
I'm afraid I'm not a teacher.
There is no one else as good as you.
That isn't true at all, I just sell swords.
But I heard a legend
that you cut off a man's arm in a duel.
No, that's just foolish.
But you have the skills of old masters.
Listen, I wouldn't encourage fighting.
Excuse me for a second.
Hello.
Travis?
Guess who.
Sir.
Hello?
Okay, baby, I need you and your team
up on him the second he leaves here.
All the usual assets?
- Of course, baby, anything you need.
- Good.
I'll be in touch. And don't call me "baby."
That would be meant for me.
- You two know each other?
- Yeah.
For a long time.
But I'm assigning you to him for right now.
Just try to stay with him.
And keep me posted.
Didn't take you that long to get here.
Yeah, I was in the area.
In a nutshell,
the Governor made a lot of enemies...
when he stated his plan to begin
the deportation of certain people.
So why are we involved?
The FBI feels sure it's terrorist related.
That makes it a concern
for the United States.
We have intel that the local Yakuza...
have been farming themselves out
for some reason.
I've been in this game a long time.
Doesn't make sense to me that
the Yakuza would be involved in politics.
Anything is possible.
Yeah, I suppose so.
That's why I brought you in, big papa.
Nobody knows the bad guys like you do.
But with homeland security,
the FBI is on board.
I'm aware.
I'll gather some intel, feed it back to you,
and you can give it to them.
You know, life is never that simple.
This is Agent Mac.
He's going to be working with you.
- How do you do, Agent Mac?
- I'm good, thank you.
- And what do you do?
- I'm an FBI field agent.
So in the event
that there really is terrorist involvement...
why don't you have the FBI
put together a special response team...
and get this boy a gun.
Always great seeing you, Travis.
That went well.
The shooter exited
on a sport bike going East.
FBI.
It was quick. It was loud.
It just came out of nowhere.
Welcome to the crime scene.
- Travis.
- Hello, Inspector.
I need copies
of all the physical evidence here.
Sure.
Immediately, I want copies
of all the surveillance tapes.
- You hear?
- Okay.
So this is the security tape
for the government's incident?
Guy on the right. Little bit closer.
See that gold emblem on his neck?
See if you can come real close on that
for me.
- I wanna take a look at that.
- Okay, I got you.
- How about that?
- Okay.
Not only do these guys look Chinese,
but that one's Quang Quang.
These guys are Tongs.
I've got somebody I've gotta go talk to.
- Can you get me a copy of this?
- Yeah, sure.
Dai-Ryu, it's been a long time.
Please sit down.
What a surprise.
You look younger and taller.
And I see
you're still reading the same old books.
Just a simple man passing the time.
Tell me, what brings you today?
I've heard a rumor about an alliance
between the Tongs and the Yakuza.
I have a little problem with the Yakuza,
but I don't want one with the Tongs.
So I was wondering
if you'd talk to them for me.
Yakuza.
I heard the rumors in the street.
I'll help you.
I'll talk with them
and I'll make sure they leave the situation.
Wait.
Since you surprised me...
I'm going to surprise you. Mei Ling.
Look who has returned.
Master.
- Her skills have much improved.
- She's gotten big.
She's been my shield. Now she's yours.
Okay. I'll see you soon.
Chen and I have been in business
for two years.
He told me you have
a sophisticated distribution network.
Yes.
With his pachinko parlors
and my fish business...
we can round the cash into US dollars...
and ship product everywhere
almost unnoticed.
What can I do for you?
Golden Triangle.
So we're meeting a Zaibatsu,
a leader in the banking world.
- But who are we?
- Obviously you're not a federal agent.
Obviously I'm not a federal agent.
Nobody knows what we do,
and that's better.
I want you to just play a role for me.
You're my martial arts student.
You're a fish out of water, trying to learn
how to swim and that will be that.
If it's okay, I wanted to ask you
a couple of questions...
about the local problems going on here.
Do you think there's any possibility...
that the Tongs and the Yakuza
are getting into big business?
A new generation of Yakuza
is starting to interfere with our business.
One of our executives
was assassinated yesterday.
There were rules Yakuza respected
and followed in the past.
Obviously, these rules do not apply
to the new generation.
It would make sense for us to assist you.
I will assist you in any way possible.
Thank you so much, Sensei.
I was hoping you'd say that.
That's why I came. Thank you.
Take a look...
Beautiful women can often lead you to bliss.
Sensei, please excuse me.
- Travis.
- Yeah?
How's it going?
Peachy keen.
Hold them longer.
Of course.
Good.
So, young man...
you are his deshi?
Deshi?
His student.
Yes, student.
What have you studied?
Kendo?
Lyai.
Kendo.
Oh, yeah.
What school?
School?
UCLA.
Go, Bruins.
What have you got?
Jahto, look up the word.
Tongs and Yakuza are working together.
Got something for you.
Be patient and leave me alone, all right?
You have to understand something. A high
government official was just assassinated.
It's only natural
that Intelligence would assume...
terrorism may have been involved.
So the Agency is gonna watch us
until they decide...
how the situation should turn out.
- What, they decide?
- That's right.
80% of the CIA's activity
goes to disinformation.
They pay close attention to the situation...
and in the end
they'll decide what happened...
in order to fit their agenda.
I'm gonna pull over here,
I want you to jump in...
take the driver's seat and drive.
Go north,
then swing back around and pick me up.
- 15 minutes, you hear?
- Yes, sir.
Nayako-san, you look so beautiful today.
These walls have many ears.
Yeah, I know.
But I'm always happy to see you.
Actually, I wanted to see
if you could get any information...
on the assassination of the Governor.
Where should I look?
I don't know if you know anybody...
that has a good connection
with the Yakuza?
There is a tattoo artist.
He is an old friend of my family.
He knows a lot about the Yakuza.
I'll call him.
I'm sure he'll be pleased to hear from you.
So, I love you. You be good.
- Where is he?
- He's leaving Fusion.
- What's a fusion?
- Fusion is Nayako's club.
Good, she's an asset of his.
Move it, move it.
Ten thousand dollars.
Now Kojima can't touch us.
We're gonna
just jump into this little kissaten here.
Watch where you're walking, asshole!
Sorry.
Fucking round eyes!
Don't fuck with me, man.
May I take your order?
Two cervezas, por favor.
Can you give me a second?
I'm sorry, I'm confused.
Why're you taking me to all these places?
This is my neighborhood, I grew up here.
That's the truth.
- No bullshit.
- Yeah.
That's great.
But what does this have to do
with the Governor's assassination?
This neighborhood is the neighborhood...
where all organized crime
gathers and does their thing.
We got Tongs, we got Yakuza.
All kinds of organized crime,
they are all centralized here.
There is major struggle for turf.
Major struggle for power.
Most of that power comes from heroin.
- Or as we call it here, Shabu.
- Shabu.
- Yeah.
- So...
Now you see, here's a perfect example.
Our little Yakuza friend is back.
Only this time, it seems like
he's got two Chinese boys with him.
That's strange.
You would have never have seen that
10 years ago.
Will you excuse me for just one second?
You aren't ready for a fight yet.
You want to fight, come back in 10 years.
Please tell me you're kidding.
You didn't just have an AD.
- Sorry, that was an accident.
- Are you out of your mind?
- I got excited.
- You got excited?
I've never seen or heard of such a thing.
Look who's here.
You're a cop, you deal with them.
I don't exist.
Fuck!
One quick call to my boss,
and everything is gonna be A-okay.
A-okay?
I need Block now.
What the fuck did he do?
Three Yakuza injured and two Chinese
hanging out in Intensive Care?
You should have seen him. God, he's fast.
You fired a weapon in public.
Shit like that could destroy
everything we have with Japan.
Sorry, that was an accident.
Listen to this.
American version of the current government
is not acceptable.
We'll continue to use force
until our demands are met.
You're clearly moving
in the wrong direction.
Has the lab heard this? What did they say?
We're working on it.
What makes you think
we're moving in the wrong direction?
This, for all we know, could be an attempt
to mislead us. We don't know.
So, if you don't mind, I'd like to go
to the lab and check it out myself.
- Go.
- Thank you.
Hello.
I'm Dai-Ryu.
Sensei is waiting for you.
I'm Dai-Ryu. Nayako sent me here.
So you must be Travis-san.
Please come this way.
Thank you.
So what is it that you want to know.
From my Nayako I've heard a lot about you.
She says you know a lot about the Yakuza.
I try to keep a low profile.
Check out Kuroda.
Kuroda.
Apparently, he made a pact with the Chinese
Tongs to monopolize the drug trade.
It seems like if this Kuroda
has that much strength...
and a direct connection with Myanmar...
maybe he can eat all the other families
and take over.
There is only one Yakuza player
who is capable of defeating Kuroda,
his name is Kojima.
But Kojima's boss is too old,
spending much of his time in his garden.
He doesn't care about the current turf war.
This Kojima guy,
is there any way you could maybe...
get me a meeting with him?
If you want.
As long as I have total access to Burma...
the Tongs are welcome to grow and prosper
anywhere I have business.
Together we win Japan.
And eventually...
America.
Don't worry, it happens to the best of us.
Go inside, kid.
Are you ready to be a man?
My behavior...
at the street market was unforgivable.
My shame is beyond what I can describe.
Please accept this as a token...
of my regret.
You're crazy.
Not at all.
Thank you for coming.
Clean it up.
Travis, they serve hamburgers here?
Stop talking shit.
I'm just going to wait outside.
You found yourself a new deshi.
What's up, dog?
Yeah, don't worry about it.
May I?
Yes, please.
So you are Dai-Ryu san.
Yes, some people call me that.
So tell me your story.
I've heard that people respect you
for your integrity in the Yakuza world.
I heard the same about you.
Actually, we have other things in common.
You want to get rid of Kuroda...
...and I feel the same.
Kuroda wishes
to send a message to Kojima.
Time to die.
I have a good reason to kill Kuroda.
Heroin trade?
That's not all.
Listen, I live as a Yakuza...
...and I chose my destiny.
I grew up in this city, in the chaos
and devastation that followed the war.
People were living in despair
and struggling in darkness.
It was a tragedy.
So, tell me about your boss in there.
Boss?
Yeah, your boss. Who you work for.
Tell me about him.
- Boss?
- Never mind.
Now fifty years later,
the Yakuza has changed.
The younger Yakuza completely ignore
our rules and tradition of "Jingi".
These scumbags live for nothing but money.
And, by aligning themselves
with foreigners,
they're becoming too powerful.
I won't tolerate their existence.
It'll be interesting to see
who will get Kuroda first, you or I.
That's right. It will be a contest between us.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Kuroda sends his love.
Good morning, darling.
Good morning, my darling.
Here it is.
But I can't do this, can I?
No, you can't do this.
It's just like it always is.
You stay safe
and you protect your anonymity.
I understand.
See you in a while.
Okay. Bye.
Sit.
So, what's the problem?
What is this?
Some girl dropped it off.
Kuroda, this is a warning...
A mystery man sending me a letter...
at your place.
Strange.
Hello?
It's me.
Keep an eye out for Kojima's men.
Get ready.
I'd like to stay. But I must go.
I have other things to take care of.
I'm sorry I asked you to come so suddenly.
I just had some things
I really wanted to talk to you about.
I came as fast as I could.
Let's walk a little bit.
Let's sit here.
I wanna talk to you. Come, sit.
What is it?
You know...
I've never had the best luck with women.
In fact, you could probably say...
I haven't had any luck at all.
But for the first time in my life...
I found somebody that I really love.
Is that a proposal?
You can call it a proposal.
Yes, I'm proposing to you.
I am so pleased to hear that.
So I guess that means yes.
The only reason why I have
been doing this job is to help you.
I have been hiding my feeling from you.
I'm very sorry...
and all I can do is promise you a better life.
I'm gonna quit this right away.
One last piece of work, that's it,
and then I'm finished.
I'll go wherever you decide to go.
Together, we'll find some place
really beautiful and quiet...
and lead a great life together.
I'll go wherever you want.
Promise?
Promise me...
...let's do Yubikiri vow.
Yubikiri, this I vow. If you ever break it,
I'll make you drink one thousand needles.
Yubi-kitta!
Hai.
What can I do for you?
I come to you on behalf of a friend
who had the incident at the street market.
I ask you as a favor
that you remove yourself...
from this incident's possible reprisal.
Sit down, please.
- Hi.
- Hey.
You know the guy
that put our guys in the hospital?
He's an American.
The American at the street market?
Yeah, he wants a truce.
Sounds like a problem to me.
That's what I think.
He seems to want an answer right now.
- Okay, take care of it.
- No problem.
Chill!
Turn it off.
There is an American
asking about my business.
American?
An American that grew up in Japan.
He's been talking to Yakuza dinosaurs
like Kojima.
Apparently, he is a sword master.
A sword master?
Is everything okay with the governor's case?
There are no sword fights
in this day and age.
But, it would be good
if I learned how to use a sword.
Maybe from this American.
A fight is won not by technique...
...but by the most furious mind.
Take it easy, boss.
How about going to the club and relaxing?
That sounds good. Let's pick up some girls.
You two go, I need to think.
Why do you think I've been sucking up
to the Chinese for?
I'm getting close...
...so close to getting everything
I ever wanted.
Now I have an American snooping around?
I told you two to go!
Let me introduce to you
the hottest girl in this club.
Check out her fishnet stockings.
Travis, do you know this man?
Yes, I do.
Travis, sorry for interrupting you.
It's kind of a sudden visit, isn't it?
Is everything okay?
Watch yourself.
You've been asking a lot of questions
on the street.
Now...
the street is starting
to ask questions about you.
Thanks for the warning.
There is an abandoned hotel
at the edge of town.
We monitored it for the last few weeks.
Kuroda's assassins are living
on the second floor.
It may be a place of interest to you.
Thank you for that intel,
it's very nice of you.
Is that a croissant on your head?
- How are you?
- Fine.
Everything's going good here?
I bought this for you.
It's a beautiful antique,
It's from the Edo Period.
Geishas have used this...
and I thought of you
because you wear a kimono so nicely.
It's beautiful...
...thank you.
I will treasure it forever.
Thank you.
Here is a singing Robo-Cop.
- Travis.
- That's okay.
I'm so sorry to bother you,
but check this out. Nice to meet you.
I just got off the phone
with the guys from the lab.
Turns out
that the tape was made at a fish market.
Skigi, something like that.
Maybe that rings a bell.
But all that background noise
apparently just gave the whole thing away.
It would have been nice
if you had called me. I'm here, I'm busy.
I'm in the middle of something.
Sorry about that.
But I figured, being partners...
I'm gonna give you one more chance.
You go over there to the fish market...
do some surveillance, take some pictures...
long-lens, remote stuff.
Don't be seen, and if it's good...
- call me.
- Okay, cool.
And no more ADs.
Nice to meet you.
He's young, you know.
"Do some remote stuff with a long-lens...
"take some pictures at the fish market."
What does he think I am, a rookie?
I hate this shit.
No guns. Put the guns away.
- Hands up.
- Okay.
I'm an inspector. Move over here.
Come on, move over here. Back the fuck up.
Chill, surfer dude!
I don't speak your language, motherfucker.
You're in a lot of trouble. Big trouble.
I gotta report to my boss
and you're not gonna like that.
- You are dead.
- Really?
I don't exist. All right?
It's a show time.
Taxi!
I'm on to something here.
I found where the tape was made.
It's a fish-packing warehouse.
And get this, I found a finger...
a severed pinkie finger
wrapped in a piece of silk.
I told you, "Do not go in there."
I told you "remote surveillance."
You know what remote surveillance means?
What is wrong with you?
If you get yourself killed on my watch,
I'll kill you again.
The battery's dying.
I found a piece of paper with an address.
It's like an invoice or something.
I'm going to go check that out.
Where's he going?
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say he's headed for the Ginza.
Is he in an apartment building?
Yeah. Our apartment building.
How does he know she's there?
You're not as sharp as you used to be.
Sharp enough for you.
You'd have kind of disappointed me
if I'd got the drop on you.
That's never gonna happen.
You think?
I like you much better like this.
I like the delivery boy myself.
The delivery boy was good.
It was a very sexy touch.
Why is Block having me
follow you around Japan?
United States government is always
particularly fascinated in any enterprise...
that could maybe bring income
to their enemies.
Why don't I go put on
something more appropriate...
and then we'll go to the office?
And don't look at my ass.
Do you like takoyaki?
Let's go for a little drive.
Open the fucking door.
- What the fuck do you want?
- What do you want...
Mr. FBI?
Are you looking for this?
Fuck you.
All right. Easy.
Let's all take it easy here.
What the fuck are you looking at, smiley?
- Who, me?
- Yeah, fuck you!
Fuck me?
Come on.
Chen, are you crazy?
Yeah, I'm crazy.
Come on.
My guess is the Governor's assassination
was a ruse by Kuroda...
to divert attention from him.
What's this all about?
This gives him a major alliance
between the Yakuza and the Tongs...
so that they could get a direct link
for the heroin out of Burma.
This is Kuroda's renovated temple
just outside of Tokyo.
No one's seen the kid.
That's because you had no surveillance
at the fish market.
He ain't around, and he's assigned to you.
He's still working for me.
I got him taking plates...
and photographs. He'll be fine.
That's fine. In the meantime...
will you please tell me
what you have got on the Yakuza?
- I'm working on that.
- Good. I'm glad.
Kojima, this is a friend. Kuroda will kill you.
Who's this?
Listen to me, time is running out.
Travis, thank you for telling me.
That's what I thought.
Thank you.
Get the door.
I can't put up
with that bastard Kuroda anymore.
We've already lost five people this month.
We are in danger
of losing our control, boss.
That bastard's involvement
with the Chinese makes it worse.
Boss, we are on the verge
of being wiped out.
I strongly request your consent.
For 60 years, I've been through hell
in this business.
On the verge of survival?
We've been there before.
Don't lose your head now.
Boss, Kuroda conspires with the Chinese
and parades around
with the fortune he's amassed.
With his staggering success,
he is expanding into a huge organization.
We have to take action before it's too late.
Boss!
Kojima says goodbye.
Holy cow.
What the hell?
Call Kuroda.
Some happened here.
They've all been killed... by sword.
It looks like Kojima's work.
This cannot go unpunished.
We start at the top with Ishikawa.
That bastard, Kojima.
Relax.
Trust me.
Trust you?
Why? You got me into this shit.
You broke the agent's neck.
Are you prepared to take of the American
if I take care of Kojima's boss?
Yes.
Fuck you!
Yo, Bonsai fart.
What is it?
Time to go.
The reason why I came here is to inform you
my American friend
would like a meeting with you.
Alright.
You have woken the sleeping giant.
No, I promise.
I didn't tell Kojima people about you.
You fucking liar.
Get up all of you.
Go, get out!
Do you want to swing by
Nayako's club, Fusion?
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Hey, Travis.
Welcome to Fusion.
Please have a seat. Please.
You haven't forgotten about us, have you?
What are you talking about? You are
some of my most important customers.
Why are you so nervous?
Hurry up and get our drinks.
Would you excuse me?
Bring drinks for this table.
Hi, Fudomyo-O. These are Tongs.
I don't want to put you in the middle...
but when I signal you,
you'll know what to do.
Mei Ling, you set up the meeting.
You come with me, handle the Chinese.
In the back.
How did it go?
Good job.
- What are you doing here?
- Little mistake.
Why did you come here?
You should show him more respect.
He is a friend of Master Cheung.
I have no problem with the Yakuza
here in Tokyo...
but I thought it'd be better
if I didn't have a problem with the Tongs.
- But I'll leave that up to you.
- So?
We have Nayako.
Really?
If you have her, for your sake...
I hope she's okay.
We found Nayako. She's dead.
Listen, I'm going after Kuroda tonight.
I will finish them or die trying.
If you feel the same as I do,
I will not stop you from following me.
Otherwise, I will understand.
Nayako was a close friend of mine.
When I lost my family,
she was very kind to me.
What about your search for the men
that killed your family?
I know who killed my family.
Kuroda.
No one is fiercer than someone
who has nothing to live for.
What about her?
I can't have her death on my conscience.
She will stay here.
This one is so sharp.
I'll have to use this tonight.
This kills very well.
Okay, find Travis.
Using PLER to locate the asset.
Come on.
He's in a car.
- Where now?
- Heading east out of town.
I see, alright.
Chen is dead.
- You ready?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
To my American bitch.
Time to kill the American.
Why don't we sneak in the back?
'Cause I'm not in the mood for surprises.
I'm going right in the goddamn front door.
What the fuck are you doing here?
I'm just visiting the temple to pray.
Bring it on!
Are you the one...
...who killed Nayako?
You are dead.
Don't fuck with the Japanese, dude!
I shall beat you to death.
See you in hell.
Idiot! I told you not to come.
Do you want to die that badly?
I swore to fight with you
and die next to you.
Hey... Thanks.
Yo, punk.
Who are you?
Bring it on!
What is this?
Sushi.
You guys really eat this crap?
Are these your chopsticks?
Now, she is too hot to kill...
I've come to kill you.
I couldn't sleep well,
knowing I hadn't chopped off your balls yet.
Take your sword.
Let's settle our unfinished business.
Yeah, right!
I want you.
You're turning me on, girl.
Kiss me, please.
You son of a bitch.
Oh, too bad, no revenge.
Now watch this.
You alright?
I just got a new tattoo.
Finish him!
Looking for your friend?
Why are you hiding in here?
You're making me laugh, my American bitch.
Fuck you!
What the fuck is an American doing,
swinging around a sword?
You piece of shit.
Get your ass out of here.
You're living in the fucking past.
Times have changed!
Alright, let's do it.
Fuck you.
Come and get it!
Don't fuck with me.
Let's go home.
All right, tell me exactly what he did.
By the looks of this place, it looks like
he removed Kuroda completely.
You know what to do. Fast and beautiful.
I'll handle it.
All right, let's move out.
You got the gear. I'll take the right.
In here.
Start cleaning up.
I am pleased to announce to Mr. Kojima...
...once you drink down the sake...
...you'll officially become the new Godfather
of this family.
When you are ready,
please go ahead and drink it down.
I would like to close the ritual
with this traditional manner.
No DNA. Very clever.
Really nice job.
- What's this?
- I don't know. It came with the other one.
"Block, put this shield in the shadow box...
"and tell his parents
that Sean died valiantly in the line of duty.
"Travis."
Yeah, talk to me.
Travis? Guess who.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org