Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Come on,
come get some bread.
Come on.
Don,t you want any?
Here you go.
Go on.
So!
You,ve been ng them
permission to eat,
have you?
Eh? Eh?
My seed, eh?
Is that what you think?
Here. Take your end.
Tip the end.
That,s it.
Watch it.
Go ahead.
That,s it.
Gentle.
What,s he done?
Nothing.
Did he hit you?
Shame on you
for leng him.
His father was
my father,s journean.
Keep in.
All rightJock.
. Fawley.
Just take this off.
For 5 seconds.
ght. Stay sll,
eveone.
Come on, ifyou,re
coming, then.
You nished
your work?
Yeah.
Good boy.
Come on.
Come on, move.
ght.
Move. Come on.
Sor I,m going?
Yeah.
So am I.
Where are you
going, sir?
Chrisinster.
Why do you
have to go?
Do you see it?
Over there.
everything else
for a while.
You have to read
your books
when your friends
are out playing,
study every chance
you get.
One day,
it,ll all pay off.
I promise you.
Once you,re there,
everything,s
open to you.
You can become
anything you want.
You can choose
your future.
Man: Dinner.
Hurry upJude.
Have some
of this bread.
You staying and
eating with us todayJude?
No.
Thank you.
Whoa, look
at thatJude.
Have a piece of this cheese,
Jude. You,ll love it.
Who have you
got waiting, then?
A chip off
the old block, eh?
"Swiftly she rose
from the gray sea
like a mist. "
Ow!
Here,s the poet.
Nor me.
Anny.
None ofyou
threw it.
He,s all right.
A w, he,s shy.
Bet you think
I threw it.
No.
Well, I did.
But don,t tell anyone.
My name,s Arabella.
My father,s a pig breeder.
We were washing innards
for black pudding.
What?
Nothing.
I don,t work Sundays.
You can see me then.
Nothin, else?
some of the Greek
Testament.
Hoity toity.
Well, I need to,
if I,m going to get
into Christminster.
Ha ha!
Christminster?
Yes. I,m going
to be a scholar,
maybe even
a professor one day.
My, my.
You ever seen me
climb a tree?
No.
A!
Jude: I,lljust
tell him.
Arabella: We didn,t
do anything.
Where are you?
Get up, Abby.
Why?
Be careful.
It,s natural for a woman
to bring a live thing
into the world.
Aunt Drusilla:
Jude.
Yes?
It,s late.
To the bride
and the groom.
Lisa.
What?
Pass that
to Aunt Drusilla.
Aunt Drusilla.
This is for Aunt Drusilla.
What shall we
call her?
Rosie,s pick.
Rosie, what?
What about
Jemima Spot?
Jemima Spot.
Do you like that?
Jude: It isn,t
your own?
So?
What?
Haven,t you got enough
ofyour own hair?
Don,t you like it?
No.
Then I won,t wear it.
Leave it on.
I want to see us.
You can close your eyes
ifyou like...
and pretend it,s dark.
Jude.
Ask me nicely.
Ask you what?
Whatever you
want me to do.
I don,t know.
A!
He,s never gonna get here.
He,s probably
bloody drunk.
We,lljust have
to do it ourselves.
Be careful
with those.
Aunt Drusilla:
It,s a bit late
You should have
listened to me.
Please don,t say that.
Shall I get
your room ready?
No. I,d better go.
I knowyou think
I really believed
I was pregnant.
Can I help you?
This is nice.
It,s the same city:
maybe a 5minute walk
from Church Street
to Scum Street.
Why don,t we go over?
Why don,t we go over
and knock on their doors?
Because theye convinced us
this is the way it is.
No change.
Why change?
to win their argument.
Hello. I,m looking
forJude Fawley.
Thank you.
Jude Fawley?
I,m your cousin
Sue Bridehead.
Aunt Drusilla wrote
and told me
you were in Christminster.
Hello.
Don,t either ofyou
take this wrong,
but you don,t look
like cousins to me.
Why is that?
Because you,re
pretty and fine,
andJude here has got
this dour slab of stone for a face.
A big nose is a sign
of nobility.
Shut up, tinker.
Are you
superstitiousJude?
No.
Nor am I,
but I think
it,s better to be safe.
Don,t you?
away from
this university.
But it,s
wonderful here.
It,s all stone.
You,re talking
about the buildings.
I,m talking
about the scholars.
I was talking
about the scholars, too.
Thank you.
Uh!
Finish it.
How much are
these 2, please?
10 shillings.
You,re not going
to buy them?
Why not?
Would you like me
to wrap them up?
No, thank you.
Why have you
wrapped them up?
Because I don,t want
to give my landlady
You mean like me?
I didn,t know
you were a girl.
Do I irritate you?
No.
Even when I keep trying to prove
how much cleverer than you I am?
You are.
Don,t say that.
Why not?
Say something.
"Hominus similis
daeus quis chaedit ad Latin. "
Godlike the man
who sits at her side,
Nothing is left of me
each time I see her.
Beautiful.
Don,t know about that.
Quite common, I hear.
What do you think,
Jude?
You two are cousins.
You tell me.
Jude: Sue?
You,ll have to do
better than that.
That,s Wilks.
I had a row
with my landlady.
She found one ofmy statues and
threw it on the floor
Joe: Do you want
a hatJude?
What,s the problem?
It,s raining.
It,s what?
Have a beer.
I thought you were
the intelligent one.
Sue!
Jude Reading: "Sir,
I,ve read your letter with interest,
"andjudging from
your description ofyourself
"as a working man,
All I know is I,d lick them
on their own ground
Aye, but can you say
the creed in Latin, man?
Yes, I can!
I definitely can!
Excuse me.
Quiet, please!
Quiet!
The gentleman in the corner
Joe: Here,s your chance.
Jude: Sue!
Sue!
Jude.
I,ve been drinking,
Sue.
Will you let me in?
All right.
I can do it.
Jude.
You,ll learn more
than they can ever teach you.
I,m sure this is the last thing
you want to hear,
Since when did you stop
believing in them?
No!
Sue: DearestJude,
He is teaching
at a new school,
and I am studying
at a training college.
The rules here
are strict beyond belief,
and our visiting hours
are limited,
but I,d love
to see you again.
Your hands are rough,
Jude.
What,s wrong?
We,re lookin,
for somewhere to stay.
Don,t take children.
We,re lookin,
for somewhere to stay.
No. I,m sorry. No room.
Thank you. Thank you.
I love this place...
even though I know it looks down
on people like me.
The self taught,
too determined.
Takes 2 or 3 generations
to do what I tried to do in one.
Do you believe in God?
You think so? Yes.
Ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
How many times have you
missed a church service in your life?
Why?
What are you reading
at the moment?
Ha ha ha ha ha.
What do you
want with me?
Come home.
You don,t know
my badness.
Yes, I do.
You make me
hate Christianity and God
and whatever
has reduced you to this state.
It,s right
that I suffer.
It,s wrong...
that a woman
like you
should give up
her mind,
degrade herself
like this
Don,t talk to me
like that!
I,m sorry.
Come home.
No, I can,t.
It,s all rightJude. I know what
to do. We,ll talk in the morning.
Write to Arabella.
Ask her to take you back.
No. How can you, Sue?
You love me.
You love me, Sue.
Say it, Sue.
Say it.
Say it. Say it.
Not for me.
How are you?
All right.
You look well.
Do I?
I won't stop trying.
I promised you that.
Jude...
Do you love me?
You,ve always known.
Sue, come with me.
No Jude.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org