Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Ten and a half!
- Nine fifty!
- Twenty-five!
- I'll take it!
- How's July? July how?
- July's at 95 and a quarter.
Ninety-four and a half bid.
Hey, bonehead, moron!
- Moron? Moron this. At 95. At 95.
- Keep your pencil to yourself!
- 94 and 3 quarter bid for 300.
- Sold, 300!
- Buy 300, yes!
- 300, you idiot? Get out of my way.
300 lots of coffee futures?
You call that a hunch?
No, Richard. I call
that an opportunity.
300 lots in this market is not
an opportunity. It's a death wish.
- Oh, ye of little faith.
- No, no, no. Me of big mortgage.
- Hi, Maddy. What've you got?
- Flight 109 leaving J.F.K., 1:00 p. m.,
arriving Caracas
at 6:22 p. m.
- All right, all right.
- Aw, come on.
You're not still leaving,
after what you did in there?
I'm getting married to Charlotte.
I need the divorce from Patricia.
- Toiletries, shirts, socks-
- I don't believe this.
You're gonna leave me
with 5,100 tons of coffee?
Richard, I put up with you because
you're the best analyst on the Street.
You give me that same
patronizing little speech...
every time you play
one of your stupid hunches.
- Yeah? And what happens?
- I'm hospitalized, and the blood pressure medication is adjusted.
Uplink. You'll overnight in Caracas,
then fly to Canaima the next morning.
Thanks.
See ya in two days.
Unbelievable.
This thing might be quicker
if you used both engines!
Senor Kromwell?
That'd be me, Michael Cromwell,
with a "C."
Senor Cromwell with a "C." I am Abe
Botero with a "B," your attorney-at-law.
I am outrageously pleased
to meet with you.
Abe, Abe.
Let me go.
My car is right over here.
Do you have any more luggage?
I travel kinda light, Abe. So,
what's the deal? Where is Patricia?
Uh, we received this letter
from your wife today.
Senora Cromwell says that
she could not come to Canaima,
- but she wants to get you to Lipo Lipo.
- Wait a second.
I travel 3,000 miles to get here. She
doesn't show up? What's that about?
Abe has a saying:
He who knows what a woman wants,
knows everything,
but not even God
knows that.
Okay. If that's the way she wants
to play it, she's not gonna get a dime.
If Cromwell should bother
to call, put him through to my office!
Has anybody seen that idiot Kempster
around here?
Kempster!
Michael, you have got
to get back here tomorrow.
Langston is going insane.
Where are you?
- I'm staying in the middle
of Nightmare on Bodega Street.
If you don't get here,
do I sell the coffee or do I hold it?
No, no, no, no. Do not sell the coffee
till I give you the go-ahead.
Call me on the uplink
as soon as London opens, all right?
- All right. Okay.
- Kempster!
Nah, I wouldn't do that.
Oh, and why not?
Oh!
Lipo Lipo. So nice
they named it twice.
Oh, my God.
She left me
for Gilligan's Island!
- Great. I'll be right back.
- Not long. I have an appointment.
You have an appointment? Well, if it's
the cable guy, you got plenty of time.
- Okay.
- Hi, um-
I'm-I'm Michael Cromwell. I'm
looking for Patricia Cromwell.
You know Patricia Cromwell?
She's a doctor.
No, a woman. Like me, but, but...
full-figured.
Paliku.
- Paliku.
- Pali who?
- Paliku?
- Where is she?
- Paliku.
- Paliku! Paliku!
- Yes, I heard you. Okay, okay.
Patricia.
Mmm.
You look different.
Michael.
You made it.
Um, yes, I did.
You look good.
So do you.
- How've you been?
- Better. Much better.
Weren't you supposed
to meet me in Canaima last night?
Botako's having
her first litter.
- Congratulations.
- Not her.
This is Pontspie. Pontspie,
Mmm.
This is Botako.
As much as I hate
to spoil this joyous event,
I took an airplane from New York City.
I have a boat waiting.
You remember the divorce? Patricia?
- Patricia!
- Paliku.
My Pinare name is Paliku.
We pick our own names here.
Do you remember 12, 13 years ago,
maybe, when out of the blue,
we weren't even married a year,
and you walked out on me.
And now you want a divorce, and you
think I'm gonna hit you up for money.
We both want a divorce,
and aren't you?
- I don't want any money.
- Great! We can get to Caracas now.
That way we can sign divorce papers.
I can be back in New York by Friday.
Tomorrow is the Fanenteyou celebration.
I have to be here.
- Ooh.
- It's a male!
Ay!
As much as I'd like to stick around
for the circumcision,
I've got a canoe waiting,
and my boatman has an appointment.
- Your boatman is gone.
- What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Tell him to stop!
- Hasta la vista.
- Hey, stop! You can't leave me here!
What you're doing is
very unprofessional!
Oh, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Come back here!
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm gonna need all these clothes back,
right where they came from, all right?
Aw, this is a Braun!
- What about my boat?
- He'll be back. Couple of days.
Wh-What am I supposed
to do now?
The chief says you can spend the night
with the bachelors.
- I'm not staying with the bachelors.
- Or Pontspie offered her hut.
Mm-mmm.
Bring on the bachelors.
Come on, come on,
come on.
- Hungry?
- I am starving. Oh.
It's yellow-eared bat, a Pinare
specialty. It's made from the bladder.
Oh, bat bladder.
Holy Kaopectate! I don't think so.
- You might prefer the kara toka.
- Yeah, right.
- Chicken.
- I would prefer that. Thanks. Ready.
Excuse me.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- Michael, I have to talk to you.
- Patricia, let's not, okay?
- There's something that you don't know.
Yeah, like why
you left me.
- Because of the fifth phone line.
- What is that supposed to mean?
One morning some guy showed up at our
apartment to install a fifth phone line.
He asked if I was the receptionist.
And I realized that
I had lost you somehow.
I packed my things and I left you alone.
I figured you'd be happier that way.
- You thought this would make me happy?
- How long before you noticed I was gone?
- Why didn't you talk to me?
- Talk to you?
I spent six months
telling you I was unhappy.
It was a crazy time for me.
I just started working at L.T.G.
- Michael.
- I had a straddled position in sugar.
The price went up,
it skyrocketed, I'm shorted-
- Michael. Michael!
- What?
It's very hard for me
to tell you this, so please listen.
What choice do I have? I'm stuck here
with you and the Village People...
till you celebrate
Banana-fana-fo-fana.
- Hello, you.
- Ohhh.
Excuse me.
The real world calls.
Hello, you.
What I'm trying
to say is that-
- Look, I was right. I was right!
- I wasn't exactly alone when I left you.
- 97 and a quarter.
- Michael. Michael.
I'm with ya.
Coffee has gone crazy.
- I didn't know it, but I was...
- 97 and a quarter, 97, 97-
- I'm gonna wait till 97 and a half.
- pregnant with your son.
'Cause it's gonna happen. Waitin'. Papa
is waitin'. Come to Papa, 97 and a half.
Sold for a tidy $300,000 profit.
God, it's good to be good!
- What'd she say?
- Hello, you.
Patricia-
All right, Patricia. What did I do?
I just told you that you had a son,
and you didn't even hear me.
- What are you talking about? What son?
- Your son.
The boy sitting next to the fire
over there is your son.
That is my son?
I must have started
a thousand letters to tell you,
but every one of them started with,
"I know you never wanted children. "
This is nuts. This is nuts.
This is unbelievable.
- I was confused-
- This is unforgivable!
I'm not asking you to forgive me, but he
didn't do anything, so don't blame him.
That's my son?
His name is Mimi Siku.
His name is what?
Mimi Siku.
Roughly translated,
it means...
"Cat Piss. "
- He picked the name "Cat Piss"?
- He was six years old at the time.
It's a territorial thing.
- You sure he's mine?
- Positive.
He's got your nose,
and he thinks he's never wrong.
Hello, you.
No, no, no! Get away!
No! Don't touch that!
Don't touch that!
No, don't touch that!
Huh?
Oh.
You wouldn't happen to have a place
where I could stick that, would you?
Hello, you.
Talk about
your wind instruments.
Oh!
Oh, ease up on the fruit,
for God's sakes.
Mitsubishi!
Mimi Siku.
Hi, uh, Mimi Siku.
I'm Michael Cromwell.
Patricia- Paliku
tells me that, um,
that I'm your father.
That's a nice pot you have.
Do you understand
any English?
Well, Patricia- or Paliku- wanted me
to say something paternal to you.
I gotta admit, this isn't easy for me.
I don't have any regrets.
Well, I have regrets.
But then again-
# Too few to mention ## Ha!
Michael.
- You all right?
- Yes. Put air bags in these things.
What do you call this place again?
The Surface of the Sun?
Mimi said that you talked
to him last night.
I told him that I was his father,
and he said something in Indian,
and then he gave
a girl a pot.
Giving a pot here is like
giving flowers. It's a love gift.
He's very popular
with the girls.
- Maybe he is mine after all.
- He is yours.
Why don't you try again? He's going
out on the river. Go with him.
Maybe I can teach him
about commodities.
Based on what I learned
in the bachelor hut last night,
he could make a killing
in gas futures.
- Go.
- Is it the local fruit?
- Baboon! Baboon!
- Huh?
No, no, no, no.
Monkey.
Toona. Toona.
Oh.
Parasite.
No, uh, Mimi, um-
Water? Wa-
Piranha.
Cut, infection, death!
Oh.
Hoko. Hoko.
Hoko- bird.
Bird who can't sing:
Hoko Ono.
No, no, no.
Hoko is toucan.
Bird is pomoko.
- You speak English?
- Paliku taught me.
So, you understood
everything I said last night.
Is it much further?
These shoes
cost me $500. Whoa!
Hey, hey, hey!
Good shot!
Buradu.
Okay.
- Scared of snake?
- No, scared of snake bite.
Ugh.
Eww.
- This buradu is dead, right?
- Sleeping. We kill it before we eat it.
No, no, no, no.
I do not eat snake.
- Lizard guts.
- Actually, the snake filled me right up.
- No. I make it for you. Tastes good.
- Oh.
Now you here, you stay
with me all the time?
I'd like to, Mimi Siku,
but I can't.
Why?
I have a whole
'nother life where I live.
Another son?
No. You're
the only son I have.
- I'll teach you to hunt.
- Tomorrow I've got to go to my village.
I'm a trader.
That's what I do, okay?
This in your village,
yes?
Woman who hold fire
up sky's butt?
I've never had her described
quite like that.
Yes, she's
in my village.
We call her
the Statue of Liberty.
When I'm a man, will you take me
to Statue of Liberty?
Sure.
Why not? Yeah.
When you're a man, I'll take you
to the Statue of Liberty.
- Wakatepe?
- Wakatepe.
Sleep time.
Ugh.
Mimi, don't move!
Don't move! There's
a giant spider on you!
Don't move!
What's it doing?
Oh, great!
It's now comin' after me!
Damn, it's chasin' me.
Stop, stop, stop!
I don't want
to hurt you, but I will.
I will crush you
like... a bug!
Mimi, don't. No, no.
I can handle this.
Go to the village.
Save yourself!
No, no, don't!
Back! Jesus!
If you scream,
Myteka attack.
If you're calm,
Myteka nice.
- But kukuve always mean.
- Who's kukuve?
Huh?
This place is a nightmare!
Baboon! Baboon!
Nice turtle.
The hair on your chest
reminds them of a monkey.
"Baboon" is
your Pinare name.
Baboon? That's the best
they could come up with?
At first they wanted to go with
"Man Who Must Be Smarter Than He Looks. "
If we get to pick our own names,
I'd like to pick this:
"Man Who's Extremely
Well-Endowed. "
Sorry.
It's already taken.
- What's he sayin' to them?
- The chief is telling the forest that Mimi's no longer a child.
- Are they finished?
- Almost.
But to become
a tribal leader someday,
Mimi has to perform a special task
that the chief will give to him.
He says he's
very proud of Mimi Siku,
and, as his father,
you should be too.
Well, I am very proud of him,
considering the fact...
that I just found out
a couple days ago I had a son,
and I'm standing
about four feet from a witch doctor.
Mimi has the task of bringing fire
back from the Statue of Liberty.
Guy doesn't
kid around, does he?
You promised to take me
to New York when I become a man, Baboon.
- And when you're a man, I will.
- In this tribe, he is a man,
and he wants to go now?
No. Tomorrow we fly to Caracas,
we sign the divorce papers.
Then I get in a big, steel bird
and fly back to New York City.
- Yakuza.
- Did you promise to take him or not?
Maybe. Mimi Siku, I have to be back
on the exchange floor.
I'm gettin' married.
I cannot take you tomorrow.
Here, if you make
a promise, you keep it.
"Tomorrow," "Can't," "Maybe. "
These words don't mean anything to Mimi.
You brought him down here to live
with the Pirates of the Caribbean.
Maybe you should have
taught him better English.
This is the most important day
in your son's life,
and he wanted you here
to share it with him,
and now you're going to humiliate him
in front of the whole tribe...
by not keeping the first promise
you ever made to him?
Baboon, I-
I want to go.
Mimi Siku, I am-
I'm very sorry.
You made
wakatepe with me.
Excuse me, Mr. Cromwell,
but the young man you're with
is urinating on the exit door.
Thank you.
Me happy to be
with you, Baboon.
Michael!
All right, we gotta
get movin' here pretty-
Get on. It's just a moving sidewalk.
Michael!
Hey, Mike!
- Michael, how ya doin'?
- Richard, what are you doing here?
I told Langston you had a reason.
You do have a reason, right?
- For what?
- For holding on to the beans.
- What beans?
- The coffee beans.
- You didn't sell them?
- No.
I told you to sell them
at 97 and a half.
Oh, God,
I'm dead!
I'm gonna lose my house!
Where will my children live?
Richard- Excuse me. Richard.
Why didn't ya sell?
- 'Cause you didn't confirm, that's why!
- What?
- You did not confirm.
- What's coffee doin' now?
It's under 90 cents
and gone limit down.
I asked you- I told you
to sell it at 97 and a half,
and you can't do it 'cause
I didn't say "confirm"?
- You're an idiot!
- Look, for 15 years, Michael,
you say "sell,"
I say "confirm. "
Sell, confirm.
You confirm, and I sell.
You didn't confirm, so I didn't sell.
Look, kid, I've given
to the rain forest, okay?
His name is Mimi Siku.
- He's my son.
- What do you mean, "son"?
You didn't have one
when you left here three days ago.
Well, apparently I did.
He's Patricia's son.
He's Patricia
and my son.
- This your village, Baboon?
- Yep. This is my village.
It's big.
Where are all the animals?
Up in their offices, where they work.
Cromwell!
Okay.
Take a look at that.
Baboon must go
fight the chief.
Look at this!
Cromwell, look at this.
Coffee is at 88,
and it's dropping like a brick!
By tomorrow morning,
it could be 85 or lower.
Just wait it out.
Something will happen.
- The market will turn around.
- But what if it doesn't?
You remember
what happened in '91?
You can't always depend
on a natural disaster.
It doesn't have to be a disaster.
We can hope for an assassination.
Would you
take it seriously for one minute?
- I'm trying to lighten this guy up.
- Stop it. Stop it!
Now, come on.
Behave yourselves here!
Something better happen fast, or I'm
gonna throw your butts out the window!
What do you hotshots
think about when you make these deals?
You seem to have forgotten,
Cromwell, that you...
were investing
the company's money.
When you invest the company's money
and win, the company's behind you.
But when you screw up like this, you're
both on the hook for any loss we take.
- That would be over a million dollars.
- That's not my problem.
And by the way, Cromwell,
when somebody is playing
with millions of dollars of my money,
I generally like them
in the country.
- This country!
- Stop yelling, please.
This is still my office.
I'll shout, I'll yell,
I'll scream as much as I want.
When I made you shareholders
in this company,
it was to share profits,
not losses!
Not losses is right!
We're not here to share losses!
We're here
to share profits. Profits!
Profits! Huh?
Look up! It's an alien circle
with Mickey Rourke's picture in it.
Look, look,
look, look, look!
Up, up! Look!
Look up! Look up!
He just found out
that he has a son.
Look, look, look, look, look!
Stop shouting, Baboon.
Myteka kill chief.
Catch the damn spider,
will you, please?
Mm. I-I-I said I was gonna go fight
the chief, not kill the chief.
Around here, only... postal employees
kill chief. Do you understand?
Boy, whatever you do in Venezuela,
do not try the chili del fuego.
And I say we should just wait it out.
You're insane. Langston is right.
We have to find a buyer for the coffee,
cut our losses and get out now.
Wow! Nice shot!
Put this away.
Would you give me a few moments with
Charlotte before you bring Mimi up?
All right.
- Michael, you're back!
- Where's Brian? Brian, let's go.
Come on.
Come, come, come.
- Mmm.
- I missed you. You never called me.
We're here, but we're
not "here," okay?
Try to think of us as,
uh, furniture.
- Just act natural.
- So, did you miss me, darling?
I missed you very much.
My pieces in the show were
such a hit that Ian-
Michael Cromwell,
this is Ian Finch-Chumley.
- Good to meet you, Ian.
- Hi, Michael.
He's doing a profile on me
for the Fashion Channel.
He'll be following me from now
through the spring collection,
and he'll be covering
the wedding as well.
Isn't that fabulous?
There's a Fashion Channel?
- Yeah.
- Forget the camera.
Just talk to me.
They're furniture.
Now, honey, did you
get everything settled?
- Yeah.
- Yes! Oh!
Actually, um- Actually, Patricia
was very reasonable.
So... what did
you bring me?
Ow!
So, Mimi,
how old are you?
The roots
of the Yomano tree...
have broken ground
three times in my life.
So, I guess that
would make you around-
- Thirteen.
- Thirteen. Thirteen.
You know, I have a daughter
around that age. Karen.
Will I meet daughter?
Yeah, yeah. She's just up
at Charlotte's now.
She's trying on her dress
for the wedding.
- What are you doing?
- Feed Myteka.
What's Myteka?
- Are you upset?
- You brought back a child.
Everyone else I know comes back
from South America with a bag of coffee.
Well, I have ten million
bags of coffee.
I thought I'd bring back something
with a little less caffeine.
I have a show to prepare
and a wedding to plan.
That's months away. Honey?
He's only gonna be here
for a short while.
- Mimi.
- Baboon.
- What have you done with Mr. Kempster?
- Excuse me. Michael.
- Do you know who Myteka is?
- Daddy!
Karen. Look at you.
You look... beautiful.
Angel on table.
- Look at me. I'm smoking.
- The rain forest is a very hot issue.
Being associated
with this, uh, jungle bloke,
it can only help you.
Where's the rain forest?
Brian, find out
where the rain forest is.
Right.
Oh!
Mimi Siku,
this is Charlotte,
and, uh, Charlotte,
this is Mimi Siku.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, Mimi Siki.
- Mimi Siku.
- This your female, Baboon?
- This is my female.
And as his female,
I'd like to invite you...
to dinner tonight
with Fiona Gluckman.
She's the fashion editor
of Elle magazine.
Very major. She wants to see
the sketches for my wedding trousseau.
And if you're available,
I'd love for you to join us.
Is there anything special
you like to eat?
Lizard guts.
- Lizard guts?
- Yes, but very lean.
- Great earrings. Honey!
- Oh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Mimi, Mimi, Mimi.
Do you remember what we talked about,
using the toilet on the airplane?
Let's continue to do that.
I will find the men's room for him,
and we will see you tonight.
Come on, Mimi.
Will he be wearing
the loincloth to dinner?
I'll get him some clothes.
No, no, no, no.
Don't, don't, don't.
Before you pee, you lift the seat. After
you pee, you put the seat back down.
Females in tribe start war over this.
Many deaths.
Oh, that's very good.
Very-
Bob Montgomery.
That's wonderful.
Listen. So, Bob, I'm standing
with Michael Cromwell,
and, you know, considering
our long history together,
you're the first person
we wanna make this offer to.
Are you ready?
Fifty-one hundred tons of coffee beans.
- We're dead. Okay?
- Baboon!
- Ah! He's doing a Fay Wray!
- Michael! Mumu!
- Mimi!
- Come back inside!
- Statue of Liberty, Baboon.
- You do as I tell you.
- Get this!
- Come look!
- No, no, no! Come back here!
- Mimi, Get back in here.
- Cool.
- Life happens around you!
- Move. Get outta my way.
Come on. Mimi!
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
- Mimi! Mimi!
- Get the wide-angle lens!
Get out of the way, please!
Mimi!
Wait, wait, wait!
Statue of Liberty, Baboon.
Statue not far, Baboon.
Mimi, you stand right there.
- We go now?
- We'll go tomorrow, okay?
Whoa. Ahhh.
People down there
so far from us.
I'd like to keep 'em
that way, okay?
I'm gonna die up here.
Nothing bad happened,
Baboon.
I just hate heights.
Whoa.
Oh.
Pinare secret:
Don't look down.
Just for the record,
it's not that big a secret.
Yeah!
Don't you ever, ever,
ever do that to me again!
When I tell you to do something,
I mean it. Do you understand me?
Mimi Siku sorry.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Mm, sorry.
I was just worried about you out there.
I really was. All right?
Well, um,
we should go.
- Baboon scared?
- Yes, Baboon scared.
Baboon not know
he could be so scared.
Baboon's pants
a little damp.
- Charlie, this is fabulous!
- Mimi, get down.
When I saw the shoulders
on this gown, I plotzed.
I said to myself, "Fiona,
this- this is
the future of fashion. "
Oh, no. Remember
what I told ya?
Forks go on the left side.
This side.
Small fork on the outside. Take your
knife, put it over next to the spoon.
The blade- The blade in.
Perfect.
Yeah. Might wanna work
on that one too.
In Lipo Lipo,
we eat with hands.
In New York, New York,
we eat with forks.
When are we gonna eat?
I'm famished!
A little champagne?
Gino, why don't you show her
the bridesmaids sketches?
Show me, show me,
show me, show me.
Oh, I'm loving this!
Ah!
What is taking so long
with the food?
I'll give them a call.
I don't eat meat, I don't eat dairy
or nightshade vegetables,
and, of course,
I don't touch preservatives.
Obviously.
- Cat fat.
- Mm-hmm.
- We eat cat.
- Excuse me?
That must be the food.
- Oh! Finally.
- Gino, Louis.
Coming.
We are not going
to eat the cat.
- Cat's job, feed people.
- No, not here.
Here, cat's job is to sleep
and lick crotch.
Oh, Charlie,
it smells so good! I can't stand it!
Of course, this is much
too much for me.
Did they forget
my tiramisu?
- Oh, God!
- This much tasty.
Your female makes
good food, Baboon.
Oh!
Oh, Louis,
you are such a cliche.
- You had no right to change the rules.
- What rules?
When we talked about
having children,
we agreed that you would be my child
and that I would be your child,
and now I find out
that you've had a child all along.
Wait a second. Are you saying
that I knew that I had a child?
Well, if I had a child,
I certainly would have known.
Hello! You're a woman. Of course you'd
know. You're there when you have it!
There's no magical bond between a father
and son that spans the continents.
The only reason I know I have a child
is because you insisted-
So now you're saying that you
having a child is my fault?
- I don't think so, Michael.
- Mimi's just visiting.
I wanna show him
a good time.
After that, he goes back home, and we
can go back to being the way we were-
entirely wrapped up
in ourselves.
Promise?
Ow!
My little darlings.
Ah. Ooh. Are your
little bellies empty?
Oh.
Bonjour.
Ah. Bonjour.
We are all
so happy today, n'est-ce pas?
What's goin' on up here?
Did you- Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go! Go!
Mimi, you can't do this. You do not
kill birds around here for breakfast.
If you're hungry, ask me.
I bought some stuff for ya.
This is what kids love.
Cap'n Crunch.
What is?
This is cereal. It's just corn,
brown sugar, yellow #5 and zinc oxide?
They've added
a sunblock to it.
You pour this on this, and that's
your breakfast. Enjoy yourself.
Charlie. Come on.
Wake up, sweetheart.
Wake up. Charlie.
Bloomingdale's burned down.
What?
Mimi's having breakfast
out in the kitchen.
I will be home
before lunch.
- Bye.
- Wait.
I can't watch him.
Women's Wear is coming to the loft.
You don't need to baby-sit him.
He'll be fine.
Now go back to sleep.
Mmm.
Mimi, I gotta get goin' here.
No. No!
This isn't- No.
No, it's not your fault.
I didn't mention that you
usually put this in a bowl.
When we go
to Statue of Liberty?
- Uh, tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
I know I told you
we were going today, but I can't today.
I- I- The Baboon's makin'
some very big trades today.
- Me go trade with Baboon.
- Baboon go alone.
I'd like to be around you,
but, but I'm obligated to go.
What means "obligated"?
Obligated.
It means...
when you do something that
you don't really wanna do.
Okay.
- Baboon obligated.
- And will you promise Baboon one thing?
You won't shoot
any more animals?
And don't eat the cat.
I'll bring
food home.
Myteka?
Myteka.
Nice pushibushi.
That is the last pushibushi you're gonna
see around here, you little savage!
Hi, we're not here
right now. Leave a message.
We'll call you right back.
Charlie. Pick up. It's me.
You're probably in the bathroom,
making yourself look beautiful.
Um, I don't want you
feelin' trapped by Mimi.
Try to open up to him.
Just don't leave him alone with the cat.
I'll see you soon.
I love you. Bye.
Michael, don't hang up!
Don't hang up! There's a spider!
This can't be happening!
This is a penthouse apartment!
# There's nothing to gain when
there's nothing to be lost #
# There's nothing to gain if you
stay behind and count the cost #
# Make a decision you can be
who you can be you can be #
# Tasting the fruit
Come to the liberty tree #
# Someday #
Help a guy out.
Spare change for food?
Spare change for food? Uh.
- Eat.
- # Changin' your ways #
- # Making those surrounding you #
- Hmm.
# Changin' your ways
More than any man can do #
Right!
# Find your brothers and sisters who can
hear all the truth in what you say #
- Much night fun.
- Honey, come on.
- Mom!
- # They can support you when you're on your way today #
# Your day
It's your day #
- Right there.
- That way?
- Thank you.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org