Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
It's okay.
Oh—
Did you just put that
back in your eye?
- It was my last one, guys.
- That's really gross.
Ow! My eye!
But, you see,
l— I'm on the list. I'm "plus one."
David Pennington, plus one.
- Hi, David.
- There he is. See? There he is.
- Oh, hey.
- David Pennington. There.
No, no, no. There.
She's— She's with me.
Thank you. Oh!
Ooh.
I'm okay. Fine.
Come on.
I got a surprise for you.
Oh, my God.
Would you look at that big, ugly...
- brown pile of—
- Uh, Ashley—
It looked like it came out of the rear end
of an elephant.
- Ashley.
- Huh?
Uh—
Meet my mother, the artist.
- Hmm.
- The artist.
Hi, Mrs. Pennington.
You know, you look
so much younger in person.
Not that I mean
you're old or anything.
David, if I'm going to listen to this,
I'll need vodka.
Good idea.
- Waiter.
- Yes, sir.
Sure. Hmm?
No, thank you.
David, darling, that awful man
from the Times is here.
It's him.
- That son of a—
- Excuse me.
Yeah? Oh, um, the waiter.
He was just—
- More your type? I totally agree.
- Wha—
- Mother, please.
- Um, if you two don't mind,
I'm gonna run to the ladies' room.
You! Finally.
- Excuse me?
- You're gonna keep your tongue
in your mouth at all times...
- 'cause this is strictly business.
- What?
- Give me back my luck. Come here.
- What the—
- Let go of me.
- Just— Uh-oh.
From the bowels of this
mortal coil come... the mud men.
- Kiss me, damn it!
- Let me up! I'm in the show!
- I am a mud man.
- I am a mud woman.
We are mud people...
and he is our mud king.
- Heart attack! I know C.P.R!
- I'm not having—
He's not breathing!
He's totally breathing!
No, he's not.
It's a cardiac reflex thing.
- I need to give him mouth-to-mouth.
- I can't breathe.
Mmm.
He's gonna be okay.
- Sorry.
- Lucky you were here.
Lucky you know C.P.R.
Yeah. You know what?
That's me. Lucky.
You know, I'm feeling
kind of— Oh!
Oh.
Irreplaceable!
It's ruined.
This is ridiculous. It was just mud.
You must have met my twin sister.
She was in here the other night.
She's the bitch.
I'm the nice one.
- What can I get you?
- Um, can I just have a glass of water?
No buy, no sit. See?
Can I use the bathroom?
N- No buy, no bathroom!
Okay. Great. Fine. Fine.
I'm leaving.
I'm leaving. Oh, are you all
enjoying the show?
You know, the real me
doesn't have days like this.
As a matter of fact,
maybe I'm not even here right now.
This is all probably
a—a dream that I'm having...
induced by a—
a deep-tissue massage.
- Yes. A massage that I won at a charity raffle.
- Shut up.
That looks good.
Are you done with that?
No. That was a joke.
I'm not gonna eat your scraps.
Gosh! Maybe just some bacon.
Mmm! Mmm!
I don't know what she's doing.
Oh, my God.
I'm like a coyote.
Perfect.
Oh, not the salt.
Just so everyone knows...
I think what I'm about to do is completely
ridiculous, but it can't hurt, can it?
Come on.
- My eye!
- Oh, my God!
Oh! Oh, my—
- It was an accident. I'm sorry.
- Miss, I think it's, uh...
- time to go now.
- Oh, my God. All right.
I'm sorry.
It was an accident.
- I think we're clear.
- Thanks for that. Sorry.
- I couldn't help but overhear your, uh—
- Oh, meltdown?
- Yeah. Broke. Jobless.
And I just ate lejambon d'étranger.
- What?
- A stranger's bacon. I thought
it would sound better in French.
- Oh.
- Guess not.
You looked a little hungry. I thought you
could use this. Turkey on rye, extra mustard.
Oh. Yes. Thank you.
- Thanks. Um, nice to meet you.
- Okay. Yeah.
I'm gonna—
Look. I know of a job—
if you're looking for one.
Really? What's the scam?
- No scam.
- Well, do you want me to
join your religion or something?
No. No religion stuff.
It's just a job. You know, a bad job.
Crummy pay for crummy hours.
That still doesn't answer
my question. What's the scam?
Let's just say I know
what it's like to be S.O.L.
- S.O.L.?
- "Shit out of luck."
What makes you think I'm S.O.L.?
Just because I spilt the salt back there?
Yeah.
Oh!
Look. Where you are right now,
I've been there.
Been there? I lived there.
I was kind of the mayor of there.
I'm Jake.
Ashley.
- Oh, God.
- Yeah, yeah. No, you got it.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Looks great on you.
Can anything else—
I mean, to be honest...
I'm not really dressed for
a job interview right now.
For this one
I think you'll be fine.
- Okay.
- Wanna check it out?
- Why are you so nice?
- Why—Just— Look. I mean...
shit out of luck—
That's my thing.
...put me in this position.
- You're gonna love her.
- This is not fair. Listen.
- She's great.
- I don't need another loser waitress here.
- Okay, Mac. Okay.
You won't be sorry.
- I didn't get it.
- No, no, no, no, no. No, no. It's not that.
You can have the job,
but it's my old job.
So?
Well, see, l— I'd hoped he would hire you
as a waitress or something.
My old gig was kind of a— like a janitor,
food delivery person, toilet attendant.
I'll take it. I'll take it.
Whoa! God!
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa. Oh!
Oh!
God.
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
Ow! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh.
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
What the—
I'll clean that up.
Come on, boys.
Move it or lose it. Let's go.
There we go.
Before Phillips will release the album,
he wants to see you play a larger space...
- like the Knitting Factory.
- Oh!
See if you can hold a big crowd
for an hour, create some preheat. Huh?
- Yeah! When?
- I don't know.
Guys! Listen. Carley, turn the radio up.
- No way!
- That's it! That's it!
Let's celebrate.
Burgers and fries on me.
All right.
Hey, sweetie. You, uh, scamper up
that ladder and— and fix that light.
- Well, I'm not so good with—
- Thanks.
Heights.
That's McFly,
a new British invasion band—
Phillips will tell us tonight. In the meantime,
we have to focus on fine-tuning—
Whoa.
Track—
See, that's not good.
She should have gone up
without the bulb...
then brought down the old one,
because now she's gonna be juggling—
Eh! Hey!
- You know where the broom is.
- Yeah. I'll—
And she should have turned off the light
first because now she's gonna be—
Electrocuted.
- Oh, my God.
- Hi.
Hi.
So, other than, uh, you know,
getting zapped, how's the job working out?
- Oh, I can't complain.
- That's good.
No. I mean I'm literally not allowed
to complain. I had to sign something.
Oh. I remember that.
- This is cold, so it'll help.
- You're very handy with this stuff.
- Thanks.
- Ah, that feels good.
- Is that toothpaste?
- Yeah. It's an ancient Chinese
remedy for burned fingers.
Yeah. It pays to be prepared.
I've got everything in this backpack.
I have first aid, extra socks.
- Isn't that a bit defeatist?
- No, it's being a realist. You've been out there.
Hey. Let me see your cell phone.
Why?
- What the—What is this?
- Oh. Flip it like that.
Like that.
Address book.
"Bergdorf's, Bendel's and sushi."
Are you nuts?
Unlucky people need hospitals.
Also, never call 911.
They take forever.
Fire responds. They're great.
National Poison Control Center.
Ask for Lou. He's very good.
You know what? Um...
this backpack has seen me through
just about everything.
And...
I think it's time to pass it on.
- Oh. No, no, no. I couldn't.
- No. No. Honestly, I think you should have it.
- Please. You need it more than I do.
- Thank you.
Uh, I better take this.
- Oh, yeah. Sure. Of course.
- Hey, Katy. How's my girl? What?
Your key? You checked the doormat?
Um, okay. What—What if I pick you up,
take you to the new place?
Yeah. You'll love it.
It's huge.
Okay. We'll have pizza.
It'll be fun.
- I gotta run.
- Okay. Uh, yeah.
See ya, Ashley. Uh, it's just a—
It's a girl. Yeah. No.
Hey. Guys. Guys. Guys. Come on.
- Hey, guys. Sounds good.
- How you doing? Thank you.
- What's going on?
- Look, Jake. The Knitting Factory fell through.
- What?
- Oh, you're joking.
- That sucks.
- But "Five Colours" has been
gettin' great radio play...
so I decided to book our boys
at the new Hard Rock Cafe Times Square.
No way!
- Who's your boy, huh? This is big!
- Beauty!
This is—This is big. How's my follow-up coming?
We're—We're working on it.
- Uh—
- All right. That's good. Don't let me stop you.
- Sounds good, guys. Congratulations.
- All right. Have a good one.
So, um, Jake, when are we gonna
hear this amazing follow-up?
- When you guys write it.
- Right.
Hey, Jake.
You got a delivery.
Over there.
Hey. Isn't that that bird
from the bowling alley?
- Yeah. The electrocuted one.
- Hey, Jakey.
Danny, let's work on your vocals
for "Too Close for Comfort."
I think we're on the right track.
Just tighten it up a little bit.
Okay. We're—We're gonna take it
from the second verse.
- Hey.
- Oh! I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- Thanks. Oh!
- I got it. I got it. I got it.
- I'm— I'm sorry about—
- No. Don't worry about it.
Come on in.
Check out this song.
Sounds great, Tim.
- They sound good.
- Yeah. Yeah. They do, don't they?
- Yeah.
- So, did you hear we're playing
the new Hard Rock?
- Wow. That's great.
- Yeah. Well, besides the fact
that it's a huge space...
I'm probably not gonna
be able to fill it...
- and I'm kind of dead.
- It's tough, but not impossible.
So, you think maybe, uh,
you'd want to go to coffee later...
or something maybe?
Yeah, um—
That'd be nice.
Oh. There she is.
- Oh. Is— Is that Katy?
- Yeah.
She's cute, huh?
She picked out this jacket.
- Oh. Nice.
- Yeah.
- Looks like a tramp.
- What?
What? Camp. Camp. She looks
like someone I went to camp with.
- Yeah.
- Strange.
Weird.
You know, l— I better get going.
Uh, Mac wants me to reset the rat trap.
So, should I call you tonight?
Um, yeah, about that—
Oh, geez.
Um, yeah. Some other time maybe.
I have other plans.
- If that's cool. Sorry about that again.
- That's okay.
- Bye.
Oh!
- Thanks for the ride, Jake.
- Yeah. Hold up one second.
Um, so I'll see you later?
Tell Aunt Martha I'm gonna send
Bernie with the car to pick you up.
Don't forget your homework.
- Yeah, yeah. I hear ya. Later.
- All right. See ya.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Don't do that.
Don't open the umbrella.
Not inside.
Very unlucky.
- Bernie.
- Yes, sir?
Back it up, will ya?
Oh, God.
You know, there's a poncho
in that backpack.
I didn't even think to— to look.
Can I give you a ride?
I only live 29 blocks from here.
Uh, at least take my umbrella.
I already have one.
You know,
I got a washer-dryer, uh...
microwave popcorn,
satellite TV.
No. L— l—
I really shouldn't.
Look. I don't do this
for just anybody, but...
I'll even throw in some hot chocolate
with those little tiny marshmallows.
I love the tiny marshmallows.
How about you toss
the lightning rod and get in?
Oh.
Thank you.
- Nice place.
- Yeah. Um—
We should get you some dry clothes.
Here. Let me get this.
- Oh, thank you.
- Laundry room's that way.
Bathroom's right over there.
Uh, kitchen's right here. Go whichever way
you think you should go.
- Thanks.
- Yeah. Sure.
Mind if I throw some of my clothes
in with yours?
No. Not at all. Wow.
Laundry room in your apartment.
- As far as I'm concerned,
that's when you know you've arrived.
- Yeah. It's pretty cool.
You know what?
I should wash this too. Hold on.
Okay.
Oh. Oh, shoot.
- Toss this in for me, will ya?
- Um, yeah. Sure.
Thanks.
- Oh. I should get this. I'll be right back.
- Okay. I'll be in here.
Since when does a washing machine
need an L.C.D. Screen?
Okay.
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
What is going on?
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, no!
Stop! Please stop! Stop!
Um, off.
Off!
What are you, possessed? Oh!
- Everything okay in there?
- Yeah! Everything's fine.
- Okay.
- Oh!
What is going on?
Okay. Water off.
Water off! Oh!
Oh, God!
Off! Off!
No, not spin!
Oh, my God.
Hello?
Oh, my God. Oh!
- Stop! Please stop!
- Okay. Uh—
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I got it. I got it. I got—
How'd you do that?
Uh, there's a— there's an off button
on the L.C.D. Screen.
What can I say? I am a pathetic
disaster, and I give up.
- You give up?
- I give up. I don't care anymore.
You know what?
It feels great.
You know what? I gave up years ago.
It's my secret to happiness.
Oh! Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
- Play fair.
- Oh.
- Ow.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, man.
- Your eye?
- You're done.
- I'm sorry.
No.
Oh, cool!
Oh, am I interrupting something?
- Hi, Katy.
- Hi.
- Wait. You're Katy?
- Last time I checked.
Hi. I'm Ashley.
No. No, that's not a problem.
I'm on it. Yeah.
So, Jake tells me you're a loser.
What? I'm not a loser.
That's cool.
I'm a loser too.
Anyway, it's just like a term of affection,
not a permanent condition.
- Oh.
- You just haven't had any good luck. That's all.
No, no. It's great.
I love these
little marshmallow things.
So do I.
Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
We'll talk later. All right, sir. Bye.
- Oh, my God.
- Hot.
- What's the problem?
- Oh, Phillips wants the new
song ready before the concert.
- And?
- And we don't have shit.
I mean shoot.
We don't have shoot.
We don't have to tell Aunt Martha
about this, do we?
Don't stress it.
I'll write you a kick-ass song.
Oh, so you're a—you're a songwriter now?
Very funny.
- You could be more supportive.
- This is serious.
- This is my life we're—
- Guy— Guys—
- No shoot.
- No shoot. That—
Uh— I think I can help you out.
What do you have in mind?
Well, I have this friend—
What a song.
I totally understand. If you don't
want to use it, it's cool.
No. No, it's great.
Just a few little adjustments.
Hey, Harry.
Double the tempo.
Danny, Tom, why don't you
kick it off tight and rough it up a bit?
- Ashley.
- Yeah?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hey.
So I hear a rumor that, uh,
you have another hit for me.
Well, it's, uh— it's rough,
but I got a good feeling, sir. Yeah.
Sounds good. Positivity.
That's what I like.
Oh, yeah. Congratulations
on, uh, selling out.
Selling out?
You mean the Hard Rock?
We sold out the Hard Rock?
- I BlackBerried you.
- I don't have a BlackBerry.
- Tiffany, get him a BlackBerry.
- Yes.
- There's a line around the corner
of people just hoping to get in.
- Ah?
Hey, hey, hey. I don't hug people,
but, look, bro.
You saved my life twice. Once
at the masquerade bash and— and now.
L— It was
a great night for me too.
I mean, ever since then I've been
about the luckiest guy in the worid.
Look. Come by my office later.
- It can't be.
- I got some ideas.
- Okay.
- Geez.
Jake. Jake is the guy I kissed
at the masquerade bash.
- Uh-uh.
- Yes.
- No.
Yes! That's great. He's hot.
You don't understand.
If I kiss Jake...
it's hello,
fabulous carefree life.
And that's a problem?
- Well—
- Go.
- Ashley.
- No, no, no.
Um, I have to go now.
Uh, now?
- Whoa!
- Oh, my God.
Taxi!
Sorry. I was just
checking something.
Five dollars. Yes.
- Thank you, luck.
- Ashley?
Miss Braden.
Listen. I am so sorry for—
- Antonio?
- Hey, Ash.
- Hi.
- How lucky that we ran into you.
I feel just horrible about
those things I said to you.
No. Stop. You were right
to blame it all on me.
Then let me blame you for bringing this sweet,
wonderful, iron-tushed man into my life.
Yes. We're getting married, baby.
- No way!
- It's true. I bought him the ring.
- Well, good for you guys. Congratulations.
- Ashley...
I want you to come back
to work for me.
- Are you kidding?
- I can't lose you. You are my good luck charm.
L— I don't know what to say.
Well, we have a huge pitch tonight.
St. Regis at 8:00.
So, say you'll be by my side...
and say you'll be wearing something
appropriate to your new vice president title.
Oh, my gosh. Yes. Yes.
Thank you.
- Bye.
Oh! Yes! My luck is back!
Oh, my God.
- Hello.
- Ash?
Anyone want some late lunch?
- Hi.
Hey. I have some surprises.
Ta-da! Last one in stock,
and just my size. Lucky, huh?
- Yeah.
- And I went to Miyakami
and got two orders of everything...
'cause I thought we could use
a little celebration.
- That's nice.
- Oh. Yeah.
What's wrong?
The band isn't
gonna do Maggie's song.
What? Why not?
Phillips is superstitious.
- Come on.
- He thinks that new groups...
should only perform music
that they've written themselves.
- That's crazy.
- No. It's just bad luck.
Look. I'm sorry this is happening.
I didn't have anything to do with—
Ashley, stop. It's not your fault.
It's life. Right?
Come on. We gotta get going. We gotta get
there before they go on. I want to wish them luck.
- You're still going?
- Oh, yeah. We have V.I.P.
Tickets. Why waste 'em? You?
Um, actually, I'm not. I have, um, a meeting.
- Job interview?
- Actually, it's a funny story.
- Um, Peggy rehired me.
- Ashley!
I am so proud of you.
You totally stuck it out,
and it all got better.
Are you sure
you're gonna be okay?
Of course.
What choice do I have?
If you dwell on
all the bad things in life...
- you miss out on all the good things.
- It's getting late.
- Well, have fun.
- Good luck on your meeting, Ashley.
Thanks.
Bye.
Cool!
We're down front!
- So big!
- So many people.
Look how many people there are.
- Hottie, mate. There's a hottie there.
- Yeah.
I hope it goes well.
All right. Guys, guys. Final touches.
Dressing room now. Come on.
- Let's do this. Come on.
- I'm so nervous. I'm so nervous.
Hey, Nick. Nick.
How are ya?
Oh, bollocks!
You look very nervous.
- Thank you. I appreciate that.
- Want some herbal tea? We have some.
Thank you.
That would be great.
The monitors hot
for Danny and Tom, right?
- The input for the reverb
in the distortion pedals?
- Two and three.
Good. Andjust remember.
The switch-outs at three, five and nine.
- Right. Right.
- Someone could fall down
in this. I'm gonna shut it.
Whoa!
Hello?
Jake? Guys?
Cab! Taxi!
- Oy!
- We're never gonna get a cab at this hour.
Think positive.
Hey. Guys.
Jump in. Come on.
Ashley.
- Let's go. We don't have much time.
- What are you doing?
I can't stop sweatin'.
Shocking!
- You guys ready?
- Yeah. Stoked.
Yeah. Born ready.
- My eye!
- My "A"string.
Danny, look at me.
You can see, right?
See, please?
Two minutes, you guys.
Good luck.
Two minutes?
L— I need some ice. I need some ice.
Hello!
Guys, I'm here!
Okay. Look. I know you guys
are nervous. That's fine. Just—
Hold that thought.
Good idea.
- Whoo!
- Air fre—Air freshener.
Oh, by the way, have you seen
Harry anywhere?
He's— He's not here?
Hello?
- Okay, guys. Spread out, find him.
- All right.
- Nick. Nick.
- Harry.
- Yeah.
- Uh, have you seen— have you seen Harry?
- Who?
- Harry the drummer.
- Uh— Harry!
Harry!
Harry.
- Harry.
- Get out of here!
- Pervert!
- Sorry.
D.M.R.'s got the money, baby!
Excuse me, sir. Could you make a left
up ahead? Union Square's always a mess.
I can't believe
you blew off Peggy Braden.
She'll get over it. If Jake's bad luck
is half as bad as mine was...
then we don't have much time.
Harry. Harry, are you in here?
- Hey. Has anyone seen Harry?
- No.
- Excuse me. Has anyone
seen Harry? The drummer.
- No.
- Harry!
- Has— Has anybody got a 20 on the drummer?
What's he look like?
Yeah. I don't know.
They all look alike to me.
Harry!
Harry.
- Harry.
- Start the show!
Harry.
- He's not here.
- We want McFly!
He's not here either.
Ah, but then— No, no. No, no, no.
- Jake, baby!
- Hey!
I understand the drill— keep 'em waiting—
but the natives are gettin' restless.
- We thought it was normal
to go up a half hour late.
- Jake.
Jake, we can't find Harry anywhere.
He's not upstairs. He's gone.
- Checked the loos. He's not in men's or women's.
- No.
There something
you want to tell me, Jake?
We—We have a problem.
Hello?
What the hell is that?
- Oh! We're so late. Come on! Come on!
- Oh, my gosh!
Thank you! Wait. You guys.
You guys. Backstage is this way.
Come on. Hi. Excuse me.
Watch out, buddy.
- Come on!
- Hold on a second, giris.
Catch up, Dana.
You got the passes.
Let's go!
Hello.
And I, for one...
am not looking forward to going
out here and telling this angry crowd...
that the band decided
not to play.
Oh. That won't be me.
That's gonna be you.
Unless you get your boys
out there now!
Mr. Phillips,
without a—a drummer?
- No way.
- It won't work.
Hey, guys. I used to be the, uh, backup
drummer for, uh, Whitesnake.
- Whitesnake? Hell, yeah!
- There you go. Here's your drummer.
- Wait a minute.
- We're not gonna go out there without Harry.
- It's not gonna happen.
McFly doesn't play...
you'll be lucky enough
to manage...
- a high school marching band.
- Jake.
- Get out of the way.
- We got a problem. We need a new band.
- Cancel the limo.
- Get out of the way, please. All right. Now go.
Ashley, now's not a—
- What the hell is this?
- Shh!
And in nine, eight, seven—
- Oh, no.
- Who hit the smoke?
Five, four, three—
Whoa.
Two—
Is that— Is that Harry?
Get started, baby!
We're on. We're on.
No way. The freak went on without us.
I don't believe it.
Hey. Do me a favor.
- Play Maggie's song.
- Absolutely.
Hey. Let's kick it off
with "I've Got You."
Yeah. Definitely.
Come on. Let's go.
- Phillips is gonna be pissed.
- Who cares?
Harry. Harry, we're playing
"I've Got You."
Ashley. Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah. I'm okay.
Oh, I'm proud of you.
- Katy!
- Yes!
- They're great!
- It's good!
Danny! Whoo!
I thought I told you
not to play this song.
Well, I guess
I'm not superstitious.
But I am.
I should fire you, Jake.
But it works.
It works. Good job.
Thank you.
They're playing my song!
- Whoo!
Is that the sound
of them clapping...
- or my nervous system shutting down?
- No. They're clapping.
Hello, Times Square!
- Congratulations!
- Ashley, thank you!
- Great to be here, everybody.
Oh. Who wants to meet
my friend Mr. Dom Pérignon?
- That would be the '94?
- Yeah!
- The '95! Yeah, baby!
- Yeah. That's okay.
All right, guys.
Champagne time! Everybody.
McFly on three. On three.
Champagne time.
One— Help me out.
One, two, three!
McFly!
All right. Danny. Everybody.
Get over here. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Let's go, baby.
Ashley.
- Come on. Let's go celebrate.
- Hey. Um, not now.
What's wrong with you?
You look miserable.
Maggie,
I think I've fallen for him.
That's great.
What's the matter with that?
I don't know. I mean, the feelings
I have generally lead toward kissing.
So kiss him. Kiss him!
I can't.
Oh, Ash.
Please don't tell me
you still believe in that stuff.
More than ever.
And I can't not kiss him.
- I gotta go.
- What? Where are you going?
Grand Central.
I'm gonna visit
my parents for a bit.
I have to sort things out.
Give me a hug, you.
Have fun, okay?
And be careful.
Okay.
Bye.
Gather round. Gather round.
Of course.
You waitin'for a train?
I'm just saying if you are,
you might as well give up now.
- Jake, please.
- With your luck...
there's gonna be an announcement
that due to some freak accident
all trains have been canceled.
Then you're gonna go outside
and wait for the bus...
at which point the acid rain will commence—
perhaps even acid hail.
Listen, Jake. I can't see you.
Okay? It's for your own good.
Luck changes, Ashley.
You know?
You know, l— I kissed this amazing girl
at this masquerade party.
No. Listen. I swear I'm not crazy, okay?
Our luck did get switched.
And it still is.
Here. I dare you not to win.
So you think meeting me
was unlucky?
No. God, I'm lucky
to have met you.
Okay?
But you deserve my luck.
- You put it to better use than I ever did.
- Well, I don't want it anymore.
- Are you crazy?
- I want you to have it.
- No. Go away.
- It's been great...
but I'll be fine without it.
How do you know that?
Because I'll have you in my life.
A few bumps and bruises along the way
are a small price to pay.
Tag. You're it.
Oh, no. You're not
gettin' away with it that easy.
- Oh, yeah?
- Not a chance.
So now who?
Who cares?
Ew! Gross!
You leave a kid sitting in a limo
so you can make out?
You take me from a perfectly good party
with really cute rock stars...
I pop a shoelace,
swallow my gum...
and now I'm stuck here
watching you two play tonsil hockey.
- Good grief!
- Katy.
I am so glad you're here.
Why are you guys
looking at me like this?
Hold still. Mmm! Mmm! Mmm!
Oh, I've been slimed!
- Try this. You'll like it.
- It's fun.
Cool.
So, where were we just, like—
- Ow.
Twenty-five bucks?
No freakin'way. I'm rich!
Oh, yeah! I'm rich!
I'm taking the limo, okay?
This I gotta show Grams.
I definitely hit the jackpot.
- Hey, Bernie!
- Thank you.
She deserves it.
- Pizza?
- You're on.
So, you think you can
adjust to life without luck?
- Right now I've never felt luckier.
- Me too.
- Do you believe in karma?
- Karma? Ash, you kidding me?
One time I helped an old lady across the street.
Next day, I found a hundred-dollar bill.
- Ash, that's luck.
- Karma.
- It's luck.
- Karma, karma, karma.
- Luck, luck, luck.
- It's karma.
- It's luck.
- Get the door.
Why, thank you.
Hey.
Quarter.
Hmm. Seems we still
have our luck.
- Who cares?
- Absolutely.
Hey! Shut the valve!
The pipe is broken.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org