Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Evenin' fell just like a star
Left a trail behind
You spitted
You slammed out the door
If this is love, we're crazy
'Cause we fight like cats and dogs
I just know
there's got to be more
Please call me, baby
Wherever you are
It's too cold to be out
walkin' in the streets
We do crazy things
when we're wounded
Everyone's pretty insane
I don't want you
catchin' your death of cold
Out walkin' in the rain
I admit that I ain't no angel
I admit that I ain't no saint
I'm selfish and I'm cruel
but you're blind
If I exorcise my devils
Well, my angels may leave too
When they leave
they're so hard to find
Please call me, baby
Wherever you are
It's too cold to be out
walkin' in the streets
We do crazy things
when we're wounded
Everyone's pretty insane
I don't want you catchin'
your death of cold
Out walkin' in the rain
Answer me honestly.
If I was to tell you
that I love you...
and that I'd throw it all away
to be with you...
w-what would you say to me?
Good night, Paulie.
Yep. Yep, that's about par
for the evening.
But what I want to see
Is the way things used to be
Between you and me
The way things used to be
Let me guess.
Your old lady got fed up because
you're out here chasing the skirt...
so she took these little ones
and left you.
It's a little more com-- It's
a little more complicated than that.
Oh, yes, it always is. Everybody thinks
their story is the one with the twist.
But let me tell you,
in my experience it's--
- Holy shit.
- Exactly.
- This I've got to hear.
- No, look, uh, it's a long story.
And I know you're ver--
I know you're very busy...
and I don't really feel
like swapping stories...
- Wait, wait, wait. No, no, no, wait.
- if you want to know the truth.
Hmm?
Okay, now tell me, Father, how long
has it been since your last drink?
Um, it's been about a minute and a half
since my last drink.
Of course.
Now, what about these kids?
Okay, um--
- Well, you see the one on the right?
- Mmm.
- The cu-- The cute one?
- Mm-hmm.
That's me.
- That's very cute.
- Brian Finn.
Paulie Chopra.
Okay, well-- Now, you see
this kid on the left?
- Mmm.
- That was my best friend Jake.
- He's a priest too?
-Jake?
No, um, as it--
as it turns out, Jake's a rabbi.
Come on. A priest and a rabbi?
I think I've heard this one.
No, look, I've heard all those, and,
trust me, you have not heard this one.
Okay? So there's this priest and
this rabbi, and they're best friends.
- Mmm.
- But before they were
a priest and a rabbi...
they both knew this girl.
- Ah, the girl.
- Yeah.
- Who's the girl?
- That's Anna Reilly.
Reilly? Let me guess.
She became a nun?
Not quite. Not quite.
See, we all met in the sixth grade
at P.S. 84 right here in Manhattan.
I think I already knew Jake,
and then we both met Anna.
No, wait, you know what? Actually,
I remember exactly how we met...
'cause, well, it was sort of
one of those defining moments.
Well, after that we were
pretty much inseparable.
Now, Jake and I were definitely
what you'd call "late bloomers."
And your average seventh-grade girl's
attentions can be pretty fickle.
But not Anna.
Her loyalty to us was constant.
Anna was the friend
that every 13-year-old boy dreams of.
You know, that magical cross between
Jonny Quest and Tatum O'Neal in Foxes.
Yes! Yes!
Yeah, we were some trio. Anna used
to call us "two Micks and a Yid."
She was gonna make T-shirts.
You know, there's eight million
people in New York...
but when the three of us were together
it felt like we were living
on our own little island.
But New York is an island.
I'm trying to sprinkle
a little fairy dust here.
- I'm-- I'm trying to tell a story.
- I'm terribly sorry.
- Continue. Go on. Sprinkle away.
- Mm-hmm. Okay.
Well, then disaster struck.
The summer after eighth grade,
Anna's father got a job in California...
and just like that,
she was gone.
Well, as for me and Jake, our friendship
just got stronger and stronger.
In most ways, we were like
any other two kids in New York...
but our relationship did have
this one unusual component--
we were fascinated
with each other's religions.
He showed me
the secret rituals of Judaism...
and I let him in on
the Catholic mysteries.
Just remember:
spectacles, testicles, watch, wallet.
I bet you're wondering what makes two
kids wanna become a priest and a rabbi
in this day and age.
Well, you know, people don't talk
that much about a calling any more...
but I just knew it was something
I was supposed to do.
And even way back then,
everybody just seemed to feel good
bringing their problems to me.
My parents had basically given up
on children when I came along...
so my mother always called me
her gift from God.
That really stuck with me, and when
I was eight I told her I had a feeling
I was supposed to return the favour.
She was so happy, she cried.
My dad just wanted to know
if working for God came with dental.
Now, Jake's sense of a calling
might not have gelled as early as mine.
Religion was really more
of a hobby for him at first.
Got it. Got it.
Need it. Need it.
Need it. Got it.
Jake was just one of those
special kids, you know.
He was smart, popular.
Everything came easy to him.
He just had that kind of aura about him.
You took one look at this kid
and you knew he could do anything
he wanted with his life.
Jake's family had been in the investment
banking business for three generations.
His father and his brother Ethan
both tried to convince him
to join them at the family firm.
I think he gave it some serious thought,
but in the end he decided he wanted
to do something different with his life.
When he made his decision
to become a rabbi, he did it
with great confidence and resolve.
I don't want to listen to any of you!
Jake and I went off to seminary
the way other guys go off to the army
or the Peace Corps.
It was an adventure.
Newly ordained as masters of theology,
we were both assigned
back to New York City...
where we quickly confronted
the practical aspects of our jobs.
Oh! Jesus!
And despite these early setbacks,
we eventually found our groove.
- Take it nice and easy.
Win 'em over slowly. Okay?
- Okay.
Shabbat shalom, everyone.
Before we get started,
I want you all to do me a favour.
I want everybody in the back there
to come on forward and fiIl up
these first three rows here.
Oh, guys, come on.
Let's try one more time. Shabbat shalom!
- Shabbat shalom!
- Thank you, Mom.
Ma'am, you in the back.
Yes, you. Come on.
God hates a solo artist,
I promise you.
We're gonna be the Fugees here
this morning. No Lauryn Hills.
Okay, my mom is the only person
in the room...
approximating the level
of "Shabbat shalom"-iness
that I think we can hit.
Sir, you're leaving. Why-- I--
It's customary to sneak out
after the Communion.
Now, give me something I can work with,
folks. Shabbat shalom!
- Shabbat shalom!
- All right! Now we're ready to daven!
I don't want to brag, but the word got
out that there was a new act in town...
and soon we were playing to
the packed houses I always knew
we'd been destined for.
I know. I know!
I-- I-- I know.
But seriously, what is the story
of Sodom and Gomorrah really about?
- Anybody. Steve Posner.
- Sexual perversion.
Sexual perversion.
Steve Posner's watching
a little too much Spice Channel, okay.
The Seven Deadly Sins.
Who can name the Seven Deadly Sins?
People, it was a very popular film
with Brad Pitt.
You have the ultimate Cliff note.
And Lot takes them in
and he protects them.
What happens next? Anybody.
Ah.
Greta Nussbaum,
before she pulls her rotator cuff.
God spares Lot and his family.
Bingo! Two-week cruise for Greta!
You're goin' to the Bahamas!
You know,
when you think about it...
God is a lot like
Blanche Du Bois.
He's always relied on
the kindness of strangers.
And that's really what the story
is about-- it's about us
taking care of each other.
God relies on us
to take care of each other.
The truth is, I don't really
learn that much about your faith
by asking questions like that...
because those aren't really
questions about faith,
those are questions about religion.
And it's very important
to understand the difference
between religion and faith.
Because faith is not about
having the right answers.
Faith is a feeling.
Faith is a hunch, really.
It's a hunch that there is something
bigger connecting it all...
connecting us all together.
And that feeling, that hunch, is God.
And coming here tonight,
on your Sunday evening...
to connect with that feeling,
that is an act of faith.
And so all I have to do is look around
the room at this packed church...
to know that we're doing pretty well
as a community.
Even if all of you
failed my pop quiz miserably.
Let us pray.
Jake and I used to talk about how we
needed to kick the dust off our faiths,
bring 'em up to speed with the times.
No more of the old routines.
Jake said, "We're gonna give 'em
an old-world God with a new-age spin."
Feel the prana.
Our first big idea was to turn
this abandoned gay disco...
into a joint Catholic-Jewish
senior centre-slash-karaoke lounge.
You know, sort of a Fiddler on the Roof
meets Lord of the Dance...
meets Buena Vista Social Club.
Not an easy idea to sell
to some of the higher-ups...
but that's what we lived for--
to push the envelope.
You know, we were gonna bring our
religions into the 21 st century
any way we could.
We were gonna shove 'em a little,
if we had to.
Jake said we were gonna be like those
young cops who come on the force
and shake things up.
You know-- the God Squad.
Well, it's just like the ocean
under the moon
Well, it's the same as the emotion
that I have for you
You got the kind of lovin'
that can be so true, yeah
So give me your heart
Make it real
Or else forget about it
Come on, bring it. Nice.
Oh. So Ben Lewis comes into my office
this morning, tells me he's retiring.
- Rabbi Lewis?
- Yeah.
- Wow, that's the end of an era.
- I know.
But that's exciting. How long before
they give it over to you officially?
Well, I'm telling you,
there are a few backwards thinkers
on that board who just--
They don't get what I do.
You know?
Plus, there's the whole thing
about me being single.
- Single?
- Don't think that's not an issue.
Wait a minute, wait a minute,
are you seriously telling me that
if you don't find a nice Jewish girl...
and settle down in the next six months,
they're not gonna give you this job?
I'm seriously telling you
that-- that there's not been
a bachelor head rabbi of B'Nai Ezra...
since the beginning of the synagogue.
- Wow. I mean--
- I know. It's--
You'd better start
getting out there more.
- Tell me about it. It's embarrassing.
- Okay, okay, but forget about that.
You do want to meet somebody, right?
No, I'm just saying that I want
to meet somebody in a spontaneous
and casual manner, that's all.
- And it's almost impossible with me.
- Why? I don't understand that.
- Because I'm a rabbi.
- Yes. Yes. What's your point?
The point is that every time
I go out with a woman I don't know
if she likes me just for me...
or because I'm Rabbi Jake.
You know?
There's a certain expectation.
It's like, I can't go with my impulses.
I have to-- I don't know.
Jews want their rabbis
to be the kind of Jews that
they don't have the time to be.
Yeah, and Catholics want their priests
to be the kind of people
they don't have the discipline to be.
- So, we knew this getting into it.
- Right.
Oh, no, man. Check this out.
- God Squad in the house.
- What's up, Shabazz?
Okay, so, you gonna give it up, Rabbi,
or are we gonna have to
go through the motions?
Get ready to say your prayers, my
friends, 'cause I am in no mood today.
- Watch your ass, Shabazz!
- Come on
Turn me loose
Just turn it up
Power to the people, y'all
- Turn it loose, hey
- Oh!
Shake hands with the 8-0-8
Like I said before
PE got a brand new funk
- Turn it up
- Bye.
- Good game, Shabazz.
- Tell your mother I said "hi."
All right.
Power to the people
I gotta quit playing with those guys
from Jewish Theological Seminary.
It really lowers the bar.
Oh, can I just say "oy"?
Amen to your "oy."
- What happened to our youth?
- I'm telling you, it ended at 30, pal.
Oh, hey, speaking of our youth,
I forgot to tell you something.
- What?
- This is big. Guess who called me.
- Who?
- Okay.
Think about who is the coolest woman
you and I have ever known, ever.
That's easy. Anna Reilly, eighth grade.
No question.
- You got it.
- What?
- She called you?
- Yeah.
- Anna Reilly called you?
- Yeah. Totally out of the blue.
- Why?
-'Cause she's coming to New York,
uh, for work...
and she wanted to get together
with us.
- She just looked me up.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Anna Reilly. What is she doing now?
She-- She's, like, analyzing synergies,
or synergising analogies,
or, or some such thing.
I couldn't follow it. She's, like, this
very high-powered business-- You know.
- Woman?
- Woman, yes. Thank you.
- Wow. And you told her about us?
- Yeah. She flipped,
in a-- in a good way.
You know, I mean, she laughed for about
ten minutes, but she was excited.
- Man, that is so cool.
- I know.
I wonder why she called you.
What do you mean?
No, I mean, she called you.
- What, are you
in the eighth grade still?
- What? That's a legitimate question.
I just-- I mean, we're both listed.
Finn before Schram, okay?
You're ridiculous.
That's a good point.
Alphabetical.
I think we should toss this.
We look like idiots.
- Shut up. We do not.
- You shut up.
- You think she's changed?
- No, I bet she still weighs 88 pounds
and listens to Leif Garrett.
For the record, it's Leif. Long "A."
Didn't you see the Behind the Music?
Hey, come on, admit it.
You're excited. This is gonna be great.
The three of us hanging together again?
I can't believe it.
- Is that her?
- No. No.
Wow.
- Hail Mary.
- Mary.
- Full of... something.
- Full of something'.
Hello, boys.
- I don't understand.
- Well, basically, I'm like a plumber,
except I fix leaky corporations.
- Oh.
-Jake Schram.
- Yes.
- How are you? Who are you?
Tell me everything. Give me the 4-1 -1 .
I wanna know.
- Well--
-Job, girls, news.
Oh, now, hey, come on, come on.
I know him. I know him. Y-You start.
Catch us up right now.
- All right. Job is good. Really good.
- Men.
News: My parents
are happy and retired.
- And, uh--
- Men?
- I take yoga.
- Men.
- That's my life.
- No.
- Men.
- Come on.
- Don't cheat us. G-Give it up.
- I don't-- Relationships? Yada-ya--
I don't have time for relationships.
I work, like, 100 hours a week.
- You guys have no idea.
- Hey. Hey.
- Excuse me. I think that we work
pretty hard for a tough...
- Yeah, working for the--
- That's a...
- boss.
- full-time thing.
No, I work harder than God.
If He had, uh, hired me, He would have
made the world by Thursday.
Great. That's great. So you're saying
that we're just never going to see you.
- Is that-- This is the big kiss-off.
- No, for you guys I will make time.
- Wow. I feel special.
- That's my bag.
- I got it. I got it.
- I got it.
- I got it, man. I got-- No, I got it.
Let me-- Let me-- I-I can get it.
Okay. Thanks.
- You okay?
- Yep-- No-- Go.
Remember the names of some of those kids
we went to school with?
- Remember Aram Salaam?
- Mm-hmm. His father
was a diplomat, right?
He was always saying
he couldn't get a parking ticket
'cause he had diplomatic immunity.
- Remember Elan Portnoy?
- Yeah, he was always complaining.
He was always smoking pot.
- Hey, remember our shoplifting club?
- Oh, yeah.
- You had to steal something
to be a member.
- How about you with the basketball?
Remember she stuck
that basketball under her shirt,
and you said you were pregnant?
- I pulled it off.
- Yeah, but you were twelve.
Yeah, but it was New York, it was the
'80s. You could get away with anything.
- We should get home, right?
- Huh?
- Yeah, it's getting kinda late.
- We should take you back.
- Well, I'm still on West Coast time.
It's only 8:00 my time.
Let's go do something.
So this is a rectory.
Sounds like a dirty word-- "rectory."
- Great place to meet chicks.
- Totally.
Oh, I'll bet.
So, what's your chick situation?
Oh, uh, don't ask.
It's, it's, it's not a good story.
- Why?
-'Cause his whole congregation's
trying to set him up...
and it makes him very uncomfortable.
- What's wrong with that?
- There's a reason that pandas
don't mate in captivity.
- What does that mean?
- It means that all these mothers
keep making these dates for me
They're very intimidating.
They're like the Kosher Nostra.
- Oh.
- It's true. They're little women,
but they're very determined.
You get a little melodramatic
about this, don't you think?
Oh, yeah? Check this out.
- I was faxed one of their daughter's
resumes this morning.
- Get out.
- Let me see that. "Ali Decker."
- Yeah. Look at the bottom.
- Oh. She has a skills section.
- Yes?
Oh. You win.
She put jogging as a skill.
See, she doesn't even know the
difference between a hobby and a skill.
- All right, well, maybe
she's a skilled jogger.
- I have to go on a date with this girl.
- Why don't I just say no?
- I don't know. Why don't you?
Because I can't alienate these women.
They-- I need body count at the temple.
Just relax. It'll be fine.
Oh, God, please let this be painless.
- Hi.
Right on time.
I like that in a rabbi.
Oh. Hey, this is a great place.
This is really--
- My lair.
- really nice.
- I'll be ready in a second.
- A lot of space.
I know.
Thanks, Daddy. Right?
You go, girl.
No pain, no gain.
Oh. Tuesdays with Morrie.
I love that book.
I'm ready.
- Oh, do you, uh, do these tapes?
- Are you kidding me?
- No.
- Hmm. No.
- These tapes are my life.
Exercise is like a religion to me.
No pun intended.
- Feel my abs. Not bad, right?
- Ouch.
- Punch me.
- Excuse me?
- You heard me.
- Um, I-I'm not gonna punch you.
I think you will find, Rabbi Schram,
that this princess is no pushover.
I can tell. And, hey, come on.
Call me Jake. All right?
Okay, let's get a few things
straight here, Jake.
One: I like you a lot.
And unless my radar is completely
on the blink, I think you like me.
- Well, I mean, we-- we just met, but--
- Two: I am many things.
No one thing defines me.
Are we clear about that, Jake?
- Yes.
- Then let me have it.
- I'm not gonna punch you.
- Punch me!
-You're a girl. I'm not gonna punch you.
-Hit me. I can take it.
- I'm not scared.
- I'm sure-- I know you're not.
I just-- You're a girl, and--
- What, are you some kind of wuss?
- No, I'm not a wuss--
- But I'm not gonna punch a--
Oh. All right.
- Little wuss, little wuss,
Oh. Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- You sure?
-J-Just get my bag.
- Okay. Uh, you said you could take it--
- Fine!
That's wonderful.
Th-That headband's so cool.
- Oh, I'm so glad you noticed.
- Yeah. What is that?
- It was-- It was beaded
by the mentally retarded.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
- Really? 'Cause it looks
really good, though.
- Oh, n--
Well, they're heavily supervised.
- Uh-huh.
- Th-They--
- Yeah, but it really-- i-it seems to--
- I mean--
- It goes together well, don't you feel?
- Oh.
- My God. Get a--
- Oh, no, no. That's--
- Get away from the table.
- Whoa, no, no, no.
- Get out of here.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. That's okay. Hey.
Hey, here, here, here.
D-Don't-- Don't-- Here.
- Thank you. Thank you. Have a nice day.
- You're flushing it down the toilet.
- Thank you. Don't-- You don't wanna--
- He's gonna spend it on booze.
Well, I had a great time.
Thank you. It was wonderful.
Uh, good night.
- Don't you want to come up, tuck me in?
- I-I-I shouldn't.
Believe me, you should.
No, I can't. I-I--
You're a congregant, and-- You know?
I'm telling you, you can.
I want you to.
I-- I-- I would love to.
I just-- I-I have a-- I got a--
I have a friend at home.
- A friend?
- A male friend. A guy.
A dog. A male dog.
- A beautiful puppy named Pinchas.
- Pooch can wait.
- No, no, no, he's a Rottweiler.
-Just come up for a minute
or two or three.
No, no, no, no! No! Don't! Don't.
No, listen to me. This dog
is a codependent little puppy.
He needs my help,
or else he'll go to the bathroom
over everything. He does it.
Well, send me the cleaning bill.
Get outta here.
- No, no, no. Don't get out. No, stay.
I-- I would-- It's not gonna--
- You are making me crazy, Rabbi.
- You're making me so-- No. No.
-Just come on. Just come up for me.
- Come on! For a minute!
- I can't!
-Just come on!
- Aah! Are you okay? Good!
- Oh, wow.
- Go! Go! Go!
- Hey! Hey!
- Thanks! I had a wonderful time!
See you in shul!
You're not playing games with me,
are you, Phil? You sure?
Okay, 'cause you know better
than that, right?
Okay. Well, if those results are
correct, then I, uh, say we have a deal.
Of course, I'll expect it in writing
by the end of the day.
Yes, by the end of the day, Phil.
What, did I stutter?
All right, Phil, you know what?
I don't have time for this, okay?
Gotta go, Phil.
Gotta go, gotta go.
No way.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Okay, okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. Take a break. Take a break.
I suck. They're gonna
take away my yarmulke.
- No, no, no, you-- you don't suck.
- I suck.
Okay. Yes, you do. You suck.
But that's okay. You're supposed to
suck. This isn't a talent contest,
this is a rite of passage.
I mean, this happens in all cultures.
It's about you being 13 years old.
God knew that your voice
was gonna change when you were 13.
There's a reason why you gotta do your
haftorah at this age. It's a challenge.
God is challenging you. He's calling you
a chump. So you gotta come back at him.
So you gotta say,
"Hey, hashem, you think You can scare me
with a little, uh, biblical Hebrew...
just 'cause my balls
haven't dropped yet?''
I'm serious. I'm serious. You gotta
show Him what Alan Klein's made of.
- How?
- By sucking with style.
Embrace the suckiness.
Just say, "I love that I suck."
- I love that I suck.
- Good, but own it. Say it.
- I love that I suck!
- I love that I suck.
- I love that I suck. Good. Good.
- You play. I love that I suck.
- I love that I suck.
- Keep going with that.
-Okay, good. I'll see you
next week. Hello?
-I love that I suck. I love that I suck.
-Hello?
-You suck. You can do it.
- Hey, Anna?
- I thought I got the Tony Robbins
hot line there by mistake.
Sorry. I just was, uh, finishing up.
How you doin'?
- I called to see how the big date went.
- That's so funny.
I had an impulse to call you
last night, and then I didn't
'cause I thought it'd be too late.
You should have. I was stuck here
barking at Los Angeles.
- Really.
- So, how'd it go?
Um, mostly horrible, with a few
brief moments of excruciating agony.
- But at least it was long.
- lam so sorry. What a waste.
People should have to qualify
to go out with you. You're too
precious to be on the open market.
- That's what I try to tell them.
- See? They should listen to you.
You're the best. You know that?
If only you were Jewish.
Yeah, well, nobody's perfect.
So, what'd you wear?
What?
I'm not gonna tell you what I wore
on my date. Why should I do that?
I wanna get an image of a young rabbi
on the prowl. What's your game, man?
All right.
Navy blue button-down shirt.
Mmm.
It's a good colour for your eyes.
- Navy blue pinstripe suit.
- I can picture that.
Tasteful,
yet with a quiet power.
That's me.
Chic but with a quiet power.
Shoes?
Black, Kenneth Cole, leather.
Size?
- Big.
- Ow!
Wanna hear about the special knot
in my tie?
Oh, baby, no.
We gotta save room for dessert.
- Don't give up hope. Okay?
- I'll keep it alive.
That's right.
Goodbye, Mr Sharp-Dressed Man.
Bye-bye.
Ah, nice.
I have a friend here
I thought you might want to see.
Will you now please turn
to page 508 for "Ein Keloheinu"?
I'm sorry, Raphae.
Just hang on one second here.
Guys, I gotta just say this
before we do this again...
because it's really
been bothering me.
"Ein Keloheinu. "
It's a joyous song.
It's a prayer
about praising the Lord...
telling the Lord how much
we love Him, or Her.
But no matter what I do, I can't
seem to be able to get you folks
to sing it with any feeling.
I mean, I brought in the band.
That didn't work.
I brought in my bongos last week.
I think we can all agree
that was a backwards step.
So this morning I've decided to bring in
a little outside help.
Maury, if you would.
You can even sing along!
Come on! Have a little fun with it!
That's right! Get up! Get those butts
out of those chairs! Come on!
Up in the cheap seats!
I can't hear you up there!
Sing it out! Come on!
Over 70!
Come on! All the young Jews!
Hey! Congratulations!
You were wonderful!
- Great job!
- Rabbi! Rabbi!
This is my daughter.
Isn't she lovely?
This is astonishing.
This is a shul.
This is a house of worship.
Do you know what my grandfather
would do if he saw this?
This is my daughter Ruthie.
She's in college.
She's going to be a physiotherapist.
What a shaineh maidel you are.
Look at this.
Oh, Rabbi, you're so wonderful.
You know my daughter Hillary.
Mom, don't embarrass me. Hi.
Jake, Bonnie Rose. I don't think
you've met my daughter Rachel.
- Hi, Jake.
- Oh! Hi.
This is exciting. We don't get
a lot of celebrities in here.
One time, once, when I was really young,
we had, uh-- Bella Abzug showed up
for a bris, but that was--
Well, I've heard so much about you,
I had to come and see for myself.
- The service was wonderful.
- Oh--
You were really, really wonderful.
Well, we're all certainly aware
of your successes.
You know, she just moved
to network prime time.
Ooh, look at that.
We got in a live feed.
- Well, my mom does all my PR.
- I know what you mean. Mine too.
No, I mean really.
My mother's firm does all my PR.
-Jake, I'm at PMK.
- Oh.
- We got her special correspondent.
- Great.
You know, she just got back
from interviewing Arafat.
- Yassir?
- In Arabic.
- That's great. I didn't know that.
-Jake, what you don't know is a lot.
You two should get together.
- Sure.
- I'm free on Thursday.
Thursday. That's--
That's fine-- That's great.
- Okay.
- Okay, great. Well,
nice to see you, Bonnie.
Rabbi. Wonderful.
- This is Hillary--
- Oh! This is-- This is the man
you were telling-- Right. Yes, sir.
Well, I appreciate what you did
for us in the war, I really do.
- How upset are they?
- Let's just say
they're less than thrilled.
-To be honest, we're less than thrilled.
-Okay, with what, specifically?
With what, specifically?
Well, with guided meditation,
specifically.
With stand-up comedy sermons,
With your loose, improvisational style,
specifically.
Okay, with people
actually enjoying services?
People-- People showing up at all?
To be serenaded by
the Harlem-freaking-Gospel Choir?
- At least they were praying.
- It was a hell of
an "Ein Keloheinu, " Lar.
- It's not kosher, Rabbi Lewis!
- Larry, what does that mean?
I have to tell you what kosher means?
Study your gemara!
I mean, is this you too?
Do you feel the same way?
It's not your ideas.
Your ideas are very good.
But sometimes you're a little aggressive
in the execution.
Yeah, but, Ben, come on!
I mean, I mean, it was working!
I know, I know, I know, I know.
- You like to shake things up,
and that's good.
- When it works, yeah.
But you have to appreciate the fact
that a lot of people come here
for a sense of continuity.
It's not just the board.
I-It's your congregation, Jake.
Mrs-- Mrs Katz likes to sing the
"Ein Keloheinu" the way she knows it.
- Tradition is not old habit.
- All right, I'm-- I'm--
- No. It's comforting to people.
- Okay, but I'm not interested
i-in baby-sitting Mrs Katz.
I-I wanna-- I wanna push people
to grow and expand.
- Otherwise, what are we doing?
- I know, I know, I know.
But you have to be patient
with them.
I think you'll get a-- you'll find
that people will go a lot farther...
if you-- if they feel
they're being led and not pushed.
Good for you, Anna.
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
No more of this
"woman behind the man" shit.
Half the men I know
are completely unworthy
of the opportunities they've had.
You know, as a woman on your own,
trying to make your mark...
what do you do with that victory energy
at the end of the day, you know?
- I mean, don't you want
someone to share it with?
- Well, do what they do. Take lovers.
- I've had more dates than Jake.
- Mom.
It's true.
And when lovers bore, which they
will, sublimate. I take classes.
Me too. I'm addicted to it.
What's your favourite?
- Kabbalah. You?
- Kickboxing.
Oh, I used to take kickboxing, but I
don't know, I found it too high-impact.
So I take Tae-Bo now. It's doubled my
energy. You really ought to try it.
- Yeah. I need that high impact though.
- Yeah, I know what you mean.
- I take Native American drumming.
- You take Tae-Bo?
Oh, look at those pomegranates, huh?
Oh.
Oh, Our Lady's Bedstraw.
The most poetic herb.
All right, now over to you. Anybody
new in your life I should know about?
Wow, 20 minutes.
I can't believe we made it this far.
It's my God-given right to check.
Now, what about that Shapiro girl?
- Oh, no, not the Shapiro girl
again, please.
- Why? She was a looker.
- That wasn't the problem.
The problem was here.
- What, bad skin?
- No, not bad skin.
- What?
Okay, all right, you want an example?
I take her out to dinner, I order
dessert, she says she doesn't want any.
So I get pecan pie.
She asks me for a bite.
I give her a bite.
Her face swells up like a chipmunk.
She looks at me and she goes,
"Oh, my God, are there nuts in this?"
- So what?
- Mom, it was pecan pie.
- Oh, there must be somebody
for you. Come on.
- Oh, no, I don't even want
- Oh, come on. Tell her.
- I don't want to talk about it.
- He's got a very hot prospect.
- Oh? Who? Who?
Rachel Rose! Okay? Rachel Rose.
That's who I'm going out with.
- ABC Rachel Rose?
- Yes, ABC Rachel Rose.
Well, I think I could be in-laws
with ABC Rachel Rose. Hmm?
Peter Jennings would be at the wedding!
Hey, hey, speaking of in-laws,
Ethan and Jackie took me to see her
mom's new play, and it was hilarious.
- How is Ethan?
- He's great. He just got a promotion.
He's a vice president now.
- They gave him Dad's old office.
- Oh.
How nice.
I gotta hear this from you.
- Hey, maybe if you called
and congratulated him--
- I don't want to talk about it.
- Mom, he would be so happy
to hear from you. Just--
- Please, Jake, please.
Don't spoil this, huh?
I got you. I'm proud of you.
I got this beautiful garden. I've
reconnected with this great old friend.
Let's just hold hands and breathe, hmm?
Together.
- You're not breathing, Jake.
- I'm breathing.
-I don't hear you breathing.
-I don't breathe audibly, but I breathe.
- Mm-hmm?
- Whoo.
All right, you know what?
I gotta go. I gotta go. I gotta go.
- I've gotta go. Yes, I've gotta go.
- I gotta go. Really gotta go.
- All right, all right. Hi.
- Why don't you just have that thing
implanted in your ear?
- Oh, I'll be top on the list.
- Beep-beep!
- Oh-- Oh.
- Hello, young sir!
- Hello, Radioman.
- I feel like I'm in The Godfather.
Look at you.
Yeah, well, you know, I'm God's
consigliere. You gotta go through me
to get to Him, so I'm very popular.
Oh, whoa. Children. Hey.
I totally forget
how amazing New York is.
I know. You know, I think
whoever said it, it was really true.
The true New Yorkers understand that
people living anywhere else must be,
in some sense, kidding.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Yeah, obviously. Anything.
It's personal, so--
- Okay, wait a second.
Are we gonna have the sex talk here?
Is that what this is gonna be?
You're my friend,
and I wanna know how this works for you.
- It's fine. Fire away.
- Really?
- "Really?"
- No-- Okay. Okay.
- Yeah, no, come on. Come on.
I know you got a list.
- Okay.
- Well, you don't, right?
- No. Right.
- At all.
So, have you ever?
- Yes!
- Had sex?
- Yes.
- With women.
- So you're not gay?
- Oh, no. No.
- Are you sure?
Yes, but even if I was,
the rules are the same.
- Okay.
- Right.
- Do you miss it?
- No.
- Are you tempted?
- Oh, admit it. If they changed
the rules, you'd be psyched.
- I don't even think about it.
- Do you fantasize?
- I have dreams sometimes,
but not really.
- How is that possible?
- What, specifically?
- I've seen the way women look at you.
- Even though they know you're a priest.
Especially when they know, actually.
- I'm not blind, okay?
- Okay, so how do you deal with that?
- It's not an issue for me.
- It's really not. It's not--
- Really?
- Yeah, I'm past that point. It's--
I'm completely committed to what I do.
I really am.
To my work, to ministering to people.
It defines me completely as a person.
- A-And it fulfills me. You know?
I'm very happy.
- Hmm.
And, and that, that particular
sacrifice is-- It's a gesture.
It's a symbol of my commitment.
- That's quite a gesture.
- Yeah, I know it seems that way.
But, you know, I-- It's like
when people quit smoking, and,
and the first year is really tough...
and then people
can light up right in front of you
and it doesn't even bother you.
I quit smoking two years ago.
When people smoke in front of me,
I want to French-kiss them...
just to suck the smoke
out of their lungs, okay?
- Well, don't be a priest.
- I-- God!
I really admire your commitment.
- Well--
- I don't think I could take it.
You've given up all kinds of things
for what you do. You--
Yeah, but there comes a point
where I just crave contact.
You know? Like, I-I wanna
touch someone and be touched.
Oh, you're amazing.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Thus endeth the sex conversation?
- Thus endeth.
Okay.
I bet no one ever asks
the Dalai Lama these questions.
You know what?
Len, don't argue with me.
Look, I have it right here
in front of me, and it's not right.
I'll be back in the office in an hour.
Run it again.
God, I hate these Harvard guys.
Mmm! Rachel Rose.
- Mmm.
- Yeah. When's that going down?
- Thursday.
- Thursday night, 8:00 p.m., dinner.
- Are you excited?
- Yeah. I have a pretty good feeling.
- Where are you taking her?
- I don't know. I thought, uh, Ernie's.
Ernie's? You can't take her to Ernie's.
Ernie's has been around
since we were kids.
You might as well
take her to Houlihan's.
You cannot take Rachel Rose to Ernie's.
- Definitely not Ernie's.
Definitely not. Mm-mmm. Uh-oh.
- No, you gotta take her
- No, hot. Definitely hot.
- Well, what's--
Okay, what's new and hot?
- What do we know about this girl?
- Rachel Rose, 29 years old,
Columbia School of Journalism.
- Middle East affairs expert.
- Perfect. Middle Eastern.
She can order in Arabic. Give her
a chance to shine. What's a good place?
Delphini's. Definitely Delphini's.
Four stars, New York Times.
Definitely Delphini's.
- Need a reservation. Delphini's.
- Now, are you gonna wear a suit,
or are you gonna go cas'?
I don't know. I don't know.
I hadn't thought about it. I guess cas'.
-No, suit.
-No, suit. Definitely suit. Definitely--
Hey, shut up, Rain Man.
Seriously. Enough, all right?
- Now you're making me think about this.
- Oh, relax. You'll do great.
Hey, what if you guys came with me?
What, you wanna bring a priest
to your first good date in two years?
That-- What kind of a strategy is that?
I don't want to bring a priest.
I wanna bring my friend Brian
and his girlfriend Anna.
We could m-make it like a double date.
Come on.
Pretend you're a couple. What's wrong
with that? What, are you busy? Huh?
- You can bring your cell phone. You'll
be totally connected the whole time.
- I'm always busy.
- That's not the point.
- What's the point, then?
- The point is, you're old enough
to date without a chaperone.
- Amen.
I don't need a chaperone, I just
need some help. Come on. Guys, please?
I'm begging you.
Yeah, that's the way the business
is going. People want their news
to have more of an edge.
- That's why Brokaw stands now.
- What?
Tom Brokaw. He stands up
when he reads the news.
- The whole time?
- Yeah.
- He does?
- Well, he's been doing it
for about a year now.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- I gotta watch the news more.
You know, I saw your saringas report.
It was very powerful.
Thanks. I really earned my stripes
with that piece.
Mmm. I earned my stripes by getting
through a bris without fainting.
- I talked Mc Donald's
out of the Mc Oyster.
- And a grateful nation thanks you.
- Made me a star.
- So, how long have you two
been together?
- Oh, right, uh--
- Oh, God, like-- Oh, we go way back.
We've all known each other since we were
kids, 'cause we grew up together.
- I used to have a crush on Anna.
- Really?
- I told you that.
- Did not!
- She knew that.
- No, you didn't.
- Mm-hmm.
- I--
- Well, anyway, we reconnected.
A couple months ago, this was,
and, and we just clicked.
Uh, very unexpectedly, but--
Oh, G-- I think it's so great
to be friends first. Don't you?
Always. Friends first.
So, do you write your own reports,
or how does that work?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, yeah.
- Well, I wouldn't trust anybody else
to get 'em right, you know.
- Right, right.
- I mean, you write
your own sermons, right?
- Mmm.
Actually, I download them off the net.
There's this great service.
- It's called www.hotgod.com.
- Really?
Ow! Ooh. No.
- No, I was kidding.
- Oh. So you-- you do
write your own sermons.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- He writes beautiful sermons.
Thanks. Actually, I like to improvise
a lot. You know, keeps everybody--
myself included-- on their toes.
I-I-I guess you really can't do that
too much with your job, with the news.
- What?
- Riff.
Oh, mmm, no, not really.
You know, I'll bet the Middle East
is lovely this time of year, huh?
Well, not if you're Kurdish.
Mmm.
Excuse me.
Oh, my God. The Iraqi defence minister
just committed suicide.
- Oh.
- Ooh.
- Is that bad or good?
Well, i-- Brian,
would you explain it to him?
I will.
- How do you think it's going?
- She's really beautiful.
- Sh-She's great too.
- Yeah.
- She's very adult.
- Oh, y-you're doing great. We've
been-- We've been totally impressed.
- You look so hot in your suit.
- Can I just tell you?
- Thank you.
- You look beautiful.
- You do. You look amazing.
- Thanks, men.
- Yeah, there's something about you.
I don't know what it is.
- Tonight there's some special--
- An absence of something.
- Of the cell phone.
- Uh-uh-uh. It's set to vibrate.
Oh, my-- Wow. That's sexy.
- Did you ever just wanna
be free of that thing?
- No-- You don't understand.
I-- I have a relationship
with my phone.
We have a chemistry together.
I can't explain it.
Yeah, well,
chemistry's a funny thing.
Yes, it is. Are you speaking
abstractly or specifically?
Abstractly.
Well, looks like
I'm going to Baghdad.
Two seconds. Two seconds.
So, it was a pleasure.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah. Take care.
- It was nice to meet you.
- Yes. Good luck to both of you.
- Thank you.
- I'll talk to you soon.
- Okay. All right. Okay.
- Okay.
- I'll-- I'll talk to you.
- Okay. Okay, call me.
- All right. Okay, thank you.
- Okay. Call me soon.
- Thanks again.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
What are you thinking about
right now?
Oh, it's funny.
I was at the Met yesterday.
- Again?
- I go every week now. And I
noticed this little painting.
It was a watercolour
by Bonnard, and I've probably
passed it every single time...
and I don't know why,
but this time I looked at it.
And I was just-- I was riveted.
It was so beautiful.
That's all. I was just wondering
why I never saw it before.
Well, I mean, sometimes...
we don't see certain things
till we're ready to see'em...
in a certain way.
You know?
Very true.
Yeah.
Hey, what's going on
with Ruth and Ethan?
Oh, uh--
Ethan married a Catholic girl,
and that did not go over well.
- That's why they're fighting?
- No, no, they're not fighting.
They're not talking.
Two years now, no comunicado.
- Are you serious?
- Totally. It's--
What? Weren't they
really close, though?
- Oh, as close as Ruth and Jake.
- Wow.
- Well, that explains a lot.
- Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, you see why tonight
is not just a date.
I feel really terrible about
having to cut the night short.
- You know, if they--
- That's fine. I totally understand.
- I mean, when the beeper beeps--
- You know, I'm just gonna be packing.
Would you, um, like to come up
for a nightcap?
- Keep me company?
- Uh, um--
I would love to, but I think
I should let you do your thing.
- I mean, you gotta
go to Baghdad. I mean--
- Yeah. Yeah.
- So.
- Long flight. I know.
- Yeah.
- It-- Well, okay.
But when you get back,
we should definitely get together.
- I would love to.
- Okay.
- It's a date.
- Okay. All right.
- Bye.
Bye.
Taxi!
- Well, this is me.
- Okay.
- You wanna come up for a while?
- Oh.
I would love to, but I really
should get home, because I have
a very early conference call.
Me too. I mean,
I gotta talk to the Big Guy.
- Right.
- He calls early.
- Rain check, though.
- Yeah. Definitely.
- Definitely.
- Okay.
Good night.
- Good night.
- Hi.
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
What am I doing here?
I haven't screamed that hard since
the U.S. hockey team beat the Russians.
You're incredible.
I've been wanting to do that since the
second you walked off that aeroplane.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Right away?
You hadn't seen me in 16 years.
I know, and you were this, like, tough,
sexy, straight-ahead businesswoman.
I just wanted to pull you off into
Security and give you a cavity search.
Now that would have been impulsive.
Yeah, well,
this is pretty impulsive for me.
- Believe me.
- But good, though, right?
Yeah, good, just, I mean, could get
a little complicated. You know?
Well, what would people at work think
if they knew you were sleeping
with a rabbi?
Could be a scandal.
Oh.
- Listen.
- Yeah.
You know what my life is like.
- I'm only here for a little while.
- Yes.
And I'm fine just hanging out
having a great time with you.
Mm-hmm.
But sometimes I wanna jump you too.
What can I say?
Is that okay?
Yeah, it's okay.
It's more than okay.
Think we should say anything
to Brian?
I-I think it might be
a little weird for him.
You don't think he'd understand?
No, I just--
I don't know.
I think we should
just keep it simple.
I'm for simple.
I have something simple
that I'd like to discuss with you.
Do you wanna know
If everythin' glitterin'
Will turn into the gold
I see in your hair
Feel it could be there
Somehow
Tonight
And do you wanna fight
Somethin' worth savin'
The change would do me right
'Cause I've been just waitin'
And hesitatin' with this heart
Of
Mine
You're still a mystery
But there's somethin' so easy
In how you're sweet to me
I feel completed
Like it's somethin' I needed
for this heart
Of
Mine
There's always somethin'
so tragic
About a hopeless romantic
We have a Jake Schram here
for Anna Reilly.
Yes? Okay.
Hey, you know, I'm gonna be coming here
a lot, so maybe in the future we don't
have to do this whole name thing...
and you could just say, "Hey, Jake,"
and I could say, "Hey, T-Bone."
- That pass is good for one hour.
- Okay. Thank you.
Wednesday night, you have
a due diligence call at 7:00...
and a dinner at 8:00.
All right. I'm make the call,
but cancel the dinner. I have a class.
Oh, he's late.
Oh, my God.
Are you guys getting serious?
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Yes, you are.
- No, we're not.
- I saw it. I can tell.
- No, no, no.
- I--
- Oh, it's-- He's here.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Uh, Debbie, this is Jake.
Jake, vice versa.
- Hi.
- Hi. How you doing?
Hi, Jake. Can I just say, um,
good-- good for you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Uh, Debbie?
- Debbie, Debbie, Deb-- What?
- Oh! Th-- Um, the numbers
are good for you, yeah?
- Good.
Good. Just run one more scenario
and assume an eight-percent I RR
and PV it to present day.
Bye.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org