Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
In New York City's war on crime,
the worst criminal offenders
are pursued by the detectives
of the Major Case Squad.
These are their stories.
Allahu Akbar.
Chilly, don't leave these behind.
He wears bikinis.
Cold beer.
Cold beer here.
Cold beer. Cold beer here.
Nice, cold beer.
Cold beer.
Cold beer. Cold beer.
Dude, look what I found.
This is awesome.
It's probably worth a lot of money.
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
딕테이션
이근양(kylee322@nate.com)
싱크편집
윤선영(seedyun@nate.com)
한글번역
이준섭(spawnhero@nate.com)
빈센트 도노프리오
(로버트 고렌 형사 役)
캐쓰린 어브
(알렉산드라 임즈 형사 役)
에릭 보고시안
(대니 로스 경감 役)
Law & Order CI
7x05. Depths
번역수정
김난주(nanjidoo@nate.com)
한글교정
도정원(winniedo@nate.com)
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON USA: 2007/11/01
Floater in a scuba suit washing up
on the hottest day of the year.
No ID.
He might have been stabbed.
I hate the beach.
Why call major case?
Someone called the FBI
told them he looked Middle Eastern.
Thought you'd want to get here
before they did.
What about the coast guard?
Anyone call in a missing diver?
Not in two weeks.
Seems fresher than that.
Yeah, his corneas,
they're not even cloudy.
He's been in the water
less than a day.
And who decided
that he was Middle Eastern?
I mean, take a look around.
Half our CSU guys look like him.
Digital camera might
have a date stamp.
Might even have a picture of his killer.
We got entry wounds...
Right here on his side.
Something penetrated his suit.
And slashed his air tube.
It's a closed circuit re-breather.
Agent Corbett, FBI.
Instead of exhaling into the water,
the diver breathes out
to that CO2 scrubber.
Come back at him as oxygen.
No bubbles.
Technical divers use it
when they stay underwater
for long periods of time.
Or a terrorist who doesn't
wanna be detected
while he's taking pictures of
our underwater gas lines.
So you think he's a terrorist?
Why else would someone
go diving in this muck?
It's late summer, you know.
Gulf stream brings in non-native
species from the Caribbean.
Yeah, butterfly fish.
You know angel fish.
You'd be surprised.
If I find any pictures of Nemo,
you'll be the first one I call.
He drowned?
He was stabbed.
Twice. In the side.
Pierced his kidney.
Didn't kill him, but made it hard for him
to swim to the surface.
What was he stabbed with?
Based on the morphology
of the wound blunt on top,
serrated on the bottom,
a notch right there,
it'd be something like this.
This knife's his,
but the killer would have had his own.
And they say it's safer
to dive with a partner.
Good morning, Rogers.
Captain.
FBI matched the prints from the body
with a British national.
They give you a name?
We've been summoned.
Our lab managed to salvage these photos.
From the diver's camera.
Underwater natural gas line.
Holland Tunnel.
Retaining wall near the UN.
All high value targets.
As for the deceased,
inspector Lindsay
from Scotland yard will take over.
Diver's name is Tarek Agiza.
Goes by the western name of Rick.
29, born in Egypt.
Comes from a scholarly family
of Islamic extremists.
- Which one, Jamaat Al-Islamiyya?
- You got it.
His father and grandfather
have been active since the 70s.
Rick has mostly managed
to stay under the radar.
Mostly?
You arrested him for something
non-terror related?
Yeah, for public drunkenness in 2000.
Shortly after he arrived in London
to start University.
He dropped out after 9/11.
Since then, Rick has traveled
extensively to Muslim countries.
Or ones with large Muslim communities.
Croatia, New Zealand, Indonesia.
New Zealand. Wow.
Is there a large community
of Muslims in New Zealand?
Relatively small, but growing fast.
All this travel,
how's he pay for it?
He has no known job,
but look in his bank account,
and, oh my, erratic deposits
of large amounts of cash.
So, protocol, we'll continue with
the murder investigation.
While we track down
the rest of Rick's cell.
Remember, Patriot Act gives us
certain liberties regarding searches.
We'll keep each other posted.
Hopefully Rick's terror cell
won't get past the research stage.
Rick dropped out of college
and was arrested for drinking.
Aren't terrorist supposed
to be a little more disciplined than that?
Well, with his family history,
maybe he didn't wanna fit the profile.
Yeah, or maybe he's just
the black sheep of the family.
And his travel.
Could be another explanation.
We gotta go back to Coney Island.
I'm out here every day, I told you.
You keep on ignoring
the beeps, why is that?
Can you tell the difference between
a bottle cap and a coin with that thing?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It beeps different.
My partner, he loves Gadgets.
I hid a bottle cap and a coin.
Tell me which is which.
- There's your bottle cap.
- Yeah?
That's coin.
That's another coin.
This a new hobby for you, Walter?
Yesterday, when the body washed up,
you and a bunch of guys
were looking for something. What?
Dammit, I gave that kid ten bucks
and an icy for that coin.
And I let him keep the fish
he found it in.
A fish with a coin in its mouth?
Where did you read that,
in the Bible, Walter?
In its belly.
Bluefish will eat anything.
I don't believe it.
We're gonna wanna borrow this.
You just, um...
It's an 1861 double eagle.
Is this what Rick was after?
Exotic travel, unexplained cash.
Rick wasn't a terrorist.
He was a treasure hunter.
- I'll take one of those.
- What, you still don't trust me?
Where's Rick? Huh?
- What?
- What's he doing?
I don't know.
I swear to God I don't know.
Okay.
All right. Have it your way.
One key for you, one key for me.
Until we hear from Rick...
You and me stick together.
What do we know about the diver?
Every country Rick Agiza traveled
to has a coast known for wreck diving.
Including here.
This area between Long Island
and New Jersey, it's called wreck valley.
Each X marks a sunken ship.
Well, it marks some of them.
There are thousands.
Dating back to the 1600s.
Privateer ships, gunrunners, slave ships.
So Rick's dive partner killed him
then framed him as a terrorist.
Modern day pirates
still killing over treasure.
Divers and recovery companies
are supposed to file for permission
before bringing anything up,
so check the court records,
but don't hold your breath.
You know, one 1861 gold coin
sells for around $3,000.
You mean sold for 3,000.
In the last two days, prices have
dropped on several civil war-era coins.
I'd give you 800 bucks.
Well, for Pete's sake,
it's a 150 years old.
The numismatic market
is extremely volatile.
- Take it somewhere else.
- We already did.
They said you're the guy
who buys stolen coins.
Oh, man. Those were stolen?
No, she told me that she inherited them
from her great aunt.
She. Let me guess,
she was pretty
and you didn't ask questions.
Between you and I, she was smokin'.
How smokin'?
Kinda old. Like, 28.
But kickass body,
short, blond hair.
Did she bring any double eagles?
Maybe a couple.
Or more.
I checked the police sheet.
None of these were reported stolen.
Did you even ask for ID?
I was asking for her license,
but she flew out of here.
- She was getting a ticket.
- Yeah, right.
No, really, she was parked
in front of the hydrant.
Meter maid wouldn't cut her a break.
I got 9 company cars
and 15 authorized drivers.
I have no idea who got this ticket.
So this would be the bright pink
Benz convertible
driven by a smokin blond with a great body.
Maybe your girlfriend.
Somebody you'd want to be your girlfriend.
She's my wife, buddy.
Dana and I are separated.
- Recently?
- Two years ago.
But she still works with you
here at Camelot.
No, not for two years.
Dana's a diver. It's...
one of two things
she has a special talent for.
She ever dive with a guy named
Rick Agiza?
I wouldn't know.
We're out of touch.
What's the last address
you have for her, Mr. Stipe?
It's a condo on Manhattan beach
two years old.
I gave her the down payment.
Do me a favor.
Tell her to pay
her own parking tickets.
Guess she didn't bother to tell Stipe
she cashed out his condo
and traded down for this.
Wait for a warrant?
I don't know, it's still an active
terror investigation.
I got three pairs of Jimmy Choo heels.
Four Versace dressed, never worn.
Looks like Dana went on a shopping spree.
Eames.
I've got Rick Agiza's passport.
So he's staying here?
I can see a European in these.
But these?
Different size.
Another guy.
Dana's been busy.
Last call was from Camelot.
Maybe Stipe did know she moved.
- 2:00 pm.
- Right after we left.
So he sent us on a goose chase
and then tipped her off.
Uh, excuse me, Mr. Harper.
- Do I know you?
- My name's Chilly.
I work with Rick.
I need to talk to you
about the expedition.
Uh, Derek, why don't you
get us a couple lattes?
I'm not sure if you know this,
but we found something down there.
A lot more than Rick told you about.
It's gonna cost a lot to bring it out.
I didn't tip Dana off.
I called to tell her
I want my car back.
You're a bad liar, Mr. Stipe.
Which brings us
to your wife's lover, Rick Agiza.
Sure you don't remember him?
Yeah, okay, Rick did a job for me
in Charleston a few years ago.
He was trying to con my clients
into financing his expedition.
- Now, if you will excuse me...
- Hey, hey, hey...
You think we could see a picture of Dana?
You don't happen to have one, do you?
Wow, she's beautiful.
Guess you could see it
all day long right there.
Guess you're still in love with her, huh?
Makes me wonder how far
you'd go to get her back.
Maybe this far?
Someone killed Rick
while he was still underwater.
- I had nothing to do with this.
- Come on, man.
You own of the largest wreck recovery
businesses in the east coast.
You're telling me that you had nothing to do
with Dana's dive in wreck valley.
I can't dive.
I tore my labyrinthine
membrane five years ago.
All right, then it's not you, it's Dana.
Dana would never willingly go along
with something like this.
Willingly?
Yesterday, when I called to ask her
what this was all about,
she sounded... off, like someone else
was in the room.
Did you hear a voice?
No, but I know Dana's.
I could hear fear in it.
And that's why I told her
to get out of there.
And go where?
Well, how would I know?
Before yesterday, I hadn't
talked to her in over a year.
They found Dana Stipe's
pink Benz at JFK,
but there's no flight record.
And she hasn't used her credit
card or cell phone since yesterday.
And we believe Stipe when he says
he hasn't been in contact with her.
I pulled his LUDs.
He called her obsessively
for the first six months,
then went cold turkey till yesterday.
Doesn't rule out Stipe
as Agiza's murderer.
That's all we need to know.
So Stipe's doctor confirms that
he has an inner ear condition.
He can only dive as deep as a pool.
Well, then maybe he captained the boat
and Dana killed Agiza.
Or maybe there's a third man.
Stipe told us that he sensed
someone else in the room
threatening Dana
when he spoke to her.
And we did find two different sizes
of men's underwear at her place.
If there was someone else
on the treasure dive,
whoever funded the expedition
might know who it was.
Take a look at Stipe's investor list.
Tell him we'll subpoena
if he doesn't hand it over.
I met Rick on a dive I funded in Charleston.
The Philomela?
Tom Stipe said it was a civil war wreck.
Yes, they never found it.
And then over Christmas
I bumped into Rick in St. Bart's.
Was he with this woman?
No.
That was the first time
Rick and I hung out.
He's charismatic.
Great ocean stories.
My wife and I were enthralled.
Well, after enthralling you,
did he approach you
about the dive in wreck valley?
Yes, he said he had a good lead
on a revolutionary war era ship.
Revolutionary war?
We were told that it was civil war era.
Must be a different expedition.
Excuse me.
Here's a copy of his proposal.
Maps, sketches, budget.
The HMS Falkirk.
After the battle.
We don't have any record
of you applying for ownership.
Well, Rick said they hadn't...
found anything yet.
I've been calling him for days.
He won't be calling you back.
Rick's body washed up on Monday.
Oh, my God.
I didn't realize...
Something you're not
telling us, Mr. Harper?
Yesterday I was approached by this man
who called himself Chilly.
He said he's working on the dive.
And that Rick took off
with my seed money.
50 grand.
You call the cops?
I was waiting to hear
Rick's side of the story.
This man, Chilly, he knew Rick
wasn't coming back.
Did he want money?
To further the expedition?
Yes, he wanted half a million to launch
a full-scale operation.
I tried to get a number, an address.
He said he lived on a boat.
That' he'd get in touch with me.
What'd he look like?
Six foot. Athletic, tan.
I'm not good with faces.
Detectives, this is my wife Trisha.
You're, uh... congratulations.
Thank you.
- Are we done here?
- Yes.
If... if you hear from your
friend again, Mr. Harper,
- give us a call.
- I certainly will.
You don't by chance
know what you're having?
A boy.
Simon Harper IV?
Oh, we were thinking of Josiah.
Nice.
Well, if he was hanging out
at a marina with Dana,
someone will remember her.
Sure, who wouldn't remember her?
A girl like that who can
captain a grand banks?
- She have her own boat?
- Nah.
She and some guy worked Chilly's boat.
Chilly?
He's the treasure hunter, right?
Takes people fishing, dives.
You know, anything to make a buck.
- His boat here now?
- It was here at sunrise.
But when I got back at 3:00,
it was gone.
All right, thanks.
Well, it doesn't look like Chilly's boat
was headed towards Harper's treasure.
Wreck site is closer to Southern Jersey.
The suspects went in the opposite direction,
heading northeast.
Hugging the coast
of Long Island for an hour.
Then they shut off their GPS.
Chilly's boat should be in this area.
Dana Stipe.
Chilly?
Someone pulled the anchor.
There's no one on this ship.
It's a ghost ship.
So they used these lift bags
to bring up the buckets of coins.
Could be Dana's size.
I found a computer.
Still wet.
In the trash.
A folder named Rick.
Those are the photos from the FBI
from Rick's camera.
On Chilly's computer.
Chilly might have framed Rick
as a terrorist before he killed him.
So, Dana and Chilly, they took
the rest of the treasure.
Staged their disappearance.
If they did, they'd need another boat.
I wonder where Dana would go to get one.
Yeah, that's Chilly.
His real name is Stan Chilton.
Used him as a day hire on charter boats.
He's working with Dana?
It looks like more than that.
From you to Rick to Chilly.
Dana's trading down.
You're the only one who actually...
cared about Dana, aren't you?
Come on, Mr. Stipe.
Where is she?
I don't know.
Yesterday afternoon where were you?
I was on my way to see
a client in Connecticut.
Dana is like...
she's like a black widow.
Isn't she? And you're just staring at that
red hourglass on her belly.
And you're just thinking
that she's not gonna bite.
Stipe's covering for Dana.
I can't tell if he's in on it,
or if he's protecting her out of stupidity.
Meanwhile, Dana's probably
on some beach with Chilly.
Unlikely. A fishing boat found Chilly's body
off the coast of Fire Island.
According to Rogers,
it's not a pretty picture.
Whether Stipe's stupid or in on it,
he's lying.
Call the coast guard
and the harbor unit.
Have them search every boat
owned by Camelot undersea recovery.
I'll add this to the list of "things
I didn't need to see."
Worst example of Caisson disease
I've ever seen.
The bends are rarely fatal.
What killed him? An embolism?
Yeah.
The excess nitrogen
formed bubbles in his blood,
one of them got to his heart
and stopped it.
But he'd know better
than to ascend too quickly.
Something made him panic.
Like the sight of his anchor pulling up?
It was on the deck of his boat.
He was in open water?
That'd do it.
Yeah, Goren.
Okay, thanks.
Harbor unit found Dana.
I should have gone to the cops
when Rick disappeared,
but I panicked.
I can get helpless.
It's not my best side.
So you turned to Chilly for support.
Is that what he told you?
I had to sleep with Chilly.
He thought Rick and I
were cheating him,
and I just wanted to show him
that he could trust me.
That helpless thing again.
How much treasure did the three of you...
bring up, Dana?
Just a handful, I swear.
Enough to buy three pairs of Jimmy Choos
and four Versace dresses.
And those diamond earrings
really highlight your tan.
Okay, so we skimmed
a little bit off the top.
What, you've never worked as a waitress?
Blonde like you?
I'm sure you did.
I mean, Rick and Chilly said that there's
so many trunks down there,
nobody was gonna miss
a handful of coins.
What about your employer,
Simon Harper?
Well, Rick said Harper
didn't care about the money.
He was just looking for a thrill.
I had no idea that Rick was dead
until Tommy called me.
Tommy. Tom Stipe,
your ex-husband.
Yeah.
He called when I was with Chilly.
And he somehow sensed
that I was in trouble.
So he said to go hide out
on our old boat, The Guinevere.
He'd take care of me.
That's nice.
Let's see. He did.
He took care of you.
Oh, my God.
Well, don't get all helpless now.
You have a bigger problem.
We have evidence
you were on Chilly's boat.
You can't think I did this.
Oh, now I can.
Yeah. Well, you sent Chilly
down for the treasure.
You had Tom come along
with one of his boats.
You know, you went away.
You left Chilly to claw his way
to the surface.
No, I've been dry docked
on Tommy's boat for the last two days.
Where's you stash, Dana?
It... it's at a warehouse.
Chilly and I each had a key.
You gotta be freaking kidding me!
Damn it.
Someone other than Chilly have the key?
No. No, I bought the locks myself.
It was just me and him.
You guys show anybody else
where the treasure was?
No... why would... I...
Oh... Tommy.
That baldheaded little bastard.
I should have known never to trust him.
Chilly is a loose cannon.
With the money involved,
I knew he was a threat to Dana.
I gave her a port in the storm.
Well, this is the chance you've been
waiting for with Dana, isn't it?
How's that?
Well, a chance to restore... Camelot.
You know, Dana's your Guinevere.
Name of the boat that we found her on.
That's sweet.
You killed Rick because
he stole your queen.
I couldn't have killed Rick.
I can't dive.
So you had Chilly do it for you.
But whoever killed Chilly
didn't need to dive.
He just had to pull anchor.
He died of the bends,
trying to save himself.
Our ME told us it was an agonizing death.
I could never do this to another diver.
Dana has an alibi.
She was on your boat.
Every guy at the marina watched her
bronze herself on the deck.
Who's gonna vouch for you?
Dana's gonna let me go down for this.
God. I have done nothing
but help her out with you,
with the Chilly... warehouse.
That warehouse, did you help her...
- Or did you just help yourself?
- What?
No, I...
She told me where it was.
I never went there.
This is what happens
when you can't let go of your ex.
So much for Camelot.
Dana had Chilly kill Rick.
And then had Stipe kill Chilly.
She takes the money,
and leaves Stipe holding the lift bag.
Um, maybe.
Uh, excuse me, counselor.
Mr. Stipe, uh, a minute ago you told me
that you helped Dana with the warehouse.
What did you mean?
Simon Harper called me... really upset.
He knew Chilly and Dana
had taken some of the treasure.
He wanted it back.
So you were, um...
So you played the middle man.
Yeah.
And you told Harper
where the warehouse was.
I never called Stipe.
I dealt exclusively with Rick.
Until that other con artist came up to me.
Tom Stipe said he told you
where the coins were.
And now they're gone.
Sister, I manage hundreds of millions
of dollars through my family trust.
I don't need a bunch of coins
to support my family.
In fact, you don't need to work at all
to support your family.
No, I don't.
Nor do I need to get caught up
in a murder investigation.
Or two. We found Chilly's body
near Fire Island.
He'd been diving at the wreck site.
No, that's wrong.
That's nowhere near my wreck site.
All right, maybe Rick lied to you
to confuse you.
He obviously lied to you
about what kind of ship it was.
Revolutionary war ship wouldn't be
carrying coins from the 1860s.
My point exactly.
Obviously, that's not my ship.
Rick take you to the wreck site?
No, I was waiting to hear back from him
about that day he disappeared.
It's my wife.
She may be going into labor.
Oh, okay.
Uh, we'll be in touch.
Why would he hire treasure hunters
if he doesn't want the treasure?
This isn't the first ship
he's tried to salvage.
He hired Stipe two years ago
to find a wreck in Charleston.
Now, that was a civil war wreck.
Harper said that they never found it.
So find it.
Any luck?
Well, the Charleston boat
was called The Philomela.
But I can't find its page
in the ship registry.
It should be here somewhere.
Look.
This shadow.
A page has been cut out.
It's just cut really close to the spine.
The only people allowed in here
are academics and historians.
Well, I bet they let benefactors in.
You were right. Simon Harper made
a $100,000 donation to the archives.
The Philomela.
Josiah.
That rings a bell.
Josiah Roundtree.
The Quaker turncoat.
The roundtrees were a revered
New York Quaker family,
till Josiah's greed got in the way.
The furs and the horseshoes to Brazil,
that's just a cover.
He was sending money to the south
to help keep slavery legal.
So the coins in the boat
prove Josiah's guilt.
Is Harper so desperate to erase
his ancestor's shame,
he'd murder two people?
Well, can you imagine him
having to explain this to his wife?
That's why Harper doesn't
want to bring the coins up.
There's something on that ship that's...
that will cost him more than it's worth.
How's he doing with his new baby?
That might have been another cover.
His wife never checked into a hospital.
Okay, well, that's good.
We have time to tell Harper
that we're raising The Philomela.
Mr. Harper!
Good news.
I think we found your wreckage.
Philomela.
I got Captain Fox,
part of our scuba unit,
on the other end of this thing.
He says as soon as they ID this wreck,
they can start recovery.
That's not my ship.
Mine is The Falkirk.
No, don't you remember?
The Philomela is the name of the boat
you looked for off Charleston.
Turns out your divers found it here.
It's yours.
I don't want to pay for the recovery.
Leave it.
- Captain!
- What do you mean?
There could be tens of millions of dollars
of gold coins on that thing.
- Captain.
- Why wouldn't you wanna claim that?
Bring that boat back.
I told you before,
I don't need the money.
Ah, that's just the Quaker in you talking.
My family hasn't been religious
for generations.
Family? The Harpers?
Your father, grandfather?
Or the Roundtrees, as in Josiah?
- We're all the same family.
- Oh, hardly.
The Roundtrees have lived in disgrace,
while the harpers, well...
they've prospered.
Especially you.
You're the only Harper of your generation.
And the last.
I want my son to have the Roundtree name.
Well, that's why you hired Rick the first time.
To prove there was no money
on the Philomela.
To prove your great grandfather
Josiah wasn't a traitor.
Very good, detective.
You figured it out.
If you raise those coins,
you'll reopen the family wound.
Now get me out of here.
No, we think there's more to it than that.
You know, when Rick told you
they found that treasure,
I guess you realized that that money
would prove that Josiah...
Josiah defrauded his father.
Josiah got wiped out
in the stock market in 1861.
His father amended his will,
gave the land to him instead of his brother.
But Josiah lied.
He didn't lose that money,
he put it on The Philomela.
What, you were there?
I didn't have to be.
Wills are filed in surrogate court.
We found a handwritten codicil.
Statute of Limitations on fraud doesn't run out
until three years after discovery.
That boat comes up,
the Roundtrees... they could be entitled
to your entire fortune.
No wonder you panicked
when Rick called you.
So you convinced Rick to take you
down to the wreck
so you could see for yourself.
And once you did, you were
prepared to get rid of him.
You know, that was good work.
Planting those photos on Rick's camera
and then on Chilly's computer.
We found the transom,
it's The Philomela.
Shall we start the recovery?
Yeah, hand on a second.
Wait till my orders.
What do you think, Mr. Harper,
you gonna tell us what happened?
Or should we bring up
Josiah's blood money
and prove that the Roundtrees
were defrauded?
No.
Don't.
The family trust is my son's birthright.
Yeah, if you erase history.
That's what you tried to do, right?
With Rick.
With Chilly.
Dana was next.
These people are lowlifes.
Bums.
Rick, he's been dead
to his family for years.
And you think they chose that?
A man with no parents, no kids.
What is he?
Nothing.
His life is wasted.
Yeah, well, not everyone can get
these things that they want.
To you, they're what,
just orphans, right?
All unloved. You left them floating
like driftwood, right?
Is that why you got rid of them
the way that you did?
I was just protecting my family.
Protecting your family?
You should have seen
the greed in Rick's eyes.
- And Chilly's.
- No one can protect their family.
- Not even you.
- My wife and son deserve...
Simon Harper, you are under arrest
for the murder of Tarek Agiza...
You won't take it from them.
Fish him out and cuff him.
So... what happened?
Harper slipped and fell.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org