Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
The following story is fictional and
does not depict any actual person or event.
In New York City's war on crime,
the worst criminal offenders
are pursued by the detectives
of the Major Case Squad.
These are their stories.
I was, I was hoping for more.
I'll go another 500 for that Hamilton.
No, not my father's watch.
He gave it to me in the hospital.
It's hard to part with family things.
Maybe 600.
Hope this girl's worth it.
Sorry to be running you around like this
for just a stupid watch band.
Miss, if I didn't sell bands,
I couldn't pay the rent.
Spotty leopard.
What about in back?
Anything you haven't put out yet?
Let me check.
M-a-r-q-u-i-s, Marquise.
Okay. Gotta go.
Sorry.
Don't choke. Can't choke.
How lucky was that?
I'm out.
Bitch! Let me win it back.
Come on! Triple or nothing!
I'm in love with love.
That's what it is.
- I thought you were set on the Marquis.
- But now I'm asking myself,
who's the beauty,
the ring or the girl?
Princess setting or the pear shape?
Nice kid, but yap, yap, yap.
Whatever you choose will be right.
I'm nervous.
I pawned my dad's watch for this.
Say, Mr. Pullman...
$600 for a 1950s Hamilton.
- You think I got ripped off?
- I'm not an expert on antique watches.
It's eating me up.
Is 600 fair?
They even took my laptop.
I'm calling 911.
Jack, why are you in the closet?
I had some cash up here.
It's gone.
Shut up! Nobody move!
You!
Diamonds in there!
Help her!
Come on, faster! Go!
Don't move! Don't move!
Shut up!
Go! Go! Come on!
Come on!
Open it! / Daniel!
- Open it!
- Daniel, buzzer's on your belt.
Come on, open it!
Not fast enough.
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
딕테이션
김철균(kim1047@nate.com)
싱크편집
윤선영(seedyun@nate.com)
한글번역
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
크리스 노스
(마이크 로건 役)
아나벨라 시오라
(캐롤린 배랙 형사 役)
제이미 쉐리던
(제임스 디킨스 경감 役)
코트니 B. 밴스
(론 카버 검사 役)
Law & Order CI
5x02 Diamond Dogs
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON NBC:  2005/10/02
Everybody's got the same story.
Friendly kid, hung out 40 minutes.
Thrilled to buy an engagement ring.
Then, boom, he flipped out.
How'd he get away?
- Foot, car, subway?
- Don't know yet.
Let's get someone
on the street and find out.
We got a security tape to watch?
- Yeah, we're setting it up right now.
- Good.
Ooh, check this out.
These are known diamond fences
in the Bronx current as of last year.
Daniel just, uh, froze there.
I told him the buzzer was on his belt.
He pressed it.
And the door opened?
- And then what did the young man do?
- He, uh...
just take a breath.
Take another one.
He, uh, he said, uh,
"not fast enough."
Then he shot Daniel. Twice.
And ran out.
Mr. Jolinari, we need you to write down
everything that was taken.
45 caliber. That's a big gun.
Hey, can we get a bulletin out to all
the pawnshops before they close today?
All right, do that.
What?
Relax, you got the job.
We got the tape cued up.
40 minutes.
Didn't knock out the camera.
It doesn't...
care who sees him.
Hey, Barak.
Security tape'ready.
Friendly little bastard.
His hands in his pockets.
No prints.
So, hmm, his idea of being a pro.
You know, you might
want to get a cell phone.
That way people won't think
you're talking to yourself.
Been working alone too long.
There he goes.
Flared trigger guard.
Extended barrel.
Could be an HK mark 23.
Can you back it up?
There.
Freeze.
Uh, his wrist.
Mr. Jolinari, before
he was tapping his wrist.
He was ranting about his father's watch.
Uh, a 1950s Hamilton.
He thought he'd been slicked
by a pawnbroker.
An antique watch.
Something else for
the pawnbroker's bulletin.
Home of Jack & Miriam Engles
28 Prince Street
Thursday, September 8
Yes, this is my watch.
Where'd you find it?
Turned up at a pawn brokers
yesterday along with these items.
Unbelievable.
This is our stuff.
See? I told you it was smart
to file a report with the police.
Is there a problem, Mr. Engles?
I mean, people are usually happy
to get their goods back.
We're very lucky.
Was something else stolen
that didn't make the report?
All right, look, pal,
this busted look on your face,
I've been there.
So, either she tells us
or you can save us a step.
I, uh...
I may have had a gun.
He did.
It was hidden in the closet.
I told him that I didn't
want guns in the house.
Was it an HK mark 23?
Beautiful.
Who knew you were out of town?
Only our work and my son.
He's at Princeton.
- Stopped the paper?
- I called on the way to the cruise ship.
Earliest they could stop
it was three days later. Thursday.
Your calendar clock
is off by four days.
That's because they unplugged it
when they took my laptop.
I just forgot to reset it.
You plugged it back in on Monday?
Count back four days.
It was unplugged on Thursday.
The stop-delivery date for the newspaper.
You wanna know who's out of town,
you ask the paperboy.
Cherry tomatos,
they're from my garden.
Well, what else you grow?
Cabbage.
Polish food.
I love pierogies.
Are your mother's any good?
No, they weren't her thing.
So what did Mrs. Logan make her boy?
Rum punch.
Private joke.
There she is. The 3:10 to Yuma.
There's our paper boy.
Hey, police!
How you doing?
Boaz?
Hey, you got badges too, huh?
Oh, yeah.
I got three five-year badges.
That's for newspaper delivery.
I got three one-year badges.
Um, and guess what?
I put in 18 years.
You deliver the paper to the Engles?
They were away last week.
Jack, on Minetta lane,
stop delivery.
Anybody ask if, uh, maybe
somebody went out of town?
Maybe some guy last week?
You don't like talking
to guys you don't know, huh?
But you'll talk to girls?
Only if they talk to me first.
Last week, it was a girl
who asked you who was away?
She was nice.
She gave me this cartoon badge.
And guess what?
It's from Japan.
What else do you remember about her?
Black hair.
And guess what?
A hat.
Yeah, I remember her now.
She was in early in the day
running Daniel around for a watchband.
Think you can improve on this sketch?
Sure.
The mouth was poutier.
Tell our artist about her pouty mouth.
He make her?
Well, she cased the store
earlier in the day.
Unfortunately, the security
system's inexpensive,
so it tapes over itself every hour.
We got no hit off the prints.
And the swag hasn't turned up anywhere.
So three days in,
you got Nancy and Sluggo here.
- And an ID on the weapon.
- We'll do better.
I'm counting on it.
Just take the jewels,
Just please take the jewels.
- You're giving me permission?
- No, no!
Oh, Lucas, oh, my god.
Oh, Lucas, no.
Oh, Lucas...
I, I saw it in his eyes.
I thought I was gonna die.
Then he just ran away.
Something happen?
Somebody came in?
He just changed his mind.
He was looking at engagement rings.
And he said that he was
in love with love,
so he killed my husband of 22 years.
I'm very sorry, Mrs. Crais.
We're gonna get someone
to take you home.
No, I wanna stay with Lucas.
Excuse me, these marks on your blouse?
That's where he grabbed me.
Hey, take a look at that.
One, two, three.
Plus two in the back wall is nine.
He shot out the camera.
He's getting smarter.
Angrier.
Fired nine shots in all.
He's losing control.
What's that?
Pool chalk.
It was on his hands.
Transferred to the lady's blouse
when he grabbed her.
Maybe he played a game to steady
his nerves before he came here.
Any good with a stick?
Fortran's Bar
Long Island City, New York
Saturday, September 10
This got to do will all
those sirens a couple hours ago?
Sir, you answered our question
with a question.
You're not hiding anything, are you?
Okay, there was a guy
in here around 1.
Might be this guy.
Did he shoot any games with this crowd?
No, people made him
as a hustler and stayed away.
I think I left my pad in the car.
I'll be right back.
What's your hurry?
You got a date with a doughnut?
Just skipping out on my tab, man.
What's this?
It's personal use, man.
That's all!
Try again.
Guy made a move for the John.
Logan picked him out.
He's one of those cops.
Always looking for the crook in the room.
I'm telling you, man,
I don't sell no smack.
Look, you see at guy there
next to my partner?
That's my boss.
And if I don't come through for him,
he's gonna boot my ass
back to Staten island.
What's that got to do with me?
I need you to give me
something on this guy.
But I ain't never seen him.
He's got an interesting interview style.
Very affable.
Cuddly cop.
Not what I expected.
And I'll owe you.
I'm good for it, ask anybody.
Mike Logan.
How about it?
All right.
Now I'm gonna pound
my fist on the table, okay?
That's the Logan I expected.
Mr. Kellogg has something for us.
Your pool player came in
looking to buy from me today.
He said he was Maya's boyfriend.
She used to be a customer.
Then you two came in,
I figure I been set up.
That's Maya up there.
He says she was living
in a squat on hunter near 43rd.
Let's go get her.
Thanks, pal.
Whoa, back up speed racer.
Okay! Heads up, ladies and gents.
We got a message for the class.
We need help finding this girl.
Her name is Maya.
She could be in danger.
The quicker you help us,
the faster you go make a connection.
Maya got pinched for shoplifting.
She got the community service
last month.
She don't come back.
- She leave this behind?
- Oh, mon dieu.
Same as the pin she gave
the paperboy. What's wrong?
You're afraid of it? Why?
He touched it.
It's bad luck.
Who touched it?
Maya's brother Roy.
He's feeble-minded.
Maya'd bring him here.
That's his toy.
Maya has a mentally retarded brother.
She brought here.
What do we got here?
My guess, liquid methadone.
Except these folks don't look like
high priority candidates for rehab programs.
But Maya's brother would be.
A mentally retarded addict'd get
fast tracked into the methadone program.
Methadome Clinic
Long Island City, New York
Monday, September 12
So just in case I need an interpreter,
how many languages do you speak?
Well, Spanish, Yiddish,
Italian, Polish, Creole.
Some Russian.
Some Cantonese from
working in chinatown.
You?
I can say "stop, police" and "what's
your sign?" in 15 different languages.
Roy Sampson!
No. Go, no!
- Let's go.
- We'll take that.
Maya, you're under arrest.
Me? I can't abandon my brother.
We'll get him to his group home.
Come on, Roy.
No! / Wait, let me tell him
I love him, please.
Give him a break, honey.
It's the same guy, Maya.
Robbing the same jewelry stores
you were in.
Me at a jewelry store?
Do I look like I'm getting married?
You don't wise up,
you're gonna take the weight
for everything he's done.
Two murders, two robberies.
I wanna talk to my lawyer.
Fresh tracks.
Is that all since you left the squat?
You didn't used
to like needles, did you?
You used to snort heroin,
until you met this boy.
Does he fix you up?
Is that his idea?
Nobody tells me anything.
Lawyer.
You're sitting in the lawyer's chair.
We need you to move.
So she follows directions.
What else do we know about her?
Well, a half dozen shoplifting
beefs last two years.
Keeps getting community service, too,
being "the caregiver of
a mentally retarded relative."
He's a soft target,
like the paperboy.
If it's the same girl.
Shoplifting to robbery-homicide
in a month is quick work.
Matches her escalating heroin use.
She went from snorting it
to spiking four or five times a day.
She's probably keeping pace
with her boyfriend.
Those stolen diamonds are going
straight up their arms.
If it's the same girl.
Call me when the lawyer gets here.
It's gotta be her, right?
Oh, god.
Oh, it won't open.
Oh, god, I can't get it open.
Hurry up, Zoilo!
Open it!
Be quiet, I can't get it open.
Open it! Open it!
Mama, please be quiet.
Be quiet. Be quiet, okay?
- I can't get it open.
- Come on, Milo.
- Let's go!
- Get out of the way, I'll do it!
Mama, no! I got it!
Let's go.
We got another one.
Back in the Bronx.
Same M.O., Two dead,
suspect matches ours,
and he had an accomplice
driving the getaway car.
A dark haired female.
I don't wanna hear it.
Just get going!
Angry, angry, angry.
Every mom and pop he hits,
it gets worse.
Something about happy families
this kid does not like.
More specifically, he put
more rounds into mom than pop.
- You noticed that.
- Hard to miss.
Okay, so, the getaway car
was a beige four-door compact.
New York plates, no numbers.
Driver, female, white.
Brown or black hair,
take your pick.
And just to make it easy, sunglasses.
Well...
Maybe Maya is a dead end.
Oh, I'm not giving up on her yet.
This guy could have
a harem working for him.
I'm gonna have to say...
number five.
Or number three.
I, I'm sorry.
It's the mouth.
They got the same pouty mouth.
Thank you for coming in.
Four eye-witnesses.
Not one positive ID.
I'm so happy,
my toes are curling.
Don't roll your eyes at me, detective.
We're done.
Thank you for coming in.
The tip that led to this girl?
From a smack dealer.
He recognized her off a sketch.
A sketch provided by
a mentally retarded paperboy?
This was your lead, detective Logan?
The tip was good.
The day I can't read a dope dealer
is the day I hang it up.
A word, captain.
This is now a press case.
Assigning a cop with
an asterisk next to his name
could come back to bite you.
I knew that going in, counselor.
But thanks for reminding me.
Anything else?
Yes, you can release Maya Sampson.
I'm not wasting resources
on a misdemeanor drug sale.
The DA declines to file charges.
We're kicking the girl.
- It's a mistake.
- We're letting her go.
Captain.
I don't wanna become an issue here.
You quitting?
No.
But the bodies are piling up.
Look, it's not about
me making a bust.
It's about catching this guy.
You become a problem for me,
I'll be the first to tell you.
Here's a lost opportunity.
Maya's mother is downstairs
looking for her daughter.
An hour earlier, she could
have helped us get through to her.
Be nice to spend some
quality time with these two.
Maya's been without a fix for...
12 hours.
Be remiss if we didn't let
a doctor look at her.
They told me at Roy's
group home what happened.
I can't hardly believe it.
Maya's always been good to her brother.
Sounds like you haven't
seen her in a while.
She came home for a week
about two months ago
and then off she went.
Do you have idea what
she's gotten herself into?
- You mean the drugs?
- No.
We mean a mad-dog boyfriend
who robs jewelry stores and kills people.
Mad dog?
That is a joke, right?
You're getting me worried here.
It's no joke.
The district attorney's willing to be
lenient with Maya if she helps us.
Oh, excuse me.
She's showing early signs of withdrawal.
But unless she wants to check herself
into detox, it's time to street her.
The doctor told her she could leave.
Did you tell her
what we talked about?
She says she wasn't
mixed up in any of it.
Like she'd tell you?
She would.
Come on, sweetie, get dressed.
You've got her confused
with someone else.
I don't think we have.
I know my girl.
She has been in enough trouble.
All those hours of com-service.
Cleaning graffiti off the walls
with the stinking solvent.
She has learned her lesson.
Right, sweetie?
Come on, let's go.
Thank you, officers.
Some mom.
A mom who doesn't get upset her
daughter strips in front of strangers.
My mom would have killed me.
This mom knew a little
too much about "com-service."
Nurse, we're gonna need
fingerprints off of that.
Community Service Detail #9
El Train Overpass
Queens, New York
Wednesday, September 14
Sure, she did 100 hours a month ago
for possession of drug paraphernalia.
Dede. Dede Feist.
Or Dede Worchak, or Dede Carbone.
Yeah, that gal told me
she'd had a few husbands.
She's in love with love,
that is how she put it.
This girl was on Dede's crew.
Maya Sampson.
She and Dede were tight.
- They know each other before?
- Don't think so,
but by the end of the week,
Dede was sharing
her box lunch with Maya.
Then they were showing up together.
I heard Dede talking to Maya
about introducing her to her son.
I read something
about a son in her file.
Went into foster care
when he was 11.
- There it is, Jonathan?
- Johnny.
That's what she called him.
You have any idea where this
roof over her head might be? / No.
Another thing is,
she was late one day
because she said she had
to put her sick aunt in a hospice.
Yeah, well, these junkies,
they break your heart.
That's what I thought.
So I called the hospice.
It checked out.
St. Timothy's in Forest hills.
Thank you very much.
Well, if the aunt's in the hospice,
I wonder who's feeding the cat.
Bedroom clear!
- Bathroom clear!
- Closet clear!
Found the cat.
Dissociative cutting.
Self-mutilation, turned outward.
Little Johnny's got issues.
From shallow to deep.
The angrier he gets,
the harder he stabs.
Hard to see where he gets the energy
with all the smack they're shooting.
I'm seeing hundreds
of empty dime bags.
Well, Dede's the lifetime addict.
She's doing 15, 20 bags a day.
Some parents send their kids out
to get them booze.
Dede has Johnny knocking off
jewelry stores to feed her habit.
No personal effects, no clothes.
No makeup.
Yeah, they flew the coop.
Hey...
black wig.
The one Dede wore
to ride the getaway car.
Oh, man.
They were shooting up
right on top of her.
That's just...
I miss her, mom.
The police have her, Johnny.
There's nothing we can do.
We...
We could bust her out!
Don't be stupid.
I'll get you another.
Next one's for Maya!
Maya didn't just OD.
She sent the tox screen off the chart.
Whether it's an accident or not,
it's impossible to know.
They killed her.
They couldn't take a chance
she'd get pinched again.
Any idea where they might be heading?
Oh, who knows?
Have smack, will travel.
The getaway car belonged to aunt Ruthie.
We got a tri-state alarm out.
You got Dede's file.
Start working her known contacts.
Abusive ex-husbands, boyfriends
it's what she's had to put up with
in order to support her habit.
Let me get out my violin.
I'll make sure Mr. Carver sees this.
It's always good to share the pain.
I was taught in catechism, even
the worst sinner deserves our compassion.
Yeah? Yours, maybe.
I'll save mine.
These dumps off aunt Ruthie's phone.
Two hours after each robbery
there's four, five calls to the same pool hall.
Pepe's in Brooklyn.
And only after each robbery.
Maybe Johnny's got a pool hall fence.
Third table on the right.
The tall guy.
He's got a jeweler's loop
hanging around his neck.
Hi.
We're getting engaged.
I'm looking for a diamond solitaire.
I'm not in the jewelry business.
Yeah, you sure?
I'm sure.
What's the loop for?
So you can find your Jingus
when you take a leak?
You fencing rocks for Johnny Feist?
I don't know no Johnny Feist.
You know, I had a partner.
Oh, what a great stick man he was.
Here's something he had way
too much decency to teach me.
What are you gonna do with that, huh?
I'm a rageaholic cop who took
a swing at a city councilman.
Everybody thinks
that I'm a ticking bomb.
Maybe today's the day I blow.
I don't know. It's up to you.
Come on, man.
This is sick, man.
- Don't hurt me.
- Hurt you? Hurt you?
How much you pay Johnny
for those rocks?
You profit by the people he kills.
You encourage him to kill more.
I have absolutely zero
compassion for you.
You know what?
Rudy's not the mayor anymore.
But that doesn't mean
we still can't have some fun.
Man, okay, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'll tell you.
Johnny came in yesterday.
He took his money and went to AC.
- He's gambling.
- He's playing for the big score.
He's going on about
some papoose that loved him.
Say what?
Uh, it's a nickname for a nickel slot casino
outside the Atlantic city bus station.
Thanks, pal.
Keno-Sabe Casino
Atlantic City, New Jersey
Saturday, September 17
They came in late last night.
Went straight to the crap table.
Dede keeps egging him on.
Rubbing his shoulders,
playing with his hair.
Like he's her toy poodle.
Bust out.
How much he lose?
Everything he had, about 12 grand.
Half a million in jewelry.
Fence takes his cut.
What they don't spend
on smack he loses in...
57 minutes.
Uh, can you back up there, please?
There.
Yeah, right there.
That's three times she's
chatted up this waitress.
Dede?
She kept singing her boy's praises.
She was selling you on him.
And you know, a gambling
addiction is such a turn on.
Hey, that's a ring around your neck.
Is that an engagement ring?
Thanks.
I could lose my job
is the customers saw this.
A cocktail waitress
has to seem available.
- Did Dede see that?
- She looked disappointed.
Then she asked where we got it.
So I told her,
double down's jewelry.
Across from the trop.
Double Down Jewelry
You okay, sweetie?
I just lost my job cleaning rooms
and my boyfriend took off
with my savings.
I'll tell you what.
I can spare a few dollars
if you help me fold this.
Here, sweetie.
You can start with my son's T-shirts.
He's at work right now.
Hey.
Can I get a smile?
Who's the real beauty,
the ring or the girl?
What do you think, ring or girl?
Oh, I have to go with the girl.
Always the girl.
Like my Rosie.
I'm with him.
Go with the girl.
But then, I'm in love with love.
Where is she, Johnny?
Where's your mother?
Every cop in this city
has a shoot to kill order.
You don't want anything
to happen to her, do you?
She's got nothing
to do with this!
You can't believe
what Maya told you!
My mom doesn't even know I'm in here!
She's just out being a mom!
Where?
Drop the laundry bag, Dede!
The future Mrs. Johnny Feist?
Let's go.
Of course I can charge
his mother as an accomplice.
But that charge would have
the life span of a flea.
There's nothing in here
that sustains it.
Unless he testifies against his mother.
- What will it take?
- What are you prepared to offer?
Minimum, he's facing four life
sentences without parole.
You could offer him a walk,
but he's not gonna roll on her.
He's not out to save his own skin.
You need to get through
to this kid.
He doesn't seem to know
that Maya's dead.
Dede's the one that
gave her the hot shot.
Now, Johnny boy might not be too
thrilled when we tell him.
A child's relationship
with an addicted parent...
is very complicated.
If we wanna turn him against her,
anger is just the beginning.
Four concurrent sentences
of 25 to life.
District attorney won't oppose
parole after 25 years.
That's the offer in writing.
An interesting offer.
Considering the evidence against him,
it should come with a bow on it.
All he has to do
is give up his mother.
She doesn't know anything.
I told you.
By all rights, Johnny,
you shouldn't even be here.
You were getting along fine
in your foster home.
Is it your idea to leave?
Or was it Dede's?
How did she put it like
I can't get along without him?
Hey, if you wanna vent on your mom,
you've got our permission.
I got nothing to vent.
I'm not angry at her.
My partner knows
about that kind of anger.
His mother used to send him out
to buy booze for her.
Tell Johnny how
she used to thank you.
He needs to hear it.
Well, after the first drink,
it was all hugs and kisses.
Then a few drinks later,
she'd grab whatever she could...
and start hitting me.
And when she got tired of holding
whatever it was she was hitting me with...
she'd just go at me with her fists.
And, uh...
the next day...
she'd send me back to the liquor store.
Isn't that what
your mom's done to you?
Just turned you into her errand boy?
Go out and steal for her
to feed her addiction?
It's not the same.
You're right.
My mother didn't make me
drink with her.
You didn't even have a drug problem
until you went to live with your mother.
- You have every right to be angry at her.
- I'm not angry.
You're not angry
but you pumped seven bullets
into that woman in the Bronx!
You take out your anger everywhere
you can except for where it belongs.
She lights your smokes,
she fluffs up your hair.
You're her poodle boy, Johnny.
- Does she let you eat off her plate?
- You shut up!
And the one thing that your mother
couldn't provide for you,
she found somebody who would.
Maya's a pretty girl.
You like her, don't you?
You turned her against us.
We didn't have the chance.
We had to let her go.
Your mother picked her up.
That's not true.
She must have brought her back
to aunt Ruthie's while you were out,
gave her a welcome home fix.
Tucked her in, like a good mother does.
Did you sit up on the couch that night?
Feet up on the trunk?
While your mother told you what
an ungrateful disloyal girl Maya was?
How could you, you bitch!
She was mine!
You had no right!
You lying bitch! Oh, god.
No!
What are you gonna
do about this, Johnny?
You wanna tell us what happened?
How your mother helped you
with the robberies?
Maybe we should get you a soda.
Yeah.
I bet you're sorry now, huh?
All that anger.
What did you call her?
A lying bitch?
She can't help herself.
It's the heroin.
Look at her, the poor thing.
I wonder how she'll do back
on the street without your help.
I do worry about that.
- Right now, I'm worrying about that.
- Of course you are.
After all, she's not a street person.
She's your mom.
She could go back
to one of her boyfriends.
Real Romeos.
This guy put her in the hospital twice.
Broken jaw, concussion.
She won't just be with anybody.
She's got a $300-a-day habit, Johnny.
She'll be with whoever can pay for it.
Can't...
Can't you put her in a program?
She needs long term care, Johnny.
That's for rich people.
People like your mother are lucky
to get 72 hours in Bellevue.
Hey, how about this guy, Lippman?
Yeah, two years ago, he threw her
half naked out of a moving car.
Oh, sorry, that wasn't a boyfriend.
That was one of her Johns.
Don't tell me that!
A junkie's gotta do what a junkie's gotta do.
You know that.
Johnny, we wanna protect her.
You don't want her
to go back to that life.
What if...
you just put her someplace
for her own protection?
We don't just lock people up
for their health.
You tell us what she did,
she'll go to prison.
A woman's prison with a hospital.
It's just better than
what she's looking at now.
Look at her.
You don't want her 60 years old
turning tricks to support her habit.
I've seen women like that, Johnny.
And it is not pretty.
Your mom, she deserves better.
I wanted to pawn that gun
after I stole it.
But mom said to use it
to do jewelry stores.
She knew the ones to hit.
She drove me to them.
She said...
"Better not leave witnesses."
"Use the gun."
"Step up and be a man.
Take care of your mom."
That's what she told me.
"Be a man."
Oh, about time.
You letting me out?
You're being charged with murder, Dede.
What?
- Your son gave you up.
- Johnny? Never.
Not my Johnny.
Johnny...
You go to hell, Johnny.
Do you hear me?
You go to hell.
I should have left you
in that foster home.
Should have left you
in that foster home!
Who would have mothered
you then, Johnny, huh?
You answer me, some foster mother?
There is no mothering
like real mothering!
You hear me, Johnny!
Go to hell!
You got no one, Johnny.
You're all alone.
Should have warned him
don't expect any thanks.
번역수정
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
한글교정
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org