Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
August 9, 2:30 p.m.
Greenwich Mean Time.
The H.M.S. Churchill,
outward bound.
On board: a joint
British-American space team.
Their mission: to intercept and study
the comet bearing Dr. Halley's name.
The Churchill is the first spacecraft
equipped with the Nerva engine.
It propels the Churchill
with constant acceleration...
enough to create Earth-type gravity for
the first time on an extended flight.
The Churchill is on course
for its rendezvous.
- Sir, this is odd.
- What?
I'm getting a small radar
cross section...
just ahead of the nucleus
in the coma of the comet.
I've got it too. Check the length.
It's at the limit of my scan angle.
- What's going on?
- You run an equipment check?
Every five minutes.
- Radar states 150 miles.
- 150 miles what?
- Length.
- 150 miles long?
What's 150 miles long?
It's a radar trace.
- Something in the coma of the comet.
- Show me.
- E.G.R. is confirmed.
- Looks good.
E.G.R. is optimal.
Track three on three.
Roger.
What's its height?
I've got a vertical reading
of two miles at least.
Ambient temperature: six degrees.
Less than two percent traces
of manganese, titanium--
Try and raise base.
Tell them we have an artificial
object out here hidden--
- Are you sure you want to say "hidden"?
- It's located in the head of the comet.
Keep sending that
until they acknowledge.
Use a secured downlink.
Sorry, Commander, everything's
been swamped by the coma winds.
We can't get anything back to base.
How long is the blackout period?
All the way.
What are you gonna do?
Go on in.
We're only gonna get one chance,
Derebridge.
That thing won't be back
for another 76 years...
and we'll both be dead.
We have to take a look now.
- Shut down Nerva.
- Shutting down.
Down.
- Solar panels retracted.
- Check. Give me a readout, Bob.
Executing E.V.A. maneuver.
Where do you suppose
this thing came from?
- Was it exploring the comet?
- Come on, guys, let's do it.
The surface looks badly pitted.
In that case,
it's been here a long time.
It's derelict, whatever it is.
Stand by, Churchill.
We're going in.
Roger, Carlsen.
We copy. We have you going in.
Churchill, it looks like
some giant artery, organic.
I almost have the feeling
I've been here before.
Oh, boy.
This is incredible.
I hope you can appreciate
the scale of this on the video.
Roger. We're getting it.
It's all on tape.
Oh, shit.
Whoa. Here they are.
Churchill...
it looks like we found the occupants
of the ship.
They look like giant bats.
- There must be hundreds of them.
- Thousands.
Dead, I hope.
Looks prehistoric.
It's completely desiccated.
- Crumbles.
- Y es, it would.
All the fluid's been lost
to space over the years.
We'll bag this one,
take it with us.
We're deploying
the specimen bag.
Jesus.
What the hell is that?
Commander...
the ship has just deployed a--
It looks like some sort
of big structure that's just unfolding.
It's enormous.
God, what is it?
We must get out of here.
Nobody's going anywhere.
Stay where you are.
Churchill, this is Carlsen.
What's happening out there?
The thing stopped opening.
The only way to describe it is
it's like a giant umbrella.
Good God.
It's absolutely enormous.
What's it doing now?
Nothing, sir.
It's stopped opening.
It's just sitting there.
- Can you tell what it's made of?
- Not metal.
It's radar transparent.
Okay.
If it starts up again,
let me know.
Any activity out there.
You understand?
Y es, sir.
That's where we're going.
There's something there.
Commander, this is Churchill.
We're losing our signal.
We've lost V.T.R.
Come in, Commander!
Three bodies.
Perfectly preserved.
They look to me
to be like an--
Something's happening to me.
What's wrong with me?
Commander, come in.
This is Churchill.
Do you copy?
They seem to be in some sort
of suspended animation or sleep.
Hold on.
We're coming down.
Churchill, if you read...
there are two nude males
and one female.
This is Churchill.
We have no picture. Come in, Tom.
Churchill,
I said we found a young girl.
"Girl"? You mean human?
Definitely humanoid.
I'd say she's perfect.
I've been in space for six months.
She looks perfect to me.
- Derebridge, what's wrong?
- What's wrong?
- How many do you want to take back?
- I say we take back all three...
and one of the dead things
in the other chamber.
Let's see if we can break them free.
Churchill, come in.
This is Mission Control, Great Britain.
Do you copy?
If they're going to pick us up,
they should get us this close.
Simply aren't receiving,
Dr. Bukovsky.
Automatic circuits don't even respond.
They're radio dead.
Christ, I hope it's just
their communications.
How's their orbit look?
You can see it's stable,
but they're slightly off.
They should have adjusted
coming in...
but they haven't.
What do you make of that?
It would appear that
they set their course...
just after they left the comet
and haven't updated it since.
- The Columbia?
- The Columbia.
We have a liftoff.
Tower cleared.
Control, this is Columbia.
Are we cleared
to initiate docking procedure?
Go ahead, Columbia.
You are looking good.
Stand by for soft dock.
Soft dock.
Soft dock confirmed.
Columbia,
the ship's completely gutted.
Oh, my God.
Houston, we have a problem.
There's been a fire.
I'll take a look in the tug bay.
You two, try the top deck.
Columbia, they're all dead.
Nothing down here, Columbia.
I'm going into the tug bay.
I'll get the tapes.
Somner...
there's something you ought to see
in the tug bay.
I see.
How did you open the girl's case?
We didn't, Minister.
We were talking about how to get it open
when it popped open of its own accord.
- Did you X-ray the crystal cases?
- We're not certain they're crystal.
The casings are not metallic.
I'm not even sure they're organic.
The casing is right there
in front of us without being there...
- if that makes any sense.
- And the bodies?
We're going to do
our first dissection now.
Provided, of course,
that Dr. Fallada agrees they're dead.
I don't know that I am qualified
to pass judgment on alien death.
You would agree that
they're less alive than we are?
Yesterday in Hong Kong,
gold closed lower.
In light trading
on European currency markets...
the pound closed mixed against
the dollar and West German marks.
There will be a full market report
after the late news.
This is James Graham
reporting from the city.
Now back to the newsroom.
Halley's Comet is now
dominating the northern sky...
stretching over 100 million miles
across the heavens...
occupying one-sixth
of the entire visible horizon.
On this exceptionally clear night...
a group of enthusiasts are commemorating
Dr. Edmund Halley's great prediction...
by holding an outdoor watching from
his original observatory at Greenwich.
Our viewers may be interested
to know...
that comets were once considered
to be hargingers of evil.
One of the earliest words
for comet was "disaster"...
which in Latin means "evil star."
It may indeed be an evil star
for the deep space probe Churchill.
There's still no word from Her Majesty's
government as to the fate of the crew...
whether they're alive or dead.
We can only await
further developments--
Use my body.
- Where's the girl?
- She's gone.
I saw her.
She did that.
- Security.
- Hello. Professor Fallada here.
I'm calling
at Dr. Bukovsky's orders.
- Get me the duty security captain now.
- Yes, sir.
Don't worry.
A naked girl is not going
to get out of this complex.
Four-nine to Control. You'll
never believe what I'm looking at.
- Control, can you say that again?
- I believe you heard me.
There's a girl on the loose
in the building. She must not leave.
Pardon me, but I thought you said
she was naked.
That's right. That's what I said.
Surely, you can find her.
Must be some kind of joke.
Don't believe it.
All right, miss,
just stay where you are.
You heard them.
They said grab her.
Take it easy, mate.
She's not in her right mind.
Control, we have located the girl
in the main lobby.
That's it. Come on.
- Yes?
- We've located the girl, sir.
- Where?
- She's downstairs in the main lobby.
Right.
She's in the main lobby.
You all right to go down there?
Nice and easy.
Come on.
Come to me.
Come to Daddy.
Make it stop.
Come on!
Let's get her!
- Are you all right, mate?
- Y eah.
All nonmilitary personnel
please clear the area.
I repeat: Everybody who has
no business to be here...
please clear the area
for your own safety.
This is a police announcement.
Sorry, gentlemen,
no photographs, please.
It's all right.
- Which of you is Dr. Bukovsky?
- I am.
- I'm Colonel Caine.
- From the S.A.S.?
That last remark is not for publication.
This is a D notice situation.
Not too close.
And this was murder, you say?
Tell me again
how the girl overpowered you.
She--
It was the most overwhelmingly
feminine presence I've ever encountered.
- I was drawn to her on a level that--
- Was it sexual?
Yes, overwhelmingly so.
And horrible.
Loss of control.
The guard was dead
when you came into the room?
- You found him as he is now?
- Yeah.
And the girl came from the ship
Churchill?
Uh-huh.
She spoke to you, in English?
That's right.
How would she know English?
Going back, you say the ship's tapes
were destroyed in the fire.
They weren't destroyed
in the fire.
That's what we were told
to tell the public. They were erased.
"Erased"?
Also, the Churchill's escape pod
is missing.
- Did someone escape?
- We don't know.
Unfortunately, the condition
of the bodies...
make an accurate count
impossible.
Could the heat from the fire
have launched the pod?
What started the fire?
The ship's oxygen system ignited.
It was a terribly hot fire.
Y et you say the three cases
containing the bodies were untouched.
- That's correct.
- Where were they found?
In the bay
where the space tug was stored.
Where everything else was charred.
Incredible, is it not?
- Have you examined the cases?
- Using every technique we have.
X-ray scans of the cases
yield only blurred images.
-What does that mean?
-They're not precisely physical objects.
More like a force field.
We're a bit out of our depth here.
The whole thing is--
Yes, I know, incredible.
Have they done an autopsy yet
on the guard? I suppose not.
What about your two other bodies?
Colonel, may I be excused?
I seem to be feeling
a little more nauseous than I thought.
Y es, of course.
I noticed from your door, Dr. Fallada,
that your area is biochemistry.
But I understand
your real interest is--
Death, Colonel Caine.
Correct.
Thanatology is the name for it.
Death for you
is a bureaucratic problem.
Who did it? When?
Why did they do it?
- Am I correct?
- And for you?
I'm fascinated by death itself:
what happens as we die, when we die,
what happens after we die.
- You mean life after death?
- Yes.
- Is there life after death?
- Do you really want to know?
But to answer your question,
yes, I think there is.
If I am correct, the lifeforce
is conserved always...
and in all things,
even after death.
You think that applies
to what's happened here tonight?
Yes, I do.
I think that girl, creature...
drained energy, lifeforce...
partially from Bukovsky
and totally from the guard.
- A vampire?
- It could be described that way.
In a sense, we're all vampires.
We drain energy
from other life-forms.
The difference is one of degree.
That girl was no girl.
She is totally alien to this planet
and our life-form...
and totally dangerous.
Jesus.
- Do you believe those blokes are alive?
- I'm not paid to believe nothing.
I believe they're alive.
Don't look bloody dead to me.
We've had some trouble,
but everything's under control.
I think you better
come down here.
Yes, sir.
Very good, sir.
It would appear these two
are no longer dangerous.
There is certainly no possiblity
of doing a full autopsy on them.
I would like
to examine the guard.
Have they started the autopsy
on the guard yet?
I believe so, sir.
This is an autopsy on the body of a
young man, dead approximately two hours.
- Did you say he was about twenty?
- Y es, that's correct.
Get the colonel down here!
Put him in an isolation cell,
quickly!
I had no idea
it could be passed on.
What do you suggest?
I would recommend that you
place this body in another cell.
It was two hours ago
that the guard was attacked.
I won't be at all surprised
if we're seeing a pattern here.
- Do as he says, Kelly.
- Y es, sir.
Also, I want the two other male bodies
that were shot.
Collect the pieces
and watch them.
- Get me the Home Secretary now.
- Sir.
- Call for the colonel, sir.
- Sir, you have a call.
I'll be right there.
They've just found a body in Hyde Park.
A naked girl.
They say she's
in an indescribable condition.
Could that be your girl?
- Well?
- That's not her.
Inspector,
what about the two boys?
They were in the park earlier, sir.
We saw her, I think, earlier.
Any rate,
that looks like her hair.
- What a mess.
- Was she alone?
No, that's why we noticed her.
She was with a dark-haired girl,
real good-looking and all.
Didn't have a lot
of clothes on either.
We thought they might be--
Well, you know.
Y es. Did you see where
the dark-haired girl went?
No, we didn't.
We angled on back
to see if maybe we could...
you know,
see them doing something.
- That's when we found her.
- How long ago was that?
- Half an hour ago.
- This lad phoned us, and we called you.
Y es. Thank you, lnspector.
Obviously, the work of the girl.
Could we have this body sent back
to the center with the others?
Y es, I suppose that's a good idea.
Inspector, let me know
if you find anything else.
- We'll be taking her back with us.
- Very good, sir.
Now she has clothes.
There's something
I want you to see, sir.
Dr. Hans Fallada, Sir Percy
Hestlestine, the Home Secretary.
You're just in time.
It's exactly two hours.
This is the guard who was originally
overcome by the space girl.
As I feared,
once transformed...
the victims need regular infusions
of energy...
- otherwise--
- Otherwise what?
Oh, my God. Dear God.
And we have the pathologist
who was attacked by the guard.
- See?
- He, too, needs feeding.
The same thing will happen
to that girl we found in the park...
in about one hour.
Good Lord! Goodness!
She's the last?
- Have there been any further reports?
- No, sir.
We're set up to get the calls here
the instant one comes in.
- What?
- Nothing.
You say these creatures
were brought back from the Churchill?
Yes, sir, but not this one.
She's a victim of the creatures.
Yes, but where did
the Churchill acquire them?
We have no way of determining that
at present.
- Perhaps that's all changing.
- What?
I've just received a call
from the J.P.L. in Pasadena.
The goldstone tracking disc
has just picked up something...
they think is Churchill's escape pod
reentering the Earth's atmosphere.
- Where?
- Texas.
Where?
Walter Reed Army Hospital?
Is he hurt? Just exhausted.
Get him the hell over here!
Colonel Carlsen?
They're expecting you, sir.
Colonel Carlsen, sir.
Tom.
I thought you were dead.
Allow me to introduce Colonel Caine
of the Special Air Services.
How do you do?
- You already know Dr. Fallada.
- Colonel.
Take a seat.
I'm sorry to drag you over here
like this.
I'm sure you'd rather be recuperating
with a pretty nurse.
We've got to know what happened
on the Churchill.
Yes, of course.
It may be very difficult
for you...
to accept what
I'm going to say.
We'll have very little difficulty
believing anything you have to tell us.
- Do go on.
- You know something?
There was a fire
aboard the Churchill.
You might be interested to know that
the bodies of the three humanoids...
were not destroyed in that fire.
They survived in their cases.
They were brought down here to London,
and the female has escaped.
She's killed three people already.
Oh, my God.
So whatever you have to tell us
is rather pressing.
Please, tell us what happened.
We found the bodies
aboard the alien spacecraft.
What alien spacecraft?
Colonel,
take it from the beginning.
Assume we know nothing,
which is understating the matter.
We approached within 9,000 miles
of Halley's Comet...
when we detected an object
in the comet's coma.
After we discovered the bodies,
we transferred them to the Churchill.
We have the three humanoid creatures
and one of the bat-like things.
This is Churchill.
We copy. Welcome back.
Have you gotten through
to Earth yet, Rawlings?
No, sir, and the tail
of the comet's heating up.
- What's the matter, Derebridge?
- I don't know, Tom.
I feel drained.
Do you?
I feel invigorated.
You okay?
- Yeah. I'm fine.
- Okay.
Everybody back
to their stations.
Let's get the hell out of here.
On the trip back to Earth,
the crew began to die...
one by one.
Rawlings...
the radio officer,
was the first to go.
Rawlings denied any knowledge
of what he had done.
I don't remember.
Besides myself, you're the only one
who has been up here in the last hour.
I've been feeling weak recently...
not myself.
Just don't remember.
We found Rawlings' body
the next day.
Exactly how...
did he die, Colonel?
The life just drained out of him.
One by one...
the rest of the crew
began to die.
Somehow...
I don't know how...
I held out.
It just seemed
to be a matter of will.
I always thought--
The girl--
Y es? The girl?
I can't remember.
What I remember next...
is the view
out of the observation window...
coming into Earth's orbit.
I couldn't expose the world
to what we'd brought back with us.
I was determined
to destroy them all.
It was the hardest thing I ever did.
We understand.
It must have taken great courage
to try and make--
No, you don't understand.
Part of me didn't want to leave.
She killed all my friends,
and I still didn't want to leave.
Leaving her was the hardest thing
I ever did.
Colonel Carlsen looks exhausted to me.
We should allow him to get some sleep,
continue with this later.
Very well.
Thank you, Colonel.
NASA tracking and ours...
have just reported an unusual structure
leaving Halley's Comet.
It's headed for us.
What is it?
Radar ranging reports the object...
is a needlelike shape,
150 miles long.
Its present course projects out
into a perfect Earth orbit...
in a little more than two days.
I've just received a call
from the Prime Minister.
There's going to be a meeting
at Downing Street.
Prime Minister wants answers.
Close your eyes.
You're giving me your life.
You're taking it.
You're draining me.
You're taking too much of me.
It was just a dream.
- What dream?
- The girl-- She visited me.
Visited you? How?
In my mind.
She has some kind
of mental contact with me.
She's draining me.
Tell us about the dream.
I can't. It's gone.
It's faded.
I can't remember.
Have you ever been hypnotized?
Do you mind if I try?
Yeah, let's try it.
- Not now. He's too exhausted.
- Fine. In the morning.
Just stare at it until your eyes
feel tired, then close them.
You'll feel very tired,
very sleepy.
She seems to speak to me
in my dreams.
She--
The girl--
I feel--
What do you feel for her?
I feel very...
close to her.
Is she in touch with you?
I feel...
as if my mind...
is not entirely my own.
If she is in contact
with your mind...
perhaps you are in contact
with hers.
Can you see her?
Can you see where she is?
Y es.
Where is she now?
A place.
I don't know the name of it.
She's walking.
She has a different face...
but it's her.
"A different face"?
How can that be?
She's using a different body.
- What is she doing?
- She's looking for a man.
What man?
Any man.
A healthy man.
Does she intend to kill him?
- Why not?
- She's afraid of being caught.
- How could she be caught?
- The body would give her away.
What is she hoping to do?
She wants to...
draw some energy from him.
Not enough to kill him.
- She can do that?
- Y es.
There's another mind.
Y es.
The girl's name...
is Ellen.
There are two people
in one body?
Two minds?
Ellen and the vampire?
Yes.
She's watching a man.
What is the man doing?
He's parked,
doing something with his car.
Get the license number.
Can you see the license number
of his car?
Y es.
Read it out.
FMC...
129E...
or R.
What is the make of the car?
A white Volvo.
What is she doing now?
They're driving now.
Does she ask him his name?
She's pulling her skirt...
over her knees.
She's--
He's...
putting his...
hand on her leg.
FMC129E or possibly R...
belonging to a white Volvo.
The driver of the car
picked up a girl named Ellen.
I have to know who the girl is
and where we can find her.
She's connected with the case.
I can't explain over an open line.
Thank you.
Do you think he's telling the truth
about the girl?
We'll soon see.
How brilliant, if she is moving
from body to body, mind to mind...
taking only a small amount
of energy from each victim.
It would make sense
that we're finding no new victims.
She's hoping to leave no trail.
If the girl is no longer in her
original body, where is her body?
- Hidden.
- Let's find it.
Supposing you're right
about all of this.
What about that ship up there?
What's it doing?
We can't know that,
but we've got to assume the worst.
Maybe they're like
the vampires of legend.
How's that?
They would carry their Earth
with them, in their coffins.
Wouldn't they?
- We have the feed from Hawaii.
- Here it comes.
- Put it on screen number one.
- Coming in 240,000 miles.
My God, it's immense.
Hugh, do you have that skin tissue
sample I asked for?
Good.
Of course, I'll follow
containment procedure.
He's here now.
Send in that soldier, please.
Thank you.
One moment, Sergeant.
Thank you for coming.
I'll be with you shortly.
Bloody awful job, chasing that car.
It belongs to a man named
Ned Price who lives in Y orkshire.
- We have him under detention now.
- What about the girl?
The girl he picked up
was a nurse named Ellen, as you said.
Ellen something.
He doesn't know her other name.
He dropped her at Thurlstone Hospital
after spending the afternoon with her.
He was reluctant to talk about it.
The man's totally exhausted.
Isn't Thurlstone an asylum
of some sort?
Y es, for the criminally insane.
How do you do? I'm Dr. Armstrong,
director of the hospital.
Come with me to my office.
- It's a cold night.
- Bitterly cold.
This is the nurses' house.
Ellen Donaldson is number five.
Thank you.
Shouldn't I come up
and introduce you?
- I'd rather you didn't.
- Come along, Dr. Armstrong.
You and I have several matters
to discuss.
Yes? Who is it?
My name's Colin Caine.
Dr. Armstrong brought me over.
I'd like to talk to you.
May I come in?
Yes?
- What do you want?
- My name is Colin Caine.
This is Colonel Carlsen,
United States Air Force.
May we come in and talk to you?
We have seen Dr. Armstrong.
May I sit down?
I want to ask about the man you spent
the afternoon with, Ned Price.
-I don't know what you're talking about.
-I think you do.
- Let me see your hand.
- Beg your pardon?
You're in there, aren't you?
- I don't know.
- Tell me.
It's gone from her.
It's in another body now.
- How do you know that?
- I can see it, in her mind.
She's resisting.
I'll have to force her to tell me.
Despite appearances,
this woman is a masochist.
An extreme masochist.
She wants me
to force the name out of her.
She wants me to hurt her.
I can see the images in her mind.
Do you want to stay?
- Otherwise, wait outside!
- Not at all. I am a natural voyeur.
Are you in there?
Are you there?
Let go.
Now.
Well?
I've got a physical description.
You better send someone
to look after Nurse Donaldson.
Is she all right?
If I described one of the inmates
to you, could you identify him?
Possibly.
Big man, fat, gray hair,
birthmark on his face.
Jeffrey Sykes, the child murderer.
Where did you get his description?
- Where is he now?
- He's in solitary confinement.
He's been naughty.
- What is this about?
- What we're looking for has moved.
- We could be here some time.
- I better call London.
- May I use your telephone, Doctor?
- Certainly.
- We have to see Sykes now.
- Couldn't this wait until the morning?
All right, I'll arrange it.
Anything to oblige, Commander.
I wish this were not so mysterious.
If the police are involved,
haven't I a right to know?
If you're going to start
messing about with my patients--
Dr. Armstrong, I sympathize
with your position, of course.
However, I can tell you
it is a matter of national security.
I see.
But don't you think
that I should be present...
to represent the interests
of my patient?
- You see--
- Can I talk to you for a second?
Of course.
The man has the l.Q.
of a child of four.
That's a decision I shall have
to defer to Colonel Caine.
Yes, of course, you can come along.
Can we start now?
- What are you going to do to him?
- I'd like to hypnotize him.
What's that?
Pentothal and morphine.
Recommended for pre-hypnosis
and patient management.
Well, he seems quiet.
- We're ready when you are.
- Lamson.
Sir.
Can the injection be dangerous?
He should have no difficulty
tolerating it.
There's always a risk, sir.
May I have that?
I'll wake him up.
- What are you doing?
- Stay where you are.
He's sick, Lamson.
Help us. I can't explain now.
There's our killer, Sir Percy.
It's madness.
I want to question him.
Where can we take him?
Up the ramp, sir.
We need to be alone.
How did you know it was him?
In the nurses' quarters,
he touched me on the shoulder.
I saw into his mind.
What?
The colonel is able to see
into the minds of people...
who have been possessed
by the girl creature, sir.
It happens when I touch them.
Let's get him on the table.
How--
How do you know
she's still inside Armstrong?
What's to prevent her
from moving to someone else?
She's trapped.
I can feel that.
Are you sure?
- Lamson.
- Sir?
- Bring me another dose of the drug.
- One dose is usually enough.
This is not a usual situation.
How long does this stuff last?
A dose like that?
A couple of hours.
We'll definitely need more.
- Bring me three doses.
- Three?
I'll take responsibility.
Just get on with it.
Y es, sir.
Is a second dose safe?
Surely it can strain his heart.
Look, you don't know
what we're dealing with here.
If he slips out from under,
she'll escape.
Can you hear me?
If you can hear me,
just say yes.
It won't let me...
talk to you.
Can you see
what's holding you prisoner?
Yes. She--
Tell her she has to talk to me!
Yes?
I brought the Pentothal.
Thanks. That will be all.
Hold him.
There's no need for that.
You in there?
Can you still hear me?
Can you get into his mind,
her mind?
Not with this drug.
It's like a wall.
Perhaps you've given him too much.
Shut up!
Listen, you bitch...
I'll keep you in this state
for weeks if I have to.
Now, you talk to me.
Carlsen, be with me.
- What do you want from me?
- I love you.
What are you?
Why are you so human, so perfect?
What are the bird creatures
on the ship?
Our bodies are unimportant.
As you and your men approached
in your ship...
we changed them for you.
We entered your minds...
and found there new bodies.
I took my shape from your mind.
I took your language.
I became the woman I found there...
in your deepest thoughts,
your deepest needs.
I am the feminine in your mind.
Where are you?
Where's your body?
Let me go!
Touch me, Carlsen.
- It's already spreading.
- How?
- You didn't stop it. It's too late.
- That's impossible.
We've only been half a step
behind her all the way.
This gentleman stopped breathing.
There's no pulse either.
I think his neck is broken.
Prepare a stretcher for Sir Percy
and one for Dr. Armstrong.
Prepare all your remaining doses
of the drug for travel.
Yes, sir.
You said the thing hadn't stopped,
it was still spreading.
- Why did you say that?
- I don't know.
Could the girl have been deliberately
leading us away from London?
Did we find all of her victims?
If there are others
besides the girl in the park--
- The thing would spread.
- In a chain reaction...
geometrically,
until, by now--
Christ.
Lieutenant, can we use the radio
to reach the S.R.C. in London?
Just a moment, sir.
There's something coming through.
It is the S.R.C.
for you and Carlsen.
Go ahead.
Can you hear me?
Fallada, speak up!
I can't hear you!
The two males didn't die.
They jumped to the bodies
of the two soldiers who shot them...
and transformed the soldiers' bodies
into their own likenesses.
That's the difference
between them and their victims.
Their victims can't leave their bodies.
Only the original three can do that.
- But I've killed one of them.
- One of which?
One of the two male vampires.
- One of the transformed ones.
- How did you kill him?
The old way, Carlsen.
A leaded metal shaft
penetrating not through the heart...
but through the energy center
two inches below the heart.
Not steel, but leaded iron.
Right, Carlsen?
- Are you there?
- Y es.
Carlsen, and you, too, Caine...
it is my belief...
that the vampires of legend
came from creatures such as these.
Perhaps even
from these very creatures.
I know it sounds incredible.
Do you hear me?
It's more than a belief.
It's true.
They visited Earth before.
- What about the other male?
- He's free.
- You have the girl?
- Yes.
- We'll be there soon. Hold on.
- We'll try.
- This came while you were talking.
- What is it?
A scrambled cryptograph to Sir Percy
from the Prime Minister.
We're to proceed directly
to the citadel at Whitehall.
Lieutenant, the controls!
We've lost her.
She's gone!
- Where?
- Her body's in London.
Where in London?
You've got to tell me
what really happened on the Churchill.
It wasn't Rawlings
who destroyed the radio equipment...
and the ship's tapes.
- It was me.
- Why?
I didn't want the Churchill
to be able to reach Earth.
And if it did, I didn't want anyone
to know what happened.
What did happen?
I opened her sealed
animation case.
Either I did it
or she did it.
I couldn't help myself.
I've never experienced such--
I was in love on a level
you've never known.
It terrifies me.
My memory plays tricks on me.
She was calling me.
Her power was spiritual.
She wanted me, Caine.
It was more than spiritual.
She took some of my energy.
And she gave me
some of her energy.
They must have been living
off of each other when we found them.
There were only three of them left.
She killed all of my men,
one by one.
But I survived.
She wanted me to survive.
She chose me!
Why?
She's not human.
She's not a woman.
She'll destroy you.
She's destroyed worlds.
There's something
you might want to hear, sir.
A special bulletin
from the BBC.
Tonight London is on the brink...
of the worst devastation
since the blitz.
I can see large areas of the city
burning out of control.
Thousands of people are now rampaging
through the streets...
in a frenzied last effort
to avoid the plague.
Martial law has been enforced now
for three hours...
but it hasn't stemmed
what is obviously--
- Yes, we've been expecting you.
- Thank you. Carry on.
- Hurry over, Sergeant.
- Right, sir.
- Go around the other side.
- Right.
Is everything ready
for the cabinet to evacuate?
- Yes, everything.
- Please take a seat, gentlemen.
Sir, I have Colonel Caine
and Colonel Carlsen here for you.
Very good.
The Prime Minister will see you shortly.
Would you care for tea while you wait?
- Our business is rather urgent.
- The Prime Minister understands that.
- Gentlemen.
- Prime Minister.
I'm Colonel Caine,
Special Air Service...
and I'm sure you've heard
of Colonel Carlsen of the Churchill.
Y es, indeed.
Gentlemen, I look forward
to hearing your report.
By the way,
where is Sir Percy?
Dead, I'm afraid.
Oh, that's a great pity.
Sir, we have information
regarding the object in space...
- which is bearing down on the Earth--
- Yes, gentlemen.
If you'll excuse me
just for a moment.
Miss Haversham,
please come this way.
Here, for a moment.
I'll be back, gentlemen.
Please.
Somebody get the doctor immediately.
We need a doctor over here.
Go!
- Do you have any weapons aboard?
- No, sir!
- There is a flare pistol, sir.
- Where is it?
Close the breach
and it's ready to fire!
Get him!
While you were with the Prime Minister,
I had a call from base operations.
The city is now under martial law.
We've been placed under NATO command.
- NATO?
- Yes, sir.
My unit's been mobilized
to a staging area at Blackheath.
Land at the S.R.C.
We've got to talk to Fallada.
I'm to land at Blackheath.
The city's under air quarantine.
If we don't do as they say,
they'll shoot us down.
Zero, this is X-ray 318 requesting
clearance to land. Over.
Zero, roger.
X-ray 318, you are clear to land.
Come away from the aircraft!
You are under quarantine!
Over here, please, sir.
Don't come any closer!
Stop there!
I want to talk
to your commanding officer.
I am Colonel Caine,
Special Air Service...
and this man is Colonel Tom Carlsen,
United States Air Force...
and former commander
of the Churchill.
Is Dr. Hans Fallada here
from the S.R.C.?
- He knows who we are.
- No, not that I know of.
Has anybody heard of him?
He must still be in London.
Colonel, what exactly do you know
about what's happening there?
All we know for certain is that
a terrible plague is sweeping London.
The incubation period
appears to be two hours.
Until that time has elapsed,
I cannot release you from this compound.
We know what the plague is.
We are not infected.
I know what I'm talking about!
We're wasting valuable time!
We have totally isolated London...
in order to stop further contagion.
If that fails, and the surrounding
areas are threatened...
Yes?
sterilization by thermonuclear device
has been approved.
We have this from General Ames
in Brussels.
He's coming up with that decision
in just under three hours.
Have you heard anything
about the ship?
- "The ship"?
- The thing from Halley's Comet.
It's parked itself in a geostationary
orbit directly over London.
All those little blue lights going up
toward the clouds are human souls.
- How do you know that?
- I feel it.
The process of conversion releases
a life energy that can be collected.
"Collected"?
Is that what the umbrella is?
A collector?
The energy doesn't go free.
It goes up there.
The male vampire is collecting
life energy...
but he has to send it through her
to get it up to the collector.
Where is she?
Over there.
I get flashes
coming from her body.
It's sensitive to its environment.
It picks up things.
- Can you find her?
- If I can get across to the city.
What about the male?
He'll come if he senses I found her.
She's drawing me.
I've got to go.
Why?
She wants back
the energy she gave me.
When they take on a new life-form...
they have to learn
from that life-form.
Mate with it, in a sense.
The girl chose me.
But when she mixed with me,
she gave me a part of herself.
Now she wants that part back.
Is there any sign of activity
in your sector? Over.
- No, sir.
- Okay, keep me posted. Over.
Colonel, listen to me. Carlsen
believes he can locate the source.
There are only two carriers.
If we can destroy them, it may not
be necessary to destroy London.
But we only have
an hour and a half.
Cease firing!
Where's Carlsen?
He knocked over two of my men
and took an armored land rover.
Did he say where he was going?
He wanted to know where
the Space Research Center was.
Rogers told him,
then I was on the ground.
- Right. Whose car is this?
- That?
- That's the colonel's.
- Give me the keys.
- What?
- I'm commandeering the car!
Give it to him.
And your side arm.
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
Once you're inside there,
we can't allow you out.
- Watch out!
- He's going in!
Colonel Caine, S.A.S.
I'm crossing the river.
- You don't want to go in there.
- I know I don't.
Get them gates in position!
Secure this post! Move!
I'm glad to see you alive.
I reciprocate the sentiment.
- Is he really dead this time?
- The only way they can be killed.
- Where's Bukovsky?
- Dead.
- How?
- Like the rest.
How did you survive?
- You're looking for Carlsen.
- Has he been here?
No. Perhaps he misled you.
- What do you know about it?
- I've been doing some more work.
- Go on.
- I've discovered...
there is life after death.
-How do you know?
-There is a certain mental transference.
Telepathy occurs between
the vampires and their victims.
- Carlsen is after the girl.
- How did you know that?
- I seem to sense it.
- Where is she?
Don't you know?
- Carlsen knows.
- Where?
She's in the cathedral.
She's been there
since she escaped.
Rather a nice touch,
don't you think?
The crypt of kings and queens.
Stay where you are.
Here I go.
I knew you would come.
I'm here.
Now can this madness end?
Come.
Be with me.
I need you.
It was always intended...
you should find us...
and bring us to Earth.
The web of destiny
carries your blood and soul...
back to the genesis
of my life-form.
Come with me.
It will be much less terrifying
if you just come to me.
I'll do just that.
What are these feelings?
Why do I feel so close to you,
need you?
Because you're one of us.
You always have been.
You're like me.
Be with me.
Just a little more.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org