Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
23.976 english
Don't worry.
You don't trust me?
I got the money.
Let's see the stuff.
Let's see the money.
Money.
This is sugar!
No shit?
Yeah, no shit.
And this...
is gasoIine.
Come on,
torch him, man!
Aah!
Oh! Aah!
Mrs. GauItier,
I'm sorry
this happened
to your famiIy.
We've done
everything we couId.
In cases Iike this,
it is very difficuIt
to make any kind
of prediction,
so for the next coupIe of months,
it's going to be touch and go.
Mrs. GauItier--
The insurance
has expired, I know.
Does he have any other reIatives,
anyone eIse that couId possibIy heIp?
No.
Come on, NicoIe.
Let's go home.
Lyon.
Lyon!
Ha ha ha.
Aye, Lyon.
Wonder what's in
the goody sack for you today?
Heh heh.
Let's have a Iook.
There we go.
''Legionnaire
Lyon GauItier.''
Ooh, yes.
- It's very nice.
- No interest, eh?
OK. Back she goes.
Aah!
Yeah, GauItier.
That's me.
This one's been out
in the sun too Iong.
She tried to caII me
two weeks ago.
Nobody toId me.
Why?
This is the Foreign
Legion, GauItier,
not CIub Med.
We're taIking about my brother.
He couId be dead by now.
And we couId be at war
with the bIoody wogs tomorrow.
I need your ass here.
Your brother
is not my probIem.
Or yours anymore.
You gave up your famiIy
when you joined the Legion.
I never gave up my famiIy.
Never.
Legionnaire, I don't have time
for this shiesse.
I need to see my brother.
You need what
I teII you you need.
And right now I think
you need two weeks hard Iabor.
You onIy have six months Ieft
in the Legion, GauItier.
Don't make it six years.
You're a reaI asshoIe.
Is there a probIem, sir?
No, no, no, no.
No probIem.
Desert fever.
This is your reaI probIem.
Too many weeks
in the hot sun.
ShaII we try
sweatbox, sir?
Yes,
this might heIp.
Just untiI his
fever breaks.
Cover your head,
Iegionnaire.
Move!
Your beIt.
Come on.
Ugh!
Move!
Your hoteI room
is ready.
OK.
Hyah!
Aah!
Ugh!
Hyah!
Get me a fucking jeep!
There's no sign
of him, sir.
He'II never make it.
If the wogs don't kiII him,
then the desert wiII.
Just in case, head down to the docks
first thing in the morning.
The ocean is his onIy way
out of the country.
Moustafa, go this way.
Hey!
Get your ass
back down beIow!
Get down to those
boiIer rooms now!
OK.
This ain't no pIeasure cruise.
Move your ass!
The Ietter was
from his sister-in-Iaw.
We are fortunate our inteIIigence
section makes a habit
of recording
return addresses.
We'II contact the Americans
and ask them to keep her
under surveiIIance.
Inspector,
this man is a deserter,
a traitor to France,
and a goddamn terrorist.
Adjutant, aII I can do
is transmit the warrant.
If the Los AngeIes cops
aren't too busy
busting dope deaIers,
gang rapists,
and seriaI kiIIers,
maybe they'II have time
to bring the asshoIe in.
And if they don't,
tough shit.
If they do not,
maybe I can heIp.
You stay off
the top deck.
First Mate's orders.
You were toId not to come up.
Am I right?
Yeah.
And you toId me this ship
was going to Los AngeIes.
What difference
does it make?
You ain't got
no green card.
You ain't got no visa.
You ain't getting off
anywhere, Frenchy,
so get your ass beIow
before somebody reports you,
a deserter,
stowed away on their ship.
You keep stoking my boiIers,
or you'II be breaking rocks
in the hot sun.
Now what's it going to be?
It's going to be simpIe.
Ugh!
Hey, maybe we make a deaI.
You've been
so generous to me.
Huh?
America.
Los AngeIes information.
PIease deposit $2.40.
No, it's my
sister-in-Iaw.
She's waiting for me.
HeIene GauItier.
I don't care if she's
the mayor's sister-in-Iaw.
If I don't hear coins,
this conversation's over.
You got it?
Hey, come on,
get him!
Who you puIIing for,
motherfucker?
KiII that fucker!
Come on, goddamn it!
You want another fight?
You sure you don't
want another fight?
You can win.
Get your money.
I ain't got aII goddamn day.
Shut up, shut up.
Wh's gonna fight the next fight?
Who's going to fight
the next goddamn fight?
Do we even have
a next fight?
Do we have a next fight?
- Yay!
AII right, aII right.
We got a visitor.
AII right.
- Who might you be, man?
- Lyon.
- What?
Lyon.
- Lyon?
What the fuck is Lyon?
Lion! The Lion!
AII right, aII right.
Who wants
to take on the Lion?
Somebody's got
to take on the damn Lion.
Hey, there's my man now.
We got a fight now, baby.
Yeah, Iet's get ready
for this one.
Bets down.
Get your bets down.
I got $10.
$10. Which one
do you want?
Ain't nobody going to bet
on the Lion? Thats it!
Bets over, bets over.
Bets over, everybody.
Bets over.
Hey, my man. Look here.
You sure you want to do this, my man?
I'm the onIy one
betting on you.
Don't Iet me down.
This is ours
if you beat this dude.
It's going right here.
Trust me, man.
Can you beat him?
Kick his Iion ass.
AII right, aII right.
Get it on.
Hyah!
That's good, man, good.
I don't beIieve this.
I got me a man here.
You see this?
That's it, my man.
Damn, boy!
Hey! You see that shit?
Look at this here!
You a bad motherfucker
with that foreign shit.
Put it right there.
You bad, boy.
What the fuck you doing, man?
Get out of my pocket.
AII right, fuck it.
Take it. It's your money
any goddamn way.
- Wait, Iet me count--
- Thanks.
Let me count this shit.
Hey, wait a minute.
You didn't give me enough.
You're a good fighter,
but you can't count worth shit.
The number you have diaIed
is no Ionger in service
and there is
no new number.
If you feeI you have reached
this recording in error,
hang up and diaI again.
Nobody home?
No.
Goddamn, man, don't be
Iookin' at the damn sandwich.
Eat it.
It won't hurt you.
You're the Lion,
king of the jungIe.
- You want to get to L.A., huh?
- Yeah.
Hey, thank you very much, man.
I'II get you back in L.A., aII right?
Thank you
for paying the check.
Yeah, sure.
That is where
you're going, L.A.?
Yeah.
Can you take me there?
Damn straight, baby.
When?
That depends
on you, my man.
We have to see some peopIe.
You understand?
Hey, now.
What's happening?
May I heIp you gentIemen?
Here to see the Iady.
You'II have to be
more specific.
Cut the shit. TeII her Joshua's here
with someone I think she'd Iike to meet.
WeII, if it
ain't oId Joshua.
My main man.
Uh-huh, yeah.
How did you find us?
Word gets out.
Know what I'm saying?
I want you to
meet somebody.
You chose a bad time.
CaII me next week.
No, no.
Now.
You don't know
when to quit, do you?
My man just kicked five asses.
You want to be number six?
Ha ha ha.
OK.
Fuck it.
FoIIow me.
I Iove New York.
Is there a fire
somepIace?
Hey, Iookit here.
Wait here.
FormaI, ain't he?
Hey, this is
your ticket, man.
Ticket to L.A.
AnypIace eIse
you want to go.
Check it out.
That, my man,
is the Iady.
And this is her show.
Been a Iong time, Joshua.
I see your taste
is improving.
Who's this?
This is the Lion,
king of the jungIe.
Joshua, pIease.
What's your name?
Lyon.
Lyon? You're French?
What's the difference?
Ha ha ha.
It's aII right.
My man don't Iike taIking about himseIf,
where he comes from, any of that mess.
Is it cooI?
CooI.
I can appreciate
a IittIe attitude,
as Iong as he can give them
what they want to see.
Come on, get him!
Get him! Come on!
Ha!
Look at that.
Come on! Come on!
Come on.
Yeah.
Ugh!
Hyah!
Come on, get up!
Get up!
Ow!
Come on!
Whoo!
Bring it in! What is this?
End your fight! Come on!
Let's do Iunch
sometime.
- Sonny! Sonny!
Now it's time to find out how bad
you wanna get to L.A., my man.
No nickeI-and-dime
shit here.
Hey, there they are.
Sure you want to mess up
that face, handsome?
You're up, stud.
Hey, wake up.
Fight's this way.
It's aII right.
Everything going to be just fine.
Hey, how you doing, Josh?
You aII right?
- What are you caIIing it?
- I make Sonny a 3-to-1 favorite.
What's the other kid's name?
Lionheart.
Hey, I got 3-to-1
against Lionheart.
3-to-1 against Lionheart.
3-to-1.
10 grand? Got it.
AII right, sir.
Dig it, Lionheart--
15% off the top
if we win,
5% if we Iose.
We?
Hey, man!
Who brought you
here, sucker?
Ok, I got it.
I got it.
I'II bet this whoIe
wad on your ass.
You whip this sucker's ass,
and we spIit 50-50.
Huh?
Man, shit.
Lookit here.
Yeah.
We're partners, man.
Huh?
Yeah.
Don't either one of us
ever forget that.
TaIk to me.
We haven't got aII night.
On Lionheart.
AII of it.
And, uh, keep this
between us, hmm?
It's over. It's over.
Come on, guys. Come on.
You know the ruIes, huh?
There's no ruIes.
You're kind of pretty.
I don't know if
I want to fight you
or fuck you.
- Ooh, Sonny.
- Ohh!
Come on, boy.
Come on!
Hey!
Come on, Sonny!
Come on!
Come on, Lyon.
That's it. That's it.
Aah!
Get up, Sonny!
Ahh!
Come on, Sonny!
Get up! Get up!
That's my man!
I brought him here!
Get up, pussy!
It's over.
He's had it.
BuIIshit!
- I couId kick this guy's ass.
- I know, baby. I know.
Not bad.
- Hey, come on.
- Who is this guy?
AII right, now,
you and me.
Lyon, Lyon. Hey, no.
Come on.
No, no. Hey, no.
Don't do that, man.
Come on, come on, come on.
Let go of me, man.
Come on, man.
You ain't going to do shit.
Hey! The winner!
Ladies and gentIemen,
Lionheart,
king of the jungIe!
Don't ever insuIt
one of my patrons again.
If there's something
RusseII or I can't handIe,
we have paid
security personneI who can.
You cIear on that?
Yeah.
Good.
Now, what's this shit
about a trip to L.A.?
I can have
another fight Iined up
in Iess than a week.
Better money for everybody
this time,
but it's up to you, Lyon.
I'm going to Los AngeIes.
What the fuck
is in Los AngeIes?
AII right. Can you at Ieast
make it back by Tuesday?
- No.
- Do us a favor.
TaIk it over
with your manager.
My manager?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
My man wants to go to L.A. What
he's got goin' there is his business.
We'II be back
when we're ready.
You understand?
Right, my man?
Let me teII you aII
something.
What I did tonight
I did for my famiIy,
not for you...
not for me.
You made a totaI...
of $5,000.
That's a pretty
substantiaI amount
for a one-night stand.
Where eIse wiII you
make that much money?
That's my business,
not yours.
Stop the car.
What if we arrange
a fight in CaIifornia?
We do have a circuit
out there, too.
Arrange it
for somebody eIse...
and stop the car.
That 5,000 won't go
as far as he thinks.
My private number...
in case
he changes his mind.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Hey. Hey, man.
Get up off the acceIeration,
wiII you?
You know how far that damn airport
is from here?
Hey, come on, man.
It's just me and you now.
I Ieft them other
jive turkeys way behind.
AII right.
I can dig it.
My brother
made me some money,
so I'II Ieave his ass
in the street.
Go ahead
with your bad seIf!
We'II see how far your ass
get without my heIp!
Wait a minute.
Jive motherfucker.
Tonight
I fought for you.
- You didn't make enough money?
- Wait a minute, man. Shh.
Huh?
You want some more?
Don't be taIking about money
around here, man.
These peopIe hear
we got $10,000,
we won't make it
to that damn corner.
Just put your money
back in your pocket.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Why don't we get a cab
out of here now?
Come on.
Hey, Iookit there.
There it is.
There's a teIephone.
That's what we need.
Yeah.
Listen to me.
I'II get you out of this.
I'm a survivor.
Come on, man.
Be out of this mess before
you know it. Come on, man.
Yeah, you Iooking
for an honest man,
I'm him.
I'II never steer you wrong.
There it is, see?
I'm right on it.
Hey, man.
What is this, man?
Shut up, man.
Hey, cuz, you want
to use our phone?
That's aII right, bIood.
We'II go somepIace eIse.
You don't Iike
my phone, cuz?
- How much you want for your phone?
- Let me do the taIking, man.
Hey, shut up, nigger!
I want to hear
the white boy.
This is my hood,
motherfucker,
and I ask
the questions.
How much you paying?
He ain't got no money,
motherfucker.
I got the money,
and I'II kick your ass.
You ain't getting shit!
Motherfucker's going to pay now!
Come on, man!
Today's your
Iucky day, punk.
That's right.
I want a cab.
What do you mean,
you don't send cabs
to this neighborhood?
You want to
use the phone?
Come on. Let's go.
Hey.
You're going to Iisten
to Joshua now, huh?
I've been
aII over the worId.
I've been around,
from the Big AppIe to the Big Orange.
How you going to get around
in aII that smog?
Huh?
Them freeways?
A Iot of peopIe
in L.A., man.
A Iot of shit going on.
A Iot of weird ass motherfuckers
running around.
Huh?
And besides,
I owe you Iunch.
Yeah, yeah,
you owe me Iunch.
But you're
wasting your time
if you think
I'II fight again.
Hey, I can dig it.
It's cooI.
OK.
Yeah.
Ah, shit.
$5,000 goes a Iong way
in the Iand of sunshine.
It finaIIy happened
Iate Iast week.
With the extent
of his injuries,
honestIy, I don't know how
he heId on as Iong as he did.
It's because I toId him
I'd aIways
be there for him.
I'm truIy sorry.
The guys that did this to him--
did they catch them?
Mr. GauItier...
he's gone,
and nothing we can do
wiII bring him back.
Doc, my question is,
did they catch them?
Yes, Mr. GauItier.
I beIieve the poIice
have them in custody.
If I were you,
I'd be a IittIe
more concerned
about his wife
and his chiId.
He Ieft them with a stack
of unpaid medicaI biIIs
and not too much
of anything eIse.
Now, I can give you
their address if you'd Iike.
I have it.
Thank you.
Hey.
You don't Iook sick
to me, baby.
Whoo.
Hey, Lyon!
Hey, Lionheart!
Hey, man, what's happening?
You act Iike they said
you were pregnant or something.
I don't need you.
Just go, OK?
Go.
Hey. Ha ha!
Lookit here.
There he is.
Ha ha! Yeah, hey.
My treat, remember?
Yeah.
Damn.
InfIation, man.
Now, Iookit here.
Here's $2.00, man.
Keep the change.
Give it to your kids.
I heard RusseII say
you don't know when to quit.
- Hey, that's me, man.
- That's you.
- Can't argue with the facts.
- You have nothing better to do?
OK.
Maybe you can heIp me, then.
Find this pIace.
That's the address.
Yeah, yeah.
No probIem, man.
Who Iives there?
You got a sister?
Come on.
Just find me this pIace
and don't ask too many questions.
Hey.
[Horn Honks]
Hey! HoId it, man!
HoId that goddamn car.
Motherfucker.
Hey, yeah.
Hey. Oh, hey!
Hey, hey. There it is.
There it is, right there.
This yours?
Do you know where
a Iady named HeIene Iives?
Can you show me?
My mommy toId me not
to taIk to strangers.
Your mommy, huh?
She's right.
My name is NicoIe,
and I'm 5.
NicoIe,
my name is Lyon.
Now you're not
a stranger anymore?
I'm not a stranger
when your mommy says I'm not a stranger.
Just give me
tiII Friday, OK?
A few more days,
and you'II have it.
Friday.
Not a partiaI payment.
Cash, 450 bucks.
Cash.
OK, if you don't,
you and your famiIy
are on the streets!
I don't think this wouId be
a good time to ask my mommy.
Deadbeats Iike you are why I can't
get the goddamn eIevator fixed!
Let's go.
Mommy,
is he a stranger?
NicoIe, go inside
and draw with your crayons.
Just for a minute,
honey.
So you finaIIy decided
to grace us with your presence.
HeIene, it was impossibIe
for me to go.
I put myseIf in a Iot
of troubIe to get here.
I've got news for you.
It wasn't worth it. You're too Iate.
HeIene, I tried.
I'm sorry.
I tried.
The onIy thing that he wanted
was just to see your face again.
- Maybe we shouId go inside.
- No! I don't want you inside.
I don't want you anywhere near me
or my daughter again.
You started her father
on that shit.
- That's not true.
- Oh, yeah?
He took that shipment
to Amsterdam for you.
That's what I toId the cop.
He was a smart kid.
I didn't want him in jaiI.
- He had a future. You were pregnant.
- Oh, spare me the detaiIs.
He might have been better off if you
had kept quiet and Iet him go to jaiI.
He was not enough
strong to be in jaiI.
It wouId have kiIIed him.
The streets that you Ieft him on
are what kiIIed him.
No, HeIene.
Come on.
I don't have anything
more to say to you.
HeIene, come on.
HeIene, you and NicoIe,
we're famiIy.
You're my onIy famiIy.
Let me try to heIp you.
HeIene...
this is to heIp you
with your biII.
I don't want your money.
Don't you get it? I don't want
anything from you ever again!
Now get out of here
before I caII the cops!
You Iook Iike you're ready
to jump off a bridge.
Here, have some chicken.
No. Thanks.
I need something eIse.
You don't even
have to say it, man.
I'm psychic.
Foreign Legion, huh?
Them guys with
white hats, right?
I thought the Foreign Legion
was something you see on oId movies.
I wish...
it was just an oId movie.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey there.
Where do you
want to go now, man?
You want to get some girIs?
You want to go dancing?
Where do you want to go?
I've got some business
to finish.
PersonaI business.
Lookit here, is it something
I can heIp you with, man?
Yeah.
Maybe.
Yeah. Ha ha ha ha!
Here, Iet's drink
to that, man.
Hey, put them up there.
Ha ha!
There. AII right?
Yeah.
Ahh, up jump the deviI
and his bIind chiIdren.
Hey, Iook.
Uh, Iook here, man.
I got to make a phone caII.
I'II be right back. AII right?
Uh, where you going?
Hey, we got to find somepIace
to stay for the night, right?
I'm Iooking out for you.
I'II be right back.
Yeah, I'II make
a phone caII.
Look out, Iook out,
Iook out, Iook out.
You're aII right.
Stand up.
Hey, huh?
Check it out, Dorothy.
We ain't in Kansas no more.
- Where are we going?
- Visit an oId friend of mine.
There. That's her pIace
right there.
Ha ha ha.
Sure you're aII right?
Yeah.
She onIy uses this pIace
when she's in L.A. on business.
Go ahead. Look around.
It's yours for the night.
How about you?
Be right next door.
That's hers, too.
It's nice to have
friends, ain't it?
Hey, Iook, you reIax, man.
Enjoy yourseIf.
[Squeaking]
Good morning.
Joshua toId me you needed a pIace
to stay for the night.
I, um...
hope this was adequate.
Yes. Thank you.
I need to go.
Excuse me.
Ha ha ha.
So go.
When I came in
this morning,
you were spread across the bed
Iike an oId throw rug.
What happened to my cIothes?
I gave them to the vaIet
with instructions to burn them.
You toId them
to burn my cIothes?
Give me a break.
There are a few shops
right down the street.
I'm sure we'II be abIe to find a way
to repIace your fabuIous wardrobe.
I just want
my cIothes back.
Not on your Iife.
I'm taking you shopping today
if I have to drag you
kicking and screaming.
Why are you so nice to me?
# WeII, there she stood #
# AII cIothed in brown #
# She saw my shadow #
# She turned around #
# Such a teaser... ##
Just try one more.
Hmm?
S'iI vous pIait?
It's nice...
but it's not for me.
No?
How about this?
Any better?
Ahem!
Everything OK in there?
Everything is fine.
You know,
peopIe in New York are stiII
taIking about your fight.
Let them taIk.
Are you pIanning on
sIeeping in the haIIway?
No. I'II stay next door
with, uh, Joshua.
Oh. Is that it?
You two, um,
got something going?
Cynthia,
I'm not your toy.
If you want a toy to pIay with,
taIk to RusseII.
Not to me.
Want to take this?
It's your favorite,
isn't it?
This your baII?
Mm-hmm.
Take some money.
[Knock On Door]
Oh, Christ.
WeII.
I'II do it.
WeII...
finaIIy.
I mean...
I'II fight.
Oh.
But first you have to heIp me
to take care of some business.
AII right. TaIk to me.
I need to open
a bank account.
- I Iike that kind of taIk.
- Not in my name. We'II make up a name.
Don't ask me why.
Just do it.
That's my condition.
I'II caII my accountant
first thing in the morning.
Anything eIse?
Yes.
I have to move out of here.
Do I have the right to ask
what brought these sudden changes on?
I'm going to fight for you.
I have to Iive Iike a fighter.
This pIace is too nice,
too soft, too easy.
I see.
Don't faII on them
damn skates, boy.
What is this, a dance?
He's got on a damn skirt.
ScotIand.
ScotIand?
ScotIand, shit.
Kick his ScotIand ass.
PuII up his dress.
I'd Iike to see
if he's got any drawers on.
Take your time.
Don't be shaking
hands with him.
Come on, now.
Aw!
Get off my car!
Get off my car, man!
Get off the damn car.
That's it.
That's it!
One more time!
That's it. Yeah!
That's aII right!
You got it, baby.
Let go of him, Lyon.
Let go of him.
Let him go.
It's over.
Hey, that's right.
Be ready
with the cash, fIash.
OK. Yeah.
I'm back! He's back!
And we back together!
Afternoon, Iadies.
Moustafa.
It's your turn.
Mommy, does this mean
I can have a bike?
Um, honey, why don't you
go in the other room
so I can taIk
to Mr. EIdridge?
Draw me a pretty picture.
I'II go draw myseIf a bike.
That wouId be
very nice, sweetie.
She's cute.
I just don't know
how I couIdn't have known about it.
ActuaIIy, husbands
do this aII the time.
Yeah. Secret IittIe
insurance poIicy
to make sure the wife and kids
wiII be taken care of
without freaking them out.
WeII, you'II get one
of those every month.
You know how the post office is
around here, so I'II bring them.
Oh, no.
That's fine. Um...
Yes. Thank you,
Mr. EIdridge.
Hey, don't thank me.
Thank the man who set up the poIicy.
May he rest in peace.
Oh, uh... just do me
one IittIe favor.
I know it's something
he wouId've wanted.
WeII, what is that?
Get the IittIe girI
a bike.
AII right.
You have a nice day.
Aargh!
Yeah! That's it.
That's it.
I Iike that. Yeah.
Hey, man. Hey.
That's bad for you
when you jog, man.
It destroys
your concentration.
Look good to me.
Get on out there, boy.
Hey, you guys.
What are you drawing?
Like my new bike?
Yeah.
Bye, you guys.
- Bye.
See you tomorrow!
Moustafa, wake up!
He's here.
Downstairs.
Come on! Let's go!
NicoIe.
Come on inside, honey.
Did he see us?
He'II be back.
Ah, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey.
OK, I'm taking some bets.
Lionheart, 5-to-4.
No wading.
I mean,
this ain't no dive.
No I.O.U.s either.
Yeah!
Better Iuck next time, man.
Ha ha ha. Yeah!
Ha ha ha ha.
Hey...
We did it.
My boy did it.
Who is HeIene GauItier?
According to the bank,
she's the one that cashed
that phony insurance check.
She used to be married
to his brother.
-He's just trying to heIp the woman out.
-Is he fucking her?
Cynthia, you one hard, coId,
sick bitch. You know that?
I asked you a question.
He don't step
inside her apartment!
She don't know where
the money's coming from.
As his seIf-appointed
manager,
I'm counting on you to keep him
out of troubIe.
You mean,
keep him making money.
That's right.
For me...
and for you.
Start keeping an eye
on those two.
Hi.
See my new bike?
[Speaking French]
I said,
that's a nice bike.
Is that French?
My daddy used
to taIk French.
[Speaking French]
I've got to go now.
Who's that?
- NicoIe!
- You go home right now.
You go home right now.
You know why we're here.
Don't force us to get rough
in front of IittIe girI.
Without me,
they'II be homeIess.
TeII your sad stories
to the court-martiaI.
We're just supposed
to take you back
any way we can.
Give me one week
to get their money.
Your time was up
in the desert,
and we stiII owe you
for that, fucker.
Go to heII.
I show you heII.
KiII the bastard!
Grab him!
Come on!
This is the end.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Lyon, if you're in some kind of troubIe,
maybe we ought to know about it.
And your spying on me--
I shouId know about it too.
OK, now you know.
Maybe we shouId Iay
our cards on the tabIe.
Come on.
Oh, man.
Those dudes did a number
on you, huh, homes?
You know what you need, man?
You need karate Iessons, man.
That way nobody
wiII mess with you.
Look at you.
You got a broken rib.
You'II have to stay in bed
for a month.
Do me a favor.
Don't taIk to nobody
about my rib.
Don't worry about that, man.
Shit. $100, man.
Have a nice day.
[Knock On Door]
Who's there?
Mr. EIdridge.
I wasn't expecting you
back so soon.
I know. Something's come up.
We got to taIk.
About what?
I heard about
what went down.
Look, pIease, Mrs. GauItier,
this is reaI important.
Look, you got to get out
of this pIace tonight.
- You and the IittIe girI.
- How did you know what happened today?
Hey, my man.
So there never was
an insurance pIan, was there?
Look here.
Now you see that?
That's where your money's
been coming from.
I think you
owe him a minute
for him to say what
he's got to say.
So?
Say what you got to say.
OK. Those men foIIowed me
from North Africa.
They knew I'd be
coming to see you.
Does this invoIve drugs?
If it does, I don't want
anything to do with it.
HeIene, I swear,
it's not drugs.
I don't have too much time,
but I'm here to heIp you.
Don't do this to me.
I mean, my Iife is hard enough.
I'm not trying to
give you probIems.
I'm here to heIp you.
PIease.
You've got to trust me.
Hi, Mr. EIdridge.
Hey, yeah.
See my new bike?
He's aIready seen it.
Yeah.
Mommy, is he
stiII a stranger?
No, honey.
This is your UncIe Lyon.
Your daddy's brother.
I knew you weren't
reaIIy a stranger.
That's him. AttiIa.
A born kiIIer.
A reaI pro.
Not some bum
we picked off the street.
He Iikes to toy
with his opponents.
Give them hope.
Then he tears them apart.
Never seen anything Iike that
in our circuit.
And that's why I can't
Iet you have Lyon just yet.
The fight's aIready scheduIed.
But if I get hassIed
by the French consuIate...
or the immigration peopIe...
it'II screw up everything.
So I need your cooperation.
and I promise you...
as soon as AttiIa
is finished ripping him apart,
I wiII hand him
over to you...
as is.
What do you say, guys?
[Speaking Foreign Language]
Can...we...watch?
Yes.
I hope this is the right stuff
Joshua picked up.
There's enough to feed
her entire kindergarten cIass.
And...
there's something eIse
Santa CIaus brought.
Merry Christmas.
You guys are
going to spoiI her.
It's my onIy niece.
I've got a right to spoiI her, right?
Yeah, I guess so.
WeII, since there
is no reaI food here,
I guess I'II pick some things up
from work tomorrow,
bring them home.
I've got something eIse
I want to taIk about.
I don't think you shouId
go back to that pIace.
Are you serious? How Iong
do you expect us to stay here?
Oh, just...just untiI
you have a new job...
or another husband.
I mean, it's no probIem.
You can stay here.
It's home.
This is beautifuI.
Yeah.
Your niece,
she made it for you
and insisted I put it
right where you'd see it.
Nice.
[Speaking French]
Oui.
[Car Horn Honks]
Hey, man.
Guess who's outside?
Let's get crazy.
Where are we going?
Loosen up.
We're going
to see some friends.
How are your reIatives
doing, by the way?
They'd be better
if I was there.
WeII, this IittIe party
we're attending tonight,
it's for their benefit
as much as ours.
These friends of mine
are thinking of betting
some serious money
on your next fight, Lyon.
Just how serious
depends on you.
We can aII retire
on this one.
Don't fuck it up.
Mr. Lionheart, weIcome.
We've just been watching your videotape.
Most impressive.
- WouId you Iike a drink?
- Yeah. I'II have a gin an tonic
with a twist of Iime,
my good man.
By aII means.
Come this way, pIease.
- Did you have a pIeasant journey?
- No, man.
So, did you get the tape?
If you knew
what I went through
to smuggIe this out.
[Speaking German]
What do you think?
Not too good.
Piece of shit.
WeII, enough of this.
WeII, I have to teII you
I'm not too impressed.
What about you,
Mr. Lionheart?
We have friends in Hong Kong
who say he'II
wipe the fIoor with you.
What do you think about that?
Anything is possibIe.
TaIk is cheap.
You've aII
seen him in action.
Draw your own concIusions,
gentIemen.
As far
as I'm concerned,
Lionheart is going to eat
this bozo for breakfast.
And I've got a quarter miI
ready to back it up.
We'II Iet you know which way we're going
on the day of the fight.
Faster?
Yes!
OK.
Ahh!
OK, that's it
for today, guys.
She's so beautifuI.
Tonight I'II have a fight.
A big fight.
Lots of money.
And if I win,
I'd Iike to take you and NicoIe
away from this pIace,
away from this city,
and Ieave aII
the bad stuff behind us.
There's basicaIIy no probIem.
No probIems.
It'II be cIear.
AbsoIuteIy sure.
It's going great.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
You don't understand
at aII, right?
Open the door.
Madhouse out there, man.
Hey, hey, hey, my man.
Hey, huh.
Lookit here.
You ready to get rich?
Throw a few.
Ohh.
I took aII my money out of the bank
and put a bet on myseIf.
We're going
to win that fight.
Confidence.
That's what I Iike to hear, man.
You know what I'm saying?
AII right, what is it, man?
You been hiding something aII week Iong.
- What's going down, man?
- Nothing.
- Nothing, huh?
You know what's circuIating
out there, man? Huh?
12 miIIion
motherfuckin' doIIars, man.
Cynthia's friends have come through
Iike a motherfucker.
Then I hear this shit
about AttiIa.
This dude's aIready
bagged eight bodies.
-I'II beat him.
-Beat him? How, if you're aII fucked up?
I'II beat the guy.
I have to.
You don't have to do shit, motherfucker,
but get yourseIf fucked up Iike I did.
Is that what you want? Be out running
$5.00 fights for winos and junkies?
I'm going to take you away
from this shitty business.
You and my famiIy.
Even Cynthia, if she wants to.
Cynthia, man?
Do you think Cynthia gives
a fIying fuck about you? Huh?
You know what your probIem is, man?
You got a big heart, Lionheart.
You're strong as a Iion, man.
But this right here,
this--this is
what fucks you up
and Ieaves you bIeeding
on the motherfucking ground
with nobody to give
a two-bit shit about your ass.
Nobody gives a shit
about you but you, man.
Nobody.
You care about me.
I'm going to win that fight.
You've got to trust me.
Hey, Joshua.
Hey, uh...
who you betting on?
Look at the board.
The wind's definiteIy
bIowing in our direction.
I didn't ask you that.
I asked you who
you're betting on.
Why?
Having any Iast-minute doubts
about your boy?
No. I...
I was just remembering
the way you did me.
Is there something
I shouId know about AttiIa?
I shouId know about Lyon?
No, no, no.
No, he's going to stomp that dude
into the ground,
send him home
in a IittIe box.
WeII, then, there's the desk.
You've got about five minutes Ieft
to pIace your bet.
It happen too Iate, man.
What's up, man?
You going to make
a bet or what?
AII the stuff.
Very good.
Which way are you going, man,
Lionheart or AttiIa?
One minute to post,
my friend.
# TaIk intentIy in society #
# It's never easy #
# When you know that it's free #
# It's too Iate to change your mind #
# It's so hard to see it
when it's aII comin' down #
# 'Cause you're onIy safe
in your mind #
# No mercy #
# Your back's to the waII #
# No, no mercy #
# It's winner take aII #
See the Iook on his face?
He's totaIIy psyched out.
# No mercy #
RusseII.
[Speaking German]
# Winner take aII #
# No mercy #
# Your back's to the waII #
# No, no mercy #
# Winner take aII ##
- Ooh!
He's toying with him.
Let's go.
That's it.
Another one.
Hit him again.
What's wrong?
Stay down, damn it!
Stay the fuck down!
Stay down, man.
Just stay down.
We bet aII the money.
Don't worry about that.
Just stay down.
Cynthia, she bet against me.
I know it.
Right?
You were right.
She bet against me.
Damn it.
This dude's going
to kiII your ass.
to kiII your ass!
He's hurt.
That dude's going
to kiII your ass!
I toId you the way
this shit did me.
Don't Iet it do you.
Stay the fuck down.
Come on, man.
Come on. Look.
We don't need the money, man.
I got us a deaI--
50-50 aII the way
down the Iine.
I'm going to spIit it
with you, man.
50-50 aII the way.
Just Iike I said I wouId.
Look. It's on him, man.
The whoIe bet's on AttiIa.
Wrong bet.
Aah!
He's going to kiII
your ass, man.
Come on!
Kick the snot out of him!
Let's go, Iet's go.
Come on, Lionheart.
Lionheart!
Come on! Come on!
You!
Go on! Go on!
AII right!
You bury that motherfucker.
Kick the shit out of him!
We got him.
Great fight, Lyon.
Your famiIy's
going to be OK now.
It's time to go home.
Let's go.
Oh, uh, Cynthia, darIing.
I just wanted to thank you
for such wonderfuI advice.
Open the door.
You definiteIy
got heart, Lionheart.
Don't ever Iose it,
'cause you'II never get it back.
Take it from me.
I've been there, man.
Miss CaIdera,
the house wouId Iike to have a word with
you regarding your unsecured marker.
This way, pIease.
If you find that bitch,
don't Iet her off the premises.
She's headed toward
the front door now, sir.
With the cash?
TeII him it's in New York.
I'II have it tomorrow.
[Knock On Door]
Oh, my God.
Look.
We're aII ready to go.
What happened?
Come on.
I Iove you.
NicoIe, you and your mommy
wiII have to go without me. OK?
Here.
This wiII heIp you.
No! Why?
You have to go with us.
You have to.
It's not fair.
Why can't you go?
It's not fair!
I know Iife is not too fair.
Sometimes it's ugIy
and stupid and mean.
But sometimes,
Iife's beautifuI, too.
I've got to go back
to an ugIy pIace.
If I don't,
I'II be running forever,
and you and your mommy
wiII be running with me.
I don't care!
NicoIe, cherie, you've seen
too much ugIy aIready.
What about you?
I'm-- I'II aIways have something
beautifuI to remember.
Bonsoir.
- You take care of them, OK?
- You got it, man. You got it.
- I Iove you.
- I Iove you too.
I'II miss you.
Come on, Iet's go.
I Iove you.
Get out.
Good Iuck.
Lyon!
- Lyon!
- Hey, man! What the heII?
Hey, boy!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org