Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
That old lady is crazy.
You can say that again.
Good morning, all.
-Good morning.
I trust we reviewed our cases
over the weekend?
Yes.
You're watching
that Mabel Simmons case.
-It's all over the news.
-Right.
Now, that old woman has been giving
the police the blues all of her life.
-She was an ugly baby.
-Okay.
-Petty theft at 9.
-Oh, my goodness.
Illegal gambling at 18.
That Afro is thirsty.
Check fraud.
Not bad. Not bad.
-ldentify theft.
-Lord, help her.
Insurance fraud.
Okay, everything,
except attempted murder.
-Attempted murder.
-There we go.
Oh, my goodness.
-Assault.
-Nice.
The list goes on and on
and so on and so on.
Unfortunately, our fine officers may
have made a mistake on her takedown.
So we have to handle this with care.
Who wants it?
Don't all volunteer at the same time.
You're supposed to be helping me.
We have no volunteers
for the Simmons case?
Okay.
Linda, it's all yours.
Thank you. Stop laughing.
By the way, let's congratulate
our Linda Davis...
...on her 89 percent conviction rate.
Thank you.
With numbers like that,
you'll be DA one day.
-Okay.
-That's my girl.
Everyone else, let's check the boards
for the new cases and let's get to court.
All right.
-Honey, there goes our appointment.
-I know.
And you're all broken up about it.
-I am. I got a lot of work anyway.
-I know.
That's all right. After this case,
it's just you and me, Tanya.
Good, that will give me time
to talk you out...
...of these taffeta
bridesmaids dresses.
Wha--? You like them,
don't you, baby?
Take my advice,
just nod and say yes.
-Of course.
-You're weak.
Yeah, he's smart.
-You're smart.
-I'm smart.
-Thank you.
-I'll see you later.
-All right.
-Sign that for me. Thank you.
-And you have fun with that.
-Thank you.
So....
-You set a date.
-Yes, I set a date.
You know you're gonna need
a best man.
Told you I got brothers.
But your brothers have not been
the kind of friend that I've been to you.
Chuck, the only reason you wanna be
in my wedding is you wanna be seen.
-That hurts.
-Yes.
That really hurts.
But you are right.
Linda's parents, they're loaded, Josh.
The governor's gonna be there.
The mayor's gonna be there.
-Get out of here.
-Come on. Hook your boy up.
-I need you to be my usher.
-I don't want-- Listen.
-That's an important job.
-What can I say?
I just don't know.
I just don't know, Cora.
Uncle Joe, are you all right?
Uncle Joe?
Breathe, Joe, breathe.
You-- You okay?
I'm good, Cora. Turn that oxygen up.
You're not supposed to be smoking
around oxygen. That's the problem.
Oxygen is everywhere in the air.
If you light a cigarette,
you're lighting it in oxygen.
If you ain't got oxygen,
fire won't work.
-Learn some chemistry, honey. Learn.
-Chemistry?
What the hell you talking about?
You don't know what you talking about.
-Oh, you--
-This helps my--
My blood pressure.
Smoke to help my blood pressure.
Fool around and blow you,
your blood pressure up.
That's right.
This here is good for you.
It's good for you.
It came straight down from heaven.
God sent it down-- And he sent Viagra.
He sent this and he sent that oxygen.
You put them all together, you'll take
a woman to heaven and back.
Thank you.
How you gonna sit there,
talk about God...
...with a joint in your hand
and some Viagra?
God made this.
He made the birds and the bees
and the flowers and these trees.
Joe, you're just like your sister.
Both of y'all are going to hell.
-What?
-Uncle Joe.
-You want some?
-Joe--
-No. I need you to focus, Uncle Joe.
-Focus on what?
Why were you running from
the police? Madea? What happened?
Mabel always running
from the police, Cora.
You're mama been running
from the police. She's a ho.
Po-po. The po-po come,
she's running like a ho.
Your mama always running
from the police.
I'm sorry to tell you,
your mama is a po-po ho.
That fool is a thug.
That's right. Your mama a gangsta.
King Kong ain't got nothing on her.
-Got nothing on her.
-Daddy.
-Stop talking about mama.
-I'm not talking about her.
-You go on--
-How you all doing?
-Hey, Brian.
-I just saw the news.
What is going on
with you and Madea?
-What's happening? Are you all right?
-I ain't all right.
What's wrong?
I can't feel my big toes.
Thank you.
I'll tell you, when your parents get to be
a certain age, it's like raising children.
My kids don't give me trouble
like you and Madea are giving me.
What is the matter?
Have you lost your mind?
Madea's on probation. I don't know
what she was thinking about.
That never stopped your mom.
I got her out of trouble.
She's going to jail this time.
To the big house, prison, the slammer.
They're gonna lock her up...
...press her down, shake it together,
gonna be in her bosom.
-I'm telling you, she--
-Mr. Brown!
Too much?
-Yes.
Oh, wait, y'all go ahead.
Finish what y'all were saying.
Come on, Cora, let's go to down there,
see if we can get her out there.
They gonna lock her up.
She's going to the slammer.
-To the big jail.
-Mr. Brown.
-We don't need you to go.
-I got to go. They'll put her in Alcatraz.
She's gonna be in solitary condition.
They gonna lock her big behind.
-It's Alcatraz.
-Bye.
Get the hell on out of here.
Better behave yourself while I'm gone.
What the hell I'm gonna do?
I'm so high, you look like
your real daddy right now.
City of Atlanta v. Washington.
Miss, you were arrested
for prostitution.
Yes, Your Honor, she was.
Miss Washington...
...was arrested several times before.
Candy?
-Joshua?
-I'm sorry, Your Honor. I need to--
I need to pass this case
to my colleague.
It seems that I know this defendant.
Then get it to one of your colleagues.
-Hey, what's going on?
-I know her.
How?
It's a long story, but will you take it?
What's the case?
It's simple prostitution.
Then you have to take
my drunk and disorderly.
-Fine.
-Then give me a foot rub later.
-Okay.
-People, today.
Your Honor, Miss Washington has
been arrested twice for prostitution.
The people request no bail.
This woman was simply
walking home from the bus stop--
Save it. Save it. Bail is set
at $1 500 cash or bond until trial date.
-Fifteen hundred dollars?
-Yes, $1 500.
Miss Washington,
if you manage to make bail...
...you better be back for your trial.
-Do you hear me?
-Yeah.
If you're not here, you will regret it.
Go see the clerk for your trial date.
Next case.
City of Atlanta v. Mabel Simmons.
Hey, Cora. Hey, Brown.
If the Lord get me out of this,
I'm going by the church.
-Better mean it.
-I'll go by the church.
-You better mean it.
-I mean it.
Hey, Judge.
Oh, girl, your hair is so pretty.
Who's doing your hair?
Lord, have mercy. How you doing?
Mabel Simmons, you come before me
more than you go to the doctor.
Listen, I've changed my life.
I am living for the Lord.
-Since when?
-I am living for the Lord.
I am living for the Lord.
Hallelujah. I feel him down in my spirit.
You know, as I think
about the goodness of Jesus...
...and all that he has done for me...
...my soul cries out,
"Hallelujah, thank God for saving me."
You finished?
I don't believe that no more than
I believe you will stay out of trouble.
-Your Honor, judge--
-Save it. I saw the video.
And I told you that if she came back
before me again, she was going to jail.
She's going to jail.
You're a lawyer.
You're supposed to be getting me off.
You're weak-ass.
I gotta get me a real lawyer.
Matt Johnson or somebody.
You weak-ass lawyer.
-Good Lord.
-Your Honor, there's something...
-...you need to understand.
-There's nothing you can do.
-She is going to jail this time.
-I don't know about that.
-And why not?
-Our officers forgot to Mirandize her.
I was waiting for Miranda to come in
and nobody came in.
That's right. Ain't nobody Miranda me.
Miranda wasn't in the room.
Excuse me?
We were fighting for our lives.
You forgot to Mirandize her?
That old woman got the strength
of any man.
I've got to let you go.
You gotta let me go.
-As much as I hate it, I have to.
-Yes, you do.
But I'm gonna suspend
your driver's license indefinitely.
Gonna suspend my license?
My license been suspended.
Hell, you ain't doing nothing.
I ain't had a license for 38 years.
She's gonna suspend my license.
What's that gonna do? I got keys.
I'm gonna order you
to anger management counseling.
She'll take it. Thank you.
We appreciate it.
Go see the clerk. Get the paperwork
done and get her out of my courtroom.
-You're free.
-Free? Look at my neck.
-Hold on. Did you see my eyes?
-Saw your eyes, saw that face too.
You're tore the hell up. I'm free to go.
I know you wish you was going home,
but I'm going home. I'm going home.
Calm down, officer. It's your fault.
You forgot to Mirandize her.
-This is ridiculous.
-Take care, judge.
I love you, but I got to go.
But the saving grace is...
...she couldn't stay out of trouble
if you paid her. She'll be back.
Hey, Joshua.
Hey.
Hey, Ellen.
-Who's this?
-This is Mindy.
Mindy.
Wait in the car, baby.
She's only 1 4, Josh.
Pimp found her in the bus station,
put her in the streets.
-Well, I'm glad you found her.
-Thank God.
Ellen, l--
I gotta tell you, I think the job
that you're doing with these girls...
...is great.
-Just trying to do the work of my Lord.
-Well, I know you make him proud.
-Well, thanks again.
-All right.
Hey, Ellen. Wait.
I want you to meet somebody. Candy.
This is Ellen Holmes.
She's a minister and she--
-She helps get girls off the street.
-Hi.
Hey.
Here is my card if you need anything.
Do I look like I'm on the streets to you?
No, but you look like
you work in the streets.
You know what, I ain't got no time
for no Jesus jokers.
Fine. Then I ain't got time
for you either, sucker.
See you later, Joshua.
What kind of minister is that?
I know, I know.
She's the real deal though.
So you bailed me out?
Yeah.
Where you wanna do this?
We can go to your car, to your house.
-I'm not tripping.
-What are you talking about?
You bailed me out.
You want something.
-Do you think I want sex from you?
-Well, what you want then?
What about, you know, how you been?
How are you doing?
No man asking a woman how she
doing unless you want something
So, what is it?
What do you want from me, Josh?
Okay. What are you doing
out here on these streets, Candy?
How about you don't worry about that?
I gotta go. I ain't got time--
Candy, hold on. Hold on. Just--
All right. Let me take you
to get something to eat.
You hungry?
Come on.
Please?
-The Lord is so good.
-Yes, he is.
He is so good, he delivered
your mama out of the belly of that jail.
-Yes, he did.
-Yes.
We're going to Church
Sunday, huh, Madea?
I ain't going to no church.
Now, hold up. Wait a minute.
Let me put some church in it.
You said
if the Lord got you through this...
...you was going by the church.
That's just what I'm gonna do.
I'm going by the church.
-So when you coming?
-We just did.
I said I would go by the church.
We just passed by one.
Hallelujah. Saint Philip.
Hail Mary full of grace
and all you people.
God bless you.
All you people. Hello.
Oh, Mabel, the Lord is just so mad--
You just make the Lord mad.
Bow your head. Let's pray for her.
Cora, bow your head.
Brian, bow your head.
-Mr. Brown, I'm driving.
-Yeah.
The Lord can watch the wheels.
Bow your head.
Mabel, you bow your head.
Brown, if you don't shut the hell up
and--
Bow your head
and put your head in your lap...
...and smother yourself.
Bow your head.
Lord, don't send Madea to hell.
Just give her a little house
right outside the gates of heaven...
...so she can watch all of us go in.
Amen.
-Amen.
But, Madea, you can't make those type
of promises and break them.
-Cora.
-Yes?
-Do me a favor.
-Yes, ma'am.
Put the shut to the up, okay?
The shut to the up.
Mad-- Cora, don't you worry.
Just let it go.
When she gets in trouble,
she'll come running to the church.
Madea ain't gonna get in no more
trouble. I ain't gonna have that.
Between you and my daddy,
that's enough.
You ain't getting in trouble.
You got off easy this time.
The hell you talking to? I'm grown.
I am grown, okay, Brian?
You don't tell me nothing. I'm grown.
I ain't got--
I wasn't in trouble that time.
-I don't-- You don't tell me nothing.
-Madea.
I was reading this pamphlet from
the courts about anger management.
It says as women get older...
...our bodies don't produce
as many hormones as it needs...
...to stay calm and have stable moods.
But you going to see this doctor
is gonna be real good for you.
I'm not going to no angry manager,
Cora.
What the hell you bring them
down here for?
Why are you yelling at me?
They wanted to come.
What was I supposed to do?
Mr. Brown jumped in the car.
You was happy to see us
when you wanted prayer.
-That's right.
-You need to see one of them doctors.
They gave me one of them,
what they say, Brian?
Coca-- Colostomy.
-You had a colonoscopy, Mr. Brown.
-Colostomy?
Same thing.
I thought that fool said Coca-Cola.
Making me thirsty for good old Coke.
Now, Mabel, when we get old,
we gotta keep ourselves checked.
Now, you know,
they checked my prostate.
Mabel, you need
to get your prostate checked too.
Women don't have a prostate,
Mr. Brown.
Cora, I'm telling you,
Madea got a prostate.
You know there's more
where that came from.
-Why you bail me out of jail?
-Because you're a friend.
I don't understand why you--
Why you have to do this.
You was a-- You were a smart girl.
You used to get straight A's.
You remember?
-What?
-You really have tricked yourself...
...into believing
that night ain't ever happened.
Well, Josh, it did happen.
And it changed my life forever.
I tried to look for you every day
after that.
You must have been looking
in some pretty high places then.
Candy, I don't understand
why you are out there on those streets.
Look, you deal with things your way
and I'll deal with them mine.
-I don't need you to be judging me.
-I'm not judging you.
Yes, you are. What you do think
you're doing talking to me crazy?
-Will you--?
-Don't you shush me.
Telling me to--
Am I embarrassing you now?
Y'all got something to say too?
What you got?
-Anybody else?
-Please.
I'm not your enemy.
Hey. What's up, Josh?
Chuck, this is an old friend of mine.
Okay. How you doing? I'm Chuck.
Okay.
Hey, baby.
-Hey.
Thought you were in court?
I was. It got kicked.
She wasn't Mirandized.
What's this?
She's a friend of mine.
What's her name?
I--
I tried your friend.
You made bail quickly.
Candy, this is my fiancée, Linda.
Oh, wait. Hold on.
You said that's your fiancée?
You marrying her?
That'll never work.
I gotta go.
Hey, Candy.
Look.
This is my number.
If you need anything,
give me a call, all right?
Yeah.
-Well, are you gonna handle it?
-l-- Yeah.
Honey,
you are an assistant district attorney.
You shouldn't hang out
with the likes of those people.
What are you doing with her?
Don't answer that.
She's an old friend.
I was trying to help.
Bad move.
What did I say, Linda?
Didn't l? Didn't I say it?
What did you say?
I was talking to your future wife here.
Remember that?
About the fact
that you feel guilty, Josh.
I know. I made it out of the ghetto too
but I don't apologize for it.
But these people,
oh, they will never let you forget.
As long as you let them do that,
you'll feel a sense of obligation to them.
-Now, am I right or am I right?
-That is not it.
Don't talk, just agree.
Well, whatever it is...
...the point is they were afforded
the same opportunities you were.
You did something, they didn't.
Linda, it's not always that simple.
Just agree to disagree
and change the subject.
-Okay, can we just order some food?
-Yes.
Oh, my dad is having a party here.
I gotta go pick up my kids.
Y'all gotta handle this.
I know Joe ain't having no party
at my damn house.
Wait, just stay calm.
-Cora, who these people, Cora?
-I don't know.
-Cora, who these people in my house?
-I didn't know.
-Holy smoke.
-Who are all these people?
The music's too loud.
How could Joe have this party?
I know Madea gonna be upset.
Madea is upset.
Hey, sexy.
You look like a bowl
of peach ice cream.
Get out of my face
before I throw this oil all over you.
Oh, now you wanna get kinky, huh?
-Kinky?
-I like that.
-The devil is alive.
-Yeah.
Hey, sexy,
you wanna spend some time with me?
And be my client?
What kind of work she do, Cora?
A lawyer in a sick room,
a doctor in the court room?
She's a-- She's a prostitute.
Say it, baby.
I'm a prostitute.
-A prosti-what?
-A prostitute is what she said.
Street walker. Woman of the night.
Oh, Cora, give me that oil.
The devil is alive.
The blood. The blood.
She's Mary Magdalene, Cora.
Madea, just stay calm, okay?
Baby, don't have
no nervous breakdown.
Stay calm, Madea. Just stay calm.
-Mabel, just--
-Where the hell is Joe?
He know I just got out of jail.
Hey, Mabel. Hell, I didn't even know
you was coming home.
How are you doing? Good to see you.
Joe, who the hell are all these people?
When I saw the news,
I said they gonna lock my sister up.
So I've been inviting all these people
so that she could have a good time...
...when she come home and I'm so--
Yeah, right. You know better
than this, don't you, Joe?
-Joe, what you doing? You all right?
-He is smoking out of this pipe.
I'm glad you're home, Mabel.
I'm so glad you're home.
Madea, I just want you to stay calm.
All these people are for you,
Mabel, enjoy yourself.
Enjoy yourself. Excuse me.
Excuse me, sexy slim.
-Just-- You look calm. You calm?
-I'm calm. I'm clam.
-You look calm like a quiet storm.
-I'm calm. I'm calm.
The hell you doing upstairs
in my house?
And get the hell out of my bedroom.
She's got a gun!
Run! Run!
I don't wanna die.
I can make it work. I can give you
some lndian hair. That's right.
It'll be $75.
You got to make that work.
What about you?
What are you gonna have?
-That's right.
-Hello, ladies.
-All right, thanks.
-There you go.
-How are you doing?
-Thank you.
-All right?
Y'all take care of yourselves. Listen,
if you need anything, come see me.
-347 Chowder Lane.
-That's right.
All right.
Take care of yourselves.
-Hi, Donna.
-Hi, Ellen.
This is my friend, Candace.
-Here we go again.
-We've met.
This is my girl. We were in New York
together. I begged her to come here.
-And she finally came.
-ls that right?
-Taking care of yourself?
-Why are you all in my business?
-All right, Candy, Ellen is good people.
-I'm just here to help.
By thumping your Bible at me every five
minutes the way my grandmama did?
I don't know your grandmama
and I don't carry no Bible.
It's at home on my mantel.
You ain't got to carry it.
You know every word.
You better know it.
Amen.
Are you gonna give me some of them
or not?
You asking me?
Go on, act right, man.
She's good people.
May I have some, please?
"May l?"
Girl, you're sounding all educated.
Here.
Here's a voucher for some food
if you need it.
-What?
-You don't know how to say thank you.
Thank you.
You on drugs?
-Why?
-What is it, heroin or coke?
Don't you be touching me. You don't
know me. You need to back up.
-You need some clean needles?
-I do.
-What's wrong with you?
-Here you go.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Take care of yourselves.
And, Donna, I'm still waiting.
I know.
Donna, who is that fool?
Man, I've been on these streets
since I was 1 6 years old.
I've seen all kinds say they come
in the name of one God or another.
But that woman right there...
...she's real.
She's good folks, man.
She'll be around all types
of dope boys, pimps, addicts.
And she treats us all the same.
She preaches down at the prison.
Why she say she waiting on you?
I keep telling her I'll get off my street.
No, sir. Well, I don't--
Well, that's all I have. I--
That's the first and last name.
That's all I have.
Sure. No, I understand.
All right. Okay.
Okay, thank you.
-Any luck?
-No.
What about you?
Nope.
Man, you know, tell me again,
why are we doing this?
I'm just trying to find somebody
to help her get off these streets.
You've-- You've never done this before
so it's--
We got history.
Oh, you--
-Not like that.
-You're trying to help this girl, man.
And I've never heard you mention her.
I've known you for, like, three years.
We're supposed to be looking for
vacation spots for your honeymoon.
-We are.
-No, no, no. We.
You called me up,
you said, man, come over here.
-Hey, baby.
-Hey, how are you doing?
-How are you?
-Oh, I am good.
Okay, you know what,
I'm gonna leave you lovebirds alone.
-I gotta--
-Where you off to?
I gotta--
-You ain't going nowhere.
-I got a date, so-- Yeah.
-What's your date's name?
-Well, lucky girl.
Leave me alone. I'm out.
So today was incredible.
I found these shoes.
The girls are gonna flip out.
I found the most amazing dressmaker
and she agreed to do the dress for us.
-That's great.
-I know.
Did you find any places
for the honeymoon?
No, actually I was--
I was--
I was looking for some of
Candace's family in Texas.
Okay, so you're still talking
about this prostitute?
-Why are you calling her a prostitute?
-That what she is.
Baby, where I'm from, if somebody
needs help, you try to help them out.
Okay, sweetie...
...you know that you can only
help someone that wants to be helped.
Those people don't want help.
-Why do you call them those people?
-I mean, those people.
People like her,
from that side of the tracks.
I'm from the same street.
-We were in college together.
-That doesn't make any difference.
It's not the same thing with you.
Sweetie, she's not like you.
It is her own fault if she didn't
make something of herself.
Linda, you've always had things
handed to you.
You've always been, like,
daddy's little princess.
Until you're on the streets,
you wouldn't understand.
That is my cue to leave.
-I'm gonna let you cool off for a minute.
-Wait, Linda.
-Yes?
-I'm sorry.
I am, but it bothered me seeing
that woman on the street.
-lt bothers you.
-Yes, it bothers me.
Okay, when she stops bothering you,
why don't you give me a call?
-Linda. Linda, hey.
-Okay?
-I don't want you to go.
-I don't wanna hear about this girl.
I'm done with her.
Now, you've helped her enough.
You won't hear about it again.
You still out here?
Yeah, girl. It's a slow night.
No, it's not.
Those Army boys just got paid.
Turned down, like, three
when I was here before.
What's up, girl?
I ran into somebody who I knew
from before earlier today.
Oh, I see.
You started thinking
what your life could have been.
No, not me. I know I ain't got no time
to be chasing no dreams.
You ain't like the rest of us, Candy.
You can get out of here
and make something of yourself.
What, me some Betty Crocker mom
or something?
No, you smart.
I see how you be reading them books.
Listen, Terry McMillan ain't doing
nothing to get me no fix, okay?
All I'm saying is if anybody
can get out of here, you can.
I've seen you talk to people.
I've seen you talk your way
out of all kinds of stuff.
You can do it.
Whatever, Donna. Please.
All right, I'm gonna make a deal
with you.
If I get off these streets,
you gotta get off these streets.
All right, that's a bet.
Maybe we can help each other.
Now, you know we always do, girl.
You know what I was thinking about?
-Remember we were in New York?
-Donna!
Candy, come on. Run. Run!
-You think you can hide from me?
-No.
I told you, you ain't gonna be out
here solo, Donna. Do you hear me?
-Okay.
-Now, get your ass out of here.
Okay, Donna. Let's go.
-No, no, no. Not you.
-No. What do you want?
You want a woman.
You don't want her.
-I see what I want. Get out of here.
-She's just been here.
I'm trying to show her the ropes.
She ain't ready. She ain't ready!
Get off of her!
Where you think you're going?
Where do you think you're going, girl?
You ain't going nowhere.
You understand me?
-Where do you think you're going?
-Please, please, please.
I won't tell anybody, I promise.
-What, you think that scares me?
-Please.
Please. Please let me go.
Please let me go.
What are you gonna do for me
if I let you go?
What do you want me to do?
You belong to me.
You're my slave.
If a slave wanna be free,
they got to buy their freedom.
Okay. Okay.
I want you to get in that bathroom.
I want you to get cleaned up.
I can get a premium for you.
All right, go on, baby.
Come on, it's all right.
Gonna learn you ain't protected on
these streets unless you got a pimp.
Do you understand?
I got this nice party
I'm gonna take you to.
A lot of new potential clients,
couple of G's easy.
I want you to make yourself
look real nice, girl.
I got a good feeling about you.
You're gonna be
one of my special girls.
Don't be wasting time in there, girl.
Come on, now.
We gotta be running now.
I don't wanna be late.
Get on with that shower in there,
Candy.
What's going on in there?
Operator, I need district attorney...
...Josh Hardaway.
Just connect me to his phone, please.
It's an emergency.
Hello.
Hey.
You okay?
Are you serious?
Where are you?
Okay, I'm coming right now.
I'm coming r-- I'm coming right now.
All right. I know. All right.
Bye.
Candace.
Can you walk? Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Thanks. I'm okay.
Baby?
I fell asleep.
How come you're not in bed, sweetie?
What? What's the matter?
I can explain. I can--
Is that my robe?
-You can explain?
-She's in trouble. I'm trying to help.
Why did you bring her here?
Linda, she needs somebody.
I don't care what she needs.
Shush? Are you kidding me?
What is it with you and this girl?
What is going on here?
Linda, I told you.
-I'm the only one that can help her out.
-No.
You have some decisions to make
and some thinking to do. I am leaving.
And stop shushing me. Shushing me
so the prostitute can sleep?
I am done, Josh.
I cannot believe this.
Linda, just don't slam the door.
You slammed it.
Can't even shut the door....
You always did know
how to pick them.
She's not your type.
How you know what my type is?
You haven't seen me in five years.
Josh, I know you, okay?
She is not it.
She's entirely too much of a princess.
It ain't gonna work.
I bet--
I bet you ain't even proposed to her.
Then why do you think
we're getting married then, smarty?
Because she told you you were.
Oh, you don't know me.
You think you know me
but you don't know me, girl.
Josh, I know you. We grew up toge--
We spent every day together
when we were kids.
I know you.
Candace, people change.
I know that's right.
-You're shaking. Are you cold?
-No.
This ain't the cold shakes, baby.
When did you start using?
When you got out of school?
I had to find some way to cope
just like you.
What are you talking about, me?
Ambition, working two jobs.
While you were in school full-time?
You did that so you wouldn't have
to think about what happened.
That's an interesting concept you got.
Josh, I don't wanna
talk about this, okay?
All right, we don't have to.
We don't have to talk.
Hey, Josh.
Yeah.
You remember that bed and breakfast
we were gonna open in Savannah?
Down by the river. Bells.
I remember Bells.
-You remember?
-Yeah, I remember.
Oh, Josh.
I was gonna buy it...
...and live happily ever after.
So why didn't you buy it?
I couldn't find a job...
...and I ain't have no money,
I was so hungry.
And then l...
...I met this man.
And he said he loved me.
And he said he was
gonna take care of me.
And he said that if I loved him
that I would...
...sleep with him and his friend.
And it turned into
his other friends without him.
And then strangers.
It took me four years...
...four years...
...to get away from him.
CeCe, I'm sorry.
CeCe?
Yeah.
That little girl,
she died a long time ago.
Boy, are those tears in your eyes?
You better man up. Don't you sit
over there feeling sorry for me.
At least I get paid for what I do now.
You do not get paid for what you do.
I told y'all I ain't got no
anger-manager problem.
Y'all still insisted on me going.
You have a anger-management
problem.
Fine, take me down there then.
That's why I'm gonna get you
one of these.
-One of what?
-This, right here, one of these.
-What is that?
-It's a reminder on how to treat people.
WWJD.
You know what that means?
What that stand for?
What's wrong with Jermaine Dupri?
No. It means "What would Jesus do?"
Everybody know that.
I don't know. Hell.
Did you see that?
-Did you see him?
-Yes, I saw it. What you gonna do?
-Well-- What-- I'm gonna WWJD.
-Cora, Jesus did not have no car.
-Better go get that fool.
-He's gonna get his.
-No, I can't.
-Cora.
He's gonna get his.
Look. He got stopped by the light.
Well, pull up on him, then.
-Okay.
-I'm gonna do a drive-by.
Madea-- No, you're not.
Oh, man, I got this. I got this.
Excuse me, sir.
-Excuse me.
-Hey, fool.
-What?
-You cut in front of me. Did you see?
Go to hell.
Wh-- Did-- What?
-Did you hear that?
-Did you show him your bracelet?
-Did you show him the WWJD?
-Don't be funny, Madea.
Cora, I didn't raise no punk.
-You better go get that fool.
-I'm no punk, Madea.
-Cora, you ain't gonna be no punk.
-I'm not no punk. I'm not--
I stopped that fool in his face,
you goddamn fool!
Mama.
Girl, I ain't your mama.
Good morning.
What are you, a size 5-, 6?
Why?
Probably a 3.
You don't look like you eat much.
Joshua?
What the hell is this?
We both set up a job interview for you.
I think I can cover that eye up.
We have companies working with our
ministries to get women off the street.
That's if you wanna be.
Who said I wanted to be, huh?
-Candy, that's what you wanted.
-Well, I told you.
Sometimes women like her
say one thing one day.
And then they wake up
and say another thing.
What do you mean girls--?
You don't know me.
Chicks. Junkies like you with
a problem say one thing one day...
...and another the other
because you're on that stuff.
-Go to hell.
-You go first.
I ain't no damn addict.
Candy.
Candy, if the public defender can
show the judge that you got a job...
...it's gonna look really good.
And they may even
suspend your sentence.
I need to know.
I need you to try this, please.
Fine.
Thank you.
Okay, we'll see you there.
I gotta go to work. After you're done,
can you come to the courthouse?
I wanna talk to your lawyer. I'm gonna
see if I can help him through this.
Okay?
Yeah. Okay. Sure.
You wanna try to get this job or not?
I told them I didn't need
to come here and see you, okay?
Well, you know,
I don't usually see people individually.
But when I saw this tape
of you getting arrested...
...I thought I have got
to talk to this woman.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you so angry?
First of all, ain't nothing wrong
with me. Secondly, I'm not angry.
Okay? I'm not angry.
-You seem angry now.
-No, I'm not angry.
This is how I am.
I don't have no hostility at all.
Well, do you have to be in control
all the time of everything?
I don't have to be.
I ain't got no problem with that.
Well, then why
do you get so angry?
I keep trying to tell you
and that judge that I do not get angry.
Somebody do something to me...
...I do something to them.
That's common sense.
-So you believe in getting even?
-Hell to the yeah.
Why do you feel
you gotta get somebody all the time?
"Get him, get him."
You don't think that's angry?
If they: "Got me,"
I gotta get them, get them.
-That's what it is.
-Then, what you call getting got...
...is different than what
other people call getting got.
It doesn't take much to get you,
does it?
When you getting got, somebody
got you, then you go get them.
Everybody's gonna get got.
But if you're getting somebody
got you...
...when they didn't get you...
...you're getting the gotters,
they didn't do anything.
But if the gotters get me,
I'm gonna get my Glock.
Yeah, well-- But you don't get
the Glock when you hadn't been got.
What I'm trying to explain,
I don't care who got me.
-I'll get them first. Get me, I'll get you.
-Why is it so important?
Okay. I'm tired of you
asking me these questions.
I didn't sign up for this.
It's the judge
that told me to come here.
Everybody wants to get even.
Everybody wanna get even.
All right, all right.
Look, let's just talk
about your childhood, okay?
-Let's talk about your childhood.
-Talk about yours.
Let's talk about your childhood.
Talking about my childhood
isn't gonna help us.
-What was your childhood like?
-What was yours like?
Why--? Let's talk about your anger.
-That's why you're here, right?
-I'm not angry. I don't know why.
-Let's just try another approach, okay?
-Let's try another approach.
Do you sleep well at night?
Let's try not to answer a question
with a question.
Could we do that?
Could we at least do that?
If we stop asking me
all these questions...
...I won't have to answer
with a question.
-Can you stop? Can you just stop?
-Can you just stop? Can you just stop?
-Are you getting angry, doctor?
-Okay. This isn't getting anywhere.
-This is not getting anywhere.
-I think I am gonna talk to the judge.
This is getting nowhere. We're done.
-Thank you.
-Okay. That's good.
-Wonderful to see you. Yes. Right.
-Yeah, well-- Yeah, great.
-Come on. Let's get the hell out of here.
-Wait a minute.
-Well?
-This lady is out of control.
She is-- I can't help her.
Wait a minute now, wait a minute now.
Now, you're the best.
-Go see somebody else. I'm done.
-Come on, Cora, here.
Oh, what am I gonna--?
Nobody gonna be able to help.
We ain't gonna....
Linda.
-Hey.
I've been trying to call you.
You know what, I got really busy
with some stuff.
You're avoiding me, right?
-No.
-I can explain.
Look, this isn't making
any sense to me, okay?
This girl,
she popped out of nowhere.
Look, what if I had a pimp
who was a friend of mine.
And he's in town for a month or so.
And he needs a place to sleep
so he's on my couch in your bathrobe.
How do you feel about that? Okay?
I mean seriously,
what would you have me think?
-I know it sounds bad....
-We have built cases for death...
-...on less than this.
-What do you want me to do?
I just want you to let this go.
I just want you to let her go back
to wherever it is she came from.
Josh, this is not our responsibility.
-Look, I gotta go.
-Okay.
-Can we finish this later?
-All right. I'll call you.
-Okay.
-All right.
-What's up, man?
-Hey, what's going on, man?
-Nothing. You....
-I don't wanna talk about it.
-We don't have to talk about it.
-Please.
I may have found a possible lead
for a brother of hers.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Thank you, man.
-It's all good, bro.
-Yeah.
-It's what I do.
You know, it's funny,
they really don't get along.
It says here that you went to college.
Yeah, I did two years.
What happened?
I ain't finished.
I see.
There are some blanks here
that you didn't fill out.
I don't know the answer.
What you want me do?
Looking at this application...
...tells me that you don't
finish anything.
So why should we hire you?
Listen, man, I just need a job.
You're gonna give me one or not?
It's really simple.
How bad do you want it?
I won't ask you to do anything
you haven't done a million times.
I've seen your record.
-What happened?
-Your Christian help ain't so Christian.
This is what your A-word get.
You're supposed to help these girls.
You know how you set her back?
Dear Jesus.
I don't know where the hell Cora is at.
I told her I need to go to the store.
People always told me
I can't be driving.
-She knows I need to go to the store.
-That child's gonna leave you to starve.
I told you,
that the way you were treating her...
...she's gonna leave you
to starve to death one day.
-And now this time--
-Shut up, bastard.
Oh, no. Hello.
-Cora.
-Yeah, hello, Madea. Yeah.
-Yes, ma'am.
Where the hell you at?
I'm still at the hair salon.
What the hell are you doing?
You've been there five hours.
Your hair ain't an inch and a half long.
What are they doing?
I'm coming. I'm just trying to--
Can I have some me time, please?
Hello? Hello?
-You need some what?
-Some me time.
Some what?
Some me time. Some time for myself.
-Cora.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Did I ever ask you for some me time?
-No, ma'am.
Did I ask you for some me time
when I had to get up...
...every four hours
and cook for you...
-...until you were 1 7 years old?
-No.
Did I ask you for some me time
when I had to hit that stripper pole...
...every night trying to bring money
into this house?
-Did I ask you for some me time then?
-No, ma'am.
Old men up there trying to make it
drizzle, they sure couldn't make it rain.
-What the hell is me time?
-I'm just taking care of myself.
-Getting some me time.
-Time for nothing.
I'm going to the store.
-I'm a grown woman. I'll go myself.
-You can't go to the store.
You're not supposed to drive.
I'll be there soon.
Who the hell are you
to tell me I can't drive.
-lf I feel like driving, I'm driving.
-You can't drive....
Shut the hell up.
You get in that car, you're going down.
I'm not playing around.
You're going down, you understand?
I'll be glad when you go down.
Down to the graveyard
and become some maggot food.
I'm hungry. What I'm supposed to do?
Just sit up in this house?
You can miss a few meals.
One or two.
Three or seven.
Nine or eleven.
Keep it up, Joe. Keep it up.
Oh, them people called.
You ain't gotta worry about no food.
You can call them,
they'll bring it down here.
What are you talking about?
Stop smoking that weed.
What the hell you talking about?
You're crazy.
They said they'd give you
three meals a day...
...and they'll give you a percentage on
the people who come through and pay.
-Where they feed you that much?
-One of the whales died.
They need another whale
at the aquarium.
Go on down there
and swim around for them.
You rusty old bastard.
You fart and dust come out. Go to hell.
Dead man walking.
Walking the green mile,
getting her out for Jesus.
I'm gonna walk the green mile
getting right for Jesus.
I don't know what you're blowing at,
but keep blowing.
Come on, grandma!
You coming--? You coming out?
Hey. You coming out?
-Move it, lady!
-I guess you ain't coming out.
I like them shoes.
Come on, come on, come on!
Here's a spot here. I got the groceries,
now I just need to get up in here.
Come on out.
I know-- Did she--?
I know damn well that you just--
Excuse me.
Lady, I know damn well you saw me
getting ready to take this spot.
I saw you.
I took it.
Why don't you move your little car
before I move it for you?
Okay, go on in the store.
Go on in the store. Just walk off. Just
walk off like you bad. You bad. Okay.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I said I was waiting for that spot, lady.
Well, it's my spot now, grandma.
Lady. Lady, look here--
Lady. Lady, let me explain some--
-You gonna follow me into the store?
-Lady, let me explain something to you.
Lord, have mercy.
She's gonna make me
tear the K and the B off of this Kmart.
I'm gonna back up.
I ought to run into her, Lord help me.
I don't wanna get in no trouble, Lord.
Help me, Jesus.
Help me, Lord. You know I'm ready
to go drive straight through this glass.
That's right. I'm gonna beat her ass.
Attention, Kmart shoppers.
We have a manager's special....
No!
Are you insane?
Didn't I tell you that was my spot...
...and you gonna jump in front of me
and take my damn parking spot?
Are you insane? Put my car down!
-Okay, I'm gonna put it down for you.
-Old woman, put my car down now!
Okay.
My husband is a police officer.
And he is on his way right now.
I ain't scared of no po-po.
Call the po-po. Call the po-po.
Honey, this woman, this Jemima
the Hutt, she ruined my car!
I'll get the hell out of here.
If he wants me...
...he better come to my house
to get me.
He will!
Get over here now!
The Kmart!
Am I forgiven?
After those flowers
and those chocolates?
-Yes.
-And that great movie that we saw?
You are definitely working on it.
That's good. Because I do not like it
when you're mad at me.
Well, I don't like being mad at you.
Oh, boy.
-Why don't we go inside and make up?
-Let's go.
Okay.
-Don't touch me.
-Candy, it's me. It's Josh.
-Josh.
-Yeah.
She's probably strung out
on something.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-You ain't gotta be sorry. All right?
-Okay, rest, rest.
-Just try to relax.
I promise. I'm trying. I'm trying.
Rest, rest.
You have never done that for me.
What are you talking about, Linda?
This.
The care that you're showing her.
You've never done that for me.
Baby, please, not tonight.
Okay?
Josh, you're in love with her.
What are you talking about?
I'm just trying to help out a friend.
I don't even know how to compete
with a drug-addicted prostitute.
Linda, there is nothing
going on with us.
I have to go right now.
I can't do this.
-I can't do this. No.
-Where are you going?
-I can't do this.
-Linda.
Please, come and lay with me, please.
Look, Candy.
I don't think that would be
a good idea, you know?
I don't mean like that.
Remember when we were little...
...and my stepdad would be trying
to get me, he knew you'd protect me.
Please, Josh, please.
Josh, please. Josh.
All right.
Okay.
It's gonna be okay.
This is the DeKalb County
SWAT Team.
Put your hands in the air
and walk backwards.
These are your Miranda rights.
You have the right to remain silent.
If you give up
the right to remain silent...
...anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney
and have an attorney present....
-Don't move!
-I ain't going down without a fight.
-What you gonna do? Come on.
-You have the right to remain--
Don't-- Put me down.
You're giving me a mammogram.
Candace.
Cand-- Candy.
Good morning.
-You scared me.
-What are you doing here so early?
I am preparing for court.
You are preparing for court, huh?
This is the...
...Candace Collin's, Sarah Lester?
Wait, hold on, hold on.
I remember this one.
This is Sarah Lester.
Yeah, Sarah-- Sarah Lester.
This case was closed
a couple years ago.
Are you padding this woman's file
with a closed case?
-Chuck, let me handle this, all right?
-You can't do that.
It's done.
So wait, wait, wait. Is this how you've
been winning all your cases, huh?
Is this how you've been
winning all your cases, Linda?
I'm not gonna stand by
and let you do this.
-I gotta--
-What?
What do you have to do?
Don't you forget
your bar exam, baby.
You remember how you cheated?
Don't try me, Chuck.
I have the proof.
And I will use it.
Why are you doing this?
I mean,
this woman has done nothing to you.
How would you know that?
He's not in love with her.
He loves you.
How deep is your commitment
to this girl, Josh?
You know, she's a friend.
A friend?
You know what a binge addict is?
No.
They could stay clean
for long periods of time.
Then something sets them off and they
can go off for days, weeks and binge.
Because this doesn't just go away
like a cold.
This is a disease that has to be cured.
And if you're in it for the wrong reasons
it's gonna destroy you so fast.
I'm gonna ask you again. How deep
is your commitment to this girl, Josh?
When we were--
We were both back in college...
...she--
I was the only person
that she knew at the school.
And I knew her
from the neighborhood.
You know, the other students,
they really used to make fun of her.
You know, like her hair
and her clothes.
I started getting embarrassed.
And they....
I started avoiding her.
When I was on the football team
we were having this, like, big party.
And...
...they told me...
...to invite Candy over, you know,
so I did.
I had a date. I really didn't wanna--
I really didn't wanna be there.
They told me that they would...
...you know, like,
keep her company while I was gone...
...and I came back that night.
And....
I came back--
I came back that night.
And I went in my room.
And...
...they raped her.
They raped her.
And I didn't do--
I didn't do nothing about it.
I didn't do nothing about it. I'm like...
...you know, I'm like-- What?
What? Candy, I'm sorry.
I never told her I'm sorry.
Josh, look at me, Josh.
You can't carry that weight.
-Why did l--? Oh, God, I had to go.
-You-- Josh...
...Iook at me.
-Josh, look at me, please.
-Yes, I get it.
-Yeah, I'm trying.
-Look at me. Look at me.
-You can't carry that weight.
-Okay.
She had problems
long before that party.
-Mabel.
-Brown.
Listen,
I'm trying to see Judge Mablean.
-Will you please be quiet.
-I'm trying to pray for you.
God don't like you.
He grew you in a Petri dish, Brown.
-I'm trying to help you.
-I don't need you to help me here.
Hey, hey, Brian, hey.
Judge Mablean
always give me a slap on the wrist.
This is not Judge Mablean.
This judge is tough.
-How tough could he be?
-All rise. The honorable...
...Judge Mathis presiding.
You may be seated. First case...
...DeKalb County
calls Mabel Simmons.
Wait a minute.
-ls that who the hell I think it is?
-Yes.
-It's all spelled out there, Your Honor.
-Yeah, I'm looking at this case.
And your record is ridiculous,
ma'am.
I don't even know
how you still on the street.
-Your Honor, the reaso--
-I'm talking.
You should have been locked up
a long time ago with this.
-Your Honor--
-Look, I speak...
...you listen.
And then I will allow you to respond,
you understand?
Yes, sir.
Don't you go there, he talking.
Y'all better get it.
-Mabel, be quiet.
-Madea.
Better be quiet.
-What do you have to say for yourself?
-Now it's my turn to talk?
You've heard the saying, "Speak when
you're spoken to or otherwise shut up."
It's time to say it.
That's how this go, huh?
I don't have time for this.
It's time for some sentencing. Bailiff,
what time you have on your watch?
Five to 1 0, judge.
Five to ten, that's your sentence.
-Have a good day.
-Oh, hell, no.
You gonna give me five years?
You ain't gonna take me back to jail--
Come here, what you gonna do?
What the hell are--?
Gonna take me out of here.
I ain't going. I ain't going.
I ain't going. I--
Linda.
-Oh, hey, baby.
-Hey.
-Thanks for letting me borrow this.
-Oh, sure.
How'd it go today?
-Seventeen years.
-What?
Seventeen years?
Baby, it was only two counts.
Sweetie, you didn't see
her New York sheet.
It is as long as my arm.
-Wow, I had no idea she--
-I know, I know.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I really tried...
...to be lenient with her.
But, you know,
once the judge saw the charges...
...and on top of that,
she didn't show up today.
You know, maybe it's for the best.
Maybe now
she can get her life together.
Maybe you're right.
So she's still at your place?
No, she left.
Maybe now, I can...
...stop being mad at you and we can
go back to planning our future?
I would like that.
Me too.
-All right.
-Okay.
Hey, sweet thing.
What you looking for?
A good time.
What's it going to cost me?
I'll give you a special, $50.
Get in.
Where are you going?
Do you wanna party?
You need a date?
Hey.
Come on.
Put your damn hands off me.
Put your hands off me.
I'm telling y'all, ain't nobody-- I ain't
scared of none of you. I ain't scared.
Yeah, keep it up. Keep it up.
I ain't scared of none of you.
I'm here, now let me go.
What the hell wrong with you?
How you doing?
Guess this is my cell.
What the hell you smiling for?
You the Martha Stewart of prison?
No.
I'm T.T.
-You're who?
-I'm T.T.
-Like two of these?
Oh, T.T. T.T., how are you doing?
I'm Mabel,
but everybody call me Madea. Hello.
I'm so happy that we're sharing a cell.
This is your bunk. I made it for you.
Oh, thank you and I appreciate it.
I ain't into that.
Because you making a bunk...
...don't mean I'm giving you nothing.
You ain't getting none of this stuff.
Put your hands on me I'll punch
that Spanish out.
You gonna be talking
straight up English.
You're so funny.
I was just being nice.
When I saw you come in, I thought:
"l hope she's in my cell."
Brownies for my brownie?
I made them myself.
"Brownies for your brownie?" You
trying to call me black or something?
Brownie.
Ain't no oven in here.
How the hell you make a brownie?
I have my ways.
No, thank you.
I saw you on TV.
That was a great chase.
How long you have here, my dear?
They tell me I got five years.
But I'm breaking
out of here first chance I get.
Can I come with you?
You seem like a nice, sweet person
The hell you in here for?
Stealing flowers? What you do?
Steal candy from Girl Scouts?
What, what?
No.
I murdered 1 8 men.
-I'm the--
-I'm sorry, you what to 1 8...?
I murder 1 8 men.
-Eighty?
-Eighteen.
One-eight men.
I'm one of the first female serial killers.
I'm going to be here till l...die.
But I'll be making you brownies,
my brownie.
Hey, which one is yours?
Oh, you can take either one.
Donna?
Candy? Oh, my God.
Candy.
-How are you doing?
-Oh, my God.
I am so glad to see you.
-I know.
-I didn't know what happened to you.
I've been trying to reach you
but you ain't got no address.
You look good.
Yeah, I'm doing good.
How are you doing?
-What?
-They gave me 1 7 years.
-For--? For what?
-Donna...
...I don't know what I'm gonna do.
No, that ain't right.
They had to trump your charges.
I don't know what happened.
I just know this ain't right.
Donna.
What am I gonna do
for 1 7 years in here?
I've been going to Ellen's services.
No, wait, wait, wait.
She teaches classes here.
You should go.
I ain't trying to be in no church.
It's not like that.
She teaches a group session.
And she is really good.
I mean, she preaches
but not like a preacher, you know.
She makes it clear
so you can understand it.
Look at me,
I've been clean all this time.
And if you take her course...
...you get time off your sentence.
You should come.
I don't know how people eat this.
This is crazy. I've seen people
on Survivor eat better food than this.
Doesn't she realize
she was running for some roaches?
You're a cute little thing.
-Get your hands off of me.
-Oh, you feisty.
-Leave her. That's my friend.
-ls anybody talking to you?
Young man.
This little lady don't wanna be
bothered, now get on up...
...go on back to where you came from.
Now, go on.
Who you think you talking to,
old lady?
You don't know me. I'm gonna
give you the benefit of the doubt.
Now, get the hell up from the table
and go on now.
Go on, go on, sir, go on.
I see nobody told you I run this prison.
I'm Big Sal and what Big Sal wants,
Big Sal gets. Get it?
I guess nobody told you
that I'm Madea.
Ma to the damn D, E, A,
you understand that?
And what I want, I get.
Do you understand me?
I'm from the west end...
...where we cut a fool first and
run like hell afterwards, understand?
You don't know me. You don't know
who the hell you talking to.
I'm gonna come across this table
and rip out your urethra tube.
I see I have to break you in.
You gonna get broke the hell in--
-We'll have our time.
-Yes, we will.
I look forward to it.
A officer and a gentleman.
Yeah, get the hell on out of here
with Alvin and the two chipmunks.
-What the hell is that?
-Thank you.
I wasn't doing nothing for you. I don't
like people messing over nobody.
I'm Terry but everybody
calls me T.T.
She say her name's T.T.
I thought she said titty too at first.
I can't understand
what the hell she's saying.
Yeah, I'm Candace.
And I'm Donna. Thank you
for sticking up for my friend.
Yeah, y'all welcome.
You have a letter.
-Why won't you talk to him?
-I ain't got nothing to say to him.
Maybe he can help figure out
why you're in here so long.
Listen, I don't wanna talk to him.
Well, obviously
that man wants to be there for you.
So why don't you let--
Why don't you just see him?
Why don't you just drop it?
Drop it. Yeah, all right.
They ain't gonna give me five years...
...Judge Mathis,
I don't care if it's Judge Judy.
You ain't gonna give me no five years.
But they did. But I've been
looking for a way to break out of here.
You folks don't know me.
I will set it all up.
Hi, sweetness.
You looking good.
I know you ain't talking to me.
She must be talking to you.
I'm ain't gonna let her
take my virginity.
-What's so funny?
-You funny.
You funny as hell
looking like Lou Ferrigno.
Old lady,
you know who you're talking to.
Yes, I do. I'm talking to you. You better
back the hell up out my face--
-Well, leave it alone.
-Go ahead on, bruh. Go ahead on.
Go ahead on.
Y'all tell him, he don't know.
So when are you coming to see me?
Young man.
Didn't this girl tell you
she don't want to be bothered?
Why the hell do you keep talking
to her? What is wrong with you?
What you gonna do?
What you...
...gonna do?
That's what I wanna know.
What you gonna do? You gonna
sit there and tell something to me.
-Would you stop it.
-Say something, say something.
-I don't hear you.
-I'll get you for this...
-...grandma.
-What's going on, big woman?
Come on, you big papa--
Come on, up in there.
Oh, yeah.
Cover up him.
What's going on in here?
We not doing nothing.
I'm just telling her how good God is.
All right, today...
...we are gonna talk about forgiveness.
Why is this so important? Yes, T.T.
Because you have to forgive
to be forgiven.
Correct.
We must forgive others
as Christ forgave us.
Last week we talked
about the first steps to forgiveness.
Anybody know?
Acknowledging what was done.
That's right.
A lot of times we don't wanna
acknowledge what we've done.
When you don't forgive somebody,
you give them power over your life.
They're sleeping at night
and you're walking around...
...remembering everything
that they've done.
You know a little bit of my testimony.
Sixteen years living on the street.
Drug addiction, prostitution.
And I did it
because I was hurting myself.
I was hurting my daddy.
I was hurting my mother.
I was hurting every man
that did anything bad to me.
Until one day, the Lord spoke to me.
And he said:
"Forgiveness
is not for the other person.
It's for you."
The longer you hold on to it...
...the longer you hold on
to the pain and the past and the hurt...
...the longer you hold yourself back
from being free.
I can't forgive my dad
for what he did to me.
-He's the reason I'm in here.
-Well, cookie, don't forgive him.
Because he's living his life,
you're in here.
Forgiveness is not for them.
It is for you.
Well, I can't forgive him.
You don't know what he did to me.
Lord, do I have to listen
to all this melodrama?
Is something wrong, Ms. Simmons?
Is there something wrong?
Sorry, reverend, doctor, bishop,
preacher lady, whatever your name is.
I don't agree with all of this.
I hear what you say about forgiveness.
You're supposed to forgive.
This child is telling
what her daddy did.
Your dad is somewhere
living his life and you're on lockdown.
You're in jail
because of what you did.
Learn how to take some responsibility
for yourself. For your own stuff.
I can't stand folks wanna be the victim.
"This person did this so I'm this way."
Everybody got a story.
Your mama and daddy
gave you life.
That's all they do. No matter
how good, how bad the life was...
...it's up to you to make something of it.
Suck it up and shut the hell up.
-But you don't know what he did.
-Let her talk.
Thank you, Biggie Smalls.
I love it when you call me
"big papa."
You're such a gentleman.
They say I come here,
I get some time off.
I'm trying to get time off. Do my time.
I don't mess with nobody.
I don't want nobody to mess with me.
People, all you up in here
need to understand something, okay?
Everybody got a life.
What you do with that life is up to you.
Stop being the victim. That's all I say.
I don't preach that stuff.
I will leave that to you.
I don't even wanna be here.
But I got to get out of here
because this is working on my damn--
This is working on my nerves.
Sorry, girls, that's what--
I can't be bothered with this. You--
Guess she told you.
I'm glad you decided
to let me come see you.
Yeah.
So how are you?
I'm making it.
-So you're getting married soon, huh?
-Yeah.
Congratulations.
Good luck with that.
I really don't know what to say.
I feel like I keep letting you down.
I've been going to Ellen.
And I've really been listening
to what she has to say.
And she says that
if you love the Lord...
...then everything is gonna work out
for good for you. Do you believe that?
Yeah. Yeah, I believe that.
I know I do because....
Josh, I gotta believe in something.
You can believe in me.
I know I wasn't there that night.
But I guarantee you
that will never happen again.
Did you know that they were gonna
do that to me that night?
No, Candy, I didn't.
Josh, I needed you.
You weren't there for me.
You weren't there. I screamed for you.
And you never came for me.
You left me there.
Candy.
You didn't protect me.
Candy, I'm sorry.
Please, forgive me.
Please.
I was so mad at you, Josh.
I was so angry for so long.
But, Josh...
...I forgive you.
I forgive you.
You gotta go on
and you gotta live your life.
And I gotta live mine.
I'm not gonna be a victim anymore.
I gotta change my life for me.
Now you go get married.
Be happy.
And I'm gonna try
to do the same thing.
I gotta go.
Have a good wedding day.
Joshua. Joshua.
Why are you not dressed?
Get the jacket on.
Linda's gonna be here, and I'm not
getting cussed out behind you.
Get your jacket on.
The mayor and the governor are there.
You gonna make them wait?
You're gonna keep working?
Look at me like I'm stupid?
-I will be out there. Thank you.
-Thank you, Josh
-Thanks a lot. Nice. Nice.
-Calm down. I got it. I got it.
-Josh, what are you doing?
-Hey.
It's your wedding,
why are you working?
-Get dressed.
-I'm getting dressed, man.
I'm getting dressed.
Yeah, you're right.
Hey.
I was looking at--
I was looking at Candy's file. And....
Something's not adding up.
The girl gets 1 7 years, right?
And the maximum
on this count is four.
Josh, I gotta tell you something.
The couple has written
their own vows.
These vows are from the heart.
And will bind them together forever.
Josh.
You are my heart and soul.
I thank God for you every day.
I promise to love you
in sickness and in health.
I promise to give myself only to you.
And I promise to be honest...
...and to love you forever and ever.
Linda...
...I will always know
that you are a wonderful woman.
But you are a conniving...
...and a manipulating human being...
...and you disgust me.
Joshua.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This beautiful insecure woman...
...that I refuse to marry...
...she padded charges
on a case that she handled...
...sending somebody to jail
for time that they did not deserve.
Thank you.
-What are you doing here? You're--
-Hey, Candy, Candy. Come here.
Come here.
No touching.
Shut up, man.
What are you doing?
I gotta get you out of here, okay?
I gotta get you out. Gotta take
you home. You understand me?
-What are you talking about?
-I'm gonna get you out.
Linda is the last person in my life
that I'm gonna let hurt you.
I'm gonna be here for you.
I'll help you kick that crap
in the streets and all the other stuff...
...if it takes every breath in my body.
Understand?
I love you.
No touching.
The heck with it.
It's a public issue because justice
is for everyone. God bless you.
You're on with Frank and Wanda.
When I was reviewing
Candace Washington's file...
...I discovered Linda Davis
tried both women--
Judges who presided
over each case gave--
The goal of the district attorney's
office is to see that...
... these seven unjustly imprisoned
women be released immediately...
...and be reunited
with their loved ones.
And it's the T om Joyner Morning Show.
This morning I am outraged.
I am outraged about this prosecutor
that has got Madea in there.
This story is so unbelievable to me.
Reverend Al Sharpton. We're back.
I wanna talk about this hotshot
district attorney...
...that's trying to build up a career...
-...trumping up charges.
-Michael Baisden.
First, the Jena Six, now the Georgia
Seven, which includes Madea.
An elderly woman sentenced
for five years for a victimless crime.
-Know how we do it--
-Seventeen minutes after the hour.
Welcome back to the ride.
Steve Harvey Morning Show.
Call us because Madea
deserves to be freed.
And march down to the DA 's office
and get this accomplished.
We are back now.
Mabel Simmons, also known
to the general population as Madea...
...has been arrested and there's been
yet another "Free Madea" rally.
Now, come on.
Okay, she carries a gun. Like carrying.
But she has to carry a gun.
She's a vulnerable older black woman.
Madea is not vulnerable.
That's how I see it.
We have a right to carry our guns.
It's in our constitution.
She bares all those arms. She got
guns, she's just cutting people down.
And she was not the only one.
You put six, seven women in jail
with these kind of sentences.
Is this the kind of justice
we're looking for?
We have a news alert.
I'm in front
of the Georgia State Courthouse...
... where Assistant District Attorney
Linda Davis...
... was indicted today
by a grand jury.
The charges include fraud, tampering,
and providing false documents.
I wish that chick had tried my case.
At some point maybe today...
...maybe tomorrow,
but at some point soon...
...Linda Davis will have
to turn herself in to the authorities...
...and she will be
officially processed.
What does that mean?
That means she will be
fingerprinted...
...and at some point she will stand
against the wall of shame...
...and have her mugshot taken.
What a fall from grace
for Linda Davis.
Hey, turn the TV on.
We sitting looking at that.
What's wrong with you?
Bernice Davis...
...Ida Mae Jones...
...Takeda Matthews...
...Andrea Thomas...
...Candace Collins...
...Mabel Simmons...
...and Elizabeth Bryant.
There's been an investigation
in the DA's office...
...that has led
to the overturning of your convictions.
Get your things. You're going home.
What?
Group hug.
Do you feel justice was served?
Yeah, justice is served.
You know, justice with--
Brian knows about the justice.
I just think that we all are really happy
that justice has been overturned.
And you know what? I'm gonna go
buy her a white dress with a white hat.
White ruffle pants, white ruffle socks
and shoes. Going to Church this time.
The person to ask is Madea.
Here she comes now.
Soldier boy.
I've nothing to say.
It's just been really tough
being up in that prison.
They did all this stuff to try to get me
down but do-- You can't keep me down.
Praise the Lord. God bless you.
Hallelujah.
They tell me you're the best.
Well, look, I don't usually do this.
I mean, you need to know that.
I don't usually see people individually.
I saw the videotape of you
getting arrested and I thought...
...I've got to see this woman.
-You can't think what you did was okay.
-You don't know what happened.
What do you mean? I saw it on tape.
I saw you forklift the lady's car...
-...out of a parking space.
-You're talking about that time.
I ain't know what you talking about.
Oh, they had that on video too?
Know what, that woman just--
I've been riding by that parking lot...
...my air conditioner don't work
in my Cadillac, that '78 Cadillac.
And I was driving around
and could not get a parking spot.
There she was, zoomed in there,
knew I was waiting for that spot.
-What else was I supposed to do?
-Well, you go on to another space.
Do you have to be in control
all the time?
No, I don't have to be in control.
That was my parking spot.
I wasn't going to another space.
That was the closest to the door.
That's the one I want.
Other people want stuff too.
It's not just about you.
It's not just about you all the time.
In my world, it's about me.
This is Madea's world.
It's about me, Dr. Phil.
Do you get angry
when you feel out of control?
I'm never angry. I keep telling people
I am not angry, okay?
Somebody do something to me,
I do something.
You don't bother me,
I don't bother you.
You weren't angry when you
flipped over this car?
I was calm and cool as a cucumber.
-I was sitting there smoking a cigarette.
-Are you crazy?
A little bit.
-I got a question for you.
-I got a question too.
-What about your childhood?
Talking about my childhood
is not gonna help your anger.
I keep saying I'm not angry.
-But you keep insisting I am.
-Are you happy to be talking to me?
I would much rather be at the casino
playing blackjack or something.
But they told me I have to see you.
-So I'm here.
-Why?
Because the court made me.
You forklift a woman's car
out of the parking lot.
Does that seem reasonable to you?
She took the parking spot.
-lt isn't your parking spot.
-Yes, it was.
Did it have your name on it?
It had handicap.
That matches what I had in my car.
She took it with her little convertible
so I lifted it, flipped it.
Well, yeah, I believe
the handicapped part. I got that.
What are you trying to say?
Something's wrong with me?
Did you see me walk in here? I'm fine.
What are you doing
in the handicapped space?
Because it was closer to the door.
What?
It's closer to the door.
They always leave the handicap
close to the door.
That's why I take it.
Do you feel
like you always have to get even?
-Hell, yeah.
-Why do you always have to get even?
Why can't you just let it roll off
like water off a duck's back?
Because I ain't no damn duck.
You don't have to attack people.
Somebody do something to you,
you do something to you.
The Bible said in second Deutoronomo,
the book of Jericho that:
"The eye for a tooth,
a tooth for the people.
If everybody got the eye,
punch them in it."
-What?
-I can tell you don't read the Bible.
Bible say, "Turn the other cheek."
Somebody hit that cheek,
turn the other. You have two cheeks.
How many you gonna let them hit
before you whup their ass?
I don't think
you have to whup their ass.
It ain't about ass-whupping.
You don't open up a can of whupass
on everybody that you meet.
-You go with the flow.
-What do you mean?
Letting people walk over you
like a doormat?
No. I've been in this life too long to
let some people just walk all over me.
-I'm not gonna do that.
-But it's easy for you to get bothered.
It doesn't take a whole lot
for you to get bothered.
"No, it doesn't."
"Yes, it does."
"l beg to differ."
-Do you sleep well at night?
Okay, let's try not to answer a question
with a question, okay?
If you stop asking questions
I'll stop answering with a question.
-Can you stop?
Okay, all right. Look, look.
Are you getting angry, doctor?
Yeah, I'm getting angry.
-Answer the question.
-Answer what question?
This isn't working. This isn't helping.
I told the judge
I didn't need to come here.
-But you're here.
-Yes, I am here.
-You're not making any sense.
Do you talk to people
like this all the time?
What? What are they gonna do?
I'm 6-foot-5,
what the hell are they gonna do?
Yes, I say what's on my mind.
Ain't nobody gonna run over me.
I'll say what's on my mind.
Well, what's on your mind?
What's on your mind?
Okay, wh--? Is there--?
What are you, a parrot?
Is there an echo in here?
There's not a parrot, not an echo.
None of those things are in here.
I'm talking. They told me to see you.
You're supposed to help me.
I keep telling I'm not angry.
-You're not angry?
-No, I'm not angry.
I don't know how many times I have
to tell you I'm not angry, Dr. Phil.
-How can you tell if you're angry?
-I could tell if I'm angry, if I'm angry.
-lf I was angry I would know I'm angry.
-You don't think you're angry now?
-No.
-You're yelling, you're screaming.
-You're yelling.
-You're driving me crazy.
But you're the doctor.
You're supposed to handle this hell.
You're a psychologist.
You've studied with the best.
You been all over the world
learning about people.
-And you let a little woman upset you.
-They never told me about you.
I missed that class,
I can tell you for sure.
I missed the class
where they went over Madea.
-Right. Madea 1 01, baby. You learn it.
-Yeah.
All right, look. We're getting nowhere.
That's enough.
-Okay.
-Enough, I've had it.
That's enough. We're out of here.
You're fired.
Great. Thank you, Dr. Phil Trump.
-Can we go now? Is it over?
-It's over, yes. You can leave. Please.
Please tell the judge we had this
session and it was the best one.
I'm gonna tell the judge
that you would have to get better...
...to be crazy.
How the hell do you get better--?
-Well, I guess that's it then.
-I guess that's it, you can leave.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org