I can help with the fishing nets.
No, we can take care of it.
Perhaps when you're older...
Good day. I was wondering,
could I work here?
That's not possible.
You're too young.
I'm good at cooking,
I always help my grandma at home.
- It's not possible... Go away.
- I'm a fast learner.
- Good afternoon.
- Good afternoon to you.
I'm just wondering
if there's work for me here.
See this sack of rice...
It must be emptied.
Put this plastic bag on the scale.
You're going to repack the rice.
Each plastic bag should weigh 1 kilo.
Put the rice in the plastic bag,
like this.
Just make sure the scale needle
doesn't go past number one.
It doesn't matter if it goes
under the line, but not over.
Mother, I can't do this any longer.
Glorla, I know you can do lt.
You're strong.
I feel like my chest will explode.
Mother, I'll never get used
to this. Not ever!
This is not what God wants.
You feel that way now,
but I belleve It's God's wlll-
- that you glve your chlldren
a better future.
No, mother!
God wants me to be with my children.
Can you understand that?
- I want to come home.
- No...
I miss my children.
Be strong my chlld,
you can do lt.
Try to be strong.
I know you can do lt.
I'm done now.
- Are you finished?
- Yes.
- Is the sack empty?
Let me see.
You're a really good boy.
Wait, I'll go inside.
I have a reward for you.
Here you are...
Some candy and mango juice.
- That's your favourite, isn't it?
- Yes, thank you.
You're a really nice boy,
a hard working boy.
You like that, don't you?
I just wanted to ask how...
What?
- How much will you pay me?
- Pay you?
- I'm not giving you any money.
- But you must pay me.
- I did all of this.
- Did you help me for money?
Get out of here. Shame on you!
Are you trying to trick me?
Go on, leave! Shame on you!
I'm not that easily fooled!
- And no sex?
- No.
- Nothing?
- Where is he from?
- America.
I love Americans.
I hate them,
but this one was different.
- You hate Americans?
- Why?
They think they're so good in bed.
The Italians are worse.
Yes, they think they're so good,
they shouldn't have to pay.
- But the Germans are the worst.
- The Germans? They're OK.
They're dirty.
No, not all of them.
But the Arabs...
The Arabs are the worst of all.
- I wouldn't go with them.
- Nobody would. They stink.
How about the Japanese?
I wouldn't go with them.
No way, not with a Jap...
I hate the Japanese.
You wouldn't because their dicks
are the size of my little finger.
My little finger, not yours.
I'm going to look for him tomorrow.
I know where he lives.
Time to get up!
We're going somewhere today.
Hurry up and get dressed.
Wake up!
- But I have school today.
- You're not going to school.
I'll be your teacher today.
This is yours...
...and this is yours.
Tell your brother's teacher
he's home sick today.
So you've worked
for that old miserly cheat!
Rita told me everything.
- I take good care of you, don't I?
- Yes, grandmother.
So why do you keep calling
your mother to complain?
Do you know where we're going?
Let's go.
Look at them.
This is what they do every day.
Look at those kids.
Is this the kind of life you want?
Look, he's only your age
and he's already collecting garbage.
- Here's some bread, eat it!
- I don't want it.
Why not?
You haven't eaten anything today.
Go on, eat it!
Do you know why your mother
is working in America?
So you won't have to eat this bread.
So that you can have a good life.
A good life, proper food, nice house.
A good education.
Money, so when you get sick
you can go to the doctor.
Those kids can't go to the doctor.
When they get sick, they just die.
They just die.
Are you enjoying your ice cream?
We should pity those people
who live in the dumpsite.
No one should have to live
in a place like that.
You know, there's something worse
happening here at night.
Kids come here to sell themselves.
- Sell themselves?
- They sell themselves to tourists.
They buy kids and take
them to their hotels.
Why are they taking the kids
to their hotels?
I don't know, they just want
someone to sleep with.
Do they get paid?
What else do they do?
Let's not talk about it.
They just sleep, nothing else.
They don't do anything,
they just sleep there.
Just eat your ice cream.
Hey, that's my bike.
What are you doing with it?
- It's mine now.
- It's not yours, it's ours.
Your slippers... take them off.
- Take off your clothes.
- Do you have any money?
You're new around here,
don't be a show off!
Hey, go away!
Wake up!
It's time to eat soon.
- Have you seen your brother?
- No.
- Have you seen Salvador?
It's very early and he's not here.
I wonder where he is.
He's probably just hanging
out with the neighbours.
- Are you sure you haven't seen him?
- Yes.
- Have you seen Badong?
- No, I haven't.
He's not in his room
and his bike is missing.
Big brother!
- Miss, have you seen Badong?
- No, I haven't.
OK. Thank you.
There's a child here!
He's bleeding. Help me!
Check his pulse.
Call an ambulance.
Hurry up!
Where is he?
He's still breathing.
Help me carry him.
We need a tricycle!
Hello...
Gloria, is that you?
My dear daughter,
I don't know how to say this...
...but something's happened
to Salvador.
- This is a very nice pen.
- I'm not really interested in pens.
I'll give you 25 dollars for all
of these, you'll get less elsewhere.
- Only 25 dollars?
- 25, max.
I can't give you more.
This one's a copy.
Okay, I'll give you 30.
That's my last offer. Agreed?
I'm here now, my son.
I will never leave you again.
Never ever.
How are you, my sweet one?
Are you not asleep yet?
I miss you. Do you miss me?
I'll be comlng to see you soon.
I promise to come and see you.
Are you falling asleep?
Do you want me to sing you a lullaby?
Close your eyes
And have a sweet dream,
my dear child
I'll be here to protect you
and to watch over you