Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
# I know a place, mmm #
# Ain't nobody crying #
# Ain't nobody worrying,
no no #
# Ain't no smiling faces #
# Lying to the races,
yeah, hey, yeah #
- # So if you want to go, I'll... #
- # I'll take you there #
- # Yeah, hey, if you want to go, I will... #
# If you want to go,
take my hand #
- # I will... #
- # I'll take you there #
# Ooh, said I'm gonna, I will... #
# I'll take you there #
- # Help me, I will, I will... #
- # I'll take you there #
# Yeah, play on #
# Feels good to me,
it feels good to me #
- # Yeah #
- # I'll take you there #
# I will, mmm #
- # If you want to go, I'll take you there #
- # I'll take you there #
# I'll take you there #
- # Whoo #
# I said it sure
feels good to me... #
Hurry up. Come on.
Mmm.
- Morning, Miss Mildred.
- Girl, you got my money?
I get paid today. I'll have it
for you when I pick her up.
Bye, baby.
Mommy loves you.
- All right.
- Here you go.
Don't you see me
trying to get to work?
Harry, these ain't
nothing but bills.
Just put 'em in the box
next time.
Come on,
come on, come on.
All right.
Have a good one.
- Bye, baby.
- Bye, Mama.
Cheryl, please don't do this to me.
Please don't do this. Please.
Henry, you know we ride
this bus every day.
- She is coming!
- Tell her come on.
Tell her come on.
Tell her come on!
You know what?
I'm moving the bus.
- And I'll sue you and this bus company.
- Calm down.
- You ain't suing nobody.
- You're not going anywhere!
- Your donuts can wait!
- Don't you worry about my donuts.
I'ma drive off.
Get out of the door.
- She can't be late for work.
- We all gonna be late for work.
And you shut up!
I don't know you.
Cheryl, will you stop talking
to the patrons like that?
Get out of the door.
Don't you be cussing at me.
Tell her to come on.
I'ma lose my job!
- She's coming!
- Tell her come on.
Oh! Thanks, Henry.
You're the best.
You have something to say?
Mm-hmm.
That's what I thought.
Oh. Oh, God.
Sorry. The kids were
running... running late.
I was not gonna
let him leave without you.
Good looking out. You know
I can't afford to get docked.
- What's all that?
- Bills.
Brenda, has Michael given you
any money for your son?
Don't ask. Oh, speaking of...
can you loan me $100?
I've got to give
Miss Mildred something.
She won't keep Lena
for me next week.
Come on. I know.
Okay, let me look at my bills
and I'll let you know.
- Thank you.
- I may be able to give you a joint loan.
- What is a joint loan?
- A loan from my joint money.
Girl. You know what?
You insane.
You know you ain't supposed
to be smoking that stuff
- with your condition.
- Whatever.
- What's that?
- It says my daddy died.
No. Your daddy died?
It says the funeral
is on Saturday.
Ay, Brenda, I'm sorry.
- I never met the man.
- Ah.
And what is this here?
Three bus tickets to Georgia.
- Are you going?
- I don't know these people.
They know you. How else would they
know where to send the tickets?
Yeah, but there's four of us, huh?
But that's a good question.
And read this...
there is a will.
Oh my God, what if
he was superrich
and left you millions
and millions of dollars?
Right. I doubt that.
We never talked about him.
You know, since she used
to do anything for money,
if he was, believe me,
she'd have still been with him.
I think you should go.
You never know, mami.
- You never know.
- Girl.
I ain't going to no Georgia.
What the hell?
What's going on?
Excuse us.
- Coming through.
- Excuse me.
Excuse me, ma'am.
What's going on, girl?
- Look.
- What happened?
They shut the place down, Cheryl.
They said they moved
the plant to Mexico.
- Hurry!
- And they didn't tell us!
- Move move!
- Go go! Come on!
Wait! We were supposed
to get paid today!
- I've got to pay my light bill today.
- Who has a match?!
I'm going to burn this place down!
Who has a match?!
Don't give this fool
no match. She bipolar.
No, seriously. She gotta take
medication just to stay right.
I know one of you have a match!
You smoke, Georgia!
Give me a match.
Give it to me.
Cheryl, put that out.
Come on, I'm trying
to chill out.
You know with your
chemical imbalance
you're not supposed
to do drugs.
- Did you take your medicine?
- I was trying to,
but then you started talking
about "put that out."
All right. I'm just
looking out for you.
I'm fine. I just can't believe they
would do something like that.
- Hello, ladies.
- Oh, hi, Miss Mildred.
- How you doing?
- Hi, Mildred.
Miss Mildred to you.
- Girl, you got my money?
- We lost our job today, Miss Mildred.
Now I'm running a daycare,
not a welfare.
You're running an illegal daycare,
so relax.
Little girl, you don't know nothing
about my business.
This is the last day.
I'm not keeping your daughter
another minute.
I'll come get her.
She's taking a nap now.
That's the trouble
with you young mothers...
only think about yourselves.
You just said
come get her.
And I meant it...
after she wakes up and eats.
- Okay.
- The child is sleeping.
Thank you,
Miss Mildred!
- She's crazy.
- Naw, she's all right.
Shoot. I don't know what
I'm gonna do now though.
- She don't play with her money.
- Yeah, me neither.
If I had known they were going
to close down the plant,
I would have beat
my supervisors up yesterday.
Well, what you gonna do?
Shoot, I'm barely
getting by as it was.
What you have to do is
go and file child support
on that Michael.
- Hm-mmm.
- You know that Jenny got
$8,000 in back child support.
They'll get it for you
and they'll kick his ass.
8,000? Shoot.
No, he'd kill me.
Mamacita,
you go talk to him.
Let me know if you need me
and my nine to pay him a little visit.
All right.
# Troubled little angel #
# Inconsistent, flying blind
most of the time #
# Drama queen... #
# Preening and untangling #
# Feathers in her wings #
# Captured by her dreams... #
- Good morning, Mama.
- Hey, sweetheart.
# Needy little baby... #
# Open up your heart... #
Are you crying, Mama?
No no, I'm fine.
We're gonna be
all right, Ma.
We've been here before,
and don't we always make it?
- Yeah, we do.
- Yeah.
Let me cook this for you.
Relax.
Uh-oh.
Here you go, Mama.
It's one of them
old songs. Come on.
- Dance with me.
- Michael. Michael.
- No, baby.
- It's your song. You'll feel better.
- Come on, dance with me.
- Michael.
Come on.
Do I have to listen to this?
Yes, and you're
gonna like it.
# You make me happy... #
All we got to eat
is oatmeal?
Yes, and you're gonna
like that too.
Baby, this is for you.
You eat that, all right?
Mama, huh-uh.
I got honeys at school
that'll give me breakfast.
Michael, I want you to eat this.
Come on now. What would
I do without you, hmm?
Hey hey, man, come on.
- Please, don't do that.
- I'm sorry.
Come on, have a heart...
for my baby.
- Lady, I'm doing what they tell me.
- I called!
- I told them I needed a couple days!
- I'm sorry.
Come on, man.
Come on.
Go up, go up!
- Yes!
- There you go!
- Defense! Defense!
- Right here!
Defense! Defense!
Time out! Time out!
Time out.
Come on!
Go go go!
You the man!
Get up!
Whoo!
That's what
I'm talking about.
What'd I say?
Good job, my Mikey.
- Goodbye, everybody. See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
Ma, you see me score?
Whoo! I saw ya!
Saw those shoes too.
Now don't worry
about that, Ma.
I told the guys on the team
that they're my lucky shoes.
I didn't know you
were coming.
- Thought you had to work.
- Yeah, I did too.
- I lost my job.
- What?
- Oh my gosh!
- We're gonna be all right.
- Don't worry.
- My teacher can help me get a job.
- No. Hm-mmm.
- But, Mama, you've gotta let me help.
No, you're staying
in school, all right?
But I can work
and go to school, Ma.
Listen, baby, I thought
the same thing. Huh?
I end up having
to drop out of school,
working a bunch of dead-end jobs
just to make ends meet.
I don't want you working.
Now you just... you just
concentrate on them books
and... and playing ball.
I'm gonna make it work.
Are you sure?
Hey.
One thing a black woman
know how to do...
that's make it. Hmm?
- Yo, what's up, Mike?
- Hey, what's up, Cal?
Chilling.
Good game tonight though.
Thanks. Nice whip, man.
I appreciate it, man.
I just bought this.
It's my baby.
How you doing, Miss Brown?
- Hey.
- Hey, we're going to kick it tonight,
celebrate a little bit.
You want to roll with us?
No, man. I've gotta walk
my mom and my sisters home.
I can give y'all a ride.
You want a ride?
- No.
- Okay.
- Hey, Cal.
- Yes, ma'am?
- Who's car is that?
- It's mine. I just bought this.
Calvin, where you working?
Hmm? Huh?
You know your mama'd turn over
in her grave if she knew, don't you?
All right all right,
I'll holler, man.
- All right, man. You be easy.
- Come on, Ma.
Bye, Miss Brown.
I don't want you hanging with them boys.
I don't even want you talking to 'em.
But, Ma, you know me and Calvin
been hanging since the third grade.
Yeah, well, he done changed.
and I don't want you
with him, all right?
- But, Ma, Calvin's cool.
- Look, do you think I'm crazy?
- Huh? Do you?
- No.
Now I know them boys
is in the dope game.
I don't want you with them.
Do you hear me?
- Do you?
- Yes, ma'am.
All right.
Come on, y'all.
Come on.
- Hey. Mike?
- Yeah.
I'm Harry Belton. Your coach wanted me
to fly up here and see you play.
You're pretty good.
You've got a lot of potential.
Potential?
That's what you call it?
Who is this?
Who are you?
I'm Harry. Mike's coach wanted me
to see your brother play.
We run a camp in the summer
for high-school players.
Are your parents around? I'd like
to talk to them about Mike attending.
- I'm his mama.
- Nice try though.
Oh. Uh, Mrs. Brown...
- Miss.
- Miss Brown,
can I take you to lunch
so we can talk about Mike?
What? No. Look, mister,
I don't know where you're from,
but what his coach
should've told you
is that I don't want Mike to even
think about basketball until after
he gets into college, which, judging by
his grades, might not even happen.
I agree. Grades are important,
especially the way Mike plays.
Whoa whoa, what's that
supposed to mean?
It means you're talented,
but talent's not enough.
You need the right attitude
plus skill.
Look, man.
Hold on, I got skills.
Watch your mouth.
You know what?
The reason that coach sent
you over here by yourself
is 'cause he knows
he don't do nothing
but tell these boys in this neighborhood
that they can make it to the pros.
And when they end up
with their hearts broken
they walk around here
mad at the world.
That ain't happening
to my son, okay?
So you're gonna
have to excuse me.
I've got too much on my mind
to deal with this.
Come on, Michael.
Come on.
Potential? Huh.
Girl, you got my money?
No, but I was just wondering
if you could keep her
for just a few hours
while I try and go get it?
Girl, do you think
I'm crazy?
Now you got to pay your money
like all the other mothers in here.
Okay. Thank you.
- Come on.
- Come on in here.
- You hungry?
- No, ma'am.
Yes, you are. Quit lying.
When you bring that baby,
oh, she be starving,
so I know you must be too.
Here, eat that.
I don't know what's the matter
with you young girls
having all these babies
you know you can't take care of.
Look, I don't need no lecture from you.
I know what I've done.
They're here now,
they're my responsibility.
You know what?
Lena, come on. Let's go.
Oh, sit down, girly.
I'm just talking to you.
Eat and settle down.
Eat.
- You're a good mother.
- Huh!
I've got enough bad ones running
through here to know that.
Now what is
going on with you?
I don't know.
Somehow I always managed
to make it through,
but now it's just
getting harder and harder.
It ain't somehow,
it's the Lord.
And all that means is you're getting
close to a breakthrough.
Till then you just keep praying.
I pray.
I try to pray
and I try to live right,
but where's it getting me?
Look at me.
If you had seen the look
on my babies' faces
when that man turned
my lights off...
Now you listen to me.
Don't you ever get tired
of doing the right thing,
'cause in the end,
that's what pays off.
You're the best mother
I have seen,
that's why I'm gonna
keep that baby.
Oh.
I wouldn't do that
for these other ones here.
At least they can afford
to pay you, Miss Mildred.
Huh! Honey, I don't
want to know half
of what they're doing
to get that money.
Go on now.
Take that with you.
Thank you,
just a couple of hours.
I swear.
Thank you, Miss Mildred.
All right.
Hold it. Ladies, ladies,
you can't be here.
This is a hard-hat area.
Oh. Hi, I'm looking
for Michael Rose.
- Is he here?
- Who's asking?
- Brenda.
- Well, he's busy.
Man, look here.
You'd better go find him.
I'm his baby mama,
and if I don't find him,
you are going to regret it.
- I don't see him, anyway.
- Go take care of this, all right?
Wait wait wait wait wait.
All right, all right.
I'm sorry, man.
Brenda, what are
you doing here?
I've been calling you.
You haven't returned my calls.
You know, this job
pays me $25 an hour.
I'm busy.
What do you want?
I lost my job, Michael.
- I ain't got no money.
- Michael...
I've been raising
your son by myself
and in 17 years I ain't never
asked you for nothing.
You know, now I just need
a little help.
- I ain't got no money.
- Well, you'd better go find some,
'cause your kids
are hungry, you fool.
- Who the hell is she?
- My name is Child Welfare,
and I'm gonna lock you up.
- Are you threatening me?
- Oh, yeah. What, you don't know
when someone is
threatening you, huh?
Mike... Michael, look.
They turned my lights off,
all right?
Your son, he needs some...
some clothes.
- I told you.
- Could you...
could you just give me
some money for food?
I'll tell you what... y'all need
to take your asses on
and don't you come
to my job no more.
Huh! Heh.
Come on.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
I'll be right there.
- Cheryl.
- You all right?
- Run. Run!
- Oh my God!
I can't go anywhere
with you, Cheryl!
- You could've hit him in the head.
- So? He deserved it!
- You're going to jail.
- Ay, I don't care.
I've been there, mamacita.
Ai, we need money.
You need money.
I'm gonna rob a bank.
Come on, be serious.
Cheryl, why are
you so crazy?
Because it's fun,
because I like it.
You know what? I've been thinking
a lot about your father.
I think you really should
go down there to Georgia.
- What if he left you something?
- No, Cheryl.
Come on. Why not?
Because I'm tired of getting my hopes up
for things that don't happen.
So what? You have nothing
to lose right now.
Come on, there's the bus.
Watch your step.
Watch your step there.
All right,
have a good day now.
This is country.
You can say that again.
Looks like we gonna
see slaves at any minute.
She look like she about
to fight somebody.
Uh, excuse me,
you must be Brenda.
I told you.
It's Chicken George.
- Yeah.
- I knowed it! I knowed...
I said to myself...
I said, "Self."
Myself said, "Hmm?"
I said, "That's Brenda.
That's got to be her." All these peoples,
I picked you out...
looked you in the face.
Girl, I'm Leroy Brown.
- Hi.
- My friends call me Leroy Brown.
- You can just call me...
- Leroy Brown?
Yeah yeah,
how'd you know?
- This is my daughter Cora.
- Hello, nice to meet you.
- This is my baby.
- Nice to meet you too.
Oh, look at you!
Hey, who are you?
Mommy, I like the clown.
He looks like a flag.
- Yeah.
- Leroy Brown?
You, um... you must be L.B.
Oh no, that's my brother
Larry Brown.
They just call him...
they call him L.B.
Mm-hmm. That's my oldest brother
on my daddy's side.
He told me to come
by here and get y'all.
Yeah. Y'all ready to go?
- Yeah, we're ready.
- Grab your stuff. Let's go.
Oh, I'm glad
y'all made it safely.
Come on. You need
some help with that?
I'll get it. I'll get it.
Here, Cora, hold that.
My back is messed up.
Y'all be careful now.
L.B., he was gonna come to get y'all,
but he had to go somewhere.
He had to go to Bingo,
I think. You see...
Ooh, Lord.
If y'all feel some jerking,
that's my transmission.
It just "snips" sometimes.
I got it fixed at church
the other day. Yeah.
- So how was your ride?
- Oh, it was fine.
- Yes, thank you.
- When my... L.B. told me
I needed to come get you,
he said you's a friend of the family.
I said I'm gonna go get her,
'cause she's a friend of him,
he's a friend of mine.
That's all right.
So where you from?
- Um, Chicago.
- Chicago.
Chicago! That's where them big
buildings is, ain't it?
Yeah, they got
a lot of big buildings.
- Ain't that where that S... Serus Tower?
- The Sears Tower.
Yeah, my daddy...
my daddy just loved it there.
He had a... he was there
and everything. I miss my daddy.
It's going to be
all right, Mr. Brown.
I just can't take it.
Lord, take the wheel.
I want you to look
at the road, Mr. Brown!
Get the wheel!
- Chicago's a nice town.
- Yeah, I like it.
- Mm-hmm.
- See, she likes it.
- I couldn't live there.
- Would you look at the road?
Huh-uh, gimme the South.
Yes, I like the trees of the South.
I don't like it. There's too much
smog and stuff there.
- Yeah?
- My daddy liked it though.
- It's okay, Mr. Brown.
- He was always in Chicago.
It's all right. I want you
to watch the road.
Oh wait, now watch the road!
He just taught me so much.
He taught me how
to dance and swim.
I miss him.
- Now this is when he was a young boy.
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, he was so handsome.
Now over here...
- this is when he married.
- That's my mama.
Oh, wow.
So how you know our daddy?
- Well, my mama...
- Where is everybody? Oh!
- Here we go.
- Y'all Daddy go.
Oh, Lord, help me.
Help me.
Vera, will you get somewhere
and sit down without all that drama?
Go on, y'all, daddy dead!
Vera, get ahold
of yourself now.
Oh, Lord, oh, Lord, I just don't know
what I'm gonna do, y'all.
I can't sleep.
I can't eat.
- You want some cake?
- Oh, yes, cake would help.
That would definitely help me.
Got any rum in that?
I don't know. Here you go.
Oh Lord, who's this big
yellow woman blinding me?
Good Lord, eclipse.
Eclipse!
- This is my daughter Cora.
- Your daughter?!
Brown, I didn't know
your soldiers marched.
Yeah, you remember in school
and you had on them tight pants,
you had a pencil stuck in the pocket?
And then he fell.
- Instant vasectomy.
- D'oh!
That ain't funny.
I got lead poisoning...
on my privacy.
- Good one.
- You do look a little familiar.
- Who's your mama?
- Oh, um... Madea.
Madea!
- Brown, that's just nasty.
- Oh, you don't know my mother.
You gonna roll up on me?
Hell to the no!
I got my purse.
I got something for you.
- Bring it!
- Don't go gospel gangster on her, baby.
Just relax.
That's your Aunt Vera.
What? Ain't no auntie of mine
acting like that.
- She drinks and smokes.
- Sit down.
- You can't tell me to calm.
- Please excuse my mother.
- Oh, this is your cousin Will.
- He a doctor... a "gonorrheacologist."
- Oh!
- A gynecologist.
- Oh, okay. Nice to meet you.
Same thing.
Brown, I want to know
what these strangers
are doing here
during our time of bereavement.
- Vera, don't be so mean!
- How are y'all doing? I'm Will.
- Vera's son.
- Hello.
Who are you?
Now wait... hey hey hey!
Hey, Brown,
this your daughter too?
I'm Brenda
and this is Michael,
Lena and Tosha.
Brenda came down
for the funeral.
- Where'd she come from?
- Chicago.
Daddy! Daddy!
- Okay, Ma.
- My daddy lived in Chicago long ago.
Help me, Jesus!
Come on, y'all. I'm gonna show you
where you're gonna sleep.
- Oh, thank you.
- Just go on up the stairs
- and turn to your left.
- See you later.
- Good night.
- Mm-hmm.
And, Vera, you all can sleep
in Pop Brown's old room.
Oh, now I ain't sleeping in some room
some dead man died in.
I've been sleeping
with a dead man for years.
- Hey!
- You following us or something?
No. It's my hometown.
I live here.
- What are you doing here?
- Minding my business.
Oh yes, that's Harry.
Yo, hey, Harry!
- Hey, Mr. Brown.
- You doing all right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah yeah yeah.
Sorry to hear
about your daddy.
Oh, it's okay. People's dying
that ain't never died before.
Yeah, he's in a better place now.
Mm-hmm, he gone to heaven.
What's up, Harry?
How you doing, man?
- Big Will!
- Long time no see.
- I know.
- Thanks for coming. What's going on?
Just came by to pay
my condolences.
Oh, you ain't got to pay
for nothing.
We got $25,
everything is covered.
Yeah, Daddy left a big insurance
policy for that much.
Hey, Mike, I was watching you
from upstairs.
- You're pretty good.
- Oh, thanks.
He just needs
to watch his elbow.
Who are you to be
giving me advice?
Mike, this is Harry Belton...
high-school all-American,
college standout.
And a pretty good professional player
until he retired.
- I ain't never heard of him.
- You ain't never heard of him?
Where you been? All you know is that
young boy "Lebanon" James, ain't it?
Gimme the basketball,
I'm gonna show you... whoa!
- That's nice, Uncle Brown.
- You done scratched my suit.
Harry's a high-school coach
here now and college recruiter
and does camps and develops
talent over the summer, right?
- Yep.
- Oh, the coach of Hillbilly High, huh?
Oooh, you're so "disrespected."
And arrogant.
We've got some
talented kids like you.
But they listen, so that would
make 'em better than you.
Please.
Oooh, you arrogant.
- Still got it.
- "Squish"!
- "Squish."
- One on one.
- Do it.
- All right.
You got some money?
I don't gamble.
Me neither. I'm safe.
I'ma... I got knicks.
I'm gonna change into my good clothes.
You don't know nothing about basketball.
Check it out.
Come on.
Whoo, I'm just coming in here
to keep y'all company.
Don't ask me to cook nothing.
Last time I was in the kitchen
I burned myself
and cut myself.
Child, slow down.
Dinner gonna be in a while.
Vera, don't start.
- Your mama don't feed you?
- Sometimes we don't have enough to eat.
- Really?
- Well, you just eat all you want here.
You hear?
We got plenty.
That's right.
Miss Sarah's a great cook.
Look like you been
eating here for years.
Oh look, you don't know me.
- You gonna make me go in my purse.
- Do it.
- Don't hurt me, baby.
- You want some more, baby?
I'd love to, but I gotta save
some for my sister and brother.
Well, it look like you ate it all.
Oooh, wow.
Something sure smells good.
- Uh, Mom?
- Yeah, baby?
I didn't mean to eat it all.
It was just so good.
I'm sorry.
Oh, honey, don't be upset.
Old mean Vera here
was just kidding.
We got plenty.
Tosha, sweetheart,
do me a favor,
go check on your sister.
- So sweet.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry. We've just been
having it...
- kinda rough lately.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, get up there.
Have a seat. Sit down, honey.
- Take a load off.
- Come on.
- Thank you.
- Here.
Oh, thanks.
I lost my job lately, but even
before then, it was... it was...
it was kinda tough.
- God will make a way. Won't He, Sarah?
- Mm-hmm.
Sure wanna believe that.
You must believe it, baby,
and don't you be ashamed to speak out.
We got your back.
'Cause I remember when my
husband died, if it wasn't for family,
I don't know how me and my two girls
would have made it.
I don't have much family.
- Where these kids' daddy at?
- They're not in our lives.
- They?!
- Vera.
- Yeah, they.
- As in...
more than one?
- Three.
- Vera.
Stay out of her business.
Well...
I wasn't trying to get in her business.
I'm gonna help her out.
Here, this should help
you get a little bit.
- Uh, no no no. I can't take that.
- It's the South, baby.
You can take it.
It'll help out a little bit.
No no no, thank you.
I'm gonna go
check on my kids.
Vera! $10, Vera? $10!
What is she gonna do
with $10, Vera?
First of all, she gonna buy
that kid a box of perm.
- You see that child's head?!
- She has dreads.
Dreads.
Let me spell that for you:
N-A-P-P-Y.
Pshh!
Uh-oh, watch the tree.
All right, this game's points.
- Be nice to him. Don't be...
- Whoa whoa whoa.
- Oh!
- Oooh!
What happened?
- Oh, I see what happened.
- Hey!
- Did you win?
- You know it, Mama.
Aw, that's my baby.
You said you want some of this?
I got on my clothes,
my basketball clothes. You ready?
Come on.
Gimme the ball.
You... don't stand there
looking like you ain't never seen this.
Come on.
You wanna play?
Hey.
Harry, Brenda;
Brenda, Harry.
Harry's a friend of the family.
- We met already.
- Oh yeah?
In Chicago. She kicked me
out of her house...
when I told her her son had
potential to play pro ball.
And what, you didn't
believe him?
If Harry says it's true,
then it's the truth.
So, what, you decided
to stalk us?
No.
- This is where I live.
- What?
Harry, you see him foul me?
You fouled me. Didn't...
you seen him, Harry?
He fouled me.
You hit me on the leg.
Excuse me.
Let me go ref this game.
Game point!
I'd still like to take
you out to lunch.
Dinner's ready, you guys.
That's my cue.
I'm coming, Cora!
Ooh.
Michael, come on. It's time
for dinner. I need you to wash up.
- All right.
- It was really good seeing you again.
Harry.
- Huh?
- Harry.
Harry.
Sly dog. Ha ha ha!
- I'll talk to you after dinner.
- Whoa whoa whoa!
Man, hey hey.
You didn't hear that?
What, is that your way of asking
to stay for dinner?
- Why, thank you.
- Whoa whoa whoa.
If you trying to holler at her, man, you
need to come out of that sweaty shirt.
Right.
- I'll be right back.
- All right.
Hey, I'll save you a seat.
- Hey, right next to her.
- All right.
And that was when we all
cried like babies.
You don't know how
to tell no stories.
L.B., Vera, y'all remember when
Daddy tried to teach us
how to swim?
- No, I don't remember that.
- Oh, I remember.
I remember it because it was
like it was yesterday.
I remember it was
Christmas Eve, 19...
1940-something,
whatever.
I remember.
Daddy said he couldn't get us
nothing for Christmas.
So he come in and he said,
"I'm gonna get the truck ready."
- He loaded up horse on the truck.
- Uh-huh.
You know, we ain't have
no engine in the truck.
We just had a, you know,
old one-horsepower truck.
- That was the horse.
- Giddy-up.
Yeah, giddy-up, giddy-up.
We went down to that river.
I didn't want to jump in right off.
That water was 50-below zero!
- Whoo!
- Sho'nuff.
Daddy got out there and he said,
"Get in the water!"
And I said, "I ain't
getting in that water!"
And he looked at me, he had
an extension cord in his hand.
I didn't want to be no disobedient.
So I got to that water
and I looked at it,
and I teenched up there
and then I teeter-tottered.
- Whoo.
- I teeter-tottered.
Teeter-totter, next thing
you know...
bang!
I never learned to swim.
I couldn't get the rhythm
of the stroke.
Why is it that I felt
that I might choke?
Mr. Brown is crazy.
Harry, how is your mother?
- She's good.
- Uh-huh.
I'm glad she's good 'cause I know
she almost had a heart attack
when she heard about all that trouble
you were in with all that illegal...
Mama! Want some cake?
Gimme the part
where they got that rum
sopped up in there. Gimme that piece.
Gimme just that rum piece.
I'm just glad to see you all right
'cause I was praying for you.
That prayer didn't get
no higher than the ceiling.
- Mom.
- What, baby?
- I got a tummy ache.
- Oh, honey,
that's probably
because you ate too much.
- Let me get you something.
- Don't worry about it, Ma.
- I'll take care of her.
- Thank you.
Young man, you know
where you going?
Oh, yes, sir.
Excuse me a minute.
Come on, Mike.
All right. Night, baby.
- Good night.
- Night.
- Later, Mike.
Brenda, he seems like
such a nice young man.
Thank you. He is.
I couldn't make it without him.
You know what? Now just a minute,
just a minute.
I'm just curious. Anybody else at this
table want to know who this woman is?
- Vera!
- All day y'all been skirting the issue.
I want to know
who this woman is.
- Mama...
- No no, uh uh uh uh!
Who are you?
Well, um...
apparently Pop Brown
was my daddy.
- What?
- Huh-uh, you's a liar.
Apparently nothing.
You a liar!
Huh-uh, the devil is a liar.
Oh, hell to the no.
My daddy wasn't no rolling stone.
Well, that's what
my mama said.
- Who's your mama?
- Her name was Carol Cassidy.
I don't know no Cassidy.
Who's that?
I ain't got no reason
not to tell the truth.
W-wait a minute.
I got something.
Yeah, let's see what you got.
Look at her.
She does look just like us.
Look, I'm the baby of this family.
She ain't coming up in here.
All that attitude and carrying on.
"We're from Chicago."
What you got, girl?
I got this letter and it
told me to come down here.
Let me see this.
It's L.B.'s writing.
- L.B., what the hell is this?
- L. B?
- What the hell is it?
- What's going on, L. B?
- Yeah, L.B., what's going on?
- I know all about this.
Papa Brown been talking
to you about her?
Yes, her and her mother.
You see, when Pop Brown
got real sick,
he started to tell me everything
about his past life.
You know, before he got saved
and became a deacon.
So you mean to tell me...
you have a sister?
Yep, and her mother
was the love of his life
in Chicago.
Oh, really?
- Mm-hmm, yeah.
- Huh-uh-uh!
'Cause I don't agree.
What are you saying?
You see, when Pop Brown
was in Chicago,
he was a pimp.
And her mother was
his bottom ho.
You don't talk
about my daddy.
Hell to the no,
this is blasphemy.
L.B., you don't talk about my daddy
like this, not at the dinner table.
- Our daddy was a saint.
- Your daddy was a pimp!
He was not a pim... my daddy
used to date nice women.
- Remember sweet Sadie?
- Yes.
- Good girl.
- She was one of his whores.
- Ho ho.
- What about Agnes with the freckles?
She was a good girl... Agnes.
Freckle-faced ho.
What about Arnette?
- Latin ho.
- What about Tommy Lee?
- Backdoor whore.
- What about Shirley?
Shirley, the one that used to make
cupcakes for me when I was a child.
Please don't tell me Shirley was no ho.
What about Shirley?
- City ho.
- Miss Edna?
She's a double ho.
What about L.B. mama?
L. B?
Nasty ho.
Ain't nothing going
on here but the truth.
Brenda, you sure you okay?
Oh yeah. I'll be fine.
But it's a good thing
this funeral's tomorrow
- so I can get out of here.
- Let me welcome you to the Brown family.
- Some welcome.
- I know it.
This is getting pretty full.
I should take it out.
Oh, okay. You sure
you want to do that?
- Yeah, where?
- Just take it right out front.
Ladies, I'm gonna say
good night.
- Well, good night.
- Nice meeting you.
Nice meeting you too.
- Hey, let me help you with that.
- Oh, I got it.
Around here men do that.
Where I'm from women do it all.
Well, then maybe
you should live here.
God forbid.
What?
What's wrong with my town?
- You call this a town?
- Yeah.
It's calming.
It's too quiet here.
Then maybe you should let me
show you how great a town it is.
You know, I'm here for my father's funeral
and you're flirting with me.
That is in poor taste.
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
Good night.
Well, we are here today to say
- goodbye...
- Lord, that's my daddy!
...to one of our dear
beloved sons.
Daddy, you should've
let me go with you!
Daddy!
Mom, Mom, take it easy.
Sit down, Mom.
And I need you to understand
that God will see you
through all this, sister.
What the hell does
he got on his head?
- And you must realize that...
- Monster, Mama, monster.
- Baby, it's all right.
...in this hour of bereavement,
there is such
a word as comfort.
Yeah, Southern Comfort!
Yes, sir!
- Hmph.
- And God is faithful
- to do exactly what he says he's gonna do.
- Preacher? Excuse me, Pastor?
He do, He do!
Psst!
- l...
- Put me on the program.
I wanted to say something
about my daddy.
- Don't, please.
- You can put me on program.
I'm trying to do
the sermon, please.
- I'm preaching right now.
- You ain't doing no...
you ain't doing no good job.
You're boring everybody.
Look at my daddy's face.
Deacon, he dead.
- Put me on the program.
- I need to finish my sermon.
- Remember that...
- Psst!
You can let me say something
about my daddy. He my daddy.
- Is he your daddy? Act like he your daddy.
- All right.
- Just put me on the program.
- Come on.
- Oh, Daddy!
- All right.
Now I have more to say,
but right now
his son Leroy Brown
has a few words
that he wants to say.
Leroy Brown, come on
and say something
right up on that.
- Me?
- Oh yes.
- What?
- Let's go. Come on now.
- Shut your mouth. Is he sure?
- Yes, Deacon.
- They want me to say something?
- Come on up here, Deacon.
I don't know what to say.
You want me to say
something, L. B?
- Till we all dead.
- Okay.
I'm "nerveless."
I didn't plan on saying
nothing today.
I just was in my room and I
jotted down a few things.
- Can y'all hear me?
- Go on, Brown. Go on, baby.
Is this on?
It's on.
I didn't plan on saying nothing.
Let the church say "amend."
- Amen.
- Let the church say "amend" again.
Amen.
I want to let everybody know
today that Daddy died happy.
He was happy...
I'm gonna miss my daddy.
Bye-bye, Daddy.
My daddy loved his people...
I'm getting sick of this. It don't take nobody
that long to put nobody in the ground.
- Stay calm, stay calm.
- I am calm. I'm just sick of it.
He'll always be right here, y'all,
right here in my heart.
And I won't chatter no...
this ain't no funeral.
- This is a "celebrate."
- Yeah!
And we here to celebrate Daddy.
And I'm telling y'all today,
- my daddy was a happy man.
- Sit down!
- That's what we need...
- Sit down, Brown!
- more superheroes in this church.
We need peoples
that'll stand up and be
heroes for the Lord.
- That's enough.
- Show him, baby.
Oh God.
I gotta stop smoking.
# Amazing #
# Gra-a-a-ace #
# How sweet, yes #
# The sound... #
One more time, Sarah.
She got one more time.
Jesus, why?
Tell me why?
That's it. Vera's really getting
on my nerves.
# That saves... #
# A wre-eeee-etch #
# Like me-eee... #
- Uncle L. B!
- L.B., what's wrong with you?
You wanna go with her?
There's room for you too, you know?
I'll wait.
I'm the baby of this family
and I deserve some respect.
- Right.
- L.B. pushed me in that grave.
I know, Mama. I know.
Everybody's act a fool.
Should have let them put the dirt
on you too... acting a damn fool.
- Calm down, everybody.
- That's just crazy!
Uh, hey, y'all.
It was nice meeting
all of you, but, um...
- I think we're gonna go now.
- Oh no.
You have to stay till tomorrow
for the reading of the will.
- Yeah.
- No! Daddy ain't left her nothing.
No, um, I really think
we ought to be going.
You can't leave, baby,
'cause... the bus only
come every three days.
- It'll be here tomorrow.
- Tomorrow, what?
- It'll be okay.
- No no!
I gotta go.
l... no...
You know what?
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna go change and I'm gonna
be back in 15 minutes.
I'm gonna take you
and your kids
to see my town.
Ah... you'll like it.
- I promise.
- Okay okay okay.
- Okay, all right. Okay, all right.
- 15 minutes.
- All right.
- Oh my God.
All right, you know
I don't know you that well,
but you'd better
watch out for him. Pshaw!
Flashing that pretty smile...
and that nickel-slick talk.
He done broke a lot of women's hearts
out here in these backwoods.
You be careful... sister.
Brenda.
Brown, where you all at?
We over here.
Where that money
you owe me?
- I'm gonna give you two.
- Thank you.
Thank you. Gracias.
You didn't know
I spoke Spanish, did you?
Oooh, you should have
got one.
See, it's not so bad.
Hey, Harry.
- Hey.
- Mmm.
One of your women?
- No, it's my cousin.
- Oh.
That don't mean nothing
down here, do it?
Oh ho.
That's cold.
I'm kidding.
- Hi, Mommy!
Hi, baby! Oh.
They're having fun.
Yeah.
Why don't you have
a woman, anyway?
- Huh?
- I'm divorced.
Ooooh.
Six years, three kids
and a whole lot of drama.
My drama trumps your drama.
Hey, step right up,
step right up.
Who can get the ball in the basket?
How about you, young man?
- Huh huh?
- Hey, Harry?
Yeah, you there, sir.
Get the ball in the basket,
you can win a cute little doll
for the lovely lady back there.
- Maybe you're scared.
- You got some money?
The young man's going to clean
me out of all my profits.
I'm in, but I'll just play.
Not for money.
- Run it.
- How about every one we win
you buy back from us?
All right.
Keep that elbow in, all right?
That's what I'm talking, dawg.
- Bing bing bing.
- Oh ho ho!
That's good form.
That's the difference
right there, man.
Come on, man, get some more,
get some more animals, man...
- Oh, man, look at you.
- Too easy.
- Tosha, take this in the house for Mama.
- Okay.
Hey, wait up.
Hey, man, here's your cut.
Oh no, you keep it.
Thanks.
Think I'm winning him over.
Don't be so sure about that.
He hasn't really had
a real man in his life.
And I sure can't afford
to let another one come running in
and out of it.
Is it his life or your life
we're talking about?
What?
I don't know who
you're protecting, you or him.
Both of us, I guess.
I see.
You really think
he's that good?
I do.
Well, how would that work?
I mean, how would you coach him?
I mean, you're here.
He's with me in Chicago.
And look, he's not
moving down here.
I can make a few trips up there,
give him some drills.
Maybe in the summer,
he can do a camp
with me and some
of the other players.
Hmm, what about
his education?
I promise you
he'll come back
smarter than he left.
Yeah, well, I'll think about it.
- Take your time.
- I have to ask him.
Yeah, do that.
Hey, thank you for the day.
I really appreciate it.
No, thank you.
Goodbye...
and thank you
so much, Harry.
Goodbye.
Oh.
It's for you.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
I'm just gonna go and pack.
No, you are gonna stay
for the reading
of the will, aren't you?
Oh, no no no no.
Stay? Daddy didn't
leave her nothing.
- Vera.
- You should stay.
- No, really.
- Come on.
Come on, sit down.
- Come on over here.
- He your daddy too.
Brenda, come on.
Come on.
Come on in here now.
Come on, you'll probably
thank me too.
You're Daddy's child,
you may as well.
- You never know.
- Why don't you shut...
Sit down now, sit sit.
L.B., she ain't no puppy.
What, you gonna have
her sit and do tricks?
Brother Sam, you read
the last will and "testicles."
Yeah, that's what
I've been waiting for.
I got dressed up
for this. Come on.
Okay, folks...
Pop Brown's last
will and testament.
Here it is.
"To L.B. and his
beautiful wife Sarah..."
Beautiful? Must have been blind,
crippled and crazy.
"...I leave all my money..."
- Whoo! Thank you, Daddy.
- Sweet!
- "...a total amount of $575."
- You rich! You rich!
- That ain't nothing.
- What? 500?
We... we took care
of that sucker till he died.
He just leave us
nothing but that?
$575.
I washed his toes
and cleaned his nose!
He's so happy he can't
get his words out. He's rich.
And and and...
keep reading, baby.
- "To Vera..."
- Yes.
"...I leave all my love."
Love, yes, and...
"May it keep you warm at night."
There's got to be more.
You keep reading, baby.
Keep reading 'cause I know
there's more for me.
"And to Brown..."
Oh, boy, this is good.
"...I leave my house."
The house?
I'd rather have the love.
That house is tore up, Brown.
Shut up, Vera.
We grew up in that house.
Yeah, us and several families
of rats and roaches.
What the hell is that?
"To my daughter Brenda..."
- Brenda?
- Wh...
- "...I leave my old rental property."
Oh, Brenda,
that's wonderful.
He left me a house?
Do you think we're living here?
Do you think
we're living here now?
Okay, well, it has potential.
Potential to be torn down.
Is this our house, Mama?
Looks that way, baby.
- I'm gonna go back to the projects.
- Yeah, me too.
Me three.
I'd stay with you, brother.
Hmm.
Come on.
At least go inside.
All right, but, Tosha, Lena,
y'all wait in the car.
Come on, go ahead.
Looks dangerous in here.
Ma.
It got a welcome mat.
Ooh.
- It's a nice house.
- Really?
What you looking at?
It just needs a little work.
This house don't need
no little nothing.
- Ma, come on.
- What?
Can we please get out of here?
I'm not trying to miss the bus.
Could you just give me a minute?
Let me ask you something.
What do you think about
Harry coaching you?
- Hmm?
- I'm cool with it if it gets us out of here.
Oh, he cool with it.
That's good.
Uh-huh.
You know, I really wish
you weren't leaving.
Well, gotta get back to my life.
- Ma, come on!
- I'm coming.
Brenda, you leaving
me so soon?
Yeah, we got to be heading back.
Okay, well, look,
here's my number.
I want you to keep in touch, okay?
- Oh, I will.
- All right.
And here...
What's this?
It's from me and Sarah.
We wanted to bless you with something.
No, Cora, no. No, I can't.
- No, take it.
- I can't.
You have to take it.
We wanted to bless you with it.
It's just a little something.
Brenda, please.
Ain't no telling when
I'd be able to pay y'all back.
Oh, honey,
don't worry about that.
If some of these fathers
don't take care of these babies,
then us single mothers have
to stick together. Please take it.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
This is the nicest thing
that anybody's ever done for me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, maybe you need
to change your friends.
- Thank you, thank you.
- Oh, you're so welcome.
- What did he say?
- Yeah, he hiring all right,
but not for the job
he advertising for.
- I go kill him now.
- No no no no.
- Cheryl.
- Let me go.
Stop it, calm down.
Hey, don't you wanna
hear about my trip, huh?
- You never told me about the trip.
- Don't ask.
- Brenda, you just...
- I'm just kidding.
Did he leave you
anything at least?
Yeah, a house.
- When are we moving?
- Huh-uh, girl, it's so raggedy.
You can't live in it.
Compared to that, we live in a palace.
Brenda, don't be selfish.
Let's move to Georgia
so I can find me one
of those big old
Jethro-looking papis
so I can cucuchanga.
Girl, you know what?
I think I might have met somebody
- who'd be just your style.
- For me?
Uh-huh.
His name's Brown.
I got it.
Who is it?
Hey.
What you doing here?
I've been thinking
about what you said,
and I'm gonna help you out.
So can I come in,
please?
Yeah.
Come on in.
Damn, girl, this how you live?
You gonna give me
some money or not?
What you gonna give me, huh?
I ain't gonna
give you nothing.
- Aw, come on, girl, damn it.
- No, stop it, stop it.
You oughta wanna do the right thing
and take care of your son.
- You're right.
- Why I gotta threaten you
with child support
to take care of him?
Damn, Brenda, do it.
- The boy probably ain't mine anyway.
- You bastard!
You need this money,
don't you, right?
So come on, baby,
where's the bedroom?
No, stop it. I don't sleep
with men for money.
Well, your mama used to,
didn't she?
I ain't my mama. Get the hell
out of my house!
Forget you then.
You all ain't getting nothing.
I don't care if both of y'all
starve to death.
You bastard. You would
do that to your own son?
- Hey.
- You're just evil.
I told you when you was pregnant I
didn't give a damn about you or the boy.
Matter of fact, what did you do with
the $200 I gave you for the abortion?
I'll bet you wish
you had that $200 now.
- Don't you?
- Hey, Michael, baby.
Hey, Mike. What's up, boy?
Mama, why you begging like this?
No no, he ain't gotta help us.
No, I know how to make some things
happen on my own.
You don't need
to beg this motherf...
Leave it.
He's still your father.
- Get your hand out of my face.
- Boy, better watch your mouth!
- No, no, it's not worth it.
- Mama, are you defending him?
Look, if you ain't
man enough to help us,
I know how to make some things
happen on my own.
- No, baby. Where are you going?
- No no.
Michael! Mike, stop him.
That boy ain't my responsibility.
It isn't my problem.
No, Michael!
Michael!
Michael.
- Hey.
Can I come in?
Yeah yeah, come on in.
Have a seat.
I'm sorry. I thought
you were Michael.
He's not here?
No.
Did you tell him about the practice
sessions I set up for him?
Yeah, I did.
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
What's up, man?
What's up? You're just
the man I need to see.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
You can't win a game
with your shoes falling off, dawg.
- Here.
- These are for me?
You know it. I got money
on this game, dawg.
I need you on your "A."
- Thanks, Calvin.
- It's all good, dawg.
Hey, man,
you hanging tonight?
Yeah.
You working?
You want in?
Yeah, show me
what I gotta do.
- All right.
- Mike.
Who is this fool?
- He 5-0?
- No, man, I'll handle it.
Dude, what are you doing here?
Your mother's looking for you.
You got some nerve
coming around here.
- So you gonna do this, huh?
- Why not?
- You're too smart for this.
- Dude, you don't know nothing about me.
I know you're about
to make a stupid mistake.
Harry, you don't know
nothing about my life.
You don't know
what we're up against.
It doesn't matter
what you're up against.
You could make a stupid mistake and have
everything in the world going for you.
I was in the league.
I started gambling.
Lost everything,
including my wife and kids.
I made mistakes
I'm still paying for today.
I know a few things about
going down the wrong road.
And this is the wrong road.
- All right, man.
- Dude,
you better get out of here.
Okay.
We're supposed to practice
tomorrow at 3:00.
If you show up,
then I'll know you're as smart
as I think you are.
Yeah, whatever, man.
I'm gonna be here for two days.
- All right?
- Yeah, let's do this.
Come here.
What?
Where you been all night, huh?
I was with Calvin.
Okay, so you're a man now.
You gonna sell dope, huh?
Now you think
that makes you a man?
Why not, Mama?
We ain't got nothing.
- Boy, are you crazy?
- No, you work like a dog,
and what has it gotten you?
You talk about God
making a way.
Mama, I'm not trying
to die to get to heaven.
I want mine here on earth.
Then you know what?
You gonna have to get out
of my house then, huh?
You think you're grown? Go.
Get out!
Mama, where am I gonna go?
I don't wanna hear it.
I done my best by you.
I done tried. Get out.
Who's gonna help you
with Lena and Tosha?
Don't you even worry
about that, okay? I got that.
You just get out.
- No no, I'm not going, Mama.
- Go on.
No child of mine is gonna
sell dope, you hear me?
I ain't sitting up in here waiting
to hear that you done got killed.
Get out. Hit the bricks.
No, Mama, I'm not going.
No, if I go, I'm a coward
just like my dad.
I'm your son.
I'm not gonna leave you
like them other dudes.
Mama, I'm just tired
of seeing you hurt
and struggling.
I'm sorry.
Mama, I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- We gonna be all right.
You hear me?
- I'm sorry.
- We gonna be all right.
We gonna be all right.
I promise. I promise.
I'm sorry, Mama.
I love you, baby.
I love you.
- I love you too. I'm sorry.
- All right, all right, all right.
Okay, just...
just... just go to bed, all right?
Go now.
All right, let's go.
On the whistle, chest passes.
Passer makes the shooter.
Pass it like you want him
to shoot the ball.
Are you coachable?
Do you listen?
It's good to see you.
On the whistle,
chest passes.
- What's up, Calvin?
- What's up, dawg?
I won six large
on you tonight.
You play with heart, son.
Here.
Look, man, that's what
I came to tell you.
Calvin, I can't do this.
Here, this is all the money.
It's your cut and mine.
I'm sorry, dude.
You know what?
I understand that.
You ain't got this
in you, man.
You go on now.
You go play basketball.
Me? I'm gonna be
a hood rat.
That's all I'll ever be.
Calvin, you can be
whatever you want to be.
No, kid.
Yo, son, you think
you can just sell on my turf?
Mike, run!
Mike's great. I wish he
was playing in my gym.
What about you?
What about your house?
What about it?
What you gonna do with it?
Let it do what it's been doing
for the last whatever years.
Which is what?
Sit there.
- That ain't no good.
- Try this. You'll like it.
Get in there. Come on.
Oh, man, that's good.
What is that?
- Is that pork?
- That's pork, baby.
I don't even eat pork,
and that's good.
Brenda, I like talking to you.
Thanks.
But this is about
helping my son, right?
Yeah.
What if I also enjoy spending
as much time with you
- as I do coaching your son?
- Harry.
I ain't going down
that road, okay?
- Thanks, girl.
- You're welcome.
- All right now, I work for tips.
- I know.
- This is your neighborhood, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
It ain't so bad, is it?
You'd rather live here
than in your own house?
Well, I know this. I don't know
nothing about Georgia.
So it's friends
keeping you here.
If I could live here,
I ain't afraid of nothing.
Brenda, aye, mami.
- Cheryl, hi, girl.
- I've been looking all over for you.
We have to go to the hospital.
- The hospital, why?
- They shot him.
- What happened, Cheryl?
- Mikey... they shot him!
Michael.
I never had much of a mother,
so I was determined
to be the best that I could.
When he was young,
I gave him to the Lord.
I said, "Lord, protect my baby.
Watch him for me."
But I can't...
I can't feed him.
I can't give him what he need.
There are nights
when I go to bed hungry
'cause I know they didn't
get enough to eat all day.
You know, I just...
feel so bad.
Why did I do this to them?
You know, I can't even
keep 'em out of harm's way.
Hey hey hey hey.
You've done more than most.
Look, thank you.
I know you have to go.
No, I'm not going anywhere
unless you want me to go.
No.
I'm here with you.
Thank you.
Hey, Brenda, what's up with all these
emergency phone calls?
Michael Jr.,
he was shot last night
trying to hustle money for me.
But I ain't paying for no funeral.
He ain't dead. You bastard.
Hold on here. Don't call me.
- You know what happened last night.
- Hey hey!
- Is everything all right here, Brenda?
- Yeah.
I'm fine.
I gotta go to work.
Hey hey.
- Michael.
- What?
This is my last $25.
That's what you make?
Can I buy an hour of your time
to spend with your son?
Don't you call my house again.
You're pissing off my wife.
- You okay?
- Miss Brown.
- Yes.
- Hi. Now we managed
to get the bullet
and stop the bleeding.
It's a miracle that
it missed his vital organs.
Is he gonna be okay?
Yes, he's gonna be fine.
I need to see him.
Well, he's in recovery right now,
but he'll be in I.C.U.
in just a little bit.
Thank you, thank you.
You're welcome.
You're welcome. All right.
# This life can make me
so confused #
# But it's all right #
# Living day by day,
I feel so used #
# That ain't right #
# I just want to run and hide #
# But I don't have
the time to cry #
# It's all right #
# It's all right, all right #
# Many thoughts are
runnin' through my head #
# It's all right #
# Wishing to be
somewhere else but here #
# And it's all right #
# I can't wait
to see your face #
# I need a smile
and your embrace #
# I'm all right #
# I'm all right, yeah #
# Life can bring us
through any changes #
# It's all right #
- # Never give up #
- # Just don't give up #
# Know that it's
gonna be all right #
- # People come and they go #
- # They go #
# It's just the way that it goes #
# Everything is everything #
# It's all right #
# Sometime the rain #
# It makes me sad
and it's all right #
# Some things in the world
they make me mad #
# And it's all right #
# In the morning
when I see the sun #
# I know I'm not the only one #
# And it's all right #
# It's all right... #
I can't believe you're leaving.
I know, but you're
welcome to come.
I don't think so.
I'll come visit
or something, but no.
And anyways, look at that.
You're in very good hands.
I know, I can't even believe
he stayed as long as he did.
Ay, you know I don't like half
the men you've dated,
but this one...
I like him a lot.
Mmm.
Uh, we ain't dating.
Yeah, call it whatever you want.
You might not be dating him,
- but he's definitely dating you.
- Huh-uh.
Come on.
Hey, beautiful,
you mess with my girl,
I come down there
and I get you...
- English, Cheryl, English.
- Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm!
What are you
doing with that bag?
# Everything is everything #
- # It's gonna be #
- # All right #
# Life can bring us
through many changes #
# It's all right... #
Are you serious?
Oh, Tosha.
Oh my God.
Welcome home.
What is this? Harry!
I can't believe this.
It's your house.
Oh my God.
Hey! Don't y'all just
stand there.
Come on in this house!
Come on now!
Come on!
Oh, Harry told us
what happened.
- We all prayed for you, Mike.
- Thank you.
Y'all come on in.
I decorated.
- What?
- No he didn't.
Baby. Awww.
Come here.
Come on.
Oh my gosh.
Mom!
Mama, I got my own room!
I know, baby.
Oh! Oh, God,
thank you.
Thank you. How did you
afford to do all of this?
Well, I pitched in
most of the money.
If you call $45 most of it,
well then, okay.
No, we had a fundraiser
at the church.
- Yeah, and we all pitched in.
- Thank you. Thank you.
l... I don't know what to say.
Money shot.
Here you go. Go up strong.
Always go up strong.
You know, I think
that Harry's a nice man.
- Yes, he is.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
- He put up the most money for this house.
- He sure did.
- He did?
And I think he likes you.
Mm-hmm.
- Mama?
- Yeah, baby.
Where do these
two lovebirds go?
Come on, I'll show you.
I think...
he likes her son.
What are you talking about?
Honey, are you that naive?
You haven't noticed all that attention
he been giving that boy?
What are you trying to say, Vera?
Oh, not like that.
He's being so nice to her
because her son
is a gold mine.
Okay? He's trying to get in
so he can get that boy to go pro
so he can get some of them perks...
maybe pay off some of them
gambling debts, okay?
Child, please.
This is an investment.
She better watch out.
- I don't believe none of that.
- Me neither.
Why else would
a man be this nice
to a woman with three...
count 'em... three kids.
Well, you know, Vera, there are
some good men in this world.
And Harry happens
to be one of them.
- That's right.
- Not according to the local bookies.
Why you think he got
kicked out of the league?
Don't sit there acting like y'all don't
know this boy got a gambling problem.
- Don't be acting like you don't know.
- You need to stop
- listening to all that gossip, Vera.
- Please.
- Stop being messy.
- Hush your mouth before she hears you.
- Yes.
- If you ain't happy,
you don't want nobody else to be.
Well, I called it like
I see it and smell it!
Well, you're always
smelling up some mess.
That's right.
Do your negative
smelling somewhere else
'cause you're always
smelling up a mess.
- Cora!
- What?
- Yeah!
I'm in the kitchen!
Your mama done went crazy!
People just everywhere!
Mr. Brown, please!
Cora, you slapped your daddy?
I oughta whup your butt.
Calm down. What's wrong?
Just sit down. Sit down.
- Turn the TV on.
- Okay...
- Turn the TV on!
- What happened on the TV?
- Get the TV on.
- I'm trying to get it on. Hold on.
- What happened?
- Look!
A routine traffic stop turned
into one of the largest and most bizarre
and shocking police pursuits
that we have ever seen.
This old woman is driving
like she has a lot to lose.
Who could this be calling
me right now? Hello.
Cora, hey.
How you doing, baby?
Madea, please tell me
that's not you.
Yeah, it's me, honey.
Yeah.
Madea, why don't you
just pull over?
- You can't out...
- I can't pull over.
- You goin' to jail.
- These police is after me.
Hold on, I'm gonna put you
on speakerphone.
Mabel, pull over. Just stop.
Oh, Lordy, there's helicopters
and everything now.
- Pull your car over...
- Mabel, you can't outrun
- the "helichoppers."
- Please, Madea, please!
- They ain't taking me to jail!
- Like hell they ain't.
...just gonna send me to jail.
I'm going all the way this time.
Madea, please
pull the car over.
They ain't gonna get me!
I'm gonna be on "Cops."
No, you can't. Madea, please.
I love you, honey.
Please just pull over.
I can't pull over, Cora.
Y'all come down there to DeKalb County,
put $20 on my book.
I'm running out of gas.
I might have to stop.
If it's any "constipation,"
I love you.
I always have
and I always will.
Madea, please.
I love you, honey, please...
Yeah, I love you too.
Go to hell.
- Hey, Ma.
- Hey, sweetheart.
- Guess what.
- What?
Harry took me to his lawyer
to sign a contract with him.
- He's my manager now.
- He did what?
Yeah, I sent some
footage to a pro scout.
I don't know
how the word got out,
but next thing I know, there's bunch
of agents at the gym pressuring Mike.
You know, I had him sign something...
so they wouldn't take advantage of him.
- Harry knows his stuff, Mama.
- I know a little bit.
Michael, why don't you
go check on your sisters,
- make sure they wash up?
- Okay.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
You been awful quiet
the last few days.
I'm fine.
Harry, can I
ask you something?
Yeah.
What's in this for you?
- What are you talking about?
- Why is he so important to you?
- Hmm?
- l...
- Hmm.
- Mike's a good kid.
He's a talented kid.
What are you
talking about?
I don't like you spending
all this time with him.
And I don't understand why you're
sending footage to pro scouts.
Trying to... trying to help.
Why? Why? What for?
What's in it for you?
I mean, if he gets
a million-dollar contract,
you think you
gonna get your cut?
Is this some
kinda game to you?
Whoa whoa whoa, hold on.
Where is this coming from?
Huh? What, have that many men hurt
you that you can't trust one?
This ain't about me, all right?
This is about you.
Now, how much gambling
debt are you in?
You didn't think
I'd hear about that?
- You think I'm in it for some money?
- Well, are you?
Is that what you think of me?
Should that be
what I think of you?
- Brenda...
- You're not going to be his manager.
- No, just go. Go. Go, please.
I paid all of my gambling debts.
I don't owe anybody anything.
Get out.
Oh, hell. I'm running out of gas.
Pull your car over to the side.
Cora, here.
Go bail your mama out.
Give her this $20.
What... what is this for?
It's for back child support.
Back...
I owe it to ya.
And there it is.
- As fast as it started...
- Oh, they got her.
But it still has gone down
as one of the longest
police pursuits in history.
What the hell? They gonna
send "helichoppers"
and all these police cars
for a little old woman.
- Get out of the vehicle now.
- Don't shoot.
I'm getting out of the car.
They gonna lock your ass up.
I ain't got no weapon.
I ain't never do nothing wrong.
- You gonna leave me up here...
- I ain't got no weapon.
All of this for me, huh?
What the hell you
got me surrounded for?
She got a gun!
She... she kidnapped me.
Get out of your
vehicle with your hands up.
Very slowly!
Put your hands
on the car, ma'am.
- Hands on the car right now...
- Hold on one minute.
- Let me tell you something here.
- Put your hands on the car.
I ain't finna put my hands on the car
'cause my hands is hurtin'.
- Ma'am, put your hands...
- Who the hell you talkin' to?
- You don't want...
- Put your hands on the car!
- You ain't gonna take me down!
- Settle down, ma'am!
Put your hands on the car now.
I'm Madea!
There's another charge.
And another charge.
- Man down! Man down!
- Another charge. That's six more years.
Get her off me!
One, two, three!
You giving me a mammogram!
Hell, you ain't going...
Get in the car, ma'am.
Get in the car.
- Transport chase suspect. Over.
- Affirmative.
- Stay back, people.
- All right, everybody.
Just a minute.
- Hi. How may I help you?
- Yeah, I'm Richard Carney.
I'm looking for Brenda
and Michael Brown.
- What about?
- I'm a sports agent and, well, can we talk?
Uh, what about?
How'd you get my address?
Ma, Ma, please.
Come on in.
Hi.
- How you doing?
- Good.
I sent your son's tape
to two professional teams.
And they were very impressed.
I've already got two teams
that are interested
in signing him right now.
- Really?
- Yes.
And I can make a really
good deal for your son.
So what do you want to do?
Hmm?
What do you think?
So what about college?
We'll have you take
college courses,
- even help you get a degree.
- Mama...
Let's do it.
- Okay. All right.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Let's do it.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Um, he signed a contract
with someone to be his manager.
Does that person have any legal grounds
to any of his money?
- You mean Harry Belton?
- Yeah.
That contract didn't ask for money.
It was more of a guidance thing.
He wasn't even trying to get paid.
I guess with all of his
knowledge of this business,
he just didn't want him
to be taken advantage of.
Listen, Miss Brown,
I'll be in touch in a week, okay?
And you, young man,
- you get ready.
- Yes, sir.
We'd like to say that the Thunderhawks
are very happy to have him onboard.
A million dollars is a lot of money...
- I'm his daddy.
...are other players going to be jealous...
Hey, son, how you doing?
Look, son, can I holler
at you a minute?
- Mama.
- He's still your daddy.
- What is he to me?
- I just want to say congratulations, boy.
- I'm proud of you. You did it.
- Hey hey hey.
When you had the chance to be in my life,
you didn't want no part of me.
You should have thought
about all this before.
Hey, now, come on.
Don't be like that.
I don't know why you here, man.
That $25 an hour is waiting on you.
What position is he
going to play?
Coach, what do you think Mike's
gonna do with all the money?
Why don't we let Mike
answer that question?
Mike, what are you gonna
do with all that money?
Make sure my mom and my sisters
are taken care of.
- And he's gonna finish school.
- And finish school.
Hey, Mike, what are you
gonna do for your dad?
- Who?
- Isn't that your father?
Well, that's funny.
I've... I've seen my father
twice since I was four.
My mom's been breaking her back
to make sure my sisters and I
had food on the table.
We lived in the projects
while he went on
and started his life with someone else
living the good life,
but somehow he seemed
to make it to my big day.
Why don't I let my dad answer that
for you? Come on, Dad.
Are you proud of your son?
What was he like as a kid?
How were his grades
growing up?
- Tell us about the moves he got from you.
- Favorite game memory?
Well, l... you know,
that was a long time ago.
He's always been a good boy.
He's always been real athletic
and... and he's always
loved his basketball.
How do you feel
about your son's comments?
Hey, you... you know, it...
you know what?
Are you gonna spend
more time with him now?
That's up to my boy.
That's up to Mike.
- I hope so.
- With you showing up at this time,
some folks would consider
that gold digging.
But hey, this is
all about my son, right?
This is all about
my boy, all right?
This is not about me.
This isn't the way home.
Yeah, I know.
What?
Ma, you were wrong about Harry.
Michael, you don't know
nothing about that, okay?
No, that's a good dude, Mama.
And you need to fix it.
Well, isn't that
what you would tell me?
Yeah.
He's in there.
Hey.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Talent, attitude, skill.
He deserves it.
Thank you
for all your help.
It's all good.
You know, um...
I can pay you back now
for all you did for us...
the house, the move,
everything.
- You don't get it, do you?
- Get what?
I didn't do all of that
so you could pay me back.
I'm sorry.
I'm just so used to being
taken advantage of...
Yeah, that you don't even know
when somebody loves you.
You love me?
Yeah.
Tell Mike I said congratulations.
Hey, what if I told you
I love you too,
but I just got scared for a second,
but I'd rather be scared and with you
than not scared and not have you?
What... why would I scare you?
Because you're everything
I always wanted in a man.
Then let me be that for you.
Cora, do you miss
your granddaddy?
I never met him.
- You what?
- I never met him.
Let me introduce you
to your granddaddy.
- He dead.
- Cora, that man died, but he can still hear.
Whoo! Don't you know
that angels got ears, Cora?
Come here, Cora.
You got to meet him.
Look the way he dressed.
Look at Daddy.
Cora, our daddy was ugly,
but he was our daddy.
Yes, he was. Cora, look at him.
This is your granddaddy.
- Don't touch it.
- That's our granddaddy.
It's our granddaddy.
- Cora... look at him, Cora.
- I'm looking at him.
Look at him!
Look down at him!
Look down
at him!
Go up close, Cora.
Cora, look... look... kiss him.
Kiss your granddaddy.
Kiss him on the forehead.
Huh-uh,
huh-uh, huh-uh!
Let her alone!
How strong is your faith?
You believe he can come back?
You believe he can
be like Nazareth?
Put your hand
on his heart, Cora.
You can beat some life in...
beat his heart, Cora!
Beat into him, Cora!
Don't touch my daddy!
Cora, I just wanted
you to have...
this is your daddy, Cora.
Cora, look at him.
You know who this is?
- My granddaddy?
- # This is your granddaddy #
# This is your granddaddy #
# This is your granddaddy,
your granddaddy #
# Your granddaddy... #
Sing it!
# This is your
granddaddy... #
# This is your granddaddy #
# Your granddaddy,
your granddaddy. #
Sing it!
This movie's been pretty deep so far,
so let's have a good time.
Cora, I'm trying...
It's okay. It's okay.
Please, you have
to open your eyes.
Hello. Yeah.
You mean... I'm driving.
They tell you you can't be talking
on your cell phone
while you driving.
Hey!
Yeah, I'm gonna pray now.
Thank you.
Y'all bow your heads.
Bow your heads, I'm praying.
Heavenly Father,
I ask that You would
put them chickens back in that coop
so she can get eggs...
...to make her pies
and cakes for the church.
- I need you to watch the road.
- We thank You... help, Cora, turn.
We thank you, Lord,
that You have made a way
for her to make cakes for the church.
Bless them chickens!
- Yes.
- Amen. Amen.
Amen.
I promise you I didn't know.
Anybody feel bereaved?
Why so many people from
the Bereaved family die?
- I'm bereaved now.
- I don't know why so many...
peoples are always dying
in the Bereaved family.
Every time you read the paper,
it say the Bereaved family.
They gonna run out
of peoples in a minute
if they keep on dying.
'Cause I looked in...
is she Bereaved?
I didn't even know she was kin
of the Bereaved family.
Whoo. Cora, don't go
gospel gangster on them, baby.
It ain't worth it.
- Don't tell me to calm...
- Cora, just relax.
- Don't do it, Cora.
- No...
- Don't do it.
- I'm gonna do it.
Cora, just sit down.
Ooh, you gonna be in that
jail and you gonna rot.
You gonna rot if
you do that, Cora.
Don't do it.
And cut.
He done broke a lot
of women's hearts
out here in these backwoods.
Yeah, you be careful, Brenda.
Tell me something.
What you gonna do
with all that money, Anna Mae?
Oh-ho.
He made me do that.
You know he made me do that.
Kick his ass.
- I'm gonna cuss, Cora.
- Don't do it.
- I'm finna cuss.
- I'ma cuss her!
- You punk!
- That's it!
Forgive me, Lord,
for I have cussed.
Yeah, we all need to pray.
And we cut.
My daddy was a good man.
Choir, join me in singing.
# Silent night #
# Holy... #
Stand!
Stand. Rise!
# All is calm #
# All is bright. #
Give me one
#Sing #
# Sing #
Shh!
#Sing #
- # Sing #
# Sing... #
Bow for me, Pop Brown.
Shh! Shh!
- # Sing #
- # Sing sing sing #
- # Sing sing sing... #
- # Sing sing sing sing #
- # Sing sing sing sing. #
She broke out
of the handcuffs!
Cora, your mama on that stuff.
She on that stuff. I been trying
to tell you your mama's on that "PPP."
- What'd you say?
- "PPP."
- She sniffing on PPP.
- PPP?
Yeah, PPP.
It's like cocaine.
LSD?
I ain't took none, Cora.
Don't ask me.
The devil is a liar.
I'm about to go home.
We got it.
That's a wrap!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org