Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
My first...
my last...
my everything.
And the answer to...
all my dreams.
You're my sun...
my moon...
my guiding star.
Sing!
That's what you are.
I know...
there's only...
only one like you.
There's no way...
they could have made two.
They couldn't have made two!
You the only one!
You're all I'm living for.
Your love I'll keep forevermore.
You're the first.
You're the last.
My everything.
Oh, shit!
Go, man, go!
What you got?
Dodgers tickets,
Lakers tickets...
and Phantom of the Opera
tickets.
It's theater.
You ever been to the theater?
What the hell wrong with you?
Nobody give a damn
about Phantom of the Opera.
Franklin,
there's money in culture.
Let me tell you something,
Roland.
Black people
don't want to see that.
Get me some good shit,
like Luther Vandross tickets.
Luther Vandross is not culture.
Fuck culture!
People complain about
these fucked up tickets.
You're making me look bad.
Next time,
come up with some better stuff.
OK.
I'm not fuckin' with you.
I'm for real!
You owe me.
I don't owe you shit.
Where have you been?
You're supposed to wash it,
not take it for a joyride.
Where you been?
I been looking for you.
What?
I've been looking for you.
I'm glad I found you.
Get the hell on.
That's him. Let's do this.
I need two on the floor.
I need $200.
Same time. I don't know you.
Willie.
All righty.
Get out of here.
Try to hide some of this.
Keep it on the down-low.
You'll get a nigger busted.
Get me locked up.
Hurry up.
-How we doing?
-What you need?
Let me guess.
Two to the Phantom of the Opera?
I've already seen it.
Wait a minute.
You that silly ass reporter
from the Channel Five News.
Channel 12, actually.
What's up?
James Russell. How you doing?
Wonder if we can talk to you
on camera.
Julio, is that all right?
Whatever you want to do.
Let's roll it.
Speed.
-Wait a minute.
-Cut.
Let me straighten out my shit.
I'm ready. Let's go.
You're ready? You sure?
I'm sure.
This is James Russell...
reporting on our city
and her crimes.
I'm here talking
to the car wash hustler.
You've got
quite an operation here.
What is going on down here?
I'm a businessman.
What the fuck you think
goin' on?
What?
You can't use
that kind of language on TV.
What language?
Fuck.
Fuck what?
You cannot say "fuck"
on television.
Fuck that.
You the one wanted an interview.
Hurry up. I got shit to do.
I got shit to do, also.
Get on with it.
Speed.
This is James Russell reporting
on our city--
Hey, Franklin!
What's up?
I gotta go.
Y'all do a commercial
or find somebody else.
What up, Carmine?
I ain't seen you in a long time.
Fucking cut!
When am I gonna get my money?
What money?
Wait a minute.
You're talking about
the money I owe you.
I'm gonna pay you.
You know I'll pay you.
And I got your phone calls.
When you call--
Somebody stole my phone.
Can you believe that shit?
I don't like brothers,
and I don't like welchers.
Killing you would be double fun.
Stop playing.
What are you talking
about killing for?
If you kill me,
how am I gonna pay you?
Open the door,
get out of my car...
get on the street,
and get my money.
I'm gonna get it,
but don't leave mad.
Give me a hug or something.
-Get out.
-A kiss?
Franklin Hatchett?
He dead. They buried him
at the Compton cemetery.
You're under arrest.
What the fuck y'all doing?
I didn't do shit!
Nobody ever does.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Wait a minute.
I'll give you $5.00
to let me out.
Bribery, too?
In the car.
Watch my head.
He offered me $5.00.
Channel 5, help a brother out?
Geraldo!
You ain't gonna do nothing?
I'm gonna get your ass!
A serious crime.
Justified punishment.
This is James Russell reporting.
Channel 12 News.
We got him.
We didn't get shit.
Let's get out of here.
I am dead serious.
The po-po trippin'.
Ever since that O.J. shit.
I was rolling down the street,
wasn't doing nothing.
They gonna pull me over.
I was just living
ghetto fabulous.
I had five of my finest hos--
Are you hot?
A little,
but I was just chillin'.
The cop pull behind me,
lights and everything--
"Get out of the car."
I said,
"I ain't gettin' out the car."
Then all my hos was scared.
They was like, "We scared."
They be saying stuff
like that.
I was like, "I ain't stopping.
I ain't do nothing."
And he said, "Get out the car."
I got out and said,
"What you calling backup for?
"This is between me and you."
They got my license,
my registration, everything.
You gotta talk to 'em.
Stop playing.
He started trippin'.
That's when I slapped him.
I put his handcuffs on him...
put him in the back seat,
and said...
"I'm gonna take your ass
to jail...
"'cause you're
the one trippin'."
They put their hands on you?
One dude tried to grab me
from the back.
That's how they caught me.
From the back? How they do it?
They tried to grab me
like this, jack me up.
Like that?
They was grabbing.
They was trippin'.
Like that.
Get the hell off me!
Where's your shirt at?
Good-bye, sweetness.
Where we going?
Just leave me the fuck alone.
Who you talking to?
What?
Vacu fela culay, you Jerry-
Lewis-liking motherfucker.
Let's move it.
Let me borrow your gun.
Come to the back of the bus.
You shut up and sit down.
What the hell wrong with you?
I don't play that shit.
Check my police record.
You don't know
who you're messin' with.
You better come to the back
before you get hurt.
Play that shit.
Wait till we get off the bus.
I'm gonna kick your ass!
Shut up!
Where you from?
That French part of Compton?
What's that you claiming?
You don't know
who you're messing with.
I'm deep in the streets.
I slap people for fun.
That's what I do.
You want to play rough?
I kill for fun.
I ain't scared to go to jail.
Take me to jail.
Would you speed up, please?
I want to go back.
All my cousins in there.
I want to see all my friends.
What are you doing up there?
Raymond!
Debray.
Let's get out of here.
No time.
We'll take him with us.
We gotta go together.
We're a team.
Move!
We made it.
Everybody OK?
What it is.
Drop me off over there.
My cousin's house coming up.
Hover over the roof.
Y'all don't even have to stop.
I can be out of here.
I know y'all probably
got shit to do--
Shut up!
You can drop a brother off.
Y'all don't need me.
Fifteen million.
Cut a brother in on that.
Let me be down.
We'll split it three ways.
Seven for me, seven for you,
and you get whatever's left...
'cause you been trippin'
since I met you.
What you doing with the ax?
Forget about what I said.
I don't know shit about
no $15 million in no Jaguar.
I don't even know where we at.
I got a bad memory.
-Be still.
-Put the ax down.
Don't move.
What's wrong with you?
Trying to cut
a brother's hand off.
Always trying to kill somebody.
Why don't you try
loving somebody?
What did you open the door for?
Y'all trippin'.
You want some girls?
I can get you any kind
of girl--black, Japanese.
I can take you over
to my grandmama house.
She cook you some chicken,
some cornbread, some poulet.
It's cold.
It's colder than a motherfucker.
A serious crime.
Justified punishment.
This is James Russell
reporting.
That's some hard-hitting stuff.
John Tesh school of journalism.
Barclay, just watch it
one more time before you decide.
Why? Nobody else will.
Who gives a rat's ass
about some two-bit hustler?
The people getting ripped off
give a rat's ass.
You're just another walking
head shot, aren't you?
Another pretty boy wanker
masquerading as a reporter.
I don't need this bullshit.
This is the skinny.
You're fired.
Have your stuff out by Monday.
Be brief.
What part of "you're fired"
don't you understand?
Not you, you asshole.
I'm talking to somebody else.
What?
Tragedy and terror
strike the Southland.
Good afternoon.
A bus delivering prisoners from
the men's central lockup...
to the Van Nuys courthouse
was destroyed...
on the First Street bridge
in downtown Los Angeles.
Fourteen prisoners and
two policemen were killed...
in what authorities describe
as a commando-style raid.
All bodies
have been accounted for...
with the exception
of two prisoners.
Witnesses saw the two men
boarding a helicopter...
shortly after the bus
exploded into flames.
The two fugitives are wanted
in connection with the murders.
This has got sweeps week
written all over it.
Let me know how it turns out.
On the left is a John Doe
police arrested at L.A.X...
for possession
of a counterfeit passport.
And on the right,
Franklin Maurice Hatchett...
a local street hustler
with suspected gang ties...
who was en route to Van Nuys...
to be arraigned on charges
of soliciting goods.
The two fugitives
are considered dangerous.
Fourteen prisoners due to face
a Van Nuys judge today...
now face the ultimate
judgment day of all--
one where sentencing comes
with no chance of reversal.
Freeze!
Come out with
your hands above your head!
I'm gonna come out,
but I didn't do it!
Don't shoot!
I didn't kill no cops!
Is this James Russell?
I'm on my way.
I cannot wait for you
to eat my ass.
Here it is.
Good afternoon.
I'm Detective Pickett...
and this is Williams.
I wondered if we might chat
about Franklin Hatchett.
Franklin's not here.
We're dealing
with a multiple homicide.
Would you just open the door?
Excuse you?
I'm sorry. Listen...
it would only take
a few minutes of your time.
We'd really appreciate it.
Please?
Thank you so much.
When was the last time
you spoke to him?
He left on the freak train
to Atlanta six weeks ago.
I haven't seen him since.
Do you think this is funny?
I got a busload of bodies
and a couple dead cops...
because of your gangbanger.
Franklin ain't no banger.
If I find out
you're helping him...
I'm going
to make your life miserable.
Back off, please.
Treat the lady with respect.
Can you help us out, Paula?
I swear,
I don't know where he is.
This is such bullshit!
You know...
It's OK.
All I'm saying is
if he tries to contact you...
give me a call.
It's so much better
if he turns himself in.
He stays out on the street,
he's gonna get himself killed.
I'm trying to protect him.
This is my card.
Will you give me a holler?
Thank you.
Keep it running.
This might be quick.
White boy.
What the fuck was that for?
That's for getting me busted.
What you bring a gun for?
'Cause you're wanted for murder.
I ain't murdered
no-goddamn-body.
I don't know that.
Now you know.
'Cause if I could,
I'd murder your ass right now...
coming down here with a gun.
Guns don't kill people.
Stupid motherfuckers
with guns kill people.
I'm enlightened.
Let me enlighten your ass.
Bring your monkey ass up here.
Got me running
all over goddamn town.
People shooting at me and shit.
You the one got me in this shit.
Ought to kick your ass
in the head.
Freezing.
I know. I was
in the motherfucker earlier.
Listen to me.
I want an exclusive.
A what?
The entire city
is looking for your ass.
The cops want payback.
How many times I got to tell you
I didn't kill no-goddamn-body?
Regardless,
they want your ass dead.
Franklin, I will protect you.
I'll get you turned in,
let you tell your story...
but I want the exclusive.
I'll hide you for the weekend.
It'll all be over on Monday.
I don't trust your ass.
How I know this exclusive shit
gonna clear my name?
I guess you don't.
But without me,
you'll probably end up dead.
They need someone to blame.
Right now, it's you.
What do you say?
I ain't staying
in this neighborhood.
I can't stay here
for no two days.
That's right. You can't.
What you talkin' about?
You're coming to my wedding.
Your wedding? Shit! Hell, no.
I ain't going nowhere.
Po-po looking for me.
Trying to kill me?
Staying on the low-low.
God damn.
How you do that?
Did a report once
on escape artists...
and the women who love them.
Teach me how to do that shit.
There's no time.
We got time.
I need you to take a shower,
shave, lose the earring...
and, please, do something
about that hair of yours.
What you talkin' about?
My 'do is tight.
Every cop in the city
is looking for that tight 'do.
I'll hook up the hair, but
I ain't touching the earring...
'cause I'm still a player!
I'm gonna make a phone call.
I don't think
there's any hot water left.
What?
You heard me.
Punk-ass white boy.
This tub better be clean.
Who is it?
Barclay, it's James.
How you doing?
I got Franklin Hatchett.
Don't play games with me.
Words like that give me
a stiffy.
At my age, I can't waste them.
I'm not kidding you.
He's at my place safe and sound.
Congratulations.
You're rehired.
I thought I was supposed
to clear out by Monday.
Didn't you say that?
You didn't really take
me seriously, did you?
You're Pulitzer material.
I've always said that.
I'll send a camera crew...
down to the 20th precinct
in an hour.
Not a chance. I'm going
to keep him until Monday.
For sweeps week.
Don't be foolish.
A bird in the hand
is worth a 10-share...
for the whole weekend.
Fuck you.
This is my story,
and you know it.
You're right. Monday it is.
Loser.
Freeze!
Vic Damone...
Get your hands on the car!
Vic Damone--
his music will last forever.
What the hell is a Vic Damone?
Vic Damone's Greatest Hits...
Ain't no greatest hit.
I ain't never heard it.
He thrilled the world...
when he married
actress Diahann Carroll.
Now he'll thrill you again...
How the hell an ltalian get
a fine black woman like that?
The timeless hits
of Vic Damone.
He can't sing.
Only reason she married him
'cause he got money.
Takin' all our sisters.
I'm James Russell.
Those stories
along with Andy Rooney...
tonight on 60 minutes.
I'm out the door.
People are already showing up.
I am so sorry.
Something important came up.
More important
than our rehearsal dinner?
Of course not.
And I'm bringing
somebody with me.
Who?
Old, dear friend of mine
from college.
Just kind of ran into him today.
Are you all right?
You sound funny.
I'm perfect.
I'll see you soon.
I love you.
I love you, too. Hurry up.
Fuck me.
I'm gonna start the car.
I'll meet you in the courtyard.
Kiss my ass!
Find something that fits
then move your ass! We're late!
This tub wasn't clean,
you dirty-ass white boy!
You had to pick that one,
didn't you?
This your ride?
Yes, and that's my favorite
fucking suit you're wearing.
I look good, don't l?
Don't get mad 'cause I look
better than you in your shit.
I should be
Ebony Man of the Month.
Is that something
to be proud of?
You wouldn't know nothin'
about that with your goofy ass.
You fuck up the suit,
and we got a problem.
We already got a problem.
Look at this shit!
You hustlin' son of a bitch.
Look who's talking.
At least I've worked
for everything I have.
You worked yourself
right into some rich pussy.
No wonder you don't give
a damn if I'm innocent.
Your ass gonna get
married and retire.
Let's get things straight
about tonight's dinner.
You don't speak
unless spoken to.
You stay by my side.
If you try
anything fucked up or funny...
I will kill you myself.
Just like you did
back on the docks?
I will beat your ass.
You ain't beatin' shit, homes.
We went to Stanford,
which is where?
How the hell I supposed to know?
It's in the Bay Area, where you
graduated with honors in '88.
And your name tonight
is Jonathan Smith.
Fuck the Jonathan Smith.
I'm me.
Do not say a word about
my fiancée's weight.
She's very sensitive about that.
You must have one
of them fat-assed
Taco Bell, McDonald-eatin',
big-booty-assed--
Mr. Cipriani.
How are you?
How many times I got to
tell you? Call me Dad.
-You're not getting nervous?
-Who wouldn't be?
That's true. Who's this?
This is
a very good friend of mine.
Vic Damone.
Junior.
He's Diahann Carroll's kid
and Vic Damone's kid.
So you're half and half ltalian.
Hey, paisan.
Me and your father?
Forget about it. Come here.
Mamma mia!
God, your house...
Magnifico!
Molto bella!
Tutti frutti!
Where'd you learn
to talk ltalian?
Did Vic talk to you in ltalian
when you were a kid?
All the time.
Here she is!
It's nice of you to show up.
I'm terribly sorry.
Fiancée Grace,
this is my friend Vic.
You're phat.
P-h-a-t--
Pretty, hot, and tempting.
I'm stunned by your phatness.
You're a lucky man to have
such a phat-ass fiancée.
She fine.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
You made it.
I thought you'd be off
covering that prison escape...
with the rest of
the low-life sensationalists.
Mother, give it a rest.
Actually, I am covering that
sort of indirectly, Mom.
How many times do
I have to tell you...
to call me Mrs. Cipriani?
Connie, this is Vic Damone Jr.
He's Jimmy's good friend.
Tell us what it was like
growing up in show biz.
Everybody's interested.
I had a lot of friends.
Junior Walker Jr.,
Sammy Davis Jr. Jr.
We hang out all the time.
And what do you do now,
Mr. Damone Jr.?
-I'm in--
-Sales.
-Retail?
-Seats.
On the stock exchange.
-Broker?
-Ticket scalper.
I can get you anything if you
let me know ahead of time.
He's a funny guy.
He's hysterical. Kills me.
How about
some nice Dom Pérignon '85?
How about some Colt .45?
Would you excuse me
for one second?
I need to talk to you.
What the fuck do you think
you're doing?
I'm mingling
with the rich folks.
I'm locking your ass
in the fucking closet...
for the rest of the weekend.
Don't even start with me.
You the one
brought me out here...
in Beverly Hills mingling
with these uppity-ass people.
I'm wanted for murder,
my life on the line--
What about my life?
I'm lookin' at your life.
Grace! What's up?
This is beautiful.
I couldn't be happier
for you and James.
It's about time
he settled down...
after all the women
he been through.
And those twins in school
wasn't his.
That was all a lie.
He had a lot of women.
He had all the women.
All the women, all the guys,
I fucked them all.
Here we go.
I'd like to propose a toast.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Everybody!
I'm going to propose a toast!
This is Vic Damone's son.
If you don't mind.
You're James' first,
his last, his everything.
And you're the answer
to all his dreams.
You're his sun, his moon,
his guiding star.
You're kind of wonderful,
that's what you are.
He knows
there's only one of you...
Isn't that Barry White?
There's no way
he could have made two.
You're all he's living for.
Your love...
he'll keep forevermore.
You're his first...
his last...
his everything.
That was beautiful.
I do what I can do
when I can do it.
Congratulations.
You got a phone?
Thank you.
You can see
this kid is ltalian.
He feels deep.
Hey, baby, what's up?
It's me.
Don't you "baby, it's me" me.
I saw your ass on the news,
talking you killed some cop.
What?
I just saw you on the news.
I didn't kill nobody!
You killed some cop!
Once again, you are in trouble!
What did you do anyway?
Don't yell at me!
Are you gonna let me talk?
Listen!
Stop watching the goddamn news!
Somebody set me up!
Where have you been
for the last 24 hours?
You better not be over
no girl's house!
I ain't over
at no goddamn girl's house!
I'm wanted! I ain't got time
to get no pussy!
I ain't fuckin' nobody but you.
What about this guy named
Carmine called here...
saying he's gonna kill us
if you don't give him $25,000?
I don't owe him
no goddamn $25,000!
We got him.
He's calling from
a 310 area code, a 274 prefix.
What's he doing
in Beverly Hills?
Lock the doors
and don't answer the phone...
and get under the bed!
I'm on my way!
Get under the--
Somebody bothering you?
Everything's cool.
Frank Sinatra Jr.
got in trouble again.
They got it down
to a one-block radius.
He's on Roxbury
between Sunset and Lexington.
They're gonna check on it.
Where do you think you're going?
I'm leaving. I'm out.
You're out?
Who'd you call, your partner?
Partner? What the hell
you talkin' about?
I called my girl.
She's pregnant,
and she needs me, and I'm out.
That is not part of our deal!
Damn our deal!
I ain't dealin' my life away.
Why you hustling me?
Why you won't just turn me in?
What you waitin' on?
I thought so.
This is bullshit.
You got me running--
I'm helping you.
You gotta help me, too.
I need your story
live on Monday.
It's sweeps week.
Fuck sweeps week!
I'm wanted for murder...
you talking about
a goddamn broom !
Get me a taxi!
What is your sweeps week thing
again?
You didn't tell me
where you're going.
You have to trust me.
I'm onto something big.
What am I
going to tell everybody?
You'll think of something.
I'll be back
first thing in the morning.
I love you.
I know.
You better not be lying to me.
What the hell
I got to lie to you for?
I happen to know
how your type operates.
My type?
Why the hell you take my type...
to your goddamn dinner
rehearsal for a damn story?
I'm stuck with you.
I figured your white ass out.
You have?
You're full of shit.
You one desperate-ass
middle-class white boy...
that don't give a damn who you
step on to get what you want.
Get your priorities straight.
My priorities?
Your goddamn priorities.
I'm not the one
wanted for murder.
I'm sick
of your smart-ass comments.
You know I ain't murdered
no-goddamn-body.
You the reason
why I'm in this shit.
I was minding my own business...
Iiving ghetto fabulous,
I wasn't messin' with nobody.
You fucked that up.
You know how much money I was
making down at that car wash?
A buck, 2.98?
I will slap the hell outta you.
You don't know
who you messin' with.
I don't even know
when I'm gonna slap somebody.
I be like, "Why did I do that?"
I don't know
when I be slappin' people.
Keep messin' with me.
I'm dangerous.
I'm scared of myself.
They call me "snap and pop..."
'cause I'll snap
and pop your ass in the mouth.
Don't mess with me.
Better watch your back.
Even in the shower,
eatin' at picnics...
you better watch your
goddamn back. Make a right.
There's my crib.
And there goes your stakeout.
Turn down here.
I know a shortcut.
She just turned the lights out.
You're up, sport.
What the hell is
wrong with you? It's me!
Don't take that tone with me.
I should crack
your thick-ass skull right now.
Leaving me here all alone!
Is this the kind of father
that you're gonna be?
I'll move back to Riverside.
Don't think that I won't.
Would you calm down?
What's up with the hair
and that suit?
You look like you stepped out
of a casket!
Calm down!
You know I ain't killed nobody.
It's me.
You know I need you.
Why you think
I came over here so fast?
I'm worried about you.
I'm sorry.
You know I love you.
She just
turned the lights back on.
Let's go.
Who is this?
And what is he doing here?
That's--
James Russell,
Channel 12 News.
The weatherman?
What are you doing with him?
That's just my white friend.
He gonna help me
get outta this mess.
But what about Carmine
and the money you owe him?
Don't worry about that
'cause he's lyin'.
I do not owe him no $25,000!
I owe him $7,000.
He added on interest.
I don't even know why I asked.
I'm sorry. Calm down.
Don't worry about it.
-How you doin'?
-I'm OK.
How the baby doin'?
He fine.
How my baby boy doin'?
You ain't
worrying about nothin'.
My baby come out with two toes,
I'm gonna kick your ass.
You've had the sonogram?
-What?
Sonogram? Did a three-part
exposé a few years back...
on pre-natal health care.
We discovered that not only--
Police. Open the door.
We know you're in there.
In a minute!
I don't know what else to say.
Gimme your pager number.
What for?
Open this fucking door,
or we're gonna break it in!
Anything go wrong, you page me.
You can reach me there.
Everything gonna be all right.
I'll take care of him.
-Police!
-Wait a minute!
Do you have a warrant?
What do you want?
We want your boyfriend.
Window!
You can't keep busting--
Shut up!
Wait for me!
Come on!
What the hell
are you shooting at?
He's a cop killer!
Don't be
trying to kill everybody.
For Christ's sake!
Right here. This is it.
Turn here.
All you've been doing
is bitchin'...
ever since we got together.
So I'm bitching.
I'm not used to getting shot at.
I'm not used to people getting
me into shit, so shut up.
That French dude
who killed those cops...
had a stamp on his hand
from this club.
A lot of Euro-trash
hang out here.
We're gonna go in here.
If we see him,
we're gonna call the cops...
get him busted,
and clear my name tonight.
Can I handle this?
Good evening.
James Russell, Channel 12 News.
We're doing
a report on local nightclubs.
I'd like to ask you
a few questions.
Oh, you're
the investigative reporter.
Yes, I am.
Get the fuck out of here.
You got
a lot of pull in this town.
I could do a report
on this shithole...
that'd close it down forever.
Fuck that.
If we can't go
to the Red Camel...
Red Camel comes to us.
What are you talking about?
Just come on.
-Where are you going?
-Shut the hell up.
Bring your ass on.
Gimme a quarter.
Hurry up and gimme a quarter!
Who are you calling?
It's Mike Vermishki.
Remember me?
You done fucked with me
for the last time!
There's a bomb in the building!
That's right!
A goddamn bomb in the building!
Get your ass out...
Fuck you!
There's a bomb in the building,
and it's fixin' to blow!
You better get your ass out
right now!
You have crossed the fucking--
Watch this.
Five, four, three...
two, one.
Move it!
Voilà.
That's him right there.
That's one right there.
-You sure?
-I'm sure!
That bitch fine.
Wait a minute.
Let's go.
This is crazy.
What the hell is--
When we get in here,
you don't say nothin'.
Only two white people
walked in here.
Keep your mouth shut, you'll
be the first one to walk out.
And another thing.
You ain't white, you mixed.
Your mama black and your daddy
Puerto Rican if they ask you.
What?
Aaron here?
Franklin want to talk to him.
Aaron don't know
no damn Franklin.
How the hell you know?
Tell him I was there when he
shot Baby Bro at MacArthur Park.
Where'd he shoot Baby Bro?
At MacArthur Park,
you big dumb--
Where'd he shoot him?
In the ass! Everybody know
he got shot in the ass!
Don't ever play me like that,
player-hater.
I'm sorry.
I was just playin'.
Black bastard.
What's happening?
What's up?
I tried calling you,
couldn't get through.
But anyway, I need your help.
I need some gats on credit.
Again?
Again? Last time,
you know that wasn't my mistake.
That was Little Johnny
who fucked up the money.
You know Little Johnny
is lnvisible Johnny now, right?
I went to the funeral.
That was fucked up what you did.
It was a closed casket
and everything.
But I appreciate this
if you do this.
You get me two courtside...
if it goes seven games,
on the floor...
and I don't mean
behind the backboard.
I gave you the wrong tickets
by mistake.
It's done.
If it goes 700 games, I got you.
Done.
What the fuck is this shit?
He's cool. He's just
a reporter from Channel 5 News.
Reporter?
What the hell--
What's he reporting on,
my lifestyle?
He gonna help me out!
Help you do what?
Help me to clear my name!
You fuck me up here...
the only thing your name
is gonna be good for...
is a goddamn tombstone.
He don't know nothin'
about you. He here for me.
He don't know nothin' about
the hos, guns, and drugs.
I won't bring no shit
down on you.
Look at me now.
How far we go back?
Elementary?
Jump rope?
Hide-and-go-seek?
Pitty-pat?
Red light, green light?
What would our mamas say
see us like this?
All the stuff we been through?
We boys.
Cool?
Come with me.
So you say you got problems?
Itty-bitty,
teeny-weeny problems.
Big fat-ass problems.
I got what you need.
There's no itch that an...
HK-MP5 can't scratch.
Unless you want a...
Uzi
with a Wilson suppresser on it.
Very nice.
Very...
urban.
I'd go with the Heckler & Koch.
It's got a closed bolt,
as opposed to the Uzi.
It's got a faster cyclic rate,
better sights, rear aperture.
It's German,
as opposed to lsraeli.
It's much more accurate than--
Look, Dan Rather.
You sure you not a cop?
I'm sure I'm not a cop.
I did a report last year
on street weapons.
If you don't shut up, the last
report you're gonna hear...
is this Uzi
going off in your ass.
I don't mean
to disrespect your shit...
but this is too heavy.
I need something lighter...
'cause we're gonna be doing
a lot of running.
See this here?
One or two of these.
This is all I need.
Couple of these, and I'm cool.
I'll pay you back.
I'm good for it.
What?
Call me if you get in trouble.
I'm gonna call you.
And thank you again.
I'm gonna get you
that money soon.
I just got
the lnterpol report back...
on the John Doe they picked up
at the airport yesterday.
This is our guy.
Raymond Villard.
Last known residence: Belgium.
He's wanted for killing a cop
in Paris...
convicted of a jewelry heist
in London...
wanted for killing someone else
in Cologne.
It goes on and on.
I don't think so.
This guy could turn up laying
flat on his face in that bus.
Forensics ain't done
with the bodies yet.
I still think Hatchett's
our man.
Not according to this.
Got a nice videotape
of your suspect here.
It's from the security camera
in the deli.
We'll see.
And now a live report
from the scene.
A cold-blooded murder...
Iast night in a deli
here in downtown L.A.
Homicide detectives have
identified the two gunmen...
through the use
of a surveillance camera tape.
We're told they are
Franklin Maurice Hatchett...
and an unnamed reporter
from Channel 12 News.
Hatchett is already wanted...
in connection with the death of
14 inmates and 2 policemen...
during
a daring prison escape at--
I have this late word just in.
Police have released the name
of the second suspect...
and he is James Russell
of Channel 12 News.
We'll continue to update you
on this breaking story...
as developments warrant.
Now back to you in the studio.
The eensy-weensy spider...
walked up the waterspout.
Down came the rain...
And washed--
How you doing?
-Morning, folks.
-Have something to eat.
I gotta talk to Grace.
I'll take a little something.
I'm a little hungry.
I was wondering when you was
gonna ask me to sit down.
I think we're interrupting
a very tender breakfast here.
That's cool. Is it cool?
The kids say it's cool.
Go take care
of your business with Grace.
Talk to Grace
as long as you want.
I'm gonna come and get you
when I'm through.
I love it, man.
Nervous about the wedding.
Best friend in the world.
Did you tell Vic
I want him to call me?
He said
he was gonna call you soon.
He was happy
to hear from you, too.
Terrific. What do you want
for breakfast?
Whatever y'all got.
I can eat anything.
You want some bacon and eggs?
Wait a minute. You're ltalian.
Make him a nice vilosh.
Put a nice gravy of ragu
and some sausages on the side.
Is that OKwith you?
OKwith me.
And give me
some ltalian grits on the side.
-Thanks, Ma.
-That's your mama?
That's how the rich stay rich.
Keep it in the family.
So how's the mistress
of the house this morning?
I've never been
anybody's mistress.
He was my first, my last,
my everything.
Baby.
Excuse me.
You pissed her off.
She always like that?
But she's worth it.
What's going on? Oh, shit!
What's in the paper?
Nothing.
So what'd you get the newlyweds
for their wedding gift?
I'll show you.
You got it already?
Come on.
This is another house.
How rich are you?
Loan me a million dollars.
You gonna loan it to me?
I was just playing.
How many people sleep
in this bed?
Me and Connie. That's it.
This is incredible.
Let me spend the night.
Anytime. You ready?
I'm ready? ls this the gift?
This is it.
That's nice. That's tight.
That's nice, but...
What?
-What's the matter?
-Nothing. That's cool.
That's all right.
You hooking them up
on some Liberace-type shit.
What's wrong with it?
That's Bulgari.
Forget about it. It's cool.
They're not gonna like it?
You know something.
Did they say something to you?
Forget about it.
I can't be saying nothing.
I'm not in the family like that.
Be a friend. Tell me.
If I tell you this,
you can't them I told you.
Why would I do that?
I happen to know that
the newlyweds want a dope ride.
We don't do dope
in this family.
Not dope. A ride.
My chauffeur
will take them anywhere.
Not a ride. I mean a car.
Oh, a car.
I got a lot of cars.
Which one did they want?
They want the Bentley?
The Rolls?
Not any type of car.
They want a European type-X
racer car.
Where am I gonna get that
by tomorrow morning?
I think we can get one.
I know a place.
I'll take these back.
Why don't you let me keep them?
I'll give them back to you.
I'm just playing, unless
you're gonna let me keep it.
You brought a killer
into my parents' house!
Are you even listening to me?
Franklin may be
a lot of things...
but he is not a killer.
-Trust me on this one.
-I am trying.
We're supposed to be
in this together.
We are.
-What about tomorrow?
-I'll be here.
You are wanted for murder.
We can't get married
when you're wanted for murder.
You're right.
I'm telling you, we're gonna
have fun at the Auto Expo.
Oh, fuck me.
Next item up
is a Mercedes 1957 gull-wing.
Only 1,400 of these were made.
Let's open up the bidding
at $100,000.
One hundred's there.
One hundred five now.
Go 110...110 out back.
One hundred fifteen
to the lady there. And 120...
All my old friends in here.
Where's Trump?
One hundred and ninety
thousand dollars.
How you doing?
How those 7-11 chains going?
Let me remind you that
Cary Grant drove this car...
in Monaco
while filming To Catch A Thief.
Cary Grant drove that car.
Is that the most beautiful car
you ever saw in your life?
That's not it.
I'll tell you when I see it.
What are you talking about?
It's beautiful.
Trust me. That's not it.
Three hundred thousand
there now.
Three hundred and ten.
Still bidding.
Three hundred twenty thousand
to you there.
And 30.
Still bidding strong there.
And 340,000 against you still.
Three hundred and fifty thousand
is now the bid.
Any advance? Last call.
All through.
All done at 350,000.
Sold to the gentlemen
in the burnoose...
with the three lovely ladies.
Thank you very much.
Now that car goes to Arabia.
I heard he didn't really
drive that car.
That's lke Turner's old car.
I seen that car.
-Who's lke Turner?
-Old pimp.
Do I have 120?
One hundred and twenty thousand
bid there. Thank you.
One hundred and thirty.
Still bidding here.
Forty thousand.
One hundred and forty thousand
is the bid.
And 150, still.
That's the one.
That's not it.
Do I hear 500,000?
And 500,000 I do.
And 550?
Five hundred and fifty thousand
there.
And 600,000 here.
And 650,000 there.
That's not it.
That's beautiful.
What do you mean?
That's not it.
The next item up on the block...
is a 1951 Jaguar XK-140
roadster...
custom built
for Princess Grace of Monaco.
Mint condition.
Bidding will commence
at $100,000.
-This is the one.
-You sure?
-I'm positive.
-Thank God.
One hundred and five.
Lovely 105.
Who'll give me 110?
One hundred and ten
there now.
Now 115.
One hundred and fifteen is bid.
Do I hear 120?
One hundred and twenty
is now the bid.
One hundred and twenty five?
One hundred and twenty five
here.
And 130?
One hundred and thirty
to you, sir?
One hundred and thirty he does.
One hundred and thirty
is now the bid.
Do I hear 135?
One hundred and thirty five
to the gentleman taking aim...
at this mechanical masterpiece.
Do I hear 140?
The gentleman
who's welcoming all challengers.
Do I hear 145?
One hundred and forty five
bid to my right now.
Suck my dick.
I believe that's 150.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Do I hear 155?
Still bidding strong now.
Do I hear 160?
One hundred and sixty
is bid in time to my left now.
Who is this guy?
I don't know.
I gotta use the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
We're in the middle of--
Who'll go 165,000?
Hello, police?
Y'all need to come out
to the auto auction right now.
The cop killer's down here.
They down here.
They shooting and shit.
Slapping people.
They acting a fool!
Cops wanna talk to you.
They on their way.
They wanna know
where to pick you up at.
You're dead.
The cops are on their way!
Hold up!
One of them dressed in black...
and the other one
dressed in a fucked-up tuxedo.
Hurry up!
People dying here!
One hundred and seventy five.
Still bidding strong.
Do I hear 180?
One hundred and eighty
is now the bid there.
One hundred and eighty five
thousand...
What the fuck is going on here?
What the hell
you doing down here?
You and I are gonna settle this
right here, right now.
Thanks to you,
I'm wanted for murder now, too.
I want some answers.
Me and Guy just down here
checking out some fly rides...
and macking some hos
and chillin'.
Imagine that.
Just like a "G" Dawg
on a fly tip...
flossin' with the posse,
cuttin' in the crib.
What the fuck does that mean?
I don't wanna have
to beat your ass...
but I will beat your ass!
Stay the fuck out of my face!
I'll be right back.
-You fucked up.
-You like that?
You done fucked up now!
Fucker.
Fuckin' with me?
Two hundred forty.
Do I hear 240,000?
Two hundred and forty thousand
bid there.
Two hundred and fifty thousand
if you wish, sir.
How you doing?
He won't give up.
Let's get out.
At 250,000, if you wish.
Fuck him.
Two hundred and fifty thousand
dollars!
dollars is bid here.
I believe
we've lost our competitor.
Two hundred and fifty
going once. Going twice.
Sold to the gentleman there.
Thank you very much.
You the man!
I'll meet you out front.
What?
Where you at?
Frenchy!
So this James is a murderer,
is that it?
No. James is innocent.
Is this other guy
Vic Damone's son, or isn't he?
I don't know.
So what are you telling me,
he's 100% moolie?
Who cares?
I had mom make him
a mozzarella omelet.
That lying
son of a bitch bastard.
There's no wedding.
You're not gonna marry
this James.
But we've got 300 people
coming here tomorrow.
Good. They come here,
they eat, they drink...
they sing,
they go the fuck home!
And what am I supposed
to tell them?
You tell them that our Grace
was about to be married...
to some no-good,
limp-dick bastard!
He is not limp-dicked.
I don't wanna hear that!
Please.
I love him, and I trust him.
Let's not jump to conclusions.
I'm gonna tell you something.
This James comes in here,
I break his legs.
And as far as Vic Damone Jr.--
That's not Vic Damone Jr.!
What the hell am I saying?
Have a drink.
Me, too.
You sure nobody followed you?
You sure?
Yes, nigger, I'm sure!
-Look under the table.
-What?
Look at that.
You done gone and done it now.
'Cause this scares me.
What you talking about?
This gonna take care of us
for the rest of our life.
We won't have to do shit else.
What we gonna do?
Where we gonna go?
We can go wherever the hell
we wanna go with this shit.
I was thinking about
buying a small country.
This is wrong.
This is right!
It can't get no righter!
This is the only way
out of this shit I'm in.
Here's the number
for this policeman.
You want me to call the cops?
You want me to call them
so they can shoot me.
My baby ain't gonna be
no fugitive.
You don't wanna call the cops,
fine.
Maybe that reporter
can clear this whole thing up.
Fuck him.
And don't give me that look
'cause it ain't gonna work.
Don't even give me that look.
I see you looking at me.
One more time.
Think.
Where are my diamonds?
Gimme a kiss.
Hey, James, that you?
I want the diamonds,
or your partner's dead.
Partner? I ain't got
no goddamn partner!
Who the fuck is this?
Listen to me.
I'm with some people
who've promised to kill me...
unless you give them
those diamonds...
the ones you forgot to mention!
What diamonds?
The fucking diamonds,
you prick!
Medulla alagata.
What?
Tell them to shoot you
in the medulla alagata...
right behind the ear.
You won't feel shit.
This isn't a joke.
I'm in some deep shit here.
Listen to me.
Three A.M.
Hangar number seven.
Long Beach airport.
Keep the diamonds
in the plastic bag.
They will be weighed.
Kiss my ass!
We meet where I say we meet,
French motherfucker.
What happened?
He hung up.
We meet on his turf,
then your ass be all alone.
Meet on my turf,
at least we got a chance.
He'll call back.
What'd I tell you?
All right, motherfucker,
this is the deal.
Watch your language!
Mama, I ain't know it you!
I ain't killed no cops.
Call me back.
Stop watching the news.
Don't be believing
everything on the news.
Who is this?
I'm listening.
This is the deal.
Fifty yard line,
Coliseum, three A.M.
And if Jimmy boy ain't alive...
you can kiss
them diamonds good-bye.
Tonight,
I'm gonna pay your ass off...
in diamonds.
Where's a piece of shit
like you get diamonds?
Coliseum, three A.M.
Williams.
Hey, cop.
This is Franklin Hatchett.
Meet me at the Coliseum,
three A.M.
Be there.
We'll be there.
That was Hatchett.
He wants to turn himself in.
I'm gonna go tell the captain.
No way, buddy.
This is our collar.
You and me. Us.
Let's go.
Roland, it's me.
Wake your old ass up.
What do you want?
I need you down at the booth
tonight.
I'm gonna owe you for this one.
Yo, Aaron?
Pick up the phone!
You said call you
if I need you.
I need you
at the Coliseum tonight.
Don't let a brother down.
Hatchett, drop the gun!
What the fuck y'all doing?
It's just for protection.
Don't you even scratch
your skinny, stanky ass...
or you're fucking dead.
Wait a minute!
I'm the motherfucker
who called y'all.
The dude you're looking
for is on his way.
Y'all just calm the fuck down.
Y'all gonna get medals
for this shit.
I'm helping y'all out.
Y'all trying to kill a nigger.
Hand over the gun!
I ain't handing over shit.
Hand over that gun right now.
How do I know y'all
ain't gonna shoot me?
I'm gonna shoot you
if you don't!
I'm gonna shoot, then!
We'll be dead motherfuckers!
-Hand over the gun!
-Shoot, then, shoot!
Shut the fuck up!
I ain't putting nothing down.
Nobody's gonna shoot you
if you hand me the gun.
You gotta trust somebody.
I don't trust nobody.
Lower the gun.
You lower your gun.
Hand it over to me.
Nobody wants to die.
Come on, nice and easy.
Just hand me the gun.
If I give you the gun,
and he shoots me...
I'm gonna kick your ass.
He will not shoot you
if you give me the gun.
Control that white boy.
Backup's on the way...
and you're gonna tell me
where the diamonds are.
What are you talking about,
backup's on the way?
And whoever said something
about diamonds?
Lieutenant, what the hell's
going on around here?
You son of a bitch.
You just killed my partner.
You just killed
your goddamn partner!
This is your gun.
Where are the diamonds?
You have my diamonds.
You three go that way.
You two go with Guido.
Find Franklin
and hold him for me.
Hey, Roland, wake up, man!
I know you're watching me!
These motherfuckers
are trying to kill me!
Wake the fuck up!
I need you right now!
Put me on the screen!
Bonjour, motherfucker.
Listen up. This is the deal.
Let my boy go, and
I'm gonna give you your shit.
So you can stop
fucking with me...
and take your old ass
back to France.
He does make a strong point.
Come on.
Get up.
I got $15 million in diamonds.
Sounds to me like you
promised them to someone else.
I don't know
who the hell that is.
I know who it is,
but I didn't say...
we was the only people
that wanted the diamonds...
but I'm the only one
who know where they at.
I got a feeling
I put a bullet in your nuts...
you're gonna tell me
where they're at.
Stop playing.
You can't shoot
a nigger in his nuts.
I need my nuts.
If you kill me,
you won't find them diamonds.
You need me. Trust me.
Believe in me.
What about them?
Forget them.
I figure for 10 million,
your boys will do their thing.
Ten million?
I thought it was 15 million.
What you think I'm doing
all this running around for?
I want some diamonds, too.
I ain't doing this shit
for free.
Look at your stingy ass.
The second we get those stones,
stick him.
Watch out!
One more step!
I was just going
to get diamonds.
Then get 'em for me now.
Fuse time, 20 seconds.
Or was it 10?
I'm ready for another close-up,
Mr. DeMille.
What the fuck's wrong with you?
What you shootin' for?
I'm the only motherfucker that
know where the diamonds is...
so if you kill me,
you won't find 'em.
So tell your boys
to stop shooting...
or you ain't getting shit.
I want to report a shootout at--
I'll hold.
You're messing up everything.
Shut up and keep moving.
Who the fuck you shooting at?
I want those diamonds!
Come on!
First, I'm gonna shoot
your right knee.
Then I'm gonna shoot
the other one.
You got that, homey?
Until you tell me
where my diamonds are.
That really must have hurt.
Kick his ass!
We gotta go.
Don't you ever say
I'm your goddamn homey!
OK, what?
OK, we done fucked up!
Listen.
I'm sorry I got you busted.
I want you to know,
for what it's worth...
I never doubted you.
Never once.
That ain't worth shit now
'cause we fixin' to die!
But thanks anyway.
You're welcome.
Hold this.
That was beautiful.
Follow me.
Let's go.
We almost there.
I get the feeling you stole from
the wrong bunch of bad guys.
You're right.
This shit ain't worth dying for.
I'm gonna give 'em
what they want.
Fuck this.
Sweet Jesus.
We surrender!
Stop, everybody!
We were just bullshitting.
I got your shit.
Is this what you want?
Come and get it!
Don't worry.
He won't get far.
And that's when
the L.A. Coliseum...
turned into a virtual war zone.
Among the dead,
Raymond Villard...
Ieader of a highly sophisticated
international smuggling ring...
and the man responsible
for Friday's prison break.
Also dead, LAPD detective
Bobby Pickett.
A dirty cop
who was Villard's inside man.
I have with me now
Franklin Hatchett...
the man once believed
to be responsible...
for the events and the chaos
that led to last night's mayhem.
Anything you'd like to add?
First of all,
I told y'all I was innocent.
For those y'all
that thought I was guilty...
y'all know what y'all can do.
Mama, I love you. I'm OK.
Paula, I love you, too.
I'm gonna be home later on.
We gonna party.
Cook some chicken
and some cornbread...
and some kool-aid...
and I'm gonna be back
at the car wash Monday morning.
Everything on sale,
half price. Peace out!
Thank you.
I'm James Russell.
This has been
a Channel 12 News exclusive.
If anyone can show just cause...
why this couple
should not be wed...
please speak now
or forever hold your peace.
The ring, please?
That's not the ring.
No shit.
Relax.
It's a wedding gift. Take it.
This is a sacred event.
I know it's sacred.
This is sacred, too.
Just take it. It's legal.
Don't nobody know about it.
How many did you keep?
Enough.
Now get married.
Take it.
Lord, forgive me.
He will.
You may now kiss the bride.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org