Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Yeah! You got asbestos, all right!
I'll bet it's up
in the ceiling, mostly!
Shouldn't take me more
than a day or two to remove it.
(Silence)
OK, then.
Um, uh, so, we're gonna go upstairs!
All right, well,
we'll all go upstairs!
Yeah.
OK, then. Yeah.
What are you doing?
- He's not listening any more.
- Oh.
Good. Well, you're the expert.
I hope you can take care
of this, whatever it takes.
We've been trying
to catch this menace all week.
Here's your problem.
Normal people are not...
psychologically equipped
to catch mice.
You have to get inside their mind.
You have to know what
they want... need.
You have to think like a mouse.
If you can do that...
if you can think like a mouse...
you can anticipate their moves.
Then, boom! Sayonara, mouse.
Well, you got some great stuff...
Whoa! Never touch that!
(Screaming)
- All right!
- What is it?
The big one.
It's a flea bomb!
Works on mice too.
It better. Because we
can't handle any more intrusions.
Sure. That's how you perceive it.
But to that mouse,
you are the intruder.
(Shouting)
We can make
enough string to meet our orders.
Just so we can keep the LaRue.
- Good luck.
- Wait! Where are you going?
I have to run a little errand.
All you have to do
is make $1200 worth.
Light a match,
they're frightened by fire!
(Shouting)
(Straining)
(Screams)
Unsanitary creature.
Defecating... in the dining room.
0915. Evidence found.
Mus communis. Ugh. Male.
Ten to, uh, twelve
centimetres long,
with a... hmm...
What's this?
A slight calcium deficiency.
That's interesting.
Hi. This is Ernest Smuntz
of Smuntz String.
Is this Zeppco International?
Vinny? Hi, Vinny.
Oh, I'm glad I can call you Vinny.
My brother and I have decided
to reconsider your offer.
I'd love to discuss
selling our factory to you.
Oh, no, not at the office.
How about Ellman Square
under the big clock at noon?
(Horn honking)
(Brakes screeching)
(Chiming)
(Knocks)
Uh, you, you must be
Mrs Lars Smuntz?
I'm afraid that status
is in transition.
Oh, well, is Lars in? I'd like to
discuss preparations for the auction.
The auction?
(Panting)
Careful, Lars.
You might catch a cold.
April!
You look like you could use
some warming up.
(Caesar) 1300 hours. I've activated
the Squeak Seeker 2000.
I'm about to join with the prey.
I'm experiencing malfunction
with the screen. Stand by.
Junk.
Nothing works.
Ah, nuts!
(Yelling)
EKG, a C-spine, a chest x-ray
and pelvis. Now move!
$1200...
Mr Smuntz, you've been hit by a bus.
I feel fine. What time is it?
You may have had a concussion.
Doc, I have to get out of here.
I still have a chance.
We saved your hat.
- I'm sorry. Are you family?
- Yes, we are sisters.
There's some paperwork
I need you to fill out.
I don't even know them!
Oh, I'm Hilde, and this is Ingrid.
- We are hair models from Belgium.
- Belgium. How exotic.
Doc. I need to find a phone before
I miss out on the deal of my life.
- He's delirious.
- I am not their brother!
- I don't have any sisters!
- Are you OK? I came when I heard.
Why are you wearing a pink overcoat?
Because April gave us the $1200!
She gave you the money?
She didn't hear about the auction?
I didn't even tell her about the
auction until after she took me back.
She just showed up at the factory
and begged me to take her.
(Sighs) We made love in a way
I've only ever seen in nature films.
Wow. I almost can't believe it.
I can open up another restaurant,
you're back with April,
you can even keep
that worthless factory.
It's funny
you call the factory worthless,
because there's something I probably
should have mentioned...
Yeah? Well, I guess
I have something to confess too.
Hey, isn't that Caesar's truck?
- Oh, my God!
- Caesar! What happened?
- Please, he's not well.
- Did you kill the mouse?
What's that? Horse?
Fiendish! I won't eat it. (Yells)
(Clicking teeth and squeaking)
How'd you find him?
911 call. No voice, but we heard
screaming in the background.
He was locked in a trunk
in the attic.
We'll call you if we get any leads.
(Rewinding)
What's that?
(Footsteps, door creaking)
(Caesar) 'Put that down.
What is that? ' (Yelling)
(Muffled groaning, crashing)
'That tickles! '
(Screaming, banging)
I don't think we're dealing
with an ordinary mouse.
(Crashing)
My kitchen!
Looks like Caesar decided
to make himself a sandwich.
(Ernie) Pickles, arugula and capers.
He toasted the side
with the cheese...
but not the other side,
so the arugula doesn't wilt.
How did he know that?
- Hello.
Ow!
(Yells)
Aha!
- Do you see him?
- Yeah, I see him.
Lars, I'm stuck!
Get me out of here! I can't breathe!
- I-I'll get a flashlight.
- Hurry!
(Hissing)
- Here, Ernie, I got it.
- I can see that.
Wh... Oh!
Hang on, Ernie.
The flashlight's broken.
- OK, Ernie. I got a light.
- Great.
(Sniffing)
(Ernie) Lars,
do you smell something?
Smells like gas.
(Screaming)
(Lars groaning)
(Strangled groans)
(Whimpering)
(Both whimpering and muttering)
(Lars) What are you gonna do?
Kill that unspeakable thing.
- Come on, Ernie...
- Stand back!
I'm a man on a mission!
- This is how accidents happen!
- (Laughing)
- Come on, put the gun down.
- I'll blow his furry head off.
And splatter his devious mouse brain
from here to kingdom come!
No, no! You'll blow
a hole in the wall.
It'll be worth it!
Think of the auction! For God's sake!
Think of the money! They'll cut our
price if there's bullet holes.
- The money?
- Yeah, the money, the moola.
- (Ernie) There he goes.
- Shoot! Shoot!
Yes... You hit the piano!
You hit the piano...
- Look...
- Shh!
What are you, crazy? The only thing
you haven't hit so far is the mouse!
Give somebody else a chance
with that gun.
- You're doing a wonderful job.
- (Tin rolling)
Whoa! You got him!
(Laughing)
(Lars) G-g-get him!
- See you in hell, mouse!
- (Laughing)
Fire!
God, I hate that mouse!
(Phone ringing)
(Ernie) 'After the beep,
start talking.'
(Vinny) 'Mr Smuntz,
this is Vinny from Zeppco calling.
'We waited in the square for an hour,
but you never showed.
'We do not appreciate
being treated this way,
'especially after your brother
already turned down our offer.
'Consider our proposal withdrawn.'
(Dialling tone)
- Betrayed by my own brother!
- Betrayal?
Don't talk to me about betrayal. You
should have told me about that offer!
- Half that factory is mine.
- And half is mi...
And half is mine, including the half
that you tried to sell.
And would have,
if it hadn't been for that bus!
Bus? You can't leave well enough
alone, can you? You ruin everything!
Me? You... you blame me for this?
Look! You blew a hole in the floor!
I distinctly remember
somebody yelling, "Shoot!"
You've never listened to me before!
- And you know why?
- Why?
Because I have no respect for you!
Spending your whole life
in that stupid factory!
It's tragic.
You think I didn't have
ambitions of my own in my life?
- Come on. You loved string.
- I didn't love string!
You and Pop were always running
something through your fingers.
It didn't matter what I did!
I made a special rack
of lamb for his 70th birthday...
- Oh, no!
- Yes! You remember.
I slaved over that meal,
making sure everything was perfect.
Did he say, "Thanks, Ernie,
it was delicious"? No.
He only noticed the string
I had tied it with.
He was crazy!
But I still wanted his approval.
I didn't leave, Lars. I was cast out.
There you go again!
Blaming everything else but yourself.
You think you're a success! Huh?
Well, you... can't... cook!
- I hate you!
- And I hate you!
- Not as much as I hate you!
- Yeah?
Yeah. Double. Double!
Oh, give me something!
I'm gonna brain you!
Here it is!
Oh, yeah, give it to me! Go ahead!
(Ernie, laughing) You killed him!
I-I didn't even know he was there!
All the trouble we'd have saved
if we'd just thrown fruit at him!
(Lars) Look! H-He's still breathing!
Kill him! Kill him!
Find a blunt object!
There. Let him have it.
- I-I...
- What are you waiting for?
- I can't just hit him.
- Why not?
Well, look at him. He's pathetic.
Pathetic? He's Hitler with a tail.
This is The Omen with whiskers.
Nostradamus didn't see this.
- W-well, he's a living thing.
- Not for long. Gimme that!
I can't!
(Sobs) God!
Look at him just lying there.
It just doesn't feel
very sportsmanlike.
Do something! He's coming to.
(Scratching)
Ah, I forgot to put holes in the box.
(Laughing wickedly)
Hasta la vista,
you little rat bastard!
- Come on. We got work to do.
- Two days till pay-day, my friend.
It's the architectural find
of the decade. Oh, let's go...
- Shall we?
- Yes.
- It wasn't easy, but we made it.
- Mm-hmm.
Ernie, I want you
to have something.
Pop's lucky piece of string.
- I'm glad you kept it.
- He, uh, he wanted us to share it.
I don't know why, but...
I think if he were here right now,
he'd be proud of you.
I think he'd be proud of us.
Hello, ladies.
How magnificent! Welcome!
Lars, you remember Ingrid and Hilde.
(Both) Hello.
(Ernie) Ladies, your hair
is positively biblical!
(Together) Oh, thank you.
Well, if you will excuse me,
I have to check on my crepes.
Keep the champagne coming. The
more they drink, the higher they bid.
You boys put on quite a shindig here.
Thank you so much, Mr Falko.
You know, it would be
very, very sad...
if you boys put on this auction
and nobody bid.
That would put a real crimp
in our evening, but...
there's no danger of that.
I don't know. There's a lot of
Eurotrash scarfin' the shrimps.
I tell you what.
You call off the auction... now...
and I will write you a cheque...
for ten millions.
As insanely generous as that is,
I have to decline,
but I appreciate
your thoughtful concern.
Enjoy the party.
Are you interested in spooling?
Oh, sure. My father...
I mean, my brother and I
own a string factory.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
I would love to see
your factory sometime.
Really?
April. What a surprise.
Dropping by for no reason, I suppose?
Does a wife need a reason?
Oh, are you entertaining?
- You mean "ex-wife"?
- Not quite yet.
- Ah, hakuna matata.
- This crepe... c'est magnifique.
- The raisins are a nice touch.
- Good, aren't they?
Raisins?
(Screams)
Ladies and gentlemen,
please take your seats.
We are about to start the auction.
I don't know whether to
congratulate you or wish you luck.
- Wish us luck!
- Hello, April.
- Oh, hello.
- Nice to see you again.
- I didn't know you knew our lawyer.
- It's just an expression.
Thank you, for joining us
for this momentous occasion
the auction of our one item,
- the missing LaRue.
- (Applause)
I would like to introduce the owner
of this architectural wonder,
- Mr Ernest Smuntz.
- (Applause)
Thank you, all, for coming.
When my father left this
extraordinary house
to my brother Lars...
and myself, uh, we...
had no idea what surprises
were in store for us or...
what was going to happen next.
(Ernie)
Uh, when Quincy Thorpe of the, uh...
Historical Society
told us of its value,
you, uh... you could have KNOCKED...
us over with a feather. We...
didn't know what... HIT US!
(Bangs gavel)
The renovation was exhausting
but ultimately rewarding.
- The house was in terrible disrepair
- (Murmuring)
But nothing that a few nails...
(Banging)
And old-fashioned
elbow grease couldn't fix.
- People are eager to start bidding.
- What? The bidding?
- The bidding!
- All right. Thank you.
- Thank you, Mr Smuntz.
- (Scattered applause)
No matter what happens, keep going.
Built in 1876, the last LaRue
in existence has five bedrooms...
- Did you see him? I thought so.
- Yes!
- He ate the string.
- What?
The string. Pop's lucky string!
The son of a bitch ate it!
- Why didn't you tell me you saw him?
- I didn't, but I found this.
- You should have weighed him.
- I'm sorry.
- Did you see where it went?
- It can't go far.
Well, shall we start
the bidding at $1 million?
Now, we all know we're here
to bid on the missing LaRue.
Shall we start at $500,000?
$500,000
from the gentleman from Japan.
- Now, can I hear a million?
- A million!
- I'll give you one and a half.
- I have $1.5 million. Two?
(Gasping) There he is!
(Auctioneer) Ladies and gentleman,
all the carpets and tapestries...
- are from Northern Turkey.
- Oh!
Now, can I have an advance on 1.5?
May I have two?
Can I have two,
ladies and gentlemen?
- Two million!
- I have $2 million.
I have $2 million, ladies and
gentlemen. Can I have an advance?
Can I have an advance on $2 million?
I'd like to draw your attention
to the Lincrusia details...
of the gold and silver-leafed
copper and pewter.
Ladies and gentlemen, can I have
an advance? An advance on $2 million.
May I hear $3 million? I have three
from the lady from New York City.
- What are you doing?
- Uh, uh, uh... nothing!
Get your hand
out of there immediately!
Wait! Wait just a minute!
- Wait!
- Now, may I hear $4 million?
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
(Man) Four million.
- Ooh!
- $4 million from the gentleman.
I got it!
Uh, the sheikh bids $5 million.
Thank you, sir. I have $5 million.
- $5 million.
- (Hysterical laughing)
Any advance on $5 million?
Ladies and gentlemen, $5 million.
An advance? Ladies and gentlemen,
it's the missing LaRue.
The bidding stands at $5 million.
(Lars) I've got you now!
- Hold on tight, I'll get it out.
- (Unzips)
Uh, $5 million for the missing LaRue.
- Have you got it yet?
- I'm not sure.
Ladies and gentlemen,
will someone give me $6 million?
- Six million.
- Thank you, sir.
Hilde, the spool is smoking!
May I have an advance?
An advance, ladies and gentlemen.
Can I have an advance on six?
The bidding stands at $6 million.
- $7 million.
- $7 million. Thank you.
- Any advance on seven?
- (Laughs)
(Screaming)
Keep her away from the walls!
The house is priceless!
C-c-can I have 7.5?
(Confused shouts)
I have $8 million over there.
$8 million going once,
$8 million going twice...
$8 million?!
You should have taken the cheque!
You shut up! You...
- Ten millions!
- $10 million. Can I have 11?
$11 million
from the gentleman from Japan.
- (All shrieking)
- 12. 13. 14. 15.
Aha!
- $16 million from Ernie Smuntz.
- No!
- 17 million!
- $17 million. Thank you, sir.
Any advance on 17?
Good idea.
When I say, turn it on full blast.
We'll flush him out.
Now!
- $18 million.
- $18 million from the lady.
You don't have that kind of money.
- Ernie?
- Not now.
- 20 millions.
- 20 million. Can I hear 21?
$21 million from the gentleman.
- Any advance?
- 22 million. That's my last offer.
22 million going once...
- 25 millions.
- $25 million dollars.
Thank you, sir. $25 million.
The bidding stands at $25 million.
Do I have an advance?
$25 million going once,
$25 million going twice...
(All screaming)
Going... going...
(Indistinct grumbling)
Hey! Don't go!
The water was just a...
a demonstration of...
of how durable...
a LaRue really is.
How about that?
Now you know this house
will last forever.
(Laughing)
- Pop's lucky string.
- I guess we got him.
Yeah, I guess we did.
(Snoring)
(Machinery starting)
What was that?
Lars! Look!
It's string.
It's cheese.
The factory has been retrofitted
to manufacture cheese-based products.
- I see.
- This is our new lactose-free line.
- What is that?
- That's quality control.
Here you go. Knock yourself out.
Oh. No good, huh? Otis, more curry.
OK. Try this one.
Huh? It's mozzarella and herring.
You can taste the herring, right?
I've got an idea
for a caviar-brie swirl
and peanut butter and jelly for kids.
But I really want
to talk about marketing.
You should be our spokesperson.
I know some people who've used
a mouse as a spokesperson.
You see, I want to turn this into the
string cheese factory of tomorrow...
Resynced by Climax69
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org