Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Five, six, seven, eight...
nine, 10.
I always know where I am
by the way the road looks.
Like I just know that
I've been here before.
I just know that
I've been stuck here...
like this one fucking time before,
you know that?
Yeah.
There's not another road anywhere
that looks like this road.
I mean, exactly like this road.
It's one kind of place.
One of a kind.
Like someone's face.
Like a fucked-up face.
Where do you think
you're running, man?
We're stuck here
together, you shit.
Don't worry.
Everything's gonna be all right.
I know. It's okay.
I know, you're sorry. I know.
# The cattle are prowlin'
The coyotes are howlin'#
# Way out where
the doggies bawl #
# Where spurs are a-jinglin'
a cowboy is singin'#
# This lonesome cattle call #
#He rides in the sun
till his day's work is done #
#And he rounds up
the cattle each fall #
Walt.
- Walt.
- Yeah, Mike?
You think, um, that you could
spot me 10 more dollars?
Ten dollars? What's the matter?
You can't get it from your dad?
My dad and I don't get along too well.
You know that, Walt.
We're not getting
along that well either now, are we?
No. We don't get along too well...
or else he wouldn't have gone out
and drowned himself at Boxcar Canyon.
- Again?
- Yeah.
He hit the water this time?
- He survived the first time. This time—
- Oh, God.
You're the only one I can ask.
You know that, Walt.
Please! I'll owe you a date.
How about that?
I'll owe you a date. Please.
Oh, God, crying tears. Hold on.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Don't worry.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Don't worry. Everything's gonna be all right.
Here. Now, mind the carpet. It's white.
Give me your shoes.
Mmm. Mmm.
Okay, just a sec.
Put these on...
so you don't make a mess.
I am so lucky.
I was born on April 4, 1944.
That's 4-4-44.
If you add that up,
it comes to 16.
One, six.
One plus six is seven.
Luckiest number of all.
- You know your math.
- It's more than math, Mike.
It's...
immaculate perfection.
Oh.
Boy, this place is a mess.
Yeah, let's make it immaculate.
- Okay.
#Deep night #
#Stars in the sky above #
#Moonlight #
#Lighting our place oflove #
#Night winds #
#Seem to have gone to rest #
# Two eyes #
Faster, little Dutch boy.
Harder.
Yeah, that sound. That sound.
# Vow that you'll love me always #
#And be mine alone #
- I'm all done.
- #Deep night ##
And now, my lucky 44th...
little Dutch boy...
you must scrub...
Daddy Carroll.
This chick's living
in a new car ad.
Feels like a dream.
A girl never picks me up,
much less a pretty, rich girl.
They don't?
I don't know why that is.
This is a nice home.
- Do you live here?
- Yes.
I don't blame you.
Oh.
Hey.
What up, Scott? What up, Gary?
Hey, it's Mikey the dike.
You men make yourselves comfortable.
I'll be right back.
There are cokes in the refrigerator.
Help yourselves.
She's cool. Shejust likes to have three guys
'cause it takes her a while to get warmed up.
It's normal. Nothing kinky.
Yeah.
Hey, dude, did you get into that
Sinéad O'Connor concert last night?
- What? To —To the Sinéad —
- The chick with the bald head.
I- I've never been
to a concert before, dude.
This is nice.
Backyard.
Oh, shit.
He always does this.
I'm surprised he can exist like this.
How do we know he's okay?
Well, he's not dead. Listen.
He's not dead. He's just passed out.
It's a condition.
He really scared the shit
out of that lady.
What causes it? Sex?
Narcolepsy doctors are saying it's brought on
by certain chemical reactions in the brain.
Comes about in situations of stress.
Some hustler, huh?
Well, where are we
gonna take him?
We can't just leave him here.
Come on, Mikey.
Hey, Mike, you stay here.
When you wake up, come back into town.
I'll be waiting for you.
You'll be safer here in this
comfy neighborhood than in the city.
- I grew up in a neighborhood like this.
And my dad —
He has more fucking
righteous gall...
than all the property
and people he lords over...
and those he also created —
Like me, his son.
I almost get sick
thinking I am a son to him.
You know you have to be
as good as him to keep up.
You have to be able
to lift as big a weight.
to throw that weight as far...
or make as much money,
or be as heartless.
My dad doesn't know
that I'm just a kid.
He thinks I'm a threat.
No, I won't listen.!
I won't listen to you.!
Hey, Scotty.! Come on, you big stud.!
When you wake up,
wipe the slugs off your face.
Get ready for a new day.
I never thought I could
make it as a real model.
You know,
fashion-oriented modeling.
'Cause I'm better at full-body poses.
It's all right so long as the photographer
doesn't come on to you...
and expect something
for nothing.
I'm trying to make a living.
I like to have a professional attitude.
Of course, if the guy
can pay me, hell yeah.
Here I am for him.
I'll sell my ass.
Do it on the street
occasionally for cash.
Or I'll be on the cover of a book.
It's when you start doing things for free
that you start to grow wings.
Isn't that right, Mike?
- What?
- Wings, Michael.
You grow wings and become a fairy.
What do you care about money?
Shit, you got plenty.
Why don't you go ahead
and do whatever it is that you do—
I can only imagine what that is—
for free?
Is that right, sweetie?
So, how much is a lot of money, honey?
What are you doing on the cover
of that magazine? Slumming?
Actually, Mikey's right.
I am going to inherit money.
A lot of money.
Hi.
- What's happening?
- Nothing.
- You want a lift?
- A lift?
Yes.
Isn't this that, uh — that lady's car?
- What's her name?
- Alena.
- Is she a friend of yours?
- No, not really.
- She's a very good friend of mine.
- Good.
Any friend of Alena
is a friend of mine.
- You want to be my friend?
- No.
My name is Hans.
I'm from Germany.
- Now I live in America selling pieces for cars.
- Mm-hmm.
- Say, why don't you get in?
- No.
I take you wherever
you want to go.
- Where you want to go?
- Home.
- Get in the car.
- No.
This guy's a pervert,
I can tell, man.
Why don't you go home?
Go the fuck home.
- How did we get home?
- That German guy, Hans.
He brought you downtown.
You were passed out.
He said he was heading to Portland,
so I asked him for a ride.
For some reason, I'm forgetting
a German guy named Hans.
Well, you were sleeping.
So, how much do you make
off me when I'm asleep?
Just a ride, Mike.
I don't make anything.
What, you think I sell your body
while you're asleep?
No, Mike, I'm on your side.
Gary's up here somewhere.
He left about three days ago.
He flew up here with a...
Hairdresser.
Exotic.
I heard something about Bob
coming up here to town. Is that true?
- You hear anything about that?
- Bob.
I don't know.
I hope he's in town.
- We'll have fun if Bob's in town.
- Yeah, I wouldn't mind seeing him.
Hey, didn't you two have like a —
I kind of remember you
having, like, this real heavy, uh —
- Thing?
- Thing. A heavy thing goin', right?
- Yeah, we had a real heavy thing going.
- Huh.
- He was fucking in love with me.
- That's what I thought.
- Yes.
- He taught me better than school did.
I love Bob more than my father.
I'd say I love Bob more
than my mother and my father.
Yeah, I wouldn't mind seeing him.
I'm — I'm hoping that he comes to town.
Hey, you dick.!
Scotty, my friend.
Ah, you — Hey. You like that, huh?
You like that.
My new Nikes.
My new bracelet.
It says Rudy, though,
but that's cool.
My new Calvins.
What a dickhead.
So stupid.
Not when I'm eating.
Don't blow it in my face.
It's the smoking section.
Um, this guy books up
in a black Porsche around the corner.
Uh, I'm asking my friend if,
you know, this guy's okay, if he's cool.
They say—They say,
"Yeah, he'll treat you really good.
"He'll, uh, you know —
He'll — He'll pay you what you want.
He'll, you know — He'll smoke weed with you.
He'll do whatever."
I hadn't dated before or tricked...
or done anything like that before,
so I went with this guy.
- Blew it off.
- Well— Uh—
"Let's go to— Let's go to the park.
Let's go to Washington Park. "
So, I said, "Okay. That's cool.
Let's go to Washington Park then. "
And, uh, all of a sudden, before I know it —
I mean, I already laid down the law
before I got into the car.
I told him what I do
and what I don't do.
So, uh, we got up there, and he just
started doing whatever he wanted.
My first date was in Portland.
I was, um —
I was hanging out at the City Club.
I was frying really hard
on acid and speed.
There was this big black guy
who had a lot of eight balls...
of speed and a lot of money.
And, uh, he wanted to get
his dick sucked.
And, uh, I was pretty broke,
and he offered me 60 bucks...
and a bunch of speed.
- So, I went up to his hotel—
- I guess you're just gonna starve.
What she's feeling sorry for herself for?
What's that all about?
So, the plan was, uh—
He was on the third floor.
So my buddy Scott would
hang out on the street on a bench.
When I got up to his room, I was gonna
toss the money out the window to Scott.
There's not really much I could do.
I was up in the — in the woods, in a thicket.
I couldn't get out or anything like that.
I wouldn't do what he wanted me to do.
So, he just kind of flipped out
all over me.
He basically raped me.
He put a fuckin' wine bottle up my butt, right?
It was like —
It was, like, horrible.
So, we get up there in the room,
and he, like, just—
He starts getting naked and jackin' off and shit.
And I start gettin' freaked out.
And I say,
"No, I don't want to do this date."
I say, "Let's go down to the street, and I'll
get the money back from my friend Scott.
And we'll just —we'll cancel it, right?"
So, we go down to the street
to get the money back...
and Scott's, like, long gone, you know.
What's this? Ooh!
So we're hanging out, and I'm all, "Wait.
He'll be right back. Let's just wait for him. "
So, we wait about five minutes, and he starts
telling me how he's gonna kick my fuckin' ass.
And how my friend's gone and how he's gonna
kill me and all this shit and beat me up.
So I had to go upstairs
and do the date anyway. And, um —
This black guy, he had
a big old fucking cock and shit.
And, um, it was this totally
awful experience, um —
And that was — that was my first date.
I never did another one until a year later.
Jesus. The things we've seen.
Do you remember a thing
since we moved from graffiti bridge?
No more of that, Budd.
Hey, Scotty!
Here comes that fat guy!
- He owes me money!
- Who?
You know, the fat one, Pigeon.!
"I think that I shall never see...
a poem as lovely as a tree."
Hey, everybody!
There goes Bob, the chiseler!
Here comes Bob, the sewer!
The thrasher.!
I think my friends can see...
that I am back from Boise.
- And the listener!
- Hey, everybody, look.!
- And more than that —
- Bob's back.!
My real father.
- Is Jane Lightwork alive, Bob?
- She's alive, Budd.
- Is she holding on?
- Old. Old, Budd.
She must be old.
She has no choice.
Here comes Santa Claus!
- Yeah.!
- Whoo!
Jesus, the things we've seen.
Aren't I right, Bob? Aren't I right?
We have heard the chimes at midnight.
That we have. That we have.
In fact, Bob, we have.
Jesus. The things we've seen.
- Where's Bob?
- Crashed out in his room.
Snoring like a horse.
What did you get?
I think this is coke.
I'm not sure though.
Yeah, it's fucking coke.
Oh, fuck!
What the hell? Scott.
My true son.
- How are you? What time is it?
- What do you care?
Why, you wouldn't even look at a clock
unless hours were lines of coke...
dials looked like
the signs of gay bars...
or time itself was
a fair hustler in black leather.
Isn't that right, Bob?
There's no reason to know the time.
We are timeless.
Aren't you forgetting, Scotty, my boy...
the mayor's son, no less...
that we who steal...
do so at midnight?
Who ripped me off?
Budd.! Budd.!
- Yes, Bob?
- I fell asleep, and I've been robbed!
- Jane!
- You'd think I could keep the peace of my house.
Jane! I know you well enough.
Bob! Bob, we'll find your drugs.
We'll find them.
This hotel is full of thieves, junkies!
You are the thief.
You have corrupted me, Scotty.
I was an innocent before I met you.
And now look at me,
just a little better than wicked.
- I used to be a virtuous man.
- Ha!
Well, virtuous enough.
I swore a little. I never gambled
more than seven times a week! Poker!
I never picked up a street boy
more than once a quarter.
- Of an hour!
- Of an hour.
Bad company has corrupted me.
I'll be darned if I haven't forgotten
what the inside of a church looks like.
I see a change for Bob to make.
From stealing... to preaching.
Stealing is my vocation, Scott.
- It's not a sin for a man —
- Hey, psst.!
To labor at his vocation.
Very early tomorrow morning
there's gonna be a bunch...
of small-time rock-and-roll promoters
coming back from their gig.
And every night they walk home
with the loot.
They stop by the Grotto Bar.
It's about a half—
No, it's about mile
down the road from here.
Dude, if we can't steal from
them going into the bar...
dude, we can get them comin'out.!
- See, Bob, dude?
- Not me.
So long as I don't know these
guys personally, it's okay with me.
See, uh —They're from Beaverton,
new to the business.
I'm not gonna go along with this crackpot
scheme, especially since Gary thought it up.
Come off it, Mike.
There is a better way to make a buck...
something to fall back on
other than your ass.
I'll fall back when
Scott inherits his money.
Bob, we don't need these guys.
We can do this ourself. Fuck them.!
- Come on, Mikey. I have a joke I want to play.
- Okay.
- Ajoke I can't pull off alone.
- Okay. I think that stuff was —
Bob!
- Aaah! Oh, my sweetheart.
- Oh!
- Come and rob with us tomorrow.
- I was going to anyway. I was just kidding.
- Good.
- Right? We'll have fun.
- All right.
- We'll be rich!
- Yeah, we'll be rich.
- We're gonna be rich.
- Gary says we'll be rich!
- We're gonna be rich!
We're gonna be rich. We're gonna be rich.
We're gonna be rich.
Ho! Ho! Ho!
Budd? Budd.
It's all right, Budd.
Budd, just —just relax, Budd.
Provide for us,
oh, great psychedelic papa!
Scotty!
When you inherit your fortune
on your 21 st birthday—
Let's see.
How far away is this?
One week away, Bob.
Just one more week.
Let's not call ourselves
robbers but Diana's foresters...
gentlemen of the shade...
minions of the moon...
men of good government.
When I turn 21,
I don't want any more of this life.
My mother and father will be surprised
at the incredible change.
It will impress them more when
such a fuckup like me turns good...
than if I had been a good son all along.
All my bad behavior
I will throw away to pay a debt.
I will change when everybody
expects it the least.
You'll become a head-roller...
a hatchet man for your old man.
No! You will be
the hatchet man, Bob!
That will be yourjob.
And so there will rarely
be a job hatcheted.
It will all be just one endless party.
Won't it?
But at least my little friend
has offered me a job.
They're so good to me.
How long has it been, Bob,
since you could see your dick?
About four years, Scotty.
Four years of grief
blows a man up like a balloon.
- There's rock-and-roll money coming this way!
- And they're drunk as skunks!
All right. All right.
You four should head them off there.
We four?
How many are walking with 'em?
- There's five of'em.
- Five? Shouldn't they be robbing us?
If they escape from you guys,
Mike and I will get 'em here.
Oh, eight feet of this muck's
like 30 yards of flat road —
Would you guys shut up?
Shut up! Pay attention.
- Squat down! Squat down!
- Squat down? You got a crane to lift me up?
- Where are our disguises?
- Right behind us.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Who are thesejokers, man?
- Look like Rajneesh.
This one looks like
he's a little thirsty.
Ha-ha! Up against the wall...
- you sully scumbags!
- Don't shoot.
Ha-ha!
Up against the wall.
Come on.! Come on.!
Don't shoot us.
That's right.
- Fags.
- Okay, set the box down. That's right.
Thank you.
Nice and gently. Nice and gently.
Let's see what we have.
Yes, my baby doll. Ooh.
Tickets anyone to next week's show?
Scott and Mike
have disappeared.
Could the shots
have scared them away?
Maybe we should get
the hell out of here.
Are they such chickens?
Let's get the hell out of here!
The thieves scatter!
Bob Pigeon will sweat to death.
Has anyone seen my son?
It's been a full three months
since I last saw him.
Where is my son Scott?
- We don't know, sir.
- Ask around in old town.
Some of the taverns there.
Some say he frequently is seen down there
drinking with street denizens.
Some who they say even rob
our citizens and store owners.
I can't believe that such an effeminate boy
supports such friends.
Hey, Mikey, how long have I been here
on the streets on this crusade?
Huh. W-Well, I came back to town
around three and a half years ago...
and that's when I met you.
- So, it's been —
- It's been three years, Mike.
Yeah, almost four years.
That's a long time.
What I'm getting at, Mike,
is that we're still alive.
Yeah. Well, that's obvious, isn't it?
Yeah. It's incredibly obvious.
They could drop a big old bomb on this city.
- Know what we would do?
- Take shelter?
- This bike was caught with much ease, Mike.
- Yes.
And the reward for the joke
that we played last night...
will be the unbelievably huge lies
that Bob will come up with now.
A plague on all cowards!
What's up, Bob?
Where have you been?
Where have I been?
If manhood's not forgotten on the face
of the earth, then I'm a shot herring.
You sit down, you little fuck.
A mayor's son.
If I jog you out of that right
and teach you to be a man...
your father would be as proud of me
as he would you, Scotty!
Why, you whoring round man.
What is the matter?
Are you not a coward?
Answer that.
- And that goes double.
- You calling me a coward? You fat duck.
I'd give $1,000 to be able
to run as fast as you can.
- It'll never happen, Bob.
- Where's the money, Bob?
Where is it?
- Taken from us by 20 or 30 punks.
- Thirty?
I was struggling with a dozen of them.
I think my arm's broken
from the fight.
Certainly a toe. Most definitely a rib.
- Let me tell you about it.
- Tell us about it, please.
- We four set upon a dozen of'em.
- Sixteen, at least, Digger, my boy.
Yeah, and got their money.
As we were splitting it, 16 others set upon us.
Thank God you had not
murdered some of them.
Murdered?
Well, they are past praying for.
I peppered two of them.
- Two punks in leather jackets.
- What?
- I'll tell you, son. These four came in close.
- You said there were two —
Four! I said there were four, Scott.
Four.
These four came from the front,
kicking at me, pulling their knives.
And I whipped out the blade
and took all seven as a target, like this!
Seven! Just a second ago,
there were four.
- In leather?
- No, Bob, my friend.
There was four of'em,
and they all had leather on.
Seven, by my count.
Leave him alone.
We shall have more soon.
As I was saying, these nine in the alleyway
that I told you about—
There's more already, I see. Nine?
Full force, and with thought,
seven of the 11 I pegged!
There are 11 now.
He started with two.
But, as the devil would have it,
three of them came at my back.
They were wearing green.
And they had it out with me.
Because it was so dark, Scotty...
that you could not see your hand.
How could you see green
when it was so dark...
that you couldn't see your hand?
- Tell us the reason. Come on, Bob.
- Tell us!
- Come on, Bob.!
- Tell us the reason, Bob.!
- Tell us why.
- You can tell 'em. Go on and tell 'em.
- Upon compulsión?
- Come on, Bob.
Not for you or I or all the rest of the worid
would I tell you...
on compulsión!
I will no longer
be guilty of this sin!
This sanguine coward,
this horseback-breaker...
this huge hill of jelly!
Punk.! You starfish.!
Oh, for breath to utter what lies
of a tailor's yardstick!
You boot case.! You vile punk.!
Breathe a while, and then do it again.
But hear me out.
We two saw you four set upon five.
And, Bob...
you carried yourself
away at the slightest noise.
And roared for mercy. And ran and roared
as ever I heard a bull calf.
What trick,
what device can you find...
to hide from this open
and apparent shame?
Yes.
What new trick
do you have for us now, Bob?
Good Lord, lads.
I know you as well as
he that made you.
Do you think that I would
kill the heir apparent?
Do you think I would turn on you, Scotty?
Why, you're our only ticket
out of this poverty and oppressión.
I am as valued as Hercules.
But beware my instinct.
The lion will not touch the true heir.
Good Lord, lads...
I'm glad you have the money.
If we're looking for a fat man,
why don't we get one under the bridge?
Oh.! Oh.! The sheriff and his posse are here.
Scotty, they've come to search the house.
Shall I let them in?
Call in the sheriff!
- God.
- Oh, God, what's that smell?
Hey!
- Hey!
- There they are.
- Over there! Over there!
- Come here, you little shit!
Come here!
There he goes! In the door!
Baby, yeah.
Wait, wait, wait! Wait, wait, wait!
Aha! What have we here?
Pardon me, Mr. Favor. An informant
has followed certain men into this house.
- What men?
- One of them is well known, sir.
- A large fat man.
- Fat as butter.
Well, he's not here.
But if I see him...
I'll promise you that
I'll send him to you by...
dinnertime tomorrow...
to answer against any such charges.
So, would you leave us alone?
- You.!
- Sorry for the interruption.
We have a message for you
from your father.
He'd like to see you
as soon as possible.
Fuck you.
I don't know whether it is God
trying to get back at me...
for something I have done, but...
your passing through life makes me certain
that you are marked...
and that heaven is punishing me
for my mistreatings.
When I got back from France
and set foot in Clark County...
and saw what your cousin, Bill Davis,
had done at his family's ranch...
I thought, by my soul...
he has more worthy interest to my estate
than you could hold a candle to.
And being no older than you are,
he organizes operations for state senators...
Iobbies for the small businessman...
and has an ambitious five-year plan for
the forest that even I would like to support.
And then I have to think of you...
and what a degenerate you are.
Don't think that, Father.
You will find out it's not true.
And I hope that somebody
forgives the people...
that have swayed
your fond thoughts away from me.
For a time will come when I will
make this northern youth...
trade me his good deeds
for my indignities.
Bill Davis is my good cousin.
But even the slightest
worship of his time —
Dad —
I will die...
a hundred thousand deaths...
before that happens.
I wanna see my face on the front
of album covers.
I wanna produce my own music.
You know, I just — I just want
total control over my music.
I wanna engineer it.
I wanna mix it.
You know, I wanna — I wanna get
my own say on opening bands.
Then I'd like to, like, stand in back
of bigger pictures of myself.
- That's good.
- And you?
I don't care.
Where should we go?
- To visit my brother.
- You have a brother?
Yeah, I've got a brother, man.
You know that.
Where is he?
Well, I'm thinking he should be
someplace in, uh, the potato state.
Idaho.
Shut up, Mike.
If I'd known it'd be this hard to start,
I wouldn't have stopped it at all.
I've been on this road before.
This is my road.
Looks like a fucked-up face.
Like it's saying, "Have a nice day"
or something.
See what I mean, Scott.
Scott, look.
Thanks.
What?
- You need some help with this, man?
- Shut up.
You shut up.
- You suck.
- Do you know anything about bikes?
Yeah, l-I've turned over a few.
Scott, man, where are you going?
Getting away from everything feels good.
Yeah, it does.
When I left home,
the maid asked me where I was off to.
I said, "Wherever, whatever.
Have a nice day."
You had a maid?
Yeah.
If I had a normal family
and a good upbringing...
then I would have been
a well-adjusted person.
Depends on what you call normal.
Yeah, it does.
Well, you know, normal,
like — like a mom and a dad...
and a dog and shit like that.
Normal. Normal.
So you didn't have a normal dog?
- No, I didn't have a dog.
- You didn't have a — a normal dad?
Didn't have a dog or— or—
or a normal dad anyway.
That's all right.
I don't feel sorry for myself.
I mean, I feel like I'm —
I feel like I'm, you know, well-adjusted.
What's a normal dad?
I don't know.
I'd like to talk with you.
I mean, I'd like to really talk with you.
We're talking right now,
but, you know —
I don't know.
I — I don't feel like I can be —
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org