Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I love it.
Oh, yes.
You're so pretty, Mona. You're gorgeous.
I've come. Give me me fags.
And that's it? I've gotta be off.
Is that it?
Are you in love with him still?
No.
Were you ever?
I thought I were.
Then why did you dump him?
He dumped me.
Why?
He said he couldn't be bothered anymore.
Twat.
Anyway, he had a wife and kid.
Men like that should be castrated.
Gosh, aren't you clever?
We should teach that Ricky a lesson.
That's Ricky.
Christ, you didn't mention he was fat.
He's not. It's all muscle. Yeah, right.
All right, come on.
Hello. Hi.
God, this is really hard,
but this is my friend, Mona.
And she has just had
to have an abortion.
So what's that got to do with
me? It was your husband's fetus.
Basically, what he did was he
just got her completely wasted...
and took advantage of her.
She's now clinically depressed,
as you can see. I mean...
she's just catatonic, she hasn't
said a word since. Have you, Mona?
I mean, it could be, I
mean, the talk of the town...
at the moment is that you're not
satisfying him enough at home.
We all know when we hit a certain age...
everything starts to go
south-- How dare you come here?
Maybe you should keep
your husband locked up.
Maybe you should castrate your
husband, maybe that'll keep him safe--
Why don't you two just go and get
lost and leave me and my family alone.
No, until you fully understand--
No, just get out of my face.
Don't touch me. Will you just go?
All right, Mona, it's
all right. This is over.
Why don't you just get.... Just go
and leave me and my family alone.
Hi, there.
Mona.
You'll be there tomorrow, won't you?
I have absolutely no intention
of coming to your crucifixion.
Will you be there, please, for me?
Can I come? Yeah.
I need you there, Mona.
We're going.
Do you see that?
# Once again I look upon
the cross where You died #
# I'm humbled by Your mercy
and I'm broken inside #
# Once again I thank You #
# Once again I pour out my life #
# Now you are #
# exalted to the highest place #
# King of heavens,
where one day I'll bow #
# But for now #
# I marvel at this saving grace #
# And I'm full of praise once again #
# I'm full of praise once again #
# Once again I look upon
the cross where You died #
# I'm humbled by Your mercy
and I'm broken inside #
# Once again I thank You ##
Has he got a girlfriend? Has he? Fuck.
He's got God, he's too busy with God.
With God, his life's
like, one long orgasm.
From morning, noon till night.
The sun never goes down on him.
If anything goes wrong...
we'll slowly bring it down again, okay?
Okay. One, two, three, go.
That's it.
Fucking hell.
Okay, there. Tie it off, lads.
Yes.
If I can be saved, anybody can be saved.
Anybody can be saved. Hallelujah.
The Lord Jesus started speaking to me.
He told me to build this cross.
To claim this valley
back in His name, for Him.
Because there's evil at
work in this valley. Yeah.
There's evil in this valley.
And it manifests itself
in hundreds of ways.
If one person comes
closer to God today...
through our actions, then
that's a victory. Yeah.
That's a victory for everybody
here. That's all it is.
We don't pray for riches.
We pray for fulfillment in ourselves and
in our hearts first and foremost of all.
But I have prayed for my sister...
who's there now.
This is the power of prayer.
'Cause I prayed to
the Lord for my sister.
I prayed that she'd be set free,
because I know she's in turmoil.
And it's so hard for me. I can't
just reach out and tell her.
But I've prayed for her, Lord.
I've prayed 'cause I love her.
And I know that the Lord
is answering my prayers.
He answers all our prayers. Yeah.
Praise be the Lord.
I praise you, Lord Jesus.
Thank you, Lord.
Yes, Lord.
Thank you, Lord Jesus.
Praise your name, Lord. I
praise your name, Lord Jesus.
Yes, Lord.
Do you really think that
there's darkness in the valley?
Absolutely, yeah. There's
darkness everywhere.
What, like the Devil?
Yeah, I know that I was filled
with the Devil at one point.
What were you like?
I wasn't a really nice guy.
I'd think nothing of putting
a glass in your face...
or punching you on the nose.
And it's the Devil that did that?
The Devil drove me, yeah.
The Devil just wants you to do bad
things, then he's got a grip of you.
It must be interesting
to believe in something.
Yeah.
But remember, there's Devil...
and there's God, and He's
far more powerful anyway.
I am the Devil...
and I have come to kill you.
I am possessed and I will
show you that you are evil.
I have come to the
valley to make you suffer.
I'm laying my hands on you, devil spawn.
As a child of Jesus, I am
ripping this seed from your body.
The Devil will leave your body.
Spirits, is anyone else there?
Did you push that?
You pushed that. I bloody did not.
Who is it?
S.
A.
D.
Sad? Who the fuck's Sad?
I.
E.
Sadie.
I'm not moving it.
I swear I'm not.
Sadie, is that you?
I don't think we should carry on.
Are you in peace?
No.
Why are you not in peace?
D.
A.
Do you blame Dad,
Sadie? Do you blame Dad?
Yes.
It's bollocks.
No, it's not.
He didn't love her enough,
that's why she died.
There's still hair on it.
It's like she's still here.
Mushrooms.
We can commune with Sadie.
Open.
# When we sway I go weak #
# I can hear the sounds of violins #
# Long before it begins #
Ricky.
# As only you know how #
# Sway me smooth, sway me now #
Fuck's sake, Mona.
Sorry about that.
Come on, you two, out you go.
Thank you, good man.
Go on. Oh, yeah.
Get out.
I love you all. Bye.
Get out!
Thank you.
We must never be parted.
Do you hear me? Yeah.
Are you listening to me? Yeah.
We're gonna spend the
rest of our lives together.
I know.
If you leave me, I'll kill you.
If you leave me, I'll kill you...
and then I'll kill myself.
I love you.
Tam.
I found loads of
blackcurrants for breakfast.
I've got loads more in me
pockets. I've only had a couple.
I don't care how many
blackcurrants you've got, Mona...
it's not enough for breakfast.
I know. I'm fucking freezing.
I've been bitten to shit.
I just want to go home.
I'm sick of this place.
Yeah.
Yeah, let's go back.
Luxor.
It's in Egypt.
Why would you wanna go there?
O-M...
S-K.
Omsk.
It's in Siberia.
It's your brother.
Just ignore him. He'll go away.
He's a very attractive
man, your brother.
I'll seek some spiritual
guidance from him.
Yeah, go on. It'll be funny.
Hello.
Hiya.
Hi.
Is Mona here with you? No,
but she'll be back in a moment.
Right.
Why don't you wait here?
Would that be okay? Yeah.
Thanks.
You can wait in the
sitting room. Thanks.
Actually, there is something
I wanted to talk to you about.
I have a real problem
believing in anything.
Or anyone.
But I can't stop thinking
about that day on the hill...
when you made that speech...
and the way you spoke.
And everything you said,
I just believed you.
That's because God was
speaking through me.
And the Lord is the truth.
And everything you were
saying about the Devil...
and all the demons.
And you really believed in it. Yeah.
I were riddled with demons.
And what did you do?
I asked Jesus Christ
to come into my life.
I asked Him to free me from
all the guilt, sin, fear.
And He came in and He washed it away.
And He can do the same for you.
But He never speaks to me.
You've got to pray to Him.
Ask Him to come into your heart...
and He will.
He's a gentle God.
He's a God of love...
and He knows you.
He knows every hair on your head.
I can't feel Him.
I can't feel anything.
I just feel empty.
The Lord can fill you up.
He's in this room now...
and He wants to be close to you.
And He wants you to ask
Him to come into your heart.
He wants to reach out and touch you.
And He wants you to feel Him.
He wants to come inside you...
and overwhelm you with joy.
I want Him to.
Do not resist him. I won't.
You're too easy, you fucking fraud.
Tam!
Tam.
Mona. What?
Look at me.
Come here.
I'm sorry I got violent, okay?
Is that it? No.
There's something with that
girl going on inside her.
There's things driving her.
You saw what happened to me, didn't you?
I want you to promise me
you'll stay away from her.
I love her. She loves me.
We're going away together, forever.
And we are never coming back.
Phil?
What are you doing?
Phil, don't lock it, you bastard!
Phil, please.
Phil.
Phil?
Can you open the door? Please.
Phil? Don't leave me, Lord.
Father, we just pray...
that You will just help
us in our prayers now.
Lord, just lead us and help us, Father.
Lord, we want to lift Mona
before You, Father God.
We just pray, Father, that You
just reach into her life, Father.
That You will start to untangle
some of that mess, Father...
that confusion in her mind,
the tangled mess of emotions.
Lord, that You put the words into his
heart, into his mouth, Father, that...
he will be able to show the love
of Jesus to his sister, Father.
That through him, Lord, she will receive
Your love and Your understanding, Father.
Can you shut up?
Lord, we glorify You.
That's right, Lord.
We bless what You're doing.
Bless what You're doing.
You bastard!
I'll be back.
No.
Mona.
You stupid girl.
Yeah? Aren't you?
You're a stupid girl.
Don't do this to me.
I love you.
I am the Antichrist...
and I will never die.
It's okay, mate. Fuck off.
Chill. Chill out.
Come on, we'll pray for you.
I'd like.... Just fucking go.
Chill out. Go.
Calm it down, brother. Don't
fucking touch me. Get out.
We're leaving. Go!
You're a bunch of
fakers. Go on, get out!
Go on, fuck off. Take
your fucking Bibles. Go on.
Get out! Fucking move.
Move it. Get out. Fuck off.
And take your fucking books with you.
You're all fakers. Come on.
Bye.
Tammy?
What's going on, Tam?
I'm going back to school.
Excuse me.
Can I have my top back, please?
You're Sadie?
Yeah.
Can I have my top, please?
I've got to go back to school, Mona.
You've always known that.
Look, I couldn't be myself back
there in front of my mother.
Anyway, I was just playing
a part. That wasn't even me.
Come on, you know me.
You know me.
And don't be upset about
Sadie. Sadie was just....
Sadie was just a bit of poetic
license. I mean, I'm a fantasist.
You can't tell me we haven't had fun.
I've never met anyone like you.
Please don't be angry with me.
What the fuck are you doing?
You fucking crazy bitch!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org