Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Oh, Skank!
Fuck me!
Hey.
What did you say?
You teach him that?
He heard it
in the locker room, Dad.
- From who?
- Everyone.
You know what it's like
in there.
He shoots.
He scores!
Wouldn't start again?
- Was it the gas line?
- I don't know. I'll ask Tinker.
- Mmm.
Take the sled, will ya?
I wanna wait for the mail.
- The magazine's supposed to be here, express.
- Okay. Better be good.
Of course it's gonna be good.
That's the whole point.
I don't exactly trust
Chuckie boy.
Come on.
Pass it off.
All right.
Let's go again.
Bailey!
Hi, Bailey.
Fat men don't shovel,
Bailey.
No, it's dry.
It's dry.
- Ew! Fuck me!
- That's a lung biscuit.
Joey!
That's it. Neither of you guys
are coming to the locker room again.
John?
Have a good game today.
- God, it's cold!
- The taters are hot.
Right here, Connor.
Thanks. Hot, hot, hot!
- What the hell kind of bird is that?
- Bobby, throw some tape.
- It's gonna be a hot one today.
- Hey, tape!
- Hey, is the magazine out yet?
- Monday.
- Johnny's supposed to get a copy expressed.
- Maybe we made the cover.
- We ain't on the cover.
- He said it would be a big story with pictures.
Yeah, Chuck exaggerates.
Hey, guys, you are
not gonna believe this.
Sarah Heinz.
I know!
She's supposed to be this shy girl.
I figure, what the hell.
I ain't that attractive.
I'll vaccinate her quick, get home for an
early sack, beat what's left of the bishop.
Like this?
- She's much fatter naked. Yeah!
- No.
I'm telling you, she got her February
fat now in the second week in December.
She's riding me
like a wet walrus,
making these fat sounds.
- Thwap, thwap, thwap.
- The boy's got no shame.
You're a sick man, Skank.
- Hey, you got the magazine? Damn.
- The mail didn't come yet.
- Hey.
- What?
- You kill one more wolf...
- Ain't no sheriffin' in here.
I ain't sheriffin'. I'm just
a teammate concerned for his freedom.
Come on, boys.
Let's move it.
It's two tenths below zero.
The committee won't be happy.
- The committee.
- You seen Weeks lately? He's been skating the river.
I don't care. I'm about to be on
the cover of Sports Illustrated.
That photographer said I have
one of those expressive faces.
- A face that tells a story.
- Too bad it's a tragedy.
- A comedy.
- A horror story.
Come on, guys.
Let's start gettin' our heads into it.
Like Connor says,
that Weeks kid, he's got jump.
I'm tellin' you, Tree,
there's rumors.
One of us is going down.
Let's go! Let's move!
Let's go!
Good game!
Stretch 'em out.
- Let's do it, Sheriff.
- Sticks!
- Line 'em up, Michael!
- Don't give me Tree. I wanna win this week.
- I win no matter what side, huh?
- Win this, Tree.
- Maybe it's you and me, huh?
- Winetka.
Here.
- Paul.
- Brown's the winner.
- Dad!
- Thanks, Mikey.
Tree!
- You see Stevie Weeks yesterday?
- Chump.
You think
we gotta do it?
- Birdie!
- Try and pass me!
- Give it to me!
- Try it! Try it!
Pass! Damn!
Whoo!
All right!
Soon, it'll be you
out there.
- Oh, I don't know.
- It will, Stevie.
- Ow!
- Daddy!
There are things you do in public...
and things you don't.
We're just kissing.
For God's sakes.
Geez.
Very effective, Walter.
Nipped in the bud.
- MaryJane.
- You got it?
I got it. Look. It's three pages
with pictures and profiles.
- There's John.
- A mix between Bobby Bond and Moose DuPark.
Yeah,
he won't like that.
"Clears the crease like a snowplow. "
Well, he can't not like that.
Come on.
- Honey. Look at this.
- Hey.
- The mayor should get first look. Not bad, right?
- Wow.
Son of a piss whore.
Our town in Sports Illustrated.
Listen to this.
"The legendary hockey players of
Mystery, Alaska, were born on skates...
in a world perpetually covered
with ice and snow.
Isolated by rugged mountains
and vast glaciers,
they hone their skills
by playing each other,
Saturday after Saturday,
for as long as anyone can remember.
The citizens attend with
religious devotion in sub-zero weather.
A committee of town fathers
decides who plays and by what rules.
The game has become
more than a sport.
It's a weekly
ritual celebration. "
"The Winetka brothers
forecheck like gophers.
When a puck goes into a corner,
a Winetka comes out with it.
- Yeah!
- Read. Read!
And then there's
Connor Banks.
- Connor!
- What about Connor Banks?
Montreal had its rocket.
Mystery has its cruise missile!"
The only rocket you got
is your meat whistle.
Hang on. Hang on. " Perfecting the art
of the pass is John Biebe,
whose precision and accuracy more
than compensate for slowness of foot.
- The only player without lightning speed.
- Every team needs its thumper.
Fuck 'em, Johnny. Fuck 'em.
On pure skating ability,
the boys of Mystery, Alaska...
rival any team in
the National Hockey League!"
That's us!
And isn't it exciting
for Charlie...
getting his article published
in Sports Illustrated?
I bet this is a big
accomplishment for him.
He kind of embellished
a little.
He's always been so smart, that Charlie.
I knew when he left he'd make it big.
Well, actually, I heard he left
'cause he skated like a homosexual.
You think because you scored two goals
today, you played a good game?
We don't talk about hockey at the table.
We've been talking about it
for 20 minutes.
We've been talking
about the magazine.
Which is about hockey.
Can't we just enjoy
the attention tonight?
Sports Illustrated,
for God's sakes.
Hockey is played
at both ends of the ice.
You, you coast in your own zone.
You skate like a figure skater.
And when you get the puck,
you don't pass.
More potatoes?
No.
I've lost my appetite.
Oh...
He never made the Saturday game.
That's what's bothering him.
Why should he tell me how to play?
- He played college 2-A, Birdie.
- 2-A isn't the Saturday game.
- That's enough.
- Well, he started it!
Margie has relatives
in Waterville, Maine.
She said as soon
as Price World moved in,
all the local shops
went right out of business.
Price World's not gonna come, Mom.
We're not big enough, for God's sakes.
Well, they've been sniffin'.
Oh, Skank.
- Yeah!
- Yeah! Yeah!
"On the left side,
Skank Marden is a master
of sticky sores... "
No, no, Shawnette.
Um, remember, you want
to sound out the words.
- Okay.
- Let's try again.
"Skank Marden,
a master of the stick,
scores on demand. "
That's right. Good. Excellent.
Tommy! What?
Word is Biebe is out
and Weeks is going up.
Really?
- Don't get too far.
- Yeah, Dad.
- Hey, Johnny.
- Hey.
Thanks for coming, Johnny.
Well, we can't hold
Stevie Weeks back any longer.
You'll be first alternate,
of course.
That's...
There's more to the game than speed,
Scott. Experience counts.
Which Stevie Weeks can't get
till we call him up.
You've been in the Saturday game
13 years, Johnny.
- That's a record!
- I can still play.
When was the last time
you scored a goal?
Look, it's not fair to the Weeks boy
to keep him back.
And it's not fair
to the Saturday game.
Shit!
I gotta go.
Donna's inside, Johnny.
- Hey.
I'm fine, Donna.
We talked about this.
We knew one day eventually...
I'm fine.
Don't tell me you're fine.
I better check on Mike.
- You could've told me.
- I can't give you that kind of information.
We're sleeping together,
for God's sakes.
Skank, we're committing adultery. It's
not like I threw in trust as a perk.
Honey.
- Hi.
- Look, you, uh... you may have heard.
- We just did it.
- I heard.
And so did I,
and it's a big mistake.
John Biebe is the anchor,
for God's sakes!
Geez.
Stevie! Stevie! Stevie! Stevie!
Guys, it ain't my birthday.
It's better.
You're in the Saturday game!
L- I could go down
as fast as I come up.
- There's no way.
- Hey, I'm next. They'll be callin' me next.
Hey, Mike.
- Hey.
- Why don't you get yourself that milkshake?
Better not hear
your grades are dropping off.
They-They won't, sir.
You skate like you can
and you'll be fine.
- Boys.
- Sheriff.
- I ordered one for you too, Dad.
- Thanks, Mike.
- Johnny?
- Yeah?
You gotta get out to Gagney Grocers.
Connor Banks just shot a guy.
Ow! Jesus!
What, did you put your finger in it?
- Try and hold still.
- Could you jam the oxygen tank...
a little further up my ass, please?
Have you done this before?
- Who is he?
- A rep from Price World.
Good. Twist it! Yeah, that helps.
Think about trimming
those nails too, Tarzan.
- Just try to hold it there.
- Are you trying to hurt me?
Huh?
- You okay?
- No, I'm not okay!
Do I look like I'm okay?
The fucker shot me!
What the fuck-ass fuck of a bum-fuck,
shithole town is this?
I make a business call.
I give him my card.
And the hick-ass fucker shoots
my foot off! Cock-fucking shit!
- John, it was an accident.
- You read him his rights?
- You have the right to remain silent.
- Oh, come on, John!
- I didn't mean to shoot him.
- Call Bailey Pruitt. Talk to him.
Don't be saying
anything to me.
Johnny, I heard.
- I'm sorry.
- Connor, you just shot a guy.
- Take him.
- Read him his rights.
Cock-fucking suck-ass fucker!
Have fun in jail, asshole!
They, uh,
got into a beef.
- Connor pulled a pistol.
Happened over in feed.
Says he was aiming at a sack
of Puppy Chow, trying to scare him.
He hit a wheelbarrow.
It ricocheted.
- Ow! Ow, ow!
- Johnny?
- Yeah?
- There's a helicopter hovering over town hall. Looks Russian.
Whoa!
I'm slow in the feet?
That's it?
That's all you got for me?
No, "Wow, nice helicopter"? No, " Hey,
great article in Sports Illustrated"?
How's Donna doing?
Does she miss me?
Twice in one year, Charlie.
What do you want this time?
I come bearing
the New York Rangers.
The New York Rangers?
Yeah, I was pretty blown away myself.
But the article sparked some kind
of brainstorm at the NHL.
- Good writing, I guess.
- The New York Rangers.
The New York Rangers.
- In Mystery, Alaska?
- Right here.
To play against our boys?
The NHL feels it'll be
great publicity,
and the network figures
a 14 share, minimum.
All right.
What's in it for you,
Charlie?
Community pride.
A sense of giving back to
the place where I grew up.
Money.
If you all settle down, we'll, uh,
we'll try to answer all your questions.
Now, nothing is definite.
There's still some dealing to be done
with the players' unions and things.
But what needs to be decided first is,
do we want this game?
- I won't kid ya, it would be
a goose to the economy.
What economy?
We can be serious
about this,
or we can simply leave the decision to
the committee, which I'm quite happy to do.
Yes, Miram?
The question is,
do we really stand a chance?
'Cause if all that's gonna happen
is we'll get laughed at,
I'm not for it
at any price.
That's fair. That's fair.
And to answer that,
I'd like to call up here
someone we all know and...
Well, we all know.
Charles Danner.
Thanks. Um... Well, first of all,
it's really great to be back.
Bullshit!
Uh... Um, here's the thing.
On a standard ice rink,
no, we don't come close.
But... our boys on a pond?
Now, hold on
just one second.
You're using words
like "we" and "our boys. "
You left this town,
Charlie Danner.
You can't even skate.
Plus, this may be
an old lady talking,
but I've always thought
you were a bit of a prick.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
This is a town meeting.
Let's have some order,
for God's sakes! John.
Could we make a game of it?
Yeah, John.
Depends on rules.
We play four on four.
They play five on five.
Boards, offsides,
two-line passing.
Rules that keep everything bunched.
It's a different kind of game.
John, excuse me, but this game
is gonna be played on a pond.
- Hey, Chuck...
- One second.
Everybody here always says on a pond,
nobody beats us, right? Nobody.
Okay, well, you got a chance
to prove it now.
John, can we win?
Shooting, passing, stick handling...
The truth?
Except for Connor,
nobody here comes close.
But on the pond,
black ice, wide open surface,
it's all about skating.
And we can skate.
Yeah, we can.
All right, man.
The New York Rangers
are professionals.
Two things we've always had
in Mystery:
Our dignity
and our illusions.
I suggest we cling to both.
Where's the dignity
in not trying?
I'll play those Rangers.
- I'm in.
- I'll play.
I'll beat 'em.
As mayor of Mystery, Alaska,
I'm gonna extend a little invitation
to the New York Rangers!
Hey, Johnny!
- This can't wait till tomorrow?
- No, no, we gotta be on the ice at sunup.
If this game happens,
it's only 32 days away.
We gotta get goin'.
- I bet you're back on the team now, right?
- Maybe.
Well, they're not gonna play the Rangers
with just ten guys.
Here he comes.
- John. Hey, Donna.
- Hey, Scott.
- Witch-tit cold, huh?
- Yeah.
Look, John,
these are the developments.
Things have changed.
We want you to coach.
Judge turn you down?
Yeah.
He's got some bug up his colon.
But next toJudge Fuck Nut,
you know most about hockey.
Scott, you'll need him
to play, right?
Oh, uh...
Well, the committee feels you can best
help the team by, you know, coaching.
You're the guy.
They all look up to you.
Scott, I don't coach.
John, I'm asking you
as mayor of the town.
Will you coach?
Look, think about it.
Let me know, huh?
You know,
every ex-player turned coach says
they prefer coaching to playing.
Why would they
all say that?
Because they can't play.
So why'd you wanna come?
You never wanna come when I plough.
- Well, um, could you pull over?
- Sure.
What...
What are you doing?
Um...
I thought, um...
I think we should celebrate
you making the team.
N- Now? Here?
I don't know where else
to do it.
I got a condom too.
- So...
- Marla.
With you on the team, Stevie,
a lot of girls are gonna be,
you know, after you.
I don't wanna lose you toJody Lange
just 'cause she gives.
Marla.
I'm not gonna leave you
on account of not having sex.
I love you.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Oh!
Oh, I'm-I'm...
I'm sorry.
That's okay. That's...
That's okay.
L...
Does this mean we're done?
I'm-I'm sorry.
I must have...
That's okay.
It's okay, Stevie.
Hey, Sarah, sorry to be calling on you
so late, but have you heard?
- The Rangers?
- Yeah.
Yeah, good news makes
the compass point north.
How about a quick rattle?
After you, Skank.
"Mother walrus going
thwap, thwap, thwap"?
- What?
- You wanna hear a thwap?
Women don't like being referred to
as fat mammals, Skank.
I never would've said that
to her face.
- Are you gonna arrest me?
- Do you want me to?
Well, if it's all over what he said, I'd
just as soon it'd be all over that I hit him.
It will be.
You gonna let the kids keep the school?
We gotta have a new rink, Donna.
You want one of those goddamn
TV trucks to fall through the ice?
Plus we need new boards, lights,
and they're sending us a Zamboni.
Oh, a Zamboni.
Gettin' wet just thinking about it.
Jesus!
- Donna. Hey.
- Hey.
- Hi. How you doin'?
- Hi. Good.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
- You ran out before I could say hi last night.
- I know. Hi.
Hi.
God, you look good.
How can you look this good? What do
you have, like nine children now?
All right, well,
we're not the Partridge Family.
- Three kids.
- I know how many kids you have.
So, you're a producer, huh?
Yeah, well,
associate producer.
What's a producer do?
Uh, well,
I'm-I'm doing it.
- Really?
- Yes, I'm liaising with the locals.
I see.
And the helicopter was...
Well, you know, it's the kind of news
you wanna deliver in person, you know,
and I can't help it if it impressed
the hell out of you.
So, uh...
Well, so did it?
Do I look impressed?
You look good.
Your Honor,
at this time I'd be asking the court
to dismiss the charges...
on the grounds of patriotism.
I'm not in the mood,
Mr. Pruitt.
If Price World
did come here...
with the one-stop shopping
and the low, low prices,
it would threaten to put every merchant
in this town out of business,
as it has in so many communities
across this country.
- Trial date?
- This Tuesday.
Tuesday?
- Fine by me.
- All right, next Tuesday.
And impanel Monday.
I don't want a trial now. Suppose I
lose? I get jail, I miss the game.
Connor, trust me. They're not gonna
lock up our leading scorer.
As the puck comes off the ice,
the left wing will always drop back.
These four swing around here,
try and force the puck this way.
So the puck carrier is
always facing three defensemen.
- Are we gonna play it?
- No.
We're gonna learn it
so we can beat it.
It's five-man, not four.
It's complicated.
Before we get into that,
There's one rule we got we live by.
What happens in this room,
what's said in this room,
stays in this room.
Now, last night Skank
took a shovel to the temple...
because somebody repeated what
was said in the locker room.
Somebody repeated
to Silvie Walker,
and Silvie Walker
repeated it to Sarah Heinz.
- I told her confidentially.
- Aw, Jesus.
What you say in the room
stay in the room.
I didn't think she
was gonna say anything.
Skank, I'm sorry.
She just smoked the hog, man.
I wasn't myself.
- It's your call, Skank.
- Oh, I want it.
Fuck!
Fuckin' wind-chill. This ain't right.
It's not that easy!
- One slip of the tongue. All right, that's it.
- Rules are rules!
Come on, guys!
- Do it!
- Come on!
Aw, shit!
Oh, shit!
Mother...
I hate you bastards!
I hate you all!
All I did was suggest we meet,
and then he pulled out a gun.
Did he say anything,
Mr. Walsh?
Objection!
Now, that question...
Fuck it.
What did he say?
Well, he conveyed his anger at the idea
of Price World moving into the community.
He threatened to shoot me if I didn't
leave the premises, and then he shot me.
Thank you, Mr. Walsh.
Reserve the right to recall, Your Honor.
Big doings we've got going here
in Mystery these days, huh?
Price World wants to come here,
and now the New York Rangers
want to come.
Mr. Pruitt, I don't want to hear
anything about Price World.
I don't wanna hear another word about
a hockey game. We talked about this.
Yeah, well, forgive me, Your Honor.
I'm fat.
Mr. Walsh, that bullet
that struck you,
did it appear to ricochet
off a wheelbarrow?
It... Maybe.
So what?
Is it legal to shoot in the vicinity
of people in this town?
You don't care very much for
our community, do you, Mr. Walsh?
- I have nothing against
your community, Mr. Pruitt.
Did you say,
"What the fuck-ass fuck
of a bum-fuck shithole town is this?"
Did you say that, Mr. Walsh?
The game is tentatively
scheduled forJanuary 16.
- Hey, this is it!
- Sounds like fun, Barry, but evidently not for everyone.
No, I don't think so, Steve.
No one thought...
to check with the New York Ranger
players about this.
The bottom line is, you only get
a few days off during this long season.
Now, instead of spending these days off
at home with their families,
they're told they gotta go to Alaska
and play a game of pond hockey.
- This is a joke.
- Turning now to real hockey news,
the NHL named Wayne Gretzky
as its player of the month.
The superstar scored 17 goals
with 22 assists...
Yeah, wait till we beat 'em.
Then we'll see who's a joke.
You guys know what you're made of.
You know what you've got inside.
Nervous?
- Come on, let's work it around.
- Don't leave him alone!
- Whoa. That guy can shoot, huh?
- Yeah.
- Get on him! Get on him!
- Okay, guys, come on, now!
- Fighting the puck a little.
- Oh, let him find his legs.
Yeah, his first game.
He'll be fine.
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Look out!
Get away! Get away!
- Stevie? Stevie!
- Give him some air.
- Biebe.
Good work, Tree. You killed him.
- Head was down.
- I know. I know.
I brought the salts, Dad.
- Stevie?
- Huh?
- It's okay. It's all right.
- Hello.
Stevie, how many fingers
have I got? Hmm?
I'm a premature ejaculator.
Let's go, guys.
Three on three.
- So?
- Anyone special in New York?
- Uh, no.
I don't... I don't want you
to feel bad about that either,
just 'cause I haven't had a relationship
that's lasted longer than six weeks...
since we broke up
in the 12th grade.
- That's... The important thing is that you're happy.
- Right.
You are...
You are happy, I take it?
Yeah.
I'm happy.
Good. Good.
How is your husband,
anyway?
Appears to be, uh,
well fed.
Of course he is.
I mean, what else
do I have to do, really,
besides slave over a hot stove,
rub my fat husband's feet,
dig splinters out of my ass that I get
while sitting around pining for you?
Well, you said it,
I didn't.
Seriously, though.
I mean, forget about me.
Don't you ever wish you lived
in a town that had a museum...
or someplace where brothers and sisters
were off-limits to each other sexually?
All right,
just follow the light.
No, just over here. There you go.
Over here. Come on.
Still sleepin'?
- How's he doin'?
- He's a little happy.
No, no, no.
Easy, son.
- I'm okay. Birdie, I'm sorry.
- All right.
I didn't even get
the condom on.
It was 'cause of your sister's breasts.
They're perky.
Well, he's out again.
- Honey, what's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Sweetheart...
- I don't wanna talk about it, okay?
Well, if you can't talk
to your own mother...
Stevie doesn't wanna
sleep with me.
Oh. Oh.
Oh.
Hmm.
So, uh, you two
have already,
uh, you know,
had relations?
No, he came in the condom.
Oh!
Where, uh,
was the condom...
when he, uh,
you know...
Um...
On-On his, uh, serpent.
Hi.
What's wrong?
Uh, Walter, get out.
This is private.
I'm entitled to know
what's going on under this roof.
After all, I am
the father of this child.
Walter, if you don't leave,
I swear I'll tell you.
Right.
The defendant will please rise.
What say you, Karen?
The State of Alaska
versus Connor Banks.
Second-degree assault.
We find the defendant
not guilty.
That's a not guilty verdict on Connor.
Betty?
And we further order Price World
to pay damages...
in the amount of $42,000.
- What?
- 42,000 bucks?
They can't do that.
This is a criminal trial.
We don't award damages
to criminal defendants.
The damage award is vacated.
What's that, "vacated"?
Look around.
Look at yourselves.
You have exalted this game
above what is right,
but you have
your star center back.
The defendant is free to go.
You have embarrassed
my courtroom.
Thanks a lot.
Fuckin' moron.
It's me that embarrasses you,
isn't it?
- Did I say that, Brian?
- I'm sorry I'm such a disappointment.
I'm sorry I don't feel like goin'
to college and getting some degree.
I'm sorry for only wanting to play hockey,
and I'm sorry that you never played...
in the Saturday game, but I would think
there are bigger tragedies in life!
Brian!
Scotty. Hey.
I want you to meet
the folks from the network.
- That's Jonathan Slaven. Scott Pitcher.
- Hi.
- And, uh, this is Janice Pettibone.
- My nostrils just froze.
It's a pleasure to welcome
a famous TV personality.
- Uh, hi.
- Janice, see how everybody skates here?
- Yeah.
- Even on the sidewalks. We should get some shots...
- I can't feel my nose.
- All right, then.
- She's cold.
- She's weird.
"Eskimos On Ice. "
In fact, that's what we're calling
the team: The Mystery Eskimos.
Well, we're not Eskimos.
Well, I don't think it refers
so much to your ethnicity.
And the Native Americans who do live
here call themselves Inuit, shark meat.
The deal here is we're selling
this as a human interest story.
The strange snowmen who play
on a lake... the Mystery boys.
We don't know who they are
or what they are.
All we know is they have poor dental
health and can skate like the wind.
It's a hockey game.
- How does she know what kind of dental health we have?
- Guys!
Guys!
It's just a name, you know?
Nobody thinks the Dallas Cowboys
are actually cowboys.
- If this ends up making fun of us...
- Scott, it won't.
- You think I'd let that happen?
- For business, who knows?
- Excuse me?
- He's right.
- You'd bite off your own jimmy if the price were right.
- Really, Scott?
My own jimmy? You know what?
Why don't you go plan a rummage sale...
- or renew a fishing licence?
- If you try pulling something, I'll be so far up your ass...
- Gentlemen.
- You sorry piece of tit meat!
- Just talkin' about the game.
- Yeah.
If nothing else,
it's good for morale.
Good night.
No blood.
Judge!
- He started it.
- Don't!
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
I don't know how to coach.
You taught half the kids in this town
how to skate. You played 2-A college.
You understand
North American hockey.
Shit, they used to call you
the Bear.
That was then.
Okay, Judge.
If we're gonna make a game of it,
it should be you.
It won't be, John.
Come on! Pull it off!
People of Mystery,
I give you...
your very own Zamboni.
- Now, don't be alarmed.
- It looks 100 years old.
Well, it works just like new,
and it's kind of in keeping with
the whole idea, don't you think?
What whole idea?
Scott, you got a Zamboni here
in Mystery, Alaska.
Yeah.
The original.
Why'd you say yes to boards?
Sponsors?
You guys have never played with boards.
Won't that be a huge advantage to the Rangers?
John?
You've been smiling
a lot lately.
- Excuse me?
- Ever since he came back.
Charlie.
You've been smiling a little more.
John, that was high school.
This is not a pond.
The fans are into it.
Let's play hockey.
- Oh, there we go.
- Oh, Domi and Langdon.
Well, eight seconds in. Domi leads
the league in penalty minutes.
A couple of short rights knocks the helmet
off. Another one. Are they gonna get tired?
- I don't know.
- We're playing these guys?
Oh, he's landing a couple of big ones,
and so is Domi.
He's got the fans
into this one early, Sam.
Yo, maybe we should fast-forward
to the hockey part.
- Yeah.
- Good idea.
- Come on.
- Come on!
- Caboose, holding on back there?
- Yeah.
- Toot, toot!
- Uh-oh! Uh-oh, we're gonna crash!
- Aah!
- Oh, no!
- What happened down here?
Are you okay? Let me see.
Are you all right?
It's a Rockewellian Christmas
up here...
skating, barbecues, snow.
We're here with defenseman
Matt Marden and...
- Cut.
- What?
I can't feel my fingers.
You need to rub 'em on
a nice warm Yuletide log.
I beg your pardon?
Look. Christmas is a lonely day
for a guy to be choking his own chicken.
And, as women reporters go,
I find you supple.
Oh, that was lovely. It's a shame
we weren't rolling for that.
I'm sure he'd be happy
to repeat it.
- You need to relax.
- Charles!
Do you like massages?
- Tree, take the man up front!
- Defense!
Tree, you've got to take
the man!
- Jesus!
- All right, all right, all right, all right.
Sorry, Johnny.
- Don't say you're sorry.
- Okay.
Sorry.
Tree, am I a big guy?
Yeah, Johnny.
No. Look.
See? You're the big guy.
And we need you to start
playing like a big guy.
Okay?
Are you a big guy?
- Yes, Johnny.
- Come on. Say it.
Say it!
- I'm a big guy!
- Okay!
- Okay? Okay?
- Okay.
Okay, hit me.
I don't want
to hit you, Johnny.
- Come on, Tree. Hit me!
- Johnny...
I'm notJohnny!
I'm a New York Ranger!
- Hit me!
- Stop it!
You look like the back end
of a moose, Sasquatch.
You all right?
Just like that, Tree.
- You hit me like that,
I'll kick your ass.
Eskimo soup.
I'm beginning to have
second thoughts about this.
And having Chuck Fuck as our liaison
with the network doesn't help.
If they're gonna be pouring
a lot of money into it,
I suppose you have to let them sell it.
I suppose.
Besides, if they're going to
be doing a profile on the town,
it's as good
as a commercial.
Our tourism might grow.
You know, this is the kind
of opportunity that...
What?
What's that?
Skank Marden's
been in this bed.
You gotta be kidding me.
Well, that's just great.
Shit!
- What?
- Uh, we got a problem.
- What problem?
- Uh...
They're not coming.
What do you mean,
not coming?
Evidently,
the Ranger players...
filed some kind of grievance
with the players' union,
- and, uh...
- We tapped ourselves on the construction.
- Are you saying that we're not
going to get that money now?
Uh, I don't think so, no.
I'm really sorry, Scott.
I don't... I don't even...
Jesus Christ, Scott!
Ow!
Jesus! Oh, man!
Hey, hey.
That's enough.
It's keeping the kids awake.
Come on.
I should arrest him.
That's what I should do.
Arrest him for what?
Fraud.
Hey, he promised something
that he couldn't deliver.
This town spent money,
relying on
Charlie Danner's word.
Flying in here
on a helicopter,
- swinging the New York Rangers from his belt.
- Come on, John.
- You can't blame Charlie for that.
- Who else is there to blame?
You want to sympathize
with the guy, fine.
But I really do not
need you taking his side.
- Okay. What is going on?
- You tell me.
Okay, I think I've been pretty patient
with this little jealousy thing.
The truth is, I've been a little bit
flattered. Now I'm getting insulted.
- You're insulted?
- Yes, John.
When you read my smiling at him
as a threat, that insults me.
It is not just
a random smile, Donna.
Ever since he came back...
you've been walking around with
a big "what if" on your face.
We've been married 12 years.
Three kids.
Sweetheart,
I know your smiles.
And that smile is not for me.
John, everyone in this goddamn town
peeks over the snowbank and wonders.
Except you wonder what
it would be like with him...
Charlie fuckin' Danner!
Don't talk to me
about betrayal.
You became half dead the minute you were
bumped from that team. You disappeared.
This is not an easy place
for a woman, John.
I thank God every day
I gave birth to boys.
I never chose to stay.
I chose you.
Give me that,
at least.
Move that puck, fellas!
He's opening up!
Pass it out
to the wing!
Pass the puck! Pass that puck!
That a boy!
Over here!
Whoo!
Hi.
Young man,
lift your elbows.
And that'll keep the blade
flat on the ice.
I mean, you paid
for the whole stick.
You might as well use it all, huh?
Try it.
- Good! Good, McGowan!
- Good.
Hey. I'm goin' on a piss later.
You wanna join me?
No.
The league is taking
the players' union...
to federal court
in New York on Tuesday.
It might help if Mystery
had a face there.
There's an estoppel argument
you could make.
Implied third-party contract too.
Hmm.
Well, now we really have something
to talk about, don't we?
You slept with another man.
What's to talk about,
MaryJane?
All I've got...
is the notion that being
adored by your husband...
is enough in life.
You never touch me.
Go ahead.
Nothing in the basic agreement
allows them...
to schedule
exhibition games.
- Of course we can schedule exhibition
games. - Pre-season exhibition, but...
Your Honor, nothing has ever limited
this to pre-season. You know this, Harold.
It's a cheap stunt,
Your Honor, and everybody knows that.
They want the Ranger players to go up to
the North Pole and play pond hockey...
with a bunch of Eskimos.
It's a big gimmick.
I mean, Mr. Pruitt himself...
has brought one of his
lumberjack players with him...
to help him further
the exploitation.
Objection, Your Honor.
That's-That's not
a very nice thing to say.
Your Honor, we've already
spent a lot of money on this game.
You can sue the league
for restitution.
That's assuming that money
damages could make us whole.
But our reputation
has been hurt.
Reputation? Price World tried
to move up there, you opened fire.
What reputation?
- Could I be heard?
- Go ahead.
We do have our pride.
And...
And, uh, maybe sometimes it's a little
too connected to how well we play hockey,
but we do have our pride.
And all of you,
and all the TV commentators...
have been going around
saying that this is a farce...
that this
is all a big joke.
Our town is a big joke.
- Is there a legal argument coming?
- It's estoppel.
It's-It's in my brief.
What-What did you call...
You called my friend something before.
- What did you call him?
- A lumberjack.
That boy has a heart bigger
than this whole courtroom.
He plays to play.
He skates to skate!
He don't make
a million bucks a year!
He loves the game of hockey!
He loves it.
Judge,
you can't take this game
away from us.
You can't.
It's not about money.
It's about our...
Mr. Pruitt?
Are you all right?
- Bailey?
- Mr. Pruitt?
- Bailey? Bailey? Bailey?
Somebody get this man some help!
He's having a heart attack!
Somebody help him!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org