Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Resync: Xenzai[NEF]
Good day Mam
Good day
Who is she, Mike?
I'm working on it
Fiona Birch
Alias Fiona Nielson
born in London, England, 1978
Wanted for murders in Spain
Brazil and United States
And here you're gonna like this
It says here she was kidnapped from
her parents when she was...
She was 12 years old
Madame M likes to start them young
I'm in the lobby. Where to now?
Look to your right
Take the VIP elevator up to 12th floor
He's in 1238
Hey guys
What took so long?
Nobody sells take away around here.
Cappuccino, right?
Here you go, Mike
Why don't you cut him some slack
He's new on the job
To be a good agent Jack
you need to think fast
It shouldn't take you twenty minutes
to get a cup of coffee
Sorry, sir. Won't happen again
So why don't we just arrest her?
The point is to let her escape
so she brings us to Madame M
I like her technique
What technique?
You know, like Mata Hari
She uses her incredible body to either
get the secret from the enemy
Or...
Or what?
Or she'd kill you
You wanna take your little
picnic outside Jack?
Sorry, Mike
You got something else to eat?
Um, no
I think I need a sandwich, Jack
Now?
Yes now
Alright
Waiter?
Can I have 2 croissant sandwiches please?
Yes, sir
Jill!
Oh, shit!
May I join you?
You are an amazing fighter
Would you like to have this?
It's yours if you want it
Go ahead and choose whatever you like
I can take you to
where all the best fighters go
You can become one of them
Do you want to come with me?
Oh shit!
October 11th
Another girl has been reported missing...
...bringing the total to 40
Their ages are all around 13 years of age
Although their nationalities
and family backgrounds vary
it is interesting to note that
each of these girls...
...excels in either martial arts or sport
Ever since the Rome incident
Madame M and her organization
have not resurfaced
In the meantime, little girls are
disappearing all over the globe
Could it be... one female assassin dead...
and dozens more being trained
to take her place?
If that's the case, I'm afraid
these girls will be scarred for life...
and can never be helped
This is your new home
And these girls are your sisters
I want to go home
I want my mommy!
For the time being
you can think of me as your mommy
You are not my mommy
You can't tell me what to do
Do you really want to go?
Yes!
I don't like it here and I don't like you!
Alright, you can go now
Go
Girls!
I would love to officially welcome you
to a brand new world
Here every exercise
every meal and every class
will be with one thing in mind...
to create a team of world class fighters
Is that clear?
Yes, sir!
We are two hundred miles away from
the nearest island
And if you try to run away,
you'll be shot
Any questions?
No sir!
Hi!
You're the one who came in with me
today right?
Yeah
My name is Charlene, what's yours?
Katherine
I like the name, Katherine
Thank you
Everybody, come! Come on!
I say we go now
tonight,
as soon as they turn the lights out
There's only one guard in the
tower and one on the pier
If we can just get to that side
of the bay before they see us
there's a boat we can use
to make our escape
We'll have to row,
but it's our only chance
I've seen that boat,
we can't all fit in it
I didn't think everyone
here has the guts to go
Alright. So who's in?
Raise your hands if you want to go
What are you doing?
I want to go with them
You won't make it
Ready. First ready position!
First!
1 , 2...
Change sides
1 , 2. OK
1 , 2...
I'm too tired, Katt
Don't stop. Keep going, Charlene!
Look, it's Ann-Marie, Renee
And Susan
Come on, keep going!
Move your ass. Go!
You people are barbaric. Go! Go! Go!
Move! Move! Go!
Go! Keep going!
Come on! Go! Go!
Come on, move your ass!
Use your legs. Use your arms. Go! Go!
Come on go!
Attack!
The centraI nervous system
and the delivery of electric pulses
from the brain to the rest of the body
depends almost entirely on
your skeleton network
and in particular the spinal column
Remember what I said about
detaching the C-5 vertebrate
It cuts the nerve cortex
instantly paralyzing your victim
Death by suffocation normally follows
Keep your back straight. Your head still
Wiggle your hip. Now stop here
And you pose
Turn
Stop. And turn
Today's lesson. Working through pain
To be a fighter, to be a killer
you must learn how to work with
the elements
I don't care if you are wet...
or if you are freezing
Your environment is your friend
It's your only friend
The water is so nice
I was sitting at the bottom
of the ocean Katt
It was so peaceful
Have you ever thought that
we would have to kill someone
That we don't even know?
I don't dare to
It's not up to you,
this is our fate together
We can't run from it
I know I can't do it
Well...
We'll make a lot of money
for our lives from it
We cannot help to do it
Come on, let's go
This is not an exercise
Today's mission is to kill
a group of enemy soldiers
They are all armed and ready to attack
They will not show any mercy
You have to fight for your survival
Good luck ladies
Let's go! Let's go!
Are you alright?
Look, we knew from the very beginning
what this is all about
And eventually we would have to kill
We're just an experiment to her
That's all. Survival of the fittest
Everything we're learning here...
is what we're gonna need out there
I know that. But today...
today just makes me feel worse about
everything
Forget about today
Think about our future
That's what I use to do as a kid
Then Madame showed up and saved me
You were awesome out there hanging
upside down from that tree and shit
Snap. Man, you should teach me that
sometime
Here let me help you
Hey you're tense.
You should relax a bit
If there is anything, just ask
I can help you
Man, did you see me today?
That fucker tried to sneak up on me
But I was really for that shit
It felt so good to kill him
Hello?
When I first came here
I had a boyfriend back home
We use to ride our bikes
everyday after school
My first memory is cleaning up
around the boxing ring
I tried to stay away
from such a lifestyle
and finally
I chose to fight in the ring
You and I are so different, Katt
And yet I can't imagine
my life without you
Listen up. Here is your assignment
Kill the nearest girl and
bring her body outside
Anyone who isn't outside
in 2 minutes...
will be shot
Wait, this is so stupid
Why are we killing each other?
Because there are ten guys
waiting outside with M16s
If we refuse there is
no way she can kill us all
There isn't time for this.
We have our orders
Congratulations ladies.
You are the survivors
You show your courage and your strength
in every imaginable situation
Take a good look around you
These girls are not
your friends anymore
Only one of you will survive
tomorrow's exercise
Who will that be?
Get some sleep, ladies
Tomorrow is graduation day for
one of you
This is bullshit!
The whole thing was bullshit
from day one!
I was wondering when it
would come to this
Tomorrow is just another exercise
That's it
Katt, if we have to face each other
Promise me you won't hold back
Get some rest
Today is the day. One of you
will earn the right to survive
Some of you may feel that
I have treated you unfairly
In fact, I'm afraid that I
might have protected you...
too much from the harsh reality of
the world outside
All of you will soon be given a number
Girl number 1 enters the cage first
She faces girl number 2
in a fight to death
The survivor must then face
two more girls
number 3 and 4
The winner then faces
three more girls
Number 5 to 7
But that's not fair!
That's right. Life isn't fair
You're sending us to our death
Maybe, but an assassin knows...
the path to your own mortality
is only a footstep away
What if girl number 1 survives
the first three rounds?
If she survives, she'll have to fight
the last four girls
One on four
The fighting is over when
only one of you remains
Behind you is a box containing numbers
Choose one and accept your fate
I want out of here. I don't want to die!
You have no choice
All you can choose is your weapon
Oh look, we're in the same group!
We can be like a team
I watch your back, you watch mine
It's a win-win situation!
From the moment I realized that
I was an orphan
I knew I didn't have future
Charlene, if I die in this cage tonight
you have to remember me
We will always remember each other
Charlene, don't be stupid!
She took my number.
I'm supposed to go first!
There is only one rule
inside the cage
No matter what method you use
to kill your opponent
you cannot leave, you cannot surrender
You have no friends, no support
All you can believe in is yourself
Today you fight until you die...
or until you are the last survivor
It's all very simple, ladies.
Live or die
Do not disappoint me
We've been friends for six years
I don't want to kill you
Maybe now you understand survival of
the fittest...
and the need to eliminate the weak
Kill her! Kill her!
Shut up!
Get off me!
Charlene, are you alright?
Oh my god!
You have to win
I will for both of us
Don't quit on me
If we join forces,
we'll be invincible
Nobody can touch us
I am invincible
You have no chance!
Don't kill her
Please
Stop!
That's it!
Bravo, girls!
What a terrific performance
You have exceeded my expectations
I have decided to break my own rules...
and keep all three of you
I'm glad we can finally sit down and
have dinner together
Let's do this more often in the future
To be honest with you ladies
I'm still in shock about the other day
It was never my plan to keep three of you
But I'm glad that I did
Let's have a drink
Cheers
Jing, taste your wine...
and tell me the year and the labeI
Petrus, 1971
Katt, your's?
Vega Sicilia, 1985
Hmmm. Good
Charlene?
It's table wine
Very good
You ladies know your wine
In a month
you'll leave here with new identities
You will be making more than
five million dollars a year
Soon
you'll become three of the most
wanted women in this world
In five years our contract be over
You can stay working for me or
you can go free
Are you okay?
I feel weak. She poisoned us
Now. I've only given you...
a mild sedative to help you relax
After today your body
no longer belongs to you
It is now your greatest weapon
You must be willing...
to do anything to please a man
no matter how vile
Because a man's happiest moment...
is also his weakest
Okay, let's go
This way, this way
He's waiting for you
Yes more... please more
More...
Do you know why you are here?
To please you
You are the most unusual young woman
I'm glad you think so
I'm sure my cousin thought the same thing...
before you killed him
Charlene, hurry!
This is great, there's no way out!
Hurry! Help me block the door!
Katt, we are stuck here!
There's got to be a way out
Don't worry, I'll get us out of here
Forget it, it's over!
Hurry!
Go on. Hurry!
No!
If this is it, we end it together!
I won't leave you. I won't!
Charlene listen!
I promise
we'll see each other outside
I promise!
I can't lose you...
Go! Go!
Please. Go!
Based on the markings surrounding
the fractured vertebra
the coroner seems to think that
he was killed by a woman
One of my first assignments was
following a suspect
named Madeline Ho
a.k.a. Madame M
Whoever did this ruptured the
central nerve with her bare hands
It's been six years since
I've seen a body like this
Jack, there's something else
you should know
The coroner found a blood sample
on the body
which doesn't belong to the victim
Run a DNA check
and send the results over to
missing persons
If my hunch is correct, Madame M
has decided to come out of her hole
Charlene Ching. All these years
you've been missing
What has happened to you?
You must be a different person now
But how much have you really changed?
Please, goddess Tin Hau
bless my only daughter Charlene
I hope she has found peace...
and joy in this world
Back again?
How are you?
Don't worry, your prayers will be heard
Goddess Tin Hau will send her blessing...
to you and your daughter
I pray.
It is Tin Hau's wish...
for me to see my daughter again
Excuse me
Mrs. Ching?
Jack Chen, CIA
What can I do for you?
I came to ask you a few questions
about your daughter
Did you find her?
Please tell me
that she's still alive
There's been a series of murders
throughout Europe
We think the killer is
a professional assassin
DNA tests points to your daughter as
the killer
That's impossible!
How could my daughter
have become a killer?
Six years ago, forty girls disappeared
at about the same time
They're all trying to be
professional assassins
We think Charlene is one of them
My God...
There's a good chance
your daughter may
either be in Hong Kong
or on her way here
If that's the case
she may try and contact you
I hope I can count
on your cooperation
You can't imagine the pain
a mother feels...
when she loses her child
I've put all that pain...
and guilt behind me
I'm sorry to put you
through all this
But my job is to find a murderer
and that's what I intend to do
Mr. Chen,
even if my daughter is a killer
what makes you think I would help you
arrest her?
Mrs. Ching?
I thought I asked you
to leave me alone
I want to help your daughter
But I have to find her first
Has she contacted you
in the last few days?
Jack, first you tell me...
my daughter is
a professional killer
Now, you think I'm hiding her from
the law?
Please, excuse me
Go! Go!
If you don't stop following me
I will kill you
I've been on this case for six years
How can I not follow you?
That's your problem, Mr.
Not mine
No, this is your problem
Do you recognize her?
Do you, Charlene?
Let's go!
Hurry!
I'm arresting you
because I want to help you
How can you shoot someone
in front of your mother?
Do you think she actually forgot you?
Don't you have any feelings at all?
Do you want to live a normal life?
I'm afraid you've got
the wrong person
Charlene is dead
Listen Charlene...
or whatever you want
to call yourself...
We're stuck here and it's cold...
and to be honest
I don't know how much longer
I can keep my arm up
I knew you wouldn't kill me
It's not that I can't.
I won't
I'm a federal agent.
I'm here to arrest you
Are you OK?
Here
Take my coat
I've been looking for a lot of girls
who disappeared just like yourself
Can you tell me...
where you've been the past few years?
Or who's been running the operation?
Forget it...
I knew you wouldn't tell me
But I'll find out
I'll find out by myself.
I'll never give up
Are you sure
you don't want your jacket?
You look cold
Don't worry about me.
I'm not cold
I'm a man
What? What's so funny?
The metabolism of men...
runs fifteen percent
faster than women
So technically, men are more resistant...
to the cold than women
I don't know about you...
but I'm freezing
Come here...
we stand a better chance
If we do like the Eskimos
and combine our body heat
Come on
You're a good guy...
you know that?
Case 538, day five
Despite the lack of cooperation
from the local branch
my investigation continues to progress
I am watching the mother of one of
the China Doll assassins
Hopefully, I wrap things up before
anyone else gets killed
For the moment, my only lead is
Charlene Ching
I believe Charlene was...
she said the most amazing thing in that
ice-cream truck...
she's lucky I gave her my jacket
What am I saying?
Even if I have to do it on my own
I will solve this case
Jack Chen, agent 75394
signing out...
...while officially on sick
leave in Hong Kong
Mommy!
Once I'm all grown up...
and well trained in martial arts
I'll protect you...
and beat up all the bad guys
Charlene?
No!
help...
Freeze!
Don't move! Drop your weapon!
Shit!
Charlene...
Take her and get out of here!
Use your gun!
I'm here to visit my mom
Why would I have a gun?
Where's your gun?
I dropped it
Watch out!
Mommy, I'm sorry...
I'm sorry I wasn't here
to protect you
I am the one who is sorry
Seeing you alive...
God has answered my prayers
You're going to be fine
There's a hospital nearby
I'll carry her
She's losing a lot of blood.
Put some pressure on the wound
Don't tell me what to do
Let's just get her to the hospital!
Jack...
She's trying to find a Jack Chen?
That's me
Please Jack, don't arrest my daughter
I promise you, Mrs. Ching I won't
Thank you
Even if someday
you do have to take me in
Jack? Is that your name?
That's right
I don't lie about my identity
like some other people
I've known about you
for the past six years Charlene
Look out!
Thanks
I'm just confused...
I don't know anymore
I don't know if I'm here for
professional or personal reasons
Charity, I think?
Goodness of your own heart?
Don't worry. Your mom will be fine
You really are a good guy
What's the matter?
The last time you said that
you hit me with your gun
Here
I know you'll be back for her
And when you do,
I'm going to be here too
I know, Jack
I know
What about the contract?
You can't see your mom
They'll kill you both
Trust me, Katt
I know when to give life
and I know when to take it
I'll make a deal with you
Finish this one last job
and we'll consider our contract over
Besides, you wouldn't want any
more harm to come to your mother
would you?
Alright. I'll take it
That's my girl
Welcome, Madame
allow me to introduce myself
My name is Ryuichi
You know the terms?
As you require, 10%
in crisp, unmarked bills
There's a traitor
within my organization
His name is Kenji
You know what I want
The thing is
I would like to watch as he dies
If you watch
it's more work more money
No one changes a deal on me
Not now, not ever!
Alright!
Since you have the balls to ask for
more money
I know you won't fail
Your greed will not allow it
Ryuichi is meeting Kenji tonight
at a local disco
Your Job is to kill Kenji before he escapes
I'll be outside waiting
in case you need backup
Shit! It's a trap!
I'll see you in hell...
You crossed the line, Madame
just for a little money
Kenji doesn't even exist!
That's what drives all the assassins
It's what brings you here tonight!
My friend Carlos...
was killed by a dancing female assassin
Do you have any idea...
how lonely I'll get without him?
I bring you here because...
I want you to suffer
as I know he suffered
Ladies. Welcome to my nirvana!
Run!
As for the darts
it's just a friendly
little aphrodisiac
Run!
You should already be feeling warm...
and happy
Hurry!
You'll come for your friend!
We'll see you at Pier 14
Hello?
Who is this?
Charlene where are you?
Charlene!
Jack
What happened?
Charlene! It's me, Jack
Are you OK?
What's wrong with you?
Wait...
No!
Stop...Stop...Stop
What is going on?
What's wrong with you?
I...I was drugged...
some kind of aphrodisiac...
We need to calm down.
Charlene!
Charlene! Charlene!
Charlene...
Charlene!
I'm here to catch Madame M and
her China Dolls
Not take advantage of a young
beautiful girl.
Not like this
I could arrest her
But now...
What am I saying?
I'm such an idiot!
Jack?
I just want you to know that
actually I'm quite traditional
I just want you to know...
it's okay
Dear Jack, if I could live
my life over again
I would love to be a normal girl
and have a normal life
But I accepted my fate a long time ago
What I am prevents me from being
a responsible daughter
So Please, watch over my mother
until she gets well
Maybe one day...
fate will smile upon us and
we'll see each other again
Charlene
Every time
just when I can reach out
and almost touch you
you disappear
Help me! Charlene!
Help me... Help me... Charlene
Help me...
Oh Charlene... save me!
Oh my God! Katt! ... Katt!
Charlene...Charlene...Charlene
You've finally come to save me
It will be a pleasure to watch...
as you and Ryuichi duel to the death
Let her go, Ryuichi!
I'm the one who killed Carlos, not her!
I've finally figured out
how to play with my China Dolls
It'd be nice if you girls came
with instructions, you know?
Stop it!
Katt!
Please... kill me...
But we made a promise, Katt!
That we would always stay together
Our time...is in the next life...
Okay, it's time to say goodbye to
your friend
Bye bye!
No!
Okay
Ten seconds
I love you, Charlene...
and I will always...
be with you.
Always...
No!
You and I are both driven...
by vengeance
Let's settle the score...
using more primitive weapons
You're beat up now
You can't even see anymore
I'm afraid our little duel
is just about over
I have one chance left.
Will my strength fail me?
Focus
Focus on one thing...
and everything
feel the vibrations
follow the energy...
Visualize the stillness of water
and let your heart...
become water...
I'm leaving tomorrow
have to go back to the States
Whenever you have time
Please come and visit
I'd like that
You think this is just superstitious
nonsense, don't you?
No. I was just thinking...
the Chinese are so strong in beliefs
You know I really never had a religion
But somehow...
this place makes me feel...peaceful
If you like, you can make a wish
Perhaps it will come true
really?
Try it. What have you got to lose?
Please let Katt be filled
with joy and happiness
And let her know
that I miss her very much
Please make sure that certain someone
the guy I told you about...
I wish the woman I love
is happy and safe
And I pray that someday...
I'll be able to tell her
how much I care for her
No. 68
Two with one mind will meet
hand in hand playing music
and dancing
I'm sorry I don't understand
Very strange, a woman was here earlier
She has the same fortune
Was she looking for someone?
Yes
She said she was looking for...
a man she met in a refrigerator
Refrigerator?
No, ice-cream truck
Where is she?
She just left
Thanks!
Call me superstitious
but sometimes I think I can feel
Charlene's presence
It's as if we're heading off
in the same orbit
If we both stay on this path
and don't stray
we'll see each other again some day
I can only hope that day
is sometime very soon
Resync: Xenzai[NEF]
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org