Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Ma'Dere?
- Morning, Joe.
You know, Christmas is almost here.
Here's your clothes, all packed.
Just put them in the garage.
How long do you think
we're gonna keep this up?
As long as the good Lord allows.
- Want me to get your bathroom stuff?
- I'll get it.
All right, guys. Let's go. Your
dad's gonna be here in a minute.
- You said you were outside.
- I just had a few more things to do.
- That's not what you said.
- I need to turn off...
But it's okay.
Let's hit the freeway
before traffic gets bad.
- Let's go. All right.
- Yes, Malcolm.
All right, guys. Let's rock and roll.
Tonight?
Thank you.
- T, let me get my drink, please, baby.
- You got it, Q.
Christmas in Chicago
is always slow, ain't it?
Oh, yeah, man, you know,
everybody out shopping.
Here you go.
Come on, let's go!
Damn!
Fool.
Baby, what is that?
This a early Christmas present
from Joe. It's called a Nikon.
It's the Rolls-Royce of cameras.
Joe! Tell me you didn't get
this boy that camera.
- Don't start.
- We talked about that.
- It's Christmas, baby.
- It's too expensive.
Let it go.
Matter of fact, snap this.
Here.
- Merry Christmas. Now...
- Guess he told you.
Boy, take this grocery list
and go to the store.
Before that lip gets you into trouble.
- This everything? You sure?
- Yeah.
I wrote it down.
Sometimes you forget stuff.
I gotta come back.
You forget stuff and have
to go back. Hurry up.
I have to change clothes.
Get ready to cook.
Ma'Dere want me to go to the store.
You want something?
No, I'm good.
I wanted to thank you too
for the camera.
- You know, I love it.
- When I was your age...
...I wanted a watch about as bad
as you wanted that camera.
Nobody could afford it.
You take some nice pictures
with that thing.
- Come here, boy.
- Oh, man.
You gonna do all this
lovey-dove stuff.
- I'm almost grown.
- Go on, get out of here.
She gonna start cooking any minute.
Don't hurt nobody on that bike.
Merry Christmas, Lisa.
Oh, baby, please. You're gonna
drive me crazy with that camera.
Come on, where your
Christmas spirit at? Come on.
- Ma, you told them 6:00, right?
- They know.
- They should be here.
- Stop. They been eating dinner at 6...
...ever since they could eat.
They know.
- Look.
- Baby, get out with that.
You're making me nervous. Go.
Come and taste some of this.
- I want your stamp of approval.
- Okay.
Should have told them 4,
then they'd be here on time.
It's frustrating being the only person
in this family that understands a clock.
You know your brothers
and sisters are always late.
That don't make it right.
Why don't you come late,
so that way you on time?
- You know what? See, you...
- Mama, get her.
This is like hitting the lottery.
- Especially if we finance it ourselves.
- Oh, yeah. Absolutely.
I'd be a millionaire before I'm 40.
I should be able to get
a couple hundred thousand...
...while I'm in New York.
But you're gonna have
to match that, at least.
I'm pretty sure
I can get a chunk of it here.
- Well, that would be a happy holiday.
- Yes, it would.
- Now, that's a car right there.
- Come on, Joe.
I'll call you when I get a chance.
- Nice.
- Hey.
Nice.
Got that new-car smell
and everything.
Damn, you got your name on the car?
Can't nobody steal it.
Hey, Joe, you need to get
some of these for your funeral home.
Hey, how much this set you back?
My old man's got a dealership
in San Francisco...
...so I got a deal,
but they run for about 60.
It's a smart investment.
Kelli's got herself a new car too.
Merry Christmas.
- Guess she's smart like you, Malcolm.
- Hey, girl.
- Joe, how you doing?
- Good.
- Good to see you.
- You too.
You look like your mama
more and more every day.
Get over here and hug me, girl.
- And if you wasn't my cousin...
- Oh, yeah. You're all talk.
Maybe, but when you gonna
put me in a commercial?
- Malcolm.
- Kelli.
Let's get inside.
Mama can't wait to see you.
- Get the rest of those bags.
- Okay.
- What you got in these bags, girl?
- Lots of goodies.
- Yeah? You bring anything for me?
- Of course.
If I get any free time,
I'm gonna call you later.
Lisa, you regifted me last year.
I don't like that.
You know you wanted
that frame, and that's...
- All right?
- You think I didn't notice. I noticed it.
All right, baby. Bye.
You could've bought me something.
Did you see the frame, Rosie?
- Merry Christmas, everybody.
- Hey, merry Christmas.
Damn, Baby, look at you,
getting taller by the minute.
You guys better stop calling him Baby,
because he's almost a grown man.
He's my youngest,
no matter how tall or old he gets.
He'll always be my baby.
Ain't that right. She's just a hater.
You just treat him special
because he's your favourite.
My favourite is whoever
I'm talking to at that second.
The one that needs
Mother's love the most.
You should've called us.
Malcolm would have picked you up.
- Maybe you'd have been on time.
- I got a car.
See our new Escalade outside?
- You know, I rented a BMW convertible.
- Sexy.
- Hey, can I try that?
- Like that's gonna happen.
Can't blame a brother for trying.
So I guess that means things
are going well on the job?
I can't complain.
I just completed a perfume spot.
You need to let me come to New York
so I can get my photography on.
What you need to do is get a college
degree, just like your big sister.
So, Ma'Dere, is there anything else
we need to do around here?
- Y'all want me to make something?
- No.
What? I can cook.
Girl, you can't make reservations.
She orders up a mean Chinese.
Ten-hut.
Merry Christmas, Claude!
- Oh, my child.
- Hi, Mama.
- You look so good in your uniform.
- You look like a formal peanut.
Claude's got all them girls
going berserk.
They take one look
at a fine specimen like myself...
...and can we say "Denzel"?
Yeah, when are you gonna settle down?
Well, I know, whoever she is, just
make sure she's taking care of you...
...and she can cook like your big sis.
- Some of us were busy...
...going to college while others chose
to stay home and learn how to cook.
And those who stayed home
helped with the cleaners...
...while the rest of us,
who shall remain nameless...
...jetted off to college
the first chance they got.
Are you two listening to yourself?
A stranger wouldn't know
you were sisters.
- She started it.
- I don't care. I'm finishing it.
Kelli, fix some Kool-Aid
for the kids.
Are you sure you don't want me
to make something?
- No.
- Damn.
Don't hurt yourself.
Kool-Aid, simple.
Play to your strengths.
Stop it. Claude, let the men know...
...we'll be eating
as soon as Mel gets here.
I'm gonna get out of this uniform.
- Okay, so I just need...
- Water, sugar. Help her out, please.
Where'd you get those pants?
I look good, huh?
Gentlemen.
Ma'Dere said the food is ready.
We'll eat when Mel gets here.
- So, what's up with you, Malcolm?
- Nothing much, man.
Good things. Good things.
Except for the storm on its way.
Who said it don't rain in California?
Rains, fires, mudslides.
I think God don't like California.
- Hey, everybody. Merry Christmas.
- Hey!
Oh, my God. Look at my... Hey!
- Hey, Fred. How you doing?
- Hey. Now we can eat.
Welcome home, Mel.
Ma'Dere didn't tell me
you got leave. Hi.
I couldn't miss Mama's cooking.
I missed you.
Where's everybody? Where's Lisa?
- In the kitchen.
- Let me go say hi to her.
You go do that. Get in there.
You got a name, homes?
Devean.
Brooks.
Well, you know, she did
always like them articulate.
I'm about to go change.
I'll show you your room.
- Come on, get your bags.
- It's okay.
Y'all are punks, man.
- Devean Brooks.
- Brooks.
Can we join hands?
Bless, O Lord, almighty God...
...the Whitfield family and home.
May health, purity...
...goodness, meekness,
and every virtue, Father...
...reign on this Christmas holiday.
May all who visit here...
...be blessed with faithfulness
to thy law and thankfulness to God...
...the Father, Son and the Holy Spirit.
May this blessing remain
on this family, Father...
...this home
and all who dwell here, Father...
...through Christ, our Lord.
- Amen.
- Okay. Dig in, everybody.
- Yes, sir.
Pass that corn bread down here.
Macaroni and cheese.
- What...? Don't put that on your plate.
- I got peas.
No, that's turkey.
Everybody's good?
Okay, okay, everybody.
Let's do the family business first.
Here are the shares
of the profit from the cleaners.
Okay? Each one of you has your own.
There you are.
- Merry Christmas.
- Thank you, Mama.
You know you didn't have to do that.
We didn't expect anything.
- I do. Thank you, Mama.
- Oh, you're welcome, baby.
- Can you warm this up?
- Sure.
- It came out of the oven.
- He likes his food hot.
I'll put it in the microwave.
That thing's going off
like a drug dealer.
Well, if you must know,
it's my ladies.
It's Christmastime, and they wanna
spend time with a brother.
I know Baby better not be
bringing any babies in here.
It's time for me to have
that special conversation.
Too late.
Me and Joe already had it.
Yeah, I learned more
than I needed to. Trust me.
I'm gonna take this in the other room.
Excuse me.
Thank you, baby.
You mind?
- Thank you.
- Oh, you're welcome.
When you're finished...
...pass the plate over here
and I'll chew it for him too.
- Shut up, Kelli.
- So, Joe...
...what do you got planned
for the holiday?
Well, after breakfast,
Baby's gonna take the family photo.
We're gonna go buy the tree.
Then Christmas morning
we're going to church.
I didn't know your father
was a minister.
No, he's not. He's a deacon.
And he's not my father.
My bad.
Yeah, our father moved on.
I'm sorry to hear that.
No, he didn't die. He just moved on.
So, Devean...
...you and Mel go
to the same school, huh?
She goes to Spelman.
It's an all-girls school.
I knew that.
- No, you didn't.
- Yes, I did. I knew that.
- I go to Morehouse.
- So...
...how do you like attending
an all-black college?
- Don't start with that nonsense.
- I went to Princeton...
I went to Harvard. What's your point?
Can you let the man
speak for himself?
Go on. I just wanna know
what your experience is like...
...attending an all-black college.
- Ignore him.
I wanna answer. Morehouse has certain
foundational principles...
...by which its existence stands.
It includes an appreciation for the
ideas of justice, equality, democracy...
...humane treatment of all people...
...development of spiritual self
and community.
Sounds like you got it from
the mission statement.
I did. But that's also why I go there.
Not because it's all-black...
...but because it embodies
beliefs and traditions I value.
The fact that all the students
look just like me is a bonus.
- I like that, young man.
- Well said.
Well, Mel, your boyfriend has
a good head on his shoulders.
I hope some of his smarts rubs off
on my little professional student.
Stop, now. Mel's smart.
She's just, you know, slow.
- Getting her four-year degree in what?
- Seven years.
I've changed my major a few times.
Nothing wrong with that.
First a doctor, then a journalist.
Now what?
- Pre-law.
Mel's major is always determined
by whomever she's dating at the time.
Devean, what's your major?
- Pre-law.
- Damn.
Come on.
That is wrong on so many
different levels.
That was so good, Ma'Dere.
We have some sock-it-to-me cake.
You want some?
As tempting as that sounds, Ma'Dere,
I do have to make a couple more stops.
Let me see you out. Hold up.
- Bye, family.
- Bye.
Bye, Fred.
- That boy, he need to slow down.
- He does.
I know.
How many kids he have now?
- Six?
- Seven.
- Seven?
I'm gonna hurt him real bad
when we find him.
Not till we get that 25 G's
he owes Luther.
Or Luther will hurt you.
Don't let your temper
get you dead, man.
What happens
if he can't cover the bet?
It's on Luther, man. I wouldn't wanna
be Quentin Whitfield, though.
- We about to run a Boston on you.
- Believe that if you want to.
I think now is a good time for us
to discuss the dry-cleaner situation.
We have a dry-cleaner situation?
Ma'Dere's been running
the cleaners for 20 years.
What little money she makes
goes to maintaining this house.
Whatever's left over after that,
she gives us in these yearly cheques...
...that amount to, what, lunch money?
You spending way too much money
on lunch.
Look, we each own a percentage
of the cleaners.
I think it's a good idea if we sold it.
You trying to sell the cleaners?
- She wanna sell her portion, let her.
- Hey, I'll buy it.
You can't sell a percentage.
We have to sell all of it.
I guess you're shit out of luck...
...because we don't
have to do anything.
Well, we haven't been
doing anything.
And I'm the one that's keeping
the books.
How is Ma'Dere gonna maintain
this place if we sell?
Mel, she doesn't need
a place this big.
You trying to sell the house too?
Well, especially since Baby
is gonna be graduating soon.
I mean, he's gonna wanna
move out eventually.
Says who? I ain't going nowhere.
Please. All these little girls
chasing after you...
...you are gonna wanna get
your own place.
All I know is everybody here
but me came home for the holidays.
You sell this house and you ain't gonna
have a home to come back to.
It's that simple. I mean,
do what y'all want.
I got a date. I'm gonna holler at y'all.
Well, despite what Baby says, he is
gonna wanna move out eventually.
This place is just too big
for Joe and Ma'Dere.
I mean, they can get
a smaller place. Maybe a condo.
What makes you think Ma'Dere
wants to live with Joe?
Hello. He's been living with her
since you left for school.
- Joe's been living here?
- Where have you been?
Think you the only one
getting her freak on?
Okay, stop. My God.
That is too much information.
I can't hear about Ma'Dere
getting her freak on.
I don't wanna intrude
in family business...
Then don't.
This was probably your idea, anyway.
You know, Kelli...
...I'm not gonna dignify that
with a response.
You don't have to.
You put her up to this.
- Oh, come on.
- So you think...
...I'm not smart enough
to come up with this?
No, you're weak-willed
and easily influenced.
- So you're saying my wife is stupid.
- I think she said "weak-willed."
I said, you sometimes allow
other people to think for you.
- So now I can't think for myself?
- You know what?
Why don't you concentrate
on the paprika?
Kelli, I know exactly where
I wanna put the paprika. Kelli.
Everybody just bring it down a notch.
It's not that deep.
The thing to do is just
to put in a family vote.
Well, we can't have a family vote
without the whole family.
Quentin isn't here, so there.
Dessert, anyone?
Go ahead, now.
Go, bougie. Go, bougie. Go, bougie.
That's my baby right there!
Come on, Devean.
Let's see what you got.
Come on, Mama.
He's here.
Quentin! Oh, my goodness.
- Hey, Mama.
- Oh, baby. You're home.
- Oh, look at you.
- Whitfield!
So I've been doing a lot of travelling,
you know, touring. I went to Japan.
I recorded an album out there.
It's been four years.
You haven't changed a bit.
You still look great.
- Don't blow his head up.
- Thank you, baby.
- You look good too.
- Thank you.
You didn't bring no luggage, man?
No, no. I just, you know...
I got another tour,
so I sent my stuff ahead.
So you're not gonna be
staying past Christmas?
Ma, I might make it back
before New Year's.
I'm just not sure yet.
Well, I guess I'll go up
and finish your room.
I wasn't expecting you to be home.
Lisa, take care of him, now,
till I get back.
Oh, my gosh.
You have got to see Baby.
- He's almost as tall as you.
- Get out of here.
- He really is.
- He's not short like you?
Oh, be quiet.
You won't believe
the stuff Joe has planned.
- Joe?
- Yes.
We have a big breakfast
in the morning.
And then the mens are gonna go
get the Christmas tree.
On Christmas morning,
we'll be going to church.
Church? You know I don't do church.
Come on, man.
So, what's that mean, man?
You don't do church.
Church ain't something you do.
It's a place you go to commune
in God's house.
I don't believe in God.
- Not in the traditional sense.
- Not in the traditional sense?
I mean, I'm a spiritual person,
you know.
I believe in a higher source. But...
- But you don't believe in God.
- I don't believe in your God, Joe.
Okay.
I'm gonna go let Ma'Dere
know I'm leaving.
- I'll see y'all.
- Okay.
All right. You do that.
- Good night, Joe.
- Good night. Drive safe.
- Why you gotta be like that?
- Whatever. Whatever.
- "You do that, Joe."
- He ain't my daddy.
How he come in?
We having a meeting.
- Come on, now. You know it's Joe.
- I don't care.
Quentin is the problem.
If Quentin says no,
Ma'Dere's not going for it.
The guy doesn't even live here.
Ever since Senior left,
he's got this weird hold on Ma'Dere.
Okay, well, Lisa,
you're his sister, right?
Talk some sense into the man.
I'm telling you, Malcolm. We've been
through this over and over again. I...
I don't know what it is, but it's like...
I don't know.
Same damn reason Joe and Ma'Dere
put on these charades...
...like Joe doesn't live here.
Oh, come on. You telling me
that Quentin doesn't know?
No. Quentin doesn't know.
Trust me. He can't stand Joe.
He's been that way
ever since he was a kid.
Like he thinks one day
Senior's gonna come back.
Hey. Hey, Lisa.
Lisa?
What?
Never mind.
You said your dad moved on.
What does that mean?
A little after Baby was born...
...Senior decided to go off and,
as Ma'Dere puts it...
...chase his dream of playing jazz.
He upped and left
and moved to Europe.
She wouldn't let Quentin Jr.
take up the saxophone.
She was afraid he'd leave too,
but she couldn't stop him.
- And did he?
- What?
Up and leave her?
First time he's been home
in four years.
A lot of phone calls and postcards,
but he's a wanderer too.
Senior's piano is in the garage.
She thinks that music is the root
of the evil that's taken her men away.
Hell, the rest of us are afraid
to even hum.
Look at that smile, girl.
I love to see you happy.
Well, it's because you are such
a good man, Joe Black.
You're a real good woman,
Shirley Ann Whitfield.
And beautiful too.
Okay.
- Tomorrow morning?
- First thing.
I'm gonna pick up a few things.
I'm gonna take off, but I'll be back.
Okay.
Merry Christmas, baby.
Malcolm.
Hey, baby.
I thought you had gone.
I was checking something
for your mother.
Oh, yeah? What's that, Joe?
Christmas lights, brother.
We might pick some up
when we're out tomorrow.
Okay.
- You know what?
- What?
I'm gonna tell you something
as a courtesy to Ma'Dere.
Now, I'm only here a few days. You
might wanna steer clear until I'm gone.
And I'm gonna say this
as a courtesy to you.
I'm here because your mother
wants me here.
If you got a problem with that,
you take it up with her.
I'll do that.
If I was here, Senior...
...I'd look after your old piano, man.
Yes, I would.
Hey, Kelli, girl. What you doing?
Just unpacking, Mama.
When you gonna settle down, child,
like your sister?
Where is this coming from?
I just love you.
I want you to be happy.
Well, I don't have a problem
settling down, Mama.
I have a problem settling for...
...less.
I'm just focused on my career
right now.
Long as you remember your career
is not gonna keep you warm at night.
All right. Night-night.
Night.
Need some batteries?
No, no. I'm not whispering.
No. No, everybody's cool.
Did you eat?
Okay, yeah, just meet me at the...
There's a club called the El Rey.
It's off Wilshire.
Yeah. Just take a cab there.
I'll meet you there in a little bit.
Yeah. Okay.
- Bad girl?
- Come here.
What are you doing?
In your mother's house?
Yeah. You're gonna get tore down.
- Hey. I thought you were asleep.
- No, I was in the garage.
I don't have my sax,
so I thought I'd play Senior's piano.
- That thing's still out there?
- Yeah.
It needs to get tuned,
but it still works.
- What you doing up?
- I can never sleep in a strange place.
This ain't a strange place.
It's your home. Pass a napkin.
You hear that?
Hey, you know,
Lisa wants to sell the dry cleaners.
- Yeah.
- Really?
- You agree with her?
- Oh, I'm only hearing it now.
I don't have an opinion on it.
Well, that's just like you.
Nothing matters. Whatever.
Right. Nothing matters
because this is the first time...
...anybody asking me
my opinion about it.
Well, you're never around
long enough...
...for anybody to ask you anything.
- Do you hear that?
- What?
I don't hear anything.
What are you talking about?
Don't nobody sleep around here?
- Where you going?
- Out.
Oh, no. Don't get stealthy on us.
Out where?
I just thought I'd, you know,
go check up on the old traps.
Oh, cool. I'm coming with.
- I'm good by myself, thanks.
- Hold up. I wanna go too.
- Oh, we should ask everybody.
- Yeah, it's not a group thing.
Well, you know, Quentin,
if Lisa's going, I'm out.
- I've had enough of her.
- No discussion.
- There's no reason to talk.
- No Lisa, no Malcolm.
We gotta ask Mel
and what's-his-name.
- How about no Q, no Kelli.
- It's like Donny or Darryl.
- Something with a D.
- It's like Darryl or Donny.
Devean.
We wanna go.
- Babe, go get that table right there.
- Okay, okay.
I'll quarterback this thing.
What y'all wanna drink?
- A beer.
- Two.
- I'm good.
- See if they got any hot wings.
Okay.
Am I tripping or is brother man
checking me out?
- Where?
- Over there.
- He is peeping you out.
- Yo, I know that cat, man.
We used to go
to high school together.
Gerald. That's who he is.
That might be true,
but he's not checking for you.
- You're from Oceanside?
- Excuse me.
- Oh, we're talking here, cousin.
- But I'm with him.
- Oh, it's like that.
- No pressure. No pressure, man.
- You do your thing.
- Yeah. Stay black.
- Who are they?
- They were just keeping me company...
...while I was waiting for you.
- Oh, okay. Okay.
Can I get four beers
and some hot wings?
We're out of hot wings.
You're jealous.
Of them? Please. Why?
Something's wrong.
You ordered four beers.
That's what took me so long.
My sisters and brother
decided to come, so I didn't...
- Where are they?
- Hang on.
You didn't tell them.
See, there's these things
with my sisters.
And then my brother Quentin
just shows up.
That's a no, right, Claude?
I'm gonna tell them.
I can't do it right now.
- You're ashamed of me.
- That isn't true.
I have to tell Ma'Dere first.
In the morning. All right?
- In the morning?
- In the morning.
I'm gonna hang out with the family.
I'll meet you at the hotel.
- You promise?
- You have my word.
- Love you.
- I love you too.
Now, get out of here.
Y'all ready to get this show started?
Make some noise.
This is open-mike night.
We do this every Sunday.
- Every Sunday we got live...
- Oh, thank you.
- and do they thing.
- Gerald, this is my family. My sister Mel.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Kelli right there.
- Nice to meet you.
- Pleasure's all mine.
- This first singer confessed...
...that this is his first time
singing publicly.
- This is my sister's boyfriend, De Von?
- Give it up for Michael Whitfield.
- Make some noise for Michael Whitfield.
- Whatever.
- It's okay, baby.
- Did he just say Michael Whitfield?
Oh, my God, it's Baby.
- This one of your peoples?
- My little brother. What's he doing?
Thanks, everybody.
I'm real nervous, but, I mean, I...
I appreciate the opportunity
for y'all let...
Letting me be out here.
Just letting me
be able to do my thing.
Okay, we need to help him.
Quentin, get him down.
- He's struggling.
- Man. Yo.
Well, I'll be damned.
Damn, Mel.
- Your brother got pipes.
- Can you believe this shit?
Where in the hell did he learn
to sing like that?
He's singing.
Yo.
Sweet.
- Come on, baby, let's go dance.
- All right, let's do this.
- I love this song. Yeah.
- Yeah? You feeling it?
It's sexy.
- Wanna dance?
- No, I'm chilling.
Not you, fool.
Yeah, come on. I'd love to.
You didn't tell me Baby could sing.
- Like we knew.
- Go ahead!
- Where'd everybody go?
- Dance floor.
Come on. Let's go get
some of these honeys.
- I'm good. I'm just chilling.
- You sure?
All right.
Yes! Love you!
Y'all make some noise
for Michael Whitfield.
- Michael Whitfield!
- What's up?
We just wanted to apologise, cousin.
We ain't know that off-brand chick...
- Off what?
- The white girl.
We didn't know she was with you.
- Oh, it's cool.
- I ain't mad at you, though.
- Like I said, it's cool.
- White girls ain't got junk in the trunk.
But I hear they got
some strong knees.
Got a lot to say, huh?
- Come on.
- Who's on their knees now?
- Say it again. Say it again.
- I'm sorry...
- What are you doing?
- I'm sorry, man.
Get out of here. Come on.
We gotta go, let's go, let's go.
- Hey. Watch out. Watch out.
- What's wrong with you? You crazy?
Wait, where's Kelli?
- With Gerald.
- Oh, she's good.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Come on.
So you pull out a gun on him
because he pissed you off.
You lost your mind? We are Whitfields.
We don't behave that way.
- Listen.
- You listen. What are you thinking?
I think you made your point.
- I don't think I have.
- He pissed me off.
Like you are now. Now, drop it.
All right. All right.
I'll drop it.
You always had
that crazy temper, man.
You'd always just flip out. For what?
I mean, we're in a club.
We got our sisters with us.
What happened in there tonight?
Baby, please leave it alone.
We have moved on from there.
- You don't want Claude to shoot you.
- We moved on, Q.
Yeah, all right. All right.
You got some explaining to do.
- About what?
- "About what?"
How come none of us knew
you can sing?
- Because of him.
- Because of me?
Before she hear you.
Who?
What you think Ma'Dere'd say
if she found out I wanna sing?
Baby, come on. That doesn't mean...
Baby, nothing.
Y'all ain't have to hear it, live with it.
She's telling me how I'm the last
Whitfield man who hasn't left her yet.
She's gonna find out.
But not until I'm ready to tell her,
and certainly not now.
Mama's real happy for this Christmas,
with everyone home.
And I don't wanna ruin it.
You have to promise
that you're not gonna say nothing...
...until I figure a way to say it myself.
- Got you.
And, Mel, tell Kelli not to say
anything in front of Ma'Dere.
- I got you.
- Man, this is too much drama for me.
I say we all get some sleep,
pick this up in the morning.
All right?
You know, Baby...
...you can sing, man.
Good night.
Come on, D. Let's go.
I was proud of you, man.
I'm going to bed.
I've never been
more surprised in my life.
Four years of "maybe this year,"
so this time I didn't even ask him.
Oh, he just walked through that door,
and my heart almost stopped.
I swear, Rosie, sometimes
I thought I'd never see him again.
He's so much like Senior.
Good morning, Kelli, girl.
"Good morning, Mama,"
would be nice.
Yeah. Good morning, Mama.
Let everybody know
breakfast is ready.
He knows it's fine.
No.
No, I... We're not gonna bend
on that, all right?
Please. Give me a break.
Listen. It's a non-issue, all right?
I'll just fly out this afternoon...
...take care of the paperwork,
and then I'll fly back.
Of course the money's there. Money's
been there the whole time. In escrow.
Look, I'll talk to you about it
this afternoon, all right?
Yeah. Sure. All right.
Oh, f...
Can I help you?
Yeah, I just came to tell you
breakfast was ready.
Well, as soon as Lisa
gets out the shower...
...we'll be right down.
Going somewhere?
As a matter of fact, I am.
Gotta fly back to San Francisco,
sign some papers.
You know, business.
Good for you.
One, two, three.
So you really pulled a gun on him?
Yo. Don't tell Ma'Dere. You hear me?
Man, I know.
Where'd you get the gun?
It's my service pistol.
You really was gonna shoot him?
Hell, no. I was just trying
to make a point.
You may think you're grown now...
...but Ma'Dere find out,
she gonna bitch-slap you...
...into the middle of next week.
And you don't wanna
miss Christmas, do you?
Man, go and pick a tree.
You guys decided yet?
- Let's take this one.
- That's a good one.
That there's an ugly-ass tree,
Mr. Black.
- I'm cool with it if Joe cool with it.
- Yeah, I'm with it.
- Yeah, we'll get this one.
- Right.
- Go on, take the photo.
- All right, let's take this picture.
Come on. Come on.
Say "trees."
- Ready?
- Ready.
I don't know what Baby is doing,
but he's killing the game.
Isn't that, like, the third gift
for him today?
The fifth. Put it over there
with the rest of them.
Oh, that's me.
- Oh, my God, it's him.
- Who?
- Gerald, from last night.
- You spent the night with him...
...and you're not gonna answer?
- No.
No, you didn't spend the night,
or no, you're not gonna answer?
Don't get your bra all in a knot.
We didn't sleep together.
You don't wanna waste a night
of sleep with a man like that.
- Was he good?
- You gave him some?
It was a shared experience,
but if you wanna get technical...
...he was the one
doing most of the giving.
- It is the season to give.
- I hope you used protection.
- I'm not stupid.
- Come on, where is it written...
...that a woman can't meet a guy,
get some and then be done with him?
- They have a word for women like that.
- Smart.
- Ho.
- What?
I'm just trying to school you.
You don't wanna end up pregnant...
...and then next thing you know
you got two kids.
Did that just come out of my mouth?
Lisa, I'm ready.
What?
Okay. Lisa, can we go?
I'll see you guys at dinner.
- What's wrong with these two?
- Nothing.
- It's fine. You got everything?
- Yeah. I'm all set.
- Hi. Excuse me.
- Hi. Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas. Do you have
any messages for room 302?
- No, ma'am. No messages.
- Okay. Thanks.
I can't believe Malcolm wants
to sell the cleaners.
I know. You gonna talk
to Ma'Dere about it?
No. We're gonna handle this
amongst ourselves.
And I'm counting on you
for your support.
- I got you.
- Kelli?
- Yeah?
- Santa's here.
- Santa?
And he asked for you.
Merry Christmas.
- And what is your name, little girl?
- Tori.
Tori. Really?
And what is your name, young man?
- Keshon.
- Did you write Santa a letter?
- Even Santa calls you that...
...when you sleep with him
on the first night.
Have you been eating some
Christmas cake or anything like that?
Don't worry, I got something really
good. Been good this year?
Because I'm making
a list and I'm checking it twice.
- So he's a friend of yours?
- He went to school with Quentin.
Well, you keep your eyes
on those kids.
You have to be careful nowadays.
You never know.
You be careful, okay? I mean,
it's nice and all, what he doing, but...
- Yeah.
- A Santa suit. Lord.
Merry Christmas.
See you, young man.
Come on over here and talk
to Santa, little girl.
Okay.
So, pretty lady...
...what can Santa bring you
for Christmas?
- Well...
- How about peace on earth?
Hell, peace in my family
would do the trick.
Let me see what I can do.
Come on and sit on Santa's lap.
- And then what?
- Depends...
...whether you've
been naughty or nice.
Well, you're Santa.
Aren't you supposed to know?
I know you were pretty naughty
last night.
But Santa can't say it wasn't nice.
- What are you doing here?
- All right, all right.
Well, as you know, I'm a fireman.
We do this every year
for the kids down at the mall.
Since your mama's house
was on the way...
...I figured I'd just come on by
and spread some holiday cheer.
And being that it's Christmas...
...I thought that Santa
would bring you this.
Oh, I forgot that I left that there.
Thank you, Santa.
- Now give Santa some sugar.
- My mother is in the next room.
She can give Santa some sugar too.
Where's she at?
- Okay, that's it. You gotta go.
- All right. Well, listen.
You gotta agree to have drinks
with me tonight.
- Okay. I will.
- All right? Nine o'clock.
- I promise. Sounds good.
- I'm gonna hold you to that.
- All right?
- Out you go.
All right.
Now, you be good,
for goodness' sake.
- Oh, my God.
- You slept with Santa.
I did not know
he was Santa at the time...
...but technically, I guess I did.
I don't see why this couldn't wait
until we got back.
Baby, for the hundredth time...
...I'll be back in the morning.
But, Malcolm, it's Christmas Eve.
Bill collectors don't care.
The car we drive,
the house we live in?
They don't pay for themselves.
You wouldn't understand that, being
I'm the one that's doing all the work.
Oh, and I don't work?
I guess I just stay at home
and sit on my behind...
...and raise your kids.
- I'm sorry.
But I'm just under so much pressure
these days, Lisa.
I realise I'm not as sensitive as
you need me to be, but we're partners.
Okay? Now, I need you
to get your family...
...to sell the dry-cleaning business...
...and then we'll have the capital
to get our life to the next level.
Do you really mean that?
We're partners?
Baby. Baby, come here.
Now, you know we're soul mates.
All right?
Everything I do,
I do for you and the kids.
All right?
Drive carefully. Here are the keys.
Oh, and make sure you put it
in the carport, all right?
Just in case it rains.
I'll call you!
Yeah?
"I love you"?
Back up, back up, back up.
Okay.
Claude!
Come help us.
Let a Marine get in here,
show you how it's done.
- Turn it.
- We're going the wrong way.
Yeah, frontways is the best.
There you go, in the back.
Ma'Dere, we have the tree!
Cocktail, anyone?
This one's from Bernice. Remember?
I thought Bernice was dead.
Oh, I'm telling her
next time I see her.
Oh, my God, Sam done put
all 15 of his kids on the card.
- Yes.
- His little boy grew up.
- Look, look, look.
- Nice.
Yeah, hey. Oh, no.
We had the family photo...
... and pick ed up a Christmas tree
and decorated that.
And my cousin Fred came by.
Oh, okay.
Oh, honey, take these.
Wait a minute, I'll be right back.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Check that out.
That's you?
There's a lot going on. Yeah, and...
Claude.
- Claude, you there?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm here.
- What's wrong?
- Oh, nothing.
That's not a nothing look.
Christmas card from Senior.
Oh, where is he now?
- London.
- That's a good place for him.
Rosie.
You need to be honest with the kids.
Tell them about the divorce
and move on.
Now is not the time, Rosie.
I haven't seen Quentin in four years.
I am not doing anything
to upset him.
It's never a good time for you.
Rosie, where are the grapes?
In the freezer.
Good, the kids love
those frozen grapes.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org