Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shit. Hey, Sully.
Baby, I just needed to rest
my feet for, like, one second.
So that's why you
can't work right now?
You get paid to dance, not
to sit on your ass drinking.
Now get to work!
You can be a real asshole
when you want to be.
Stupid bitch.
Lock up the joint
when you're done here.
I'm going out.
Hey, dude!
Get the fuck off of
me! Get your hands off!
And then they beat them by,
like, 65 points last year.
That wasn't even football game.
That was a basketball score.
You know, he could have said USC. He
could have said a lot of other things.
Now he's going to the Aztecs.
My friend.
If I'd only gotten
sober 10 years ago.
Our attention turns
back to a story
that we have been following
for the past several days.
The greater Los Angeles area
has been plagued with
a rash of kidnappings
with as many as 4 victims
disappearing in separate attacks
and all possibly by the
same masked individual.
Now, a source inside
the LAPD refuses to say
whether or not there is a connection
between the kidnapped victims.
I'll take the check.
A detective with the
West Los Angeles division
has also fallen prey
to this masked criminal.
You want to get
out of the car?
Well, isn't that cute?
Sorry, guys. Gotta go. Got
an audition in the morning.
Hey, I saw your
commercial the other day,
and you sucked, asshole.
Hey, it's Kelley.
No, I don't know any
more than the cops do.
Jackson got nabbed,
and they think it might
be linked to a priest
who got nabbed in the
valley on Thursday.
And then I got a report
across my desk this morning
about a kidnapping in Barstow,
and they like Jackson's
guy for that too.
I don't know. I guess we
got to pull over every green
Chevy Malibu in the state
and see if Jackson's
locked in the trunk.
Yeah, I know that's not practical,
but we got to do something. I mean,
who knows who's next
on this guy's shit list?
No.
No, no.
You're dead.
Do you have any idea who
I am, you son of a bitch?
You're messing with the
wrong woman. Do you hear me?
Much thanks.
Dear Lord.
What you gonna do? Why took
me here? I wanna go home!
What the hell is this place?
You're never gonna
get away with this.
I wanna go home.
I wanna go home!
Let me out of here,
or you're dead.
I'm gonna bust out of here.
I'm gonna bust your head.
And I'll take that gun
and stick it up your ass.
I brought the 9 of you
here today for a reason.
And your survival
depends on you discovering
what that reason is.
I'm gonna leave you alone
for your discussions,
but I'll return every 10
minutes and kill one of you
until you either figure it out
or until you're all dead.
If you do manage
to figure it out,
I'll free the survivors,
notify the police
of our location,
and make a full confession
to all the crimes
I will commit here today.
Wait; I don't get it. I
mean, I didn't do anything.
You have 10 minutes.
Did he mention about
us getting home?
I don't know who all of you are,
but somebody better start talking,
'cause I am not
dying here today.
Dude out there's full of shit.
What makes you say that?
I just know. No one
does this deal for real.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The
Lord is--
the
shit!
Dude, how does
the rest of it go?
One of you has
to know something.
What did you do?
Don't look at me, bitch.
There's 8 other
guys in this room.
Can anyone think of a
reason why they're here?
He's gonna kill us,
so there has to be something.
Well, I'll be
the first to admit
that I have a pretty
messed-up history,
but I don't know
who that guy is
or why I'm here.
And I'll be the last to admit
shit. To hell with that guy.
He's a punk,
and my money says
that he's a cop.
What? You're insane.
The punk-ass pig
puts a bunch of
criminals in one room.
All right?
Gets them all scared and crowing
about the shit that they did.
The cops write up a
list and bust us all.
I'm not saying shit.
This is not a
setup by the cops.
I had a friend a
couple years ago,
got in a barroom
fight with a guy.
Guy turns out to be a cop.
A couple hours later,
he's in room like this.
They threw him a hell
of a blanket party.
The guy never did
walk the same since.
It's not the cops.
How can you be so sure?
Because I'm a
fucking genius, okay?
Yeah, well,
anything is possible.
I had a customer a
couple of weeks ago
threaten to kill me
when I cut him off at the bar.
But then he drove his
car into a building.
Maybe this is all
just a mistake.
What, do you think he
kidnapped all of us by mistake?
Look, he's obviously crazy,
so that's something we
can use to our advantage.
Are we supposed to think of
a crime that's so horrible
that he would kill
9 people as a result,
some horrible
crime that we did?
I'm sorry, Father,
but the worst thing one person
can do to another
is child molestation.
Never.
I never would do such a thing.
I have.
Was it, like, boys or girls?
Does it matter to you?
No, no.
Me neither. You
sick son of a bitch.
You put me in a room with you
and no windows and no doors,
and you're gonna wish
that you were never born.
Sweetie, we are in a room
with no windows or doors,
and the only thing you're
gonna do is try to survive,
just like me. Maybe
you deserve to die.
What I've done might
have gotten me here,
but you two
and all of you...
What have all of you done
to deserve the death penalty?
My name is Eddie Vigoda.
Hi, Eddie.
Maybe that helps somebody.
No, Eddie.
No, it doesn't.
I'm Dean Jackson.
I'm Kelley Murphy.
I'm an assistant
district attorney
for Los Angeles County.
Can you think of
anyone you've put away
that would want revenge,
like a crazed killer,
you know, some escaped psycho?
Take your pick.
I mean, I've made more
than a few enemies,
but there are people
that keep tabs on parolees
that might come after me.
And no one saw
this guy coming.
Jackson, anything
you'd like to add?
I know you.
Says you.
We did some business
together years ago.
I'm sure it was
small-time stuff for you,
but it was pretty big for me.
My name is Christian
Collins worth.
What kind of
business are you in?
Sully's with the mob.
You know, it doesn't surprise
me that you don't remember me.
It's been a long time.
What's your name, anyway, man?
Sully Fenton from Vegas.
What kind of business
did you two do together?
Ask the kid. Hell if I know.
A deal came my way, some
pharmaceutical-grade speed.
I was about 5 grand
short, so I went to Sully.
I heard he was in the business
of loaning money for drugs
for part of the
product and profits.
I'm sure 5 grand sounded
pretty sweet to me at the time,
especially selling meth.
So what happened?
I sold the stuff
to these 2 cool guys
who turned out to
be undercover cops.
And I went in for 3 years.
But you still paid me, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Everybody knows what happens
when you don't pay Sully Fenton.
I'm not stupid. Are
you sure about that?
I had nothing
going into prison.
I had even less getting out.
But I got what I needed
as soon as I hit
the streets in May.
You were paid by
the end of the month.
Now I'm an actor and
bartender in Hollywood though.
Good for you.
I'm gonna miss my
sitcom audition.
Your audition?
Where the hell do
you think you are?
Jesus, will you cut the
kid some slack already?
We're all scared here.
He's doing his best.
Hey, is Sully the only one
who's not from Los Angeles?
My travels have
taken me all over,
including Los Angeles.
More than a few prisons.
I'm Father Michael Francis.
I have Catholic parish in
the San Fernando Valley.
Eddie, where are you from?
Barstow.
You guys forgot about me.
You said you ain't talking.
I just figured you're
from Los Angeles,
since, you know,
the city's chock-full
of you pussies.
I got your...
pussy.
Excuse me.
No one appreciates your
pissing match more than I.
But I think we're
forgetting about someone.
Do you speak English?
English?
Say something. I know
you understand us.
I know you guys were trying to talk
to me, but I just don't understand.
I'm gonna need helps from you guys.
Just tell me what I have to do.
Does anybody know
what this language is?
Anyone know what it
is? Chinese, I think.
How the hell do you know?
Old-school kung fu flicks.
It's annoying, whatever it is.
I hope he cap her ass first.
You're a "black
ghost". Nigger!
The chick does speak English.
Yeah, she's funny.
Let's see who lives
and dies first.
This situation
stinks of a pig setup.
Jesus. Told you.
God, for the last time.
This has absolutely
nothing to do with the cops.
How can you be so sure?
Because I am a cop!
I knew it.
I thought if I told you
scumbags I was L.A. County,
you wouldn't say anything,
knowing I was one of the good guys.
Good guys? Yeah.
You're one of the
good guys? Yeah.
In my old neighborhood, the
cops weren't the good guys.
I'm not a scumbag.
I'll make you a bet
that our masked host
comes back in here,
grabs one of us,
brings him outside,
shoots the gun up into the
air, and we all think he's dead.
Yeah, that's what
he's gonna do.
He's gonna sweat us.
That's what he's gonna do.
You think? Yeah,
he's gonna do that.
Really? Come on,
guys, come on.
We can do this.
Yeah. If he figured out
why we're all here,
we can figure it out.
You know what?
I really appreciate
your can-do spirit,
but if this pig is wrong,
my name's Coogan.
And I got to say,
what a pleasure it was
to spend the last 10 minutes
of my life with you all.
Well, we still haven't
gotten your name.
You didn't?
Miss chink over there
said it plain as day.
It's what you and everyone
else think: nigger.
All right?
Yeah, is that with 1 G or 2?
That--that--
With 2.
You think this is funny?
This isn't funny.
Hey, what else am I gonna do?
In about 3 seconds
we're gonna find out
if Coogan's right
about this being a bust,
or we're gonna
find one of us dead.
Why are you here?
You got to give us more time.
You're asking the impossible.
We're all willing to
do whatever you want.
But you have to give
us something in return.
Okay, okay.
How could I have known that?
Please just wait a
second. Please don't!
What are you doing, man?
God!
Fuck.
Sorry to see him go,
but that's one less
to worry about, right?
As I said,
you have to know why I brought
each and every one of you here
in order to survive.
If you want to walk
out of here alive,
you'd better figure out
why he was here as well.
I can't die like this.
Please, God. We
ask that you--
Hey, Father.
You think we can toss the idea
of him faking the
killing outside the door?
Who are you praying to?
God's not here.
You still think
this is the cops?
If we don't figure out
what's going on before
somebody else dies,
we're not gonna get
out of here alive.
Well, does anybody
here speak Chinese?
I speak a little Spanish.
Habla español?
I don't understand what you're
saying. Don't speak to me.
I'm getting mad
at you. Really?
No dice.
Padre, you sure you
didn't touch no kids?
I have never harmed
a child in my life.
Anyway, that thing over there,
he's already admitted to the
crime, so stop looking at me.
Hey.
Guys, I might be a
little screwed up,
but I just spent
5 years in jail.
I'm trying to be
a reformed man.
What did you serve time
for? Grand theft auto.
Not child molestation?
No, that's all they
could hit me with.
You see, they
couldn't find a body.
You're a winner, ain't you?
Thank you.
Piece of shit.
I think it's about
time we heard from you.
All right.
I'm Leon, from L.A.
My brother and I used to do
work up and down the West Coast.
What kind of work did you do?
Looking for this?
Don't give me those
fucked-up looks.
At least I never sexed
and killed no kids.
I never killed anybody.
But I'd rob your ass
if the price was right.
Cash is king, and I
stick to what works.
But guns?
Guns can be better than cash.
Kelley, did you
ever prosecute Leon?
No, he doesn't look familiar.
That's because I
never got caught.
Yeah, well, our friend
out there caught you.
Yeah, coming out the
USC library no less.
The library?
Yeah, it pays to do
research in my business.
If the cop and
Kelley know each other
and Christian and Vegas
Sully know each other, then
it would make sense that
we're all connected here,
whether we know it or not.
Well, if I busted you, you
guys would know better than me.
I mean, that list is long.
Yeah, I'm in the same boat.
I wouldn't even
know where to begin.
But in my business,
we don't do this shit.
I forget how you people can
be so thoughtless and careless
when it comes to human life.
I spend every waking
moment serving God
by trying to help
people in my community,
and all you seem to do
is try to destroy life.
You put yourself
up on a pedestal,
but you're here just
like the rest of us.
So why don't you stop talking
about why you shouldn't be here,
and let's figure
out why you are.
Hey, Eddie.
Eddie. What?
Nobody's stopping you
from talking, Eddie.
I work for a health
insurance carrier.
I'm from Barstow.
That's fascinating.
Any other useless facts
you'd like to pass around?
I'm doing my best.
Tell us about your work.
What do you do?
Come on, what
do you do, Eddie?
Okay.
A couple of years ago, I
helped out my brother-in-law.
He has colon cancer.
My company does a lot of
experimental medical work,
and I falsified his forms
so that he can
get the treatment.
But I did it to help
my brother-in-law.
I mean, this
doesn't make sense.
I'm a good person.
I don't deserve to be here.
I shouldn't be here.
Hey!
Relax there, leaky faucet.
Okay.
I'm human. Jesus
Christ, Eddie.
So you know, I
mean, all right.
Everybody have a look.
You know, laugh.
But you know what?
If we don't start confessing,
I mean,
we're never gonna make
it out of here alive.
Everybody--
everybody's got to help.
Jackson and I used
to sleep together.
Yeah, until my wife found out.
Would your wife go this far
to get back at you
for cheating on her?
No, she divorced me
and moved to Arizona.
I think that's far enough.
Plus, she has no way of
getting us all here together.
And she has no reason
to. I pay my alimony.
I don't think she hates me that much.
No ex-wife would want her man dead.
That's her money train.
Look, no one knows you two,
so I doubt it's the ex-wife.
And nobody really wants to
hear about your sex life.
Yeah, well, she's
just pissed off,
'cause we got caught.
Yeah, it was your big
mouth that got us caught.
You know what, Kelley? You're
not the only one who got hurt.
I lost my wife.
Yeah, and I was labeled
the home-wrecking slut.
That did wonders
for my career.
And I wasn't the only person
you were screwing around with.
What was it, a month before
some judge knocked you up?
Hey, kitty cats.
Why so hostile?
An affair is an affair.
Now we're getting relationship
advice from a pedophile.
What the fuck you looking at?
You one tall drink of water.
You're turning faggot now?
No, I just realized how
I'm getting out of here.
None of you guys are
gonna come up with shit.
Closest one to me.
What are you doing?
So start kicking.
You are crazy, man.
You got a better idea?
Break my hand so I can
get out these cuffs.
You're crazy.
I'm not kidding.
Start kicking, man. All right.
My pleasure.
Come on, game it
up. I'll get it.
Wait! Come on!
Stop.
Wait, I almost got it.
Come on.
One more, one
more. Just do it.
Okay, okay, okay.
All right, all right.
Leon, Leon, get up.
Hey, get behind the door.
And when he comes in, you push
him in, and we'll attack him.
Yeah, bring him my way.
Leon, get behind the door.
Come on. That's a good idea.
But I got a better one.
Later. You can't leave us.
Bitch, you think I
give a damn about you?
To hell with you.
Leon, you can't leave
us in here like this.
He's gonna get us killed...
You stupid piece of shit!
Don't do it. You know you
can't leave us in here.
Don't leave us here.
Damn it!
Fuck!
Punk-ass bitch.
You stupid fucking bitch.
The thoughts that's been
going through my mind
while I was in
that fucked-up room.
And that's a fucked-up room!
Now that I got this gun,
the shit that I got
in store for you.
I have been planning
this for 2 years.
Nothing is gonna take away
what I have in store for you
and the others.
And I mean nothing.
Before I enter,
I place one bullet
into that gun you hold.
But this gun?
This gun holds 6.
Fuck.
He didn't make it.
Why are you here?
Maybe you should move them
out of the way of the splatter.
I'd hate to see somebody die
before you get a chance
to kill 'em yourself.
Yeah.
That's a good reason.
God, please.
You don't have to do this.
Up until now, the
order has been random.
I just want you to
know that you're next.
Fuck you.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
Blessed
art thou--
Blessed art thou
amongst women.
I can't remember
the prayer either.
I used to know it.
I've said it like
a million times.
Can you help me, Father?
What?
What's wrong?
I don't know. I...
I can't remember,
but it's so familiar.
Look.
We got another 10 minutes.
It can take me that long to
find my keys in the morning.
You finding something
funny there, bleeding boy?
I'm gonna die
like the man said,
and you guys are
gonna die with me.
I got 8 minutes to live.
And I've been thinking
about you bitches.
I got to make peace.
Look, if you're
gonna die a happy man,
then I'm gonna die a happy
man laughing at your misery.
Look, we know
Leon's next to go.
That means we have 8 minutes
to figure out why he was here
and another 10 minutes
before somebody else dies.
Come on, we can
figure this out.
Let's put our heads
together, guys.
Come on, we can do this.
You look familiar. Know you somewhere.
But I've never caught your name.
Do I look familiar to you?
Ah! I remember now!
You're the lawyer!
Uh, I got robbed, and
then you helped me out...
Something turned the slant on.
It's you! It must be you! It's
almost comical if you watch it right.
Wearing glasses.
Pictionary? Wearing glasses.
Glasses?
Wearing glasses. Glasses.
I haven't worn
glasses in years.
I remember when
you wore glasses.
This lady knows you,
or she did know you.
Bang, bang!
A shooting?
Some kind of
shooting, a shooting?
Robbery? Bang!
Robbery!
Mrs. Chan?
Yes, yes! Chan, Chan!
Her name is Nhung Chan.
Right, right... I'm Chan.
But we haven't contacted
each other since then.
Did you get the
guy who robbed her?
Yeah, Chan picked him out of a lineup.
I prosecuted. He went to San Quentin.
What was this guy's name?
Greeley, Wade Greeley.
He was a total punk
kid, 20 years old...
A total loser.
So that's it? That's
why we're here?
Because this kid Wade Greeley
is pissed off that
you sent him to prison?
All we have here is
a robbery and a name
and a whole hell of a lot
of unanswered questions.
Okay, I don't even
remember busting this guy,
Wade Greeley.
What about you, Father?
Does any of this
mean anything to you?
I'm sorry. I can't help you.
Okay, if Wade Greeley
going to jail is
the end-all-be-all,
then we must fit in to
this before that happened.
I think I've got
us a time line.
You know, listening to
you guys, I've got a...
a glimmer of hope.
I thought for a sec you
had the son of a bitch beat.
Well, well, well.
Look who's back from the dead.
Ease up, man. Ease up.
I'm having a change of
heart or something like that.
I'm thinking letting
you people die,
it's not right.
I haven't done nothing
good in a long time.
I said I never killed nobody.
That's a lie.
I want my cut of cash you
gave that bitch of yours.
What cash?
Man, you fucking tripping.
I know about the money belt
and those Brentwood
bitches last month.
You accusing me
of holding out?
Nah, I'm straight saying it.
Don't turn your
back to me, man.
click!
Pull guns on people?
For sure, motherfucker.
I got a gun too.
I dumped his body in a
dumpster in downtown L.A.
at the Cinco de Mayo festival.
He said he never liked the
Mexicans and their parades.
One last childish
act on my part.
A couple of days later I went
to the morgue with our mother.
I stood over the body.
I didn't say anything.
I went to the street and
sold the rest of our stuff.
I never told nobody that.
I didn't speak or see too much
of my mother after the funeral.
I'll never see
either of them again.
I'll never have a
chance to say I'm sorry.
I want my mother...
to forgive me. I
deserve to die. But
I want to be
forgiven. Somebody
just forgive me.
He who seeks forgiveness
shall find it.
We're no better off
than we were before.
We have nothing new, and
there's like a minute left.
Here's something new.
That guy said he's been
planning this for 2 years.
Okay, what were we
all doing 2 years ago?
2 years ago I did 30 days
for busting some joker in the head
for hassling one of my dancers.
But no one is going to
give 2 shits about that one.
No.
2 years ago
I was just--
I had the same job
selling insurance,
approvals, dismissals.
I don't know.
It's nothing unusual.
Kelley?
2 years ago?
Why are you here?
We know part of the answer.
We've got some of it.
All or nothing.
Son of a bitch.
I'll see you in hell.
I know.
What are you doing?
Stop this!
Father, you still with us?
You're not going to
like what I have to say.
Anything is better than
nothing at this point.
Either say it or don't.
I figured out why I am here.
Well, holy shit!
I know why someone else
was in this room as well.
I know what we have done to
the man that holds us captive.
So what is it?
Yeah, spill it.
I can't.
What do you mean, you can't?
Come on, Father.
What was said to me
was said in confidence.
I can't repeat it.
You want to play Pictionary
or something? Fine.
Me and you, Father, against
her and Mandarin Duck.
I can't reveal
what was said to me.
There's nothing I can do.
My relationship with God
goes beyond my life and yours.
This is bullshit, Father.
You better start talking
right now, or so help me,
I will goddamn crack
that head of yours.
You'll do what?
I'm facing death already.
I have no fear of death
when it comes to
upholding the Lord's law.
My loyalty will
not be questioned.
My devotion does not exist
only when the situation
deems convenient.
People are dead
because of you.
You don't know
that to be true.
The hell I don't, cocksucker!
Leon laid there dying,
but at least he had the
balls to speak his mind,
even though it went against
his own fucked-up judgment.
And now you're going
to have all of us die
because you're
gonna keep quiet
behind some collar
and dusty oath?
Sully, would you
turn in your brother
for a lighter sentence?
My brother's dead.
So then your father.
Would you give up your
father to save your own skin?
I would never cross my father.
So then you can
understand my situation.
No, I can't!
It's like waking up from
one nightmare into another.
Shut the hell up, Eddie.
If Father Francis
has made up his mind,
we're just gonna have to
get out of here without him.
What? You're defending
the cocksucker?
No.
But I got a wife to get home to,
and we're wasting time arguing.
To hell with Francis, okay?
If he's not gonna talk,
we're never gonna
figure out why he's here.
So if we want to live,
we're gonna have to escape.
Okay, we're gonna
have to take him down.
And we have to face the fact
that we may have to kill him.
On, I ain't got no
problem with that.
Okay, hold on.
What do we know?
We know Greeley robbed
Chan's liquor store.
And we know Kelley
prosecuted him.
Okay, well, that's
2 out of 9, Eddie.
Maybe there's more to it.
Maybe it goes
beyond those people
who are directly responsible
for him going to jail.
Maybe he's thinking
in bigger terms.
Yeah, maybe we're not
all connected in this.
Maybe he's going after
everybody that's ever done
anything wrong to this guy.
We need to come clean.
Completely clean about
everything, right now,
all of us.
All right.
You want a story?
8 years ago
this old man came in
and slapped me around
in front of my crew.
Some crazy bastard
who owed me money
came in and tried to punk
me in front of my people.
I went back to his
pawn shop that night.
Yeah, I went back,
and I firebombed it.
The problem...
the problem...
I didn't know he lived
upstairs in an apartment
with his grandkids.
That's why I deserve to die.
It was my first year...
on the force,
I was working the
valley division, and...
my partner got into it
with this speed freak.
It was bad. The kid
was all tweaked out,
and my partner was
having a really rough day.
The kid took a
swing at my partner,
and that was it.
He beat the hell
out of this kid.
I really wanted to stop it,
but he looked up at me.
He looked at me, and he asked
me if I wanted to join in.
You joined in?
Yeah, I didn't want
to hurt my reputation.
You know, I mean,
it was my first year out on the street.
I mean, you know what I mean, Kelley.
So you beat the kid.
Yeah, but God damn it,
I'm not proud of it.
Well, did you go
to Internal Affairs?
No.
I stuck around
for 2 more years
and got transferred
out of there.
So why would your old
partner pull you down here
if you never turned
him in or told anyone?
It wasn't my partner.
I was thinking maybe the
kid finally tracked us down
not for beating him up.
For blinding him.
That's awful.
What was the kid's name?
Alfie Martinez.
And I don't know if that's
the reason why I'm down here,
but that's what haunts
me every day of my life,
that I didn't stand up.
I didn't have the
courage to do anything,
to stand up to my superiors.
So if your old
partner is still alive,
wouldn't it make sense that
he'd be in here with us?
Yeah, that's just a dead end,
another dead end.
I'm telling you,
we're wasting time.
We've got to find our own
way out of here like Leon did.
Yeah, that worked
out real well for him.
It's time for
your redemption...
Yeah, sing it, sister!
Hallelujah! Right, cocksucker?
Shut the hell up, Sully!
We got to think of something.
I just thought of something.
I don't know if
this is anything,
but since we're
confessing our sins,
and there is
a priest here--
All right, just
spit it out, Eddie.
When I was in college,
we had some girls--
strippers over for a party.
We were all drinking,
and I spent some
time with one of them.
We both got
really drunk, and--
And you banged her.
Yeah, but she
said it was rape.
And here all this time we
thought you were so perfect.
It turns out you're just
another asshole frat boy.
They dropped the charges
due to lack of evidence.
Mom and dad must
have been so proud.
I'm just trying to help.
I mean, something might click.
Isn't that the whole point?
No, you're getting us
further away from the point
I was trying to make.
Guys, look, this is
about the robbery.
We're missing
something. I know we are.
No, there's nothing else with
the robbery; I promise you.
What was that, Francis?
You know we're going down
the wrong road, don't you?
Yeah, 20 years of poker
tells me that's a "yes."
What do you know, Father?
Forget about the robbery!
Okay, it doesn't matter what
he knows. Shut up, Kelley!
You were about to
beat that kid to death,
and now you won't
help me kill the guy
who's ready to execute us all?
What the hell is wrong with you?
What's wrong with all of you?
Hey, I'm with you, Kelley.
But this cocksucker here
is about ready to crack,
and I'm pretty damned interested
to hear what he has to say.
I know you want
to tell us, Father.
Come on.
You ready to break
that oath, Father?
This isn't easy, okay?
Just say it. It's
the right thing to do.
What if I said that
I knew for a fact
that Wade Greeley did
not rob Chan's store?
Bullshit. Chan
was the eyewitness.
Greeley didn't have an
alibi, and I had the evidence,
concrete evidence.
Did Greeley say he was innocent?
Of course he said he was innocent.
Everybody's innocent.
Nobody wants to be convicted
once they're caught.
What do you know
about it, Father?
No, I'm telling you.
Greeley was guilty.
Son of a bitch.
What?
One of us confessed to the crime
in Father Francis' confessional.
I bet that's it. Is that it?
Is it, Father? Whatever
Father Francis knows,
he knows from
the confessional.
Otherwise, he would tell us.
Has anyone ever been to confession
in the San Fernando Valley?
Yeah, right.
No.
Christian!
It has to be Christian.
You all saw the father's face when
I couldn't remember the Hail Mary.
I reminded him of Christian.
He forgot the same
prayer earlier, remember?
What could Christian
have told Father Francis?
That he robbed
the liquor store.
You've known this whole time?
I did not know the whole time.
It wasn't until after Chan
came up with the robbery
that I knew for sure.
Cocksucker!
I told you you wouldn't
like what I had to say.
Are you absolutely positive
that it was Christian
in the confessional?
The Lord is with thee.
Dude, how does the
rest of that go?
If I had a Bible, I
would put my hand on it.
You got the wrong
man, prosecutor.
Wade Greeley's the wrong guy.
I had the evidence
against him.
Regardless, I mean, this is
a whole new ball game now.
Holy shit.
Sully.
Yeah?
Christian got out of jail the
same time Chan's store was robbed.
So what does that
have to do with me?
What happens to people
who don't pay you?
If they owe a little,
I go for their knees.
If they owe a lot, I
go for their jugular.
Yeah, well, does Christian look like the
type of kid that could take a beating?
So what?
What are you saying?
Christian robbed Chan
to get you the money.
He said that he got
out of jail in May
and paid you soon after.
How else could he
have gotten the money?
It fits.
Wait a second.
So you're telling me, of all
the fucked-up shit I've done
through the course of my life,
I loaned some dead
dumbass 5 grand,
and that's what
I'm gonna die for?
The kid needed a motive.
I think you're it.
That's goddamn ridiculous.
You're serious?
All I did was
give him some cash.
I got to die for
that? That's bullshit!
The connection between
you and Christian
has been there the whole time.
We just never thought
anything of it.
And I still don't.
Of all the shit I--
Hey there, asshole!
Why are you here?
You know what? We don't know.
But guess what. I
don't give a fuck.
I don't know what kind of
shit you got going on here,
but I'm sick of it.
You've got me sweating,
rethinking all the horrible
things that I've done in my life
and all the people
I've crossed.
For what?
For some dumbass that I loaned
$5,000 to?
Well, guess what.
That's how I do business, and
that's how I get shit done.
I don't apologize for shit.
Knowing what you know,
knowing how your life will end,
would you change the
way you do business?
Hell no!
I don't regret anything.
I wouldn't do a
damn thing different.
What's the matter?
You don't like that, do you,
you dirty revenge-seeking pussy?
I don't regret anything.
What, you want me
to regret my life?
Fuck you.
Tou want the satisfaction
of me begging for my life,
don't you?
Fuck you.
You want the satisfaction
of killing all of us,
thinking it's gonna
change our lives.
Well, fuck you!
I take that back.
I take all that back.
Yeah.
I'm not gonna give
you the satisfaction
of me being pissed
off while I die.
Of all the shit you
could have killed me for,
5 grand?
Fuck you!
Come on, bastard.
Let's do this.
Hit me right here in the
head, just like my brother.
Reunite me with him.
Come on, asshole!
Pull the trigger.
But it's not your turn.
It's Eddie's.
Me?
No, no, no.
Please, no.
No, no.
Don't kill me.
Just tell me why I'm here.
Damn it!
1 person dies
every 10 minutes.
That's what you said!
Father Francis is dead.
You cannot take Eddie now.
Really?
5 grand?
You shouldn't be in
such a hurry to die.
If this is the end for you,
you'll want to make
every minute count.
This doesn't have to continue.
Okay, we know why you
brought most of us here,
and we know what you
must have been feeling,
what you must be feeling now.
Okay, I think I
speak for all of us
when we say we wish we could
go back and change history,
but we can't.
Wade.
Wade Greeley?
Whatever it is that you think
we've done to you, whatever--
whatever it is you've done
here today, we can make right.
You just have to talk to us.
Look, we can help. I can help.
Okay, whatever it is you want,
we--we-- I can
make that happen.
Do you understand what
I'm telling you, Wade?
I'm not Wade Greeley.
It's not Wade Greeley.
This doesn't make any sense.
There's way too many
coincidences for it not to be
this guy, Greeley.
I've spent 5 grand
on a bottle of whiskey
without a care in the
world. Sully, we get it.
I'm telling you, he's
gonna kill us all.
Okay, he doesn't care if
we come up with his plan.
If he just wanted to kill
us, we'd be dead already.
He's here to make a point.
But do we really think
this isn't Greeley?
If it isn't, it has to
be somebody close to him,
somebody that could
help him plan this.
Kelley, back at the trial,
was there anyone there?
Were there any friends or
family, anyone who stood by him?
No, no, he didn't have
anything or anyone.
I don't even
think he made bail.
Can you give us a
few more details?
Jeez, this was so long ago.
Do you realize how many trials I've
had since then, since before then?
Okay, let's think.
Now, Leon said that he'd been
planning this for 2 years.
When did Greeley's
case go to trial?
I don't remember.
Can you at least tell us
how many years
he got in prison?
Armed robbery,
assault, no plea.
5 years, maybe.
Well, then the
years don't add up.
If I was wrongly
convicted of a crime,
I would start plotting my
revenge the day I was convicted.
That's what I'm saying.
Nothing about this makes sense.
The only way we're gonna get
out of this is if we escape.
Was Christian in the lineup
when Chan picked Greeley?
No, if Christian
was in the lineup,
Chan would have recognized him
when we pulled the hoods off.
She didn't recognize
Kelley until later.
Well, maybe she did. I mean, nobody
understood what she was saying.
Mrs. Chan? Give it up.
We're getting off track.
I'm just coming up
with possibilities.
Well, to hell with
your possibilities.
Why are you pissed at me?
Because maybe we still
don't know jack about you!
Are you really that stupid
to think I'm hiding something?
I told you everything that I
can think of, so don't blame me.
Something about you still
doesn't sit right with me, Eddie.
You know, you've been riding me
and picking on me this whole time.
What is your problem? I
might be dead in 10 minutes!
That's my fucking problem! I
think we all know who's next.
Calm down.
What about you, Jackson? We
still don't know why you're here.
All we know is that
you beat a kid blind
and cheated on your wife.
Well, look who's
grown some balls.
I think I got it.
You better watch
your tone Eddie,
or I'm gonna start thinking
you're the psycho's partner,
or at least until I see
your brains against the wall.
Yeah, yeah, well, not
if I see yours first.
Fine, go ahead! Sign me up!
Hey, shut up!
All right, you guys are
worse than my strippers.
Now listen.
Leon said that he
killed his brother
and dumped him during the
Cinco de Mayo parade, remember?
So what?
Well, Christian said that
he got out of jail in May.
And?
What if that was
around the same time?
Look, Christian got
out of jail, right?
And he said he got my 5
grand right afterwards, right?
Well, if we go back
and think about it,
Christian said that he had
nothing when he left jail.
I had nothing
going in to prison.
I had even less getting out.
But somehow he was able to pull off
this big liquor store robbery heist?
Where did he get a
gun to rob Mrs. Chan?
Leon said the easiest
product to move were guns.
Guns can be better than cash.
So you think Leon sold
the gun to Christian
that he used to rob
Chan's liquor store?
So Sully gave Christian
the motive for the robbery.
Leon gave him opportunity.
Chan identified the wrong man.
Kelley locked him up.
And Father Francis
didn't go to the cops
after he found out the truth.
Okay, so that leaves...
Jackson, me, and Coogan.
But we can all agree that
this all started with Christian
borrowing money from Sully.
Between that and
Greeley going to jail
is our new time line.
When Christian borrowed
the money from Sully,
I was studying
pharmaceuticals in Arizona.
Okay, well, Christian said
that he was dealing drugs.
Could he have
gotten them from you?
No.
I didn't have any
access to drugs.
All right, all right, we've
narrowed this down some.
Narrowed it down?
All we got is a robbery,
drug dealing, and a pedophile.
Sorry, buddy. Buddy?
Look, Sully is a criminal.
Okay, he's a killer.
We would have taken him down
100 times if we had the chance.
And now he's your best friend?
I'm sorry for liking the guy
who's trying to save my life.
Thank you.
And for bacon, you're
not so bad yourself.
Look, our only chance is that
we think Eddie might be next.
And then hopefully
after that, Sully's next.
So you and I can
take him down.
God, you are one twisted
home-wrecking bitch.
Well, it's good to know it
only takes a gun to your head
for you to speak your mind.
You know what?
The worst thing I did was not
beating that kid till he was blind.
It was fucking the lawyer.
That hurts.
Jackson, I hope you die
for getting me into this.
What are you talking about?
I didn't get you into this.
No, no, wait, wait, wait.
You just said that
Jackson got you into this.
What does that mean?
What does what mean? Look,
we have, like, seconds
left till he comes in.
Why are you here?
Because this bitch knows
something, and she won't talk!
Please don't kill me.
It's none of my fault.
I have nothing to do
with your son's death.
I'm begging you.
Don't kill me...
Spare me. Let me go, huh?
Let me go.
Please, please!
I beg you!
You can't kill me.
You have to let me go.
My child needs me.
Okay, my son needs his mommy.
You're a human being.
You can understand.
You can't take a mother
away from her son.
Your son William goes to
the Sacred Heart School,
where he is picked up every
day by your hired help.
And when was the last time
you actually spent
time with him?
And how long will it be
before you pack him off
to some boarding school?
Do not use your
child as an excuse.
It pisses me off.
And it should piss
you off as well.
What was he talking
about, Kelley?
It looks like you
might be a dad, Jackson.
Billy's mine?
I didn't think I could.
My wife and I, we'd
been trying for--
I didn't think
it was possible.
Yeah, well, it's possible.
Maybe if you had spent a
little less time with me
and a little more with her.
How could you do that to me?
How could you just
keep that from me?
I know our relationship,
the breakup was bad,
but how could you just
cut me off like that?
I had to do what
was best for me.
Okay, jackass over there was
never gonna leave his wife.
He would rather
just lead me on.
So when I found out, I
I just blamed it
on someone else.
What you did was wrong
and downright selfish.
You need to start talking.
And it doesn't matter
what you're holding back.
I don't care.
I forgive you, but we have
to get out of here alive.
Do you want to die?
I might as well be
dead if this gets out.
Before, you said Jackson
got you into this.
How?
Look.
Wade Greeley was picked up 2
miles from the liquor store.
He was a good match
to Chan's description.
And no one could verify
his lame-ass alibi.
And then Chan picked
him out of the lineup.
I had him. I had to have him.
You remember what I was
going through, Jackson.
The mother and son,
the abortion case:
two in a row lost.
I was just getting into the life
that I had worked so hard for,
and I felt the pressure.
You know, I had to have a
conviction, or I was on my way out.
I was the lowest on the totem pole,
and no one was taking me seriously.
I had to win at all costs.
Losing cases doesn't
make you incompetent.
No, but combine
that with budget cuts
and an affair with Jackson that
was growing more public every day,
and it doesn't look good.
What did you make
me do, Kelley?
I had Chan's testimony,
but it was shaky at best.
I would never be able convince
a jury that a 60-year-old woman
could positively
identify someone,
especially after she'd
been pistol-whipped.
I had to put
Greeley at the scene.
During the struggle,
Chan grabbed Christian by the
head and got a few couple hairs.
So I knew I just had to get some
of Wade's hair and make the switch.
So I snuck the
sample out of the lab.
I got a few hairs
from Wade's comb.
And--
and I couldn't get the sample
back into the evidence room.
And I thought me and Coogan
were the most fucked-up
2 in this room.
Don't you realize that you
helped kill these people?
How could you not
tell us this before?
Look, if the truth ever gets
out of this room, I'm over.
I'll lose my job.
I'll go to jail.
I'll never see my son again.
I might as well be dead.
I committed a felony.
Yeah, welcome to my world.
You know, I know we're
not a team or a family,
but we have a child together.
Doesn't that mean something?
No, he's my son,
Jackson, okay?
You're not a father.
You'll never be a father.
You were just a
dick, literally.
You're fucking
unbelievable, Kelley.
You're not a father. What?
No, no, no.
Hear me out for a second.
Greeley said that he
wasn't Wade Greeley.
I'm not Wade Greeley.
Did you see how upset he got
when Kelley tried to
use her son for pity?
Do not use your
child as an excuse.
It pisses me off.
I mean, if it's
not really Wade,
then maybe it's his father.
Has anybody thought about
what happened to Wade Greeley
after he went to prison?
Remember when I said
Wade Greeley going to prison
was the end-all-be-all?
Well, I could have been wrong.
Jackson was on to
something a minute ago.
We've been trying to
see how Coogan and I
fit into the time
line before the trial.
We weren't thinking
about what happened
after prison.
You said that Wade
was in San Quentin.
Did Christian say
what prison he was in?
No, but the sick
fucker over there
said he'd been to
a couple of prisons.
My travels have
taken me all over,
including Los Angeles.
More than a few prisons.
This must mean something.
Christian couldn't
have known Wade Greeley.
Christian got out of prison
before Wade Greeley went in.
But Coogan knowing
Wade Greeley,
that's a possibility.
That just leaves me.
Wait, wait!
We need more time!
Why are you here?
Look, we think it
has something to do
with what happened to your
son after he went to prison.
Isn't this what you want? You
want us to think about our lives
and our actions and crimes and
how they've affected other people?
Well, that's
what we are doing,
and it's killing us.
Look, no one has suffered
like you and your son.
Okay, no one
here was on trial.
No one here was punished
for their crimes.
We've just gone on with our
lives and never looked back.
But you have to look
back every single day.
Look, you asked Sully
if he would change,
knowing what he's done.
Well, I guarantee, you ask
anyone in this room now,
and we would change.
We would change
for the better.
Now, speak for
yourself, kiss-ass.
Kiss my ass.
You could have died finding
some humanity or humility.
I'd rather go out in style.
Maybe we do deserve to die.
I just wish I knew why.
What, you two are
ready to give up?
You're both ready to die?
Well, fuck you both.
Okay, never give up.
I've lived through worse than
this, and I'll live through this.
Worse than this, Kelley?
What could possibly
be worse than this?
Well, back when you
and I were still dating,
I was stupid enough in this day
and age to think that I could
walk to my car alone at night.
Some...
sweaty, bald-headed bastard
grabbed me from behind
and threw me in his van.
He bashed my head on
the steel flooring.
I was dazed, but I could see
that there was
already blood there.
This wasn't his first time.
He put his hand over my face
as he ripped my clothes off.
It's
like my--
my brain didn't really
register the pain.
I just--
I just kept
thinking about how I
was gonna get this guy,
this thing, you know.
And I was gonna put him away
for the rest of his life.
I kept imagining the courtroom
and how I would be looking
into his eyes, and I would say,
"I'm the one that
ruined your life."
But then I realized we
weren't in a courtroom.
There was no judge, no jury.
It was just me and this shit
head who thought he could
put his hands all over me.
Who the fuck was this guy to
violate me, to take my life?
What right did he
have to touch me?
I wasn't scared.
I was furious.
Why didn't you
tell me, Kelley?
We could have done
something about that.
You could have
searched everywhere.
You never would
have found him.
When he was done,
he rolled off me,
and I saw that there was
a baseball bat in his van.
And I grabbed it,
and I hit him hard.
Then I stepped back,
thinking someone must have seen,
someone must have heard. But,
as I waiting for someone
to come help me, I...
hit him again.
And then I hit
him again. And I...
I just kept swinging.
And he just kept screaming.
You know, and he begged. He
begged. Can you believe that?
I swear, I think that
made me hit him harder.
And
then--
and then he just
stopped screaming.
He stopped moving.
And I looked around again,
and still no one was there.
No one heard.
No one cared.
So I...
I went home, and I cleaned up,
and I burned the
bat in my fireplace.
And I just went on
with my life like that.
It was just over.
And the next day when
they found his body,
I made sure no one went
looking for his killer.
And now I'm here.
And I promise
you, I promise you,
I will live through this,
and I will survive
at all-- at all costs.
What about rape?
We all heard Coogan.
He didn't care if
it was boys or girls.
And if he was in the
same prison with Wade,
why not a
20-year-old kid?
We did this to him.
How could I have known what
was gonna happen to him?
Think about Wade
Greeley, an innocent kid
and all the things
he went through.
And think about his father
having to think about
what happened to his son.
Think about that.
When Coogan was shot,
when Greeley came
in here and shot him,
what did Coogan say?
I don't remember.
What are you thinking?
He said something about a
splatter and killing everyone
or something like that.
Maybe you should move them
out of the way of the splatter.
I'd hate to see somebody die
before you get a chance
to kill 'em yourself.
Yeah, he was being a smart-ass.
He was talking about the bullet,
if it went through him
and killed somebody else.
I thought the same thing.
But what if that's
not what he meant?
What if the joke was
about something else?
His blood, for instance.
His infected blood.
What if Coogan had AIDS?
That's a big stretch, Eddie.
Not really.
That's the final
piece of our time line.
It starts with Christian
borrowing money from Sully.
I know you.
Says you.
No, we did some business
together years ago.
But then he loses that money after
a bad drug deal and ends up in jail.
When he gets released,
he buys a gun from Leon,
uses it to rob
Chan's liquor store,
'cause he still
owes Sully the money.
Then Chan picks Wade
Greeley out of the lineup.
Kelley makes sure the
evidence fits her case
and uses Jackson to
secure that evidence
against Wade for the trial.
Father Francis learns the
truth during confession
but being bound by
God, says nothing.
So Wade ends up in prison
where he has a
run-in with Coogan.
And that's how I'm
tied into all this.
So why are you here?
Back around the time when Wade
would have been
released from prison,
my company had acquired
the exclusive rights
to an experimental drug
therapy for AIDS patients.
It was said to
prolong the life
of people living with AIDS.
It was very new expensive.
I think Coogan infected
Wade Greeley with AIDS.
And the reason Wade's
dad waited 2 years
is because that's exactly
how long his son lived
outside of prison
before he died.
It's his father
acting out revenge for
the death of his son.
Wade must have been
one of the applicants
for the new AIDS drug.
Part of my job was to
turn down applicants.
Improper insurance,
not enough money,
wrong age, and
criminal records.
I was the one whose name was signed
to all letters denying applicants.
If I had accepted
Wade into the program,
he might be alive today.
That's it.
That's the answer
he's looking for.
So why are you here?
Because your son died of AIDS.
He contracted it in
prison from Coogan.
When he was released,
you tried to get him into my
company's drug therapy program,
but
they--
I turned him down.
Your son could be alive today
if we all hadn't turned
our backs on him and on you.
He was so,
so beautiful.
My son was a very
brave and lovely boy.
And all of you made sure
that he would never
grow up to be a man.
It didn't have
to end this way.
Any one of you could
have prevented his death.
But you all...
saw him as a suspect or
a number, a toy
to be played with.
His only fault
was that he became
a part of your lives.
But it was his life.
And you destroyed it.
When
we--
when we leave here,
my life will end, but
you will all still have yours.
And I want you to remember,
just remember this.
Remember what it
is you have done.
And I hope that it haunts you
until the day you die.
Show's over.
The police are already here.
They're in the building.
Unlock yourself
and the other 2.
It's time to leave.
What are you doing?
He was letting us go!
I told you I couldn't have
anyone go to the police
with my story. I'd be ruined.
Survive at all
costs, remember?
So you're going to kill him?
You're never gonna get away,
no matter what you do.
You don't get to make any more decisions.
You don't get to do or say anything.
Jesus! I can't
take this anymore!
Just get me the
hell out of here.
Kelley, look.
It's time for us to leave.
Just calm down, and we
can all go home together.
Kelley, we survived.
Together we can do this.
We have a child
together. Come on.
I can't have anyone know
what I've done, Jackson.
She's gonna kill
us! Shut up, Eddie!
Let me handle this!
Shut up, Eddie!
No, no, look!
I'm not gonna say
anything. I swear!
And you.
You've lost. I haven't lost.
I've been in control
the whole time.
See, everybody's
been watching.
Everybody now knows who
the real Kelley Murphy is.
What will Kelley do now?
You don't know me.
You don't know
what I'm capable of.
Good luck.
Thanks.
Subtitles/ translation: Arigon
Move over here.
Come on, this way, this way.
Over here.
Clear.
[Course of
Nature's Anger Cage]
* Since the day
that I was born
* I've been a
prisoner of the storm
* But the time has come
* Now I've had enough
* I can't take it anymore
* The blood rushes to my head
* You deserve
everything you get
* The love is gone
* And there's
nothing left here
* But the love you try to hate
* Tell me now who's to blame?
* Will I burst from your rage?
* Hear it callin' my name
down in your anger cage
* You are the cause
of the fightin'
* You force my
rage out of hiding
* Well do you
stop and look at me
* As you bomb the enemy
* You know that you've crossed
the line for the last time
* When you trampled over me
* The blood rushes to my head
* You deserve
everything you get
* The love is gone
* And there's
nothing left here
* But the love you try to hate
* Tell me now who's to blame?
* Will I burst from your rage?
* Hear it callin' my name
down in your anger cage
* You are the cause
of the fightin'
* You force my
rage out of hiding
* I started losing it
* I-I'm out of control
* This rage is killin' me
* Yeah, it's takin' its toll
* I'm fallin' apart from here
* I can see the end
* It's all so clear
* I might choke, suffocate
* Inside my anger cage
* Tell me now who's to blame?
* Will I burst from your rage?
* Hear it callin' my name
down in your anger cage
* You are the cause
of the fightin'
* You force my
rage out of hiding
* Don't care what you say
* I don't give a damn
* You talk about me but
you don't know who I am
* Don't care what you say
* I don't give a damn
* You talk about me but
you don't know who I am
* Talk about me but
* Talk about me
but you don't know
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org