- Permission to enter?
- Come.
Where's the rest of the company, captain?
Where do you think?
Moved out with the battalion.
I've been waiting here for you.
- You took your time getting back.
- I got lost in the smoke.
What happened to your gun?
Have you ever seen a shell-shocked horse?
He stomped all over me and got my rifle,
knocked it to smithereens.
Well, I suppose horses have as much right
to go crazy in this war as men have.
What do you think?
What the hell is it?
It's a "one." First Infantry Division.
The Red One. You think
General Pershing will like it?
- Oh, sure.
- I got the idea from a cap of a Hun I killed.
- When?
- Oh, about an hour ago.
Did he yell out anything?
Well, the same old kaiser stuff, you know,
"The war is over," all that junk.
- Finish it.
- Sir?
Finish it.
The armistice was signed
at 11:00 this morning.
The war's been over for four hours.
Well, you didn't know it was over.
He did.
A quarter of a century later,
that piece of red cloth...
... from the dead Hun's hat had
become famous all over the world.
It was the insignia of
the 1 st Infantry Division.
The Fighting First, the Big Red One.
Twenty-four years later, the Big Red One
was fighting the Krauts again.
It was World War II this time.
We were invading North Africa.
Hey, Griff.
Great! Thanks, sergeant.
We were his rifle squad.
First Squad, 1 st Platoon,
I Company, 16th Infantry.
He called us his wet-noses.
Griff, he was a hell of a sharpshooter.
Johnson was a pig farmer
with hemorrhoids.
Vinci was a street kid who played hot jazz
on the saxophone, and that's me, I'm Zab.
I thought I was the Hemingway
of the Bronx.
You really a book writer?
- Yeah.
- What book did you write?
The Dark Deadline.
- Never heard of it.
- Never read it.
It's an unpublished mystery novel.
I left it with my mother.
Why's a book writer a rifleman?
To come out with a war novel,
meathead. Why else, huh?
What about you, Griff?
You gonna be a cartoonist
for a big newspaper or something?
Say, Griff. You do everything left-handed?
Everything but shoot.
And play with my pecker.
"Watch out, Vichy.
Here comes the Big Red One."
Vichy?
I always thought Vichy
was some kind of soda pop.
No. Vichy's the French,
fighting on Hitler's side.
Yeah, that's why we're wearing these
so they don't shoot Americans, huh?
We dropped leaflets
so they know we're coming.
But if they start a fight,
we'll have to kill them.
We were in this war to fight Germans,
not Frenchmen.
We were kind of hoping
they were feeling the same way.
Put your rubbers on
and keep the salt water out.
Thanks, Griff.
I'll bet the guy that invented these...
...never figured they'd be used on a rifle.
- I never could screw with them.
How about you, Johnson?
Not me.
Over on the Algerian beach, a lot of
French soldiers were reading our leaflets...
... and also wondering
if they were gonna fight.
The colonel is stupid not to believe
these leaflets.
We are no good. You, me, all of us here.
Defending this miserable Algerian beach
for Marshal Pétain and Adolf Hitler.
I can't kill an American.
There were four things
you could hear on the boat:
The waves, the engines...
... an occasional muffled prayer...
... and the sound of 50 guys
all heaving their guts out.
French troops, don't shoot.
We are Americans.
Don't shoot. We come to fight Hitler,
not to fight with you. Don't shoot.
Hold your fire!
- Yes, colonel.
- Open fire.
Not on Americans.
Medic! Medic!
Nail him, Griff!
How the hell could you miss him?
Hell, he was close enough
to kiss on both cheeks.
What the hell's the matter with you?
I never saw you miss.
Medic! Over here.
Sixteenth Infantry, hold your fire!
Americans, this is Captain Chapier.
General Tavernier is dead.
Americans! I surrender my troops
to your hands.
Frenchmen, we do not accept
your surrender.
You surrender only to the enemy.
If you're Vichy, fight us.
If you're Frenchmen, join us!
We were feeling cocky as hell.
Except Griff.
In the middle of the battle, he froze.
It got to Griff.
He kept away from the rest of us.
Nobody wanted to use
the word "coward," not yet.
How come we're not pushing inland?
Red Company's carrying the ball.
Take your malaria pills.
Smoky-smoky for zigzag.
Bladder juice.
- Jeez.
- Not bad.
Hey, how come you never miss?
They always take off backwards.
Smoky-smoky for zig-zig.
Smoky-smoky for girl.
And I'll bet you can get a whole harem
here for a pack of smokes.
Girl. Zig-zig. Girl. Zig-zig.
I wonder what they gave you in
the other war not to get a hard-on?
The same stuff you're wolfing down now.
It has saltpeter.
Griff's back.
I can't murder anybody.
We don't murder, we kill.
It's the same thing.
The hell it is, Griff.
You don't murder animals, you kill them.
The truth is, none of us had
the faintest idea what war was all about.
I'll send your relief up in an hour.
I'm not gonna tell you again,
no lights at night.
Third Squad lost five men.
I heard that they
bury wounded men alive.
- Know what else I heard?
- Tell it to the chaplain.
A lot of good he does
if you're buried alive.
Well, maybe it'll do him some good, huh?
Do you think Bedcheck Charlie's
gonna tuck us in again tonight?
Well, he's never on time. But a couple
of bombs and a little strafing...
...good for you. Keep you
on your toes, keep you alert.
Hello, suckers of the Big Red One.
This is your German lovey-dovey
bringing you the latest war news.
The Germans are in Moscow.
Don't look for the truck
playing this record.
Seven Gls from the 34th Infantry
tried it last night...
... and they're deader than the
Unknown Soldier in Washington, D.C.
Adolf Hitler has nothing
against you American dogfaces.
I wonder what she looks like.
If she's half as good as she sounds,
I'd eat her on sauerkraut.
You know Hitler's beef is with England.
Hey, how old do you think she is?
I'll bet she's old enough
to shove a swastika up her.
All those limeys hate your guts
for licking them back in 1776.
Why fight for them?
Knock off the bratwurst, Brunhilda.
And sing us a lullaby.
I'll get to the song in a minute, honey.
Now, news from the good old U.S.A.
The workers in the defense plants
are striking for a raise in pay.
While you suckers are getting all of
$ 10 a month extra for combat pay...
... your wives, your sweethearts, are shacking
up with draft dodgers and deserters.
You think of your women back home
in the sack with these lucky, lucky 4-F's.
Zab.
Quit poking me with your rifle.
That's not my rifle, Johnson.
Sounds like we found the lost squad.
Where the hell's that radio?
- Where's the radio?
- Dead!
Pull the squad back to those arches.
I'm gonna see what's on the left.
Chapier, blind that tank.
Get these horses out of here.
This is gonna blow. Move out!
Will you get them out? Get them out,
get them out! This is gonna blow.
I never smoke them.
Lieutenant just got word from Battalion.
No more swapping smokes
with the Goums for Kraut ears.
The Goums have been
cutting off American ears.
Sergeant, my Goums never kill Americans.
I didn't say killing them.
I said, cutting their ears off.
But these are Kraut ears.
After a fight, you can't tell the difference
between an American and a Kraut ear...
...so there will be no more
swapping cigarettes...
...for any kind of an ear.
Not in my squad.
Communications Center caught
an American bomb.
These wet-noses found the phonograph
and one record undamaged.
Look at the faces
of these puppies, Schroeder.
They think the Horst Wessel song is so...
Horst Wessel was a pimp who supplied
Hitler with baby faces like you.
He was killed in a brawl,
over a whore in Berlin.
A poem by a pimp became
the hymn of Hitler's party.
Is that right, Schroeder?
Don't want to disillusion
these infants, huh?
You're getting soft.
Schroeder used to be tough. In Libya,
I saw him murder a German officer.
I didn't murder him, Gerd,
I killed him...
...when he ran from a fight
with the British.
Murder. Killed. It's the same thing.
We don't murder the enemy, we kill.
Everything is on the move.
Battalion is sending us
to the Kasserine Pass.
- We're going to choke on panzer fumes.
- Not me, Schroeder.
Let Rommel's panzer grenadiers
march behind those tanks.
But not me. I want no more.
I'm no damn Nazi fanatic like you.
Germany is through singing
for Adolf Hitler.
Our brilliant generals had figured...
... that Rommel's push would come
at a place called Speava...
... so they massed most
of the Allied forces over there.
But they sent our regiment
around the back way...
... through a shit-hole called
the Kasserine Pass.
Our squad was on point.
We got an eyeful, all right.
The whole damned Afrika Korps was
coming through the Kasserine Pass.
Rommel had caught us
with our pants down.
We got tanks, boys,
and infantry with them.
They'll be looking behind the rocks
for antitank guns, so let's go!
- Oh, shit.
- Let's go.
Sergeant, where are we gonna run to?
They'll spot us out in the open.
- We're not running, we're digging in.
- Digging in? Are you crazy, sergeant?
All right. Dig in and let them roll
over our heads.
Hey, they're going off to the right!
Guess again, jerk-off. Look over there.
Tanks! They're all over the place!
You are in a temporary
German hospital in Tunis, sergeant.
The war is over for you.
We won. You lost.
I speak good English.
Our doctors cannot understand
what is keeping you alive.
How could such a decayed country
like America...
...produce such a magnificent soldier
like you?
You are a very beautiful man, sergeant.
I adore supermen.
I can understand your being horny,
Fritz, but you've got bad breath.
We'd better get out of here.
You heard what that orderly said.
This is an unmarked hospital,
and they'd just as soon blast us.
Anybody here from the Big Red One?
Sixteenth.
Eighteenth!
Where's that Big Red One man?
What happened at the pass?
You with the 16th?
You one of them goons?
I Company, 3rd Battalion.
What are you doing wrapped up
in that Arab bed sheet?
- What happened at the pass?
- We counterattacked after you jokers ran.
We took Kasserine, Gafsa,
El Guettar, Tunis.
- We ran Rommel right out of Africa.
- You mean the Big Red One took Tunis.
We sure as hell did.
This is Tunis.
You're right.
We took Tunis.
Where's the 1 st Squad?
Out of the original 12-man rifle squad,
the four of us were the only ones left.
This invasion wasn't gonna
be like North Africa.
The beach would be heavily defended.
So now at least, we could all go
to Sicily and get killed together.
I gave the supply officer a Luger for it.
By the way, what were you doing
in that Arab bed sheet?
They were shanghaiing
all the combats...
...and noncoms and training
replacements for those rebel devils.
Where'd you steal it, stupe?
My name's Shep, not "stupe." I got it
from the St. George Hotel in Algiers.
I understand you're an Italian, Vinci.
How come they let a wop
in this man's Army?
I don't think a wop's
gonna fight a wop.
I think all you'll do is drink dago red
and sing "O Sole Mio."
I like "O Sole Mio."
The creepy thing about battle
is that you always feel alone.
All you can see are the guys
right next to you...
... and the bodies you keep tripping over.
Sergeant!
- Sergeant!
- Ho!
- Throw me a hot one!
- I'm out of them!
Johnson!
- Johnson!
- Ho!
- Throw me some live ones.
- I'm out of them.
- Zab.
- Ho!
Throw me live ones.
I'm out! Griff!
- Griff!
- Ho!
Throw me live ones!
I'm all out. Hey, Shep, you got
any grenades on you?
Shep?
Shep.
You chicken bastard.
Hey, Zab. I got some live ones for you.
- Johnson!
- Sergeant!
Vinci!
Give me another one!
Zab!
- Johnson!
- Sergeant!
Vinci!
Why are we always sent out? It's the only
damn squad in the whole U.S. Army?
- Where's the rest of the Army?
- There are eight patrols...
...checking the villages for diehard snipers.
Anybody wants to transfer,
just let me know.
I want to transfer.
Okay, Vinci. You're transferred to the point.
You know how you smoke out a sniper?
You send a guy out in the open
and you see if he gets shot.
They thought that one up at West Point.
- Are you okay, sergeant?
- Why?
- You just let Vinci walk into a sniper.
- That's why he's here.
We got plenty of wet-noses here too.
You really want to finish
that book, don't you?
That's why I'm here.
Vinci made it.
Come on, Carlos, your turn.
Let's go. Come on!
- Hey, Vinci?
- Ho!
You know where he lives!
Work to your right, I'll go left.
It's your ball.
Bravo! Bravo!
- You had him in the sights all the time.
- All the time.
You just wanted to see me sweat.
It's punishment for transferring me to the
point. May I rejoin the rear echelon now?
You are transferred back to the point.
Oh, my aching butt.
By now, we'd come to look
at all replacements...
... as dead men who temporarily
had the use of their arms and legs.
They came and went so fast
and so regular...
... that sometimes we didn't even
get to know their names.
Truth is, after a while we sort of avoided
getting to know them.
L... I brought some water.
Do you know what they call
you four guys down at Battalion?
Sergeant's Four Horsemen.
I don't get it. You guys lived
through North Africa.
You didn't even get a scratch.
That's because replacements
keep getting hit instead of us.
You think...? You think maybe I'll get it?
Why not? You something special?
I'll go get some, all right?
I'll... Excuse me.
Water.
You'll live, Smitty.
You did tripwire the mine.
They're not designed to kill you,
just to castrate you.
Castrate me?!
Oh, my God!
Hey, here it is. I found it.
Hey, that's my cock! Give it back to me!
Give me back my cock!
It's just one of your balls, Smitty.
You can live without it.
That's why they gave you two.
I still got my cock! I still got it!
I got my cock!
They're supposed to be
coming this way.
Hold it up.
I said, hold it up!
I'm eating.
Okay, let's try this.
Come on.
- Keep an eye peeled for snakes.
- Yeah, and bats.
Bats? I love bats.
Sergeant, what's the word
from Headquarters?
Yeah, what did the lieutenant say?
The lieutenant said that Hermann Goring's
panzers overran the 2nd Battalion.
If they break through the division...
...we're in the sea.
- Where are they headed?
- Right for us.
Our big guns will clobber them.
- They're still on the water.
- None of them have unloaded yet?
Not yet.
Patton's got tanks.
Still on the water.
Jesus. We're sitting in our own coffin.
We knew he wanted to run for it...
... but we knew he wouldn't...
... way before he did.
Anyway, the sergeant
would've shot him if he tried it.