Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Some chefs calls them "turtledoves",
a very romantic plate.
Well cooked they are so
soft as the butter.
They can be made to the grill,
padded with wild or cooked rice
... roasted, poached, to
the fathoms and even fried.
But there is not bigger sin that
to cook too much a quail.
To be perfect, he/she should have
the breast a little rosy.
You need the correct quail. It should
to be fleshy or he/she dries off very quick.
I prefer to serve them roasted.
That gives him/her a flavor
more robust and more succulent.
With a garnish of truffle raviolis
and wild mushrooms, are delicious.
Of course, you can also cook them
in a pig bladder.
... with a mixture of Madeira and brandy.
The bladder helps to protect the
quail, maintains it juicy.
You can serve it with a soft one
sauce of thyme, chives...
... carameled chalotas, truffles.
The truffles go perfectly with
almost any quail plate...
... because they stand out their delicate flavor.
Does it feel well?
Very well. It continues.
They increase marvelously
the delicate flavor of the quail.
But, you really have to have
the money to buy the truffles.
... but, better you forget them.
Now, as appetizer I suggest...
Kate, would care you...
if I change topic a moment?
- No.
- Why do you come every week?
My boss told me that me
he/she would discharge if he/she didn't go to therapy.
And why you believe that her
does he/she think that you need therapy?
Why?
Does he/she know what?
Not I have the smallest idea.
Two appetizers.
Leah, a quail and a
sole for nine o'clock.
I am still waiting those
fillets. Where are they? Clever!
Terrine, carpaccio.
Chef, Hal Reeves says that the one
lamb has never been better.
Seriously? And him what he/she knows?
Kate, Peterson arrived.
They love you how brilliant you are.
Thank them, but the chefs
brilliant they should be in the kitchen.
At least greet them. You know that
they belong to my best clients.
In one minute.
Don't cook them too much because...
- Yes, they become hard. I already know it.
- No, they dry off. They dry off, Leah.
I become hard. The quail dries off.
Kate, I want us to speak
of the menu of next week.
You are a maga, Kate.
And you know that my husband
he/she never stops to eulogize you.
In fact, it could become jealous.
I adore anyone that
it can surprise my palate.
It is always a pleasure
to cook for you.
- Will we see you next week, not?
- Of course.
- Good night.
It was a pleasure to see them.
I tell him/her that it is not well cooked.
- Can I ask what it happens?
- Kate, I take charge.
- You should be the chef.
- It is this way.
- Wonderful. I want to show him/her something.
- Ken, don't make that.
The foie gras was not cooked enough.
Pardon?
I will bring him/her a new one
appetizer, courtesy of the house.
My foie gras is
perfectly cooked.
Not he/she has to be embarrassed, pretty. To
all can fail them the foie gras.
This doesn't have anything of bad.
It is perfectly comme d faut.
- What does that mean?
- Comme il faut?
"As it should be." 60o in the oven,
26o, in the temperature of the water...
... 25 minutes, neither a lot neither a little,
with the rosy, pretty perfect tone.
Coarse.
We will leave to another part.
Vámonos.
Go to the position of hot dogs of
Vinnie, in the corner. He/she cooks to the order.
How many times have I told it to you?
Not you can make a scandal each
time that he doesn't like somebody your food.
Please. That type is a barbarian.
And a client that pays. If he says that
the foie gras is not well, it is not well.
The foie gras is cruel for the animals.
- Leah.
- Don't enter.
I swear that if you were not one of the best
chefs of the city, said goodbye to you today.
One of the best chefs?!
What does that mean?
Comely to that says
only to bother me.
He/she says it alone to bother me.
- Or not?
- What you say, chef.
Mailbox of messages, not
he/she has any message.
- How are you?
- I am well, Frank.
I have some pretty lobsters of Maine.
That is very small. Better this.
Do send them to me before 2:30 o'clock, do you want?
And it sends those squalid ones to Fontaine!
Kate! Who is your best friend?
- Did you get it?
- Didn't you request it to me?
Gilded Blanquillo?
Bob!
- Alone for you!
- They are beautiful.
Beautiful blanquillos
golden, fishes with line.
- Beautiful.
- Give me a kiss.
- Bob.
Why to my he/she didn't play me kiss?
Why didn't he/she play you kiss?
You didn't get him/her anything!
- And to this how you call it?
- Not I see any golden blanquillo!
Hello?
Hello, I am me! I am reporting myself.
We will arrive like at nine o'clock.
Fabulous, I will make sure
of being of return.
Well. What are you making?
Reading a recipe. no?
Christine, be not ridiculous.
I have other you interest.
Of course. One mentions.
How is Zoe?
Adorable. It has changed a lot
from the last time that you dressed her.
- Is certain affection not?
- I don't know.
What will they have dinner?
Don't worry about us. Us
we will eat a pizza or something like that.
Undoubtedly not. What him
does Zoe like these days?
He/she eats any thing. It is a vacuum cleaner.
Mom!
I will call you when it is close.
Say goodbye to your aunt Kate.
- Good-bye, aunt Kate!
Hello, Kate. You have just arrived?
No, I forgot something.
- How are you?
- Well.
Do you work tonight? I know a
Thai fabulous restaurant.
I will work. Alone a couple of hours.
My sister and my niece
they will come to visit one another.
I don't surrender easily. A day of these
I will convince you of go to have dinner with me.
Be, you should already know
that I don't usually make that.
- What thing? To have dinner?
- To leave to have dinner with somebody.
And to have breakfast?
You live in my building.
Not I go out with anybody that lives
in my building. It is a rule.
It seems that you have many rules.
Not you did say that you forgot something?
- Ah, thank you. Yes.
- Of anything.
What does he/she have of bad to have rules?
Not I am controladora neither anything of that.
Alone I prefer that the things
be made correctly.
For that reason finished
making everything myself.
He/she has idea of that complicated that
is it to coordinate 40 plates at the same time?
I hope he likes scallops.
Not we had been in that
would you no longer cook for my?
I don't make it for you,
alone I prove new ideas.
To who will I give it if not?
We will attempt something new this week.
I will make you wonder
and you will respond them.
Does he/she make how much your last relationship was?
Is that not a little personal?
Good, it is a therapy.
Does he/she make how much?
Not I know. Three years. Maybe four.
Who did finish it?
Me. It was becoming very demanding.
In what sense?
After two years he/she wanted
that we lived together.
Did it prove the sauce of saffron?
Pardon, what does he/she have of bad to live together?
It asked me him to leave my apartment.
Why will that make?
He/she would leave it, we would live in another side,
would he leave me then and then what?
My God.
How rich the sauce is.
Thank you.
Where is my lobster for 12 o'clock?
It lists, chef.
I am an actress and I don't make movies
with naked scenes of submission.
The world is full with degenerate.
The type of 10 o'clock is the worst. Each
week he/she brings to a different rosebud.
I swear you that if he/she looks my breasts
another time, he/she will be sorry.
Damned it is, Carlos!
Notice for where you walk.
Put attention all!
Two lobsters now
same. Wait for 9 o'clock.
- I regret it a lot.
- That it doesn't happen again, do you want?
They will stay without
lobster as soon as I leave.
Kate, we don't run out of anything,
we are well. Moisturize you.
You are already a real mom.
I have to practice
all that can, not?
- Thank you.
That somebody answers the telephone.
- He/she cooks.
If he/she is my sister, tell him/her that I said
at 9 o'clock. Not I can arrive before.
It is for you.
He/she takes the message.
Kate.
... I believe that you have to take it.
- Say.
- The one one is well.
She speaks.
Srta. Armstrong? I Am Dr.
Burton. We talk on the phone.
Zoe is well. He/she will recover.
Did they already tell it to him?
We think that it would be better than it
he/she made somebody of the family.
He/she knows how we can
to locate the father of Zoe?
It has never been...
I not even know their name.
Dr. Burton to emergencies, please.
How much I sit down it.
I have to leave, but I will return to give him/her
a glance later, of agreement?
Yes.
Hello, Zoe.
Where mom is it?
Did he/she die?
Yes, truth?
Yes.
He/she has a new message.
- Hello, I am me.
- And me!
We wanted to warn you
that we were made late.
Be a terrible traffic!
But, we will already arrive, Good-bye!
Not he/she has more messages.
This is a beautiful Dolcetto 2002.
Can they tell me from where he/she comes?
- Probably Piedmont.
- Of the south of Australia, Adelaide Hills.
If they don't find a substitution soon,
I will have this baby behind the stove.
I believe that it would be a violation
the health code.
Bernadette. Look at the color
of this wine. It is beautiful.
And it is clever for...
Tell me three words that
describe this he/she came. Three words.
Did you know that he/she would come?
Kate, what do you make?
- To what do you refer?
I thought that you would take
some free days.
- No.
- Are you sure?
Yes.
I want a duck, two red meats
and some lamb ribs.
I still wait the fillets.
Clever.
I want a quail and a
blanquillo for 9 o'clock. Let us go!
Move!
Terrine, carpaccio.
Carlos, I need more saucepans, soon.
- Five minutes for the lobster.
- We need it at once in 13 o'clock.
Another beefsteak, quick.
Two duck breasts, two
lamb ribs. Let us go people!
Why there is not food in the one
counter? Let us go, be many tables!
Dear Kate: The baby is beautiful.
I called it Zoe that means "life."
Now that it arrived, I realize the
enormity of what I am making.
I want you to know that if it happens to me something...
... I want him to stay
with you, nobody more.
I know that you will love my baby the same as me.
Listen to me...  it should be the
melancholy of the three days.
I love you, it mates. Christine.
Kate.
... I want you to take a free week.
Not it is a suggestion, it is an order.
How's it going, doc?
Hello, Zoe.
I prepared something rich.
Not I am hungry.
Good.
You will be able to leave on Friday. Did you know it?
Yes.
Zoe, you and I have to speak
about what will happen.
Can I return home?
I fear myself that not.
Why not?
You would be alone.
Your mom asked me him to take care of you.
So you will come to live
with me, of agreement?
The kitchen is there.
The room.
This is my room and the bathroom.
This will be your room.
He/she calls himself Nelly. I have it since
he/she was 3 years old. He/she has an entire family.
You should see my other animals.
Zoe, is clever the dinner!
Good!
Bon appetit.
Is all well?
What does he/she spend? Not you are hungry?
Can I return to my room?
Clear.
Zoe, I have to happen for
the restaurant some minutes.
Will you be well if I leave you alone a while?
Yes.
If you need me, alone it presses
the one one that is my cellular one...
... or two that is the restaurant. well?
It is to single two blocks, so if
you need I can come me at once.
Is it well?
Yes.
I don't take a long time.
Hello.
He/she says: He/she "looks at the stars that
they tremble with love and it thrills!"
Hello, chef.
My God! You are you!
I beg you you to give me the one
I secrete of your sauce of saffron.
Pardon?
Listen this, boys. Listen.
"To paint the stars,
all the stars."
You are my section of strings.
"In the morning I will wake up"
"This is our love"
Now all: "With our love"
It is well. Let us continue working!
Who is it believed that it is?
Nicholas Palmer.
And allow me to say that the world would be
a somber and depressing place...
... without your quail in sauce of truffles.
We have to speak.
- You could have asked me.
- I sit down it. Not I could wait more.
Nick was available.
I had to act quick.
That that less I need now
it is a moonstruck one in my kitchen.
Not it is a moonstruck one.
It is a little exuberant.
God knows that we need
something of that here.
Exuberant? Do you joke? The
type feels Pavarotti.
Good night. Do you have reservation?
- Yes, Matthews.
- Matthews. Yes.
Can I take their coats, please?
Allow me to take them to
their table. With permission.
At once their waiter comes.
When I took the position I insisted in
that I would decide with who I work.
Leah had been well
without me for a couple of days.
- Leah can already be standing hardly.
- It had been well!
Feeling pains while it cuts. Give him/her
the opportunity. He/she is an excellent cook.
Not I know anything about him. No
I have idea of what there is...
Give me credit. It was the one
sous-chef in II Treviso.
Italian?
You bring to a sous-chef of a restaurant
Italian and am I who needs therapy?!
We were lucky of getting it.
Peninsula offered him/her to be executive chef.
Why didn't it accept it?
Because he/she said that he/she wanted to work for you.
Zoe.
The amusing thing of going in those taxis
when you are in Manhattan...
... it is that for some reason not you
you scare although they go very quick.
You know that he/she goes managing quick and
unwisely. He/she is a professional.
He/she has a license of
taxi driver, I am seeing it there.
I not even know what is needed
to get taxi driver's license.
I believe that alone you need a face.
That seems to be the biggest requirement.
Nobody that doesn't have face can
to manage a taxi in this city.
Kate, awake.
Kate.
The school begins at nine o'clock.
It is 8:20 o'clock.
Oh, not.
Skies! Well, we go to
to get dressed. Ah, you are already dressed.
Well, give me one minute.
Do you need useful? Feathers or paper?
They usually have those things.
I prepared you the lunch yesterday.
I hope you like the duck.
Well, let us go! Vámonos.
Non encounter my scarf.
Don't worry.
You can arrive your late
first day of classes. Vámonos.
I need my scarf.
Zoe, uses a mine. Later
do we look for yours, yes?
We will look for your scarf.
Here it is.
Is this?
That!
Fabulous.
How simple.
Vámonos!
Ah! Your lunch.
Can you open up please?
Why didn't you open up?
Not I should open the door to strange.
Clear. Yes, that is very intelligent.
Hello, Be.
Will you have some coffee? I ran out of it.
Clear. We go a little
take, but...  one second.
Good morning. I am they are. I live below.
You should be the niece of Kate.
Zoe, not?
My children are as of your age.
They will stay with me the end
of week. Will you be here?
Here you have.
- Thank you.
- Of anything.
- It is of the good one.
- Yes.
Well, vámonos.
Thank you for the noodles
last night Thai.
- Not there is problem.
- You were very kind.
I suppose that now
do you have to enter, not?
Not I know.
Clear. We go.
You will be very well.
Srta. Armstrong? I am
Ellen Parker, the directress.
Kate.
- You should be Zoe. It is a pleasure.
- Hello.
I will take you to your living room and
we will know your teacher.
He/she has to have somebody
more appropriate for this.
Not I have idea of what to make with a girl,
especially one that lost their mother.
How do their brains work?
Non achievement that Zoe eats
anything of what I prepare.
What should I make, to force it?
Maybe strange their mother's kitchen.
My sister never cooked.
- It reheated.
- There the matter is.
Perhaps Zoe needs something more
family, less sophisticated.
What did you eat when you were girl?
Not it is the same thing.
To what do you refer?
My mother was a sensational cook.
Undoubtedly I was the
only that appreciated it.
And when your mother died, your
did father take charge of the kitchen?
No. He didn't take charge of anything.
We were lucky if him
we saw during the dinner.
Then, who you
did he/she take charge of you two?
Cannot we speak now of that?
Well.
How's it going fish sticks?
The children love they.
Fish sticks?
Yes, they come frozen and empanizados...
I know what you/they are the fish sticks.
But I cannot believe that she is
paying for these suggestions.
Fish sticks.
Did you learn something interesting?
No.
Something not interesting?
- How is your teacher?
- Bald patch.
Good, that is interesting.
Ta-give! Fish sticks.
The other day I was thinking
in the little thing that I know on you.
We are family and everything, but neither
though I know which your favorite color is.
Red.
Red? Do you see? Not he/she knew that.
I love the red one. The
red it is a fabulous color.
Which is your favorite number?
Not you have to make this. do you know?
To make what?
To make an effort so much.
I already go!
Hello, I am Charlotte.
Of the agency?
Does he/she wait another Charlotte?
No.
Then, can I enter or not?
Clear! Ahead.
Apologize a moment.
I told you that I don't need one
nanny. I am no longer a bebita.
What will I make? Not I can
to leave you here alone the whole time.
Why not? I am perfectly well.
Zoe, you put a barricade
in the door, do you remember?
I get paid from the moment
in that arrive, does he/she know?
Yes.
I see that you brought something to read Zoe.
It is for my thesis.
Mortal virus with mutations
quick. As the ébola and those things.
Well that have a good time in the work.
22 Bleecker, can I help him/her?
Table for five? Yes,
I can sit down them at nine o'clock.
I know it.
Yes.
How do you want to prepare the bass today?
Tell them that we will serve them
to very important people.
Don't you like the music?
It distracts the personnel.
Nick, you were right. The sex
with Pavarotti it is better!
What pleasure. With Bocelli also,
but alone for you tie of one night.
Soon. Eat. Paunch. Now.
Thank you.
Me, more the baby, similar to
big portions extra, please.
Bernadette...
Bernadette.
That is.
David. Victor. I believe that
they will be pure men.
I can with them.
Good luck.
John.
Chef.
No, thank you.
Delicious, chef.
Alone a true cook can
to truly judge a plate.
When one is hungry, everything knows well.
Never like in the afternoon.
My grandmother whispered me this recipe
to the hearing in their channel of death.
He/she brought it from the old world and today
I prepared it especially for you.
Contentment?
Very happy.
I believed that your grandmother lived in Miami.
Good...  you already know...
We all think that he/she would die.
It was as a miracle.
It was a miracle!
You make you position of these
plates and I will take charge of these.
We won't intervene this way in
the one on the way to the other one, of agreement?
Your half is more than mine.
Clear, clear.
I have more important things.
Meat, fish, rabbit.
It is hour gentlemen! We go.
15, two terrines, a
blanquillo, two lambs.
Seven, carpaccio.
- Did it season it well?
- Yes, chef.
It is well.
Well, how do I go? Where is my lamb?
Can I wonder something?
Do I have another alternative?
Where did you learn how to cook so well?
With my mother.
Your mother, seriously?
I thought that you had studied with
Alain Passard in L'Arpege or something like that.
I made it. But my mother was
better and I didn't hurtle plates.
Rays! I need more space.
- Why is it so angry with me?
- Not I am angry with you.
You are very angry.
Look, this it is my kitchen.
I have worked very hard for this
and I won't allow him to take off it.
And why you think that
do I want it to you to remove?
How another thing could want?
You treat me like to a dog, Larry.
Not I am a dog. I am a being
human! A human being, maldi...
I sit down it, it is that...  I have an audition.
Would you care it?
He/she looks, I don't need this work.
I can work where I want.
I like to work here because
it is a honor to cook with you...
... but I prefer to work in
a place where it is welcome.
So, if you want that I leave, tell it to me.
They can tell me what
is it happening here?
Good...
A moment, to where do you go?
I sit down it. Paula, you have
that to look for another person.
- Kate, what did you make?
- I didn't make anything.
Nick, please. We need you.
I have to hear it of her.
It is my restaurant.
It will be your restaurant, Paula,
but this it is their kitchen.
Without her...
... all this would be a heap of metals
hot and dirty plates, so...
She decides.
Kate.
It seems that he/she doesn't leave me another option.
Do you want me to stay?
Not I have just said it?
I didn't hear those words.
I want him to stay.
I would love it. I thought
that he/she would never request it to me.
You are burning.
I know that they are afraid, but
it is well, because I am here.
But if he/she really scares a lot them,
wake up and I will take them by the hand.
Especially you, Louie,
because you are the smallest.
Zoe?
Hello.
When did Charlotte leave?
Not I know. He/she makes a while.
It is very pleasant there below.
I have an idea.
What it would seem you to come with me
to the restoring morning in the night?
Good night.
Please.
I have attempted everything. Not it cares
that makes, he/she doesn't want to eat.
Why you don't try of
done to give him/her eat normal of boy?
Have you been speaking with my psychologist?
Well, two foie grass, a tartar,
two bisque and a goat cheese.
Smell it.
It is basílico.
Kate, your biggest admirers
they die to see you.
Leah, finishes the duck of the
5. I should take a rest.
Yes, clear.
I need a terrino, two bisque
and a prawn, please.
The twelve you is
disturbing. Does it lack a lot?
Subject this.
A duck, a bass and
a souflé, please.
He/she leaves a little for me.
You know, in old Rome, the boys...
... they chewed basil bad for the
I encourage before the graduation dance.
It is true.
Thank you.
Not there were dances of
graduation in old Rome.
Ah, not? Are you sure?
I thought that yes.
We see each other tomorrow.
Thank You, Leah.
To where do you go?
- Hello, Bob.
- Hello, Kate! How are you?
Well. What do you have?
I have fish blue cool air.
It arrived five minutes ago.
Here I have mussels babies.
What are there behind you?
- Colorado.
- Allow me to see them.
Incredibly fresh. He/she looks at this.
Good morning, we are to 24 grades
and this very sunny one this noon...
... this Tuesday, February 28.
Zoe.
Awake!
You will arrive late at the school.
Here your boots are. Let us go!
Tell them that it was my blame. of agreement?
Young ladies, today they had much
luck. I received a remittance.
He/she comes from all parts.
Modena, Montferrato, Bologna.
Smell it. It is black truffle of Parma.
Not it is bad.
Does he/she have white?
My best product. Very, very difficult
of finding in this time of the year.
Where did it get them?
He/she knows that I never reveal their origin.
- How much for the white ones?
-2.200 the pound.
- Oh, my God!
- It is that they come from Alba.
No, no, not. I believe that
I broke the source.
- What? You are joking.
- No, I am not joking.
- My God! Are you well?
- Not I know.
- Can he/she call to emergencies?
- No, no, not! The police not!
Not to the police. We need one
ambulance. He/she will have a baby!
My God! Stay relaxed.
We have a pregnant one
in Bleecker and Charles.
The 22 of Bleecker.
He broke the source.
-22 Bleecker, in the corner with Charles.
- Bernadette!
Well, thank you.
Respiera, this way.
Breathe.
Oh, not!
There to the left. You see those
do stagger? Give birth to here! Wait for me.
Oh, Zoe!
- How much I sit down it.
- You forgot my.
- Not it is what you think.
Leah had its baby, I had
that to take it to the hospital.
Same you forgot my.
Well, I forgot you.
And I sit down it a lot.
They Come, Zoe. We go home.
Zoe, we go, it is freezing.
Zoe! Move!
Zoe, I sit down it. I made a great error.
I know that I am making all bad.
But I am making what I can.
Why you don't think in what
can I make to compensate you?
As...  a desire?
Yes.
Yes, you request a desire
and I will make it reality.
And to change, you forgive me.
- Can I keep it it stops later?
- Clear.
Kate...
... you are not making it bad all.
They are expensive.
All they know it in the kitchen.
The carrots are another thing.
Here they have. How many are they?
- Kate?
- Yes?
- Not you will work tomorrow, truth?
- No.
And does Nick neither work tomorrow?
On Sundays we close.
Why?
And that why?
It is my desire.
It was idea of Zoe, not mine.
Why did I already know it?
He/she says that he/she prefers Italian.
- Your kitchen or mine?
- Not it would be simpler to make it here?
- It is well, we will use mine.
- Mine is completely equipped.
Perfect. At twelve o'clock?
I will make the purchases.
- Not you are cold?
- He/she was made late.
Men!
I open up.
- Do say?
- He/she helps.
There I go!
- Hello you!
- Do you need a hand?
No, I can.
Here. I take that.
Good afternoon, chef.
Delights! Where is the kitchen?
There. That. that. yes.
Well, sous-chef, put on your apron.
Do you have an iron pan?
Undoubtedly I have an iron pan.
Well.
No, no, not. Non touches my Tupperware.
Tonight, Zoe and I will prepare
the dinner. Single Zoe and me. Zoe.
- But I can help.
- It is my desire.
Tonight we will make pizza!
- The pizzas, for
favor, sous-chef. -Well.
Now the flour, the eggs
and do let us prepare the mass, yes?
Make it with the fingers. This way.
... and you can create your
own person and to buy them.
Well redondita.
Then, when you are
it lists, make this and this.
It is the first that they taught me.
Both hands. You should know how to make it.
Then you have to sing
in Italian. You will like it.
Then the ribbons this way.
He/she remembers that that you
I said. You can make it.
Kate! We are clever.
Without shoes.
Well.
He/she closes the eyes. They come with me.
Which is the secret?
You will already see it.
Not spy.
We already almost arrive.
He/she opens the eyes.
Surprise!
I suppose that we won't have dinner in the table.
Not we have one. We are of safari.
I already see.
You forgot plates.
Sit down. Not we need plates.
- Without plates?
- Without plates.
The dirty plates attract
to the big cats.
Undoubtedly we don't want big cats.
Allow me to guess who the pizza made.
Me! Me, me.
Seriously?
You were so close!
Anything didn't move.
But if I dry off the eye, there is not problem.
That is a vampire.
The lion...  "The King León!"
I should take it to the bed.
Allow me.
Thank you.
When did you go to the kitchen school?
When he/she was boy I sat down
in my grandmother's legs.
Ah, yes, in Miami. Certain.
In Pittsburg, in fact.
My father worked in steels.
But did you go to the kitchen school?
Are you joking? The
he/she cooks it is for small.
After the secondary, me
I went with a backpack to Italy.
I owe him/her my career to
a called girl Sophia.
She was my first love.
A bigger woman. 19.
Their father had a small one
trattoria in Tuscan.
He/she was a brilliant chef and
he/she taught me all that I know.
Sophia told him/her that alone we were friends
and he gave me a work in the kitchen.
I fell in love madly with the food.
Of the Italian food.
Of all the Italian one, in fact.
What did it pass with Sophia?
Their father found out
of everything and he/she said goodbye to me.
What pity.
They were opened a heap of doors.
The two following years I passed working
in the best restaurants in Milan.
And why to these heights
don't you have your own kitchen?
I don't know it.
I suppose that there am not me
arrived the ideal offer.
What you would make you if you
did they grant your desire?
I was already granted.
I prepared it this morning.
- I don't like desserts.
- Not you have proven my tiramisú.
Perhaps yes I like the desserts.
You know that in Italian, "tiramisú"
does it mean "food of gods?"
No, it is not certain.
Because it would should.
You have a little...  a
little of cream, here.
I have to leave.
You are supported in my scarf.
Ah, is certain. Yes.
Pardon.
Good night.
It is so...  impredecible.
- In what sense?
- In all the senses.
He/she never makes what should make
in the correct moment. It is...
Kate. The life is impredecible.
But not in my kitchen.
I am sure that
you will be able to prevent the worst thing.
The worst thing?
That it ends up tolerating you for some time.
What is this? A new form
of therapy? To insult the client?
Alone the best psychologists use it.
I will see you after the school,
yes? That you have a pretty day.
Hello, Kate.
We arrive on time.
Do you have one minute?
Clear.
I have been speaking
with the teacher of Zoe.
Frequently he/she stays
slept in the class.
And does he/she know which the explanation is?
He/she says that he/she works until very late.
He/she tells to their partners that
he/she works as kitchen assistant...
... in their restaurant for
to pay their room and their food.
I already see.
If I really believed that Zoe
he/she works at night in a restaurant...
... he/she would have to call to
Services of Infantile Protection.
- Not it will be necessary.
- I know it.
It is better for all when those
relatives take care well of the children.
He/she would hate to see that the state was taken to
Zoe after all that has passed him/her.
But I am sure that
you will fix this...
... and there won't be necessity
of arriving so far.
I will be observing Zoe and
we speak soon again.
Then the cellular telephone
of Sr. Daniels sounded...
... he answered and he/she was speaking
during the whole class. It was very amusing.
Zoe, we have to speak.
You can no longer come to work with me.
Why not?
Because I fear that not you
allow to stay with me.
- But to my I like to go to the restaurant.
- I know it.
I know that you like but it is not good that
a girl is awake until so late.
You don't want to have me there.
No, that is not true.
No, it is alone that you need
to sleep well in the nights.
Do you hear me?
Not you want them to take you.
What does it care?!
Anyway you don't love me!
Zoe.
Zoe!
Zoe, coarse! Coarse!
Leave me! Leave me!
Come unfastened! I want
to my mom, not to you!
Zoe?
Can I enter?
No.
Zoe, please. I sit down it.
Veto.
Hello, boys. Is their dad?
Yes. Dad!
- Hello.
- Hello, Be.
- How are you?
- Well.
- Can I request you a favor?
- Of course.
I know that it is of last minute but
I should leave and Zoe and I fight.
He/she wants to lower or you want
that it keeps on him/her an eye?
Alone see to see it from time to time.
Not there is problem. Play
inside, boys.
- Do you have a key?
- Yes, here I have it.
- Thank You, Be.
- And you how you are?
- Everything is very new for my.
- I know what can help you.
He/she Calls to Anna. It is a blessing with those
children. it saved me after the divorce.
I am sure that she will be able to take care
to Zoe every time that you need it.
Thank you.
Of anything.
Boys, if they will play for
Ireland will have to be strained well.
"Srta. Armstrong presents pieces
of truffles in an endivias salad...
... accompanying a wonderful and silky
halibut lightly cooked to the vapor.
All that emphasized with the glorious one
aria of their emulsion of saffron."
Not he/she can decide if you are
cook or composer.
"Their artistic and distinctive quail
with truffles he/she leaves very in clear...
... that now he/she has a great sous-chef
to supplement their singular style."
Does that say?
He/she wanted to know if you were
putting attention.
It seems that you need a swig.
I never drink in the work.
Tell me how other things never make.
To what do you refer?
Good...  you never eat dessert.
You never drink in the work.
I am wanting you to tell me that never
salts with types that you/they sing opera.
I go out never with types that you/they sing opera.
Well, I have one for you.
Which the three secrets are
of the French cuisine?
We go, everybody knows it.
Ah, yes? Which are they, know-it-all?
Butter, butter and butter.
You are good!
Not you had why this to make.
Not I am drunk neither anything of that.
Ah, Be. Hello!
Nick, he is they are, he/she lives below.
He is Nick. We cook together.
How's it going?
Obviously he/she doesn't live in the building.
How is Zoe?
Very sleeping. He/she is a fabulous girl.
- Good night.
- Thank You, Be.
Yes, it is so sweet.
He/she was only taking care Zoe.
He/she is a very sweet, very kind man.
Not he/she could have a better neighbor.
Yes, it is always so...
... good neighbor...
He/she takes an aspirin.
Yes.
Let us go!
It is hour of getting up, affection.
Not I want to go to the school.
Do you know what?
I don't want go to work.
Seriously?
Today will be one day for us two.
"To all in 22 Bleecker, allow me
to present to my small hors d'oeuvre."
Allow me to see the picture. Emma
Jilliam. Here they have.
"Three kilos and room"
It is adorable
"He/she desires to be able to know them to
all. Love and kisses, Leah"
Kate is retarded.
He/she requested me the free day.
A personal matter.
One, two, three, four,
five, six! Well, Park Place!
And with the hotel...
-  ...  1,500 dollars.
- Not I have enough.
It mortgages, baby. It mortgages.
Let us go! I adore this game!
Let us go!
Fantastic. Thank you! What do I need?
A nine. Give me a nine for
to have parking lot free.
Skies! Here we go.
That!
No!
Not it is exactly! No!
I am rich! I am rich! I am rich!
Do you know what that means, not?
- No, what does it mean?
- The war!
I will fight with you! Him
do you fear to a pillow?
How the rib eye goes,
boys? I need two basses.
Panceta, goat cheese, oysters,
beefsteak Tartar and rib eye to the grill.
How much does it miss the rib eye, Mario?
Let us go! Quicker!
He/she needed the suflé he/she makes five
minutes. Let us go, boys!
We had 110 covered this
night. Everything was excellent.
You really have dominated the menu, Nick.
You put your signature in the plates
and...  All the regular ones noticed it.
What it would seem you
to stay permanently?
I believe that I would like.
If Kate doesn't care it.
Who is?
Do you have idea of what time it is?
What?
It is very, very late.
Without you, the kitchen was a
place different tonight.
I am sure that him
you made very well without me.
It was a hell.
That is better.
Brandy...
... he/she came white...
... celery...
... but, chalotas...
... and I age.
I sit down the truffle.
Not there am...  I think that...
Not think.
Hour of the pancakes!
Hour of the pancakes.
Where is my sous-chef?
Pancakes?
Do you want to help me?
Now turn it.
Well. You can have your own one
restaurant. "Zoe" will call herself.
I will call it "Nick and Zoe."
Pardon? I squeezed the oranges.
Good. "Nick and kate and Zoe."
I like like it sounds that.
Not in front of Zoe.
Zoe, I will kiss your aunt.
What shame.
How will we work together now?
We will make what we always make.
You will tell me what to make and I will go to
your backs and I will make what I want.
I want to show you something. Quick! Vámonos.
Excuse. Does he/she have leaves of file kaffir?
- There. Yes he/she plays, he/she buys.
- I know it, I know it.
- For what reason do you need them?
- You will already see.
Here they are.
- One for you.
- He/she smells well.
Do you like it?
One for you.
Why do I know this scent?
It is your sauce of saffron.
It seems that we no longer have secrets.
He/she played...
I know it. I buy.
Purchases.
Two dollars.
Today, he/she eats special plate,
we have duck of the valley of Hudson...
... on a pumpkin puree and...
... served with cupcakes
of zapallo and sanguine...
... decorated with a sauce
of wild mushrooms...
- Of the...
-  ...  of the region of brandy in France.
- What do you find?
- What is that?
To Nick he/she was happened the idea of
to have mini desserts to take.
... in a box.
It is so obvious.
So obvious.
And Nick, I adore the wines that
you recommended for the new menu.
You will have to speak of that with Kate.
John, speaks to us of the one
plate of asparagus.
We are also serving
a special accompaniment...
... and an accompaniment
of watermelon slices.
Nick, the couple of the table
eight want to greet you.
They are fascinated with the bass.
Kate is responsible for all the food.
She doesn't care it.
It hates to leave the kitchen.
How interesting. How more
can you tell us of her?
Do you know what? Not I will begin with
this. I don't care who leaves.
But if you go, it tries of not
to stab anyone that complains.
Don't look me.
You. Me. There inside. Now.
- Which is the history?
- To what do you refer?
I give your back a couple of days and it is
"Nick, the wine, the clients, the boxes"...
She offered me your position.
What?
Why didn't you tell it to me?
- Not I can believe it!
- Not he/she wanted to get angry, he/she will tell it to you.
He/she knew that it could not trust you.
From the moment in that I met you,
I knew that it could not trust you.
The truth is that you cannot trust
in anybody. You have never made it.
Why he/she will make it
when this happens?
Why you don't have the gills
of having your own kitchen?
... instead of coming here
and to appropriate of mine?
- Is that what you think?
- That is exactly what I think.
You Know, Kate...
... allow well to enter
to somebody at some time.
Perhaps one day of these you realize.
You don't understand. This place is my life.
This is what I am.
No, it is not what you are.
It is alone a small part.
Anna, I am me.
Hello.
How was everything?
I believe that we pass it
well. We Play Monopoly.
Who did win?
Her.
Thank you. Anna.
We see each other tomorrow.
He/she has a new message.
Monday, 11:54 p. m.
Ah, and so that you know it, I didn't accept it.
Not more messages.
Kate.
Are you still awake?
Where is Nick?
He/she left to their house after the work.
Already fall asleep, it is late.
Kate?
You can sleep with Louise if you want.
Oh, affection, how sweet.
He needs you, I am well.
Good night.
Not you were entitled to make that
he/she left. This is my restaurant.
- That has made it to me to see clearly.
- It will be better than the quick remplaces.
Not you needed my help for the last.
- Kate.
- Well. I will look for somebody.
As a certificate or something like that?
Not I do have the papelito, does he/she understand me?
But there are types without
it licenses in the streets...
... and if they can
to drive...  you know.
My specialty is in
the area of the meat.
I fight with meat the whole time.
Sausage, beefsteak, pig.
I am famous for my ribs
of hoggish Vietnamese...
... with mashed potatoes and
saffron and asparagus with lemon.
I take myself well with people.
I am very good with people.
Ah, I am a...  I like people.
I always work in team
that all follow me to my.
I had a malentendido
with the main chef...
... and the manager and the owners.
"Discharged" it is something
as: You are discharged!".
But I believe that it was one
friendly separation.
Why does Nick no longer come to visit one another?
We had...  kind of a fight.
On what?
Adults' foolishness.
Why don't you love me?
- Not it is that he/she doesn't want it to you to say.
- Will he/she never return?
No, affection.
Zoe.
For Zoe, with love, mommy.
Zoe, are you awake?
I already finished.
Are you having breakfast?
Zoe?
Nick, I am me.
Is Zoe with you?
When I woke up he/she had left.
I am here now. They have not seen it.
I don't know it. I told him/her of it ours
last night and it became sad, but...
My God.
What does he/she say the police?
They will look for in the stations of trains
and of buses. It could be somewhere around.
He/she is a girl. He/she would choose
some place that knows, not?
He/she has gone to the school and
to the restaurant, it is everything.
Kate will be well. It will be well.
Go to see if
he/she didn't return to the house.
Zoe?
Perhaps he/she left a note in some side.
Not it is here.
Was their backpack taken?
If anything was not taken...
- It was not taken to Louie.
- What?
She would not leave the
does he/she marry without Louie, truth?
I failed him/her, Nick. I sit down
that I complicated everything.
We will find it. I promise it to you.
She needs their mother.
He/she simply needs their mother.
I believe that I already know where it could be.
There it is!
Thanks to God.
Zoe, are you well?
Zoe, please, don't make this again.
I was so afraid that
it had happened you something.
My affection, what does it happen?
I am afraid of forgetting her.
We will never forget it.
I promise it to you.
Never.
Never. And we will be able to come here
every time that you want, you find it?
Will you enter, truth Nick?
Today not, affection.
- Do they still continue angry?
- No.
We go.
You see ascending.
- You know...
- You Know, Kat...
Alone he/she loved you
how much I sit down it, Nick.
Don't apologize. In fact
I have to thank you the.
I have thought a lot of what you told me...
... about not having the gills
of following my dream and you are right.
It is for that reason...
... that I accepted a work.
In San Francisco.
Executive chef of a new restaurant.
Go, that is fantastic.
Yes. Not it could have him fact without you.
Executive chef.
That of the table 7 say that if he/she wanted it
burnt he/she would not have requested it raw.
- That is raw.
- It seems that not enough.
Rawwer and it would leave walking of here.
They are people of publicity.
They spend a lot of money here.
Not make fits
today. Alone he/she prepares another.
Well, it leaves a raw beefsteak.
It leaves a raw beefsteak.
Where is the lamb for six o'clock?
- How does the quail go?
- Well, chef.
Clever!
Terrine, carpaccio.
Of the idiot of seven o'clock another time.
He/she wants to know if at some time
you have seen a raw beefsteak.
Is the sufficiently raw thing?
Has madwoman become?
Yes. For that reason I go to therapy.
I sit down it. I will bring a new cloth.
No, please, he/she leaves
that I take me charge.
Not it was bad!
That made me feel very well.
He/she only wanted a beefsteak.
God willing there was a book
of recipes for the life.
You prescribe saying us
exactly what a to make.
I know it, I know it. He/she will say: "Of what another
does it form we can learn, Kate?"
No. Not he/she will say that.
Do you want guess again?
No, ahead.
What will say was: "You
you knew it better than anybody.
The best recipes are those
that yourself has created."
Subject this a moment.
I believe that you should know what
another thing has never made.
What thing?
I never enter to the apartment of
a man, I cover him/her the eyes...
... I give him/her to prove sauce of
saffron and I beg him/her him not to leave.
- Never faces that?
- Never.
What pity.
Will you burn it first, not?
Yes, chef.
Not forget to reduce
the sauce a little, hey?
- You are spending of the line.
- No, it is not true.
Yes, it is true. He/she looks, your
tablespoon is in my territory.
What it accuses I have that your reduction
a slight little bit be. I should say something.
Not I want to speak, but
your sambayón has clots.
You should be crazy.
- It is perfect.
- Allow me to judge to my.
You are right, it is perfect.
Pancakes.
Thank you.
Zoe, is already enough.
Hello.
To see...  what do we have here?
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org