Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
#Now it's always once upon a time
in New York City #
#It's a big old
bad old tough old town #
#It's true #
#But beginnings
are contagious there #
# They're always
settin'stages there #
turnin'pages there for you #
#Ain't it great the way
it all begins in New York City #
[ Boy ]
Let me have one. Please.
#Right away
you're makin'time #
#And makin'friends #
[ Meowing ]
- #No one cares
where you were yesterday #
- [ Giggles ]
#If they pick you out
you're on your way #
# To a once upon a time #
# That never ends #
#So, Oliver
don't be shy #
# Get out there
and go and try #
#Believin'that
you're the guy #
# They're dyin'to see #
# 'Cause a dream's no crime #
#Now once upon a time #
- [ People Chattering ]
- # Once upon a time in New York City #
#If it's always once upon a time
in New York City #
- [ Thunderclap ]
- # Why does nightfall find ya
feelin'so alone #
#How could anyone
stay Starry-eyed #
# When it's rainin'
cats and dogs outside #
#And the rain is saying
''now you're on your own''#
[ Meows ]
[ Whimpers ]
#So, Oliver
don't be scared #
# Though yesterday
no one cared #
# They're gettin'
your place prepared #
# Where you wanna be #
#Keep your dream alive #
#Dreamin'is still
how the strong survive #
# Once upon a time
in New York City #
[ Growling ]
[ Growling Continues, Barking ]
#Keep your dream alive #
#Dreamin'is still
how the strong survive #
- [ Thunderclap ]
- # Once upon a time in New York City #
#Keep your dream alive #
#Dreamin'is still
how the strong survive #
# Once upon a time
in New York City #
#And it's always
once upon a time #
#In New York City ##
- [ Man #1 ] Forty seconds.
- [ Man #2 ] All right. Here we go.
[ Truck Engine Starts ]
[ Car Horns Honking,
Sirens Wailing ]
[ People Chattering ]
##[ Rap ]
# You see the feet walkin'
down the street in the fast lane #
#Walkin' on the street
where they goin' #
#Just makin' a move
tryin' to survive #
# Find a way or not
to stay alive #
# Cool cat in a cruel world knows
good from bad his mind is in a swirl #
# Got to look out
and open your eyes #
# If you're in a jam
you got to realize #
- # You're in the fast lane #
- # Wait, wait, wait wait a minute #
- #In the fast lane #
- # Wait, wait, wait ##
- Hi. Sorry I'm late.
- That's all right.
Come on, sweetheart.
We're late.
You can play with the kitty
some other time, honey. Come on.
[ Tires Screeching, Horn Honking ]
- [ Man Humming ] Hey, 'scusa me.
- [ Meows ]
- Don't ya see I'm pushin'
somethin'here ? Thank you.
- [ Gasps ]
## [ Vendor Singing In Italian ]
## [ Continues Singing ]
[ Vendor ]
Hey, come on, folks! Step right up.
- Get your hot dogs.
- [ Sniffing ]
The best hot dogs in New Yo-ork.
##[ Singing ]
Hey, it's a beautiful day, eh ?
Come on, folks.
Step right up.
## [ Whistling ]
- [ Sniffing ]
- Hey. Go on.
Get outta here. Shoo !
Get outta here. Go on, kitty.
Get your sausages.
All right, let's go, folks.
Step right up. I got the hottest dogs
in the big apple!
Hmm.
Psst. Psst.
[ Kissing ]
Hiya.
- [ Gasps ] Hmph !
- Ooh.
- La-de-da.
- [ Vendor ] Hey! Hey, get off of me!
- What's the matter with you ?
I said get outta here.
- Well, well.
Looks like Louie's got a visitor.
Could be time for the Dodge to turn this
into a total ''cat-astrophe.''
Hey! Get off me!
Hey! Get outta here. Go on!
Shoo!
Ooh,you sure picked the wrong guy
to get hot dogs from, kid.
- Get away from me !
- Whoa ! Chill out, man.
I don't eat cats.
It's too much fur.
I've been watching you,
and I think you're in serious need
of some professional guidance.
Now what do ya say we team up
and change old Louie's mind
about sharing those hot dogs ?
I'm not goin'
back there again.
Hey. It'd be a snap, kid.
I'm an expert at these things.
All you gotta do
is learn some moves.
- Moves ?
- You know. Tempo.
Ooo-cha-ba. A rhythm. This city's
got a beat. You gotta hook into it.
And once you got the beat,
you can do anything.
- I can ?
- ''Absitively posolutely.''
The man you see before you
is affectionately known as ''Old Louie.''
A well-known enemy
of the four-legged world.
Our mission, cat, is to liberate those
all-beef kosher franks,
and hightail it outta here.
- Startin' to feel that rhythm ?
- Well, uh--
Yeah ! Yeah !
I do feel it !
When are we gonna get those hot dogs ?
Right... now.
[ Barking ]
[ Yelping ]
Hey ! Dog.
[ Gasps ]
Hey ! Get outta here ! Hey !
[ Giggling ]
Hey! Hey. Get outta there!
- [ Kitten Screeching ]
- [ Screaming ]
I'll get you!
[ Groans ]
Get outta here!
- [ Dodger Humming ]
- [ Gasps ]
Hey, you really got
that rhythm, kid.
Uh... yeah ?
We were good, huh ?
So when are we gonna eat ?
- We ?
- Yeah. I'm starvin'.
Listen, kid.
I hate to break it to ya,
- but the dynamic duo
is now the dynamic uno.
- What do ya mean ?
What I mean is, our partnership
is herewith dissolved.
But, wait !
Wait. You're not being fair !
Fairs are for tourists, kid. Consider it
a free lesson in street savoir faire...
from New York's
coolest quadruped.
Check ya later.
Hey, wait !
I helped you get those !
Half of those are mine!
Ya want 'em ? Come and get 'em.
[ Howls ]
-# Uh-huh #
- But I'm warnin' ya, kid.
# One minute
I'm in Central Park #
- # Then I'm down on Delancey Street #
- What the-- Hey !
#Say, from the Bowery
to St. Marks #
#There's a syncopated beat #
#Like I said
woo-hoo #
#Woo-hoo-oo #
# I'm street wise #
#I can improvise #
# Said ooo-hoo woo-hoo-oo #
#I'm street smart #
# I've got
New York City heart #
#Why should I worry #
#Why should I care #
#I may not have a dime #
# But I got street
savoir faire #
#Why should I worry #
#Why should I care #
#It's just be-bopulation #
#I got street
savoir faire #
# Mmm-hmm #
# The rhythm of the city #
#Boy, once you get it down #
# Then you can own
this town #
# You can wear the crown #
#Why should I worry #
#Tell me
why should I care #
# Say, I may not have a dime #
# Oh, but I got street
savoir faire #
# Why should I worry #
#Why should I care #
# It's just doo-wopulation #
#And I got street
savoir faire #
# Everything goes
everything fits #
#They love me at the Chelsea
they adore me at the Ritz #
# Why should I worry #
#Why should I care
yeah #
#And even when
I cross that line #
# I got street
savoir faire #
#Woo-hoo #
- # Said ooo-ooo woo-hoo-oo #
- Whoa !
- [ Dogs Barking ]
- #Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo-oo #
- [ Blubbering ]
- [ Screams ]
#Woo-ooo
woo-hoo-oo #
#Woo-hoo
woo-ooo-oo #
Come on. Where you goin' ?
No ! No !
#Woo-hoo
woo-hoo-oo #
- #Woo-hoo-woo-ooo-oo #
- [ Horns Honking ]
[ Howling ]
#Woo-hoo
woo-hoo-oo #
- [ Howling ]
- # Woo-hoo-wooo-hoo-oo #
#Woo-hoo
woo-hoo-oo ##
[ Cawing ]
##[ Salsa ]
##[ Continues ]
## [ Man Scatting ]
[ Snoring ]
Huh ?
Tito! Stop that racket!
I'm trying to watch this show.
There would have been time
for such a word.
- Oh, tomorrow, tomorrow
and tomorrow creeps...
- [ Mouthing Words ]
In this petty pace
from day to day and all...
- our yesterdays have lighted fools
the way to dusty death.
- Hey, Frankie, whatcha watchin' ?
- Hey, does he get the girl ?
I mean, what happens ?
- Shut up, you little rodent.
Hey, man, this stuff
is boring, man.
Come on, let's watch some boxing.
I wanna see some action.
[ Laughing ] Hey, Frankie.  Que paso ?
You're getting slow, man.
- [ Laughs ]
- My name is Francis.
Fran-cis.
Not Frank.
Not Frankie.
Francis.
No kidding, man ? Hey, so what did
you bring in today, ''Frahn-cees'' ?
It's none of your business,
you intrusive little pipsqueak.
Look what I got.
Oh, good show, Einstein. Now all we need
is the court and the net.
You think this place
is big enough ?
Hey, come on. What we need is
some good quality stuff, man.
- Check it out.
- Oh, shredded leather.
Shredded wha-- what you talkin'
about, man ? That's a primo wallet, man.
-Rubbish, you mean.
-All right, that does it, Frankie, man !
You insulted my pride !
That means death !
- [ Francis ]
Behold. The runt of the litter.
- Cut it out, you two.
- Frankie ! Frankie !
- Arf!
Fagin's not gonna be
too happy about this.
So, Francis, you got the food, right ?
- Well, no. I--
- Ooh, Frankie.
- Frankie.
It was your turn to get the food today.
- It's newspaper burritos again !
- [ Dodger ] Hey.
Whoa. Whoa.
Cool it, Dodger fans.
I'd like to introduce you to...
your dinner.
- Hot dogs a la Dodger.
- Hot dogs ! All right, Dodger man !
[ Francis ]
You remain our preeminent benefactor.
[ Einstein ]
Yeah. And you're okay too.
[ Female Dog ] So how'd you do it
this time, Dodgie baby?
Let me tell you, Rita. It was tough.
Only I could have done it.
Did you have to fight, man ?
Did you fight ? How many were there ?
Picture the city.
Eighth and Broadway.
The crowds hustling.
The traffic roaring.
The hot dogs are sizzling.
I love a story with food in it.
Enter Dodger;
one bad puppy.
Not just out for himself,
but community minded.
But he's not
the only one out there.
- Enter the opposition.
- [ Sighs ]
- A greedy, ugly, psychotic monster...
- [ Gulps ]
With razor-sharp claws,
dripping fangs,
and nine lives,
all of them hungry.
He comes at me, eyes burning.
I knew my time had come.
- Suddenly--
- [ Screeches ]
Gang war ! Gang war !
- Watch out ! Here comes a gang war !
- [ Francis ] Take cover!
- Help.
[ Grunting ]
Well, what is it ?
Hey, man, check it out.
[ Sniffing ]
Aye, it's a alien !
Cool it, guys.
It's just a cat.
- I mi madre, un gato!
- Feles domesticus!
Now, how'd you
find this place, cat ?
I-- I-- I followed
this dog.
- He's lying ! He's lying !
He's lying ! He's lying !
- Shut up, Tito !
- Why would a cat follow a dog ?
- Yeah ?
I-I just wanted some of the sausage
I helped him get.
He's a spy, man ! Come on,
let's eat him. You're dead meat, kitty.
I-I saw him come down.
Hey ! That's-- Hey, that's him !
O-Over there.
- Hmm ?
- Hey, kitty. What took you so long ?
- [ Rita ] Relax, kid.
- [ Dogs Laughing ]
Dodger, razor-sharp claws ?
- Dripping fangs ?
- I kind of like those burning eyes.
Hey, keep it down, guys.
The game's on.
Oh, boy, Dodger. Top dog has to get
help from a cat. [ Giggling ]
Hey, Tito, cool it, man.
- Come on. Let's see this big,
bad kitty fight in action.
- Hey, Tito, look !
[ Shouts ]
Oh, boy ! Dog pile !
- [ Grunting ]
- Oh, what a bunch of overgrown-- Oof!
- All right. That's it.
- [ Fighting Continues ]
[ Barking, Yelping ]
All right, all right,
knock it off! Enough!
What's the matter with you guys ?
Don't you understand ?
Sykes will be here any minute.
[ Whimpers ] And I don't have--
- No, no, no, no, no !
- [ Barking ]
[ Laughing ]
No, no. Stop it.
No. No.
No licking.
[ Chuckling ]
What a joke!
All right, settle down.
- [ Horn Honking ]
- Sykes !
All right, all right.
I'm coming.
[ Whimpering ]
I'll be right there.
You guys, listen.
Don't let me down.
What do you got ?
Let's see what you got ?
[ Gasps ] It's worthless !
What have you done ?
Oh, how are we ever going
to pay Sykes off with a--a pussycat ?
- [ Pounding ]
- [ Ferocious Growling ]
Oh. [ Nervous Chuckling ]
Look who's here, kids.
Company.
Nice doggies.
I was just on my way out.
[ Both Laughing ]
You guys... miss us ?
Mr. Sykes. I, uh--
[ Stammering ]
He's gonna kill me.
[ Chuckles ] Hello.
Oh, lovely evening.
I was just saying this
to your two lovely,
- purebred dobermans.
- The money, Fagin.
Actually, I've got something
much better than money.
Some luxury items that should make
a considerable dent in my debt to you.
Oh, my!
You waxed your car, didn't you ?
Did they use the buffer on it,
because I can see myself.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
I don't want
your garbage, Fagin !
Oh, please, Sykes.
Oh, please. Oh, please.
I don't think you grasp...
the severity
of the situation.
Oh, no !
Oh, no, I did grasp it.
This is how I grasp. Look.
[ Screams, Stammering ]
Accident.
Accident !
Ooh-hoo-hoo !
- Mr. Fagin !
- Sorry.
Now, I lent you money
and I don't see it.
Do you know what happens when
I don't see my money, Fagin ?
- [ Wheezing ]
- People get hurt.
- People like you get hurt.
- [ Gasps ]
- Do I make myself clear?
- [ Coughs ]
[ Squeaking ]
Clear ! Perfectly clear !
Ya know, Rita,
I can't figure out...
why you'd rather hang around
a dump like this...
when you could be living uptown
with a class act like myself.
Isn't it rather dangerous to use one's
entire vocabulary in a single sentence ?
[ Laughing ] Hey, Frankie,
get down, brother. You bad, man.
- Hey, you got something
to say to me, fat boy ?
- [ Stammering ]
Come on, you guys don't scare me.
I'll kill you both.
- Come on, let me at 'em ! [ Growling ]
- [ Doberman Chuckles ]
Go ahead. Let him go.
Why don't you pick
on someone your own size ?
- Like you, old man ?
- [ Dodger ] Hey, Roscoe.
Roscoe, is this us
losing our sense of humor ?
Nah. I ain't lost
my sense of humor.
[ Crash ]
See ? I find that funny.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, please.
[ Crying ]
Please.
Oh, please !
Three sunrises.
Three sunsets.
Three days, Fagin.
Three sunrises.
Three sunsets.
Three days. Three, three, three.
That's nine.
- Nine ?
- No, Fagin.
- Three.
- Three !
Oh, you mean,
just three days ?
Oh, my goodness !
[ Sobbing ]
Oh, I'm having a bad day !
- [ Horn Blaring ]
- [ Gasps ]
[ Water Splashing ]
Hey, hey, Roscoe.
Look what I found.
Forget it, DeSoto.
We gotta go.
I like cats.
I like to eat 'em.
[ Yelping, Growls ]
[ Both Growling ]
Get out of my way, Dodger.
That's enough, Roscoe.
- [ Horn Honking ]
- [ Rita ] Run along, Roscoe.
Your master's calling.
- [ Growling ]
- [ Honking ]
Come on, DeSoto.
We ain't finished, Dodger.
You guys are gonna pay for this,
starting with that cat.
Oh, yeah ? You guys don't scare me !
Come on and say it to my face !
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on !
Yeah, those creeps'll think twice
before hassling us, man. [ Chuckles ]
All right, kid.
What'd I tell you guys ?
Ol' Dodge can
really pick 'em, huh ?
[ Door Closing ]
Ooh, three days.
[ Whimpering ]
[ Sighs ]
How am I ever gonna come up
with all that money? [ Crying ]
What's the use ? I'll never get out
from under that maniac.
[ Sighs ]
My days are numbered...
and the number is three.
It's hopeless.
Thanks, guys.
[ Laughing ]
That reminds me.
I saw DeSoto's nose.
Who did that ?
You ? You.
[ Laughing ]
That took a lot of guts.
- [ Purring ]
- We've never had a cat
in the gang before.
We can use all the help
we can get.
[ Groaning ]
- [ Cracking Neck ]
- Ahhh. All right.
Time for bed.
We've got a big day tomorrow.
- [ Whining ]
- Aww, no.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, all right.
But just one chapter tonight.
Umm, let's see.
[ Muttering ]
Here we are. Here we are. Chapter seven.
[ Clears Throat ]
''Sparky stopped and he rolled
in a field of wildflowers.
''The dandelions tickled his nose...
- '''til he laughed out loud.
- [ Heavy Panting ]
''And then something caught his eye.
''It was Bumper the rabbit.
''Sparky jumped to his feet...
and ran toward Bumper
barking loudly. ''
[ Weakly ]
Woof. Woof.
Well, you try it sometime.
[ Clears Throat ]
Ruff! R-Ruff!
Well, that's because
you're a dog.
''Sparky knew that Bumper would run and
that he could chase him over the field.
But Sparky would never catch him
or hurt him because Sparky
was not that kind of a dog.''
[ Snoring ]
[ Purring ]
[ Horn Weakly Honking ]
This is the big one.
- We've got two days to do or die.
- [ Honking ]
Dodger, you keep an eye on the new kid.
Show him the ropes.
I don't wanna put any
undue pressure on you, but...
as you march off
to do your duty,
- I want you to keep one thing in mind.:
- [ Crash ]
Dead men do not buy dog food !
So, big smiles
and get out there...
and fetch !
[ Engine Starts ]
[ All Coughing ]
All right.
If Mr. Sykes don't see some cold,
hard cash soon, we are doberman chow.
Come on.
We'll start
on Columbus Avenue.
- What kind of work do we do anyway ?
- Investment banking, man.
[ Grunts ] Didn't you read about us
in the Wall StreetJournal?
- Really ?
- Yes. Captains of industry.
Gosh ! Can I be one too ?
Hey. When you got your pals,
you got all ya need.
- Okay, Dodge.
- We gotta clean you up, child,
and give you some on-the-job training.
# Ooo, yeah
Now listen up #
#You got a lot to learn #
- #And if you don't learn
you don't eat #
- [ Yelps ]
# But if you're tough
and always use your head #
#You'll be right at home
on the street #
# When you got talent
everything is free #
#Watch how we do things
ooo, I guarantee #
#You're gonna see how
the best survive #
#We make an art out
of staying alive #
#If you do
just as you're told #
#These are
streets of gold #
#Every boulevard is
a miracle mile #
-# You'll take the town and
you'll take it with style #
- [ Growling ]
- #If you play it brave and bold #
- [ Yelping ]
- # These are streets of gold ##
- [ Yapping ]
- [ Laughing ]
- [ All Grunting ]
- Hello ? What have we here ?
[ Tito ]
All right! A chauffeur shuffle!
- Listen up. Einstein, gimme
a fender bender at two lights.
- Yeah.
Tito. You're in charge of electronics.
Rita and I'll work the crowd. Fran-cis.
I know. My public awaits.
- Hey, but what about me? What do I do?
- You help Tito.
All right ! Come on, gato. Uncle Tito
will show you how it's done.
Ready ? Go !
Winston, listen to this.
''After a little sightseeing,
we left Paris by car...
for the con-- confer--''
- Conference,Jennifer.
- Oh, yes. Conference.
''...In Rome on Wednesday.
Jenny, I'm afraid your father
and I won't be able to make it--''
Is there anything wrong,Jenny?
Are your parents all right ?
- They're staying longer.
- Oh, don't worry.
I-I'm sure they'll be home
for your birthday.
No.
[ Sighs ]
- [ Horn Honking ]
- [ Banging ]
- What was that ?
- I, I don't know.
- But, but now, don't be alarmed.
- [ Horn Honks ]
- I'll be right back.
- Run, Sparky. Go find Bumper.
[ Clears Throat ]
[ Moaning ]
Why me ?
Today of all days.
Hey, check it out, man.
Beep, beep.
[ Chuckles ] Hey, forget Fagin, man.
Let's take this baby to Atlantic City.
What have I done ?
Poor thing.
- [ Woman ]
You oughta be ashamed of yourself!
- I'm sure he's just fine.
- Harming that poor--
- Probably just a little stunned.
- Run along, little fellow.
Go on, now. Shoo.
- [ Moaning ]
- Hey, Tito. What can I do ?
- Well, uh--
Why don't you be a lookout, man.
Yeah, that's it. Be a lookout.
Okay.
What is a lookout ?
Aye ! Look,just look
out the window.
Make sure it's
still daylight, okay ?
-[ Tito Grunting ]
-[ Window Sliding Down ]
Hey. Hey, Tito.
Tito, there's somethin' back there.
Hey, stop hasslin' me, man. I only got
one more wire, okay ? [ Grunting ]
- But-- B-But--
- [ Car Starts ]
[ Screaming ]
What's goin' on here ?
Let's get outta here !
Oh,you poor kitty.
Here. Let me help you.
[ Panting ]
Jenny... are you all right ?
- Where's the kid ?
- [ Coughing ]
He must still be in the car, man.
[ Rita ]
Oh, that poor little kid.
You were supposed
to keep an eye on him, Tito !
[ Coughing ] Yeah.
Well, it's hard to watch anything...
- when you're getting barbecued, man.
- What are we gonna do, Dodge ?
Tito, come with me. The rest of you we--
get back to Fagin.
Now, really,Jenny. We can't
just take in a stray off the street.
But look at the poor thing.
- Winston, he's half starved.
- [ Grunting ]
Ah. I know you're growing
attached to the little fellow,
but do try to understand.
- Your parents left me
responsible for you.
- They won't mind.
Really.
Don't worry, kitty.
I'll take care of you.
Georgette is not
going to like this.
Rise and shine, Georgette.
Your public awaits.
[ Yawning ]
[ Gasps ]
# Girl, we've got work to do #
# Pass me the paint #
#And glue #
# Perfect isn't easy #
# But... it's... me #
#When one knows
the world is watching #
# One does what one must #
# Some minor adjustments
darling #
# Not for my vanity
but for humanity #
# Each little step a pose #
#See how the breeding shows
Ooo #
# Sometimes it's too much
for even me #
# But when all the world
says yes #
#Then who am I to say no #
# Don't ask a mutt to strut
like a showgirl #
#No, girl
ya need a pro #
[ Twittering ]
# Not a flea or a flaw #
#Take a peek at that paw #
# La-de-da-da #
# Perfection becomes me
Ne c'est pas #
# Unrivaled
unruffled #
#I'm beauty unleashed
yeah #
#Jaws drop
hearts stop #
#So classic and classy
we're not talkin'Lassie #
#Aaa #
#Aaa
Ooo #
- # Ooo #
- [ Howling ]
[ Georgette Barking ]
# Though many covet
my bone and bowl #
# They're barkin'up
the wrong tree #
#You pretty pups
all over the city #
#I have your hearts
and you have my pity #
# Pretty is nice
but still it's just pretty #
# Perfect, my dears #
# Is me ##
Ooo !
[Jenny ]
Wait 'til you taste this.
It's a secret recipe
I just invented.
- [ Dishes Clattering, Bell Rings ]
- What on earth--
My goodness!
Jenny!
Don't you think a tin of kitty chow
would have sufficed?
Nonsense. He'll love this.
Now,young lady.
- I really think we should've
waited until your parents--
- [ Cracking ]
Eeew !
- [ Phone Ringing ]
- Oh, bother !
And for ze kitty,
the house speciality.
- [ Phone Ringing ]
- Oeufs a la Jenny avec Cocoa Krispies.
Mmm.
- Jenny, it's your parents!
- Yeah ! Wait 'til I tell 'em !
Oh, yes, sir. I do assure you
everything is absolutely hunky--
Georgette, I wouldn't go in there
if I were you.
- Uh, everything's fine here.
- They're gonna be so excited.
- Here she is now.
- [ Gasps ]
A cat!
What is the meaning
of this ? Bark, bark.
Winston !
Bark, bark, bark.
[ Seething ] I guess I'll have to
handle this myself.
- Hello.
I, um, hope you won't
think me rude,
but do you happen to know...
out of whose bowl
you're eating ?
- Yours ?
- Ooo.
Aren't you
a clever kitty ?
And do you have any idea
whose home this is ?
I... thought
it was Jenny's.
Well, it may be
Jenny's house,
but everything from the doorknobs down
is mine !
Oh, Georgette. I see you've met Oliver.
Isn't he cute ?
I've got great news.
Mom and Dad just said I could keep him.
I'm sure you two are gonna be
the best of friends.
[ Chuckling ]
[ Man On TV]
Now for $200--
- Where's the kid ?
- We tailed him all the way up the park.
- [ Panting ] We never had a chance.
- You should see this place.
There's gotta be,
maybe 200 people livin' there.
We can't let the kid
take the heat for us.
Yeah, man. If we don't get him,
they're gonna torture that kid.
- What in heaven's name
are we waiting for ?
- But what about Fagin ?
Alas, our beleaguered benefactor,
bearing the brunt
of our futile endeavors.
Gimme a break.
Speak English, Frankie.
Francis. Francis.
Francis !
All right, cool it !
Now we got work to do.
First, we'll spring the kid.
Then we'll take care of the old man.
All right ?
Yeah ! That's right, man !
He's family. He's blood.
- Here ! Here !
- Okay, troops.
Our mission begins at daybreak.
Einstein, go up to the door.
Francis, you're our--
[ Giggles ]
[ Winston ] Oh,Jennifer.
I don't hear any practicing!
All right, Winston.
I gotta practice now, kitty.
##[ Playing Scales ]
- ##[ Discordant Note ]
- Ooh,you wanna practice too.
#You and me together #
#Will be... forever #
#You'll see #
# We two can be good company #
#You and me #
- # Yes, together we two #
- Hmph !
#Together that's you #
# Forever with me #
#We'll always be
good company #
#You and me #
#Yes, together we'll be #
[ Birds Twittering ]
# You and me together #
#Will be... forever #
#You'll see #
#We'll always be
good company #
#You and me #
#Just wait and see ##
Good night, Oliver.
[ Horn Honks ]
Bye, Winston.
Good-bye, Oliver.
[ Girl ]
Hi,Jenny. Sit over here.
All right, listen up. We checked it out.
All we gotta do is--
[ Pounding ]
Oh, man!
He's dead meat now!
I'll handle that ruffian.
Body slam ! Body slam !
Oh, come on,you fool!
- [ Doorbell Rings ]
- Hit him ! Hit him ! Oh, bother.
Einy.
Get outta there!
Huh ?
Yes ? Who is it ?
[ Moaning ]
Oh, my.
- You !
- [ Barks ]
[ Grunts ]
I'll show you, you, you--
- Come back here!
- [ Door Closes ]
What--
[ Door Opens ]
Mira lo this place.
Check it out.
[ Gasps ]
Chagall. Matisse.
These are all masterpieces.
Huh, this place looks pretty nice.
I mean, how bad off could it be here ?
[ Sniffing ] Hey, man, if this is
torture, chain me to the wall.
- [ Dodger ] Tito!
- [ Door Rattling ]
We're here for the kid, remember ?
Now let's get him and go.
[ All Sniffing ]
''I love you, Oliver.
Play with Georgette.''
I'd like to play with him, all right !
The little fur ball !
Oooh.
[ Screams ]
Who are you ?
What do you want ? Winston !
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Calm down.
- [ Crash ]
[ Grunting ]
Oooh !
[ Pans Rattling ]
Don't come any closer !
I knew this would happen one day.
You're barkin' up the wrong tree.
It's not you I'm after.
It's not ?
It's not !
Well, why not ?
What's the problem, Spot ?
Not good enough for you ?
I mean, do you even know
who I am ?
Fifty-six blue ribbons.
Fourteen regional trophies
Six-time national champion !
Ooo, and we're all very impressed.
Right, guys ?
Very impressed.
[ Panting ]
- Oh !
- [ Kissing ]
Allow me to introduce myself. I am
Ignacio AlonzoJulio Frederico de Tito.
Get away from me,
you little bug-eyed creep !
- Winston!
- [ Sighs ]
- Excuse me, uh, sister. Who's Rex ?
- None of your business !
And you, tubby, off the bed!
- [ Sniffing ]
- Get away from there,you--
- [ Sneezes ]
- All right ! That does it !
You yo-yos clear out
and I mean now !
Winston !
Bark ! Bark !
Relax, champ. We'll leave
as soon as we get our cat.
If you think I'm intimidated by a bunch
of flea-bitten, dog-pound rejects--
Your cat ?
[ Giggles ]
How stupid of me. You must be
the friends he keeps talking about.
- Yes.
- [ Winston ] Georgette.
Something's not
quite right here.
Shh. Quick. Before he comes back.
Follow me.
Look at him, Dodger. Honey,
let's just forget the whole thing.
No, no, you can't do that !
You don't understand.
- The poor dear's so traumatized.
- [ Winston ] Georgette.
- Huh ? What ?
- [ Winston ] What is going on here ?
Now get going. Hurry.
Use the fire escape.
- [ Muffled Shouts ]
- [ Francis Grunting ]
Hey, there's no time for long good-byes,
but here's something
to remember me by, baby.
- [ Kissing ]
- [ Smacking ]
[ Tito Yelps, Groaning ]
Ooo, I think she likes me, man.
# Ooo, I could've danced all night
I could've danced all night ##
- [ Francis ] You were very good.
- [ Oliver ] What ?
- Nice job, Dodger.
- Hey, wait. What's goin' on, you guys ?
-Just the rescue of the century.
Shoulda seen Frankie handle that butler.
- Rescue ?
- [ Howling ]
- I was rather good, wasn't I ?
And how about Tito
and Miss Six-time National Champion ?
Hey, hey, but, wait.
I-I-I don't understand you guys.
- You okay, kid ?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, sure he is !
He's back with his Uncle Tito.
I was happy there.
Why did you guys take me away ?
We rescued you, kitty.
We, we brought you home.
But-- well, I, I have
another home now.
And someone who loves me.
What do you mean, kid ?
You're in the gang.
- But, but--
- The gang means family.
We risked a lot
to get you outta there.
Look, I'm sorry,
but all I ever wanted was--
What ? This place is not
good enough for you anymore ?
Don't wanna mix with the riffraff?
No, no. I like you. I mean, I like--
I like every one of you, but--
But there was a little girl.
I just wanna go back.
[ Sighs ]
We never should've took him, Dodger.
- But, Dodger, please--
-you wanna leave ? Fine !
There's the door.
- But he just got here.
- Go on. No one's stoppin'ya.
Hey, uh, Dodger, man,
uh, lighten up.
You lighten up !
If he doesn't like it, let him go.
[ Name Tag Rattling ]
[ Fagin ]
Oh, it's hopeless.
[ Fagin Moans ]
[ Yawns ]
[ Whimpering ]
- [ Rattling ]
- What's this ?
So that's where you've been !
Looks like you're doing
all right for yourself, Oliver.
Your owner probably spends
more money on catnip...
than we do on food in a month.
He's probably worried
sick about you.
All alone in that big house
with only his money to comfort him.
Only his millions
and millions of dollars to--
[ Giggling ]
That's it ! We're saved !
[ Laughing ]
Oh-ho-ho. What a plan !
Ah, yes !
Uh, paper ! Paper !
Whoo, it's so great. [ Laughing ]
[ Grunting ]
Dear Mister Rich--
Aah.
Mister Very Rich.
[ Chortling ]
- [ Children ] Bye,Jenny!
- Oliver !
Oliver ?
Oliver !
- Feel it. That's it. Very good.
- Oliver!
- Two, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Oh, you love it !
Oliver, I'm home.
That's funny.
Georgette,
help me find Oliver.
Oliver! Oliver!
Oh, where could he be ?
Oliver?
He's not here.
Where is he ?
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Hmm.
''Dear Mister Very Rich
Cat-owner Person.
## [ Humming ]
Whoops.
''And if you don't
bring the money,
you'll never see
your cat again.''
Oh, no.
Georgette,
something terrible has happened.
- They've kidnapped Oliver.
- [ Snickering ]
Oh, Georgette,
you loved him too.
- Don't worry.
We're going to get him back.
- [ Gasps ]
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
[ Fagin ] This is an airtight plan,
Sykes. Sweet and simple.
I ransom the kitty,
and you get paid in full tomorrow.
I'll even toss in a little extra
for your patience. [ Guffawing ]
Whaddya say ? It's my final offer.
Take it or leave it.
- [ Buzzing ]
- [ Sykes' Voice ] Yeah, who is it ?
- Oh--
- [ Camera Whirring ]
Fagin, it's you.
Why didn't you say so ?
[ Nervous Chuckling ]
Oh ! Good question.
But listen... if you're busy,
we can drop by some other time.
Don't be silly.
Just push the door.
[ Buzzing ]
[ Grunting ]
I said, push!
Ooh !
What do you mean ?
You start with the knuckles.
Ahh, Fagin. Do come in.
I'll be right with you.
- [ Door Squeaks ]
- Yeah. No,
you don't kill 'im yet.
Huh ? Yeah.
And then, what's-what's the last thing
you do ? You put on the cement shoes.
[ Chuckles ]
- Yeah. Yeah,yeah, that's right.
Come on. Hey, don't worry about it.
- [ Clinking ]
- [ Slams, Dings ]
- So, Fagin.
- Did we bring something green
and wrinkly to make me happy ?
- Sykes,
I've got an airtight k-kitty--
plan... plan !
It's sweet and simple--
the plan.
- Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
- Let's just take this from the top.
- [ Dogs Growling ]
- What--
What am I gonna do with you, Fagin ?
- I've got this kitty, you see--
- Fagin.
[ Stammering ]
- You don't got the money.
- [ Snaps ]
- Oh, no! Oh, no!
- [ Snarling ]
- Oh-- no, no, no !
Stop ! Please, sykes, please !
- [ Dogs Growling ]
Sykes, I'm getting your money tonight!
It's coming tonight!
Please. It's from a rich cat--
no, I mean, a cat from
a rich family's paying-- Ow !
They're coming tonight with the money
I owe you, uuh, to get the cat back !
- [ Snaps ]
- [ Whimpers ]
[ Sykes Grunts ]
Hey, I think there's hope
for you yet.
Oh-ho !
I'm proud of ya, Fagin.
Yeah, you're startin'
to think big.
You've got 1 2 hours.
- And, Fagin ?
- [ Lighter Clicking ]
This is your last chance.
[ Clicks ]
Turn left-- right when you get
to the big propeller.
Oh, Georgette,
I can't read this.
It says-- No, that--
No, that's not right. It's left.
- Oh, Georgette, where are we ?
- [ Wheezing ]
- [ Insect Buzzing ]
- I think we're lost.
- [ Yelping ]
- Stick close, Georgette.
It's creepy down here.
[ Foghorn Blowing ]
-He's late. I drew a perfectly good map.
-[ Watches Ticking ]
Well, there was
a few smudges on it, okay.
I went outside the line with
the green crayon... but not that much.
- Oh, Dodge.
- [ Fagin ] A child could read that map.
Hey, Rita,
they never laid a paw on me.
Ooh, wait. What if he comes
and he's huge and mean ?
- Excuse me, sir.
- [ Yelping ] It's the F.B.I. !
I didn't do it! I didn't do it!
I was framed!
Oh-ho-ho ! Whaa--
[ Groans ]
[ Wheezing ]
Listen, little girl,
this is a tough neighborhood.
- You'd better go home.
- [ Kissing Sounds ]
- Uuugh !
- I can't.
- I'm lost.
- Aw, gee.
Lost. Well.
I'd help you,
but I'm kind of busy right now.
What're you doin'
down here anyway ?
I came to find my kitty.
- Your kitty ?
- Somebody stole 'im.
But-but, uh,
are you sure ?
- Maybe you made a m-m-mistake.
- No.
- No, somebody stole him
and sent me this note.
- [ Dogs Growling Lowly ]
- [ Exhales ] Easy, boys.
- See ? Now I'm lost.
- Look. I even brought this
to get him back.
- [ Coins Clinking ]
Oh-ho-ho-ho-hoo !
You brought a piggy bank.
- That's all I have.
- That's awful.
I know. And what kind of a person
would steal a poor, little kitty ?
But I--
I mean, maybe he--
Maybe he was up against the wall;
at the end of his rope.
[ Sobbing ]
He must have been
a poor, desperate man.
It's still wrong !
I'm so scared.
I don't know what to do. [ Gasps ]
- I don't know what to do.
- Neither do I !
[ Clanking ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Frustrated Yelp ]
[ Groans ]
[ Quiet Gasps ]
- [ Meows ]
- [ Gasp ] Hey ! Guess what ?
I found a little, lost kitten.
[ Chuckling ]
I don't know; take a look.
Maybe he's yours.
- Oliver ! Oliver ! Oh, my Oliver !
- [ Car Engine Starts ]
[ Gasps ]
Sykes.
Sykes ! I was gonna--
Yaaah !
- Hey! Hey, wait!
What're you doing ?
- Let go ! [ Screams ]
- [ Fagin ] No! No, wait!
You can't do this!
- [ Dodger Barks ]
- Keep your mouth shut.
Consider our account closed.
- [ Choking ]
Stop ! Stop ! Time out !
- [ Fagin Shouting Indistinctly ]
- [ Dogs Barking ]
- Wha-- What happened ?
- You okay, kid ?
-Jenny-- He tookJenny !
- Don't worry. We'll get her back.
You--you will ?
Hey. ''Absitively,'' kid.
Come on, man, let's go !
Come on !
- Let's get 'im, man !
- All right... let's do it.
-[ All Barking ]
-Wait ! Come back ! Stay. Sit. Wa-wait !
- [ Engine Cranking, Sputtering ]
- Come back !
- [ Tito ] Oh, man. It don't look good.
- It's all locked up, Dodger.
All right.
There's gotta be some way in.
Yeah. Francis.
- [ Whimpering ]
- Now, don't cry, little girl.
They only eat when I tell them to.
[ Chuckles ]
- Francis, you all set ?
- Farewell, Dulcinea.
- [ All ] Francis !
- Peasants.
- Maestro ?
- [ Drumroll ]
- Ready, kid ?
- Yeah.
[ Dodger ]
Go!
Oof!
- [ Sykes ] Roscoe. DeSoto.
- [ Both Snarling ]
- [ Growling ]
- [ Gasp ]
[ Sniffing, Growling ]
[ Roscoe ]
Come on, DeSoto.
Hey, hey, hey!
There is a lady present.
Well, it's nice to see
that one of you has some manners.
After you,
my little croissant.
Good grief.
- [ Whispering ] And remember, quiet.
- [ Georgette Yelps ]
- [ Both Snarling ]
- Oh !
- I broke a nail.
- Oh, balderdash.
- What'd you call my woman, man ?
- [ Dodger ] Freeze!
[ Whirring ]
- Yo, Tito.
- Right. I'll check it out.
- [ Electrical Crackling ]
- Uuhrr !
[ Chuckling ]
Yeah. Oh, that's funny, Mr. Winston.
But I don't think you really
appreciate the situation.
Somebody could get hurt.
Why not just get the old man
on the phone and tell him
it's about his daughter...
Jenny ?
[ Dodger] Okay, listen up.
Tito, Francis, I want you--
[ Fades To Whisper]
[ Sniffs ]
You smell that ?
- [ Sniffs ]
Yeah. Heh-heh ! It's party time.
- [ Growls ]
- [ Knocking ]
- What the--
Didn't order any pizza.
[ Tito ]
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go !
Where are those dogs ?
- [ Meowing ]
- Oh, Oliver !
I thought I'd never
see you again.
- [ Tito, Francis Shouting ]
- [ Snarling, Chuckling ]
Ahem... gentlemen.
- What's the occasion ?
Come to rescue your little friend ?
- Say good-bye, Francis.
Oh, boys!
Whoopsy-daisy !
All right !
What a woman !
[ Dodger] Francis, you keep an eye
on the monitors. Rita, over here.
[ Grunting ]
What is this, a slumber party ?
Get goin', ya stupid mutts !
Francis, is the coast clear ?
Francis !
[ Francis ]
Goodness!
- [ Rita ] What're we gonna do, Dodge ?
-[ Dodger] Yo, Tito, hot-wire.
Hey, no way, Dodger, man.
I've been barbecued too many times, man.
- Good luck, Alonzo.
- Huh ?
I'll be waiting.
Hey !
# Heigh-ho, heigh-ho #
# It's off to work we go #
## [ Scatting ]
- [ HandleJiggling ]
- What is this ?
- [ Knocking ]
- All right, girlie. Open the door.
- [ Crackling ]
- Come on, now.
Girlie, I'm warnin'ya.
- [ Glass Crashing ]
- Come on, Tito.
[ Sykes ]
You just--back up. DeSoto. Come on!
[ Barking ]
- Come on.
- Yaaah !
- [ Tito Screaming ]
- [ Shouting, Barking ]
[ Chuckling ]
This has all been very entertaining.
But the party is over.
- [ Horn Honking ]
- Ow-oh-oh-ow !
Uuh ! Come on !
Come on, come on ! Let's go !
- [ Barking ]
- [ Sykes ] Fagin !
Heh-heh!
Hey, man,you're ugly!
And you're uglier than him !
And you're Ugly, Part 3 !
Hey,you're Revenge of the Ugly !
[ Laughing, Gasps ]
- [ Bark ]
- Aaah !
[ Fagin Muttering, Yelping ]
Ooh-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo !
[ Screaming ]
Whoo !
Yow ! Ooh-hoo-hoo-hoo !
[ Screeching, Grinding ]
[ Barking ]
[ Barking Continues ]
[ Screams ]
Yaagh !
Uuh !
[ Both Growling ]
- [ Yelping ]
- [ Crackling ]
[ Crackling ]
[ Yelping ]
Mr. Fagin !
Mr. Fagin, help me !
All right !
Check it out ! Heh !
[ Imitating Revving Engine ]
- [ Screaming ]
- Uuh !
- Help me ! Oh !
- Yaaah !
[ Train Horn Blowing ]
- Aah ! Save me ! Save me, Alonzo !
- [ Choking ]
Hey, get off my back, woman !
I'm driving !
- [Jenny ] Let go !
-Jenny,jump !
- [ Horn Blaring ]
- Alonzo !
[ Georgette ]
Aaah ! Ooo !
[Jenny ]
Oliver ?
[ Panting, Gasps ]
[ Soft Meow ]
Oliver ? Oliver !
Whew !
Whoo !
[ Horns Honking ]
- [ Dogs Barking ]
- [ Fagin, Winston Singing ]
#Happy birthday to you #
#Happy birthday, dearJenny #
- # Happy birthday to you #
- [ Howling ]
- #And many more ##
- Don't forget to make a wish,Jennifer.
[ Fagin Laughing ]
- [ Barking ]
- [Jenny ]
All right, anybody want some cake ?
Okay, Einstein.
But not the whole thing.
- ## [ Salsa On Boom Box ]
- You got it now, baby !
Yeah, left foot, right foot.
All right ! Check it out !
There you go. Relax, hey.
[ Chuckles ] Tito,
you dance divinely.
- He's cheating !
- Body slam !
- [ Ringing ]
- Come on, hit him again.
Murder him ! Twist his arm !
- [ Fagin ] Whoa!
- Foxworth residence.
[ Gasps ]
Mr. Foxworth !
- Body slam him now!
- Shh-shh-shh ! My goodness.
You're back tomorrow ?
Oh, she'll be so
surprised to see you.
Y-yes, good-bye, sir.
All right.
Get 'im ! Get 'im !
- Hit him ! Come on !
Murder him ! Get him !
- All right,you got 'im !
- Pick him up! Hold 'im there!
- Ta-da!
- I believe that's a ten spot,
- Now, where--
- old sport.
- Where is that check book ?
Oh, look at the time.
- Well, heh-heh, we better be goin'.
- Indeed.
Francis, Rita,
Tito, vamonos !
- The streets are calling!
- [ Winston ] Now,Jennifer,
have we forgotten anything ?
Oh, yeah. Thanks everyone.
The gifts were great.
Bye, Mr. Fagin, and thank you.
Oh, bye-bye,Jenny.
Come on, boys ! [ Chuckles ]
It's time for us to go.
Alonzo, darling, could I see you
for a moment... privately ?
Privately ?
[ Sniffs ] Ooo !
Coming, Alonzo ?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah !
You guys beat it.
Uh, my baby and I, uh, we gotta talk.
You know, you're not so bad
for a bug-eyed little creep.
- With a little grooming--
- Grooming ? Uh-- [ Nervous Chuckle ]
That's it !
We'll start with a bath.
Bath ?
- Let's go !
- [ Engine Backfires ]
- Bye-bye.
- Oh, Oliver, we shall meet again.
Hey, see ya 'round, kid.
Good-bye, you guys.
- [ Screeching ]
- Boys ! Let's go !
- [ Barking In Distance ]
- Listen, kid, ahh, you just
want to hang out or anything--
Aiee-hee ! Hey, Dodger, man !
Do you see her anywhere ?
- Hey, whoa !
- Man ! I can't keep this woman off me !
- Oh, man, I gotta get
away from that chick--
- [ Georgette ] Alonzo!
- #Alonzo-o-o ##
- [ Gasps ] Uh, good-bye, Oliver.
- Hey, you guys, wait for me, man !
- [ Horn Honking ]
- Hey, wait up!
- Alonzo Fredrico Tito,
you come back here this minute !
Hey, whoa, kid.
Do you think you can handle the champ ?
Sure.
Hey! You're okay...
for a cat.
We'll keep a spot open for ya
in the gang--
vice president,
uptown chapter.
Later, kid.
- #Why should I worry #
- Bye-bye ! Bye !
- # Tell me why should I care #
- What a delightful scoundrel.
# Say, I may not have a dime
Oh, but I got street savoir faire #
#Why should we worry #
#Why should we care #
#We may not have a dime #
# But we've got street
savoir faire #
# Why should we worry #
- [ Siren Wailing ]
- #Why should we care #
# It's just be-bopulation #
#We got street
savoir faire #
- # Uhh-uhh-uhh-umm #
- # Whoo-hoo-hoo #
#The rhythm of the city #
# Boy, once you get it down #
# Then you can own this town #
#You can wear the crown #
#Why should we worry #
#Why should we care #
# It's just doo-wopulation #
#We got street
savoir faire #
# Why should we worry #
# Why should we care #
#And even when
we cross that line #
# We got street
savoir faire #
##[ Soul Vocalizing ]
# Woo-ooo
Woo-hoo-oo #
Woo-hoo-oo ##
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org