Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
You're still a bloody
attractive woman.
You mean after you
take to me with your fists?
You make me sick.
Oh, hon, you still
on about the other week?
I told you,
I'm sorry.
And I told you when I get like that,
get out of my way.
But you have to get all lippy on me.
I got a temper on me,
but who hasn't?
You're priceless.
Well, at least
I try to make it up to you.
Get off me, Jake.
Oh, you're a hard lady.
Hey, where do you think you're going?
Sit down and keep a man company.
I've got things to think about.
Like what?
Since when were you interested?
Well, if you can't tell by the way
I just grabbed you...
...I must be losing my touch.
If you're not gonna take me
seriously, Jake...
Take it easy.
Talk to Jakey.
It's just...
It's just what?
Jeez,
you're pretty.
I want us to visit Boogie.
Is that all?
Go together,
as a family.
You know,
make a day of it...
...take up a nice picnic lunch.
Maybe we could rent
a car for the day.
Oh, yeah. Maybe we could fuckin' fly.
It's not impossible, Jake.
I've worked it out.
There's the money Auntie Matawai
sent me at Christmas.
If I put a bit aside each week
from the housekeeping...
...in a month,
maybe we could go.
Please, Jake?
And this whole day
means a lot to you, huh?
Yes.
Book the fuckin' limousine.
Horses, babe.
Honest.
Now, will you come here?
Tell Jakey you love him.
That's the trouble,
Jake. I do.
- What's going on?
- It's Heke, sir.
He's got your taiaha, sir.
If you want to smash things, boy,
you start with me!
You think you're man enough
to hold a taiaha, boy?
- I hate this fucking place!
- You're not supposed to like it!
Let me go,
you black bastard!
We are the same color, boy!
The British used to think
the bayonet was the most lethal...
...of all hand-to-hand
combat weapons...
...till they came across our warriors,
who fought with a taiaha.
You think your fist is your weapon?
When I have taught you...
...your mind will be.
You'll carry your taiaha inside you.
Come on.
Whoa, this is the life, eh, kids?
Don't even have to change gears.
Want to come and visit
your brother, son?
Nah. Got something else on.
Oh, come on, son...
as a family.
What? Too fucking busy
to visit your own brother, boy?
Rather be with a pack of wankers.
He would have come, Jake,
if you would have waited.
He would have.
Visits don't start till after lunch.
We may as well take a drive, eh, kids?
- Yeah!
What's that place over there, Mum?
Taku Whenua Tuturu.
My piece of dirt.
That's where I was brought up, kids.
What's that big house over there, Mum?
That's the Wharenui.
It was a lot different
when I was a girl.
It was always impressive.
What's impressive?
Choice.
It was always choice.
And inside are
the most choicest carvings.
Go on, Mum.
Oh, and inside
are photos of the old people...
...and the Tukutuku panels.
You know, I used to help Nannie
and Auntie Matawai repair them.
Well, why don't we
ever go there, Mum?
One day we'll all end up there.
See over there to the right?
That's the Urupa...
...the family cemetery.
All my family are buried there.
I'd love to go and see them.
Not before me,
you don't.
Your father and I were going to
get hitched there.
Except we didn't.
I wasn't bloody good enough...
...not for their royal highness.
Tell them everything, why don't you?
Your mother was beautiful...
...pride of the fucking tribe...
And this old black-ass comes along
and steals her away.
And you know where
I come from, kids?
A long line of slaves.
Fucking slaves.
I'd like to see those wankers
call Jake the Muss that now.
Ah, this place gives me the creeps.
Come on, kids.
Doesn't give me the creeps.
You never met my grandmother.
Eh, Jake?
Just want to show
our flash car to my mates.
Whoa, bro, you know what
the penalty is for car theft?
Just one beer, huh?
One, Jake.
Just the one.
Promise?
Cross my heart.
Cheer.
- Cheer.
- Ah, cheer.
Cheer, bro.
- Cheer.
How long is Dad gonna be?
I'd get that tone out of your voice
if I were you.
How many times have you seen
your father like today, Grace?
Never...
that's how many...
...so just give him a chance, eh?
Bethie!
Name your poison.
Oh, no, thanks,
Dooley.
Jake and I are going to
visit our son Boogie.
- Aren't we, Jake?
- Yeah, yeah. Just a minute.
I'm trying to listen to
the horse race here.
You promised, Jake.
Shut up, woman. You'll make me miss
who won the fuckin' race.
The kids are hungry.
Well, feed them.
You got bootloads of the stuff.
We'll be waiting.
Come on, come on.
Come up, come up.
So he's not coming?
Oh, he's coming,
all right.
You're hopeful.
No, Grace.
It's just a woman's lot, that's all.
One day you'll understand.
No, no, no,
no, no, no.
Stop, stop.
It's good, but it's
not good enough!
I've told you fellas time and again,
this haka won't work...
...until you get
the first action right!
You're reaching up
for all these ancestral lines...
...and you're pulling them
down into your body!
The weight of your ancestors.
Some of you look as though you're
reaching for butterflies or something.
Now, let's do it again...
...and wake up!
- Give me the keys, Jake.
- What?
I said, give me the keys.
What for?
I'm going to visit Boogie.
Bad idea.
The problem is you've spoiled the boy.
You've got to toughen him up.
- Give me the bloody keys!
- That's it, woman. Just fuck off!
Take a bloody taxi.
You got all my bloody money.
Fuck.
Come on, kids.
We'll walk around to the taxi stand.
Taxi? What for?
We're going home.
No. We're going to see Boogie.
You promised.
Please, Grace,
try to understand.
I don't want to listen
to any more of your lies.
I hate you!
I hate you both!
Come on, kids.
Boogie? Son?
We were on our way.
We rented a car for the trip.
We had a bit of an accident, son.
Oh, well, you know what your father's like
when he gets behind the wheel.
Had a picnic lunch all prepared.
Stayed up all last night.
I got in just what you like.
It was just a stupid accident.
Whoa. Party at
my place tonight, boys.
Fuck. I need to piss.
Thanks, mate.
We really needed to know that.
Bethie, you awake?
Come party with us.
No.
No more, Jake.
I could tell straightaway it was a holding.
What's more, it's my mate's holding.
Next thing I know,
I give him a smack.
Oh, if it isn't Gracie.
Hu wanted some water.
Come and give your uncle a kiss.
You're growing up fast, girl.
- Where is Mum?
- She's in bed, where you should be.
- What happened then, Jake?
- He comes back at me with this crowbar.
Yeah? And then what?
I take the crowbar off him
and give him another smack.
Good night, Hu.
Night-night.
It's OK, Gracie.
Uncle Bully is going
to be gentle with you...
...as gentle as a lamb.
Your mum and dad are going to be
real angry at you, turning me on like that...
...coming downstairs in nothing
but that flimsy little nightie.
It's our secret,
hey, Gracie?
You hear me, girl?
Keep your mouth shut.
Did Huata wet the bed again, Bub?
You should have left it.
I'd have done that.
Just go away.
Go away.
Look, I don't blame you, Grace.
I wanted to see Boogie as much as you.
You don't care about any of us.
That's not true.
I love you all.
But you're a liar!
Go on...
...got your period, Bub.
It's bound to make you
a bit uptight...
Get out! Get out!
What's for breakfast?
You want something to eat,
...fix it yourself.
Give me a coffee.
Go and have a wash, Jake.
Clean your ears out
while you're at it.
What the fuck's up with you?
I'm not going to take this anymore.
Do you hear me,
Jake Heke?
No more.
We never got to see Boogie.
I don't want any more
of these drunken parties...
...or your bloody ugly
mongrel mates coming around.
It's no good...
...no good for the kids...
...especially now Grace is growing.
Who the fuck do you think you are, eh?
Sitting there like
Lady Bloody Muck...
...telling me in my own house
who I can and can't have here.
Well, I've asked them back tonight,
and you'd better be ready for it.
Do you hear me?!
Now, get off your fat ass
and get busy.
Oh, Grace!
Leave that girl alone! You know, that's
your problem. You spoil the lot of them!
No wonder they're all
so fucking screwed up!
It's got nothing to do with you,
eh, Jake Heke?
You're such good father material!
You chased Nig off!
You couldn't give a damn
about Boogie!
You're not gonna
hurt my babies anymore...
...not while I can do
something about it.
Oh, you want something to eat?
Learn how to cook.
Grace!
What's up?
What?
I said, what's up?
How long have you been sitting there?
Why is everything so black, Toot?
Don't know.
Maybe 'cause we're all bloody Maoris.
You got something...
...you got something to sniff?
Yeah. A couple of old socks.
What's going on, G?
I thought you said
we were best friends.
If you're too bloody mean,
just forget it.
Hang on. Hang on.
No glue, OK? OK?
But I've got some dope.
You want some of that?
Yeah.
What's going on with you, Bub?
What colors are you seeing now, G?
Still all black?
Nah. Not an old black in sight.
Notice how you never see black
in a rainbow, do you?
Just bright colors.
Must be their pot.
You know, the pot at
the end of the thing.
Oh, dumb.
Pot... the end of the thing.
You're shit! You're just like
everyone else around here.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
You're just a stupid kid
that lives in an old wreck of a car.
G! G! Come back, G!
G, come back!
What did I do?
Please, G!
I'm sorry!
Please.
Shit. It's nearly on empty.
- I've got money.
- Forget the money. It's just no good.
We've been driving around for hours.
When was the last time
you phoned home?
Uh, about 9:00.
Jeez.
It's nearly 11:00.
Bring your ass in here, girl!
I said in here!
Move!
Your mother's been out all day,
half the fucking night!
Now, where the fuck you been?
Come on, bro,
she's home now.
Let the kid go to bed.
Come on, Jake.
Play the guitar, man.
Go on.
Piss off to bed.
Hey, come on, give
your Uncle Bully a kiss good night.
I don't want to.
What? I didn't hear you.
I said I don't want to.
- What, you got a hearing problem, girl?
- Hey, no. Leave it.
Daddy, no!
Daddy!
I told you about this thing, eh?
No fucking wonder you don't do
what you're fucking told!
Take it easy, Jake.
She's just a kid.
Go on.
Get out of here.
Bully,
play us a song.
Go on, dude.
Where is she?
Stop your panic, woman.
She's home.
She won't be taking off anymore.
Where is she, Jake?
She pissed off out the back.
What the fuck?
Some-- someone help me get her down!
Please! Please!
Come on, baby.
Come on, girl.
It's all right, baby.
Mummy's home.
Come on, Grace.
Oh, God.
We've got to do something.
My baby!
I'll get help.
No, Grace!
Don't cry, Mavis.
Doesn't do any good.
Auntie Matawai?
It's Beth.
Ka mata oku tamahine...
...last night.
I want to bring her home, Auntie.
Will you come and get us, please?
Thank you.
We're going to play spacies.
Come on, you two.
Oh, where's Gracie?
She's having a long sleep.
No, she's not.
Her bed's empty.
That's enough, Polly.
Come on.
What the fuck's going on here?
I want us to take Grace back home...
...to the Marae.
This is her fucking home.
No, it's not.
This was never her home...
...never.
And that fucking place is?
Fucking Maoris who think they're better
than the rest of us?
I hate them.
Bastards living in the fucking past.
It's our past, too, Jake.
What's that supposed to mean?
I want Grace to be with her people.
We should have gone back
a long time ago.
Fuck off!
You're not taking her anywhere.
I'm taking her, Jake,
with or without you.
I wasn't there
when Grace needed me.
This time I'm going to do
the right thing by her...
...and you're not going to stop me.
You fucking do, and I won't be here
when you get back.
Well, go on, then.
Go! Get the hell out of here!
I'm taking her.
I'll kill you first!
Well, go on. Do it.
You're still a slave, Jake...
...to your fists,
to the drink...
...to yourself.
Well, go on.
Kill the bloody lot of us!
Stay out of my fucking way...
...or I'll kill you.
You've come home, Grace.
We're home.
Oh, my baby.
Am I that much of a bastard, eh?
You're my mates.
You tell me.
It's not too late
if you want to go to the Tangi.
We'll drive you.
Fuck off.
I'm not going to give them
the satisfaction.
I was never fucking good enough...
...not for their Beth.
I'll knock her bloody head in.
Never mind, bro.
What's the key to her, man?
You think I was tough on the kid?
Nah. It wouldn't have been
just that, mate.
Bull, what do you think?
You think I was tough on her?
Fucked if I know, bro.
I'll try and tell you
a story, eh, Gracie?
The story about a young girl...
...growing up in this beautiful place.
She was given an honor.
She was made Puhi of the Marae.
The special one.
Well, you see,
the girl fell in love...
...as all young people do.
But you see,
the problem was...
...the old people
wouldn't agree to the fella.
The girl, being headstrong...
...went with him anyway.
Her father said she'd be back...
...that when everything
went to hell, she'd be back.
So the girl...
made a promise to herself...
...and said she wouldn't.
No matter what,
she wouldn't.
You see, Grace...
...I did know how to keep a promise.
I did.
I'm so sorry, Bub.
I'm so sorry.
I should have been there for you, sis.
You were always there for us.
Oh, son.
Hey, G.
Best friends...
forever.
Remember?
That's all I meant.
Honest.
But you were right.
I'm just a stupid kid
who lives in an old wreck of a car.
She loved you, man.
She loved you.
Have you ever seen so much piss?
That's because they love you, man.
Yeah.
Yeah. Why not?
I'm a lovable chap.
Jake the Muss.
Where the fuck are you?!
You bastard!
Fucking bastard.
Don't forget your hat,
eh, uncle?
Hey, uncle, did you
get all the ghosts?
I sure did.
Got the whole lot of them.
You come and stay.
Bring the kids with you.
We've got a lot of work
to do back home.
And here, too, auntie.
You sort out here first.
Be strong.
Good-bye, auntie.
You made me real proud today, son.
Me, too, eh, Mum?
I made you proud today.
You sure did, Bub.
Well, I suppose I'd better
be taking off, then.
Take off?
Where to?
I dunno. Probably back to my car.
I like it there.
Well, do you think
you could like it here, with us?
Because we like having you.
Don't we, kids?
Well, whatever you say, Mrs. H.
I mean, if you need me,
that'll be great.
I do need you.
Need you all.
Well, we'll say grace.
Grace!
Thank you for my family...
...thank you for the food.
Amen.
Good look, bro.
Would you like one, bro?
No, thanks, man.
I wear mine on the inside.
Don't you think you should take
the car back, son?
In the morning.
Your mates did you proud today.
There.
Mrs. H, could you read me
one of G's stories?
I can't.
That's why she reads to me.
I mean used to.
Yeah, the one about the Taniwha.
OK.
What's wrong, Mum?
Toot, put the kids in the car.
Thanks, bro.
Anyway, this fucking ape
comes over to me...
...takes off his shades,
and says the classic line.
The classic line!
Wait for it.
Waiting, waiting, waiting.
"What the fuck you staring at, man?"
So I say to him, cool-ass...
"Well, not you, mate.
Your spunky missis."
Trouble is, she was
fucking uglier than him.
Then all hell broke loose.
Old Jimmy, eh?
Hey, you can stay at
my place tonight, mate.
Yeah, fuck it.
Why not?
Beth!
Bully, give the lady a seat.
- You fucking animal.
- What the fuck?
Women and children, eh?
You fucking coward!
Please, control your missis there, mate.
Who the fuck do you think you are
coming in here mouthing off at my mates?
Get the fucking hell out of here
before I kick your bloody head in.
That's always your answer, eh, Jake?
Violence.
It's bad enough that you did it here...
...but you brought it home with you
and I damn well let you.
What the fuck are you on about now?
It was violence that killed my Grace.
She didn't have
an ounce of violence in her, Jake...
...but we made damn sure
it was all around her.
She killed herself!
You bloody bastard!
It was your bloody mate
who handed her the rope!
Hey, I don't have a clue
what you're on about.
- You fucking child--
- Shut up, Nig!
You animal.
You raped a 13-year-old girl...
...then sat here drinking with her father...
...while the rest of us buried her.
She's off her fucking head, man.
Sneaking around my house and laying
your dirty, filthy, fucking hands on my baby!
My Grace!
Hey, you're not
on the fucking Marae now...
...so don't come in here
accusing my mates of shit!
Hey, come on, man.
Look, no one's thinking straight.
We're family. Right?
Beth. Sit down.
Have a drink.
I won't drink with you fucking animals!
Read it.
Uncle Bully.
Uncle fucking Bully!
Let's go, son.
You dumb bastard, Bully!
Fuck you, Beth.
Where are you going?
I found something better, Jake...
...and I'm going to make damn sure
my kids have it all.
From now on...
...I make the decisions for my family.
Fuck off, then!
You'll get nothing from me.
You've got nothing I want.
Our people once were warriors...
...but not like you, Jake.
They were a people with mana, pride.
People with spirit.
If my spirit can survive
living with you for 18 years...
...then I can survive anything.
Maybe you taught me that.
Oh, you are fucked, lady!
Really fucked!
You think I need you
and your fucking spirit?
Fuck off! Go on, go!
I don't want you, ever!
I'll knock your fucking head off!
Fuck you! You'll be back.
Fuck this warrior shit.
You'll be back!
Fuck you, Beth!
Do you hear me, Beth?!
Fuck you!
Where are we going, Mum?
We're going home.
Oh, fuck all that fucking warrior shit!
You'll be back!
You'll fucking see.
You'll need me!
You'll fucking want me!
You'll be back.
Fuck you, Beth!
Beth, fuck you! Beth!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org