Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Turn to your right.
That's it, sir, you're done.
Please follow the orange line.
We processed the film
we found in your bag.
They're not very pretty pictures.
Also, you left the camera
in the hotel.
- We processed that roll as well.
- Can I see them?
That's not a courtesy, Mr. Parrish,
this is evidence.
Do you guys have your own lab,
or do you have to send it out?
We have a lab.
Your legal aide should be here
within 30 minutes or so.
You don't have to talk to me until
she gets here if you don't want to.
You know that, Sy?
Good.
- Sy, can I ask you one question?
- Sure.
What was it about William Yorkin
that upset you so?
I mean, what did he do
to provoke all of this?
Family photos depict smiling faces.
Births, weddings, holidays...
...children's birthday parties.
People take pictures
of the happy moments in their lives.
Someone looking through
our photo album...
...would conclude that we had led
a joyous, leisurely existence...
...free of tragedy.
No one ever takes a photograph
of something they want to forget.
We're gonna go.
- Sure you don't need my help?
- Yeah.
- Sorry, kiddo, I gotta work.
- Doesn't matter!
- I'll get takeout for dinner, okay?
- Okay.
- See you.
- Jake, are you coming, or what?
- I'm coming!
- There's one.
- Okay.
Can I look at toys?
For a minute. I'm just dropping off
some film. Make sure you can see me.
- Hey, Mrs. Yorkin.
- Hey, Yoshi, how are you?
- How have you been?
- We're doing good, thanks.
Got three rolls today.
- Can I get the address?
- It's...
326 Serrano Terrace, Yoshi.
I'll take care of Mrs. Yorkin.
What have we got today?
Two rolls, and I think I've got one
in here as well.
Can I have two prints of each, please?
Leica minilux.
That's a very nice camera.
Really? Will's trying
to get me to go digital...
Don't do that. I'd be out of a job.
- You have one shot left.
- That's okay.
- It's a shame to waste it.
- It's fine.
No, please, I look horrible.
- How's Jake doing?
- He's great.
He just had a birthday, and...
- How old is he, 9?
- That's right, he just turned 9.
Nine.
There we go. Got a winner.
Thanks.
- When do you need these by?
- Can I have them today?
We close at 7 on Sundays.
Well, it's not important.
I can swing by tomorrow.
You're one of our best customers.
I'll have them for you
by the time we close.
- Thank you so much.
- No problem.
- I'll do some shopping.
- See you in 40 minutes.
Thanks, Sy. Bye.
Bye.
Hey, Jake.
You sliced through an exposure
on that last roll.
Yes, Yoshi, I know. I made a mistake.
Mrs. Levitt has a problem,
offer her a free roll of film.
All right.
I've been doing P.O.S. mini-lab work
for over 20 years now.
I consider it an important job.
When houses are on fire...
...what's the first thing people save
after their pets and loved ones?
The family photos.
Some people think
this is a job for a clerk.
They actually believe that any idiot
attending a two-day seminar...
...can master the art of making
beautiful prints in less than an hour.
But of course, like most things...
...there's far more to it
than meets the eye.
I've seen the prints they fob off
on people at the Rexall or Fotek.
Milky, washed-out prints.
Too dark prints.
There's no sense of reverence for
the service they're providing people.
I process these photos
as if they were my own.
I see someone had
quite a birthday party.
I did them 5-by-7 for you.
I wanted them 4-by-6.
The larger ones are better.
I didn't charge you extra for them.
It's okay, I guess.
- How much do I owe you?
- 30.06. But let's call it an even 30.
All right, thanks.
- We have a gift for birthday boys.
- Really?
That's right. Birthday boys
get a free camera.
- Jake, what do you say?
- Thanks.
You're welcome, buddy.
We're taking Jake to Six Flags, so...
- I'll see you very soon.
- See you.
- Come on, Jake.
- See you, Jake.
- What a cool camera, huh?
- Yeah.
Good night, A.J.
That's just great.
Look, this is a great shot.
- Nice truck.
- I remember that.
- You guys are so cute.
- This is a funny picture.
That is so sweet.
This one's going into the trash.
Oh, my God.
Look at your face, that's classic.
- I need that back.
- You're not getting it back.
- I'm serious.
- Don't give her it.
She's serious. She's serious.
Told you.
How'd this one get in here?
- Oh, that's Sy.
- Sy?
- Sy the photo guy.
- Sy took it to finish off the roll.
Great. Now we have a picture
of Sy the photo guy.
All right, guys, it's so past
your bedtime, come on.
- Can I get you anything else?
- No, thanks, just the check's fine.
- What you got there, family photos?
- Yeah.
You mind if I take a look?
These are beautiful.
That's a good shot.
These your relations?
- Yes. That's my little nephew, Jake.
- He's a handsome boy.
Isn't he? Yeah, I got him
a camera for his birthday.
- You must be his favorite uncle, then.
- Oh, I don't know.
Sure I can't get you
no more coffee, then?
- Oh, no. I'm fine, thanks.
- Have a nice night, now.
You too.
Mom?
What, pookie?
I feel bad for someone.
Somebody at school?
No.
What do you mean, you feel bad?
When someone seems sad,
they don't have any friends...
...and people make fun of them,
that makes me feel bad for them.
Who is sad
and doesn't have any friends?
- Sy.
- Sy?
- The photo guy at the one-hour place?
- Yeah.
- Oh, Jake.
- I really feel bad for him.
But, Jake...
...we don't know that Sy is sad.
We really don't know that much
about him, you know.
I mean, he might even have
a lot of friends.
And he probably has a girlfriend
and a mommy and a daddy who love him.
I don't think he does.
That is so sweet of you to think of
somebody else like that, you know.
Listen, Jake...
...not everybody is
as lucky as we are.
You know?
But maybe if we send them
good thoughts...
...it'll make them feel better.
So why don't we close our eyes
and send Sy some good thoughts?
Okay? All right.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
There.
I bet next time we see Sy...
...he won't seem so sad.
Okay.
- You have to go to sleep, pookie.
- Okay.
I love you.
- Good night.
There you go. Come on.
How do you think we pay for all this?
I'm just asking you.
You think a money fairy slips an
envelope under my pillow every month?
- What are you even talking about?
- All of this stuff.
The new Mercedes,
the matching washer and dryer...
...the fucking Jil Sander blouse
you have on now. How?
I love you, Nin, I do.
But if you want our life to look
like something out of a magazine...
...l'm sorry, I've gotta work
to make that happen.
Do you even believe
what you're saying, huh?
This is not about things, Will.
And it's not about money.
You're neglectful.
- Do you understand that?
- What?
You're an emotionally
neglectful husband.
And you're an emotionally
neglectful father.
- Got it now?
- That's fucking great. Neglectful?
You're not here, Will.
You're not here.
You're never here.
I'm going to bed.
If in your mind...
Bart, what's wrong with you?
Oh, my God!
Someone's trying to kill me!
Oh, wait, it's for Bart.
Who'd wanna hurt me?
I'm this century's Dennis the Menace.
It's probably the person
you least suspect.
That's good, Dad.
Monday is our busiest day.
People shoot most
of their pictures on weekends.
The store has several
regular customers.
There's Mrs. Von Unwerth,
who only takes pictures of her cats.
I've never seen a picture
of a human being. Just cats.
Two copies, please, Mr. Parrish.
There's Mr. Siskind. Mr. Siskind
is an insurance claims adjuster.
He only brings in pictures
of wrecked cars.
The usual, Sy. I need these by 3.
We get all the new parents, which
makes up a big part of our business.
New parents go photo-crazy.
I don't know how many rolls
I have here.
Cindy, a nurse from a nearby
cosmetic-surgery clinic, is a regular.
- We do all the before and after shots.
- Thanks, Sy.
Then there's the amateur porn artists.
We have to report kiddie porn
and animal cruelty.
But anything else,
no questions asked.
- How many prints do you need of these?
- Just one set is fine.
- Sy, are you kidding me?
- What?
I've got three of these
fucking machines down today.
I've gotta be in Heber Springs by 3.
Larry, all I'm asking you to do
is look at these prints.
Plus.3? Sy, are you
fucking kidding me?
Point three? Nobody cares
until the shift's in double digits.
It's blue, Larry.
Well, I'll bet Brandt cares
about a plus.3.
Are you fucking threatening me?
You're breaking my balls
over a plus-three blue shift?
Fucking asshole.
Next time you call me out here,
that thing better be belching fire.
That's a great attitude, Larry.
Thanks for your precision work!
- What the hell you doing?
- Excuse me?
What was the deal
with you and the Agfa guy?
I'm preserving a level of quality
for my customers.
Your customers.
He thinks that a plus.3 shift
to cyan is insignificant. It's massive.
Sy, let me try and explain something
to you one more time.
You need to look again
at your place on the food chain.
These aren't your customers,
they're Sav-Mart's.
If you haven't noticed,
this isn't Neiman Marcus.
People come here with their kids
for a good time...
...and to save
on paper towels and socks.
If they wanted to see yelling,
they'd stay at home.
It was wrong to create a scene in front
of customers. It won't happen again.
Sy, don't you have
some vacation time saved up?
I guess I probably do.
You should take some time off,
go down to a Club Med.
You know, relax, lay in the sun.
Enjoy life.
I'll think about that, Bill.
Your lunch break ended a half-hour ago.
What the hell you been doing in here?
I'm trying to figure out
if this will work with my Mac.
I'm sorry. This isn't my section.
You're Will Yorkin.
Sy Parrish. I'm the photo tech here.
I do all your family's pictures.
Oh, right. Sy the photo guy.
Right.
Here you are in the flesh. It's just
I don't see you in here too often.
Nina usually does most of the shopping.
Can you help me with this?
This is computers. I do photo finishing.
It's not my section.
I'm in a rush and I had one question
I needed answered.
- No problem. I'll get someone.
- Thanks.
Customer needs immediate assistance,
aisle 4. Customer assistance, aisle 4.
- Someone will be here soon.
- Great.
You got it.
So is the rest of the family here?
Jake's around here somewhere.
You're a very lucky man, Mr. Yorkin.
I'm sorry?
You have a wonderful family.
And if you don't mind my saying so,
a very beautiful house too.
Well, thank you, Sy.
I appreciate that.
I really need to get this stuff
and get the hell out of here.
I understand.
- Thanks for all your help.
- Oh, it's okay.
- You say hello for me.
- I will do.
I gotta get back.
There'll be someone here in...
There you go.
Great. It doesn't say
if this will work for a Mac.
No. This is PC only. We have
some Mac-based stuff down here.
I was just talking to your dad.
- What do you have there?
- Evangelion.
Neon Genesis Evangelion.
What does he do?
He's a good guy, he can fly and he has
a silver sword that can kill bad guys.
- Really?
- Yeah. And he's 60 feet tall.
- You really want this, don't you?
- Yeah.
- No more toys, we're leaving.
- Gotta go.
- I'll put this back for you.
- Thanks.
- See you.
- See you later.
I told you not to talk to strangers.
I'm sure my customers
never think about it...
...but these snapshots are their little
stands against the flow of time.
The shutter is clicked...
...the flash goes off...
...and they've stopped time...
...if just for the blink of an eye.
And if these pictures have anything
to say to future generations...
...it's this:
"I was here.
I existed.
I was young. I was happy...
...and someone cared enough
about me in this world...
...to take my picture. "
How much for this one?
Most people don't take snapshots
of the little things:
The used Band-Aid...
...the guy at the gas station...
...the wasp on the Jell-O.
But these are the things that make up
the true picture of our lives.
People don't take pictures
of these things.
You really have to tidy up
your room, pal.
I'll bet your mother's told you
a thousand times.
Hey, Chaz.
It's a good game.
- Hi, Sy.
- You said you were going out today.
Uncle Sy.
Can you help me put this together?
- How many prints would you like?
- Just one set.
Maya, that's a very beautiful name.
Thank you.
- Have you picked up prints here before?
- Maybe once, a long time ago.
Your face looks very familiar.
You work around here?
Sort of near here.
- I've probably seen you at the mall.
- I'm in here pretty often.
We're backed up today. Is 6:00 okay?
I won't be able to pick them up
till tomorrow or the next day.
- See you then.
- Thanks.
Come on! A little hustle.
Here we go. Right there.
Come on.
Good shot. That's the way
to strike the ball.
Get in front of those, son.
Jake, visualize where you want
the ball to go and drill it.
Good one, Jake.
Jake, that's not good enough.
We have to work on that.
Pay attention, fellas. A little focus.
Drill it in there, Matt, come on!
Good shot.
Next practice, Thursday.
If you can't make it, tell Derrick.
- Hey, Jake.
- Tobey, you forgot your sweatshirt.
On my way home, I saw you out there.
I thought I'd check it out.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Is your mom picking you up?
No, I got my bike.
It's a great shot you made.
Your coach was a little rough.
He should be more supportive.
- Want me to have a word with him?
- That's okay.
- I will.
- No, thanks.
When I was your age,
I wasn't very good at sports.
I was kind of a chubby kid.
Let's face it. I was fat.
I was sick all the time.
Kept coming down
with mono and hepatitis.
Then I broke my collarbone
and had a weird cast...
...that kept my arm up
like this all winter.
I wasn't exactly the most popular kid.
- How'd you break your collarbone?
- I fell out of a tree.
- How's your dad doing?
- Good.
- Does he come to see the games?
- Yeah, sometimes.
- Does he come to any games?
- He's really busy at work.
- I don't know, he's busy all the time.
- Sounds like an important guy.
I guess. He owns a company
and everything.
Probably wants you and your mom
to have nice things...
...like that cool bike
and those soccer shoes.
Hold on.
Those things cost money.
He'd be here if he could.
I guess.
I got something for you.
Wanna guess what it is?
What's wrong? It's the one you wanted.
Mr. Parrish, I can't take this.
Sure you can, Jake.
My parents wouldn't let me.
I'd better be getting back home now.
- You sure?
- Yeah, thanks anyway, Mr. Parrish.
See you around the store.
- Hey, Jake. The name's Sy.
- Okay, Sy.
Well, there's been,
like, some kind of shift.
I don't know.
A couple of weeks?
Maybe five weeks.
Six.
No, I know that, but...
Yeah, but this feels different,
you know?
Listen, Jan, I can't talk right now.
I'll call you back this afternoon.
Okay. I know. I love you too.
Bye.
- Hi, Sy.
- Hi, there.
I was at the Dairy Queen.
I saw you and thought I'd say hello.
- I'm just grabbing some shopping fuel.
- I never see you away from the store.
You'd think we'd run into each other.
- Why, do you live around here?
- I live downtown.
- Well, that's quite a drive.
- No, I'm used to it.
- You have a nice boy there.
- Oh, Jake. Yeah.
A little sensitive, maybe, but...
He likes you, Sy.
- He calls you "Sy the photo guy."
- I've known him since he was this big.
That's right. You've been doing
our pictures for a long time.
You know, I almost feel
like "Uncle Sy."
Well, I've got some serious
shopping to do.
Oh, sure.
Take care.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
It's so weird. I'm reading
that exact book right now.
You're kidding.
No, I can't believe that
you'd be reading that book.
He writes a lot about noticing
coincidence, doesn't he?
Yeah, he does.
That thing he says about fear...
"The things we fear the most
have already happened to us."
I had no idea you were
such a deep thinker, Sy.
I wouldn't say that.
- Do you have any children, Sy?
- Me? No. No, I'm not married.
- No girlfriend?
- No.
I have a snapshot
of my mother, though.
- She looks very nice.
- She's passed away.
I'm sorry, Sy.
Gosh, you know, I have to go.
- It was really nice chatting with you.
- It was nice chatting with you.
I'll probably see you soon. We can't
go a day without taking a picture.
- Lucky for us.
- Okay.
- Bye, Sy.
- Bye.
Sy Parrish, please see the manager.
Sy to the manager's office
immediately, please.
- What's with the getup?
- It's Wednesday. I was doing the SRS.
There's been some discrepancies
in the click count.
That's Yoshi. His math skills are weak.
I told you that when you moved him.
The discrepancies are
on logs you initialed.
- They are?
- Yeah.
I guess sometimes at the end
of the week, you get a little tired...
We're not talking
a few innocent math errors.
The net-clicks all zero out.
They always zero out.
The problem is the shut-down clicks
don't correspond.
They don't come close to matching
the amount of prints we've sold.
Then it's probably
the reorder counter.
- Well, I asked Larry about that.
- What did he say?
He looked at the counter
and said that it checked out.
Also, in 1 4 years of servicing...
...he's never seen
a faulty counter on an Agfa.
Really?
The question is, where did all those
unaccounted-for prints go?
- What's the discrepancy, Bill?
- We're talking hundreds of prints, Sy.
That's not possible, Bill.
I've done the math.
The P.O. 's confirm it too.
- I don't know anything about it.
- Well, I think you do, Sy.
Well, I don't, Bill.
Look, Sy, I've got a family.
I'm not losing my job over this.
I'm letting you go.
No.
These discrepancies would be enough,
but you're spacing out...
...taking 90-minute breaks,
creating scenes...
...giving away free merchandise.
- What?
Free disposable cameras
to customers on their birthday?
Sure as shit isn't company policy.
- You can't do this.
- It's done.
I talked to Sims at district. Finish out
the week and clear out your locker.
If you do something
like fuck up the prints...
I haven't fucked up
a customer's prints in 1 1 years.
Just get back out there.
Hey, Sy.
Jake wanted to get
his birthday gift processed.
I'm sorry?
The camera?
Right. The birthday gift.
- Number of sets?
- Just one is fine.
4-by-6, 5-by-7?
The ones we usually get.
Standard.
Jake had a great time
with the camera, didn't you?
What was that address again?
It's 326 Serrano Terrace.
- Sy, are you all right?
- I'm fine.
I'll have these for you tomorrow.
All right. Thanks, Sy.
Bye.
I'm leaving early today, Yoshi.
Okay, Sy.
I won't be coming back, Yoshi.
Bill let me go.
You were fired?
- Really?
- Really.
I've really enjoyed working with you,
Yoshi.
Yeah, me too, Sy.
Sy, I just wanted to...
I guess I just wanted
to say thank you.
- For what?
- For teaching me all this stuff.
You're welcome, Yoshi.
- Don't let the place go downhill, okay?
- I won't, Sy.
- Here they are.
- My pictures. Let me see.
Come on.
What the hell's wrong
with these people?
The universe grows smaller every day.
There must be security for all,
or no one is secure.
It is no concern of ours
how you run your own planet.
But if you threaten
to extend your violence...
...this Earth of yours will be reduced
to a burned-out cinder.
Now, we do not pretend
to have achieved perfection.
But we do have a system, and it works.
Your choice is simple:
Join us and live in peace...
...or pursue your present course
and face obliteration.
We shall be waiting for your answer.
The decision rests with you.
According to
the Oxford English Dictionary...
...the word "snapshot"
was first used in 1 808...
...by an English sportsman
by the name of Sir Andrew Hawker.
He noted in his diary that almost
every bird he shot that day...
...was taken by snapshot...
...meaning a hurried shot,
taken without deliberate aim.
"Snapshot, " then, was
originally a hunting term.
Can I help you?
Just dropping off some film.
Just a customer.
- I can still shop here, can't I?
- No, you can't still shop here.
I believe I can.
There's no law that says
I can't shop here because I was fired.
- I checked.
- There's other places to do photos.
There's no reason to come here
other than to fuck with me.
There's a good reason.
I calibrated that machine personally.
It's the best mini-lab in the state.
All right, Sy. Just this one time.
But find another place to do your film.
I do not want you back in here.
Thanks, Bill.
What is it? You can't just leave
your station unmanned.
- You need to see these, sir.
- Is it the anal sex fiend again?
Motherfucker.
What was Mr. Parrish's demeanor
when he came in?
- Demeanor?
- Yeah.
How did he seem? Did he seem upset
or agitated in any way?
- I don't know, he seemed fine.
- Sy and I had words when he came in.
I was surprised to see him,
and asked him what he was doing here.
I suggested in strong language that
he bring his pictures somewhere else.
I need Xerox copies of this.
Can you show me
where I can get that done?
Mr. Owens, why don't you grab a seat
and try to calm down?
Your wife and child,
they're somewhere safe now?
They're at my mother's.
I'm sorry. I'm a little upset.
No, no, no, no. I understand.
It's understandable.
So how did he take his being fired?
I've fired a lot of people.
People get upset when they get fired.
He got pretty upset.
He knew Mr. Araki would show the
photos to you and that you'd call us.
I think it's just a warning.
- You have to take it seriously.
- We take it very seriously.
Your child's life was indirectly
threatened. We take no chances.
There's an APB on him.
Officers are en route to his home
with a search warrant.
I have officers
inside the store and out.
He may come back and pick up
his photos. He may not.
It's hard to say. I doubt he will.
Is that a good idea?
This place is wall-to-wall families.
If he's stupid enough to come back,
he'll never make it inside the store.
Mr. Parrish? This is the police.
If you're in the apartment,
we need to know right now.
Kill that TV.
Mr. Parrish!
It's clear.
- Officer Lyon. Double 6, 3-2-1.
- Go ahead, 3-2- 1.
I need to be patched through
to Van Der Zee in TMU. Right away.
3-2- 1, that's a 1 0-4.
Hey, Dan, take a look at this.
What do you got?
Y-O-R-K-l-N.
I'm sorry, sir. I don't find
that name registered.
Could you try a Maya Burson?
B-U-R-S-O-N.
Let me check that for you, sir.
- I'll ring that room for you now, sir.
- Thank you.
- Hello?
- Hello. This is room service.
Sorry to bother you,
but we have your order ready.
We need to know
if you'd like coffee with that.
Will, did you want coffee?
No, just the drinks.
And this is for room 21 7.
No, we're 5 1 1, right? We're 5 1 1.
51 1. Oh, my gosh. I must be looking
at the wrong thing here.
I'm sorry. We'll have it up
in just a minute.
Okay. Thanks.
- Hotel operator.
- Room service, please.
One moment, please.
Room service, this is Jon.
May I take your order?
Jon, this is Will Yorkin in 51 1.
We've decided to go out for lunch.
I'd like to cancel our order.
- No problem. That was 5 1 1?
- Right. Thank you very much.
You're welcome, Mr. Yorkin.
Yes?
- Nina Yorkin?
- Yes.
I'm Detective Van Der Zee
of the Threat Management Unit.
- This is Detective Outerbridge.
- Threat Management? Is Jake all right?
Everyone's fine. We actually need
to speak with your husband.
Will's at work. What's this about?
- You mind if we come in for a minute?
- No. Sure.
- How can I help you, sir?
- Hi.
I need a room.
But not too high a floor.
I'll check, sir.
Yes, we can offer you 31 3.
Anything on five?
I'll check, sir.
- Will Yorkin's office.
- It's Nina. I need to talk to Will.
He's not in. I'll have him
return when he gets back.
Duane, get him on the phone
immediately. This is an emergency.
I'll try him now.
I'll put you on hold.
No, Duane...
He's trying him right now.
- Where's your son?
- He's at his friend Eric's house.
It might be a good idea to have
Eric's mother drive him home.
Oh, my God.
- Mrs. Yorkin?
- Yes, Duane.
There was no answer, but I left him
a 91 1 page. He'll call you...
I know he's fucking Maya Burson.
I don't care about that now.
I just need you
to tell me where he is!
- I want a glass of water.
- Get it yourself.
Room service.
Can you just leave it
outside the door, please?
No, ma'am. I'm afraid
you have to sign for this.
Just a second.
You. Get on the bed.
Get on the goddamn bed!
- I've got plenty of cash in my pants...
- Shut up!
Close the drapes. Close them!
Good.
- Who said to do that?
- I closed the drapes.
Did I tell you to wrap
a towel around yourself?
Let me explain what's going on here.
I tell you to do things.
Then you do them
exactly like I tell you.
I'm gonna tell you this one time
and one time only. You got the picture?
- Do you understand me?
- Yes.
Good.
Now, get on the bed.
No!
Am I talking to a brick wall?
Did I tell you to touch her?
- No.
- I don't want you to touch her.
If you touch her again,
I stab you in the heart.
Proceed to Deerfield, the Edgerton
Hotel at Hunter Valley Road.
TMU officers en route to scene.
- Can you ring the room again?
- I'll try one more time.
Now, missy.
You have to take the robe off.
No.
I'm not asking, I'm telling.
Off!
She can do it!
The person in this room is not
available. Please leave a message...
What's this? What's this?!
Can't you stop your sniveling?
This is supposed to look like fun.
Okay.
No touching!
Smile. You have to look like you're
having fun, like it's a game.
Come on!
Smile!
Wipe your nose. You look disgusting.
Now. Put his thing in your mouth.
Don't do it!
- Pretend. This is all pretend!
- I'm doing it! Stop yelling at me!
You're not doing it the right way.
Like this!
No!
- Mr. Belmer?
- Yes.
Detectives Van Der Zee and Outerbridge.
We spoke earlier.
Right. So, what is all this about?
- Any word from Miss Burson yet?
- No.
Have you seen this man?
- He checked in about half an hour ago.
- What room?
I put him in 51 9.
I need a pass key. Now, please.
Mr. Parrish, this is the police.
Will you open the door?
The retinal implant
is a microelectronic prosthesis...
...that can reverse the effects
of retinal degeneration.
We owe a...
James.
Let's find Yorkin.
Check 51 1.
Bravo? Where is it? Where is it?
- It's the rear kitchen access.
- It's in the back, rear kitchen access.
Miss Burson?
Police! Freeze!
William Yorkin?
Drop the bag!
Do it!
Put your hands on top of your head.
Miss Burson?
- I just took pictures.
- You have the right to remain silent.
If you give up the right
to remain silent, anything you...
Outerbridge? We got him.
...the attorney present
during questioning.
If you so desire and cannot afford one,
an attorney will be appointed...
Dad!
Are you married, detective?
You have any children?
- I'll be the one asking the questions.
- I know. Just one question.
Are you a family man?
- That's none of your business.
- You're right. It isn't.
It is none of my business.
But I'm guessing by your answer and
that ring on your finger that you are.
And that makes you
a very fortunate man.
I can also tell by the way
you've treated me...
...and the way you do your job,
you're a good man.
A good husband and father, a man
who appreciates his good fortune.
You're not the type of father
who'd cheat on his wife...
...hurt his family,
betray their trust.
You would never neglect
and abuse your children.
Make horrible demands
of your children.
You would never ask...
You would never ask your children
to do things...
Things that children shouldn't do.
You would never take disgusting,
sick, degrading pictures...
...of your children
doing these things!
You would never treat
your children like animals.
Will Yorkin had it all,
and he threw it all away.
He is not a good father.
I think I understand now, Sy.
Thank you for answering
my questions so candidly.
You're welcome.
Can I see my pictures now?
Sure, Sy.
Thank you.
[ENGLISH]
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org