Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
ONE WEEK ...
... What if everything you arias
have is that one day,  ...
... or a week,
one month old
I fear that you have good news.
Detected in cancer cells ...
... your blood, liver and
lymph nodes.
We need to start the
treatment immediately ....
... that is so serious ...
... in this category four ....
... relation to the degree that there?
Four ......
... These are the first three
unfiltered thoughts  ...
... now the head of Ben ....
cancel the wedding ... ....
relief to be able ...
use this excuse  ...
... to get rid of the brand ...
... six of the testing
English classes ....
... How many people at his funeral .
The fourth  thought,
he called.  ...
Are you sure ...
he had made a mistake?
You know, I feel good.
Sure.
So, What are we talking about?
You have a way of
extremely aggressive cancer.
You need an aggressive treatment ....
... ¿Cuáles are my options?
Enter a scale of 1-10.
The survival rate
is about 10%.
Die?
When it comes to people
launched the odds.
In some cases, a
complete recovery is unprecedented.
And if the treatments do not
work, how long do I have?
A couple of years.
At least?
So, What is the minimum?
There ......
...- Are you good, son?
- Yes
Yes, I'm fine, thanks.
They are the bike?
Yes, but I am a few years ago.
Never had hoped to sell.
My ... eyes are rising.
I could not renew the license.
I do not think we have old bones.
I tell you, it's a snap
Dependence diapers ....
... ¿Quieres take a turn?
No, thanks. I
thinking of buying a bicycle.
If.
Certainly not ....
... We concluded that the
opportunity to buy a motorcycle  ...
... so soon after the hearing
Ben cataclysmic news,  ...
intervention can be ...
divine.  ...
... That would be a mistake ....
... In fact, Ben has moved
looking for a certain time ....
... But before proceeding,
a bit of the background story .
Gerald Benjamin Tyler was born on 14
January 1979 in Toronto, Canada.
The outside temperature was ...
... time to -9 degrees
Arctic centigrade ....
... 12 years have passed since the last ...
time sheets won ...
Stanley Cup.  ...
... So, What are the moments
more decisive in the life of Ben?
I now there is a gene.
Keep your eyes on the ball.
Tyler!
Perhaps, if you stop sticking your finger
nose every two minutes ...
... can can actually catch the ball.
Ben  never be caught ...
... to put the finger on
nose in public .
Nor  also
trapped in the world of the moon .
Both events seem  floor
of the hand .
O  finger in the nose, as well as .
The second seismic event  .
Ben's parents took him ...
... to believe that he had
voice of an angel ....
... But the dream died during the hearing ...
... the production of school
H.M.S. Pinafore.  ...
... He is an English ...
Enough! Enough!
Before leaving to make my ears bleed.
It was horrible!
Ben did not return
more singing in public ....
... However, comments
Ms. Bell derogatory  ...
means ...
as an act of revenge.
HOLIDAY IN GRAN RABO
The third  event.
Ben's first novel.
A poorly disguised autobiography
not find publishers ....
... He had created an orphan.  ...
How different could  ...
things have been for Ben  ...
... finger on the nose and in the world
the moon could have continued?  ...
... If I had believed in
praise when you hear?
And if he had decided
Against all hope  ...
submit your manuscript ...
HarperCollins to
For  had hired
Recently, a young editor  ...
... who took the lead
Bid Type ...
... literature that has produced Ben .
It is five minutes, Malta.
Ben  taught the same books
who had taught her.  ...
... What has been taught by his father .
And that probably  ...
... they have been taught
father of Shakespeare ....
... not ... to be totally untrue to suggest
... that education was not
Ben's passion ....
... Although rarely
still trying to give their best ....
'Despite the very
have been taken, much in the ...
'and although we are no longer
that strength which in old times ...
"moved heaven and earth,
what we are, we are ...
'a similar time to
heroic hearts, ...
'weakened by time and
fate, but strong ...
... to strive, to seek,
to find, and not to surrender. '
Marriage is  Ben
with Samantha Pierce .
The wedding was planned in three months.
This is yours?
I was beginning to think
he would never ask.
All of us, baby.
We all.
You did the right thing, son.
I am proud of you ....
... I know what they are thinking.
Ben was a career
and now would like a woman .
But before going
too far with this theory,  ...
... five things you should know
Ben loves Samantha .
His left hip.
Not that there are some
problem with the right,  ...
... but the left is
perfection.  ...
... The playlist .
Samantha has become a real
DJ soundtrack
Ben's life.  ...
...  parents ....
... Mary Jo and Tom were the most
nice that someone can tell .
Their ability  little value ...
to provide ...
quotes dark,  ...
... but at the same time
surprisingly important,  ...
... which has always a greater truth.
Samantha became a
golf fan ....
only knew ...
Ben liked sports .
The bride  acquired an interest
evidence, even in high Deferred  ...
Asian competition  ... ....
... If this is not love ...
What?
Despite  Samantha
not the demanding type,  ...
...  was firm about one thing .
hated motorcycles ....
... as  act, driving a motorcycle ...
... represents the peak
the stupidity ....
... ZY?
I understand.
I am not surprised.
The price is not negotiable.
Well.
Shit, me da-ta seven.
It is not necessary.
No, I insist ....
... ¿Dónde you think?
We still do not know.
After listening
news of his cancer,  ...
... the plan was to go to the home of Ben
Samantha and tell her prognosis  ...
... and possibly make
hope your love ....
...  Night ....
... First,
needed a coffee ....
... Why are there still
trace dreamer
Ben  the building where
edge to see if they had won.
A GO WEST, YOUNG
Ben decided to wait until after
the birthday party of his father  ...
... revealing the news to Samantha.
It would not be able
to hide the secret ....
...- I have a toast.
- Oh, my God.
You can simply send an e-mail?
Well, I just want to say ...
No.
I admit that, despite
my increasing decrepitude, ...
... never been happier ....
¿Tienes ... ...
somehow ......
... desenrascar life with a lot of luck.
And I have a toast to my family.
Thank you all.
Health
Health, Dad.
We will not cancel the wedding.
Not after all the work.
If you do not want to.
No! I'm not worried about marriage.
I. .. I'm worried
with the madness going on vacation.
The treatment adias,
worse are the possibilities.
Do not go on holiday ...
Once your foot in the hospital,
I am bombarded with drugs so powerful
I think the shards of glass ...
... below the neck
every time you swallow.
Before becoming a patient,
necessary to do so.
You have to do what,
exactly?
I have to have an adventure.
If it were me, join me
for all treatments in the world.
Drinking urine goat
I knew it was different.
I know, Sam,
but only for two days.
And once more,
in the treatment of 100%, I promise.
It is incomprehensible
wait for me to go ...
But it is not incomprehensible to me ....
...- I. .. just ... You only need ...
- What?
Come on.
I see only.
No, I too angry
with all the time ....
ZY ... your family?
I count my family when I return.
Ben insisted that the marriage
continue as planned.
MY LIFE?
Because Ben
have failed to answer your question,  ...
... the nurse can  Forrester
Work  ...
12 minutes ... more
earlier than usual ....
... an explosion of power walking,
he managed to take
train 17:45 ....
... are not  Gayle
ido so quickly,  ...
would have been one of ...
13 victims of the train 18:10  ...
derail even the ...
Etobicoke doors .
factóide Ben ....
... Without irony, he loved
tributes to the great world .
Part of the pleasure is
inventing stories around the  ...
about these ...
creations became reality.
And I say that our city
is necessary to put on the map.
Something with a factor of 'wow'.
Photomosaic of the largest world.
Ben recalled that he has read ...
... about a man in
Britain,  ...
John Brandrick  ... in fact, that
Was diagnosed with cancer
pancreas  ...
... and it was a year old ....
... He spent everything I had,  ...
... only to discover that
a misdiagnosis  ...
... and it would be cool.  ...
... What happens if Ben had received
a misdiagnosis?
Samantha was right .
swim was the famous river in Egypt .
He  go home .
Friends ....
¿Sabes if any ...
Canadian Tire store here?
No. Sorry, no idea.
We will lose the bet if
we have to go to the foot of Sudbury ....
What is so important ...
find a Canadian Tire here?
Our friend Gurvy
paid a case of beer ......
Each ...-.
- Each one, if we go ...
... from Newfoundland to Vancouver,
less than six weeks ...
... and spend less than $ 400, so ...
Each time we have a failure,
what happens more than you think ...
... simply the nearest store
a bike and replaced by another.
Come on, I do not think that way ...
... bike to the coast
West as a whole ....
... Why not?
You do not have the proper equipment.
Besides the damn wind front
there have been no problems so far.
Listen, I give you for a ride
the city to take a look?
Sorry, we can not accept rides or
lost the bet. The rule number 6.
We were completely drunk
which agree with that.
So long.
Good luck.
Win a donut
Compared to the pure insanity ...
bike cross ...
contravento country for ...
... a box of beer
Ben returned to the commitment
go west.
Looking for GRUMPS BY BEN TYLER
Our children called LOVE
When you read THIS BOOK
Hello ...
... Are you pregnant?
I mean,
You're pregnant?
Of course not ....
Why write a ...
note on our children ...
... Why throw in your heart .
I was praying
Ave Maria for a  ...
... the thought of his unborn child
you can come home sooner.
But definitely not Are you pregnant? ...
... N s
No, and even that was
did not believe in the code.
Looking for GRUMPS BY BEN TYLER ...
'What should we do ?'...
'We must continue to demand the Grumps'....
'So I tried all day ...
... but not for
any sign of Grumps'....
... Ben's father, an accountant
very convincing stories,  ...
totally convinced of the ...
son of the existence of Grumps .
A mythical creature as  evasion  ...
... to see even one,
that unprecedented luck ....
... In that moment of childhood ...
... that the ratio exceeded
Imagination  ...
... Ben and concluded that
Grumps was not in the world?
Ben had a desire
the overwhelming embrace of random  ...
... and restarted the search for Grumps .
What if you have any
objections to a marriage by the Church.
No. Definitely not.
And all you want
incorporated into the marriage?
No. ...
... Can I ask you a question, Ben ...
¿Tiene you ... a belief ...
How ... can not believe in anything?
We talked about children.
We had the financial discussion ....
How ... can not be
religious debate?
It can be as upset about this, ¿verdad?
I married my nihilistic.
Samantha  think, that of Ben ...
trying hard ...
to hear God.
JESUS SALVA
YOUR RECEIPT ...
... however, did not seem capable of ...
tunable frequency ...
divine right .
Hello
Listen  ...
When you say that no cree
who was married to a nihilistic ...
... were in the game?
No.
But that does not worry me ....
Dime ...  only comes home .
This is a commitment
very important, ZnO ...
... There is a minor .
Resigned to the fact that no
we see the faith with the same eyes ....
¿Dónde ... are you? ...
¿Hay something more ...
you think is committed?
Yes, this is in a relationship ....
Well ... .. what kind?
Only, you know, an example.  ...
... Why are we talking about this ...
¿Tiene his back ...
consultations on Monday .
Perhaps one of the things
who are committed ...
... is, in fact, one of
things I like most about me.
No hay muy importante, de verdad.
This is great. Then
maybe just a small example.
Well.
I do not want to smell your feet.
But ...
I am not smelly feet.
This is a ridiculous conversation.
Forget what I said.
It is ridiculous, because you said that
my feet do not stink when it smells.
Well, maybe
olfactory also a problem.
I never said that before
I knew that might react badly ....
... Why does not exist.
Believe me, that stink.
You can pay on it.
In fact, I ......
... need to ask a favor.
Well ....
... ¿Me could say whether the
my shoes smell bad ...
¿Perdón ...?
I know it sounds absurd, but
is very important to me.
Help yourself
to be brutally honest.
Well, in my professional opinion ......
... no problems.
Ben  is questioned
on the real objective  ...
hostility Samantha ...
the alleged problem of the foot ....
... The most important consideration:  ...
... Why not ask
to which he did not like her?  ...
... You are the north?
Am ...
¿Adónde you ...?
A west.
Somewhere in the west, in particular?
Not yet.
So the direction, but not ......
... destination.
Yes, it is more or less ....
... ¿Sabías that marijuana is medically
approved for cancer patients ...
¿Eres ... a kind of guess?
No.
So you, because in cancer?
Breathe wrapped
with it the right time.
He has had treatment?
In fact,
disappeared by itself ....
Zen ... Really?
No, I'm just stick with me, man.
I had treatment.
You married?
Compromised ....
ZY you ...?
Spouse?
25 years ago.
And counting ....
Zen ... Really? There were some
4 years old when she married?
Was 17, actually.
Still in love?
Yes ..
... How I knew was the real thing?
If you have to ask ......
... you're not.
And you already knew that.
THE HOLY BIBLE
What are we, USA. UU. --
Ulysses, Alfred Tennyson ...
... What the fuck ...?...
... Here was the most westward
when Terry was able to run ....
... But of course that
has never ceased to dream ...
... back on the road and
reach the Pacific ....
... All I can say is that if
There any way to back  ...
finished ... and I will.  ...
Zhol ... ...
... What are you doing?
Attempt Clothing
my sister's marriage ....
... What happened to send a
I have decided to return to
review that decision ....
... ¿Otra time?
Yes, again.
Grab your breast so funny?
Yes ..
... ¿Alguna you ever thought that perhaps
and sinuses are not the clothes?
Come home.
Please.
I'm not ready yet, Sam ....
...- I. ..
- What are you doing?
Well, I just joined
in the ring to escape the heat e. ..
E. .. What?
Well, I thought it was
have a heatstroke.
I mean, not thinking
was the real Stanley Cup.
Is the real Stanley Cup, ¿verdad?
Yes, of course it is ....
... What are you doing here?
It is the day of Vincent and Derek is in
Manitoba since Anaheim won the cup ....
expositive  ... Done ....
... Each member of the champions cup
Stanley is with her for 24 hours.
Derek was the right time .... 7
Derek Vincent ...- You?
- Am.
Congratulations, man.
Thanks ....
... ¿Dónde is the kind of publicity?
You know, the kind of white gloves
the guard with his life.
In fact, I asked a few
my friends to distraction.
To be a moment
only with the cup, ¿sabes?
I could never endure, ¿verdad?
I left halfway through the game with
a concussion, so ...
Yes,
I remember that fight.
Everyone remembers
this fight, except for me ....
... I'm going ¿Quieres calculation, ¿verdad?
No. ...
... come true.
Doctors diagnosed
Cheryl O'Reilly as infertile.  ...
... One night, Mike Ricci Colorado
Avalanche took the Cup to a party.
Cheryl kissed  and nine months
later, Stanley was born .
You want to kiss the cup?
Give luck.
Yes ..
... Maybe it was the champagne,
But a small part of Ben  ...
... felt that the ghosts of all
Players who have kissed the Cup  ...
... might be able to block
cancer and make it fall into oblivion ....
... On the other hand, perhaps your
karma was irreparably screwed .
hockey stick and the Stanley Cup
would not be enough for a day  ...
... Why  Ben insisted ...
... access to the same
Direct doubtful  ...
... for the camel's largest
prairie in the world?
What do I do now ...
Please, please ...
Here, your damned!
We ...
Damn!
Not here, not now ...
God ......
... Come on!
Please, please ...
I do not do this now.
I do this ...
Orders! ...
... Why? ...
... Why not try ...
... Has a new message
voice mail .
Hello  Behind
newspapers, sitting at the window,  ...
... and now read
Phil on the loss of the court.
Please call me.
If Ben's life could ...
... will be coffee and newspapers
with Samantha,  ...
... that would be a joy .
I do not know how to thank him.
Most people
unrelated, ¿entiendes?
Simply went ahead.
It was not anything else, really.
Sorry about your dog.
You know, the funny thing is ......
more ... slept in my bed between spouses.
Combined.
This is the first time in ten years cries.
You appear to have dirty gasoline.
This is serious?
No.
I just have to clean.
You should not take long.
I never expected to complete two
often divorced ...
... and only see my son
once a year if lucky.
He lives with his father?
Has only 20 years.
Anyway, her father
long before it dropped.
Come on, not
has a son aged 20.
If.
And a granddaughter just made 4.
Only saw once.
My son works in Fort McMurray.
The money is too good
understand here ....
ZY ... why not let you go?
Do something else.
I am also indebted.
And if the weather and the markets
no freaking arm ...
... maybe you can adjust the payment of
my loans at the end of the harvest.
I feel a fool if
all the farmers around here ...
... not in the same situation.
That makes you bitter?
That's the thing, no.
The earth has a way of
Scratching the skin ...
However, if you could give a shit
Every so often, it would be much happier.
Not a bad light, but as
my men are XXL.
Moreover, when normally the progress ...
implies some conditioners ...
air to the wine ...
... and a total lack of subtlety.
Well, let's around a horse.
You know, I really ...
never rode on horseback.
Obviously you never lived.
When I come here I think
where else I want to go ....
... Beyond the hills,  ...
asked if another ...
life would have been a cowboy,
Ben wanted no part of France that is ...
... so rigid with the size
of men ....
also wanted to have a ...
air conditioning box of wine ....
...- You are better than ever.
- Okay.
Ben's journey  revived
friends who were lost.  ...
... At the weekend ...
... instead of repair
fencing,  ...
...  Fran made a surprise visit
his son in Fort McMurray.  ...
... Unfortunately, Brad
was a double turn.  ...
... The positive side is that,
while killing time,
Fran  finally found the
the love of your life .
Sorry.
Can you tell me
Dawson left the street ...
... Most of the Indians shop
World was a big disappointment.
Ben could not say why .
In fact  wait ...
... most of the dinosaurs
largest in the world .
This is a  note 3 at 10 s
Maybe 3 and a half ....
How many of you ...
you already know ...
... Dinosaur Provincial Park
is home to the largest collection ...
... the bones of a dinosaur in the world.
Only by competition
the Gobi Desert in China.
It makes us feel
means negligible, ZnO?
They know that the most powerful
planet has been completely eradicated.
Reduced to a pile of bones.
We conclude that  stranded somewhere ...
... between the bones of
old animals,  ...
Grumps  ... the question is hidden ....
... instead, it occurred to Ben that
as were his prehistoric friends,  ...
... the Grumps  be extinguished .
True Story ....
... In 1997, Gina Lalapola,
an Italian stripper,  ...
suffocated while waiting ... ...
to jump from ...
inside a cake.  ...
... What I mean is that
All times are uncertain.
One minute we're trying to ...
find a good ...
song on the radio,  ...
... in  ... ...
... ¿Cuál is the minimum in life?  ...
... And so, inexplicably
happy to be alive  ...
... Ben  tried to recreate a
moments of the film,  ...
... the type where the
uninhibited dance hero,  ...
... ... finally able to symbolically
... break from their moorings
conventional  ...
through the power ...
processor of a pop song ....
... However, not Ben
achieved this feat.  ...
felt like a fool ...
try to be that guy.  ...
... Furthermore,
no dance .
Six hours of relentless  cold  ...
... and Ben has decided that
came the attraction of the street  ...
... and lack of route ....
... not to save for retirement,
had its advantages.  ...
... Mom and Dad are going up.
We all passarmo us.
Back to Toronto  and deal with it.  ...
... Ben is the mother.
I have to hear his voice.  ...
... I love you so much ....
... Hi, son. Listen,
We can handle this.  ...
...  called Dr. Morgan and
you can get  ...
the best experts ...
Sunnybrook Cancer ....
... sorry ....
... not intended for this.  ...
... You can call your
mother, please?  ...
... Come on,
Prisoners were not
Love solo
We must leave behind
We like a million dollars
Everywhere you look,
They cover
Let's drink Rolling Rock,
And returning to the sea
I agree there and then turn to me
Forget all
Our friends and family
Our fans, enemies
When we left the sun sets
This city turn its back
Let's go,
Prisoners were not
Love solo
Leaving behind you
We like a million dollars
Everywhere you look,
They cover
Thank you very much.
I have that anywhere else.
He promised not to tell anyone.
I know.
And he promised that
return within two days.
Returning home?
Not yet.
So you ....
¿Vienes ...?
Yes ..
¿Dónde ... are you?
In Banff.
Booking a plane ticket tomorrow.
Goodbye .
Ben knew that ...
... to turn more
travelers,  ...
... search by Grumps  seems stupid.
Two hours after
Escape the room
Presidential  ...
...  was lost .
If it came  Pacific Ocean ...
... and west without it,
What would you do?  ...
... Oh, my God ...
... Damn!
Nice doggy, nice doggy! ...
...- Lindo perrito ...
- Mick Launches!
Lie!
Sorry. Not expected
find someone here.
No problem. I only
is distracted, was not it ....
... Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I just ... I am a. ..
I feel a bit silly ....
...- ¯Quieres water?
- Yes, it can be. Thank you.
A Canadian Errant
Banned from their land
You know the song?
Yes
A Canadian wanderer ...
... That was a statement
greatly attenuated.  ...
... Ben's mother had
singing 'Un Canadien errant',  ...
a traditional song ...
French Canadian
every night during his childhood.
Words
in their DNA.  ...
... Of all the songs
Tracey could have chosen,  ...
... for having chosen
mean something .
In foreign lands
Thus.
The fundamental rules
songs around the campfire ...
clearly say that ...
all must participate.
Honestly, no ¿Quieres sing.
Seriously. I insist.
If you see my country
My unfortunate country
Ben had never
made a complete inventory  ...
of things ...
Samantha did not like to ....
... She was a girl routines ....
... Everything had to be
done in a certain order.  ...
... A deviation from this, directed ...
... lack of sleep and
irritability general ....
... Despite the efforts of Ben,
Samantha refused to be a  ...
... quantify  movies, books y. ..
... behavior of
family members  ...
...  scale of 1 to 10 ....
... A big disappointment for Ben,  ...
... because that is the filter
classified many parts of your life .
Ben  regretted the
how your sex life  ...
have lost some ...
of his previous carnal ....
Whether ¿Le ... wait until tomorrow ...
... And finally,
the most annoying of all:  ...
Samantha's jaw ...
lap while she ate.
Ben was sure that
as the years passed,  ...
...  alerting him that ....
... Come on, I say to my friends
I remember them ...
I remember them
You have a fantastic voice.
It's nice of you to say
but there is much left
I hope she can sing.
Well, I have perfect pitch,
and you can definitely sing ....
... That was horrible!
My teacher s class 4
I lied ....
ZDE ... do you mean?
It's nothing important.
His second book is about what?
I wrote a second novel ....
... any idea ¿Tienes o. .....
... Oh, no. Rejection
killed my creativity.
You know, my grandfather
Thomas Edison quotes for me ...
... until they run out like a child.
His favorite line: ...
'Many of the failures of life
are people who are unaware ...
... how close
of success when he fell.
Fine, but perseverance,
and then there is only an illusion.
I think someone has to fill
the proportion of delirium in the world ....
... What would you do if you had one week of life?
Maybe ... only
what I'm doing now.
My mind is not tomorrow o. .....
... in yesterday, or even a
three hours. You are just here ....
... What would you do?
Love ....
... Why?
I am just a matter of urgency
more than words.
Samantha could
find a flight that evening,  ...
... instead of in the morning
Then, as planned.
When Ben  agree
was deliriously happy ....
... Maybe it was the fact
that somehow ...
... succeeded in solving
their demons ....
What  ... this way much
more sense,  ...
...  that treatment ....
¿Dónde ... have you been all night? ...
... How you can just forgive me ...
ZNO ... bother you?
Of course I'm upset.
But at least not lied in this regard.
You are completely
lost at this time.
So I say to myself
which is not us.
Maybe later, I get upset.
But now we have more things to try.
As for why not go home.
Simply can not.
It's selfish.
Es .. is not ....
... Are you being an idiot.
Treatment ....
ZTE ... seems there is no hope?
I do not want to be patient.
No, it does not make sense.
We have still not out ...
... even the fight? By
course that makes sense.
And if this fight?
And if this is the right thing?
I know.
Changed everything.
But Why?
What happened? ...
... Why not have
only by the diagnosis.
Because, Samantha, I am watching
a wall that can not overcome.
Because I do not know
¿cuáles are good answers ....
so be honest ... What?
Well ....
¿Quieres know ... what was the first
What went through my head ...
... when the doctor said I had cancer?
The first thing?
Is that I wanted to cancel the marriage.
I absolutely wanted to marry ...
... and do not want to return to work,
and do not want to do what it was.
This is a normal reaction.
So I wanted to cancel the wedding.
However, Samantha,
it is not cancer,
has to do with life
he built for me.
Why I have so much insurance?
Because I care so much
to be responsible all the time?
Because I have to mess with that
tools that we put in our kitchen?
I am becoming like my father.
And no offense to him, love him ...
... is a decent man, but this
was never the ambition of my life.
So ¿cuál is the alternative?
This!
This is the alternative.
You can simply walk
to travel by bike forever.
At some point,
This leaves you on top.
Especially you.
I just want time.
If you can have every
in this day and make life ...
... then it must be a better choice.
But you should not be killed.
You know that. Allows
go against the odds.
That has allowed us to do this.
This has nothing to do with us.
This is the problem, Samantha.
This has to do with me ....
... ¿Alguna once loved me?
Is not the way it deserved ....
... Why I asked you to marry?
Due to the large part of me wanted ....
Why not find ...
a reason for not having done so.
I never thought it had been withdrawn.
A security option ....
... How they have seen?
Any indecision,
All questions ...
They always see us.
And do not see you.
I'm an idiot.
Samantha ....
ZNO ... dare to follow me.
Shut up!
Hi, Mom.
It has a good point.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Sorry.
You can help us
to take a picture?
Bright.
Thank you very much.
Thanks ....
...- Not.
- It's Canadian, Zeh?
Am
Let me tell you who lives
one of the most beautiful countries in the world.
I know.
Love them was not an illusion.  ...
... However, as in
most relationships,  ...
had some waves ...
treacherous it could sink.  ...
... In these times of
storm at sea,  ...
... Ben is a picture of a
eg ¿cuál is the best .
Nobody knew  say
degree of certainty ...
... that in fact the
Grumps appearance of ....
It is difficult  ...
detected this way.  ...
... However, a good rule of thumb
where his father has always believed:  ...
Reconhecê him ...
finally, when you see .
And Ben  was positively sure ...
... that the universe was
Grumps cough ....
... There is one thing to do.
Smell the sea ....
... ¿Cuál is the divorce rate ...
... 36%.
This is not some
very good opportunity.
Are better than one in ten.
Well, I guess they are.
When it comes to people
free numbers.
You have to.
You have to stop it?
I asked a man
walking on the road ....
'How you know you love ?'...
... He told me 'If you have to ask ......
... you're not. "
You never had to ask
anyone ¿verdad, Sam?
No.
Of course not ....
... Are you crazy?
Yes
And not just because of that.
Of all the various forms
this can be a bitch.
I'm obsessed with a
completely selfish.
That everyone thinks she is a woman ...
... left her boyfriend because he had cancer.
I think not.
I think anyone listening to the files.
Sorry for us
this confusion.
Although that is good ....
... How are you feeling?
Patient ...
Its worth the trip?
Yes
But you took pictures?
It's worth a lifetime.
When we have the
rare moments of clarity,  ...
those moments ...
that the universe makes sense,  ...
tried desperately to ...
agarrarmo us to them.  ...
... They are the life rafts
sometimes the darkest,  ...
... in the vastness of everything,
the incomprehensible nature
of life  ...
...  escapes us completely.
So the question becomes,
or should have been: ...
... if they knew what
that there was only one day ...
... or a week,
or month of life ...
What lifeboat hold ... ...
What secret ... ...
banda ... What to see?
The person to declare his love?
You want to do ...
What exotic place ... went for a coffee?
He wrote that book?
ONE WEEK BY BEN TYLER
To strive, to seek,
And I find it will not fail
To be used for translation: rakovina@cancer.com
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org