...from Uptown, Downtown,
in town, out of town.
We got it going on, 1-4-5,
it's famous, baby,
here we go.
It's the world-famous
Brucie B.
on the speciaI mix tip
for all my playa niggas,
all my niggas gettin' paper.
Ladies lookin' good,
fellas, y'all lookin' good.
We gettin' money Uptown style,
a'ight?
...to my niggas from 1-5-5,
1-1-2, 1-4-9,
49 is in the house.
# Thinking of a master plan #
# 'Cause ain't nothing
but sweat inside my hand #
# So I dig into my pocket,
all my money's spent #
# So I dig deeper,
but still comin' up with lint #
# So I start my mission,
leave my residence #
# Thinking how could I get
some dead presidents #
# I need money #
# I used to be a stickup kid #
# So I think of all the devious
things I did #
# I used to roll up, this is
a holdup, ain't nothin' funny #
# Stop smilin', be still, don't
nothin' move but the money #
# But now I learn to earn
'cause I'm righteous #
# I feeI great,
so maybe I might just #
# Search for a 9:00 to 5:00
if I strive #
# Then maybe I'll stay alive #
# So I walk up the street #
This is the stage.
# Feelin' out of place 'cause,
man, do I miss #
If you was here,
you was definitely somebody.
# And a nice,
big plate of fish #
# Which is my favorite dish #
# But without no money,
it's still a wish #
# 'Cause I don't like to dream
about gettin' paid #
# So I dig into the books
of the rhymes that I made #
# To now test to see
if I got pull #
And I was there.
Me, Mitch, and Rico.
We did our thing, you know?
We was living.
We was living that life.
So, you know, I'm up at this
birthday party the other day.
You told me about it.
Talkin' about Charlie Rucks?
Exactly.
Yeah, I couldn't make
that shit.
So, I'm up
at that birthday...
I didn't bring him nothin'.
So, I see everybody up there
got stuff for him,
so I walk up
to the table...
Ain't got no soy sauce
up there, B.?
No, they didn't put no fuckin'
soy sauce in the bag, man.
Why these Chinese niggas
always doin' this shit, man?
Fuck the soy sauce, man!
Mitch, can I tell a story?
I walk up to the table, right?
- Chinese niggas...
- Pick up the cake...
mush it in his face,
tell him, "Happy birthday. "
Niggas at the party
looking at me like I'm buggin'.
I showed that nigga
mad love, B.
We lookin' at you
like you buggin', man.
You buggin', man.
This nigga... thinks it's funny.
You took the whole cake
and mushed it in his face?
Whole cake.
What's up with this nigga here?
That's love right there, man.
Why you doin' that, B.?
Why you fuckin' a birthday
party up like that?
I know his girI was there.
Ace, make that shot again.
Five thou
you can't make it again.
I ain't gonna take your $5,000,
man. Hold onto your money.
Penny-pinchin'
nigga here, man.
You know,
he fucks me up, man.
You always trying to save
your dough and shit, B.
The thing is, baby, you're
fuckin' with the wrong nigga.
You need to be
fuckin' with me, man.
Give me that bet, man.
Yeah, you got the bet,
Mr. Mitch. What, you drunk?
I'm gonna take this nigga
Uptown, man.
- Yeah, take me Uptown, man.
- I'm gonna take you Uptown.
Five thou you can't make
the shot. You off right here.
You off right here, man.
Your man drunk.
That's off right there.
Ahh!
- Where's my money, man?
- Lucky cat right there.
- Let me get my money, man.
- Nigga, bet it right back.
- That ain't nothin', man.
- I need paid.
- Go ahead, nigga.
- Thank you.
But double up.
Bet it right back.
There go your five.
Bet it five right back.
Go ahead, Mr. Mitch.
Double up.
Well, now this nigga feelin'
lucky, man.
Feelin' like he like you or
something, man. Double it up?
Like him? I'm me!
Double up!
Let's see if you gonna
make the shot now, Mr. Mitch.
Make the shot now, baby.
You're soft, Mitch.
Mitch! Make the money count!
Make the money count!
Ah, nigga, that's off!
Give me my money.
- Give me my money.
- Come on, man.
- I ain't got it right now.
- Right here, man.
- You ain't got it? No ribs!
- Now, come on, B.!
No ribs, no rice,
no champagne!
You don't eat nothin'! Fuck you,
man, I'll get my money, man.
Pay me my money, man.
Yo, A., man, just...
loan me $ 10 G's reaI fast
till I get back to the crib.
Loan your man $ 10 G's, 'cause I
ain't givin' him his food back.
- And no more soy sauce, nigga.
- That's $5,000, man.
What the fuck you mean?
Lend me $ 10,000 reaI fast, B.
I'm gonna give you the dough
when I get back to the crib.
I got $5,000 man. I'm payin' for
your paper bag games, is it?
You're a
cheap-ass motherfucker.
You're a cheap-ass
motherfucker.
This motherfucker
rich as shit,
acting like
he ain't got $ 10,000.
You just burned anyway
'cause you lost, man.
Hello? Word.
- Take your money.
- Take your food.
No, I'll go get Aunt June.
I'll pick her up.
All right.
- I'm gonna slow down.
- All right, it's on, baby.
N- N-Now, hold up, B. I ain't
finished taking your money.
Nah, Keisha having a baby, man.
- Word?
Yo, congratulations,
my man, having a baby.
Keep that for yourself, man.
You good?
Do your job, man.
Congratulations, motherfucker!
Congratulations,
motherfuckin' father!
You was good, motherfucker!
This motherfucker layin'
the motherfuckin' power!
- Congratulations!
- Yo, we family now!
Fuckin' look!
- # Baby #
- # Doo-doo, doo-doo #
# Bum-dun-dun-dun #
# Baby, I pray to God above #
# Doo-doo #
Uhh! Aah! Uhh!
All right.
I need stat portable X-rays.
I want full blood work, coags.
Hey, you okay? Can you hear me?
Huh? Can you hear me?
What's your name, man?
Tell me your name.
Tell me your name?
You with me?
All right, now,
who did this to you?
I did.
Move him, move him.
I see you checkin' out
that "help wanted" sign.
What? Nah.
Nah, I was just thinking
about them, um...
Yeah, so...
so, why you got the "help
wanted" sign in the window?
That sign is to make sure
you're handlin' your business.
That's whack... basically,
you're making it look like
we ain't taking
care of business in here.
"Hey, yo, Mr. Pip, I know you
need help up in this joint. "
- Come on, man.
- Mm-hmm.
What I need you to do
is make some deliveries.
You always got me
making deliveries.
Hello?
Cece, my nigga.
All day, every day.
How much you wanna do?
Come on, baby, you gonna
get the hair and the nails.
Yo, damn, nigga. Every time
I step up in this motherfucker,
you runnin' the joint!
Man, why don't you just
put your shit in a bag, man?
Fuck a bag, man.
Just, uh... you worry
about the cleaning and shit,
you know what I mean,
'cause I know you making
money up in this bitch.
Can I help you?
Uh, nah, that's cool. My man
Ace Boogie gonna handle that.
I got it, Mr. Pip.
No, he on his way out
the door. I'll help you.
You can change that, right?
That's a big-ass bill.
Hey, you know how it go down.
No, sorry.
A'ight, well, um...
why don't you keep the change?
Nah, you know what?
Fuck that.
Give it to my man,
Ace Boogie, a'ight?
He's family, right, baby?
- Hmm.
- Yeah, right, man.
Nah, I'm just saying, I hate
to see Cakes' big brother
working in a sweatbox.
So, yo, you ever
want to get out, then...
Come on, Calvin.
Calvin. Don't do that.
He's doin' fine.
Yo, baby, what I told you
about runnin'...
Why don't you relax, Doctor?
How you doin', baby?
I'm doin' fine, Mr. Pip.
Yeah, she doin' fine,
thank you.
Hey, yo, Hop Sing, why
don't you keep workin' hard,
'cause it's gonna pay off,
you know what I mean?
I'm gonna catch you
on the rebound.
All right, let's bounce, baby.
His monkey-ass ain't worked
a hard day in his life.
That's why he don't know how
to act with all of that money.
Think he the king of Harlem.
I hope your sister know
with that fooI...
it's only a matter of time.
A matter of time.
Well, congratulations!
Good job, and you really put it
away there in that speed round.
And now,
last time, you got a car...
All right, now, let me
see what you working with.
Come on.
All right, all right.
It's looking good,
it's looking good.
- Now, you did this side yet?
- I did.
Nah, it don't look like
you did this side. Stop Iying.
I did!
Look, first of all, man,
you gotta get you a toothbrush.
You ain't gonna be able to
keep the white bottom clean
without it, all right?
Secondly, man, tuck
the laces in. You buggin' out.
You don't give nobody
a chance to, God.
Give you a chance? You gotta
do it in the beginning.
You don't get the shoelaces
all wet and dirty,
man can't start calling you
a poo putt.
You know what I'm sayin'?
All right?
All right, man.
Who is it?!
It's Ace.
Hey, Boogie.
- What's up, nigga?
- What's up, man?
- What's up, homeboy?
- I'm chillin', man.
- Everything all right?
- Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah,
before I forget, man,
I need you to do me
a favor if you can, man.
Run some clothes down to the
cleaners for me if you could.
- Okay, cool, man.
- That's cool?
I know it's hectic for you
out here and all that.
Keisha! Keisha!
- What?!
- This nigga A. here.
Hey, Ace.
I didn't know you was here.
Go in the back
and get them clothes for me
so he can bring them
to Mr. Pip's.
Nigga, what's wrong
with your big-ass feet?
What, man?
Get you in need of some grease
for them whack-ass baby hairs.
Shut up.
And tuck in that little butt.
Nobody wants to
see that little butt.
- Whassup, Ace?
- Whassup, little man?
Hey, Mitch,
can we shoot some hoops?
I can't, little man. I'm busy,
B. I gotta go to work.
I got you, man.
He don't know nothin'
about no hoops.
You need to be
comin' to me for that.
I'll have you workin' on your
left hand. You'll do nice.
All right, man,
I'll see you later.
You talkin' back.
You just came for the clothes?
Nah. Pfft.
What you talkin' about?
What's up, man?
How you doin'?
Good, baby.
What's up, man?
- Everything all right here?
- Yeah, it's good.
Let me see that.
Is this $800?
Come here!
- How you doing, Mr. Crawford?
- Hey, Ace.
Got your delivery here.
- Everything cool, though?
- Yeah, yeah.
Good, all right.
I'll be back.
All right, all right.
Hey, Paisan.
Hey, excuse me, my friend.
You work for
the cleaners, right?
Yeah. Here you go.
Could you take some
clothes for me, please?
Just a few things.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
- Okay.
- Go ahead, man.
Thank you.
Come in!
Come in.
You want something to drink?
A soda?
Um... nah.
But I'll take that
laundry you...
Damn.
Okay.
All right. Oh! I...
Gotta get these clean, too!
What's your name?
Ace.
Aceito?
Yeah.
You live
in the neighborhood, right?
Yeah.
Look, I gotta get
outta here, man.
- I gotta get back.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Your friend who's the dealer?
Take him to a movie.
That's your friend, right?
Yeah.
I'm Lulu.
What?
Lulu.
Okay, what kind of name
is that?
I don't know.
It's my name.
Show me your left.
Come on, man.
Anybody could do that.
You think you slick? You trying
to go between your legs?
Come on... Nah, the left!
The left, baby!
Show me the...
Terrible. Terrible.
Oh, snap!
Whoo!
I gotta see this!
Yo, that's yours?
Nah, little man, that's ours.
- Can I check it out?
- Go check it out.
What's up?
What up, baby?
Come on... no, no, no!
Come on around here, man!
Come on, baby,
Stop playing, man.
You know my style, baby.
It ain't my style
to be running around here
getting all sweaty
on the court, baby.
So, that's your little
new bike, huh?
- It's fly, right?
- Yeah, it's fly.
I see your shit shimmering, man,
you know what I'm saying?
I see you got the Rolex.
You know about this, B.
We need to get you one, man,
and stop playing.
- No, no, no, no.
- Straight-up pussy magnet, man.
You gonna have
no problems, man.
- It ain't my flow, man.
- Oh, it ain't your flow.
Oh, you too smooth, now?
That's what it is?
Nah, man, it's you.
Oh, it's me.
Yeah, you right, man.
Making money is me, man.
Nah, I'm just
fuckin' with you, A., man.
Yes, you'll probably have
a whole chain of cleaners
in a hot minute anyway,
you know?
Be the George Jefferson
of the ghetto, B.
Yeah, nigga's got jokes.
In 10 years, me and you
gonna have matching Benzes.
10 years?
I'm thinking more like
10 days, man. 10 days.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- All right. Yeah.
All right. Get outta here.
Hey, come here for a minute.
What?
Fuck you mean, "What?"
Come here, G.
Talking to myself.
You, uh...
you talking to
Mitch's sister, right?
Yeah, 'cause I be seein'
y'all around and all that.
You know, that's cool, man.
The girI kinda bangin'.
You hittin' that, right?
Come on, man.
Oh, my God!
Kid, you're supposed
to be hittin' that!
Sweatin' in that laundry
for nickels and dimes
is not gonna get you that ass.
Look here... you saw that
Jonesin' motherfucker
that just ran out of here?
That's my clientele.
That's reaI money right there.
Like... like what?
I just made enough dough
to bake biscuits
for the projects, nigga.
Try a quick $800 in one day.
The fuck are you shrugging for?
There's something wrong
with your back? Yeah?
Look...
This here
is a hundred a pop.
Only niggas with reaI dough
fuck with this.
And that's all yours?
Hell, yeah, this is all me!
Eight niggas.
AII I'm tryin' to tell you...
is that with this money...
your girI'll suck your dick
all day.
- Okay, man.
- No problem.
Hey, Ace.
Hey.
Hey, what's goin' on,
Miss Billips?
Calvin.
What's goin' on, baby?
You know, we're just gettin'
ready for dinner.
I put the tips in the thing.
Hey, how about that?
A number eight.
Here, this here
is for the, uh...
for groceries, Mrs. Billips.
Thank you, CaI.
Yeah, no problem.
Yo, uh...
Come on.
Come on where? We eatin'.
Oh, Miss Billips,
we, uh...
you know, we, uh...
we were gonna go out
to eat somewhere.
Why don't you go on ahead,
Calvin? She'll be right there.
What's the next product
up to win?
It's a sturdy washer and dryer!
You're stupid.
Whatever!
Come on, Ace!
How many times
I gotta tell you
about this boobity-boob
shit playing in the store?
What you want me to do?
Like, not listen to the radio...
What?!
I said, half the time,
you ain't even in here!
What you want me to do, sit in
here and not listen to no music?
It don't make no difference
if I'm here or not!
It's my rules, my radio,
my store, my music!
You know I don't listen
to this shit!
I... I can't even
understand them!
Look, can you even
understand this shit?
It's for my ears.
Yes, I understand it.
Yeah, you can understand
that bullshit,
but you can't understand
when I tell you not to...
Ahh.
Yeah. That's it.
That's what I'm talking about.
You hear that? You hear that?
That's music. That's singing.
There's beauty in singing.
That other shit
is just talking.
"Yak, yak, yak,
yak, yak, yak. "
That's what I'm talking about,
you understand what I'm saying?
That's quality shit.
Hello?
Shit, nigga, make it easy
on yourself. I don't know.
No, baby, I ain't...
Ain't you sick of
giving me your money?
Oh, shit. Ho... oh!
- I know he didn't do it, baby.
- Yeah. Hold on one second.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Where you going?
I'm about to go
make these drop-offs!
What up, niggas?
Everything all right, man?
That chillin', man?
Everything a'ight?
Are you feeling the joint,
baby?
It's that new shit, man. White
niggas ain't even got this.
Hey, Boogie!
What's up, nigga?
You feelin' me, man?
It's like a motherfuckin'
spaceship, man.
You got the, um...
You feelin' me yet, man?
You got the gold BBS
on this motherfucker.
What's up, man?
Let me take you for a spin,
show you what it feeI like.
I gotta go
make these drop-offs.
You think you're the only one
out here workin', B.?
I gotta make drop-offs,
too, B.
Come on, man, get in, man.
I ain't takin' no for an answer.
It's the world-famous
Brucie B.,
on the mix for my man, Mitch.
You know how we do...
we got the brand-new song,
we coming through town,
we bouncin'.
A'ight, here we go.
It's flavor!
It's my man, Mitch!
I see you, baby. Yeah!
# Pump back the bass,
the freak lands the best #
What's up, niggas?
What's happenin'?
Money Mitch. Aw, so you got
that new Saab thing?
Come on, man, you know
I'm out here, man.
- Okay, what's up?
- What's up, B.?
I hope you didn't stop
to disappoint a nigga, man.
- I hope that game is still on.
- What?
Man, I still hope we got
that $5,000 bet happenin'.
- What?
- The Knicks, nigga.
- What? What?
- Turn down the boom-ass stereo.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
We still have 5 G's, nigga?
You gotta stop acting like
you ain't makin' money, man.
Make it $ 10,000, man.
What's wrong with you?
Make it 10 G's,
you poor-ass nigga.
We gettin' more money than you,
man, you know what I'm sayin'?
I got a G. for every
bump on your face, nigga.
Whatever you want, man.
Hey, what's you laughin' at,
man?
You need to put your man on.
He look bad.
Tell him to get hit with
an ounce of somethin' somethin'.
Yo, this is my Thursday car.
On Saturday, I'm breakin' out
with something new, all right?
- Saturday, report to bridge...
- Yo, man,
I am the bridge, man.
You report to me, man,
always, man.
Hey, none of that shit, man.
You might wanna holler at me.
You dumb-ass niggas.
Oh, yeah.
Everybody's chillin'.
- Tommy Tom.
- Yeah, what's up, baby?
- What's up, man?
- Hey, baby.
My streetside negro.
Taking care of the community?
Yes, indeed.
I'm takin' care of you, too.
It's all good.
Yep. You're so damn neat
with your money.
Come on, man.
You know me, man.
Cleanliness is
next to Godliness.
What's up, little niggas?
How y'all livin'?
You left this in your pants
last time.
Do you always return everything
you find in the laundry?
Nah.
I didn't think so.
You find something
in there, you keep it.
It's a tip for you.
- This?
- Mm-hmm.
That's nothing for me.
My job brings me plenty.
But you ain't no drug dealer.
I'm not?
Moneymakin' Mitch.
Tell me somethin' good, baby.
It's all good, Ice.
I know it is.
Why am I not a drug dealer?
I'm sayin'
I don't see you outside.
The way you dress...
you dress nice.
What about your friends?
They dress nice. Fancy.
Tuck them laces in, all right?
Don't be slackin' on that.
Yeah, he's your
right-hand man, now.
- Next week, nigga.
- Makin' that reaI money.
Yeah, but you... you dress
nice-nice, you understand?
They dress...
whatever, loud-nice.
Okay. Thank you.
You don't even
got a car, do you?
What do I need a car for?
Family movin' up
in the business.
I know
you gonna look after family.
What family
you talking about, Ice?
Fuck,
I look invisible, nigga?
Did I pass the test, compre?
It's not...
it's not a test.
I'm just sayin'...
You like money, right?
Yeah.
I'm broke, baby.
I ain't got no money.
Bullshit.
I see you shinin', nigga.
I can smell a motherfucker
with money.
Even Ray Charles could see
you got money.
Dang.
Look at this nigga.
Little Sonny and his crew,
the future of our nation.
Ain't that a bitch?
Damn, man.
You got the John Wayne shit,
man.
Fuckin' gun all up in the
007 compartment, man. Damn.
Well, the way you dress,
nigga,
you ain't got to worry
about those cats.
You'll be invisible up in
the club.
Exactly.
Nah, I'm just
fuckin' with you, bud.
What you doin', man?
What's that?
You tell me, man.
It looks like coke, nigga.
You fuck me up, A.
You never say shit, B.
Just come out the blue
with some coke, huh?
To tell you the truth, I ain't
fuckin' with coke right now.
The shit
just ain't clickin', B.
You know what you
need to do, man?
You need to fuck with that cat
your sister be talkin' to,
that nigga, Calvin, man.
He sells coke.
Nah, I ain't fuckin'
with that nigga, man.
Nigga's dumb.
Hey, man, what, man?
What you mean, "What?"
I'm just tryin' to picture
Mr. Jefferson
hustlin' on these streets.
I've seen you roll up
in the black Saab
with the gold BBS's, man.
I said, "Damn,
this dickety-stick
is really makin' this money.
He's really makin' money,
man," you understand?
Listen, hey...
It ain't just about the money.
It's not.
You know what it's about, man?
It's about fuckin' those
skeezers like that right there,
it's about drivin'
these fly-ass cars,
and it's definitely about never
dressin' like a nigga like you.
Okay, man.
Come on, man. Let's go be stars
up in this joint, all right?
Yeah, baby!
Dance it up, y'all!
Go on and get out there
and move it!
Come on!
Yeah! This is
all about boogie.
We boogie nonstop.
We at the top.
We got it goin' on.
A'ight, here we go.
- What's up? What's up, man?
- Hey, hey.
Hey, my man!
Ladies' lookin' good...
Yeah!
Mitch was a reaI star...
See, when the lights caught him,
he always looked good.
Yo, my man,
Mitch, in the house!
Yeah! Lookin' good, King!
I see you!
A'ight, here we go!
And Mitch got love
from everybody.
I mean, everybody.
What are you doing?
Go to sleep, little man.
Lucky, you're up.
You workin' today?
You know,
don't call me "Lucky," Ma.
Been a long time since...
I found food stamps
or something like that.
Now, don't forget
when you picked that $ 700...
Ma, that was when I was 12,
you know what I'm sayin'?
I'm grown now, and there ain't
a whole lot lucky to do with me
getting up and goin' to
work right now,
so... I don't wanna be called
"Lucky. " Thanks, Mom.
All right, baby.
Guess your sister got to get
a better man now.
Boy just got busted
by the cops.
He was dealing right in
front of your building.
Didn't I tell you?
Can't do shit
with that cash now...
except hire a lawyer.
Did you see it?
Nah.
I heard about it
on the way over here.
Cops must've been watching
his dumb ass.
Yo, chief,
you seen Calvin?
Nah, he got locked up.
Yo, takin' his place?
Never mind.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Hold on one second, man.
What, um...
what you lookin' for?
Just one.
A'ight.
Fuck, B.
One.
You ain't got no bottle?
What? Bottle?
What you need
a bottle for, man?
Plastic bottle, whatever?
Damn,
this is a big-ass rock, B.
Mmm!
All this for a hundred?
Man, this is better than
Calvin's stuff. Word up.
Yo, I could hook up
with you later, right?
Nah, man, I'm...
across the street.
The building
All right, G.
Peace out.
You know what this is?
Yeah. It's coke.
Yes,
but that's a kilo of coke.
How much is it worth?
$25,000.
Damn.
No "damn. "
Damn, that's damn good, okay?
A'ight, I'm sayin'...
The shit on the street
is garbage.
This crud that's washed
with acetone and kerosene.
This is the best product,
and you gonna be the only one
in the street holding this.
$25,000.
$25,000 is the street price.
Of that, I get $ 18,000.
$ 7,000.
That's right,
for every key that you move.
You know I...
I still got my job
at the cleaners, um...
No, it's perfect, man,
because that's how
everybody knows you... as Ace.
Forget about heroin.
This is the wave
of the future, baby.
Crazy, man.
I'm gonna give you...
an eighth of a key, okay?
Break it up.
Do like you did with the rock.
See me in four days, okay?
'Sup, niggas?
How you niggas livin'?
You all a'ight?
Everything good out here?
What's up, baby?
Good, good, good.
How you feeI, baby?
Chillin'.
Got that money for me, man?
I gotta make moves.
Yeah, I got it,
but not all of it, yo.
What you mean,
you ain't finished?
I got robbed, yo.
Park it around the block!
Around the block, man!
The fuck you mean you got
robbed, man? Who robbed you?
Got robbed, man.
That nigga, Duff.
Nigga Duff?
Let this nigga Duff up on you,
man, and take your shit?
And my piece, man.
You had your fuckin' gun
on you, man?
What the fuck is
wrong with y'all niggas?
You niggas stand out here
like the Three Stooges
of Harlem or somethin', B.?
You gonna let this nigga
come and take your shit?
Aren't you a motherfuckin' man?
You wanna let another man
take your shit, B.?
You done lost your privilege
of getting any money, man,
untiI you show me
where that man is at.
UntiI you find that man,
you dead up here, man. You dead.
A'ight? You hear what
the fuck I'm sayin', man?
Now, get the fuck
off my stoop, man.
Go ahead, man.
Go find that man, B.
Go find him, B., unless
you like being broke, nigga.
Go this way, man.
Hey, my man, go this way, man.
Go that way, man.
Them niggas don't seem
to understand me out here, B.
Nobody playing games
on these streets, man.
Y'all niggas better hold it down
out here, a'ight?
Them niggas gonna be lookin' for
motherfucking work in Queens
or some shit like that, man.
This is Harlem, man. Y'all
niggas better hold it down, B.
Y'all don't know nothin'
about this.
Things really got hot in Harlem
when "Scarface" came to town.
It was like niggas love
seein' a poor-ass Cuban
just blow up
to be the man all by himself.
You wait for me.
I coming back.
Call police!
What the fuck you lookin' at?
Come on.
You wanna fuck with me?
Okay.
You... cockroaches.
Come on.
You wanna play games?
You wanna play rough?!
Okay.
Say hello to my little friend!
You want more?!
Mitch backed up his words
and ended up doing some time.
Now I'm all by myself
in the game,
just like Scarface.
What's up, old man?
What's going on
over here, man?
Man, bust it.
You ain't taking my messages
or something?
Keisha didn't call?
I dropped some tickets
behind this counter,
and this is what I find.
Is this yours...
or you keepin' it
for a friend?
Man, it ain't even like that,
Mr. Pip.
Well, then,
what's it like, Ace?
It really ain't none
of your business what it's like.
It's my store.
Anything up in here
is my business.
You don't have to worry
about that.
I'm gonna take that
out of here.
I got a life of my own.
Oh, check you out.
I guess you know somethin' about
the game Calvin didn't, huh?
Ace, you better say something
to me if you wanna stay here,
'cause, see, I ain't doing
these type of favors for no...
I'm missing one of my tapes.
You seen my tape?
Yeah, you been wantin'
to get out of here.
Fine, fuck it, then.
Take your ass home.
I want my $ 75 on Friday.
What you gonna do with $ 75,
Kingpin?
Hey, June.
Yeah, hold on a minute.
Hey, Ace. How you doin'?
I'm good.
Your mama ask you
to come pick up something?
Nah.
Oh, so what's going on, honey?
You wanna make some money?
Yeah.
Come on in.
Yo. Check this out.
How many bottles is this?
2,000.
Damn. 2,000 bottles?
That's a lot of
motherfuckin' bottles, man.
$ 100 a bottle, man,
this shit ain't gonna
never sell fast enough.
All that for $50?
Yo, man, this shit weak
or somethin', man?
- Don't sell me no...
- Hey, man, you know me, man.
This the best product
in town, man.
Don't insult me. Here.
Man, fuck it, man.
Give me two of them Jones.
You trippin'.
Yeah, I was trippin', a'ight,
but I was gettin' money...
talkin' 'bout reaI money.
Bottle this shit up quick, man.
See, other dealers
were selling it
at the highest price
they could get.
I sold it cheaper,
so I was sellin' it faster.
I sold it so cheap,
I started
taking their customers away.
See, I was wholesale
on the streets, you understand?
Hey, Lucky,
you want something to drink?
Don't call me Lucky, I said.
Whatever, Lucky.
What you drinkin'?
Fillin' this all the way up.
Now, in the end,
I made more money,
and Lulu always got his return
when he wanted it.
But I wasn't trying to keep shit
all to myself, see.
I- I wasn't tryin'
to get on the stage,
and I didn't want
people hatin'.
I put people on, understand?
Streets was happy.
Everybody could eat.
Yeah, dealin' was a'ight.
Oooh.
Put this in there for me, man.
Damn, B.!
Hey, yo!
What you doin', man?
Yo, come on, man.
You watchin' that ass...
count that cash so we can
get up out of here, man.
In lockup,
brothers always heard
what was goin' on
on the outside,
especially when
it involve money.
And they knew Mitch
was first in line
to get put on when he got out.
Have you been
keepin' it tight for me?
Yo! Hurry up off the phone,
nigga!
Wait.
Hold on a second, B.
- Did you hear what I just said?
- What the fuck?
I'm talkin' to you, nigga.
Oh, shit!
Yo!
Oh!
Come on!
10 niggas jumped the nigga,
fams.
10 niggas pounded him out,
stomped the shit
out of this nigga, man.
A- A-And then this other
Panamanian-type of dude...
I don't even know...
he had, like, 10 razors
in his ass, man.
He takes it out his ass,
he's... give a nigga a buck 50
across his face, man,
blood everywhere,
shit gushin',
C.O.'s not even comin',
lettin' the whole shit
go down, man.
What's up
with your peoples, man?
- Hey, but, yo.
- Go ahead.
What was, um, what was
the Puerto Rican kid's name?
Rico, Chico, some... Mico...
some shit.
He from the East Side, man.
You know him.
He be poppin' willies, man,
selling coke,
always fuckin' with the bitches,
think he a pretty nigga.
You know...
you know that nigga, man.
You know him.
He sell a lot of coke, man.
When you get out, man?
Shit, man.
I don't even know, man.
We gonna keep that on the low,
'cause I ain't seen you,
you ain't seen me, a'ight, Ace?
Ahhh, speciaI.
You stay cool
like how you be cool, a'ight?
- No doubt, baby.
- A'ight. Water.
Yo, I'm Rico, man,
how you doin', G.?
Just wanna say good lookin'
on that little situation
back there.
Oh, that shit back there
was nothin', man.
Anything you need, let me know.
That's why I'm here, B.
Good lookin', man.
Yeah, definitely, man.
Hey, yo,
let me get an extra water, B.
Good. Thank you, man.
Where you from, B.?
Oh, I'm from everywhere,
baby...
Bronx, Brooklyn, Queens,
Uptown, Downtown...
Oh, yeah?
You from everywhere, huh?
It's early.
It's only midnight?
30.
Damn.
Who that?
Hmm?
Who's that?
I don't know this number.
Oh, you don't know
the number, huh?
Here come the bullshit.
Unh-unh.
Can I get
two more grape sodas?
Get on over here.
No, don't come over here.
I'm serious.
You got the sauce
all on your cheeks.
Oh, yeah,
now you wanna be all on me.
When we was in the club,
you was dashin' out.
What was up with that?
What you mean
what was up with me at the club?
The club ain't my scene.
I like to go to the club,
take care of my business,
talk to the people
I need to talk to,
put it down like that.
Everybody checkin' you, checkin'
me, all flashy and shit.
That's not my thing.
You're just borin', that's all.
That's all.
I ain't that boring.
Oooh, oooh.
I really ain't that boring.
Big shit. What, I'm supposed to
take this and go shopping?
If I'm so borin', then,
what...
you know, why you with me?
First of all,
I ain't impressed by that.
I'm with you
'cause I'm borin', too.
A'ight?
Give me that money back
and give me a kiss.
Mmm.
Word to mother, man.
She's feelin' good.
Word.
Yo. Yo, these guys have been
lookin' for you all day.
I don't know
these motherfuckers, man.
Yo, Ace, right?
Yeah, man.
What's goin' on, baby?
Yo, I hear you got that butter.
You holdin'?
You know me, man, or somebody?
I don't think you know me, man,
you know what I'm sayin'?
I think somebody been misleadin'
you, you know what I mean?
Ah, come on, man.
Look at you.
Got this European joint
all done up,
all rimmed out
and everything..
Hey, yo, my man...
me and my man right now,
we chillin' right here.
We tryin' to build right here
inside of here.
I don't know nothin' about what
you talkin' about, understand?
Yo.
We'll meet up again, right?
Different time,
different circumstances?
Yeah, maybe it'll be love next
time, you know what I'm sayin'?
A'ight.
Maybe.
Corny motherfuckers, man.
Got the silent routine,
his boy with him and shit.
Something was up
with those cats.
They was either stickup kids
or the feds.
Either way,
I wasn't fuckin' with 'em.
Hey, yo, Lulu?
Moneybags?
The messengers.
With $2,000.
Yes, Pedro.
I know you didn't hear it.
I know.
But...
Excuse me, um...
What's going on?
Do you know this man?
No, um...
but I'm here about Lulu.
Lulu... uh...
He... somebody killed him.
You know, I found him.
Why come here?
Well, it being that,
you know,
me and him, we did a lot
of business together, right?
So, one time
he brought me here before,
so that's why I came here.
Hmm.
How much in the bag?
200 long.
200?
Why didn't you keep it?
Damn.
Nah.
I ain't like that, man.
Know what I mean?
Oh, um...
Eduardo... calm.
Not here, man.
Calm yourself, Eduardo.
What you got there?
It's just some stuff
that I, you know...
What?
It's Lulu.
Eh?
He likes the rocks.
Luis Lujano.
Yeah,
cash is too bulky for him.
ReaI estate and rocks...
that's his game.
Hmm. So, let me
get this straight...
you just gonna give me
all this stuff.
Why? I mean,
it's not my birthday.
I'm saying I sold a lot for him,
you know what I mean?
And, uh...
maybe we go on.
Oh.
Can you handle 10 keys
all by yourself?
Yeah.
Good.
See, the thing
about the game is,
the shit don't stop.
You could be hurt,
and it don't matter.
Business will still
roll up on you.
Hey, yo. Yo, yo, yo.
What's up, man?
Rico buggin' out.
Oh!
Holy shit.
My nigga.
That's my nigga.
What up, B.?
What's happening?
- What's up?
- You're Ace, right?
Huh?
Yeah, no doubt, baby.
It's a navy blue Beemer, huh?
Yeah.
Doin' your thing, man.
Gold BBS's, '87.
'87 joint, huh?
Word.
Hey, yo, man,
I'm Mitch's man, B.
You got any problems, man,
let me know, man, a'ight?
Yeah, no doubt.
We'll talk.
We gonna talk, B.
We definitely
gonna do some business, B.
When Mitch get out,
me, you, and Mitch
gonna do some business.
What's up, my nigga?
- Home!
- I'm home, baby.
- Yeah!
- Yo, yo, yo.
Nobody can't hold you.
Listen, give this to Mitch.
Yeah, that's
the little punk there.
Got little man
giving me bricks of money now?
Hey, what you doin'
over here, man?
Y'all doin' things
while a nigga gone?
Check this girI out!
You all right?
I'm good.
Yo, baby.
Glad to be home, man.
Yeah, man.
Glad to see you, man.
I been hearin' wonderfuI things
about you, man.
- Oh, yeah?
- No lie about that, man.
I see you got
your little jeweI shining,
got a beeper now...
got a beeper now.
Nigga got a Rolex now.
What you doin', B.?
Yeah, yeah, no doubt.
And that's lookin' very fresh.
Very fresh.
Yeah?
I see you
doin' good things, B.
- You like that?
- Love that.
That's my style right there.
Hold onto that, man.
It is your style,
you know what I'm sayin'?
Ain't quite my style.
This nigga here.
- Little somethin', kid.
- That's my man.
Word, man, word, man.
No doubt.
Yo, but on the reaI...
hey, man.
You wanna hook a nigga up,
man?
Hook me up with some of them
keys I been hearin' about,
you know what I'm sayin'?
- I got you, man.
- Back, baby.
You know what I'm sayin'?
Your nigga's back, man.
- A'ight?
- Let's do this.
- I got you.
- Do this.
Let's see
what this lookin' like.
See what the hell's
going on with this here, man.
Let's see
how the engine sounds, Ace.
You understand, making sure
you ain't, you know...
...to my nigga Mitch back home
for beatin' that murder rap.
Can't keep a good nigga down.
Yeah, we get money...
Uptown style, a'ight?
It felt good
to be rollin' through Harlem
top down
and Mitch at the wheeI.
I just wanted
to get my man set up
and back where he belong...
on the stage.
The Maximas, the Jettas...
don't know how we do the roll.
We got a lot of things
poppin' off, yo.
poppin' off.
Feelin' good out here.
How you doin'?
I saw your man, man.
I talked to your man, um...
Panamanian, Puerto Rican cat.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, I seen him.
Talked to him.
He came up on me.
Oh, uh, Rico.
I had a little confrontation
in there, you know.
He definitely did, uh,
come through, man, you know.
Not sayin' that a nigga
ain't gonna handle
what a nigga gotta handle,
you know.
He definitely did,
but at the same time...
you know, the nigga definitely
did show me some love, so...
thinkin' that, you know,
it might be good...
you know, maybe we could throw
him in there somewhere,
you know, I don't know.
We might be able to use...
you know, it's up to you,
you know what I'm sayin'?
Hey, Mitch,
how much this cost?
Man, why you worried about
how much those cost?
You 'bout
to buy a car or somethin'?
Yo...
So, when you gonna
take me to the club?
Come on, little man,
you don't need to be
up in no club.
I just wanna see it.
Well, Uncle Ice say y'all in
there throwin' your cash around,
lookin' all fly.
Let me tell you something,
little man... fuck Ice.
Don't be listenin' to Ice.
You hear what I'm sayin'?
Look at me, man.
Ice ain't no reaI man.
A reaI man
handles his business.
takes care of his family.
Ice don't do none of that.
You understand?
The only thing you need to be
concerned with right now
is going to schooI.
- That's it, a'ight?
- A'ight.
- A'ight?
- You ready to be a big man?
- Yeah.
Come sit
in the front seat, man.
A'ight?
Mr. Mitch, man, I've been
lookin' all over for you, man.
How you doin'?
- I'm chillin'.
- Good.
Life is good, man.
I can tell.
Cherry Beemer, huh?
This next year's shit?
You know how I do, man.
Shit is hot right here, man.
I seen you and A. up at
55th 10, the Porsches up, man.
Happy you back in business, man,
you're doin' your thing, man.
I'm hearin' life is good
for you, too, man.
You know, cats is tellin' me
you're doin' your thing
on the East Side,
so I guess that situation with
A. is workin' out pretty good.
Listen, man, you know
I'm gonna do my thing.
I'm gonna eat regardless.
That don't mean nothing
but trou... I been down in D.C.
D.C. is definitely
ready for us, man.
D.C. is it.
I'm tellin' you, man.
Mitch, look at me.
D.C.
D.C. is it.
We need to make that happen.
Yo, you spoke to A. about that?
I mean, you know,
I spoke to A., but A. is A.
You know, he runnin' around,
tellin' me
get with him later on...
you know how it is.
But we need to make
the D.C. thing happen.
I'm gonna talk to him, B.
I'm gonna talk to him.
- That's why I love you.
- I'll talk to him.
That's why I love you.
Good lookin' out, man.
I appreciate that, man.
Good lookin' out.
That your little man
right there?
- What up, little man?
- What's up, man?
- You a'ight?
- Yeah!
Little motherfucker
need a medallion
'round that
big-ass head of his, B.
But, Mitch, get with me, man.
D.C. is it, man,
Holler at me, man.
Rico came through,
acting all excited and all that,
talkin' 'bout he ready
to expand or somethin'.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
What you think about that, B.?
- Expand like what?
- I don't know.
I didn't really get to talk
to him too much about it.
He talkin' 'bout he wanna go
to D.C. or somethin',
he got a connection in D.C.
or somethin'.
No, man. No, man.
I ain't goin' nowhere, man.
That's what I'm sayin'...
you know, Harlem, man.
Showin' us love here.
No doubt.
Life is good in Harlem, baby.
# I can feeI it
comin' in the air tonight #
# Oh, Lord #
# I've been waiting
for this moment #
# For all my life #
# Oh, Lord #
# I can feeI it
in the air tonight #
# Oh, Lord #
# Well, I've been waitin'
for this moment #
# For all my life #
# Oh, Lord #
# I can feeI it
comin' in the air tonight #
# Oh, Lord #
Yo, remember me, junior?
What's up, baby? You out?
Yeah, but fuck all that, man.
I heard you top dog now.
Yeah, man,
know what I'm sayin'?
- Live and maintain.
- Yeah?
This nigga maintaining.
Niggas all over the world
tellin' me you runnin'
the neighborhood.
Walk with me over here, man.
Yeah.
I'll be back.
Hey, yo.
Y'all hold on, man.
Yeah.
Hey, you know
I'm gonna handle this, right?
I mean, you know how I was.
Yeah, but, you know,
that was then.
Now, see, listen...
this how it's gonna go down.
Look, I'm gonna set you up
with a little corner,
you know what I...
you understand what I'm sayin'?
But, um, I'm gonna
let my man work it.
So, all you gotta do,
Calvin, man,
is just lay low
and make this money.
Yeah, come on, baby.
You know
I don't relax with the help.
You know how I get down.
And if... I'm sayin',
look at you, though, man.
- This is... God.
- Come on, man. You understand.
Junior doin' his thing.
Ace.
Just call me "Ace. "
You're about to get your
motherfuckin' head slapped off
your motherfuckin' shoulders,
bitch.
Wait right here, man.
Hey, yo, B.
What's up, B.?
This nigga, Wedge,
one of your workers, man?
Word. So, what's up, D.?
They sayin' he was tryin'
to set you up, B.
- Come on, man.
- Hey, man, come find...
Hey, yo, bring this bitch-ass
nigga over here, B.
I know this nigga ain't tryin'
to set me up. What's up, man?
You feedin' this motherfucker,
too, man.
- Fuck.
- Hey, yo, what's going on, man?
I'm hearin' things, man.
- Both hands down, man.
- Put your fuckin' hands down.
Everything ain't all right,
man?
I ain't eatin'!
You ain't eatin'?
What you mean you ain't...
You ain't
makin' this paper, man?
Everybody eats, B.
Man, fuck this nigga, man.
Don't look me in my
motherfuckin' face like that.
Man, fuck this nigga.
Turn around, matter of fact.
Fuck this nigga, B.
Turn around. Move up.
Stay still, motherfucker.
Ah!
Get your ass out of here,
motherfucker.
Hey, yo, B...
Hey, yo, A., man,
that's what the fuck will happen
to anybody disre...
Put that away, man.
You're right, you're right,
you're right.
But that's what the fuck
will happen to anybody
who disrespect this family,
man.
Me and you is family.
I'm not gonna let
that shit slide, B.
If I hear somethin' goin' on,
I'm gonna handle it, B.
'Cause niggas
not gonna disrespect,
when my niggas
feeI the same way, B.
And that's what's gonna
fuckin' happen to anybody
who disrespects you, B.
I love you, B. Anything, B.
Let me know, man.
- All right, baby.
- A'ight?
Look out. Let this nigga
get in the whip, man.
Let me know, man.
You got it, baby.
The chain, B.?
Oh, got your man.
You're shinin' now, nigga.
You good now.
You good now, nigga.
You a ice nigga, we good.
A'ight?
Where the fuck is the flash at?
Where the fuck is the flash?
Take the fuckin' picture
right, man.
Get it right!
Hey, what's goin' on, dog?
It's good, man?
Poppin'!
Lookin' good, D.
Chillin', man,
you know my peoples, man.
- Y'all met already.
- What's up, man?
- He's family, coz.
- Yo, man.
Yeah, we met up on that ride.
Know what I mean?
Yo, sorry 'bout all that,
you know?
I wasn't tryin' to get up
all on you or nothin' like that.
You know, hope there's no hard
feelings or anything like that.
In my part of D.C.,
it's just not poppin',
so I thought I'd come to you.
A'ight.
What's goin' on?
I got his number,
so you can holler at him
when you get a chance,
know what I mean?
My peoples. My peoples.
Yo, by the way, you got a price
in on them things?
Yeah, man, I got your number,
you know what I'm sayin'?
A'ight, man.
I'll give you a call.
A'ight, dog.
It's all good, man.
A'ight.
What you doin', cousin?
Hey, why your family act
so motherfuckin' nervous, man?
- They're my peoples, man.
- Nigga act like the feds.
Let's take
the motherfuckin' picture.
That's how you fuck, nigga.
You see?
I hit her with
the "Doug E." shit right there.
You see it?
You see it right there?
- Do you see it?
We got it goin' on.
You know how we do...
a'ight, here we go.
This is the greatest stuff.
What's happenin', baby?!
Nigga, you see.
You see, right?
Do you see?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, yo, man.
You really don't have to be
out here like this,
broadcasting
all your fuckin' porno shit
and takin' your pictures puttin'
your guns in the air, man.
You drawin' too much
motherfuckin' attention.
Nigga, that's what I do, man.
I'm livin'.
What you doin'?
Nigga, I'm definitely
fuckin' livin' with you, B.
You understand what I'm sayin'?
I'm just doin' my shit
on the low side, you know?
- Oh.
- You know what I'm sayin'?
No, A., what are you sayin'?
Throw that ass back!
I'm sayin'...
live and maintain.
Maintain?
My niggas is maintainin',
and we gettin' money, so...
What are you
really sayin', A.?
I'm sayin'
you keep shit cool, nigga.
Everybody's gonna eat.
Everybody gonna get this money.
Everybody can be happy.
We don't have to be on
Front Street all the time, baby.
Okay, take it easy, man.
Keep your voice down, man.
Niggas ain't gonna talk.
Hey, yo, A., man,
niggas been talkin', man.
You know,
I'm with y'all niggas
'cause I'm lovin' this shit
and everything, B.
But niggas wanna position
theyselves to make other moves.
Half of these niggas
wanna be the man "just 'cause. "
AII I'm sayin', A...
I'm not everybody, B.
Know what I mean?
But everybody do need to check
out that nigga right there,
'cause he's gettin' money
and pussy.
And niggas need to be gettin'
it just like that, A.,
in that position
right there...
on video and shit.
Funny-ass nigga, man.
You ain't even seen
when I put my leg up.
Don't forget to pick up
on them... y'all.
Got it right here
in the deejay booth.
Yo, man, let me talk to
you for a minute.
...on the roller skates,
my man.
...on the roller skates.
Keep it movin'.
Let's go. Whoo!
You should've said
somethin' to him.
Yo, what's up with your man?
Who... Rico?
No, I'm talking about this kid
you got running my block for me.
I mean, he's cool and all that.
Don't get me wrong.
Kind of reminds me of you
when you was out here
runnin' 'round broke.
But the point is,
I don't fuckin' need him.
You hot.
- I'm hot?
- Yeah, nigga, you hot.
You just got out the joint,
understand what I'm sayin'?
The cops are watching you.
Yes, you hot.
Come on, A.,
what you take me for, man?
Your man Mitch
just got out of jaiI.
Is you schooling him
like this, too?
I don't have to do that
with him, man.
Y- You just need
to lay low, man.
That's all you gotta do.
I'm hookin' you up.
H- How is you hookin' me up?
How I'm hookin' you up?
Nigga, you got money
in your fuckin' pocket?
I'll deaI the block.
It's my block.
No.
You can't do that,
'cause if you get
fuckin' busted,
you fuckin'
all of my shit up.
You understand that?
And I ain't havin' that.
You better have this the way
I'm givin' this to you,
or you can step.
Man, fuck him.
He don't get shit anyway.
I mean, who the fuck is this
Kermit the Frog-face ass nigga
right here, B.?
Co, co, co, co, co.
- Slap the shit out you, B.
- Hold on, hold on, Rico.
Who the fuck is this nigga?
Co, hold on
one motherfuckin' second, man.
I said I got it
over here, man. Thank you.
You know what, A.?
I see you out here,
you're doin' your thing
with your man, and that's cool.
He's a funny guy
and all that.
So, I'm gonna step, a'ight?
But I'll see you later.
Fuck out of here, man.
Bitch.
Man, I keep tellin' you
the same fuckin' thing
about things, man.
You always tellin' me, man?
What the fuck is the use havin'
soldiers if you can't use 'em?
That's why I'm Rico.
That's why I do what I do, man.
Mmm. What's up, baby?
Nothin'.
Mm-hmm.
So, when we gonna
have this kid?
As soon as you start spendin'
more time with me.
Now you're stressin' me?
Come on, baby.
It's just...
this is the last time
we gonna have alone,
and you just visitin' already.
Did I say
I was gonna be there?
Yes.
Okay.
It's gonna be fine, baby.
It's gonna be a nice, fine,
boring life.
Sonny.
Sonny, come on.
Get up, man.
What you doin' here?
Huh? What you doin' here?
I fa... fa... fall asleep.
Where's Mommy?
I think she left.
She left?
Sonny?
Who you talkin' to?
Come on, man.
Go on to the room, okay?
Go ahead.
Hey, Sonny, you hear me
talkin' to you, man.
Well...
Moneymakin' Mitch.
High roller come to visit.
What the fuck
you doin' here, Ice?
Hmm? You live here?
I don't think you do, B.
The fuck you talkin'...
fuck off me, man.
Yo!
I'm tired of seeing you
comin' through them doors, man.
You in here,
livin' off my moms,
you gettin' high
in front of Sonny, man?!
Don't fuckin' come back
no more!
You understand that?!
Hey, baby, you the one
sold me the drugs
I'm gettin' high on.
Come on.
Yo, don't fuckin'
walk away from me, nigga.
I sold you those drugs
so that you could make money,
you forgetfuI motherfucker!
You got high,
so you fucked up, nigga.
- Oh, I fucked...
- You!
I fucked up?
Yeah, you fucked up!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You fucked up!
What, you think bringing
a couple bags of groceries
in here means somethin'?
You ain't supportin' shit.
You got a pocketfuI of money!
You won't even give your mama
no reaI money!
Hey, what about Sonny?
Aw, you so worried
about Sonny.
Oh, that's right.
He gonna follow
in your footsteps.
Moneymakin' Sonny.
Ungh!
I better not ever see
your fuckin' ass
walk through these doors
again!
- You understand me?!
- All right, yeah.
Let me tell you
somethin'...
you, Tommy, the rest of them
bum-ass niggas at the store
are dead on the streets.
You ain't never gonna see
none of my money. Never!
You understand that?
Get the fuck out of here!
Get the fuck out!
And give me
them fuckin' keys, man.
Give me the fuckin' keys.
Get the fuck out of here
and you better not forget it.
I see you again, Ice,
I gonna fuckin' kill you.
Fuck.
Sonny?
Come here, man.
Come here.
I'm sorry about that,
all right?
I'm sorry about that, man.
Don't worry, man.
We gonna get out of here,
all right?
$5 down on this?
Right now.
Peace. What up, man?
What's up, man?
You a'ight?
Chillin', man.
Word.
Know what, A., man?
I think I need
to go out tonight, man.
All right?
Meet me at the top.
We're gonna party for reaI.
Everything a'ight?
Everything's cool, man.
You know, I just need to be
around some love, that's all.
- You a'ight?
- I'm chillin'.
All right,
well, come around here, baby.
Come on the other side
of this gate.
I'll show you some love, Mitch.
Come on, Dick. Come on, Dick.
Get out of here,
you sweatin'- ass nigga.
You wanna see some love?
It's love day.
I'm showin' people love
out here on the court.
You ain't ready for me, A.
I got you. I got you
right here in the pocket.
- All right?
- All right, my nigga.
Do something,
you bum-ass nigga!
I'm sayin' y'all got to know
who's coming to the stage
to represent.
Are y'all ready to rock
or what?!
All right,
without any further ado,
we want to bring
to the Rooftop stage
the one, the only,
the world's greatest...
Doug E. Fresh!
Everybody from the Rooftop
make some noise!
# I wanted this to be speciaI,
something more #
# Than any other feeling
that you felt before #
# Pushin' through the doors
I see girls havin' a good time #
# I might say a rhyme #
# Old schooI, new schooI
no schooI rule, baby #
# But other than that,
everything is cool #
# I see guys and girls dancin',
doin' the new dances #
# Kissin' while
I'm over here romancin' #
# You ain't sh...
no need to curse #
# Ask me who she is
and let me tell you first #
# Slow down, be cool,
and don't act ill #
# I came to have a good time,
party and chill with you #
# But plans are made to be
broken, smokin' #
# I'm not jokin', try to dis me
and I will give you a token #
# We're the type of people
that can't be stopped #
# And no matter what
we're gonna #
# Keep... keep...
keep risin' to the top #
Let me hear you say
"Ho! Ho!"
Ho! Ho!
Say "Ho! Ho!"
Ahh!
Make the shot there, baby.
That's all, Mitch.
Mitch!
Ah, nigga, that's all.
Give me my money.
Bet it right back.
But double up.
Right here, man.
What the fuck you mean?
This is...
I ain't giving him his food.
Hello?
Get the fuck up, motherfucker!
Get the fuck up!
What you waitin' for, man?
Ohh!
Open the fuckin' safe, nigga!
Do what they say, Ace.
Open up
the motherfuckin' safe, man.
It's too dark in here, man.
What the fuck?
I can't even see the...
Yo, get this nigga
some light.
Come on, man.
Open this fuckin' safe.
Yo, Calvin, man,
why you doing this to me?
- I can tell that's you.
- Well, fuck all that!
Shut the... fuck up!
Fuckin' asking me "Why this?"
Or "Why that?"
Now, you think I'm playin'?
Leave him alone! Please!
You think I'm playin'?!
Open that fuckin' safe, man!
Look at me.
No!
I said look at me!
You think I'm some
Kermit motherfucker now? Huh?
Listen, man,
don't fuckin' do this, man.
You think I'm fuckin' playin'?
Open the safe!
Hold on, man!
Now, next time
I ain't gonna miss.
A'ight?
There ain't even no money
in this safe, man.
There ain't shit in here.
I got 100 grand at the crib.
Look at this nigga
playing games.
There ain't no money
in the safe.
I can't see
with fuckin' blood in my eyes.
Get his ass up out of here.
- Fuck!
- Take his ass home.
Clean him up.
Get up, man!
Get in there, man.
I told you, I'm not playin'.
Shut the fuck up!
What's
the fuckin' combination? Huh?
Shut up with that cryin' shit!
I'm not trying to hear that!
What's the fuckin' combination?
# It's up to three #
What...
M- M-Motherfucker!
Aah!
# I'll be yours,
and you'll be mine #
She was 7 pounds...
and her daddy survived.
Only God and love
could have kept me breathing
after all those bullets.
I told myself when I could
breathe without a tube
I was gonna breathe deep.
What's up?
Nigga needs some work, man.
What's goin' on?
Ain't nothin' pumpin'
right now, B.
Come on, man.
I know y'all got something.
Fuck, is you deaf, man?
I said we ain't got shit
goin' on right now, B.
So a nigga's supposed to starve
'cause your man got shot?
- What?
- Damn!
What's that, partner?
Calvin must got you niggas
shook.
Calvin?
What, you one of Calvin...
what the fuck?
Is you
one of Calvin's hoes, man?
Get that nigga
out of the car, man.
Get that bitch out of the car.
- Get the fuck up.
- Shit.
Get up. Do you know
what Calvin did?
- Come on, man. Don't do this.
- Get the fuck undressed.
Everything!
What the fuck are you...
- Your sneakers, too!
- All right, man.
Next time you talk
about Calvin...
Get off the block!
With me out the game,
shit got dry up on the streets
reaI quick.
Watch your fuckin' mouth
next time!
And Rico
wasn't showin' nobody love.
Bum-ass fuckin' bullshit.
Hey, yo, A.,
niggas get shot every day, B.
You be a'ight, nigga.
You're tough, right?
I'm out, Rico.
You understand what I'm saying?
Look at me.
I've been shot in the head,
baby.
My body different.
I'm breathing different.
You understand
what I'm saying?
The doctor said I wasn't
gonna walk the same.
You understand what I'm saying?
I'm out.
Yo, A., man,
pull your skirt down, B.
The streets is missing you, yo.
Come on, man. What you want...
give all this shit up?
Yo, A., man,
it's like this, man.
We down
on our last bricks, man.
Shit's drying up out there.
You hear me?
Niggas ain't eatin'
on the streets.
Everybody gettin' antsy
out there, baby.
I know what floats A's boat.
Remember this, nigga?
We can go right around
the corner.
Trying pull over to the side
on the street
like I'm some kind of hoe.
You got paper.
Right here.
- What's poppin', Carmen?
- Aah!
A'ight, nigga?
You clean now.
Aah!
That motherfucker's gone.
He's not coming back, B.
I laid the murder game down
letting niggas know
we not fuckin' around, man.
Let's just cool, yo.
What the fuck
are you doing, man?
Do you even know
what you're doing, man?
Don't have the fuckin' cops
coming up in here
looking for me, man, on account
of some shit you did.
You understand?
Shit is hot.
Then you need to give up the
connect and let us handle shit.
Look, man, we know what's hot
on the streets, man.
Believe me, man.
We out there e'day.
But, yo, man, we just got to
take it easy, man. That's it.
I mean, it's like what the fuck
are we waiting for, B.?
You know your connects
on the other motherfuckers.
We wastin' time.
And there's crack shit
movin' in.
You know what?
You just need
a little more rest, B.
Cover up.
Get you some soup.
Some tea.
Come on, man.
You're talking crazy, B.
Hey, yo, check here your man.
Give him a thermometer, take his
temperature or something, man.
I'm outta here, Mitch.
Peace, baby.
Still got the flash of that gun
in my head, man...
that white light.
And it was like that light, man,
was sayin'...
"You're dead. "
A., you ain't got to be
thinking about that, man.
You here. You blessed.
A'ight, baby?
You blessed.
Seeing that light
for a long time.
Gettin' this money.
Trying to stay, you know,
trying to stay
up out the light,
up out the spotlight,
the club,
and all that kind of stuff,
man.
Trying to hide.
Trying to, you know...
But it's all fake.
Understand what I'm sayin'?
This life...
this game...
there ain't no love in it.
It don't love you back.
No. I feeI ya, A.
I do, man.
But see, man,
a nigga like me, man,
I love the game.
I love the hustle, man.
I be feelin' like one of them
ball-playin' niggas, you know?
Like Bird or Magic
or something.
Yeah,
you know a nigga got dough.
A nigga
could leave the league.
But if I leave,
the fans
still gonna love me, man?
I get love out here
in Harlem, man.
I done sold coke
on these streets, man...
hash, weed, heron.
As long as niggas
is feeling it,
a nigga like me can hustle it.
That's my gift in life, A.
You know?
What? What the fuck
you laughing at, B.?
You, man.
You're funny, man. You're
a hustling motherfucker, man.
For reaI, baby.
You're fuckin' killin' me,
man.
Come on.
You know me, baby.
Man.
Yo. I'm gonna hook you up
with that connect, man.
I'm gonna put in a word. You
just gotta give me some time.
Man,
you just take all the time.
You just get better, baby.
A'ight?
Definitely.
Yeah, what up? Who this?
Wait, wait, wait. What?
Wait, calm down.
Calm down, first of...
What...
A'ight, I'm coming home,
a'ight?
Just take it easy.
I'm gonna be there in a minute.
What's up, Ma?
What's going on?
Huh?
Sonny here yet? Sonny!
Mitch.
What the fuck is th...
Who gave this to you?
What's this...
a joke or something?
Where's this nigga Ice?
You told him not to come here!
What is he supposed...
Look, I know
what I told him to do.
Look, did he tell you anything?
Does he know anything?
No, Mitch! Shit!
Just pay the guy!
What are you talkin' about?
Who gave this to you?
Where's all the money
you have? Huh?
Look, look, look. Stop talking
about my money, all right?
No. I'm going to the cops.
Look, let me find out
what's going on first!
- I didn't do anything!
- Just calm down. Calm down!
Get away.
Look, he's probably on
42nd Street playing video games
or something like that,
all right?
Let me just take care of it.
Let me look and see what's
going on out there first.
All right? Calm down.
Yo, A., Sonny's gone, man.
- What?
- Yo, somebody took him, man.
What you mean
somebody took him?
Na, this shit is reaI, B.
They dropped off a note, man,
asking for money, man.
Who? Who?
Look, they want $500,000 or they
gonna kill him or something.
That's what they said, man.
Shit. $500,000.
W- W...
I only got 120 thou on me
right now... cash.
A., I need that connect, man.
I need to get these keys, man,
so I can get this money
for Sonny's ransom fee.
Yeah, listen,
slow down a second, man.
You know what I mean?
I- I-I got you. I got you.
You know what I'm saying?
'Cause this ain't for him, A.
This ain't for him, man.
Right.
They jerked him, man.
They fuckin' jerked him, man.
They sent me his finger
in an envelope, man...
all bloody and shit.
I don't know
what to do, A. I don't, man.
I feeI naked out here, B.
I'm thinking about
how they got Sonny...
in some abandoned building
or some basement
just fuckin' bleedin', man.
He's dyin', man.
They're killin'
my little man, B.
I'm about to beat on
some reaI murder shit, A.
I'm telling you, man.
Any nigga that ever
looked at me wrong,
owes me money,
or ever said
any jealous bullshit about me
is fuckin' dead.
You understand what the fuck
I'm saying, A.?
They're fuckin' dead, man.
I don't give a fuck
about nothing, man.
But I need
my little man back, B.
I need him back, man.
I'm dead out here, man.
I can't function.
I can't, B.
There's 22 keys.
14 of them for Sonny.
8 of them I kept.
Sell those,
pay this connect back.
It's in the bag,
you know what I mean?
Yeah. A'ight.
Listen...
Fuckin' hear anything, man.
You understand?
You got what you need?
Yeah.
Let me know, man.
'Cause that's my motherfuckin'
little man, too, man.
Let me know.
It's gonna be a'ight.
It's gonna be a'ight, man.
Gonna get him back, man.
No doubt, man.
Keisha?
What's wrong?
Fuck.
They found Sonny?
No. Not Sonny.
They found Mitch.
He got... he got shot
in the head, baby.
He's dead.
What?
He's dead!
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Oh.
What?!
Fuck!
AII I had left of Mitch
was his voice in my head
saying that he was gonna meet up
with Rico that night.
You good?
You know I got all my niggas
lookin' for the little nigga
now, B.
Sonny like
my little brother, too.
Anything you need,
let me know.
Good lookin', baby,
'cause I need your help, Ric.
I need you to help me sell
these 14 keys
so I can get this ransom money
for Sonny, man.
You got 14 bricks
right there?
Yeah.
Who'd you off... A.?
Yeah, man, but look, B.
Once we get my little brother
back, man,
we right the fuck back on,
baby.
We right the fuck back on
once I get Sonny.
It's gonna be business...
Ugh!
What the fuck?
Hey, yo, A.
What up?
You a'ight, B.?
No, man. Fucked up.
You know I'm fucked up
over this shit, too, B.
I murdered them niggas
who did that shit to Mitch, B.
I'm trying to find out.
I haven't found
any of the damn keys
in that building with Mitch.
Keys?
Yeah, I gave Mitch a set of keys
to get Sonny back, man.
I know he had the fuckin' keys
in there with him, man.
Now, you know, I got to get
the money or the keys, man,
to pay this connect back with.
Hey, yo, B., why you ain't
callin' me on that shit, B.?
You know I would have went
with that nigga Mitch
and made that shit happen
for you.
I know, I know, man.
That's on me. I fucked up.
You talk to Mitch yesterday?
I ain't talked to Mitch
or see that nigga
the whole goddamn day
yesterday, B.
What happened to your face,
man?
What?
I said, "What happened
to your face?"
This shit?
I was fuckin' with this
wild-ass bitch last night.
You know how I play, B.
That's wild, boy.
You a wild motherfucker, man.
- Yeah.
- You videotape that shit?
You think you know me
and shit, man.
I ain't tape that shit
last night, B.
I kept another set of keys,
understand?
To sell for when the ransom
was paid.
Now, look,
the way shit is now, man,
it's too hot
out on the streets
for me to be caught
with myself
trying to go out there
and conduct something.
I'm gonna need you
to do me this.
I want you to sell these keys
for me.
Give me the money,
I can pay it to the connect.
You know what I'm sayin'?
Then I take you in there,
introduce you to the connect.
So you want me to sell
all the keys?
Yeah. It's like this.
I been talking to these kids
from out of town
who say, you know,
they'd take these keys...
Buy them at a higher price
than what's goin'.
You understand
what I'm sayin'?
So, you know, all you got to do
is sell them.
Then you take the extra cheese
off the top.
You understand
what I'm sayin'?
Then I can walk away.
We all can walk away set.
And you're cool with that?
I'm cool.
I'm cool with that.
I don't believe you, A.
I mean, you gonna give up
all this shit?
About how much?
Yeah, nigga.
I said I was going.
I wanted out.
Oh, no. I'm gonna need more
than that for sure.
I wasn't playin' when
I said that. You understand?
What's up, man? A'ight?
- A'ight.
- Good.
Let's go up here.
After you.
You're crazy, B.
Nigga fucking giving up.
I love you, B.
Put it down!
Fucking gonna give up
all this shit, man.
Freeze!
Put your hands up!
- You a'ight?
- No. I'm fucked up, man.
Drop the bag!
Anything you need,
let me know, man.
- Down!
- We need an ambulance here.
You lookin' to play no ball,
baby?
Yo, A., call me, B.
Call me, B.
A'ight?
Yeah, I called him.
And I gave him the number
of fake-ass deals
who turned out to be the feds.
See, I knew Rico's greed
would destroy him
and set me free.
I'm sure that he would say
I went out like a punk.
But fuck it.
It's a price I could live with.
I don't like the motherfucker
anyway. I did it.
But 25 to life...
I did that.
Rico can't live with that.
I ain't snitchin' on nobody
from Harlem, man.
I'll give you a couple cats
down in D.C.
doing they thing out of town,
doing they thing,
but, um, I'm not snitchin'
on nobody in Harlem
'cause when I come home,
I'm still gonna be the king.
Meanwhile,
Janet sat by the phone,
but no more calls came.
Mitch had it right about Ice.
His uncle was the one
not looking out for family.
His bitterness
towards his nephew Mitch
was taken out
on his other nephew Sonny...
his own blood.
Stand back.
Tommy did Ice's dirty work.
When the ransom money
didn't come,
he killed Sonny.
The game was over.
All right,
you know what I'm sayin'?
# Throw your hands up #
# Wave 'em around some #
# Wave 'em around, 'round #
# If you want a million dollars,
put your hands up #
# If you like sex,
# And if you want a million
dollars, throw your guns up #
# And if you like sex,
pull your nuts up #
Now there's a new game.
Us old players are gone.
But you can see our story
on music videos
with prop guns
and fake champagne.
I guess you don't have to be
somebody no more.
I guess you can just front
like you somebody you ain't.
I have a family.
Lulu's bag of diamonds made
a down payment on a new life.
As my man Mitch would say...
"Life is good. "
# Put your hands up,
wave them around some #
Maybe I will be
the George Jefferson
of the neighborhood.
# Wave them around, 'round #
I'll get back to you on that.
Like "What?"
Looking down here like...
look at the world like
down here like "What?"
Money, money.
Action!
# Put your hands up...
in divorce court #
# Mr. Media Multi, stage
and screen, "Fit" Magazine #
# The radio, cassettes,
and CDs #
# Put your guns up #
# You know I don't tease,
don't say "please" #
# If you want a million dollars,
put your hands up #
# And if you like sex,
# And if you want a million
dollars, throw your guns up #
# And if you like sex,
pull your nuts up #
# Throw your hands up #
# Wave 'em around some #
# Wave 'em around, 'round #
# Now, if you want a million
dollars, put your hands up #
# And if you like sex,
put your hands up #
# And if you want a million
dollars, throw your guns up #
# And if you like sex,
pull your nuts up #
# Crowd motivator,
the home invader #
# I'm my own bouncer,
bodyguard #
# Alpha, gamma, to the beta,
Darth Vader #
# May the force be with you,
may the Ford hit you #
#... slipping rhymes like... #
# Gymnastics, 21/2 sumi with
a full twist, full pike #
# Want to break my shit?
Give me 5 mics #
# 5 mics, 2 turntables,
20 joints, and... #
#... cause I got
a lot of balls #
# Got guts like...
I'm flying like homing pigeons #
# My own religion...
drunken monkey #
# The... a secret
for keepin' it reaI #
# I'll take a record deaI #
# You started, you starved
like it was... #
# Cut a hit to win,
hit again, win again #
# Hit again, it's great
don't hate, celebrate, yo #
# Throw your hands up #
# Wave 'em around some #
# Wave 'em around, 'round #
# Ladies with
the reaI hair... #
# Put your hands up...
in divorce court #
# Mr. Media Multi, stage
and screen, "Fit" Magazine #
# The radio, cassettes,
and CDs #
# Put your guns up #
# You know I don't tease,
don't say "please" #
# If you want a million dollars,
put your hands up #
# And if you like sex,
# And if you want a million
dollars, throw your guns up #
# Now, you hearing the hot new
shit like this shit here #
# You need to go check out
my man... #
Battle physically.
Conquer mentally.