Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Here you go, miss.
- Thank you.
Step through, please.
Open your laptop, please.
I guess people take their computers
with them everywhere nowadays.
Security blanket.
Lucky blanket.
Next.
Wow, even answer your own door,
senator.
- I'm impressed.
- Front-porch mentality.
I like to know who's visiting.
Plus, my secretary, Laura,
just stepped out for an early lunch.
Caroline Eldridge from
Family First is visiting.
You're early. I like that. Come in.
- Let's take the sofa.
- Okay.
Hope you don't mind if I take
this out.
My hard drive is now officially
my only source of memory...
...and I wanna get all those
old-fashioned values down accurately.
Now, as you know, we're putting
together our Family First brochure...
...and we've got pictures
that we could use captions for.
- Fire away.
- Okay.
Let's start with this one.
That's me and some of the staff
in the Gulf of Mexico after Katrina.
Heartbreaking stuff.
Okay.
Let's call this:
"Senator Sachs and staff
lend a hand in hurricane relief.
- Good.
- How about that?
That's one of my former interns...
...Josh.
Must have been taken his last day
of work.
Let's call it:
- "Intern programme a success."
- Okay.
Met a lot of good kids that way.
I'll bet.
How about that one?
Wait, let me try.
"Intern programme
has fringe benefits"?
Let's see.
- Let's call it "extramarital Sachs."
- Who are you?
Someone who thinks it's a bit
hypocritical for the past two years...
...you've tried to limit the civil rights
of gay individuals...
...while being gay yourself.
- Lady--
Preach family first
as if there's one kind of family.
I don't know what you think you got
but let me explain something to you.
What I've got is a signed statement
by Josh.
We've got cancelled cheques and
he's ready to turn over the love notes.
- Laura.
- Out to lunch, remember?
It's gonna be your word against his.
We're running his tomorrow.
I work for David Shane
at the New York Courier.
Jesus Christ.
Josh came to us seven
months ago...
...and thought we'd be interested
in knowing...
...that he's not the only handsome
skeleton in your closet.
So we thought we'd give you
an opportunity to respond.
Anything you want.
I will give you anything
that you want.
Anything.
I will give- - I will give you anything
that you want.
Anything.
You just did, senator.
You just did.
Tell me you got that, Miles.
Please tell me you got that.
I got it, you psychopath.
Jump on the shuttle,
get down to the paper.
And we'll get fantastically,
exceedingly drunk.
I will give you anything that you want,
anything.
One more time.
You transmitted from D.C.
And recorded in New York.
- Go to Legal. It'll check.
- I intend to.
Also we need to clear
the quote from the intern.
He's at home waiting for the call.
This your headline, David Shane?
Yep.
We'll be at Chumley's...
...ordering copious amounts of drinks
on this paper.
God, I love this job.
Hey, hey. To David Shane.
May this article bring you
all the prizes you deserve.
Fame, alcoholism,
rehab, relapse, rehab.
When you win the Pulitzer,
don't forget the little people.
Oh, fuck the little people.
Hey, you're empty. You buy, I fly.
Excuse me, sweetheart.
Careful, Ro. Next round he might aim
for your lips.
Mr. Arvis Narron.
What kind of name is Arvis?
Family name.
Story's been pulled, Ro.
Somebody got to your intern.
Made him clam up.
My guess is somebody with lots
of zeroes.
What?
Well...
...I'm just gonna go call him.
You'll get his lawyer,
just like we did.
Do you know I've been working
on this story for six months?
Six.
Take a couple weeks off.
You've earned the break.
I'm gonna go back to the office
right now.
This guy's got a stack
of interns, trust me.
Kolski wants you to take
a couple of weeks off.
That's not a request.
Okay, wait, hold up.
Please tell me...
...you're not saying because the paper
endorsed Sachs' last campaign...
...that he's off-limits now.
Please tell me that is not
what you're saying.
- What's up, Narron?
- Get this, Miles.
Tomorrow's headline:
"Free Press Dead."
Kolski wants to shut me down
because I went after the senator.
Does it ever get to you, Narron?
The idea that we're supposed to be
reporting the news not covering it up?
Like we couldn't show the dead
bodies coming back from Iraq.
If you don't see it,
means it never happened.
Your source ran dry.
- My source didn't run dry.
- You can't try to cover up--
My source was paid off.
This is a good story, Narron.
The story's dead.
Classic.
Powerful men
protecting powerful men.
I backed you when you wanted
anonymity...
...when you wanted to write under
an old boy's name.
This is not the first time you shut me
down but this is definitely the last.
So you tell Kolski keep his paid
vacation because I fucking quit.
Taxi. Hey.
Rowena?
Rowena. Wait up.
Wait. Wait.
Fuck.
- Rowena.
- Grace. Shit, you scared me.
You didn't return my phone calls.
Well, yeah, I've been pretty busy
working out of town.
Oh, yeah. The Senator Sachs scandal.
Don't worry. I didn't tell anyone.
Besides, I got a better story for you.
It's about Harrison Hill.
- Come on.
- We met online.
We did.
He was giving a Q and A, I e-mailed
him and told him how great it was.
You know, stroke a man's dick
and you get him for one night.
Stroke his ego,
you get him for life, huh?
Yeah, we sort of struck up
a friendship online...
...but I could tell that he liked me.
So I decided to come to New York
and accidentally bump into him.
I knew about his fundraiser,
so I bought a ticket...
...walked right up to him and said,
"Harrison, it's Fast Filly."'
I thought he was gonna be angry.
But instead, he's turned on by it.
He likes the balls of it.
"Stick around," he says.
Couple hours later, we're doing it
in his Beemer, his hotel suite.
He keeps one, creep.
What happened to Chuck?
We're fighting more
than we're fucking.
Anyway, I get back to Philly,
our online stuff gets pretty hot.
He misses me.
I mean, he practically begs me
to move here.
So I check out apartments
and agencies...
...and I wanna tell him, you know,
I'm really excited.
But suddenly,
I can't get ahold of him.
I mean, I sent him a million e-mails
and he just cuts me off.
Cold. Fucker.
I know where Hill lives.
I've seen his Armani wife.
He has no idea what I can do
to him.
What is it you want from me this time,
Grace?
Actions have consequences, Ro.
You can't just forget people.
Bury them and pretend like
they never existed.
It always comes back to haunt you.
I wonder what Hill would think if David
Shane publishes a few of his e-mails?
I'm sure the wife would find them
interesting.
Take them. Read them.
Because I'm about an inch away
from ringing this guy's doorbell.
Regards to your mother.
I know where Hill lives.
I've seen his Armani wife.
He has no idea what
I can do to him.
To David Shane. May this article
bring you all the prizes you deserve.
And when you win the Pulitzer,
don't forget the little people.
Here comes the beep.
You know what to do.
Hey, Ro, it's Miles, again.
I've been calling for lik e a week.
Are you looking for a job?
If you are, come on, tak e me with you.
Guess what,
my sister had a boy, Fletcher.
How cool is that? I fly home
in an hour. Call me later, please.
I hate Narron too.
Narron's a dick. Bye.
Here comes the beep.
You know what to do.
Ro, it's Elizabeth Clayton.
Grace's mother.
- I need help.
- Elizabeth.
- Hi.
- Ro? It's Grace.
She's missing. They started calling
from her agency last week.
She goes to New York a lot and
I thought maybe she contacted you.
It's just that I filed
a missing person's report.
A woman drowned in New York.
- They ask ed for dental records.
- Elizabeth, hang on a second.
- I saw Grace last week.
- Oh, thank God.
- Spare yourself a trip.
- But if it is- - If I weren't there- -
I know half the people at the city
morgue. This is not Grace, I promise.
I'll call you when I get back.
Hi, I'm Rowena Price.
Here to ID a body.
Whoever did this tried to weigh
the body down.
Amateur move.
- Why is that?
- Didn't work.
Fair warning.
This isn't pretty.
We're guessing an anchor...
...or some sharp metal debris
ripped off the face and neck.
So we're hoping that you could
identify something else.
She has a birthmark, scars...
...and it looks like a tattoo--
Hi, Rowena.
Do you wanna play?
Well, are you coming?
Let's go around back.
I live up there.
You do everything you can to protect
your children.
Right schools, right opportunities.
But it's all an illusion.
Nobody's safe.
Who would do this to my daughter?
We're gonna find out, Mrs. Clayton.
Do you mind if I ask you
a few questions?
- Can you excuse us?
- No. She's a friend of the family.
Do you know if your daughter
had been seeing anyone?
Yeah.
Chuck. Chuck Freeman.
But they'd been having trouble.
Yeah, she told me that too.
I ran into her on the subway
last week...
...she mentioned
that they were having fights.
Was that the last time you saw her?
Yeah.
I mean, I tried to call her, but she was
in the middle of something, and... .
Well, I wish now I had tried
a little bit harder.
Oh, I know, honey.
They knew each other
since they were kids.
You were so close, you two,
especially after your father--
Yeah, I know.
Well, you were always so good to me
and my mother.
So was Grace.
Mrs. Clayton, we're gonna need you
to sign some papers downstairs.
Certainly.
I'll be just a minute.
Ro.
You know, Grace was so proud
of you.
She saved all your articles.
She bragged about you.
How did she know
that I was David Shane?
I assumed you told her.
I probably did.
Thank you.
The police are gonna find out
exactly who did this.
I'll make sure they do.
Thank you, honey.
Hey.
Hey, Miles.
Let me get the key.
I'm usually a key-above-the-door
kind of guy.
- Hey, Miles.
- Yeah.
When was the last time
you saw Grace?
Oh, God, you know me
and dates, l--
All right, well, roughly. A week?
A month? A year?
Five years? What?
Yeah, something like that. Why?
Because.
Just because I cut somebody out
of my life...
...doesn't mean I expect you
to cut them out of yours.
- Well, maybe you do.
- All right, maybe I do.
- Why you got to keep it a secret?
- We exchanged e-mails...
...a couple times. I was only nice to
her because she was a friend of yours.
So you told her I was David Shane?
Yeah. Busted.
Could you be serious for five
fucking minutes?
I'll bet you told her
about Senator Sachs too, didn't you?
I stopped associating with her
when she fucked your boyfriend.
Ask him who told her.
You need to stay in your own
fucking lane, that's what I think.
You just better leave Cam out of it.
I mean it, Miles.
Ro, I'm sorry.
I was being insensitive.
It's just-- I was the one
who was left picking up the pieces...
...after Grace and Cameron
tore you apart and l-- And l--
Yeah. So, what do the police say?
They're chasing a lead on some guy
she was dating in Philly.
But I have another idea.
Why's that?
Because I saw Grace last week.
Oh, I'm the one
who's keeping secrets?
She wanted me to chase down
Harrison Hill.
Harrison Hill, Harrison Hill?
Yes, that Harrison Hill.
Here, take a look at this.
She was threatening
to go to his wife.
Apparently, they met online
in July...
...and had one hell of a weekend
in September.
I mean, that's assuming
he is ADEX.
- Wait. Who? Who?
- ADEX.
The guy she's been e-mailing,
ADEX.
I mean, it tracks.
Harrison Hill owns...
...the biggest ad agency
in New York City?
"I'm gonna fuck you so hard,
I'm gonna split you in half."
Oh, my.
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute, Ro.
This is not a story.
Miles, I would love, love, love to get
my hands on the rest of these e-mails.
Because the way I see it, Grace was
fucking Hill, he dumped her...
...she got pissed, threatened to go
to the wife, and she wound up dead.
I mean, come on.
- It's simple, that's it.
- This is Harrison Hill.
If he wanted somebody dead,
he won't do it hims--
- That's just the first of all.
- She was stalking the guy.
She sent him a million e-mails.
She probably even went to his house.
Who knows?
All it takes to commit a murder...
...are the right ingredients
at the right time.
Son of a bitch.
- Hey, where are you?
- G.W. Bridge.
Why? What's up?
I got into Grace's Hotmail account.
It's her main one.
There's a shitload of guys in there,
by the way.
But none of them are ADEX.
But that's not the account
I gave you, Miles.
Well, hold on. And then I looked at her
other account, FastFilly@iol.com...
...and guess who's all up in her box?
ADEX. Ro.
- Yeah?
- You got to read some of this shit.
I wanna read it all, Miles.
Okay. So, I'm gonna bring over
everything after work.
And, Ro, we still don't know
that ADEX is Hill.
And we still don't know
that he's not.
Yeah.
Hey, your dinner's getting warm.
Hold it.
Can I just say for the record, wow.
Can I also say that's just a ridiculous
outfit to be wearing for takeout?
Well, I didn't know
you were bringing takeout.
Well, I didn't know you had a date.
- Oh, God.
- Who's the...?
Who's the lucky guy?
Can we just look at the e-mails,
please?
Sure. Yeah. Here, here.
Have a seat.
Okay.
So yeah.
You told me that Grace wanted you
to threaten Hill.
Well, she was doing it without you
for a while. Listen. This, this--
This e-mail's a week old
and it's her last one.
"Harrison, if you don't," capital,
"pay attention to me...
...you're going to," capital,
"pay the price.
I'm in the city
and I know your wife's away.
Meet with me now,
or I'll meet with her later."
So Grace knew that the wife
was out of town.
You're going under the assumption
that Grace actually knew...
...what she was talking about,
which is a mistake.
By the way, even though she calls
ADEX Harrison...
...it doesn't prove that it's Harrison
Hill. It's not proof enough to print.
Okay. So how do we prove it?
Well, technically we can't prove it...
...but if we can get ADEX
to send us an e-mail...
...I can tail it, jimmy the lock, and then
take a closer look into his account.
You are amazing.
I love you, man.
This is just such an obstruction
of justice.
No, no, no.
This is the pursuit of justice.
I'll make you a deal.
We get anything concrete on Hill...
...we'll go to the cops
and to Narron on the same day.
They get their man.
We get our story.
But even if ADEX turns out
to be Hill...
...it's not a crime to chat nor cheat.
But it is a crime to be walking out
on a feast like this in that outfit.
And yet, I have to because I'm late.
So you finish up.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Shut the door. It locks by itself.
Have fun.
Harrison Hill.
Oh, there you are.
Cam.
- Oh, Cam.
- Come here.
- You are naughty.
- Come on.
Come here.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
- You like that?
- Yes, baby.
Oh, come on. Say it.
Yeah, oh, yeah.
You like it? You like that?
Yeah, good.
I need to get closer to Hill.
Hello, Miles. How are you?
Fine. You? Thanks.
Fine. You?
Okay, I need to get closer to Hill.
Close as you got to Cam last night?
It's a little soon to be going
on dates with Grace's ex.
Oh, I'm sorry, your ex.
Are you fucking spying on me now?
No. A friend of mine saw you
two last night.
And he said it look ed friendly.
What? You get him by default?
Well, not that I owe you or
your friend an explanation.
I wanted to see Cam. Somebody
had to tell him about Grace.
Well, I guess we all
grieve differently.
You know what, Miles? Forget it.
If you don't wanna help me,
Terry wouldn't mind.
He's been dying to get
into research.
Oh, Terry couldn't find his ass
with both hands and his ass.
All right, fine, fine, fine.
I'll play nice.
Okay. Good.
While you look around
in cyberspace...
...I need to be looking around
at my new job...
...that you, clever friend,
are going to get me.
Oh, God love you.
Something temporary.
Easy in, easy out. Can you do that?
Does a bear shit in the woods?
H2A's got a blade server...
...that gives more entry points
than a college girl at Mardi Gras.
I'll access the needs list they send
to temp agencies.
Shouldn't be too hard.
There's always openings.
- And, hey, wear something sexy.
- What?
You need to bait the hook.
Just make sure I'm working for Hill.
Yeah, your new name
will be Katherine Pogue.
I choose my own names.
Well, tough. I had a crush on a girl
in high school named Katherine.
It's an homage.
- Going to H2A.
- H2A.
Hill's a Jersey native who slipped
and fell into a big pile of money...
- ... when he married- -
- Mia Rheinhart Hill.
She's also the daughter of Max
Rheinhart, principal owner of H2A.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Now, if you'll follow me.
Hard to separate a man
from his wife's money.
Money is the root of all evil, Miles.
Check your scriptures.
Love of money is the root of all evil,
Ro.
Love.
We have a new temp.
Her name is Katherine Pogue.
- Hi.
Thank you. I'll show you
to your desk.
And press 9 to get out,
3 to reach me.
I'll be right across from you. You
shouldn't have a problem finding me.
Katherine, we need a coffee setup
in Conference Room A.
- Will I be working for Mr. Hill?
- No.
I'm working for Mr. Hill.
You're working for me.
And you'd better roll up your sleeves.
We are short-staffed this week.
Sensational, Harrison. Really.
Spectacular.
I hear you're thinking about opening
in Amsterdam, by the way.
- Yes, we did. In April.
- Really?
Excuse me, Mr. Hill.
Mr. Kirschenbaum's car is downstairs
and your 2:00 is waiting.
Thanks, Esmeralda.
- I'll walk you out, Jon.
- Great. Thanks.
You're doing well.
I'm very proud of you.
I couldn't have done it without you.
I learned from the best.
- I appreciate it.
- Thanks for coming by.
Listen, this is probably
just bullshit...
...but one of my guys heard that a
couple of your execs were in Canton...
...sniffing around
my Reebok account.
If you're sure it's bullshit,
why are you asking me?
Because they heard about it
from inside your agency.
I just don't want you to make that kind
of mistake, Harrison.
I've been representing Reebok
for 11 years.
They're my main account.
They're not gonna jump ship for your
smile and some downtown hype.
Eat or be eaten. Right, Jon?
Isn't that what you always told me?
Now, you left the Reebok account out
on the table.
If I didn't pick it up, someone else
was going to and you know that.
Ten years ago you wouldn't have let
this happen. You fumbled the ball.
You really are that stupid.
Give my regards to Vanessa.
Esmeralda.
We have a leak to
Kirschenbaum and Bond.
I wanna find out who the fuck it is.
Right now.
Hold the door, please.
- Wait. Thank you.
- That was close.
Harrison, will you be attending
the Victoria's Secret meeting tonight?
I was hoping maybe I could catch
a ride.
- Yeah, I think I'll be going.
- Okay.
Keep the metre running.
We can go now.
74th and Broadway, please.
Rowena.
Got you.
You know how much
Daddy likes bath time.
We have a Victoria's Secret
party tonight.
- Good morning, Esmeralda.
- Good morning, Katherine.
Two hundred guests,
200 gift bags, too little time.
Five items per bag. Have fun.
- Miles, what? I'm at work.
- Well, it wasn't just a drowning.
She was poisoned.
She had a hole in her gut the size
of a fruit bowl.
Oh, come on.
No, that's a direct quote
from the examiner's office.
The killer also put it in her eyes...
... which is weird.
Ro, they haven't announced it yet...
...but Grace was pregnant.
She was in her first trimester.
Hello. I'm Gina.
- Ro?
- Katherine Pogue, are you in here?
Oh, there you are.
I could tell you Victoria's secret,
but then I'd have to kill you.
- Clever, huh?
- Yeah.
Mr. Hill came up with it for the
"Very Sexy Collection" launch.
Very sexy.
And in a rainbow of colours.
Here, keep a few for the home fires.
I know a pretty girl like you
has a boyfriend.
- No.
- Girlfriend?
- Pets?
- No.
Well, we've got some
local talent here.
I'll say. What's up with Hill?
He's interesting.
Married.
Rumour is, and you didn't hear it
from me...
...he had a couple of interoffice flings
a few years back, led to lawsuits.
Paid a lot of money
to make them go away.
That's when he got his front girl
to run interference.
That would be Josie.
Or, if you get on her bad side,
Cujosie.
She's his gatekeeper.
His walking hard drive.
So he never forgets a name,
an account, an enemy.
No one gets to him now
without going through her.
Let me guess, he's done her too,
right?
Oh, no. No.
She'd be more interested in you than
in him, if you catch my heavy drift.
I think I do.
She's his watchdog, not his bitch.
- The guy's reformed, unfortunately.
- Right.
His wife's all over him.
She's got eyes in the back
of your head.
Trust me.
She finds him cheating,
she and her money are out the door.
See Jesse Drake over there?
He had this blond temp last fall
could melt butter.
Her name was Veronica.
One day, the boss's wife comes in...
...sees Mr. H and Veronica talking
close over the Sparkletts...
...the next day the temp's toast.
The boy's been leashed.
But since I have it on good authority
he's into some very kinky shit.
He probably likes the tight collar.
I'd let him give me a little spank.
- Did I just say that out loud?
- You're sick.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
You're Katherine, right?
And you're Harrison Hill, the boss.
Yes.
It's good to be the boss.
Yeah.
So I'll see you at the party tonight,
Katherine.
Here we go.
On behalf of Victoria's Secret, I would
like to thank our very special angel...
...Harrison Hill, for making us
sexier than ever.
Harrison.
I have no idea how we could
possibly make...
...you look any sexier than you do
tonight, Heidi.
Thank you so very much.
I'd just like to raise a glass
to everyone at Victoria's Secret...
...and all my people at H2A...
...for making this
a successful campaign...
...a Very Sexy Collection
is H2A's most sexful--
Succsexf--
We did really good
with this campaign.
Happy Valentine's Day.
God bless you.
Thank you. Good night.
So is part of the torture the fact
we get to watch all this fun?
Are you kidding me?
We got the best seats in the house.
Okay, see the guy with the bad
combover standing by the statues?
Bob Milstein, Accounting.
He may look unlucky in love.
He recently nailed Kay Rolands,
Sales...
...the giant standing by the shrimp.
- Corporate America, ain't it grand?
- One big happy family, eh?
Who's the loud-laughing brunette?
The one that looks a little tipsy.
Oh, Bethany Lee, account manager.
Long legs, perfect teeth,
may they rot in hell.
A few years back
there was chatter...
...she and Mr. Hill were going over
more than just the company numbers.
- Really?
- Yeah.
But that was before the lawsuits,
before Cujosie...
...and before the wife
started paying attention.
Now it's all hugs and kisses
and they're going to fertility clinics.
I think her oven's on the fritz.
Is there anything you don't know,
Gina?
No.
I don't get it. Mrs. Hill is pretty.
I mean, she's really pretty.
Show me a beautiful woman, I'll show
you a man who's tired of fucking her.
- Nice, Gina.
- What? I've got brothers.
Hi.
Hey.
You're embarrassing him
and yourself.
Okay, I'll be better.
His wife is out there.
I'm sorry.
Here's money for a cab.
Come on.
- He'll call me, right?
- Good night, Bethany, good night.
I told you already, Narron, I quit.
I figured two weeks was enough
to let you cool off.
I gotta go.
I'm sorry about the senator, Ro,
but I can't lose you.
- David Shane is this paper's star.
- You don't bench a star, Narron.
There will always be powerful people
covering things up, Ro...
...at every paper, in every city.
It's called editorializing
and it's a reality.
Don't give up
because one son of a bitch...
...pulled some strings at the paper
and silenced your source.
Rest up, come back...
...and nail the next son of a bitch.
Maybe.
So I set up your IOL account,
but you're gonna need a name.
How about Rocket?
That was my nickname
from college.
Are you sure you don't wanna be
"Hot Bitch on Wheels"?
No, I'm kidding.
All right, Rocket, Rocket, "Rocketgirl."
A little sexier than
DShane@NYCourier.com.
So I put ADEX...
...into your friends file
and as a little extra added bonus...
...your computer has a few things
to say. Listen, this is good.
Miles is sexy.
- Translation?
- Let me guess.
Miles is sexy?
- You think so?
- And I need this, why?
Because it's fucking radical.
Every time you get an IM,
you'll have a voice to match.
I don't want my computer talking.
I don't want it saying:
- "Miles is sexy."
- I'll just give an audio to Hill.
I sampled his voice
from some streaming video.
- You don't mind if Hill talks?
- Do I have a choice?
No.
So, what's he like up close
and personal?
Well, tell you one thing,
there's more to the guy than you think.
You should check out his offices.
Go online, take the tour.
You'll see. It's outrageous.
Sick. Just what you'd like.
Oh, you know what, by the way,
I did find something out. Apparently...
...Hill has squashed a couple
of sexual harassment suits.
- Could you chase the money trail?
- Yeah, well...
...I guess he's a likely
candidate for that.
No, not really.
He's now got this gorgeous
Amazonian woman...
...that does all the dirty work.
- Oh, really? Is she hot?
Yes.
She's very hot.
She's also a lesbian.
Bastard.
All right, so seeing
that you're a chat-room virgin... .
- Big deal, I'm a chat-room virgin.
- No, I think it's a compliment.
I think you should practise
online flirting.
- Why would I want to do that?
- Because you'll tell a perfect stranger...
...something you won't tell your best
friend. Especially if you're anonymous.
You should know that,
Mr. David Shane.
Oh, by the way, I got a dollar that
says Hill's not our guy.
We got a pregnant Grace,
threatening to go to the wife, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay, but meanwhile, the wife...
...is busy trying to haul Hill off
to a fertility clinic.
And let's not forget the most
important part, the wife is the money.
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
That's motive on a big stick.
- Motive on a big stick?
- That's what I said.
So I'll take your bet.
Game on.
Welcome to chat.
"Trublu?" Okay.
Welcome.
"Haven't seen you around."
New to this. Who are you?
Hello, Neil, I'm Tiffany.
Okay, Trublu, let's go.
How do you imagine me?
"Long blond hair, longer legs--"
Really close.
Welcome.
"When you said you were getting off,
I didn't know you meant literally."
Leave me alone.
I haven't contacted him.
"I did on his--"
- Hello.
- Okay, look, this isn't funny.
- You're taking advantage of me.
- This is exactly what we talked about.
Once he responds,
I get past his firewall.
It's the price of admission.
I wrote, " Dear Harrison...
...the answers are: Great sex,
cheap beer, the Rolling Stones."
- What?
- Come on.
We got to push his buttons. By the
way, I sent it from your account.
Oh, shit. He's on.
- There he is. Let me drive.
- He's on, Miles, he's on.
- Wait. Wait, wait, wait. Miles.
- Harrison--
- What are you doing?
- Nice to hear from you.
Miles, you're typing for me?
- It's a riddle.
- Miles. Stop it.
- Miles, stop it.
- All right, fine. Fine. Fine.
I'm through the firewall into ADEX's
account. He's all yours.
Miles, you bastard.
- What's your name?
- Shit.
Veronica.
What colour is your hair?
Blond.
Dirty.
I lik e dirty.
Filthy.
I'd lik e to get a fistful.
Are you turned on?
I am.
Fucker.
I should go.
But you just warmed me up.
Yeah. Don't blueball the guy.
"Yeah, Ro. Don't blueball the guy."
- I'll be back. Bye.
- Goodbye.
Would you quit spying on me,
you fuck?
You are officially in the way
of how I work and I'm not having it.
- It's Hill. We can prove it now.
- Don't send e-mails on my behalf.
And do not speak for me in any way.
How about, "Thank you, Miles,
for your subversive genius"?
Thank you. Bye.
Good morning, H2A.
May I help you?
- Hey, good morning.
- How are you?
Good morning, H2A.
Hello.
"What happened to you last night?"
Morning.
"Tiffany? Veronica?"
Katherine.
You forgot to fill out your l-9.
Okay.
I told Human Resources
I'd run it right back over there...
...now.
Okay, well, I'll just fill this out.
- You looking for permanent work?
- Always.
Where have you temped?
I don't know. Got a phone book?
Yes, I do.
Okay.
Zaffman, Meyer and Pearce, I.P.E. --
- I love the new building.
- Great bathrooms.
What about Kirschenbaum
and Bond?
Average bathrooms.
When did you work there?
I don't know, maybe April.
I don't know. My life is kind of crazy.
One day just runs into the next.
Heineken Amsterdam
is gonna love it.
We should start talking
about print, scheduling, tie-ins.
It can play internationally too.
Jesse, why don't you start talking
about media buys with Chuck...
...Toni and Steve.
I need a couple minutes.
- I'll be right back.
- I'm glad you're happy.
So glad you're happy.
When do you think we could roll it
to print?
Here, hold this, please.
Esmeralda, hold my calls
for a few minutes.
Phelps. Mr. Phelps.
Afternoon, boys.
Kindly do me a favour and stand up,
would you? Get out!
Piece of shit?
You're gonna spy on me?
Here, get the fuck up,
you piece of sh--
You were a fucking bike messenger.
I made you rich.
I hope they have a job for you
over at Kirschenbaum.
I accept your resignation.
Gunnar.
Congratulations.
Now clean up your new office.
Back to work.
What are you guys looking at?
Shit. What just happened?
Gunnar Hope just got a promotion.
"Veronica, how did you know
about my ADEX account?"
I used to temp at H2A.
Yeah.
My boyfriend wouldn't like that.
Shit.
Does this phone call mean
I'm forgiven?
You've got once chance
to redeem yourself.
He wants a photo of Veronica.
- Who?
- Me. Rocketgirl.
- Is nude an option?
- Miles.
There was a temp
that used to work here.
- Veronica something.
- "Veronica something."
- You gotta be kidding me.
- She worked for Jesse Drake.
Every employee here
has got a security photo ID.
- She's got to be in the files.
- Oh, come on.
Miles. Do it.
I need this, Miles.
Just do it. Please.
- Hurry up.
- A last name would really help.
Yeah, well, how many Veronicas
can there be in the system?
Come on, Miles.
Hurry.
- Miles.
- This is ridiculous. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
I can see him from here.
Come on, Miles, hurry.
Miles.
Hurry up. Miles.
- Okay.
- Hurry.
Come on, come on.
Yahtzee.
Veronica Carter. Just download,
upload, exhale and send.
You are awesome.
Yeah, well, remember that
the next time you're firing me.
Oh, Ro...
...I'm meeting my guy
from the M.E.'s office, Bill Patel...
...at Chumley's at 7:00.
He's got the talks on Grace,
everything the cops have.
Great. I'll meet you there.
- Shit.
- What?
My computer screen is frozen.
And Veronica's face is screen saver.
What?
- Miles.
- Turn it off.
- Oh, fuck.
Turn the power off.
Fuck, he's coming.
- Hi.
- Pretty busy for the end of the day.
- Yeah.
Just working away.
Anything I can help with?
Nope.
Not unless data entry turns you on.
You know what?
Surprisingly, it doesn't.
But seriously, how you doing?
Let me tell you about my night.
I have to go to dinner at Sapa.
Average jokes, exceptional food.
If you find yourself bored...
...in the area of 24th and Sixth
around 10:00...
...you could fall by for a drink.
I really appreciate that offer,
but I think I'm gonna have to pass.
Okay.
Is there something else I can do
for you, or--?
No.
I'm just waiting for you to change
your mind.
Look, Mr. Hill--
I recognise that tone.
Sounds serious.
I really like working here.
And I would really like for my work
to speak for itself.
Fair enough.
Have a splendid evening,
Miss Pogue.
Wait. Mr. Hill?
In case I change my mind...
...keep an eye out around dessert.
Hey, how you guys doing?
- Miles.
- Bill Patel, Rowena Price.
- A pleasure.
- You can lose the glasses.
This isn't Deep Throat.
Here's your pina colada,
hold the umbrella.
We know about the drowning, Bill,
but what was this poison?
Belladonna.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org