Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Scared of what? Dying?
- My sister, Zelda...
- I know. She died.
Spinal meningitis.
She was in the back bedroom,
like a dirty secret.
'My sister died in the back bedroom,
and that's what she was,
'a dirty secret.
'I had to feed her sometimes.
'I hated it. But I did it.
'We wanted her to die.
We wished for her to be dead. '
It wasn't just so she wouldn't
feel any more pain.
It was so we wouldn't
'Because she started to look
like this monster. '
Even now, I wake up and I think,
"Is Zelda dead yet?
"Is she?"
'My parents were gone when she died. '
(Zelda, laughing) Rachel!
(Zelda growling)
'She started to...
'She started to convulse
and I thought,
'oh, my God, she's choking.
Zelda's choking!
'They'll come home
and say I murdered her by choking.
'They'll say, "You hated her,
Rachel," and that was true.
'They'll say, "You wanted her to be
dead," and that was true, too.
(Sobbing) 'And then she died.
'I started to scream. I ran out of
the house, screaming, "Zelda's dead!
"'Zelda's dead!"
'The neighbors came out
and they looked... '
They thought I was crying.
But you know something?
I think maybe...
I was laughing.
If you were, I salute you for it.
If I needed another reason to dislike
your parents, I have one now.
You should never have been left alone
with her. Where was her nurse?
They went out and left
an eight-year-old kid
in charge of her dying sister,
who was probably insane by then.
- Where are you going?
- To get you a Valium.
- You know I don't take...
- Tonight you do.
(# The Ramones:
Sheena Is A Punk Rocker)
# Well, the kids are all hopped up
and ready to go
# They're ready to go now
# And they're going to
the Discotheque Au Go Go... #
(Rachel)
Look! Daddy's flying the kite!
(Ellie) Mommy, look! There it goes!
(Jud) That's it, Louis.
- Go, Daddy!
- (Jud) Higher! We want it higher!
- Louis, let Gage do it.
- Here you go, buddy.
# Oh, yeah, oh, yeah
# Sheena is a punk rocker,
Sheena is a punk rocker
# Sheena is a punk rocker now
# Sheena is... #
- You're flying it.
- There's the kite.
Gage is flying it. You got it?
- Can I fly it now?
- Let Gage finish his turn.
- We gotted it.
- We got it.
(Gage) Kite go.
(Jud) You're flying it. Go ahead.
Go ahead. Run, boy. You're flying it.
- (Rachel) Gage is flying it.
- I'm flying it.
(Jud) That kite's getting up there!
Uh-oh!
It got away from him, that numbshit!
- (Gasps)
- Ellen Creed!
Oh. I dropped it.
(Ellie) Daddy, can I fly it now?
(Louis) OK. In just a minute.
- (Rachel) I wanna fly it.
- Uh-oh!
- Daddy, it's my turn now.
- All right. Just a minute.
- Don't let him go in the road!
- Get him, Louis. Get the baby!
Get the baby!
(Rachel) Get the baby!
(Louis) Gage! Stop!
(Jud) Gage!
(Squelching)
(Crash)
No!
(Echoing) 'No!
'No! '
The sedative finally took hold.
Rachel's asleep.
I wanna go back to my own room.
I can't sleep with Mommy.
She keeps stealing the covers.
Ellie, what you got there?
Hmm? What you got there? Let me see.
Can I see?
Ohh... Ain't that real nice?
You pulling him in the wagon.
Bet he liked that, didn't he?
I'm going to carry this picture,
Mr. Crandall,
until God lets Gage come back.
Ellie...
God doesn't do things like that.
He can if He wants to.
I have to keep his things
waiting for him. That's what I think.
I've got this picture
and I'm going to sit in his chair...
Ellie...
Louis...
Take care of your little girl.
She needs you.
(Ellie sobbing)
I knew something would happen.
I told her when you got married,
"You'll have all the grief you can
stand and more. " Now, look at this.
I hope you rot in hell! Where were
you when he was playing in the road?
You stinking shit!
You killer of children!
Daddy!
Ellie!
- Stop it!
- You son of a...!
(Screaming)
(Rachel, screaming) Oh, God! No!
- (Yells)
- Louis!
- My God!
- Son of a bitch! You have no right!
What's wrong with you?
It's your son's funeral.
Get a hold of yourself, please!
Good night, Ellie.
Good night, Daddy.
Daddy?
God could take it back
if He wanted to, couldn't He?
If He really, really wanted to?
Can I have faith in that?
Yes, I suppose you can.
Good night, Ellie.
(Church growling)
(Fierce growling)
Fuck off, hairball!
(Screeches)
(Meows)
Jud, I buried my son today.
I'm very tired.
I wonder if we could just...
You're thinking thoughts
best not thought of, Louis.
I'm thinking about going to bed.
I'm responsible for more pain
in your heart
than you should have tonight.
For all I know, I may even be
responsible for your son's death.
What?
Jud, you're talking crazy.
You're thinking
of putting him up there.
Don't deny the thought
hadn't crossed your mind, Louis.
Louis...
You asked me...
if anyone had ever buried a person
up there in the Micmac grounds.
I lied to you when I said no.
It's been done.
What you've been thinking of
has been done.
He was a local boy.
It was towards the end
of the Second Worid War.
His name was Timmy Baterman.
'He was killed on his way home
from the Second Worid War.
'His father Bill Baterman
was so grief-struck
'he buried his son up there
'before he ever had a chance
to get to the bottom of the truth. '
I'll bite, Jud.
What's the bottom of the truth?
Well, that sometimes,
death is better.
'The person you put up there
ain't the person that comes back.
'Lt may look like that person
but it ain't that person.
'Because whatever lives in the ground
beyond the pet cemetery...
'ain't human at all. '
(Manic laughter)
It was four or five days
after Timmy's funeral
that Margie Washburn seen Timmy
walking up the road
towards Yorkie's livery.
'As time went by, lots of folks
saw Timmy walking back and forth. '
But it was Margie who finally came
to some of us men folks
and said it had to be stopped!
She knew it was an abomination.
So us men sat down and talked it out.
'We went over to the Baterman place
to take care of it.
'One way or the other. '
He's gotta burn!
You're wrecking the house!
Stop it! Timmy, stop it!
- The place is goin' up.
- Go away!
Get out while you still can, Bill!
- Bring out the cans!
- Wait a minute, fellas.
He's a monster, Bill!
Leave us alone! He's my son!
- Come, Timmy, let's get out!
- (Timmy) Love death! Hate living.
Come on, son!
(Timmy) Love death! Hate living!
'Louis, sometimes dead is better.
The Indians knew that.
'They stopped using that burial
ground and the ground went sour.
'Don't think about doing it.
The place gets hold of you.
'The place is evil. '
Sometimes, dead is better.
You see, Louis, what I'm getting at?
You understand?
You're telling me that place
knew Gage was going to die?
I'm saying...
that place might have made Gage die
cos I introduced you to the power.
I may have murdered your son, Louis!
This could be the beginning of
patching things up with your folks.
If something good doesn't come
from Gage's death, I think...
- I don't want to go to Chicago.
- Why not, darling?
I had a bad dream last night.
About what?
About Daddy... and Gage...
and someone named Paxcow.
(Louis) You guys better get going,
you're gonna miss the boat.
Louis... I am sorry.
What can I say? I lost my mind.
We all lost our minds.
- You take care of your mother.
- Come with us, Daddy, please!
I'll be there in three or four days.
Please, Daddy. I'm scared.
- Everything's gonna be all right.
- Do you swear?
I swear.
Come on, Ellie. Let's go.
It's wrong.
What happened to you is wrong.
(Pascow) Remember, Doc...
The barrier...
was not meant to be crossed.
The ground is sour!
If it doesn't work...
If he comes back...
and he's like Jud said
Timmy Baterman was...
I'll just put him back to sleep.
'And they don't have to know.
'Rachel and Ellie
don't ever have to know. '
(Ellie, crying) Mommy. Mommy!
Mommy!
Mommy! Mommy! Mommy!
(Rachel) Honey, you just had
a bad dream. That's all.
It wasn't a dream. It was Paxcow!
Paxcow says Daddy's
going to do something really bad.
Who is this Paxcow?
Is he like the bogeyman?
He's a ghost. He's a good ghost.
He says he was sent to warn us.
He says he was near Daddy
because they were together
when his soul was... dis... dis...
I can't remember!
Listen. There are no ghosts.
There are no ghosts.
Go to sleep and forget
all this nonsense. Do you hear me?
Will you at least call
and make sure Daddy's OK?
Of course I will.
Paxcow? Why do I know that name?
- Pascow.
- Pascow?
Was she saying Pascow?
'He was trying to help me
because Daddy was helping him
'when his soul dis... dis... '
Discorporated.
I'm gonna bust you out, son.
(Phone)
(Ringing)
He's not home.
He probably went out for a hamburger
or a chicken dinner.
You know how men are
when they're alone.
(Phone)
Hello?
Jud, it's Rachel Creed.
I'm calling from Chicago.
'Chicago? Is Louis with you? '
No. We're going to be here a while
and he needed a few days
to close things up there.
'I just wondered if he was with you. '
No.
But if he drops by,
I'll tell him to call you.
- Don't bother. I'm coming home.
- Rachel, no!
- 'Don't do that. '
- I have to. Goodbye.
Rachel! Rachel!
(Owl hoots)
(Police radios)
You've done it, you stupid old man.
Now you've got to undo it.
Oh, Gage.
It's going to be all right.
I swear it's going to be all right.
(Eerie creaking)
I'm coming for you, Rachel.
And this time...
I'll get you.
Gage and I...
will get you.
For letting us die!
(Cackling)
(Gasps)
(PA) 'Good evening again.
We've had a strong tailwind
'and we expect to arrive at Boston's
Logan Airport almost on time. '
Thank God.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Excuse me. Excuse me!
Don't do that.
- Make it wait!
- I can't!
All right, I'll call the pilot.
(Owl hooting)
I'm not gonna stop, Gage.
I'm not gonna look down.
(Distant screeching)
(Cackling)
(Creaking and splintering)
I'm sorry. It's been very busy.
I don't have anything.
What about the Aries K -
the one with the scratch?
I do have an Aries K.
It's rather beat up,
there's a long scrape up one side.
I'll take it.
OK. Major credit card and a license.
(Eerie voice) 'Louis... '
(Screaming echoes)
See?
It's just imagination.
(Tyres squealing)
(Screams)
- Now what?
- It's trying to stop you.
Do you hear me?
It's trying to stop you!
(Thunder rumbles)
Is anyone there?
(Owl hoots)
Come back to me, Gage.
(Rumbling)
Come back to us.
(Low growling)
(Horn blares)
Hey! Hey, stop!
- Hop in, babe.
- Oh, thank you.
(Growling)
(Snoring)
(Door slams)
Oh, my...
(Gage giggling)
Who's here?
(Giggling continues)
(Gage) Let's play hide-and-go-seek.
(Clattering)
Gage?
Are you the one playing games?
(Giggling)
Gage?
Come on out!
I brought you something.
(Giggling)
(Screeches)
Where did you...?
(Growling)
(Gurgling)
Aaargh!
(Jud groaning)
(Munching and squelching)
(Jud screaming)
Thank you so much.
Think nothing of it.
Hell, I didn't get a ticket,
lady, so you're welcome.
Whatever your problems are,
I hope they work out.
End of the line for me too.
I'm not allowed any further.
I'm sure things will be fine.
I'm not.
(Zelda) Rachel!
(Giggling)
(Screeches)
Church?
Jud?
(Low groaning)
(Groaning continues)
Jud?
Are you up there?
(Zelda) Rachel!
Rachel...
Rachel? Is that you?
I finally came back for you, Rachel.
I'm going to twist your back
like mine,
so you'll never get out of bed again!
Never get out of bed again!
(Cackling)
(Gage giggling)
Gage?
I brought you something, Mommy.
Gage...
Ohh... Oh, Gage! Gage!
I brought you something, Mommy.
(Squelch, Rachel screaming)
(Blood-curdling scream)
Oh!
Oh! Christ!
Gage...
- Oh, my God.
- (Gage giggling)
Gage?
(Phone)
- Hello.
- 'Hello, Louis. It's Irwin.
'I just wanted to be sure
Rachel got back all right.
- 'Louis, are you there? '
- Yes, I'm here.
- 'Did she get back all right? '
- Yes. She's fine.
'Put her on at that end
and I'll put Ellie on this one.
'Ellie's very worried
about her mother.
'She's almost in hysterics. '
She...
- Rachel's asleep.
- 'I suggest you wake her up.
'Ellie had a dream
that her mother was dead. '
Irwin, I can't talk to you right now.
(Phone)
Irwin, I can't talk to you right now!
(Gage) 'I'm at Jud's, Daddy.
Will you come over and play with me?
'First I played with Jud.
'Then Mommy came
and I played with Mommy.
'Will you play, Daddy?
We had an awful good time.
'Now I want to play with you. '
What did you do?
(Giggling)
What did you do?!
(Gage giggling)
Hi, Church.
Want some grub, Church? Church...
(Growls)
(Hisses)
Don't mind me.
Eat it while you can.
That's right.
Today is Thanksgiving Day for cats.
But only...
if they came back from the dead.
(Church snarling)
(Whimpers)
Go on! Lie down.
Play dead!
Be dead!
(Wind whistling)
Gage?
(Clattering)
(Eerie rumbling and growling)
Gage, what have you done?
Rachel!
(Rumbling stops)
(Gage) Scared you, didn't I?
- Gage?
- Hi, Daddy.
Now I want to play with you. (Laughs)
All right, Gage.
- Let's play.
- (Gage laughing)
(Gage laughing)
(Yells)
- (Yelling)
- (Choking)
(Laughing)
(Screams)
(Gage growling, Louis screaming)
(Gage groaning)
Daddy.
Come here.
(Growls)
- (Laughing)
- Come here.
No fair.
No fair. No fair.
I'm so sorry, Louis.
I'm so sorry.
But don't make it worse. Don't!
I waited too long with Gage.
With Rachel...
It will work this time!
Because she just died.
She just died a little while ago.
Louis!
Don't! Please! Louis!
No!
It will be all right, Rachel.
I promise.
(Jud) 'The soil of a man's heart
is stonier, Louis.
'A man grows what he can,
then he tends it.
'Cos what you buy is what you own.
'And what you own...
'always comes home to you. '
(Bell tolls)
(Ringing)
Darling.
(Louis screams)
# Under the arc
of a weather stain boards
# Ancient goblins and warlords
# Come out the ground,
not makin' a sound
# The smell of death is all around
# And the night
when the cold wind blows
# No one cares, nobody knows
# I don't wanna be buried
# In a pet cemetery
# I don't want to live my life again
# I don't wanna be buried
# In a pet cemetery
# I don't want to live my life again
# Follow Victor to the sacred place
# This ain't a dream, I can't escape
# Molars and fangs,
the clicking of bones
# Spirits moaning
among the tombstones
# And the night
when the moon is bright
# Someone cries,
somethin' ain't right
# I don't wanna be buried
# In a pet cemetery
# I don't want to live my life again
# I don't wanna be buried
# In a pet cemetery
# I don't want to live my life again
# The moon is full, the air is still
# All of a sudden I feel a chill
# Victor is grinning,
flesh is rotting away
# Skeletons dance, I curse this day
# And the night
when the wolves cry out
# Listen close
and you can hear me shout
# I don't wanna be buried
# In a pet cemetery
# I don't want to live my life again
# I don't wanna be buried
# In a pet cemetery
# I don't want to live my life again
# Oh, no
# I don't want to live my life
# Again #
Ripped by:
SkyFury
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org