Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
WOMAN: Oh!
Oh!
- Oh!
Oh, oh, baby.
Oh!
Tommy, Tommy.
Ah!
- Oh!
WOMAN: Oh, oh!
Oh! Oh, that was great, baby.
( Grunts )
Jody.
Hi, Reg.
How's it goin'?
( Sighs ) Tommy's gone.
It's, uh...
it's a hell of a way to end a trio.
It's hard to believe.
Killed himself.
Hey, I, uh...
I'm gonna go visit somebody. Uh...
- I'll catch you insie.
- Yeah.
( Scrabbling sounds )
( Scrabbling )
( Engine dies )
- ( Engine sputters )
- ( Scraping )
( Scraping )
The funeral is about to begin...sir!
OK...sir.
( # Organ # )
It was a good idea not to let
your brother come to the funeral
and see Tommy like this.
Yeah, after Mom and Dad's funeral,
he had nightmares for weeks.
And forgive us our debts
as we forgive our debtors.
Lead us not into temptation
but deliver us from evil...
Hey, I don't like this place.
Well, say goodbye to Tommy.
Let's just get the hell outta here.
( Dogs barking )
Hi, Michael.
Hi. Is your grandmother home?
Sure, come in.
Grandmother, Michael has returned
and wishes to speak with you.
Grandmother is pleased you've come
and wants to know what's bothering you.
Uh, tell her that I, um...
She can hear you.
Oh, yeah.
Uh...it's Jody again.
I found out that he's leaving.
( Whistles )
( Sighs ) I think
it's one of these headers in here.
( Whistles )
- Hey, Toby!
- Hey!
- So what brings you back?
- Tommy.
Yeah...yeah, shoot.
I just don't get off on funerals, man.
They give me the creeps.
I just wanna tell you
I heard about you folks. I'm sorry.
Yeah, thank you, man.
In two years I guess you can
just about get over anything.
- So, I hear you've been out on the road.
- Yeah.
How come you're hanging
around this dump?
Well, I'm taking care of the kid.
Shit, I'd think after all that action,
this town'd drive you nuts.
You're damn right.
Now the kid's 13, I'm thinking
of sending him off to live with his aunt,
but I'll tell you, he ain't gonna like it.
As it is, he follows me everywhere,
it's like he knows I'm gonna leave.
He's a tough little kid. I love him.
I'm gonna miss him.
Grandmother says not to worry.
If he does leave, he'll take you with him.
- God, I hope she's right.
- She always is.
There's somethin' else.
I'm really scared about something I did.
I was messing around up at Morningside
Cemetery and I saw something...
something really scary.
( Bang )
( Whispers )
Michael,
Grandmother wants to play a little game.
Wow! How did you do that?
Put your hand in the box.
- What's in it?
- Just put your hand in the black box.
OK, but what's in it?
- Hey, this thing really hurts!
- Don't fear, Michael.
- I can't get my hand out!
- Don't fear.
- Gimme back my hand!
- Don't fear!
It was simply a reflection.
Fear is the killer.
That's what Grandmother
wants you to learn.
Boy, that really hurt.
It was all in your mind.
Um, yeah.
Come and visit us again soon.
Yeah.
( Laughs )
( Guitar playing, man singing )
Hi, Reg.
- Writin' a new tune?
- Yeah, working on it.
# I'm just a-sittin' here at midnight #
All right.
# And I'll be sittin' here till noon #
# You see my lady left me lonely #
# Yes, she did #
# My baby left me blue #
BOTH: Oh!
- ( Laughs )
- Huh! Whew!
All right. We're hot as love, you know.
( Screaming )
( # Cicadas chirping # )
( # Disco # )
Well, uh, let's see.
It's, uh, just right up the street.
( Dog barking )
This is, uh...kinda spooky, isn't it?
No, it's exciting.
( Cicadas chirping )
So, uh... what's the only thing to do
in this town?
Well, it's, uh, something...
WOMAN: Oh.
- Wow!
( Low growling )
( Growling gets louder )
( Loud growl )
( Low growling )
( Loud snarling )
( Screams )
- What the heck?
- ( Screaming )
- Wait here. It's my little brother.
I think he's got some kind of a problem.
( Screaming )
Mike!
What's wrong with you, man?
There's something up there.
I know it, I saw it!
What?
OK, look, I was following you guys.
I didn't mean any harm,
but it's out there, it's gonna get me!
What's out there?
I don't know. It was...it was little and brown
and low to the ground.
It's probably just a gopher in heat.
It wasn't any gopher!
Where's that girl, anyway?
She's waitin' back there for me, you idiot!
- ( Scrabbling sounds )
- Hear that?
- ( Wind whistling )
- Nah, it's only the wind.
You better go get her
before it get her.
You got some kind of overactive
imagination or somethin', man?
Look, tell you what...
You go on home.
I'll talk to you when I get back.
- You sure you're gonna be OK?
- Ah, get outta here.
( Wailing and moaning )
- ( Screeching )
- ( Yells )
( Footsteps echoing )
Did that chick I left with last night
ever come back in here?
What happened? You get a hold
of something you couldn't handle?
Nah, she just ditched out on me, I guess.
We were, uh, messin' around
out there at Morningside.
- At the funeral parlour?
- Mm.
- The cemetery.
- ( Laughs )
( Squeaking )
Jody, is that you?
( Creaking )
( Breathing )
( Rattling continues )
( Tearing )
( Grunts )
( Yells )
You hit my fuckin' foot, man!
You won't believe this, but these things
were here and they were gonna get me!
Ah, gimme a break, will you?
They were jumping on the car,
making these weird sounds.
Sure it wasn't that retarded kid, Timmy?
No, it was the same thing
that chased me last night!
Well, what are we gonna do?
You're crazy, man.
Huh.
( Rattles gate )
( Loud bang )
( Door bangs )
( Bang )
( Banging )
- ( Growling )
- ( Gasps )
( Whooshing )
( Yells )
Um...
Oh, shit!
( Screaming )
( Screaming continues )
- ( Screaming stops )
- ( Banging )
( Pattering sounds )
( Squeaking )
- ( Growling )
- ( Gasping )
( Grunts )
I gotta talk to you.
- And it's in that box?
- Yep.
OK, I believe you.
Jesus!
What's goin' on up there?
Well, there's somethin' I didn't tell you.
I was spying on Tommy's funeral
from the groves.
After everybody left, that tall man
picked up Tommy's coffin all by himself,
- put it in the hearse, and drove off.
- You're crazy.
I helped carry that sucker myself,
it must have weighed over 500 pounds.
( Sighs )
I can't figure this thing out.
But I do know one thing.
Something weird is going on up there.
We're going for the sheriff.
Go get your...evidence.
All right!
That's funny.
( Screeching )
( Buzzing )
Jody! Jody!
( Buzzing continues )
The garbage disposal. Come on.
( Buzzing )
You ready? Go!
( Grinding )
Would you look at that.
( Knock on door )
Hi, guys.
Thought I'd come and see what was goin'
on before the kids got outta summer school.
Mike, you wanna ride along with me today?
It's pretty warm outside
and the ice cream'll be flyin' fast and furious.
Remember how good you were
at crowd control last time...
Hey, what's goin' on here?
( Buzzing )
Ah!
- Ah!
- ( Buzzing )
( Grinding )
What the hell is goin' on?
Here, you keep that.
Now remember, you don't aim a gun
at a man unless you intend to shoot him,
and you don't shoot a man
unless you intend to kill him.
No warning shots.
Hey, you listen' to me?
- Yeah.
- No warning shots.
Warning shots are bullshit.
You shoot to kill, or you don't shoot at all.
Now, you'll be safe here.
Just lock all the doors and windows.
And don't follow me.
You sure you're gonna be OK with that?
I'm just gonna go up there and take
a look around. Nobody's gonna see me.
But heck, a Colt army issue
will put a man down, and keep him there.
Remember that broken basement window
around by the side...and be careful.
( Growling )
- ( Grunts )
- ( Growling )
- Ah!
- ( Gunshot )
- ( Growling )
( Growling continues )
( Car approaching )
( Breathing heavily )
All right, who's in there?
Mike?
- Mike.
- Damn door latch! Get in.
( Tyres squeal )
- Uh-oh, here it comes!
- There nobody drivin' that mother!
Pump's in the back seat.
OK, slow down
and let him ride right up on our ass.
There was nobody...
there was nobody driving!
I'm gonna get that bastard!
Oh, Jesus!
All right, speed up.
I'm gonna put a few in the engine.
OK.
Holy shit!
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
It's one of those dwarfs.
He went right through it!
Tommy!
Reggie...
we got one of 'em.
Uh, in Colton, in the groves.
All right. Uh, Reg?
Bring your truck.
Jesus!
You didn't tell me the dwarf was Tommy.
Hell, we buried him on Monday
and look what they did to him.
He's only three feet long,
he must still weigh 200 pounds.
What's all this yellow shit
comin' out of his head?
Careful, get him in there.
- Better padlock it.
- Yeah.
Hey, this guy's not gonna leak
all over my ice cream, is he?
Nah. I'll see you back at the house.
Right.
Hey, you boys back again?
Jesus Christ, Myrtle,
you almost gave me a coronary!
But I just can't figure out why.
Why they're taking these bodies
and crushing 'em down to half size.
Crushing 'em!
What about Mom and Dad?
They're up there too.
Hey, just forget about that.
OK...I see it, I see it all now.
What we gotta do is snag that tall dude
and stomp the shit out of him,
and we'll find out what the hell
is goin' on up there.
We'll lay that sucker flat and drive
a stake right through his goddamn heart!
You gotta be shittin' me, man,
that mother's strong!
Hey, hold on.
First thing is, I want Mike outta here.
Reg, you take him over to Sally's,
the antique store.
He'll be safe there. Then hustle on back.
And Mike, no arguments.
Jody sure sounded strange on the phone.
I hope he's feeling OK.
Sally, did you see these new settings?
Oh, these are nice.
You know, I think I'm gonna lock up.
Michael, when you get sleepy,
I've got a bed made up for you in back.
You have to take me home.
- But why?
- No questions. You must take me home.
( # Van chimes play Three Blind Mice # )
( Thumping )
( Growling )
( Creaking )
( Wailing )
( Footsteps echoing )
Aargh!
Oh, my God, pull over.
MIKE: Stay in the car and don't get out.
I'll be right back.
WOMAN: Michael, wait a minute.
Is that Reggie's truck?
( Dripping )
Let's get outta here, quick!
Michael, what is going on?
Just get me home.
( Rattling )
What the hell's that?
Oh, shit!
( Rattling continues )
Get outta here!
( Rattling )
Don't open it!
- No!
- ( Screams )
( Mike grunts )
( Screaming continues )
Oh!
( Glass shatters )
( Screaming )
Hey, man.
They got Sally and Susie.
What?
Up at Morningside. And Reggie too.
You better get on up to your room.
- I'm goin' with you!
- Nope.
I'm not letting you go by yourself.
Let me go, God damn it!
Son of a bitch,
you're not letting me go, are you?
You're never coming back,
you goddamn bastard!
Don't leave me alone!
Open the damn door!
( Breathing heavily )
I've been waiting for you.
No.
( Laughs )
( Tyres squeal )
Ah!
( Grunting )
He has to be in there.
( Buzzing )
I'm sorry, Daddy...but we had to.
( Yells )
Oh, my God!
( Whirring )
- Jody...
- Yeah?
Um, I opened up his...
Forget it.
C'mon.
There's this door down here...
and I'll bet there's something behind it.
Well, let's take a look, then.
( Electrical humming )
Well, that's the door.
- Hey, man, I dunno...
- Hey!
Hi guys.
Reg...you ain't dead!
No, and I ain't three foot two yet either.
- What's goin' on?
- Hey, man, I don't know.
I've been hiding in a casket
playin' like a stiff, but I did find the girls.
I found Sally and Sue, and a couple
of other girls I never even saw before.
Were they dead?
No. I snuck 'em out a window and they took
off through the bushes like scared rabbits.
All right.
Well...after you, my friend.
You be my guest.
Gee!
Dwarfs!
God, Reggie, look at this!
( Whooshing )
GIRL: Don't fear.
Aargh!
( Wailing )
Jesus!
God...I just grabbed him there.
- Slaves.
- What?
Slaves!
They're using 'em for slaves!
The dwarfs.
And they gotta crush 'em...
cos of the gravity...and the heat.
And this is the door to their planet.
Yeah!
And these guys are all ready to go.
Yeah.
( Humming stops )
JODY: OK, stay together.
- MIKE: Wait, I think I got a lighter.
- JODY: Light it up.
( Yells )
JODY: Over here, follow me.
( Bang )
REGGIE: Jody, where are you?
Mike?
( Growling )
Aw, shit!
Mike!
Mike, where are you?
( Electrical humming starts up )
( Humming stops )
( Gasps )
( Howling wind )
Jody!
Jody, where are you?
Jody! Jody!
Jody!
( Gasps )
Jody, where are you?
Mike! Mike!
Mike, Mike, c'mon, we gotta find Reggie.
( Gasping )
( Groans )
Where's Reggie? We gotta find him.
- It's Reggie! We...
- No!
- C'mon, we gotta help him!
- No, you can't help him, he's dead!
There's a...
there's an old mine shft, way down
by...by the end of Singer's Creek.
A thousand feet straight down.
We just gotta...gotta figure out a way
to get him up there.
What are we gonna do without Reggie?
Reggie's the last he'll ever get...
cos we're gonna run that tall bastard
straight down to hell.
( Sighs ) Look, you go in
and try and find some more ammo.
I'm gonna get rid of that warning barrier
around the mine shaft and camouflage it.
OK, lock up the house good,
and stay in there. I'll be right back.
Ah!
( Crashing )
( Laughs ) Boy!
You play a good game, boy,
but the game is finished.
Now you die!
Don't fear.
Oh!
( Wailing )
( Wailing continues )
( Gasps )
Don't fear.
Ah!
( Screams )
( Thunder rumbles )
( Thunderclap )
I hear the sounds.
I know those rocks aren't gonna hold him.
Not for long.
Hey, you had a dream. Just a nightmare.
What do you expect? You've
hardly slept since the funeral last week.
- I know those rocks aren't gonna hold him.
- ( Thunderclap )
First he took Mom and Dad...
then he took Jody...
now he's after me.
Mike, that tall man of yours
did not take Jody away.
Jody died in a car wreck.
( Birds singing )
Mike...you had a bad dream.
Now, I know you're scared...
but you're not alone.
I'll take care of you.
I know I can't ever take Jody's place...
but I'm sure as hell gonna try.
Seems so real.
You know, partner,
what we need is a change of scenery.
Why don't you and me hit the road
for a couple of weeks?
Where will we go?
Well, I don't know. I guess we can
figure that one when we get there.
OK.
Well, get on upstairs,
get your gear together,
cos we leave when the sun comes up.
( # Humming # )
Boy!
Aargh!
( Growling )
Captioned by Grantman Brown
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org