Subtitled by
A C E   C R I S
- Good morning.
- 'Morning.
Can you spell "parakeet"?
Parakeet.
B-l-R-D.
- Wrong. Try again.
- Wrong?
Wrong, Aunt Trish. Try again.
- What's for breakfast?
- My turn?
Darling, Donna has locked herself
in our bathroom.
Would you get her out of there?
- My favorite role, the wicked stepmother.
- Absolutely.
- It's chilly in here this morning.
- I'll check that.
- You making breakfast?
- Aunt Trish said it's my turn.
Shh with that "Aunt Trish" stuff.
I have been begging you since you got here
not to call her that.
- It's been a month already.
- Bruce, old habits die hard, you know.
- Right, they do.
- My mom always calls her Trish.
My grandma always called her Trish.
But Aunt Pat hates it.
She thinks it's déclassé.
Déclassé?
- Call her Pat, will you?
- I'll try.
- You want to help me make breakfast?
- I'd love to.
What does "déclassé" mean?
Come on.
I heard Mom and Pop called last night.
Yeah, they did.
Just a second.
We're gonna be late again,
and you still have to use my eyeliner...
which I have.
- Here.
- Thanks.
You look great.
Now remember, less is more.
We got eggs, sausage, bacon, dill pickles.
What will it be?
Toast'ems.
No. Not again.
I cook. You set the table.
- Done.
- A masterpiece.
- A veritable Picasso.
- He would have put your nose over here.
Can I borrow this?
- You look like an Eskimo.
- I'm a California person.
I'm not used to wearing this stuff.
Listen, surfer girl,
the week before you got here...
the temperature got above zero
for about six minutes.
If it's this cold inside, you're gonna
appreciate those when you get outside.
Doesn't it ever get warm in Chicago?
You are going to regret
that remark come August, young lady.
August? I'm supposed to go home
before August.
If I had my way, I'd keep you here forever.
- What are you gonna wear tonight?
- Last year's salary.
- It wasn't that expensive.
- Yeah?
- What are you gonna wear, Dad?
- My tux.
- The one you wore to your wedding?
- Yeah, that one.
- Fashion's never been your father's thing.
- It's a year old, dear.
I think he looks handsome
in his wedding pictures.
- There you are. The voice of sanity.
- I agree.
- Handsome, but conservative.
Wait a minute,
you're on my side, remember?
A woman's entitled to change her mind.
No, thanks. We'll take the next one.
- Who's driving me to work?
- Me.
Let's go.
All aboard.
Thank you, my lady.
Fasten your seat belts.
You better be careful, honey.
- Remember what happened to Narcissus.
- Who?
Greek mythology. He loved looking
at his reflection in a pond so much...
he fell in and drowned.
- Only a boy could be that clumsy.
- You got that right.
What's wrong?
Every new building has its problems.
We'll get those problems
before they get us, right?
Right?
Hold it, please!
- Bye, honey.
- Have a good day.
- Thanks for the lift.
- 'Bye, Dad.
'Morning, Gene. How you doing?
- 'Morning, Bruce.
- 'Morning.
- 'Morning, Mr. Gardner.
- 'Morning. What's with the heat?
I'm checking it now.
Probably a thermo on the fritz.
Get it fixed and have somebody check out
Freight Elevator 15. It's got a stutter in it.
15? Sure.
Wait up!
Great! I don't have to go
to that creepy school today.
Oh, no.
Come on, we'll cut them off at the pass.
Our 50 elevators will be carrying...
approximately 12,000 passengers a day...
swiftly and conveniently,
to our many shops, offices...
condominiums, and restaurants.
Come on!
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen,
to a glimpse of the future.
Taxi!
It's hotter than Hell out here.
There they are.
Look, there's that snot Donna
and her yucky little cousin.
- They're late again.
- Cool it, Marcie.
Hi, Donna.
- Sorry.
- It's okay. Your turn on Monday.
You get two fun-filled weeks
to pilot the Enterprise.
- Two weeks?
- Two kids, two weeks.
- Just like me.
- Come on, Mom. We're going to be late.
- Okay.
- 'Bye.
In fact, we like to think we are a city,
a safe, efficient metropolis...
that will take us into the 21st century.
Hi, Mary.
Konnichiwa.
Did you forget to pay the heating bill?
It's freezing here.
I know, it's strange. It's warmer outside.
Why are they moving the Tods?
Takamitsu doesn't want them
intermingling with his work, darling.
Is he going to be responsible...
for $26,000 worth
of postmodern neo-abstraction?
You're the one who gave him carte blanche.
Is everything set?
Caterers, brochures, music?
Everything is set.
Calm down, go sit down and relax.
Nothing is gonna go wrong.
- Not over there!
- That's where he told us to put it.
- Take it easy.
- Watch it!
Got it!
It's okay. We got it.
Nothing's going to go wrong.
- You're coming to my party tonight?
- I don't think so.
- How come?
- She can't come to our party tonight.
She has to stay upstairs
and take care of Carol Anne.
Because her mother's having her own party
tonight. I heard her mother tell Mom.
- It's my party, not ours.
- Listen, mouth, Pat's not my mother.
And if I wanted to come
to your brother's party, I could.
- You got a second?
- Yeah, what's up, Nate?
Come here, let me show you something.
All right. Where are we going?
What? Somebody broke the mirror.
Replace it.
Not just this panel. Every panel from
the concourse all the way up to the top.
You guys have to see this.
Ice.
Now, how the hell could that happen?
I kind of hoped you'd tell us, Mr. Gardner.
Sally, call the heating
and air conditioning contractor.
Tell Stan to get to my office
with a schematic for the ventilation system.
- Pronto.
- Yes, sir, Mr. Gardner.
How come you go to
the Seaton school for weirdoes?
It's for smart kids, not weirdoes.
That's why you don't go there.
- There she is.
- Yeah, okay.
Thank you, Mrs. Moyer.
- Seen any ghosts lately?
- Leave her alone.
- You a cop or something?
- Watch it, you little asshole.
Shut the door.
You're so déclassé.
Damn.
Yeah, I know.
The kids have started teasing her.
I was hoping we could keep her ghosts
in my closet.
This doesn't make my job any easier.
- That's why you get the big bucks, Doc.
- Funny, Deborah.
- You could call in an exorcist.
- Funnier.
I'm really sorry
you're not coming to the party.
I kind of hoped...
you were.
Scott, my knight in shining acne.
Shut up, and leave them alone.
Maybe we could catch a movie
tomorrow night.
Maybe. Call me.
He's still panting.
I wish Dusty would pant that way for me.
Jeff's constantly in heat.
I practically have to muzzle him every night.
It's a real drag.
Maybe he could give Dusty ideas?
- I don't know if you could handle it.
- It'll be totally radical to try.
Get a grip, girls.
This...
is the Second Piano Concerto by Chopin.
I'll bet all of you probably think...
this was written by some old geezer
who looked like Dr. Seaton.
Well, it wasn't. In fact...
Freddy Chopin composed this
when he was only 19 years old...
and he'd already written a lot.
He'd been playing by ear
and making up tunes since he was 6.
At 8...
he had written
his first of several polonaises.
And at the ripe old age of 1 2...
he was asked to play for the Czar of Russia.
Pretty scary, even for an old-timer of 1 2.
In this school, where we're dealing with
gifted children with emotional problems...
we have to open them up.
So, we make them aware of the fact...
that other famous child prodigies
shared similar problems.
It makes them comfortable
to know they're not that different.
These kids are about to find out
that Chopin was crippled by shyness...
- And used music to overcome it.
- Excuse me, Dr. Seaton...
that little blonde girl keeps staring
at the mirror as if she sees us.
- Do you think she can?
- No.
But you think she's staring straight at you?
That is one of her dubious talents,
making people believe things.
- Has she ever...
- Let's talk in the hall.
She's a very interesting case,
our Carol Anne.
Reasonably well-balanced,
extremely intelligent...
IQ well into the 150s,
and one hell of an imagination.
- Most bright kids do.
- True...
but even the brightest ones allow adults
to intimidate them back to reality.
"Dad, there's a purple cow in our yard."
"What, are you nuts? Get out of here."
But Carol Anne's different
than most of our other geniuses.
She seems able to project her imagination...
convince others that
the purple cow in the yard is real.
Apparently, she actually convinced
an entire neighborhood that it was haunted.
There's a talent.
You think she's able to create
some sort of mass hysteria?
No, not really. It's more like mass hypnosis.
As I work with her, try to work with her,
the child's impossible...
the more I'm convinced she actually might
be capable of inducing mass hypnosis.
- Have you put her under?
- Only once. It was terrifying.
- For her?
- For both of us.
I started to experience what she was seeing.
My God.
He found her.
I'm sorry. Stay and finish your tea.
I've got to go.
Mommy, where are you? I can't see you!
Where are you?
He's after me, Mommy! I'm scared!
Yes, I am ready!
I can't find you! He's getting closer!
Who?
The man! The ugly man!
I've got you, Carol Anne. You're safe.
You're in your room in Cuesta Verde.
You're safe.
Everything's calm.
Tell me about what's just happened.
The man wanted me
to lead him into the light.
It's so cold there. I heard them talking.
He said it was my daddy's fault
because of the houses...
the houses my daddy built on their graves.
He said I had to lead them into the light.
Into the light.
- Why do you have to lead them?
- I was born in that house.
- Robbie! The tree's eating Robbie!
- Sleep.
I'm going to count to three.
And when I snap my fingers,
you will awaken.
You will not remember any of this.
One...
two...
three.
How do you feel?
Okay.
One word.
How do you feel deep down inside?
I don't know.
Lonely, maybe.
Lonely?
Sure, why not?
It gets Ionely being away from home,
doesn't it?
Yeah. Aunt...
Pat and Bruce and Donna are real nice,
but I miss my mom and dad.
And even my brother.
That's very good.
- What?
- The way you made me look in the mirror.
I didn't make you look at anything.
That's what he meant, manipulation.
What were you looking at
that made me turn?
Nothing.
You were looking at something.
I don't want to talk about it.
When you talk about things
that bother you, they go away.
No, if you talk about things, they happen.
Who told you that?
Go away!
Are you all right?
What happened? What broke the mirror?
A little demonstration in mass hypnosis.
She made me believe I saw a coffee mug...
fly off my desk into the mirror...
while giving you a suggestion to smash it.
Beautiful sight, isn't it?
Did I ever tell you
how to make a little girl laugh?
I never did?
It takes a lot of practice.
The first thing you got to do...
is tickle right here in the ribs.
Don't worry about
that seven years' bad luck stuff.
That's old wives' tales.
- I didn't break it.
- I believe you.
But I'll tell you a secret.
If that old nerd were my doctor,
I would have done it.
I didn't. He did.
Dr. Seaton?
I don't want to talk about it, okay?
How's Carol Anne?
I don't know.
How would you feel if some quack told you
you had supernatural powers?
Do you remember that guy
who was on all the talk shows?
What was his name?
He was from Israel or someplace.
He used to bend keys, fix watches...
took Polaroids of himself in the dark.
Maybe Carol Anne...
Please, not you, too.
Give the kid a break, please.
First your crazy brother-in-law
uses her as a scapegoat...
for those $250,000
collapsible homes he builds...
- Steven didn't...
- Steven and your sister have put...
that poor thing through hell, with
those weirdo psychics and witch doctors.
Weirdo psychics and witch doctors!
Come on!
Darling, you are the only sane person
in your family.
Please.
Don't let that pompous-ass shrink...
tell you she's Carrie or Houdini
or some damn thing like that.
Nobody really knows
what happened there this afternoon.
Maybe we shouldn't leave
the girls here alone tonight.
Maybe we should forget
the opening altogether.
Don't be stupid.
We're both being stupid.
You have opening night jitters...
- I have a building falling apart.
- Exactly.
We needed my sister pressuring us to take
her kid like we needed a hole in the head.
I really don't mind
a house full of beautiful women.
- The more the merrier.
- Then hire us a maid.
Swedish, about 24?
- 5'2"? Talk about pressure.
- Will you go get dressed?
What did I say?
Hi, sweetie. Can I have a good night kiss?
All set.
- Have a good night's sleep.
- Good night.
Be right with you.
She's got the hots for him. I'm serious.
I see her every single day.
Look for her at the start of the day.
I'm dead serious.
She follows him all the time. Yeah, what?
Will you do me a favor?
- No ghost stories tonight, all right?
- Gotcha.
- Good night.
- 'Bye.
My dad.
I don't know what he's talking about.
Not bad at all.
Forget it.
However, after the opening...
I know it's going to be a great party,
but I can't come.
No, I'm brat-sitting.
She's not even a relative.
She's sort of a relative, but not really.
Yeah, if Scott wants to call me
from the party...
I might talk to him.
'Bye.
- What you doing?
- Eavesdropping.
- Why don't you go to Martin's party?
- You know I can't.
I'll cover for you, they'll never know.
If I get caught, we'll be in trouble.
I can take the heat.
I didn't mean
what I said to Sandy on the phone.
I don't mind being "sort of a relative."
As long as we're friends.
Good.
There are some people over here
I'd like you to meet.
It looks like the show is a success, darling.
- Like the art. Love the sushi.
- It's nice to see you.
Excuse me, Pat, come here,
I've got to talk to you.
Hello, Mary.
- Are you trying to save money on the heat?
- I wish that were the case. New equipment.
- Trying to work out the bugs and all that.
- Good to see you.
- You look great.
- Anne Klein II.
Remember, less is more.
You look great.
Maybe I ought to stay home
with you tonight.
Just go already. I'll be fine.
How come you're taking
your dad's passkey?
I'm gonna use the emergency stairs
so nobody sees me in the elevator.
You got Martin's number, right?
- I won't stay long.
- Have fun.
- Be good.
- I will.
- What's the matter? Is the stereo broken?
- It's my parents.
- Thought they weren't gonna be home.
- Tell me about it.
My father's not well, and my mom says
if she can hear the party, it's over.
I thought you couldn't come.
Couldn't stay away from hot Scott?
Back to your cage. It's feeding time.
- $50 and she's history.
- You're on!
Hi there.
I can't believe
I risked getting into trouble for this.
I bet we could find some trouble.
Your parents aren't home.
Sounds great.
How many bedrooms have you got?
- Shut up.
- Carol Anne's up there.
Is anything open in the galleria?
Forget it, didn't bring my fake ID.
My stepmom's having a party there.
I can't go.
You're a real killjoy tonight, aren't you?
- Isn't there a pool in this building?
- It's locked at night.
But...
G-O-R...
l-L-L-A.
That is correct.
Can you spell "pheasant"?
P-H...
We're back!
- Leave me alone!
- I've got you!
Let go of me!
You can't get away. I've got you.
You can't get away!
You can't get away.
We need you.
Come here, Carol Anne.
Closer.
You can't get away. I've got you!
I've got you!
Break the mirror.
No!
Hello?
- Who is this?
- Carol Anne needs your help.
Kane found her, and it's all your fault.
Carol Anne, are you on this line?
This is one of your little pranks?
Hello?
- Who was that?
- A pest.
Bruce Gardner, please, on Michigan Avenue.
My little pest from the west
playing her little tricks.
Thank you.
Jesus Christ!
- What did that?
- It's not a what, it's a who.
I'm gonna nip that little prank
right in the bud.
Where are you going?
To that art gallery opening
we decided not to go to.
Put dinner on a low flame.
Don't forget the cilantro.
Hello, Mrs. Moyer? This is Carol Anne.
Is Donna there?
Are you sure?
Okay, thank you.
There's a camera in the hallway.
We'll go in twos. I'll tell you when to go.
Run under the camera
and stand against the door.
You ready?
Go!
Ready?
Get ready.
Let's go.
Hurry up!
Watch the camera. When the red light
goes off, go into the locker rooms.
- There's always suits on the clotheslines.
- Who needs a suit?
- You do!
- Come on.
Come on.
We need you.
Sam, the stairway alarm just went off on 70.
Anything on the monitor?
It looks like that camera ain't working either.
Better go check it out.
Come on.
You knock on the door, tell Burt
you saw some creepy guy walking on 67.
As soon as he leaves, we'll go in.
- He's coming out.
- Where's he going?
- He just got in the elevator.
- Wait.
Okay, let's go.
What are you gonna do?
Gonna run the videotape back two hours...
then I'm going to change the monitor
from camera to VCR.
When he comes back in, he'll be watching
two hours of videotape on the monitor.
- Okay, let's go.
- Have you got a key for that?
- Yeah. Why?
- Beer.
- I'm not going to steal...
- I got money.
- No way.
- Yes.
I'm your friend, Carol Anne.
We need you to lead us into the light.
Lead us into the light.
Come on.
Let's go.
Want to see real panic?
Pretty impressive.
This is the police. We have you surrounded.
Come out with your hands up
and your pants down!
Hello, this is your camp director.
Jeff, quit pissing in the pool.
Scott had a girl
And Donna was her name
Donna, Donna
Shit!
Don't be afraid.
We won't harm you.
We love you.
You are the only angel...
who can lead us into the light.
We would never hurt you.
Never!
Don't run away from me.
We need you, Carol Anne.
Lead us into the light.
Help me! Let go of me! Help!
Donna! Help!
Help me! Donna! Quick!
Holy shit!
Donna, help!
- Just hold on!
- Please help me!
- Grab on to me!
- Donna, pull.
- Pull her! I got her!
- Hang on!
- Pull her! Hold on!
- Help me!
Don't let go.
- Hold on to her!
- Pull!
- Hang on!
Hold on.
I love that! Love it! Yeah!
Smoking more now and enjoying it less?
Thinking more and enjoying it less.
- There's something wrong.
- Tell me about it.
Takamitsu offended
everyone he talked to tonight.
Excuse me, Mr. Gardner. I just got a call.
There's a bunch of kids
partying up in the pool...
who claim they're guests of your daughter.
Excuse me.
Okay, so you all left the party together,
and they let you in here...
went to the security room
to turn off the camera...
- And then where did they go?
- I don't know where Scott and Donna went.
We didn't hurt anything.
All we were doing was swimming.
- Where was Carol Anne through all this?
- Not with us.
Thanks, guys. Take the kids back to 56-E.
- I'll talk with their parents later.
- Right, Mr. Gardner. Come on!
My parents are going to ground me
till I'm 40.
It'll give you time to study.
You might get something
besides Auto Shop this year.
- They got Donna.
- Who's got Donna?
- They got Donna and Carol Anne.
- Who's got Carol Anne?
- They got them.
- Who, damn it?
- What happened?
- He just came up through the ice.
- What ice?
- The ice in the...
pool.
She's gotten to you, too.
It's a suggestion, Mr. Gardner.
A posthypnotic suggestion.
They got them. They got Donna,
and they got Carol Anne.
They got them both. They've got them.
Aunt Trish, help me!
She's mine!
Please help me.
Help me!
- Help me!
- Hang on, I'm pulling!
Hang on.
I've got you.
Hold on!
Help!
Hold on, Carol Anne! We've got you!
Pull!
- Grab hold of her!
- I've got her.
Pull! Don't let go!
Get away!
That's not Carol Anne!
Damn you!
Stay back.
He's got the girls and now he wants you.
- What are you talking about?
- The preacher Kane.
He knows as long as there's someone
on this side that loves them...
you can get them back.
How did you know that wasn't Carol Anne?
What surprised me, dear...
is that you didn't.
Who the hell are you?
I'm one of your brother-in-law's...
weirdo psychics.
Carol Anne and Donna are not in that room.
- Some goddamned thing is.
- Yes.
Anger, rage...
evil, they are in that room.
Can you feel the cold?
He's devouring the heat, the energy.
He's gathering his strength.
We must find the girls
before he becomes too strong.
If Donna and Carol Anne aren't in that room,
then where are they?
The other side.
Before we can find the girls,
we must find out where they entered.
Where did Dr. Rasputin...
take Scott?
Excuse me, Dr. Seaton?
Excuse us.
Do your stuff.
I want you to look at the light.
Look at the light.
- Security.
- Burt, this is Gardner.
Get your guys together. My daughter
and niece are roaming the building...
and I'd like them found
as soon as possible, okay?
What?
Damn it!
Yeah, okay.
Terrific.
First the heating,
then the electrical problems...
now the security monitors.
This is really happening, isn't it?
Depends on who you want to believe.
Tweedledum or Tweedle-dumber.
You and Donna are at the swimming pool.
You're leaving.
Where are you going?
The security room.
We saw Carol Anne on the monitor.
Which monitor?
She was in the garage.
The puddle!
Hands came out of the puddle!
They grabbed us, the hands!
Keep her away from me!
What puddle?
In the garage.
They're between dimensions...
behind reflections...
behind mirrors, stealing images.
The light!
The light, it's so cold!
Listen to me.
Find your way back to your room.
You must go back to your room.
He won't let me!
I'm so cold!
Find Donna and go back to your room. Run!
Enough. Stop this stupid sideshow.
It's a great act. Carol Anne creates the fire,
and you feed it.
You made this happen.
You made her talk about him,
you made her remember him.
He was lost. You brought him here.
Ludicrous.
It's your choice...
Tweedledum...
or Tweedle-dumber.
Tell us what to do.
Pray that Carol Anne heard me and listens.
We must get up there as fast as we can.
This is stupid, idiotic!
What's the matter with you people?
Can't you see Carol Anne's behind this?
She's making us believe this is happening.
It's all a hypnotic...
That's as stupid and idiotic...
as you hypnotizing that coffee cup
through the mirror.
That's good.
He'll try to trick you.
He'll try to separate you.
Don't let him.
Your love, your bond...
your caring for these two children,
is our most valuable weapon.
Let me take the chances.
What's that? Some sort of mystical amulet?
- A tool of your trade?
- It was a gift...
from a good friend...
a powerful medicine man,
who walked among the spirits...
and returned.
There's power here.
I only pray it is enough.
Because Kane still thinks he needs her.
He was insane when he lived.
And now, in death, that insanity...
has become the beast.
He wants Carol Anne now...
before she grows up.
Youth is a strong life force.
Innocence is pure life force.
We lose strength as we lose our innocence.
You see, innocence is the only gift
we're given in life.
All else must be fought for.
In that gift is purity.
In that purity...
lies strength.
- That's a lot of meaningless crap.
- Shut up.
Unlock it.
Can you spell "gorilla"?
G-O...
R-I...
L-L-A.
That is correct. Now try "pheasant. "
Look at the mirror.
...H- E...
A...
S-A...
N-T.
That is correct. Can you spell "parakeet"?
P...
...R...
Come back to this side, Carol Anne.
Come through the mirror.
We want you to come join us.
We miss you.
You can come back through the mirror.
Please come back through the mirror.
Come back to this side, sweetie.
Come to me, Carol Anne.
Don't be frightened.
Don't be afraid, sweetie. Come to us.
Won't you join us, Carol Anne?
- Come here!
- No!
Don't just stand there!
Get over here, for Christ's sake!
I got you, baby. It's okay.
Here you go.
You're all right.
- Where is she?
- Carol Anne is drowning!
- She's drowning!
- Where?
You're safe now.
Where?
- She's drowning!
- What does it matter anymore?
Who the hell goddamn cares?
Baby.
Take care of her for a minute.
It's okay.
Carol Anne's drowning!
- You got to get a hold of yourself.
- I can't deal with this anymore.
I love you and Donna. That's our family.
Let's get out of here.
- Let Dr. Seaton deal with Carol Anne.
- She's your niece.
I don't care.
I can't take these sick little games anymore.
I never should have let Steven and Diane
send her to us.
Bruce, please!
Dad!
Relax, Donna.
You're safe.
You're just having a bad dream.
We're all having a bad dream.
Where's my dad? I want my dad.
Lie here and relax.
I'll go get your dad.
Hello?
And they thought I was her.
I saw her.
- You think you saw her.
- I saw her, damn it!
Your daughter's upstairs,
a shivering, emotional wreck.
Then you run out on me
to chase after that evil little brat again.
Don't you understand?
Don't you see what she's doing?
It's just like Dr. Seaton said.
Nothing Seaton said
explains what happened tonight.
Come on.
The man, he grabbed my hand!
Remember what Tangina said.
Open!
Help us!
Oh, God!
Outside in!
Help us!
Tangina gave this to me.
She gave this to us!
She's trying to save us.
She's trying to bring us through this.
- It's a lie. It's not true, any of this!
- No, baby.
It's not true! You're a liar!
None of this is true! You're a liar!
She's trying to get us through.
She's trying to save our lives.
Just hold on.
Just hold on, baby.
No!
Who are you?
- What do you want?
- You!
It's not cold anymore.
She said we could do it!
She said we could beat them!
It's over, baby.
It's over, darling!
- I want to believe that.
- Believe it!
It's finished, and we did it together.
Look at you.
You two are pitiful. You know what?
No, I don't want to know.
I understand these things.
Anyway, everybody went home.
And it went fine. I locked up.
You two can read about it tomorrow
in the society columns.
Newlyweds.
Donna's been looking for you. She called.
She and Carol Anne are with that shrink...
what's-his-name from the school.
You ought to talk to him.
He's probably never met anybody
with a garage fetish.
Mañana, y'all.
Mr. And Mrs. Stanley, how are you tonight?
I did some plumbing.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
What inconvenience?
We didn't have a problem.
If there was a problem, I'm sorry.
But the hot water's gonna be on very soon.
I had to say something. I mean, look at us.
I didn't get much use
out of last year's salary.
I think you look great wet.
- You can lie like that anytime you want to.
- I usually do.
I know.
I can't wait to get upstairs,
stretch out in bed...
and act normal.
- Getting upstairs sounds great.
- What have you got in mind?
Packing everything
that belongs to that brat...
and sending her home to my sister.
It wasn't her fault.
Yes, it is!
Oh, my God!
- Outside in!
- What?
Damn it! Outside in.
That's what Tangina said.
He controls the inside, but not the outside!
We can still get to him. Come on.
Don't look down.
All right, hold onto this.
No matter what happens, don't let go.
Fucking son of a bitch!
Go away!
He doesn't want them! He only wants me!
You don't love me. You don't want me here!
My parents don't love me, either!
They sent me away!
Kane loves me! Kane wants me!
Give me Tangina's necklace,
and you can have Bruce and Donna back.
They're your family.
I'll go with Kane.
Your mom and dad do love you!
They love you very much.
And I love you, too!
It's hard for me to show it sometimes,
but I do love you!
Save your family!
They're the ones who
mean something to you, not me.
That's not true!
You are part of my family!
You and Donna are like my children!
I love you, and I'll do anything to prove that!
You've got to believe me!
No! Go away!
Go away!
God!
Where are you, Kane?
Where have you taken my family?
I want them back!
Tangina said you can't take them...
as long as someone here loves them.
I love them.
And I have this to protect me.
The necklace!
Give me the necklace!
No.
The necklace!
Oh, God!
Give her back her family.
You don't need them!
You don't need Carol Anne!
I can lead you into the light!
I have the knowledge and the power!
No! Tangina, don't!
Tell me how to use the necklace
so I can save all of you.
Thank you, Pat.
But this is the way it has to be.
Say goodbye to Carol Anne for me.
Tell her I'll always love her...
and that her nightmare is over.
Tangina, wait!
Where are they?
She did it.
She saved us.
Subtitled by
A C E   C R I S