Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
But cancer or madness
contort reality.
The possibility I'm talking
about pierces reality.
I'm unable to say it, maybe.
Maybe it's impossible to say,
maybe I'm too stupid.
You're looking at me as if you...
You're looking at me as if to tell me
that I need you to fill me up,
as if I'm an empty space.
Well, I love you too,
but what makes me go on
is to know he'll return,
and I'll make him suffer, and...
And I'll hurt him, and...
I'm betraying him, but...
this brings me small rewards.
Well... But yet, I...
I can't exist by myself
because I'm afraid of myself.
Because I'm the maker of my own evil.
Because...
Because I'm...
Goodness is only some kind
of reflection upon evil.
That's the way it is.
What are you doing?!
I'm sorting out his things
to take to the laundry.
I can do it myself.
-But it's my job!
Very kind of...
-I'm better at it!
Maybe you could do it
when Bob is at home.
It's getting... so difficult
for you, isn't it? You're not as...
You're not as strong or as sure of
yourself as you thought you were,
so you keep coming back.
You must be...
torn apart.
I can...
I can think more clearly now.
I guess ...
I guess when you're there...
you want to be home,
and when you're home...
you want to be there.
If what you have there
is so strong for you,
if it's what you never had,
stick to it. Keep it.
It's very quiet here when you're,
when you're out.
It was very quiet
when you weren't here!
Come over here,
let's just see if we can
sit together peacefully, still.
Is it the same there?
-No!
Can you tell me now?
I messed everything up.
Even Bob.
I've been a cheat, a liar,
completely alone, wounded.
And you think I'm immoral shit.
I think so too but not
the... same reasons...
I feel nothing for no-one!
It's as if the two sisters
were too exhausted to fight anymore.
You know these women
wrestling in an arena of mud,
with their hands locked
at each other's throats.
Each waiting to see
who'll die first.
And both staring at me.
What I miscarried there
was Sister Faith.
And what was left is Sister Chance.
So I had to take care of my Faith,
to protect it.
That's what you're doing there?
Yes.
You look uglier.
You've hardened.
For the first time, you look...
vulgar, to me.
I remember when I was a kid...
Have you ever seen a dying dog,
you know, one of those old
dogs that comes to die under the,
under the porch of the house?
At the last moment...
It... yelps.
In terror.
As if it's seen something real.
I want you to take off
the ring and the wristwatch
I gave you last time I came home.
Don't forget to give him his yoghurt.
No.
I have to go!
If I threw myself at your feet and
yelped, would you still walk over me?
Yes.
Hello, this is Anna's husband speaking.
-Anna's not here.
I don't have the slightest idea
what's happening to her.
Do you love your son?
-Sir!
Tell him that I love him too.
I love everybody and everything.
I accept everything,
I have become wise,
and profound, and good.
Do you want to talk to him?
We're just having coffee.
No, I don't want to talk to him, I...
I don't want your coffee to get cold,
either, I certainly love your coffee.
Just tell Heinrich
that Anna's address
is Sebastianstrasse 87.
First floor.
Five, six, seven, sky!
Eight, seven,
six, five, four, three...
Madam teacher, my apologies
for being late. -No, it's alright.
Anyway, we were waiting for you.
Thank you.
And goodbye, Bob.
what is it?
My name.
I respected your wish to be alone,
I thought you needed the time,
but now it's time enough.
Besides, what are you doing here, anyway?
Don't resist me.
You know I'm stronger than you.
I'm the only one in your life
who has rights on you.
Because I don't claim any.
I brought it from India.
You know, this is what the French
poet Michaux was writing about.
I kept it for you.
With this,
love opens to absolutely
unknown horizons.
Absolutely unknown...
We are made to swim
in the center of the stream.
Not to wait on the dry banks.
Yes ... exactly.
I showed you the door to God.
And this door is always open.
Come.
Is this a joke?
What is it?
Anna!
These must be removed.
They are beginning to smell.
This can't be true.
I've got to keep this
place clean and well.
Oh my God!
-Are you going to help me,
Heinrich?
You are no different
from anyone else.
We are all the same.
But in different words.
In different bodies.
Different versions.
Like insects!
Meat!
Calling all ambulances and
fire engines to the site of the crash.
And two trucks!
Where?
Can you answer the door, Bob?
Now listen, Heinrich.
Just stay where you are.
At the bar at the corner?
Bleed for a while.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
My son took the car.
An automatic one...
Can you look after Bob
till I get back? -What is it?
It's Mommy calling me.
No, not, not here.
Go to the toilet.
Need a Tampax?
How can you joke
while I'm so hurt?
There are corpses in there.
At least two bodies.
I thought she was pulling
my leg, but no, there's blood.
She cuts them. A monster,
a joke, but it was alive.
You're drunk, Heinrich.
She cuts us to pieces, Mark!
-Maybe she just didn't want to see you.
Don't joke, I am not joking!
-Alright, I'm not joking.
So what do you want?
-Don't you understand?
She's killing people.
I understand she's killing people,
so why do you call me and not the police?
She is sick, Mark,
doesn't that mean anything to you?
There are dead bodies there!
-I don't believe you.
Maybe you're stoned
on some shit you suck on.
Some mushroom you gobble?
Perhaps you did it to yourself.
Maybe you're learning how to suffer.
Now that would be an achievement!
-I feel for people!
You talk for people,
you take their wives.
I take what I want!
And I'm at peace with myself.
Nobody saw me come in, nobody.
I called you because we have
to do something to help her.
What?
It isn't normal,
it wasn't even human.
It was ...
Divine?
Perhaps you met God a moment
ago, and you didn't even realize it.
Now, you believe in God,
don't you? Certainly.
That great incomprehensible God
whom you reached through
fucking, or dope.
Am I right?
-Look, Mark.
That woman is crazy.
We have to do something.
We?
I'm not going to do anything.
-I can't leave it this way,
it's Anna, it's murder!
You are not a man, Mark,
you're a woman.
Alright, if you don't intend to do
anything and want to keep me silent,
you will have to pay.
You have money, I know it.
You have to get me out of here,
and send me on a long trip
to restore my harmony!
I deserve it!
If you had only seen what I saw!
Heinrich, help me out
of here, I'm sick!
I'm the one who is wounded,
not you!
Please!
God's light avenge them!
Giving it out clean,
and getting it back dirty!
Do you believe in God?
God?
It's in me.
Take me.
Did Margit see it?
-Yes.
That's why you killed her?
-She tried to take it away from me.
Is this Faith that helped us?
-It needs to be protected.
Like a child?
-Yes.
You know, for me,
God is still under the porch,
where the dog died.
And on the branch of the Eucalyptus tree
where I'd lie for hours,
and watch how the clouds
change the color of the grass below.
I need money.
I had to leave there.
Oh, I've cleaned all the mess,
I washed the floor,
I made the bed.
I didn't know where to go.
It became so unsafe there,
people couldn't stop
trying to take it away from me.
Okay.
Now, leave me the car.
Take Margit's keys and
go to her place and wait there.
Can you drive a motorbike?
Heinrich taught me.
It's outside. Now, I'll take
care of Bob and everything.
I'll go to the bank on Monday
and take the money out.
If Bob wakes up,
tell him...
I will.
It's only me. Go to sleep.
I have to go.
Please close the door.
Because it's here with you?
-Yes!
I'm sorry to disturb you, but...
-Yes?
You understand that it is very late,
and Heinrich hasn't called me yet.
He calls me every night so I won't
worry about when he comes home.
Maybe ...
Maybe he just forgot your number.
No, you don't understand.
Mothers always feel it
when their sons are in trouble.
Are you worried ...
Are you worried that he's not there
having sex with my wife?
They should come here.
I've put clean sheets on the bed,
and they could have dinner.
Are you quite sure you know
who you're talking to?
I am.
I went there.
-Where?
I was worried, you understand.
There isn't any apartment there
under the address you gave me.
There's only a smoking hole that the
police won't allow anybody to come near.
So I went to a bar at the corner,
to call home, to find out
if Heinrich had returned.
Yes?
And Heinrich was there.
Nobody could identify him.
Yes?
I recognized his body,
of course.
Did you... identify it
for the police?
No, it was only Heinrich's body.
But his soul was not there.
Perhaps he and the soul
had parted company before.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
No, no, you're quite right. I don't
have any idea what I'm talking about.
He must have seemed to you
better and more beautiful than you.
When Anna met him,
she immediately worshipped his soul.
And you sent him there.
Now, listen to me.
I recognize Heinrich's
superiority in every way.
I was... proud
that Anna accepted him.
Now, Anna...
has gone missing.
AAnd... I'm here,
all alone, you understand?
With our little son.
Now, I must find her,
maybe it's her fault.
I'll find her, and I'll force her
to tell me what she's done.
With Heinrich's soul.
And then I'll come to you.
And tell you.
Won't you come up?
-I'm in a rush.
Is it your wife?
-Here.
Will you promise me something?
-Yes?
Whatever it is?
I promise.
Almost.
-Yes.
Heinrich's dead.
Isn't he?
-Yes.
And you found Anna?
You come like the Angel of Death.
The one who kills.
I have thought about killing him.
-And now?
And now I don't know.
Did you see anything
that made you change your mind?
I don't know what I saw,
but Heinrich saw it too.
And you came to tell me
that you don't know...
where Heinrich's soul is?
Yes.
I can see it in your face.
It would be good to think that the
soul lives separately from the body.
That the soul lives forever,
and the body only for a time.
But it isn't so.
I don't know anymore.
-I do.
I have to be
on my son's side.
Even if he's made you unhappy.
I know all there is
to know about him.
That I love him.
-Yes.
I was wondering
which is worse:
Take away someone's wife,
hurt a child,
or to kill?
He also had a wife
and a child.
I used to like her.
I liked your Anna too.
I had to like both of them.
Since they loved him.
The world is only what it is.
Murderous.
If we are the best of it.
You don't have to worry about me.
I don't want to be here.
If Heinrich is not around anymore.
That dog didn't die of old age.
What about you, Mark?
Our man won't confide
or deal with your successor,
he wants you.
In fact, Mark,
there is no successor.
We can take care of drowning dogs,
but please help us take care
of the drowning world!
Don't you think it's uneconomical
to waste yourself on dogs?
Even dogs you love?
I met a man who loved everything.
And he died in a flood of shit.
We know.
That's just details.
When I was a boy ...
I had a dog
and his name was Louie.
When he crawled
under the porch to die,
I stayed there with him.
-So what?
I wanted to see what it was
that made him crawl under there.
Nobody's a boy anymore.
Must we prove it?
Back up, then full speed,
and crash into the police car.
My pleasure, sir.
Anna, the car!
Anna!
Run away, go!
How could you find me?
How could I not?
I wanted to show it to you.
It is finished now.
Oh yes.
So hard to live with it,
eh, Brother?
Is there a way out?
Will you help me?
-Yes.
Take it.
Shoot them.
How do you want
to finish it?
Would you open it, please?
Why not, Bob?
It could be your father.
Don't open.
-Oh, but I want to.
-But I want to!
Don't open!
Please, don't open!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org