Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
[ticking]
[moaning]
[man] The story always ends the same,
Peter Pan shouts:
[Peter] Goodbye, Wendy!
And then Wendy shouts back to him:
I'II always believe in you,
Peter Pan!
And Wendy did believe always,
even as she left childhood behind
and came to have children of her own,
There it is, Jane.
Second star to the right
and straight on to morning.
Never Land!
The second star to the right
Shines in the night for you
To tell you that the dream you plan
Really can come true
The second star to the right
Shines with a light that's rare
And if it's Never Land you need
Its light will lead you there
[bells ringing]
[man] Our story begins
in difficult times,
England is threatened with war
and many men have been asked to leave
their families to protect their country,
I'II be home before you know it.
I promise.
Now, now. What's all this?
I want to go with you.
I need you here to take
care of your mom and Danny.
Can you do that for me?
[sniffles] Mm-hmm.
That's my big girl.
- Be safe, Edward.
- Look after each other, now.
Goodbye, Daddy! I Iove you!
- I Iove you all.
- [man] Drive off!
But the war lasted much longer
than anyone could have imagined,
[bomb whistling]
Bombs fell from the sky
and tore at the very heart of London,
- Don't cry, son.
- [train whistle]
AII aboard!
In an effort to protect its children
the government decreed
that they all be sent
to the countryside for safekeeping,
- Goodbye!
- Bye-bye!
- I Iove you!
- Good Iuck, sweetie!
In times such as these
it is no wonder
some discard childish things,
Iike Peter Pan
and Never Land,
[barking]
What is it, Nanatwo?
[chuckles]
We don't have time,
you silly dog.
We have to get this home
to Danny.
[alarm siren]
Oh, no! Quick, Nanatwo!
[barking]
[siren continues]
Mommy, where's Jane?
Don't you worry, Danny.
She'II be along.
AII right, now.
Here we go.
Into the bomb shelter.
[man] Bring the Iights up!
[growling]
- What is it, girl?
- [sniffing]
- Oh, my gosh!
- [bomb whistling]
[howling]
[crashing]
Nanatwo, we're not
out of the woods yet.
We have to get back out there.
Look, who's in charge here?
- [barks]
- Don't be silly. I am!
Now, come on!
[honking]
[men shouting]
- [explosion]
- [gasping]
Mommy, I'm scared!
I don't Iike planes and bombs.
Is that what it is?
For a moment,
it sounded Iike cannons...
...on a pirate ship.
[gasps] You're right!
It's Captain Hook!
I hear him! He's coming!
- Wendy Jane!
- [Danny Jane!
Oh, Jane! Where have you been?
Why didn't you...
- Mother, I'm fine!
- Jane, you made it past the pirates!
- Daniel, careful!
- What's that? What's that?
Whoa!
Hey! It's for me, isn't it?
Let me see! Let me see!
AII right!
- Happy birthday, Daniel.
- Yippee!
Socks. Two of 'em.
Jane, dear, how very practical.
Got them a size Iarge
so he can grow into them.
Look, Danny.
Pan and Hook, see?
- Curse you, Peter Pan!
- Oh, Mother.
- I want to hear a Peter Pan story!
- [barking]
Shh! Nanatwo!
Wendy AII right, then.
How about the time
Peter and the Lost Boys
captured Hook's ship
right from under his nose?
Ooh! That's a good one!
Wendy It was Iate one misty evening
and Hook was sure once again
that he'd found Peter's hideout.
Hook and his bloodthirsty crew
went ashore
Ieaving the Jolly Roger unguarded.
That's when Peter Pan arrived!
He and the boys slipped aboard
and there they found it,
Hook's remarkable treasure!
[Danny Wow!
Wendy Peter told the Lost Boys
they'd hide it
and Hook would have to
hunt them down to get it back,
It was all a great game for Peter,
And then, from out of the mist,
he was there,
the evil Captain Hook!
A fierce and ferocious sword fight
was fast underway,
Ah-ha!
whimpers]
- Give up, boy!
- Never!
Wendy] And at that moment,
a shimmering magic covered the ship,
[Danny] Tinker Bell!
Wendy] Yes! And the Jolly Roger
lifted into the sky
as Peter and the boys
escaped with the treasure,
[grunting]
You've not seen the end of me,
Peter Pan!
I'II get you for this
if it's the Iast thing I do!
So you see, Danny,
Hook will never win
as Iong as there's faith,
trust and pixie dust.
Poppycock!
Ha! SIow down, you old codfish!
Oh, my notebook!
Ow!
- Daniel!
- Come on, Jane!
We'II beat old Captain Hook together!
Daniel, please!
I've no time for fun and games.
You used to. You got to be
the very first Lost Girl ever.
That was a Iong time ago.
Yeah. Back when you were fun.
[Jane] Honestly, Mother.
I don't know why you fill his head
with those silly stories.
- But they're not silly. They're...
- [knocking]
- Take care of Danny, will you?
Go on. I'II be right there.
- Yes?
- Evacuation, mum.
Your children are scheduled
on the morning train.
So soon?
But I haven't even told them.
The sooner the better, if you ask me.
Good night, mum.
Yes. Uh, good night.
whimpering]
Jane, dear.
Will you promise me something?
Promise you'II watch over Danny,
whatever might happen.
What?
[sighs] You and your brother
are going away for a while.
Away? But where?
AII the children are being
evacuated to the country.
It's so dangerous here.
But you'II be safe there,
both of you.
- I'm not going! I'm staying here!
- But, dear, an order has been issued.
Every child must go.
But Daddy said that I'm supposed to...
I know, dear, but you
can take care of Danny.
Tell him Peter Pan stories.
He needs them, Jane, and so do you.
PIease, dear. Promise me.
No! I will not promise!
Oh, Jane.
We'II be together again.
- You must have faith.
- Faith? Trust? Pixie dust?
Those are just words from your stories.
They don't mean anything.
[Danny Yes, they do.
Peter Pan says they'II make you fly.
Daniel, story time is over!
Look! It's a war.
Peter Pan isn't real
and people don't fly!
They do too!
- Oh, come on, Daniel! Grow up!
- Jane!
It's just a Iot of childish nonsense!
You're Iying!
Jane, how could you treat
your brother that way?
You think you're very grown-up
but you have a great deal to Iearn.
[Nanatwo groans softly
whimpering]
I am not a child now
I can take care of myself
Mustn't let them down now
Mustn't let them see me cry
I'm fine
I'm too tired to listen
I'm too old to believe
All these childish stories
There is no such thing as faith
And trust
And pixie dust
'Cause I try
But it's so hard to believe
I try
But I can't see what you see
[ambulance siren]
[man] I don't know if it's going!
Is that water pressure up?
Peter Pan.
Pixie dust.
Childish nonsense.
[seagulls calling]
[creaking]
Hello, Wendy.
- My apologies, miss.
- [shrieks]
[alarm siren]
Curses! Bring her down!
Hurry, Smee!
[gasps]
Oh, come on, now.
Don't fuss.
Cast off, ya mangy dogs!
[grunting]
- Hoist anchor!
- [grunting]
[Jane grunts]
[bell clangs]
[Hook] I'II get you, Peter Pan,
if it's the Iast thing I do.
[voices shouting]
[ringing]
I've got a Iittle
surprise for you, Peter Pan.
[sailor] Drop the mainsails!
Prepare to drop anchor!
[Hook chuckling] This is simply perfect!
Yes, Mr. Smee, with Wendy as bait
we shall Iure Peter Pan to his doom!
Summon the beast!
Yes, sir, Captain. Right away!
Oh
Yo ho ho, another plan
To try to capture Peter Pan
Captain Hook's a brilliant man
Who else could think
of the perfect crime
And bumble and fumble it
every time
- Smee!
- Whoa!
[sucking sounds]
Set the bait!
whimpering]
Make no doubt, Smee.
That wretched boy will be
but a notch in me scabbard.
- Only in your dreams, Hook!
- Pan!
I didn't know a codfish could talk.
Did you, Tinker Bell?
BIast him!
Take your best shot, Captain.
Come on! You're gonna have
to do better than that, boy!
Whoa!
Uh-uh-uh!
Three strikes and you're out!
[groaning]
Come down here, boy.
I've a Iittle something for you.
A present for me?
Aw, you really shouldn't have.
Call it a token
of me affection.
You see, it is a certain
friend of yours.
Who?
[Hook Iaughs] Wendy.
Wendy?
Let her go, Hook,
you black hearted scoundrel!
You want her? Ha!
Well, go and get her! [Iaughing]
- [Jane screaming]
- [growling]
I did it. I did it!
I... I can't believe it. I... I'm free!
Free of Peter Pan forever!
Mr. Smee, who is
the most brazen, bold
and brilliant buccaneer
who ever sailed the briny blue?
Um, BIackbeard?
Boys?
Hook! Hook! Hook!
Thank you, thank you.
I was good, wasn't I?
[cocks Iike a rooster]
- Did you miss me, Captain?
- How did you escape the beast?
[men gasping]
Aah! Help...
...me!
Yum!
Now, now, stay away!
No! No, no, no!
[screaming]
No, no! No!
Oh, Smee!
Hang on, Captain.
Here I come!
Smee!
[Hook screams]
[cat snarls]
[Hook] Mr. Smee, be a good fellow
and fix the plank...
...so I can make you walk it!
Aye-aye, Captain!
[groaning]
- [Peter chuckling]
- [muffled screams]
Easy does it, Wendy.
You should have seen
Hook's face when I...
- Ow!
- Ow! Ow! Ow, ow, ow!
- Whoa!
- Oh!
Peter Pan?
Well, you're sure not Wendy!
Tinker Bell?
Oh, I get it. I'm dreaming.
- You're not real.
- [canon blast]
Huh? Look out!
Pan, you double-crossing pipsqueak!
Come back here and fight Iike a man!
Come and get me, you old codfish!
[blows raspberry]
Come on.
We gotta fly out of here.
Aah!
Wait! What are you doing?
If you're not Wendy, who are you?
I'm her daughter Jane!
Huh! Well, if you're Wendy's daughter,
you're gonna Iove it here!
Hey, this is great.
You can stay here forever.
[screaming]
Help!
- She did that on purpose.
- Aw, she's just jealous.
- AII girls get Iike that around me.
- Oh, really? How very nice for you.
[Jane screaming]
That was fun, huh?
Lost Boys, fall in!
[Lost Boys] Whoo!
Oh, careful!
You're going to fall!
Sound off!
- SIightly!
- Nibs!
[both] The twins!
Ow!
- Cubby.
- And that's Toodles!
Oh!
[spitting]
- Eww.
- Boys, this is Jane.
She's gonna stay here
and be our new mother
- and tell us stories.
- What do you mean by...?
- Yay! Stories!
- Tell us a story, Jane. Come on!
Um...
Actually, I'm afraid I'm not
very good at telling stories.
Ah, that's OK.
We're not very good
at Iistening to stories.
- Ooh!
- [Iaughing]
I know. Let's play a game instead.
Red rover! Red rover!
Nah. Something else.
Let's play the "no more hitting
Cubby on the head" game.
- Hey, how about a treasure hunt?
- Good idea!
- Yeah! A treasure hunt!
- I hid it really good this time.
- You guys will never find it.
- Sure we will!
- Diamonds and rubies!
- Treasure! Treasure!
- Diamonds...
- Yeah, come on!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- No!
No, no, no, and no!
You remind me of someone I know.
Oh.
I have to go home.
What's the matter with her?
I don't know.
She acts kind of Iike a...
...grown-up.
Eww!
[gasping]
I've got to get out of here.
[Hook] Smee!
[Smee] Coming, Captain!
[gruntings]
[Hook] Oh, my back!
Oh, dear, dear, dear, Captain.
A nice massage
is just the ticket for you.
Now, you just forget
about old Peter Pan.
[cracking]
Perhaps you're right.
[groans]
[cracking]
AII in the past, I say.
AII in the past.
Ah, the past.
- Likes when he stole your treasure.
- Ooh.
My treasure?
And then Iaughed in your face.
Laughed in my face.
Or today, for example,
tricking that there sea monster
- into pulling down your pants.
- Aah!
Right in front of the crew too.
Right in front of the crew!
We've got to find him!
[popping]
[Smee] Catchy.
Smee, Iisten!
[crash]
Great Scott!
No sooner do I rid me self
of that cursed crocodile
and now this!
- [sobbing]
- Oh, there, there.
He's just a playful
Iittle sea urchin is all.
I swear, Smee,
this is propelling me to delirium.
I detest cephalopods.
Thank you.
[screams]
Smee! Save me!
Oh, you big brute, you!
Off with you.
Go on, now. Shoo, shoo.
And take your arms with you.
You ought to be
ashamed of yourself.
At Ieast the crocodile had manners.
BIast that scurvy boy!
This is all his fault.
Mr. Smee, pipe up the crew.
We're going ashore
to find Peter Pan!
[Peter Pan] Tink, what is she doing?
It Iooks Iike she's Ieaving.
Shh!
Half-dozen bananas. Check.
Ten coconuts. Check.
- Two oars...
- Hey, Jane.
How come you want to go home so bad?
I have to get back to my family.
Why?
Well, um, I don't want
to talk about it.
Why not?
If you must know, we had a fight.
- Why?
- Oh.
I told my Iittle brother
you weren't real.
What? Why?
[sighs] Well, oh, I don't know.
But I have to get back
and set things right.
- Why?
- Because!
That's why!
Well, you know,
you can't get home that way.
I... I've got to try.
Well...
...goodbye.
It was nice meeting you, Peter Pan.
Duty calls.
Oh!
Oh, dear! Oh, no!
Whoa!
You OK?
I just want to go home.
Well, you know, the only way
out of here is to fly.
Come on, I'II show you how.
Step softly, you worthless dogs!
Set your sights for Peter Pan!
Oh, goodness.
Haven't we searched the island
a thousand times before?
I beg your pardon, Mr. Smee?
Uh, I said that, uh,
searching for Pan is, um, uh...
...fun galore. [nervous Iaughter]
There'II be no rest until
we have that boy in irons.
[gasps]
- Hey!
- Watch it, Cubby!
Oh, no, Peter.
I really don't think this will...
This is ridiculous.
I can't fly!
Well, of course you can't,
but I can!
I guess I'm just smarter than you.
I highly doubt that.
- Braver.
- Right.
- Stronger!
- Oh, yeah, that's it.
Well, then it must be my good Iooks.
Or maybe you're full of hot air.
Hey! Look, anybody can do it.
Tink?
Yeah! AII it takes is faith...
Trust.
And, uh, something else.
Pixie dust?
That's it!
Ow!
OK, Tink, Iet her have it.
Tink.
Gosh, Tink, if she can't fly home,
I guess she'II have to move in with us.
Now, that's enough!
[sneezes]
[all Iaughing]
Odds fish, what's that?
- OK, Jane.
- Don't even think about it.
- Ready or not...
- [screams]
- I got her!
- I got her! I got her!
I thought you said you got her.
Oh, how will I ever get back home?
So the girl can't fly,
yet she wants to go home.
Smee, do you know what this means?
Six more weeks of winter?
No, you imbecile.
We'II get me treasure and the boy.
- Hey, what's this?
- Oh, give that back.
It's my Iist!
Things to do, places to be.
Important things!
Huh? That stuff's no fun.
- No wonder you can't fly.
- Give it back, Peter.
[chuckling] SIightly, catch!
- Keep away from Jane!
- I got it!
- You boys are horrid!
- Come on, over here!
- You're ripping it!
Come on! Why don't you guys
ever throw to me?
No, stop it! This isn't funny!
- Whoo hoo!
- I've got it!
- [belching]
- [Iaughter]
This is just a game to you, isn't it?
Well, I'm tired of playing.
Gosh, Jane, we didn't mean
to make you mad.
Oh, grow up. You did so.
You're just a bunch of silly,
ridiculous children.
No, no, Ieave me alone!
Oh, I don't believe in any of this!
And I especially
don't believe in fairies!
[gasping]
Goodbye!
Oh, yeah?
Well, good riddance!
Hmm!
[Cubby Uh, Peter?
I think there's something wrong
with Tinker Bell.
[coughing]
[hooting]
[rumbling]
[thunderclap]
[chirping]
[Edward] I need you here to take care
of your mom and Danny.
Can you do that for me?
- Mm-hmm.
- That's my big girl.
I Iove you!
[no audio]
[sobbing]
Ooh. Looks kind of bad.
Kind of bad? Kind of?
Oh, it's hopeless!
Poor Iittle Tinker Bell!
[crying]
Hey, put a cork in it!
Shh!
Uh-huh.
- What?
- What did she say, Peter?
If we don't get Jane
to believe in fairies
- Tink's Iight's gonna go out.
- [gasping]
Well, Iet's just go
and make her believe!
- Hang on a minute.
- Ow!
You can't just make somebody
believe in fairies.
- [twins] But we believe.
- Yeah, it ain't hard for us.
That's it!
We gotta make Jane one of us!
[all] But she's a girl!
- You want to help Tink, don't ya?
- Uh-huh.
We gotta do it! [spits]
Don't worry, Tink. We'II save you.
[Hook sobbing]
- Stay where you are!
- PIease, go right ahead.
Run me through.
You'II be doing me a favor.
AII right. I give up.
What's your problem?
AII I've ever wanted was to get away
from this dreadful place
and home to my dear, sweet mother.
But blast it all!
Peter stole my treasure
and my men would mutiny if I so much
as tried to Ieave without it.
So here I am...
...stuck in this absurd place.
My sources tell me
you wish to return home as well.
Huh. You got that right.
- I guess we're in the same boat.
- The same boat!
- That's it!
- What's it?
I'II give you passage home
on my ship
and you can help me
recover my treasure.
Uh, don't you see?
The treasure's useless to Peter.
He's not sensible Iike you and I.
He's just a boy who'II never grow up.
Hmm. Tell me about it.
And, really,
what other choice do you have?
It's not as though
you could fly home.
Hmm, well, I suppose.
If it is rightfully yours.
And if it's really no use to Peter...
Splendid, splendid!
Wait! You must swear
not to harm Peter.
Me? Actually harm Peter Pan?
Perish the thought!
It's all a game, you see.
I shan't harm him.
You have my word.
"I, Captain James Hook,
do hereby swear
not to harm a single hair
on Peter Pan's head."
You see? Ironclad, unbreakable.
Leave the Iight on, Mommy.
Your baby boy's coming home.
Now, when you've Iocated the treasure
just give this a wee toot.
You're doing the right thing, my dear.
I'm your only way home.
Jane!
Jane, come on back!
- Jane!
- Jane?
Jane!
[chittering]
[both] Jane!
Jane!
- Jane!
- [Jane] Peter!
- Hmm?
Peter Pan!
Ooh!
[both] There you are!
[both] I've been Iooking
all over for...
- I, uh...
- No, no, no.
[both] You.
I'm sorry for wrecking your book.
We want to make it up to you.
We want you to feel Iike...
Well, Iike you're one of us.
We'II do anything for you.
[chuckles]
Honest.
Anything?
Anything at all!
You just name it.
Well, um, why don't we play a game
Iike maybe treasure hunt!
Treasure hunt?
That's a great idea!
But you'II have to think
Iike a Lost Boy.
- Uh...
- And have fun Iike a Lost Boy!
[chuckles] Tell me what to do.
[cocks Iike a rooster]
- Well, to be one of us...
- Yes?
- There are some things to know.
- What's that?
We like to dream all day
And then at night we play
We swing on limbs of trees
Till we wake up the bees
These are the things
we Lost Boys do
We swing from rope to rope
We have no use for soap
With open mouths we chomp
On mud pies from the swamp
And then we top it off
With pudding from a trough
These are the things
we Lost Boys do
We 're rolling in dirt
And we won 't change our shirt
We 're marching around
To see what makes a sound
[honks]
Ugh!
[chirps]
- Dare you to throw that rock!
- I'II get a triple skip!
Dare you to explore that cave!
I'II have an overnight trip!
And if you're feeling scared
I'll have my friends right there
These are the things
we Lost Boys do
The treasure!
I found...
[Hook] Now, when you reach the treasure,
just give this a wee toot,
[Peter Pan] Hey, Jane, you did it!
Lost Boys!
Jane found the treasure
in Dead Man's Cave!
- Yahoo!
- The treasure!
Attention!
Fall in!
In honor of your downright unbelievable
skill at finding hidden treasures
I now proclaim you, Jane,
a Lost Boy!
Uh, I mean a Lost Girl.
Me?
The very first Lost Girl?
What's the matter?
Don't you want to be?
Oh, yes.
I'd Iike that very much, Peter.
- [Cubby Let's hear it for Jane!
- Yippee!
Now that you're one of us
feel free to sing along
We are so proud of you
that you can do no wrong
And we don 't even care
if you pull on our hair
These are the things
Lost Boys,,,
that Lost Girls,,,
These are the things
we love to,,,
- [toots]
- [gasps]
- No, wait! No!
- Whoa!
[men Iaughing]
[men shouting]
The treasure is ours!
- Oh! Hey!
- Let me go!
It's time for you
to meet your maker, Peter Pan!
- Stop it! PIease!
- Sorry. No can do.
And thank you, milady.
I couldn't have done it without you.
- Jane?
- I never meant...
Oh, my. Have we
Iet the kitty out of the bag?
No, wait!
You said no one would get hurt.
You gave your word!
And Captain Hook
is a man of his word.
I promised I wouldn't harm
a single hair on his head.
- And...
- Ow!
...this is the one I won't harm!
Here. You keep it.
The rest of him is mine!
I didn't do it, Peter!
I never agreed to this.
You're a traitor, Jane.
You Iied to me!
And because you don't believe
in fairies, Tink's Iight is going out!
Tinker Bell?
No. Peter, I...
- I'II save you, Peter! I will!
- [Hook Iaughing]
My dear, no one can save him now!
[Iaughing continues]
Tinker Bell!
Tink! Tink!
Tinker Bell.
It's true.
I can finally see it
Now I have to believe
Oh. Oh, no.
This is all my fault.
All those precious stories
All the world is made of faith
And trust
[sobbing] I'm so sorry.
And pixie dust
So I'll try
'Cause I finally believe
I'll try
'Cause I can see what you see
To fly
Tinker Bell?
Oh, this is wonderful!
Wait until Peter...
Oh, my gosh. Peter.
- [pirate] Aye. Keel haul the brats!
- He's fish food now!
Hey, he's Iike a pinata!
Look at him, Smee.
He's nothing but a child.
And I Ioathe children.
Uh, cut him down.
[gasping]
- [crashing]
- Oy!
Any Iast words, boy?
- Let the Lost Boys go.
- Oh, they'II go... right after you,
one by one, off the end of the plank!
[Iaughing]
Be brave, Iads.
Don't Iet 'em see you cry.
[all crying]
Say your prayers, Peter Pan.
[Iaughing]
Not so fast, you old codfish,
or you'II have to answer to me.
- Yippee!
- Yay!
Jane?
Good heavens! Run!
Run for your Iives! It's...
...a Iittle girl. [Iaughs]
[all Iaughing]
Tinker Bell! You're alive!
Oh, and Iook, Captain, a fairy too.
Ohh!
Don't just stand there, you fools.
Get the girl! Oh!
Destroy them young tykes!
Smee!
I got her, Captain. I got her.
- Oh, watch your head.
- Waah!
Aah!
Nyaah!
[growling]
I've got you now...
Oh! Ohh!
Huh?
Yay!
[snarling]
Ooh!
Gimme! Mine! Mine! Big shiny!
Miiii...
[splash]
Hmm?
Get her off! Get her off me!
Captain?
- Ha!
- Aah!
I've had just about enough
of your childish games!
- Jane, Iook out!
- [Hook] Ha-ha!
Aah!
Give up, girl.
Never!
Don't you see, Hook?
You'II never win.
Not as Iong as there is faith, trust
and pixie dust.
Odd bodkins!
Yay!
Unbelievable!
[giggling] Mere child's play.
- [gasps]
- Gotcha!
Ha! Looks Iike I've got
the upper hook now.
Game's over, Hook.
I win! Ha!
Whaa!
Hey, Captain, you forgot your anchor.
[grunts]
[howls]
Abandon ship!
[thud]
[growling]
Help me, please! [screams]
You know the rules, Hook.
A good captain always
goes down with his ship.
I don't want to be a good captain!
Uh-oh.
Look!
Smee!
[groans]
[Lost Boys] The codfish!
The codfish!
The codfish! The codfish!
- Hooray!
- AII right!
Whoo-hoo! Yay!
[cocking Iike roosters]
Yay!
Let's hear it for Jane!
The one and only...
...Lost Girl!
Thank you.
- [Lost Boys] AII right!
- Yay!
What's wrong, Peter?
Aw, you can fly now.
You can go home.
- I can go home.
- But...
[sniffling] But...
- We'II miss you.
- Yeah. A Iot.
And I'II miss you. AII of you.
But there's someone back home
who needs me.
And besides, now I've got
great stories to tell him
and they'II all be about
Peter Pan and the Lost Boys.
Yeah! AII right!
Hey, in that case...
Mademoiselle, it would be my pleasure
to escort you back to London.
The pleasure will be all mine, good sir.
Whoa!
Hey!
Well, it's a Iong way home.
Give me your best shot, Tink.
[all Iaughing]
Whoa! Whoa!
[clock chimes]
Oh, my gosh!
Mother. Mother!
Darling, what's wrong?
- Mommy!
- What is it? Oh!
Oh, you were right.
He is most remarkable.
- Who, dear?
- Oh, Mother, I'm so sorry.
Oh, if only I'd Iistened to you.
I had a bad dream.
Did you now? Was it Hook again?
Were those pirates up
to their old tricks again?
Whoa! Hey! What's going on?
I know how to take care
of that old codfish.
- We can do it together, Danny.
- We can?
- The two of us.
- Really?
I saw him, you know.
Captain Hook kidnapped me.
Stuffed me into
an old dirty bag, he did.
He took me off to Never Land
and tried to feed me to a giant octopus.
- Wow!
- [Jane] There were pirates everywhere.
And, oh, Tinker Bell was so beautiful.
- [Danny You saw Tinker Bell?
- [Jane] Uh-huh,
but her Iight almost went out.
You have to be very careful.
- Shh!
- Huh?
Wendy?
Hello, Peter.
You changed.
Not really.
Not ever. [gasps]
Hello, Tinker Bell.
Oh, Tink.
[giggling]
Madam.
Goodbye, Wendy.
Goodbye, Peter.
Wow, Iook at him! It's Peter Pan!
[sighs] I'II always believe in you,
Peter Pan.
[truck engine]
- Here we go, then.
- Thanks, mate. I appreciate it.
Daddy?
- Daddy!
- Edward!
Daddy's home!
- [chattering]
- [Nanatwo barking]
Come on, Tink. Let's go home.
[ BBmak: Do You Believe in Magic]
[ Jonatha Brooke: I'll Try]
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org