Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I'll never manage to do it!
Faster Farfella!
Come on!
Good!
I can't do it, Karas!
I can't do it!
Run!
Run away!
I like to be pretty everyday.
I like to be in good shape.
That's why I love Avalon.
With Avalon,
I know I'm beautiful.
And I know I'll remain that way.
Avalon,
for a better world.
Health...
Beauty...
Longevity.
Avalon...
We're on your side for life.
I already paid you, didn't I?
Give it to me!
Sorry, beauty.
I've had...
a few extra expenses.
Hey!
Your sister is with Dimitri.
Don't play this game with me!
You have to pay the price
if you want it!
Let go of her!
Baby!
Out!
Get lost!
What are you doing here?
Good evening, Bislane.
Stop it, Ilona.
What were you doing?
We didn't see you at the office.
Cut out the acting!
When I find you a good job
you could go there at least
2 days in a row.
They're going to fire you.
How awful!
We can never tell you anything Bislane.
You never talk.
They're waiting for you
at the poorhouse.
Ah!
Illitch!
Hurry up, we're waiting for you!
Section K, in position.
Hostage in danger!
Fall back.
I don't think so.
Fall back!
Hostage in danger!
Karas!
Are you crazy?
Is there a problem?
It'll be over soon.
Close your eyes,
..I'll tell you
when you can open them.
Close your eyes.
What?
Let's go!
Amiel, is your wife feeling better?
Whereas I'm away..
..or present,
it's infernal.
I'll be glad when
she'll have the baby.
Captain.
The prosecutor is waiting
for you outside.
Ilona Tasuiev, one of Avalon's
youngest researcher.
Outstandingly intelligent.
Recruted in Caucasus
when she was 13 years old.
The favourite of vice-president
Paul Dellenbach.
Avalon wants us to find her,
..to find her alive.
Sort things out yourself but
bring her back to me.
Do you actually never talk
or is it...
to stick to your character?
Ilona Tasuiev, this young
22 years old scientist,
promised to a brilliant future,
has been kidnapped
while on her way to help
underprivileged people.
Can Avalon accept this?
No!
We've always considered such acts,
to harm any of our employees,
as a personal attack against
the whole company.
Ilona's sister.
Bislane Tasuiev.
She's working for Avalon,
at the archives.
Ilona saw her...
just before being kidnapped.
It's Dr Muller, her superior,
who gave the alert.
As for the 71,
it's the jungle.
4 homicides, 32 complaints...
Are you listening?
I'll see her later.
Tell her!
I want to know everything
about her.
Habits, vices, obsessions,
strengths, weaknesses.
Her colleagues, her friends, her lovers.
Avalon must give us her schedules
and her current works.
As well as
the list of her patients.
Put some pressure.
The narcotics will
tip us on the 71.
Without a ransom demand,
we shouldn't neglect any lead:
industrial espionage,
robbery, sexual crime.
The kidnapper bypassed the watchmen
and security cameras.
He's fast,
calculating and organised.
It's not
his first kidnapping.
Amiel...
Check the convicts, the psychopaths
and those released on parole.
Montoya.
Check Ilona's car.
Contact Gavary
and Lionet at the Casbah.
If the car appears somewhere,
they'll know about it.
Is it clear?
We find the girl
then we can rest.
Does anyone know where she went?
Woeller?
Sport shoes, size 38.
Considering the footprints
the kidnapper must weight around 60kg.
A woman.
Or a teenager.
Make a DNA search
on everything we found.
Cigarette butts, various wrappings.
I have some information about Muller.
He was a researcher in genetics for Avalon.
I'm switching to e-call.
When his brother died
he quit everything
to take care of
the underprivileged in an
Avalon's clinic.
Dog hair...
here and there...
I found some old underwears.
A lil' tip?
She's working at Avalon's laboratory.
But Ilona is regularly
on duty here
during her free time.
There are better things
to do to relax.
Facing reality puts
ideas back in place.
Genetic exploration is hazardous.
I've known more hazardous things.
Research is a never ending fight.
Lose its the purpose
and you'll lose its meaning.
That's why I'm pushing
young people to
get their hands dirty.
Is it the reason you quit?
You did your duty.
I realized I'd be more useful here
than in a laboratory.
You're still working
for Avalon.
It's difficult to get away
from Avalon.
You called
the police at 0h34.
A 22 years old girl
is 20 minutes late.
Don't you think it was a bit
too fast to sound the alarm?
Unfortunately I think I was right.
She's never been late.
Not even for a minute.
Ilona made big sacrifices
to succeed.
She would have never given up.
She's an exceptional woman.
And beautiful.
You don't miss a thing, Karas.
Do doctors make you nervous?
No, hospitals do.
We all have our bad memories.
I'm done Cecilia.
Very well doctor.
Thank you.
One last thing:
What's the subject of Ilona's research?
She's preparing a biogenetics Ph.D.
About progeria.
An abnormality provoking
premature ageing.
A disease affecting children.
A tough fight I used
to carry on myself.
It was a long time ago.
Come!
Did you miss me?
Karas!
I hate it when you come here.
Me too.
So?
Nobody knows anything about the girl.
Her sister is often
at the Zbench and at the 71.
I don't give a shit about the sister.
I've got nothing else.
Zilch!
Your blonde just vanished.
You're the magician, Goran.
I'm doing all I can.
Ok! Ok, Ok!
I know someone,
a Romanian, she's a clairvoyant.
She knows crazy stuff!
You're...
Follow the sister and gather
anything that might be interesting.
Starting with
my own pleasure?
My sweet little princess!
Champagne?
Where is she, Dimitri?
What are you plotting with her?
Ah, ah, ah!
You really think I'm the one...
What would I do with such
a pain in the ass?
I thought you were here for me!
Don't take me for a damn fool!
I saw you together last night.
Did you forget?
Ah yes?
And...
I haven't talked to the cops yet.
Not yet.
That's what she wanted.
I was supposed to steal it for her.
What?
What is it?
She didn't pay me
the last instalment.
Health
Beauty...
Longevity...
Avalon...
We're on your side for life.
Let go of me!
Calm down.
I won't
hurt you.
It's already done.
Ah!
Where were you?
Do you think I kidnapped her?
You tell me.
You're the cop!
Stop running me around!
You found me.
Are you always
so aggressive?
Only when my sister is kidnapped.
We've always been very different.
Even when we were children.
Before the death of our parents.
Did they die during the war?
I was 15 years old,
Ilona was only 10.
I took care of her after that.
We're very close to each other.
But it's complicated.
Avalon noticed her,
she was
13 years old.
They took us here.
We would still be there
without her.
And Dellenbach?
He changed her.
She has faith in her.
Talk to me about Dr Muller.
She met him when she started
her Ph.D.
He offered to help her in exchange
of some duty at the clinic.
They admire each other.
Anything else?
Let me known if there's anything else.
Don't hide anything.
Or I'll know it sooner or later.
Can I stay here tonight?
This way I'll know where to find you.
She's an...
exceptional woman.
I know you can hear me.
I can feel your presence.
Answer me!
My name is... Ilona Tasuiev.
I'm 22 years old, 22!
I want to live!
Pssshhh!
Hmmm...
Greetings, captain.
Welcome to Avalon.
Your gun and your e-call, please.
The legendary
captain Karas.
Nice to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you.
No news?
None.
At least for now.
This situation is intolerable.
If I may...
Sorry, was Ilona working
on a confidential project?
Like all our researchers
she does her best to improve
the life of all the people.
Anything else?
Is Ilona Tasuiev your mistress?
I knew you were a direct man.
Hmmm!
I have sex with my secretary,
my wife.
And even my wife's sister.
But with my scientists,
never.
Goran is looking for you!
There's a problem with the sister.
Poor kid!
What's so important in this book?
You're raising your child with love
and look how he ends.
Shut up.
Don't you know how yours
will end, do you?
Karas should sign the report.
After you.
There was a Japanese.
Children lined up
just like on a class photo.
There was a date on the cover, 2006.
That's all?
That's all he let me see.
I'll trust you,
I have no other choice.
But if you hide
something else...
We got Ilona's car.
We found it.
The car
is given chase to,
unknown driver.
It's heading towards the center.
Karas, do you copy?
It's going
to the center.
Damn!
Move away, fuck!
Take the Pont des Arts.
Come on!
Welcome to the Galeries Lafayette
Notre-Dame.
Leaving for the week-end...
Move away!
We finally got him!
He's one of Farfella's henchmen.
It's Farfella who's
gonna be happy!
So?
It's a 42 and a half.
It's not him.
Shit!
Where did he get the car?
He won't talk.
We must wait
for his lawyer.
Karas!
Don't leave me alone
with this lunatic!
I don't know this chick!
Come here!
I swear, I don't know anything!
What about paying a visit to Farfella?
Salam aleikum, Farfella.
Aleikum salam, Karas.
Once every 20 years.
We don't see each other very often.
You put on some weight.
I always wanted to look like you.
It's your turn to
honor your debt.
How nice of you!
You brought me
a present!
Hmmm...
You know that Naghib
has nothing to do with it.
You know that he stole the car.
Where? When?
How? You'd better tell me right now.
You forgot to say "please".
Hmmm!
Security cameras
in one of my parkings.
you should find something
of interest in it.
May the Prophet be with you.
32 exploitable comparison parameters.
Enough for a visual identification.
Switch to the convicts file.
Search all files.
Witnesses, suspects.
Shit!
I can't believe it.
General identification.
Send the picture to
Avalon and Muller.
Widen the search
if we don't find anything.
Army, Health.
Top priority.
Nora, take over.
More secrets?
I never saw this guy.
Not even in the book.
I'm sure of it.
Whose book was it?
What was Ilona looking for?
Repeating your questions
won't do you any good!
I was wrong to cover up for Dimitri.
I didn't want to give him away
without being sure.
You can understand, can't you?
To protect such a scumbag?
He wasn't always like that.
This investigation will be very difficult
with friends like that.
What about you, Karas?
Do you always meet perfect women?
No.
You're wasting your time
in this shitty world.
This shitty world,
it's the only one
I know.
If you know of a better one
I'll take it.
We must have missed something.
It's here somewhere.
We'll inevitably find out.
This way!
Move it!
Hands up!
Igor Vord?
You're under arrest!
No!
Him, not Igor!
Igor Vord, where?
Igor!
2 more names
for the same face
on different metro-passes.
We're right in the middle
of an identity traffic.
Er...
Absolutely, captain.
Er... Vord,
Novalis and Hemen.
All incinerated here.
Igor Vord, 10 years ago,
in march 44.
Thomas Hemen,
5 years ago.
Alfred Novalis will be incinerated
next month.
As you can see
everything is noted here.
Those deaths weren't registered.
According to my report
the hospital took care of them.
You can have a look by yourself.
Burial certificate sent
by Avalon's clinic.
Everything is in order.
The same doctor
signed for the 3 of them.
Dr Muller.
Nora, call Reparaz,
we're going to Muller's place.
We're gonna lose him if
we don't act now.
He knows we're making some progress,
he has the picture of the kidnapper.
You have nothing.
Muller signed the 3
burial certificates.
He's signing 300 of them a year!
A fuck up
will be his lawyers delight.
I don't give a fuck,
I want a warrant!
It's 5 in the morning.
I need at least 1h.
Karas!
Listen!
I'll get you
if you go in!
Karas!
Police!
Amiel...
Investigate on Muller
and Avalon, year 2006.
Report anything you can find.
Why don't we have this kind of stuff?
Remain calm.
They pirated my e-call,
they shot me!
I want a warrant for
arrest for Dellenbach.
You don't have any evidence.
They were Avalon's men!
You break into Muller's house
and you kill 2 men.
Do you want to be decorated?
Muller is behind Ilona's kidnapping
and Avalon is covering up for him.
What's your share in this?
What are you saying?
You're suspended.
Hmmm!
Nice show!
Go fuck yourself.
You're not alone.
You have a team with you.
You were right about the
metro-passes.
They've been used around
Muller's district.
I gathered all I could about 2006.
Muller was one of Avalon's greatest hope.
He quit everything
after his brother's death.
He tried everything to save him.
But Claus was infected
by an incurable disease.
Progeria.
Muller?
It doesn't make any sense.
He took advantage of
his situation
to steal identities.
The book belonged to him.
Muller is involved.
Why Ilona?
She discovered something about him
during her research.
I must find out
what happened in 2006.
Why did Ilona want
this book so badly?
But I need you
for that.
What?
Avalon archives?
You hate your job.
It's too dangerous.
It never stopped you.
Where are you?
I'm heading to
the archives.
It's fine, I see you.
Ah!
Do you understand,
I...
I'm there.
Good, now be very careful.
I can see everything
Ilona consulted on 2006.
Focus on progeria and Muller.
Oh shit,
an alpha confidential!
What?
A secured file.
I can check it
but I'll be discovered.
Too dangerous.
It never stopped me.
There's...
Children who all carry
a mark on the back of the skull.
A triangular scar.
What did they do to them?
We put a definitive end
to Muller's protocol.
He's the guy on the book.
Dr Nakata.
Our supply of patients depleted
after these deaths.
Genetic experiment tests
all failed.
Intruder alert!
Block 4.6.4.
Maximum alert!
We're terminating the tests.
Bislane, get out of here!
Authorizations
have been rejected.
All files relating to our research
have been destroyed
by Dr Muller.
We lost 9 children.
7 of them had mutated
before dying.
They're here!
Move away!
They were all suffering
of heart condition,
pulmonary troubles
and brain damage.
Code black!
I repeat: switch to code black.
Stay put during the
duration of the alert.
They shut down everything!
Stay put during the
duration of the alert.
I can't see anything!
Karas!
What is it? Who's there?
Ah!
- It's me, quiet!
- They killed the children!
- I heard, calm down.
We're gonna get out of here.
Find them and don't lose them,
understood?
Try to get rid of the girl.
We'll leave at dawn.
We should sleep.
I grew up in the Casbah.
Do you think I've always been a cop?
I have no other choice
than to trust you.
But if you're still hiding something.
Stop!
You're crazy!
I'm not afraid of you.
You're the one afraid
to reveal yourself.
No one is born as a gangster.
You become one,
that's all.
Me, Farfella...
We still were kids.
It was a game for us.
One night...
We were carrying money for someone.
A rival gang trapped us,
they lock us up,
and beat the hell out of us.
Run!
Farfella managed to escape.
So, under what charge
do we arrest her?
What the hell is this?
I don't have any other choice.
To protect you.
Having sex with me doesn't
give you any right!
Where is Amiel?
He got a boy,
the funny thing is...
What?
He wanted to call him Karas.
But he got worried it might
bring him bad luck.
Anything on Nakata?
What would you do without me?
Of course,
I didn't tell you anything.
He was Muller's assistant until 2006.
He's the only survivor of the team.
A 93 years old young man.
You came to talk about
Jonas Muller, didn't you?
I don't care about your opinion.
I'm not ashamed of what I did.
You killed all these children.
We did everything we could to save them.
They had progeria.
Nobody killed them, nobody.
These children were doomed.
We tried everything to save them.
Muller couldn't bear it
when his brother died.
He gave up his research,
and destroyed all his work
without hesitating.
20 years of work gone in smoke.
The clinic was his redemption.
Ilona was the only one
to understand him.
How do you know Ilona?
She came here for the first time
about a year ago.
She really wanted to
understand Dr Muller's past.
She wanted to understand
the reason of our failure.
What did Avalon do?
They tried everything they could to
convince Muller to keep working.
They offered him a fortune.
Captain...
Do you have the slightest idea
of what Muller's protocole was?
Progeria was just a step,
not a final goal.
Our protocole wasn't complicated.
It was even very simple.
Our goal
was immortality!
Ah, ah! Oh...
What time is it?
- Immortality!
Some results must remain secret.
Really? Why, Jonas?
It's too dangerous.
You're scared.
Go ahead, shoot!
Be done with it and shoot.
When I think I've been
admiring you for all these years!
Do you want me to tell
you what you are?
A coward,
that's what you are.
Don't move!
Where is she, doctor?
Your gun!
Your e-call!
Call some back up.
Karas!
What are you gonna do?
Shoot me?
On your side!
Tie yourself to the guardrail.
She's alive, isn't she?
Yes, unfortunately.
I'm not a murderer.
I couldn't convince her.
I tried to
warn her about those people.
Tell me where she is doctor.
I hear you.
And I understand.
It wasn't easy.
You don't know anything.
You're completely wrong
since the beginning.
Ilona is the danger!
What are you talking about?
Just like me,
40 years ago.
She found the answer,
she discovered the secret.
The protocol of immortality!
And Avalon knows it.
I know that you want to save her.
But then you'll give Avalon
unlimited power.
The power of life and death
will belong to them forever.
No!
We're running out of time.
I've been hiding my discovery
from Avalon for 40 years
to save us from hell.
Without death, life has no meaning.
Where is Ilona?
You're not listening.
Ilona isn't just another victim.
If Avalon finds her
we'll all become victims.
No, don't do that!
You're our last hope.
Life is so beautiful,
death will be sweet.
In peace, I'm reborn.
Noooo!
What did he tell you?
What you really are.
Lecturing people
isn't my strong point
but I'm infallible
to smell sons of bitches.
Despite this talent, a lot of
people die during your investigations.
Dimitri Ostrovski.
Jonas Muller.
Hishiro Nakata.
Don't you know it?
Everything has a price, captain.
The one we earn
or the one we pay.
I'll make sure that
yours is high.
I'll break you.
I originally came
to smash you to bits.
Now I only have to pick them up.
Dr Muller death remain a mystery.
Reserved, he dedicated
his life to the poor.
It's a irretrievable loss...
He fell off
the roof of officer
Karas house.
It may be a suicide.
Captain Karas,
recently suspended,
remains at police disposal.
People disappear around me.
At least we have something in common.
You're not safe with me.
We're gonna make it.
It's just another little scar.
What's going on?
Karas?
The scar!
It's Claus,
Muller's brother.
Oh, my god.
He's alive.
Muller had found
the secret of immortality.
To protect him from Avalon,
he destroyed all his work.
Except one important thing:
Claus himself.
He stole the identity
of dead patients
To allow Claus to live
anonymously for 40 years.
He condemned him to live
trapped in the body of a sick child.
But Ilona discovered his secret.
If Dellenbach finds
llona before me
everything Muller did would
have been useless.
You're not gonna abandon her?
I'll find her.
But she'll have to forget
her previous life.
Promise me to save her.
Promise me.
I promise.
You must hide.
Dellenbach will do anything
to hurt us.
Hmmm, hmmm.
Come back to me safely
or I'll kill you.
After 20 years...
We're finally even.
May the Prophet
be with you, Karas.
Salam aleikum.
I loved him too.
Claus?
I know what you went through.
I grew up alone too.
Jonas took care of me
when I arrived.
He gave me back hope.
He was like a father to me.
I need you, Claus.
Everybody is looking for you.
The video from the subway
security cameras
near Muller's palce.
Carry on.
Our friend gave us
his nicest smile.
Look.
One more time.
Closer.
Stay on him.
Stop!
We got him.
Here's his hideout.
Let's go.
I'd rather go alone.
I can't tell you why.
Go back to your family.
Wait, Karas!
Good luck!
Be careful.
Karas!
Where is your captain?
I'm losing patience.
If you have better things to do...
Hmmm...
Your son weighted 3kg at birth.
A beautiful child.
Congratulations.
It would be a shame if
anything bad happened to him.
But rest assured.
Avalon always took care of its children.
It's only the 2 of us now.
Ah!
Claus, I...
Ilona, let go of him!
Let go of him!
He tried to kill me.
But I...
Come with me.
I know who you are.
You killed Muller.
IT's not true.
He was crazy.
He wanted to protect you.
I don't understand.
What do you want?
Let go of me!
But... no!
I promised Bislane to save you.
And I'll do it, that's it.
Help!
Another word and I'll kill you.
Find them!
Let go of me.
Please!
Ah!
Come on.
They're coming, Ilona.
You must disappear.
Forever.
Hurry up.
Come one!
Pleae, I beg you.
You are our only hope.
Our only hope?
Oh!
Who do you think you are?
The world is waiting
for my discovery.
Since the dawn of mankind.
Avalon will change your dreams
into nightmares.
How can you know anything
about my dreams?
Ilona!
You wouldn't understand.
You're not fit for that.
Bislane is safe.
You can have a new life.
I want eternal life.
Ilona, no, no!
Don't do that.
Ilona, stop!
Please, don't do that.
Our goal was immortality.
Without death, life has no meaning.
Promise me to save her.
- Ilona is the danger.
You don't understand.
Promise me.
Ah!
Noooo!
- Karas...
Karas...
I gave her a new identity.
Ilona had already made a choice.
She knew
she had to give up.
She left forever.
She did for her own sake.
For our own sake.
I can't leave her alone.
I can't abandon her.
I must find her.
No, you must respect her choice.
You'll never see her again.
But you can be proud.
Proud of your little sister.
I like to be beautiful everyday.
I like to be in good shape.
That's why I love Avalon.
With Avalon,
I know that I am beautiful.
And I know I'll remain that way.
Avalon,
for a better world.
Health...
Beauty...
Longevity...
Avalon...
We're on your side for life.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org