Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Five hundred twenty-five
thousand Six hundred minutes
thousand Moments so dear
Five hundred twenty-five
thousand Six hundred minutes
How do you measure Measure a year?
In daylights, in sunsets
In midnights, in cups of coffee
In inches, in miles
In laughter, in strife
In five hundred twenty-five
thousand Six hundred minutes
How do you measure A year in the life?
How about love?
Measure in love
Seasons of love
Five hundred twenty-five
thousand Six hundred minutes
thousand Journeys to plan
Five hundred twenty-five
thousand Six hundred minutes
How do you measure The
life of a woman or a man?
In truths that she learned?
Or in times that he cried?
In bridges he burned?
- Or the way that she died?
- It's time now to sing out
Though the story never ends
Let's celebrate Remember a
year in the life of friends
Remember the love
Oh, you got to You got
to remember the love
You know that love is
a gift From up above
Share love, give love, spread love
Measure, measure your life in love
Seasons of love
Measure your life
Measure your life in love
December 24th, 1989, 9 p. m.,
Eastern Standard Time.
From here on in, I
shoot without a script.
See if anything comes of it...
...instead of my old shit.
No, get out of here. Hey.
I said, get off the window.
How do you document real life
When real life's getting
more Like fiction each day?
Headlines, bread lines Blow my mind
And now this deadline Eviction or pay
Rent
How do you write a song
When the chords sound wrong?
Though they once sounded Right and rare
When the notes are
sour Where is the power
You once had to ignite the air?
- We're hungry and frozen
- Some life we've chosen
- How we gonna pay?
- How we gonna pay
- Last year's rent?
- Hello?
- Hey, guess who's back in town.
It's Collins, man.
Throw down the key. Cool.
Hey.
- You got a light, man?
- Yeah.
- Give me that shit.
- Come here, man.
Get that son of a bitch.
Pick his ass up. Come on.
How do you start a fire
When there's nothing to burn
And it feels like something's
stuck In your flue?
How can you generate heat
When you can't feel your feet
- And they're turning blue?
You light up a mean blaze
- With posters
- And screenplays
- How we gonna pay?
- How we gonna pay
- Last year's rent?
How do you stay on your feet
When on every street It's trick or treat
And tonight it's trick?
Welcome back to town
Oh, I should lie down
Everything's brown
And, uh-oh, I feel sick
- Where is he?
- Getting dizzy
- How we gonna pay?
How we gonna pay?
How we gonna pay
Last year's rent?
The music ignites the
night With passionate fire
The narration crackles and
pops With incendiary wit
Zoom in as they burn
the past To the ground
And feel the heat Of the future's glow
How do you leave the past behind
When it keeps finding
ways To get to your heart?
It reaches way down deep
And tears you inside out
Till you're torn apart Rent
How can you connect in an age
Where strangers, landlords, lovers
Your own blood cells betray?
What binds the fabric together
When the raging, shifting winds
Of change keep ripping away?
Draw a line in the sand
And then make a stand
- Use your camera to spar
- Use your guitar
When they act tough You call their bluff
We're not gonna pay
Last year's rent
This year's rent
Next year's rent
Rent, rent, rent, rent, rent
We're not gonna pay rent
'Cause everything is rent
Hey.
Bum.
Get your ass off the Range Rover.
Benny, that attitude toward...
...the homeless is exactly
what Maureen is protesting.
Maureen is protesting losing
her performance space...
...not my attitude.
Come down, I wanna talk to you.
Close-up: Benjamin Coffin
III. Our ex-roommate...
...who married Allison
Grey of the Westport Greys.
His father-in-law bought
several buildings on the block...
...and a nearby vacant
lot, home to Tent City.
Benny hopes to evict all of
the homeless from Tent City...
...and build a cyber studio.
Roger, you're looking good for a guy
coming off of a year of withdrawal.
- What do you want, Benny?
- Well, my investor...
- You mean, your
father-in-law? - Right.
Read about Maureen's
performance in the Village Voice.
Got pissed and sent me down
here to collect the rent.
- What rent?
- This past year's rent, which I let slide.
You said we were golden.
- When you bought the building.
- We were roommates.
- Remember, you lived here?
- How could I forget?
You, me, Collins and Maureen.
How is the drama queen?
- She's getting ready for a performance.
- I know.
- Still her production manager?
- Not exactly.
- Still dating her?
- I was dumped.
- She got a new man?
- Well...
- No.
- What's his name?
- Joanne.
Thanks for being so understanding.
You expect sympathy from the guy...
...who shut off our
power on Christmas Eve?
Got your attention, didn't it?
What happened to Benny?
What happened to his heart
And the ideals he once pursued?
Any owner of that lot next door Has
a right to do with it as he pleases
Happy birthday, Jesus
- The rent
- You're wasting your time
- We're broke
- You broke your word, this is absurd
There is one way You won't have to pay
- I knew it.
- Next door, the home of CyberArts
And now that the block is rezoned
Our dream can become a reality
You'll see, boys
A state-of-the-art, digital,
Virtual interactive studio
I'll forgo your rent
And on paper guarantee
That you can stay here for free
- If you do me one small favor.
- What?
Convince Maureen to cancel her protest.
Why not just get an
injunction or call the cops?
I did, and they're on standby.
But my investors would
rather I handle this quietly
You can't quietly wipe
out an entire tent city...
...then watch It's A
Wonderful Life on TV.
You wanna produce films and write songs?
You need somewhere to do it
It's what we used to dream about
Think twice before you pooh-pooh it
You'll see, boys
You'll see the beauty of a studio
That lets us do our work And get paid
With condos on the top Whose
rent keeps open our shop
Just stop the protest
And you'll have it made
You'll see
Or you'll pack.
Here you go.
Merry Christmas.
Hello?
Oh, my God. You okay, honey?
- I'm afraid so.
- Did they get anything, or...?
I didn't have any money,
but they took my stuff.
No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm Angel.
Angel?
Friends call me Collins.
Tom. Tom Collins.
Come on. Let's get you cleaned up.
I sort of have to hurry.
- I have a Life Support meeting.
- Life Support?
Yeah.
It's for people with AIDS.
People like me.
Me too.
I was gonna go try to find Collins.
You wanna come?
I thought maybe we could
all grab some dinner.
Zoom in on my empty wallet.
Touch?
Take your AZT.
I'm writing one great song Before I...
One song Glory
One song before I go
Glory One song to leave behind
Find one song
One last refrain
Glory From the pretty-boy front man
Who wasted opportunity
One song He had the world at his feet
Glory In the eyes of a young girl
A young girl
Find glory
Beyond the cheap colored lights
One song Before the sun sets
Glory
On another empty life
Time flies
Time dies
Glory
One blaze of glory
Find glory
In a song that rings true
Truth like a blazing fire
An eternal flame
Find one song
A song about love Glory
From the soul of a young man
A young man
Find the one song Before
the virus takes hold
Glory Like a sunset
One song To redeem this empty life
Time flies
And then no need To endure anymore
Time dies
- What'd you forget?
- Got a light?
I know you, you're...
You're shivering
It's nothing They turned off my heat
And I'm just a little weak on my
feet Would you light my candle?
- What are you staring at?
- Nothing
Your hair in the moonlight
You look familiar
- Can you make it?
- Just haven't eaten much today
At least the room
Stopped spinning anyway
- What?
- Nothing
- Your smile reminded me of...
- I always "remind people of"
- Who is she?
- She died
- Her name was April
- It's out again
Sorry 'bout your friend
Would you light my candle?
- Well?
- Yeah?
Oh, the wax
- It's...
- Dripping
- I like it between my...
- Fingers
I figured
Oh, well, good night
- It blew out again?
- No, I think that I dropped my stash
I know I've seen you out and about
When I used to go out
Your candle's out
I'm illin' I had it
when I walked in the door
It was pure Is it on the floor?
The floor?
They say that I have the
best ass Below 14th Street
- Is it true?
- What?
- You're staring again
- Oh, no
I mean, you do have a nice...
I mean, you look familiar
- Like your dead girlfriend
- Only when you smile
But I'm sure I've
seen you Somewhere else
Do you go to the Cat Scratch
Club? That's where I work
I dance
Yes They used to tie you up
It's a living
I didn't recognize you
Without the handcuffs
We could light the candle
Oh, won't you light the candle?
Why don't you forget that stuff
- You look like you're 16
- I'm 19
But I'm old for my age
I'm just born to be bad
I once was born to be bad
I used to shiver like that
- I have no heat, I told you
- I used to sweat
- I got a cold - Uh-huh,
I used to be a junkie
- But now and then I
like to feel good - Uh-huh
- Oh, here
- What's that?
Candy-bar wrapper.
We could light the candle
Oh, what'd you do with my candle?
- That was my last match
- Our eyes'll adjust
- Thank God for the moon
- Maybe it's not the moon at all
I hear Spike Lee's
shootin' Down the street
Bah humbug
- Cold hands
- Yours too
Big Like my father's
Do you wanna dance?
With you?
- No, with my father
- I'm Roger
They call me
They call me Mimi
We got power.
Merry Christmas.
- Speak.
Mark, are you there?
Are you screening your calls? It's Mom.
I just wanted to call and say we
love you. We'll miss you today.
Cindy and the kids are
here. They send their love.
Hope you like the hot plate. Don't
leave it on when you leave the house.
- Honey, give me the phone.
- Oh, here's Dad.
Listen, Mark, I'm sorry to
hear that Maureen dumped you.
I say, c'est la vie.
Let her be a lesbian.
She doesn't know what she's missing.
Happy holidays.
You know...
...there are times
when we're dirt broke...
...and hungry and freezing...
...and I ask myself, "Why the
hell am I still living here?"
And then they call. And I remember.
What's that?
The girl downstairs.
Oh, the dancer from
the Cat Scratch Club?
- Well, you are going, right?
- No.
- Oh, come on, Roger.
- Merry Christmas, bitches.
- Hey, Collins.
- Your keys.
- Yeah, 14 hours later.
What the hell happened
to you? Are you all right?
I've never been better. Here.
Oh, hi.
- "Oh, hi. " After seven months?
- I'm sorry.
You know what you need?
This boy could use...
...some Stoli.
- This is a complete Christmas feast.
- Thank you.
- You struck gold at MIT.
No.
They expelled me for my
theory of actual reality.
One for you. One for you.
Oh, wait.
For me.
So I came back home. Merry Christmas.
- Cheers.
- Welcome home.
I got a teaching gig at NYU.
Oh, so that's how you can
afford to splurge on us.
No. Sit down.
Gentlemen, our benefactor
On this Christmas day
Whose charity is only
matched By talent, I must say
A new member of the
Alphabet City Avant-garde
Angel Dumott Schunard
Today for you Tomorrow for me
- And you should hear her beat
- You earned this on the street?
It was my lucky day today On Avenue A
When a lady in a limousine Drove my way
She said, "Darling, be a
dear Haven't slept in a year
I need your help to make my
Neighbor's yappy dog disappear
This Akita, Evita, just won't shut
up I believe if you play nonstop
That pup will breathe its
very last High-strung breath
I'm certain that cur
Will bark itself to death"
Today for you Tomorrow for me
We agreed on a fee
$1000 guarantee, tax free
And a bonus if I trim her tree
Now, who could foretell
That it would go so well?
But sure as I am here That
dog is now in doggy hell
After an hour, Evita, in all her glory
On the window ledge Of that 23rd story
Like Thelma and Louise
did When they got the blues
Swan-dove into the
courtyard Of the Gracie Mews
Today for you Tomorrow for me
Back on the street Where I met my sweet
Where he was moaning and
groaning On the cold concrete
The nurse took him home
For some Mercurochrome
Then I dressed his wounds
And got him back on his feet
Sing it Today for you
Tomorrow for me
Today for you Tomorrow for me
I say Today for you
Tomorrow for me Today for you
Tomorrow
For me
That was dope.
That was fresh.
- Speak.
Mark. Hi.
It's me. Maureen. Look,
I have a bit of a problem.
I really need your help.
I hired Joanne as my
production manager...
...and I don't think she knows
what the hell she's doing.
If you could just... Please, baby,
come to the performance space.
- Hey, Maureen. Hi.
- Hi, baby.
- Sure, I'll be there.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Okay, see you soon.
Can you believe her? I mean,
first she just dumps me...
- Maureen dumped you?
- Yes. She dumped me.
For a lawyer named Joanne.
Now she wants me to help
her fix her sound equipment.
- Well, Mark, you could've said no.
- I know, but...
- That's cute. You still love her.
- Yeah, right.
You do.
- We have to go.
- Wanna go to this gathering?
- Where?
- Life Support.
On Christmas?
Some people don't have
anywhere else to go today.
You should come.
Knock yourselves out.
Everyone's welcome. It's not
just for people with AIDS.
Okay, yeah, I'll be there, but
first I got a protest to save.
See? Told you.
I'm just playing with you, boy.
Well, it's Christmas.
Don't stay in the house all day.
Bye.
Hi.
Maureen called me to try to
come help fix the equipment.
You're Mark?
Joanne?
- Maureen said she'd be here.
- Well, don't hold your breath.
This is so typical.
I told her not to call you.
Oh, well...
Can I help anyway?
I've hired an engineer.
Great.
Well, nice to have met you, then.
He's three hours late.
The samples won't delay But the cable...
There's another way
Say something, anything
Test, one, two, three
Anything but that
- This is weird
- It's weird
- Very weird
- Fuckin' weird
I'm so mad that I don't know what to do
Fighting with microphones
Freezing down to my bones
And to top it all off I'm with you
Feel like going insane?
Got a fire in your brain?
And you're thinking
Of drinking gasoline?
- As a matter of fact
- Honey, I know this act
It's called the Tango: Maureen
The Tango: Maureen
It's a dark, dizzy
merry-go-round
- As she keeps you dangling
- You're wrong
- Your heart she is mangling
- It's different with me
And you toss and you turn
'Cause her cold eyes can burn
Yet you yearn, and you churn And rebound
I think I know what you mean
- The Tango: Maureen
Has she ever pouted her lips
And called you "pookie'"?
Never.
Have you ever Doubted a kiss or two?
This is spooky
Did you swoon When she
walked through the door?
Every time, so be cautious
Did she moon over other boys?
- More than moon
- I'm getting nauseous
Where'd you learn to tango?
With the French ambassador's
daughter in her room at Miss Porter's.
And you?
With Nanette Himmelfarb,
the rabbi's daughter...
...at the Scarsdale
Jewish Community Center.
It's hard to do this backwards.
You should try it in heels.
- She cheated
- Maureen cheated
- Fuckin' cheated
I'm defeated I should give up right now
Gotta look on the bright
side With all of your might
I'd fall for her still, anyhow
When you're dancing her
dance You don't stand a chance
Her grip of romance makes you fall
- So you think, "Might as well"
- "Dance a tango to hell"
"At least I'll have tangoed at all"
The Tango: Maureen
Gotta dance till your diva is through
You pretend to believe her
'Cause in the end You can't leave her
But the end, it will come
Still you have to play dumb
Till you're glum and
you bum And turn blue
Why do we love when she's mean?
And she can be so obscene
My Maureen
The Tango:
Maureen
Mark.
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Actually...
...I feel great now.
I feel lousy.
And we're patched.
Thanks.
- Maureen?
- Hi, baby.
- Hi, honey, we're...
- Pookie.
"Pookie"?
- You never called me pook...
- We're late.
Forget it.
- We're patched.
- Thank you.
Pookie.
Shut up.
Okay, everyone, let's begin.
First, I just want to welcome you all.
Why don't we start by going
around and introducing ourselves.
Steve.
Gordon.
Ali.
Pam.
Sue.
Hi.
I'm Angel.
Tom.
Collins.
I'm Paul.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
And you are...?
Oh, I'm not... I don't have...
I'm here with...
I'm just here to...
Mark.
Mark. I'm Mark.
Well, this is quite an operation.
Does anyone have a problem...
...if I film a little of
this for a documentary?
Make yourself comfortable, Mark.
Who wants to begin?
Well, I'm...
Yesterday...
...I found out my T cells were low.
What was your reaction?
Scared.
How are you feeling today? Right now?
Okay.
All right.
Pretty good.
Is that all?
It's the best I've felt in a long time.
- Months.
- Then why choose fear?
I'm a New Yorker.
Fear's my life.
Look, I find Some of
what you teach suspect
Because I'm used to Relying on intellect
But I try to open up
To what I don't know
Because reason says I should have died
Three years ago
There's only us
There's only this
Forget regret
Or life is yours to miss
No other road
No other way
No day but today
What's the time?
Well, it's gotta be close to midnight
My body's talking to me
It says, "Time for danger"
It says, "I wanna commit a crime
Wanna be the cause of a fight
I wanna put on a tight skirt
And flirt with a stranger"
I've had a knack from way back
At breaking the rules
Once I learn the game
Get up, life's too quick
I know someplace sick
Where this chick'll Dance in the flames
We don't need any money
I always get in for free
You can get in too
If you get in with me
Let's go
Out tonight
I have to go
You wanna play? Let's run away
We won't be back Before
it's New Year's Day
Take me out tonight
Meow.
Yeah
When I get a wink From the doorman
Do you know how lucky you'll be?
That you're on the line
With the feline of Avenue B
Let's go
Out tonight
I have to go
You wanna prowl? Be my night owl?
Well, take my hand we're gonna
Howl
Out tonight
In the evening I've got to roam
Can't sleep in the
city Of neon and chrome
Feels too damn much like home
When the Spanish babies cry
So let's find a bar
So dark we forget who we are
Where all the scars From
the nevers and maybes die
Let's go
Out tonight
I have to go
You're sweet Wanna hit the street?
Wanna wail at the moon
Like a cat in heat?
Just take me
Out tonight
Please take me
Don't forsake me
Out tonight
I'll let you make me
Tonight
Who do you think you are?
Barging in on me and my guitar
Little girl, hey, the door is that way
You better go You know
the fire's out anyway
Take your powder Take your candle
Your sweet whisper I just can't handle
Well, take your hair In the moonlight
Your brown eyes Goodbye, good night
I should tell you I should tell you
I should tell you, I should... No.
Another time, another place
Our temperature would climb
There'd be a long embrace
We'd do another dance
It'd be another play
Looking for romance?
Come back another day
Another day
The heart may freeze
Or it can burn
The pain will ease
If I can learn
There is no future
There is no past
I live this moment as
My last
There's only us
There's only this
Forget regret
Or life is yours to miss
No other road
No other way
No day but today
Excuse me if I'm off track
But if you're so wise Then tell me
Why do you need smack?
Take your needle
Take your fancy prayer
Don't forget, Get the
moonlight out of your hair
Long ago you might have Lit up my heart
But the fire's dead Ain't
never ever gonna start
Another time Another place
The words would only rhyme
We'd be in outer space
It'd be another song
We'd sing another way
You wanna prove me wrong?
Come back another day
Another day
There's only yes
Only tonight
We must let go
To know what's right
No other course
No other way
No day but today
I can't control
Control your temper
My destiny
She doesn't see
I trust my soul
- Who says that there's a soul?
- My only goal
Is just to be
Just let me be
- Who do you think you are?
- There's only now, there's only here
- Barging in on me and my guitar
- Give in to love, or live in fear
- Little girl, hey
- No other path
- The door is that way
- No other way
No day but today
The fire's out anyway
Take your powder Take your candle
No day but today
Take your brown eyes, Your
pretty smile, your silhouette
No day but today
Another time, another place,
Another rhyme, a warm embrace
No day but today
Another dance, Another
way, another chance
Another day
No day but today
- Speak.
Mark, Roger, it's Benny.
Look, you still got a few
hours to stop Maureen's protest.
My offer expires after dark.
Hey.
How you doing?
- Look, about last night...
- I don't wanna talk about it.
You know, Mimi's gonna be
at Maureen's show tonight.
You should come too.
I'd hate to see you pass up
something that could be good for you.
You'll only regret it.
I'll live.
Right.
Will I lose my dignity?
Will someone care?
Will I wake tomorrow
From this nightmare?
Will I lose my dignity?
Will someone care?
Will I wake tomorrow
From this nightmare?
- Will I lose my dignity?
Will someone care?
- Will I wake tomorrow
- From this nightmare?
- Will I lose my dignity?
- Will someone care?
- Will I wake tomorrow
- From this nightmare?
- Will I lose my dignity?
Will I lose my dignity?
- Will someone care?
- Will I lose my dignity?
- Will I wake tomorrow
- Will someone care?
- From this nightmare?
- Will I wake tomorrow
From this nightmare?
- Will I lose my dignity?
- Will I lose?
Will someone care?
Will I wake tomorrow
From this nightmare?
I am so glad you came, man.
- I'm proud of you.
- Thanks.
Come on, get up.
Come on, let's go.
- Wake up.
- This ain't a campground.
Let's go. You gotta go.
Christ, it's a lady. Come
on, ma'am, you gotta get up.
Smile for Ted Koppel, officers.
Who do you think you are?
I don't need no goddamn help...
...from some bleeding-heart cameraman.
My life's not for you to
make a name for yourself on.
Easy, sugar, easy. He was just trying...
Just trying to use me to kill his guilt.
It's not that kind of movie, honey.
This place is full of artists.
Hey, artist, you got a dollar?
Didn't think so.
New York City
- Center of the universe
- Sing it, girl.
Times are shitty, but I'm
pretty sure They can't get worse
- I hear that.
- It's a comfort to know
When you're singing
The hit-the-road blues
That anywhere else you could
Possibly go after New York would be
A pleasure cruise
Now you're talking.
Well, I'm thwarted
by a Metaphysic puzzle
And I'm sick of grading
papers, That I know
I'm shouting in my sleep I need a muzzle
And all this misery pays no salary So
Let's open up a restaurant In Santa Fe
Sunny Santa Fe would be nice
We'll open up a restaurant In Santa Fe
And leave this To the roaches and mice
- You teach?
- Yeah, I teach.
Computer Age Philosophy.
When my students would rather watch TV.
- America.
You're a sensitive aesthete
Brush the sauce onto the meat
You can make the menu
Sparkle with a rhyme
You can drum a gentle drum
I can seat guests as they come
Chatting not about Heidegger, But wine
Let's open up a restaurant In Santa Fe
- Santa Fe
- Our labors would reap financial gain
- Gain
- We'll open up
A restaurant in Santa Fe
- Santa Fe
- And save from devastation our brains
Save our brains
We'll pack up all ourjunk
And fly so far away
Devote ourselves to projects That sell
We'll open up a restaurant In Santa Fe
Forget this cold bohemian hell
Do you know the way To Santa Fe?
You know, tumbleweeds
Prairie dogs
Yeah
Oh, guys, I'm late for Maureen's
sound check. I gotta go.
- Here, you can help me.
- Bye.
See you later.
It's cold.
Come on.
Live in my house
I'll be your shelter
Just pay me back With 1000 kisses
Be my lover
I'll cover you
Open your door I'll be your tenant
Don't got much baggage
To lay at your feet
But sweet kisses I've got to spare
I'll be there and I'll cover you
- I think they meant it
- When they said you can't buy love
- Now I know you can rent it
- A new lease you are, my love
- On life
- Be my life
- Just slip me on
- I'll be your blanket
- Wherever, whatever
- I'll be your coat
You'll be my king And
I'll be your castle
No, you'll be my queen
And I'll be your moat
- I think they meant it
- When they said you can't buy love
- Now I know you can rent it
- A new lease you are, my love
- On life
- All my life
- I've longed to discover
- Something as true as this is
- So with a thousand sweet kisses
- When you're cold and you're lonely
I'll cover you With a
thousand sweet kisses
- You've got one nickel only
- I'll cover you
With a thousand sweet kisses
- When you're worn out and tired
- I'll cover you
With a thousand sweet kisses
- When your heart has expired
- I'll cover you
- Oh, lover
- Yeah
- I'll cover you
I'm gonna celebrate tonight.
All right, cool.
- The usual.
- Cool.
- Hey.
- Hey. Can I talk to you for a sec...?
Hey. Lover boy. You
steal my client, you die.
You didn't miss me, you won't miss her.
Look around. Got plenty of customers.
Look.
About last night, I'm sorry.
- I don't know what the...
- Just forget it.
I was out of line. Can
I make it up to you?
How?
Bunch of us are getting
together tonight.
At the Life Caf? after Maureen's show.
Yeah?
Would you like to come with me?
Sure. I'd like that.
So you're a tough guy?
No. Not really.
That's pretty good.
Over there. The guy with the glasses.
Right there.
- Angel.
- Mimi.
Oh, my God, you look so good.
Maureen! Maureen! Maureen!
Last night I had a dream.
I found myself in a
desert called Cyberland.
It was hot.
My canteen had sprung
a leak, and I was...
...thirsty.
Out of the abyss walked a cow.
Elsie.
I asked if she had
anything to drink. She said:
"I'm forbidden to produce milk
In Cyberland we only drink
Diet Coke"
She said:
"Only thing to do
Is jump over the moon"
I
Gotta get out of here
It's like I'm being tied to the
hood Of a yellow rental truck
Being packed in With
fertilizer and fuel oil
Pushed over a cliff By
a suicidal Mickey Mouse
I've
Gotta, gotta, gotta, gotta, gotta
Gotta, gotta find a way
To jump over the moon
Only thing to do Is jump over the moon
Yeah! Go, Maureen!
Then a little bulldog entered.
His name, we have learned, was Benny.
And although he once had principles...
...he abandoned them
to live as a lapdog...
...to a wealthy daughter
of the revolution.
A one, two, three "That's bull," he said
"Ever since the cat took up
the fiddle That cow's been jumpy
The dish and the spoon were
evicted From the table and eloped
She's had trouble with that
milk And the moon ever since
Maybe it's a female thing
'Cause who'd wanna
leave Cyberland anyway?
Walls ain't so bad
The dish and the spoon, for
instance, They're down on their luck
They come knockin' On my doghouse door
And I say, 'Not in my
back yard, utensils.
Go back to China"'
"The only way out is up,"
Elsie whispered to me.
"A leap
Of faith"
- Yeah.
- That's it.
"Still thirsty?"
"Parched. "
"Have some milk. "
And I lowered myself
beneath her swollen udder...
...and I sucked the sweetest
milk I had ever tasted.
"Climb onboard," she said.
And as a harvest moon
rose over Cyberland...
...we reared back, we
sprang into a gallop...
...leaping out of orbit.
I awoke, singing...
Leap of faith Leap of faith
Only thing to do
Only thing to do is jump
Only thing to do is Jump over the moon
Over the moon
Over the...
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org