Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Can you see that area behind me
beneath the red-tinted sky?
That is what's left of Raccoon City
after the military fired a missile at it.
According to unconfirmed reports,
the missile was allegedly nuclear.
If this is the case,
there's little hope of finding...
...any survivors among
the city's 100,000 inhabitants.
Mr. President, what is the connection
between Umbrella Corporation...
- ... and this incident?
- No more questions.
Was the missile launched
as a result of this connection?
Can you shed light on this?
The president has announced
his resignation.
Umbrella Corporation stock
plummeted here in Europe.
This dealt a blow
to the business giant...
...resulting in its
complete dissolution.
The estimated number of bioterror
victims has skyrocketed...
...from hundreds of thousands
to over one million.
The president announced that
the Republic of Bajirib...
...led by General Grande,
was the latest addition to the list...
...of countries
that sponsor terrorism.
- announced it plans to put
taxpayers' money to work...
...by allocating one billion dollars
for an anti-bioterror program.
Pharmaceutical company WilPharma
issued a press release...
...on establishing
a research facility in Harvardville...
...home to 100,000 residents.
We've taken every precaution
to ensure that a catastrophe...
...such as the one suffered by
Raccoon City, is never repeated.
Inflamed by Senator Ron Davis'
full support of the new facility-
Dr. Curtis Miller, a longtime opponent
of the WilPharma research facility...
...was arrested and charged
with obstruction of business...
...and issuing threats to proponents
of WilPharma's ex-
Our organization has disassociated
itself from Dr. Miller.
The human rights organization
Terra-Save has demanded...
...WilPharma release the results
of their tests conducted in India.
WilPharma stock fell sharply as
a result of scathing accusations...
...hurled at them by Terra-Save.
WilPharma must go.
We say no. WilPharma must-
Members of Terra-Save lie in wait here
in front of Harvardville Airport...
...in anticipation of Senator Davis'
imminent arrival.
The group hopes
to confront the politician...
...who will be attending the National
Pharmaceutical Conference.
Now arriving in Gate 32A...
...Flight 349
from Newark, New Jersey.
Will a Brock Silverstein
please report to Gate 7?
Brock Silverstein to Gate 7.
Flight 89 from Columbus
has just arrived at Gate 17.
For those waiting to depart,
it'll just take a minute to de-board...
...and turn the plane around.
It's been ages.
You look great.
You look tired.
Blame my new boyfriend,
he won't let me get any sleep.
Boyfriend, huh? Is that what
you're calling the W.H.O. report now?
FDA, actually.
Aunt. I'm tired.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Stay here, and I'll bring the limousine
around as quickly as I can.
Will you watch Rani for a minute?
- Sure thing.
- I'll be right back.
Well, we should
introduce ourselves.
I'm Claire Redfield.
- You can call me Claire.
- I'm Rani.
Nice to meet you, Rani.
That's a pretty name.
Excuse me, sir,
are you feeling all right?
Would you like me
to bring you some water?
It's urgent I reach Frederic Downing
from WilPharma.
Emergency.
We say no. WilPharma must go.
Do you work for Terra-Save too?
Yep. Just like your aunt.
I like everybody from Terra-Save
because they're all pretty cool.
You fight bad guys, right?
- Bad guys?
- Like him.
Senator Davis, you serve as a special
advisor for WilPharma Corporation.
After viewing photos of their
latest human test subjects...
...what are your thoughts?
That Halloween is celebrated earlier
in India than in the U.S., maybe?
Really, I simply don't understand
American humor.
Apologies. I didn't mean to-
Don't worry about it. I can relate.
Are you two waiting for someone
as well?
Yeah.
Well, I think the asylum let
the patients out for the day.
It's a bit crazy outside.
That's an understatement.
The Air Dome Research Facility
isn't the only thing...
...Senator Davis
brought to Harvardville.
It's like the wacko circus hit town.
Well, I-
I'm weary of waiting.
I'm going to grab a taxi.
Good day, ladies.
Who the hell let it leak out
that I was coming?
Now those damned agitators
are out there stirring up trouble.
I don't need this.
Get them out of here.
What tar pit did this crap
ooze out of?
I'm sorry, I'll get you another.
I don't care what it takes,
just get rid of them now.
Arrest them if you have to.
But, sir, we don't have
any grounds for arrest.
They haven't done
anything illegal yet.
Senator, may I make a suggestion?
We could slip out through
the regular entrance.
No one would expect that,
so the crowd won't notice us.
What? Hell, no.
I am an elected official.
I will not skulk out of here
like some whipped dog.
Now, I won't budge from this spot
until you get that swarm of vermin...
...out of the building.
The bad guy. Claire.
It's him. The bad guy we saw on TV.
Senator Davis.
Can I have another word?
- You cannot.
- Please, senator. Please.
Just one more question.
Why would you-?
What the hell is this?
Rani, wait here, okay?
Did someone put you up to this, or is
this stupid costume your brilliant idea?
Okay, genius,
you got something to say...
...get it off your chest and move on.
This is too much.
Ma'am, are you involved in this?
Indirectly, in a manner of speaking.
Then, in a manner of speaking...
...you're coming with me too.
- Now, wait just a minute.
- Chief.
Oh, my God.
What's going on here?
Stand back.
Move, move, move. Out of the way.
Move away from him now.
Damn.
Too late. He's dead.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Run.
Get away. Hurry.
Hey, wait.
Where are you going?
Reporting live
from Harvardville Airport.
A protestor demonstrating against
WilPharma Corporation...
...attacked and supposedly killed
a police officer.
But now, that same officer
has just attacked...
...Senator Ron Davis' bodyguard
in a similar manner.
Eddie, why did you stop rolling?
Wha-?
Rani.
Rani!
Curtis Miller.
Rani?
Please. Help me.
Attention all persons
inside the terminal.
Evacuate the building immediately.
Repeat, evacuate
the terminal immediately.
This is not a drill.
Use all exits.
Everyone evacuate
the terminal building immediately.
No.
No way.
This can't be happening.
Local police have secured
the entire airport in a lockdown...
...and access into the area
is blocked.
Authorities are not releasing details
and we have very little information...
...at this time.
However, according
to unsubstantiated reports...
...a bioterror event has occurred
in one of the airport terminals.
Senator Ron Davis is among those
who are confined within the airport.
At present, his condition...
Give me a hand.
I want to go home.
I don't understand
why you won't let me leave.
Why can't we stage
rescue operations?
Please, chief.
You've gotta talk to your higher-ups.
You heard the 911 call, didn't you?
Come on, please.
Damn it.
What's the matter?
Chief Jackass again?
What's the status of the site?
Well, the entire airport
is completely blockaded now.
We were attacked by two people
that I believe were recently infected.
But don't worry.
We caught them and locked them up
in a task-force vehicle.
But even so, becoming infected
by being bitten...
It's like something out of
a horror movie.
Those creatures rising up
out of their graves.
Come on, I'm just kidding.
But seriously...
...do you think this WilPharma drug
has something to do with all this?
I don't know.
Even if there is a connection,
that shouldn't kick off...
...a spontaneous outbreak
of some creepy-ass plague.
It definitely reeks of terrorism.
That explains why the state Board of
Health hauled ass to get here so fast.
What do you think the suits
are trying to cover up?
If I knew that, I'd have
a hell of a lot more clout.
The White House sent a special agent
to handle this mess.
He ought to be here soon.
You can ask him.
Ask all you like, but honestly, there's
nothing to discuss on that subject.
Who the hell are you?
Leon S. Kennedy.
Then you're the one?
This is one of the 911 calls
that was made.
- How many are alive?
- Four, including me.
One's wounded. The senator.
Can you give me your location?
We're in the VIP lounge,
west end of the arrivals lobby.
Listen, I don't know how long
we can hold up.
Send help now before
those things get at us. Please hurry.
Most likely, that call came
from here.
We believe they're in the VIP lounge
for Atmos Airlines.
Right now, the airport police
and state Board of Health...
...are the first responders.
They've completely shut down
the main entrance here...
...and the two side entrances
here and here.
There are no other routes
into the terminal building.
We believe our best bet
is to fly in by helicopter...
...and enter through the roof.
- The team should be comprised-
- I'll take the two of you. No one else.
What? Why?
Because I don't care to risk increasing
the number of infectees.
You don't want to be forced
to shoot your friends, do you?
Hey. Hey. Hold on a second.
You can't be serious.
Who does this guy think he is?
He doesn't look military.
He's the special agent
assigned to this incident.
Let's just see what he can do.
Those infected with this virus
will attack other people...
...anyone, without exception.
The people that are bitten become
infected and go on to attack others.
The only way to stop the infection
is to destroy the infectees' brains.
Destroy their brains?
Shoot them in the head.
We're here.
The song of the infected.
Wait.
Are you okay?
Take it easy.
Help is on the way.
What the hell are you doing?
Look.
Stop or I'll shoot.
That's impossible.
Angela.
You like that, huh?
- You want some of this? Get off.
- Stop, enough.
Yeah, come on. Yeah!
- That's enough. Stop.
- Get off.
Freaks.
Yeah.
Hey.
What the hell, man?
I shot her point blank.
There's no way I could've missed her.
I told you. The only way to stop them
is to shoot them in the head.
It's their only vulnerable spot.
Don't forget it, otherwise
you'll waste time and ammunition.
And that can prove to be fatal.
Let's go.
- Those were gunshots.
- They sent help.
We're gonna get out of here.
You should thank me.
If you hadn't told them I was here,
they would've ignored your call.
You might want to stick your ego
up your ass...
...considering your own secretary
left you here to die.
What was that?
Someone who isn't infected.
We have to help.
It's too late.
There's nothing we can do.
That's right.
I mean, if you, then I leave too.
No, Claire, don't go.
When my father left,
he said the same thing.
He said he was going
to go help my mother...
...but he didn't come back,
and neither did she.
And if you leave,
you won't come back either.
It's okay.
I am gonna come back.
- I promise.
- Really?
By the way, do we have anything here
that can be used as a weapon?
Never saw this coming.
Is there anyone there?
No answer. Never a good sign.
Get down.
Leon.
- What are you doing here?
- I could ask you the same thing.
You're the one?
Is this it?
- Yup.
- Reinforcements?
None. We're getting out alone.
Is it too much to hope
you at least have some sort of a plan?
- We're gonna run across the lobby.
- Are you insane?
The lobby is crawling
with those creatures.
It's also the widest area.
It's too dangerous
to take the long way around.
He's right.
They aren't fast.
We can get by them.
Oh, yeah?
And since when
did the NGO member...
...become such an authority
on the subject?
She's one of the rare survivors
of Raccoon City.
She has more experience
with this kind of hellish nightmare...
...than anyone else here.
Hey, Raccoon City,
isn't that where the-?
Yes.
Run.
Keep up with me, Rani.
- Go.
- Thanks.
Senator.
Sir.
Greg.
Shit.
He got bit.
He damn well got bit.
Stay back.
Go on without me.
- Greg. Wait.
- Greg.
You got this?
Greg.
Greg. No.
Greg!
You okay?
Do I look like I'm okay?
Are we going to make it out of here?
We have a clear view
and a straight path to the exit.
We'll take out as many as we can...
...and run like hell.
Angela, back me up.
Got it.
Can't you get rid of them any faster?
They're starting to gather over here.
We're not gonna make it out,
are we?
It's getting tough.
We gotta go.
Rani.
Claire.
You all right?
Barely.
- Rani, are you okay?
- Claire.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Where's the senator?
Finally.
I'm over here.
The light. Run towards the light.
Get that perimeter set up. Move.
Don't stand there, man. Set it up.
Move in, move in. Open fire.
- Light them up, boys. Light them up.
- Get a move on.
Move, move.
Rani!
Rani.
Aunt.
- Aunt.
- Oh, my God. You're all right.
I was so scared.
Aunt.
They were everywhere.
- I didn't think I would see you again.
- I can't stand kids.
They're a real pain in the ass.
Oh, my poor darling.
Bastard.
That girl will have nightmares...
...for the rest of her life
because of you.
Let me go. Give her to me. Please.
I got it, I got it.
Claire.
You okay?
Oh, honey, I know.
But she's fine, really.
We just have to wait.
No problem.
I'll take care of it.
We can use that
in the worst-case scenario.
I have no intention
of letting WilPharma...
...end up looking like a savior.
Hey, Hunnigan. I'm reporting in.
I already heard.
The Marines landed
in the nick of time and saved the day.
I can't tell you how relieved I am.
I'm amazed and impressed
you got authorization for that.
- You must have pulled a few strings.
- Yes. Well, I have my resources.
After I received confirmation
from USAMRIID...
...that the virus used in this attack
was indeed the T-virus...
...I submitted a plan
to the president.
He pushed it through
as a special emergency act.
Every Marine involved in the assault
was vaccinated.
- Have the terrorists made demands?
- No, not yet.
But the FBl captured a member
of General Grande's army...
...in Los Angeles just moments ago.
When we interrogate him,
he might give us some information...
...that'll establish a link...
...between this terrorist attack
and the one in India.
Maybe we'll dig up a lead
on the whereabouts...
...of former
Umbrella Corporation employees.
They've gotta be the ones peddling
the virus on the black market.
What the hell is going on?
Why are WilPharma drugs
being brought here?
It's the vaccine.
You. What are you doing here?
He's WilPharma's head researcher.
May I introduce Frederic Downing.
He's the one who developed
a vaccine for the virus...
...which you, in particular,
are so familiar with.
You mean the infection
in the terminal?
You thought that was
WilPharma-engineered, didn't you?
Utterly ridiculous.
An inoculation.
That's what they've been working on.
A way to prevent further outbreaks.
- But-
- Claire, it's true.
- You knew?
- Yes.
I didn't think its use
would be sanctioned this quickly.
Then the human testing
that took place in India...
An attack by terrorists
that somehow got hold of the T-virus.
All the members of the group
supported by General Grande...
...were infected,
so we don't know the details.
The U.S. government obtained
permission from Indian authorities...
...to administer the T-virus vaccine
to the nearby communities.
A vaccine secretly developed
by WilPharma.
It was a success.
The infection rate
was kept as minimal as possible.
Why the hell didn't you
break out the vaccine for this?
If we'd been inoculated before
we entered the terminal, Greg would-
Inoculation would have been
entirely possible...
...had Terra-Save not backed us
into an adversarial corner.
Had we been able
to follow proper procedure...
...as outlined in the original schedule,
the government medical stockpile...
...could have been shipped anywhere
in the U.S. within 12 hours.
Oh, my God. Then...
...it's all our fault.
I wouldn't argue with you there.
We just ended up
making things worse.
That's not true.
The villains here
are the ones who used the virus.
But worse than them
are the ones who made it.
Seven years ago,
our lives were changed forever...
...by the virus from Umbrella Corp.
Umbrella collapsed...
...but their viral legacy
continues to spread.
I'm gonna scrub this virus
from the face of the Earth.
You chose the role of rescuer
rather than fighter, like me.
You chose a path that
your brother and I couldn't follow.
You weren't wrong.
Leon, thank you.
Hurry.
Find some extinguishers.
Clear the area
before the gas tanks blow.
Let's go, let's go.
Where's the rest of the team?
Come on.
- How do I use this thing?
- Help.
Somebody help. I'm stuck.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Hurry up, come on.
- What happened?
- The trucks carrying the vaccine-
How much vaccine is left?
Everything we brought today was all
we were able to scrape together...
...from vaccine samples
inside the company.
And most of that has just been lost.
Where's the manufacturing data?
- You think they're after the data too?
- Could it be?
Why don't you tell us
what their demands are already?
If you don't wanna talk
I'll just go directly to the president.
The truth.
Truth?
They demand the truth.
The viral weapon from which Umbrella
Corporation's T-virus was derived.
They wanna reveal everyone from the
U.S. government who was involved.
Was the government
really involved?
The proof went up in smoke
with Raccoon City.
Wait a minute.
The truth didn't disappear.
- There never was any.
- Convince the terrorists of that.
If they don't get that information,
what will happen?
They'll disperse the T-virus
in every populated area in the U.S.
The deadline is midnight.
That's only four hours from now.
And there's no vaccine left.
Can we find out
who the terrorists are?
I have a clue as to the identity
of one of them.
Right after the first infected victims
appeared in the airport terminal...
...I noticed a man in the lobby.
His name is Curtis Miller.
I know him.
He's one of those bleeding hearts...
...protesting the construction
of the new research facility.
If the terrorists' demands
are the release of information...
...on what really happened
in Raccoon City...
- ... then he might-
- It can't be.
Curtis Miller is...
...my older brother.
My brother
wouldn't do something like this.
He was arrested
for threatening WilPharma.
He just demanded
information be made public.
Unfortunately, the rest of the world
doesn't see it that way.
If you claim he's not a terrorist...
...why don't you bring him here
to explain himself? Now.
You're sure packing a lot of hardware
just to go see your brother.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the office
and check on the development data.
Can I help you with something?
Don't worry. I'm not scheming...
...to infiltrate your organization
for my own devious purposes.
I'm afraid there's only one thing
you can do.
Join me for a late afternoon tea.
There you are. Comfortable?
It'll be nice to have some company.
This is the road to Curtis' home.
I haven't heard a word from Curtis
in three years.
He lost his wife and child
in the Raccoon City tragedy.
That's odd. It won't accept my card.
- Has that happened before?
- No. This is the first time.
I'll have to use the master code.
We're entering an air dome.
The roof is supported...
...by creating a difference between
the exterior and interior air pressure.
The danger levels in this facility
are assigned...
...according to the microbes
that are handled in each section.
From the right,
the levels ascend from 1 to 4.
The higher the number,
the higher the danger level.
Rest assured, however, that there are
stringent safety measures in place...
...in the unlikely event
a problem occurs.
If anything positive rose
from the ashes of Raccoon City...
...it's that security and safeguard
standards have been elevated...
...in order to avert
any future calamities.
What about this zero area?
That contains researchers' offices,
meeting rooms and the like.
That's where we're headed next.
This isn't paradise.
This is what you came
to assist me with.
Thank you.
Smells delicious.
- What are you doing?
- Checking on the development data.
- Yes, senator.
- I figured you must be there by now.
What do you want?
Why did you bring
that woman there?
You're not feeling sorry for her,
are you? That's not like you.
Don't you understand?
This is our chance.
Yes, I know.
Yes.
What did he say?
Nothing of any consequence,
I assure you.
He said something to you, didn't he?
He warned me
not to let you see anything.
Would it cause trouble
if I saw something in particular?
No.
When I started out as a rookie cop...
...I responded to a call
about a small child...
...that was stranded on a sandbank
in the middle of a flooding river.
I impulsively jumped into the river.
The next thing I knew...
...I was waking up in a hospital bed,
bleary and disoriented.
They informed me afterward...
...that I had saved the child.
But three S.R.T. members
were injured...
...while fishing my sorry butt
out of the water.
Talk about depressed.
I felt lower than dirt.
What was I thinking,
putting others in harm's way like that?
Not to mention
that I could've been killed too.
But then Curtis said something...
...that made me stop
beating myself up.
"If you don't try to save one life...
...you'll never save any. "
In the end...
...his own words
came back to haunt him.
Let me through. Let me through.
There is something,
but Davis wants it to remain hidden.
This is the G-virus.
You have that here?
It remains a secret
even within the company.
The government affiliates
don't know about it either.
It was obtained
through special means.
A group with which neither we...
...nor someone in the senator's
position can be associated.
You got it on the black market.
What did you plan on doing
with the G-virus?
Create a vaccine. But even the senator
couldn't adequately express...
...the threat
G posed to the government.
The plans were shelved
and it remains in Level 4 ever since.
The senator is a member
of the committee...
...that decided
to bomb Raccoon City.
I've gotta tell Leon.
Wait, no. I-
If you do that,
what's going to happen to me?
You didn't seem worried about that
when you were telling me everything.
Looks like- Looks like there's
something wrong with the server.
I'm going to stop Curtis.
Claire, what's wrong?
Leon, get over here
to WilPharma right now.
They've got the G-virus.
They were gonna make a vaccine
like for the T-virus...
...but Davis just called Frederic
and told him to get rid of it.
- Is Frederic there?
- He just went to go fix the server.
Or he may have gone
to dump the virus.
- Couldn't be.
- Claire?
There's a call
coming from inside the building.
Hold on.
- Claire?
- Frederic? Where are you?
- In Level 4.
- Why?
You were
going to the server room.
I saw someone suspicious
on my way and followed him.
You need to get out.
There's a time bomb.
It's too late to stop it.
We'll have another biohazard
if this thing-
Claire? Claire!
- Damn it.
- What's wrong?
I don't know. We got cut off.
Attention all personnel.
A system error has occurred.
Terminate all activities immediately
and evacuate the dome...
...until safe conditions
are re-established and verified.
Attention all personnel.
A system error has occurred.
Terminate all activities immediately
and evacuate the dome...
...until safe conditions
are re-established and verified.
Attention all personnel.
A system error has occurred.
Terminate all activities immediately
and evacuate the dome...
...until safe conditions
are re-established and verified.
Attention all personnel.
A system error has occurred.
Terminate all activities
and evacuate the dome...
...until safe conditions
are re-established...
Looks like sections are blocked.
Let's split up. We can meet up again
in the inner garden.
- Ready?
- Ready.
Angela.
You're not alone.
We're together in this.
I know.
Leon.
What happened? Where's Frederic?
He was telling me about a time bomb
he found in Level 4 when-
- A nasty wound. We gotta get out.
- I'm all right. Listen to me.
Curtis was here, I saw him.
He came out of Level 4
where the G-virus was kept.
Curtis.
Angela.
You're hurt.
You need medical attention.
- Why, Curtis?
- I couldn't forgive them...
...for covering up
the Raccoon City atrocity.
I refused to let the government
rewrite the truth as they saw fit.
So when I finally learned the truth,
I swore...
I swore I'd make them reveal it,
no matter what it took.
Curtis.
But he also told me...
...that I couldn't make things
any worse.
Even if it was deserved...
...there was no chance of me-
Of me causing a recurrence
of that horror...
...here in the town
where I was born and raised.
That's why he left me.
That's why he blew up this place.
Wait.
Nothing can stop it now.
In a moment...
...I'll reveal the irrefutable truth...
...in my own personal way.
And all of you
will be the very first witnesses!
Go straight down this corridor.
Head to elevator AD-2.
It'll take you to an outside exit.
Got it.
Claire.
- Try not to get killed.
- Okay, ditto.
Move.
No!
Stop.
Cease fire. Cease fire.
The target became aggressive
and resisted capture.
I deemed it necessary to open fire
and issued the order.
The target was terminated.
Warning: A lethal viral strain has
been detected in the garden sector.
Commencing feedback.
Warning: A lethal viral strain has
been detected in the garden sector.
Commencing feedback.
- Captain!
- You've gotta be kidding me.
My men shot the shit out of you.
My leg.
Angela.
Angela, get clear.
Leon.
Somebody.
Somebody pull me up.
What is this?
Anhydrous ethanol.
Are we being sterilized?
Not us, the building.
Incineration will initiate
in five minutes.
- All exits are now sealed.
- What the hell?
We're still in here.
Get all survivors
to the central rest area now.
Move it.
Come on.
Warning: All exits are now sealed.
Oh, shit.
Come on.
- We'll catch the next one.
- Right.
We'll send it b-
Go!
Stop.
You'll ignite us all.
- Oh, my God.
- It's impossible.
- He's still alive.
- No, no, no!
No, no, no!
- Leon.
- Angela.
- Incineration in two minutes.
- No!
Run.
- What?
- Run!
Incineration in 60 seconds.
It wants you because of
your blood connection.
It sees you as a breeding tool.
That thing isn't
your brother anymore.
Curtis is dead.
Incineration in 30 seconds.
Come on.
Twenty. Nineteen.
Eighteen. Seventeen.
Sixteen. Fifteen. Fourteen.
Thirteen. Twelve.
Eleven. Ten. Nine. Eight.
Seven. Six. Five. Four.
Three. Two. One.
Oh, shit.
Now what's gonna happen?
No. No, no.
Level 4 submerge system
will engage soon.
We need to go up.
Disable the system.
There's gotta be a way.
I know what Leon would do.
Right.
There.
Come on.
Warning:
Level 4 submerge system
will engage soon.
Twelve. Eleven. Ten. Nine. Eight.
Seven. Six. Five. Four.
Three. Two. One.
Level 1 submerge system
will engage soon.
Ten. Nine. Eight. Seven. Six.
Five. Four. Three. Two. One.
Curtis.
Run.
No. No.
I don't wanna hurt you.
Please.
No.
All right, Curtis.
Let's finish this.
Warning: Level 0 submerge system
will engage soon.
Ten. Nine. Eight. Seven.
Six. Five. Four.
Three. Two. One.
After the system verifies
there's no more virus in here...
...the hole will close.
Let me go.
Let go of me, damn it,
or you'll fall too.
You can't die.
You have to destroy these viruses.
Please, Leon, don't try to save me.
If you don't try to save one life,
you'll never save any.
Isn't that right, Curtis?
Are you okay?
It recorded.
Where's Frederic?
Dead. No vaccine data, no nothing.
The same as Raccoon City.
What?
Frederic said it.
You couldn't convince countries
to invest...
...in the development of the
insufficiently researched G-virus.
What are you talking about?
At first, I didn't suspect you were
connected with this terrorism.
If for no other reason than you were
in the airport when the event occurred.
But you had a motive
for causing all this.
Stocks.
WilPharma stock tanked
because of our accusations.
You were afraid that the situation...
...would turn out the same
as it did for Umbrella Corporation.
So you needed an excuse
to use the vaccine.
Now, wait a minute.
Yes, I'm a stockholder.
And WilPharma should regain
the public's faith after this incident.
But there's no way in hell I would
support terrorism to ensure that.
First of all, what is the G-virus?
I've never even heard of it.
I know you ordered Frederic
to dispose of the G-virus...
...when you called him.
I told him
not to show you anything more...
...than you needed to see,
that was it.
I doubt he knows anything.
Leon.
General Grande's
communication man talked.
It seems that all of us, the senator
included, were fooled by him.
Who are you talking about?
- Frederic? Where are you?
- In Level 4.
Why? You said you were
going to the server room.
I saw someone suspicious
on my way there and followed him.
You need to get out.
There's a time bomb here.
It's too late to stop it.
We'll have another biohazard
if this thing-
It can't be.
It's me.
What do you think?
Yes, per your request.
As of now, General Grande...
...only you will be in possession...
...of a set
of the T-virus and the T-vaccine.
Nothing would offer greater
advantage when negotiating...
...with a country that wants to keep
the existence of this virus a secret.
You needn't worry.
I've anticipated everything
down to the last detail...
...including my own
escape arrangements.
Don't forget...
...you owe me extra money
for the data on the G-virus.
And one last thing:
As a friend...
...heed my advice
and forget about G.
The stuff is wickedly volatile,
and it can't be controlled.
Right on time.
You were supposed to come alone.
I just wanted to see your face
one more time.
Don't move.
I have the last of the vaccine,
and the development data.
This is all that remains
in the entire world.
The rest is gone.
Yes, that's right.
You two can appreciate the situation
better than anyone...
...after your up-close-and-personal
experiences with virus victims.
Mankind will need this.
Wait. Please. Don't shoot me.
Let's talk.
You're a smart woman,
and smart women like money.
I can make you rich.
We'll split everything 50-50.
I meant 70-30. I'm happy with 30.
Please. Please, take it all.
Don't- Don't kill me.
I'm begging you. Please, no.
You're too pathetic to kill.
- All units, move in.
- Yes, sir.
Suspect has been apprehended
and is in custody.
Frederic confessed everything.
He was also the one that provided
the T-virus to the terrorists in India.
He even acted
as the black-market broker.
He stole the T- and G-viruses...
...then escaped right before
the Raccoon City disaster.
But Frederic decided he could
only sell them as a set with a vaccine.
So he erased his past...
...found employment
at WilPharma...
...and gained unrestricted access
to their research facilities.
He had the luxury of searching
for potential customers...
...while manufacturing the vaccine.
This is how he stumbled upon
General Grande.
The terrorist incidents
were demonstrations...
...staged for
General Grande's benefit.
Sort of a...
...twisted sales pitch.
And my brother
was just a tool to them.
He was used.
This doesn't absolve Curtis
of what he did.
But we share
something in common with him...
...and that's his passionate desire...
...to prevent any further tragedies
like Raccoon City.
I gotta go.
All right.
Catch you later.
Leon.
Let's go diving together again...
...sometime.
Love to.
When did you two go diving?
Don't worry about that.
More importantly,
what are you up to?
Need a lift?
I have a limousine waiting.
Claire.
Next time
we bump into each other...
...let's hope it's some place...
...a little more normal.
Definitely.
Until next time.
Senator Ron Davis
announced his resignation...
...after being accused of insider
trading with WilPharma stock...
...a company of which
he is a major stockholder.
Next, in international news:
General Miguel Grande
has suddenly decided to participate...
...in a Central Asian
disarmament conference.
But the real motivation behind
his participation is not yet known.
Government sources seem to be
optimistic about the turnaround...
...and say that it is to alleviate
economic blockades...
...while rumors state
that it is because...
...his ability to produce biological
weapons has been removed.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org