Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
% Return to me
Oh my dear, I'm so lonely
Hurry back, hurry back
Oh my love, hurry back, I'm yours
Return to me
For my heart wants you only
Hurry home, hurry home
Won't you please hurry home
to my heart?
My darlin'
If I hurt you I'm sorry
Forgive me
And please say you are mine
Return to me
Please come back, bella mia
Hurry back, hurry home
To my arms, to my lips, to my heart
Shame we've got to put roofs on 'em.
All right, Bill, I'm goin' home.
See you, buddy.
Solo tu, solo tu,
solo tu, solo tu, mio cuor
- See you, Big Mike.
- Hey, Bob. Have fun tonight.
As always!
So this is what I'm gonna say -
I'm gonna get up on the podium
and I'm gonna say,
"Good evening, ladies and gentlemen."
"Tonight I'm speaking on behalf
of my friend Sydney..."
And, um... Sydney, I'm really nervous.
- But do you care?
- Liz?
I knew I'd find you here.
Sydney, how you doin', brother?
I need your signature here
so I can change the polar bear's diet.
It's already five. I'll check the calf.
Just go home and get ready, OK?
Thanks. Bob's picking up my dress, I have
stockings, I have to take Mel for a run.
My hair, make-up... God, I'm so nervous!
You'll be fine. At the worst you forget your
speech and we don't get any donations.
- Don't even say that.
- Just kiddin'.
Oh, look at him, Charlie.
We'd go nuts in a place this small.
I know. But we're workin' on it.
Wish me luck, Sydney.
He only does that with you.
- Who are you bringing tonight?
- Haven't decided. Still got two hours.
Don't shake.
No, no, no, don't!
Oh, wet dog.
Come on, let's do it. Wet doggie!
Good boy! You hungry? Let's eat.
Let's go, Mel. She'll be home any minute.
Come on. Come on and eat. Let's eat.
Ooh, this looks good!
Go get some dinner. Come on, come on!
Dinner! Come on!
All right, she'll be home in a minute.
- Hi, my baby!
- Hey, babe.
Hey, honey! It's pouring out.
- Did you get my dress?
- Yeah, picked it up from the cleaners.
We're on schedule.
Mel, I'm so nervous.
I took Mel out.
In your tux?
Honey, your pants are soaked.
- Tell Mel to eat.
- Mel, eat!
You are cute!
Spend all day with an ape,
what do you expect?
Under our care at Lincoln Park Zoo
Sydney has regained his strength
and maintained excellent health.
Over the years Sydney has become
a part of the family.
Here he is with my husband.
My husband's the one on the right.
With the generous donations
we've received tonight,
along with continued
fund-raising, hint hint,
I hope - we hope - to expand
the gorilla habitat to triple its size.
Thank you all for your tremendous
support, and enjoy the evening.
Elizabeth Rueland.
Thank you, Dr Rueland.
Let's hear it for the doctor.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome Mr Joey Gian!
Good evening.
Speaking of animals, the band and I
have worked up something special.
So let's get this party started.
In the village, the peaceful village,
the lion sleeps tonight
In the village, the quiet village,
Wimoweh, wimoweh,
wimoweh, wimoweh
"What do you expect most
from a relationship?"
"A) Companionship,
B) Sex or C) Respect?"
I'd go with B, but let's put C so we get
a higher score. What do you think?
I think...
What do you need? Is it your neck?
I'll move the pillow.
Your back? I can raise you up.
Rosebud.
Very funny. You almost gave me
a heart attack - excuse the expression.
Meg, you can go home.
To what? My cable's out.
Joe and the kids.
They're OK.
It's good for him to be with them when
they're comin' down from the sugar.
He usually fuels them up
and then they detox on my shift.
Well, you've seen it!
Promise me
you'll take care of my grandpa.
What's got you talkin' like that?
I may never get a heart. You know?
I know you'll get one. I know.
You'll be able to do things you were
never able to. Concentrate on that.
Think about it, Grace.
Picture ridin' a bike.
Yeah, ridin' a bike.
That's what you need to think about.
Travelling, painting in Europe
and dating handsome men!
It's got to happen to one of us.
I'm getting a new heart, not a new ass.
Bob!
Bob... excuse me... Bob Rueland!
Mr Bennington. I didn't see you
or I would have stopped and said hello.
- Elizabeth's speech was wonderful.
- I'll go tell her that.
I suppose she told you about
our sizeable donation?
- My... Mrs...
- Mrs Bennington?
My wife gave, you know...
strictly anonymously.
Of course. Very generous.
I'll let Elizabeth know.
We also gave a chunk to the rainforest.
And before I knew it, I was on a safari!
Can you imagine me on safari, Bob?
No, I cannot.
I was. Me and the missus,
hackin' through the bush.
- Charlie?
- Hey, Bob! Mr Bennington!
Charlie, did you hear about
my sizeable donation?
The anonymous one. Yes, I have.
- She loves this song.
- Apparently.
- We don't want keep you, so...
- Stay, I'm going to put on more lipstick.
Is that possible?
- I'll go with you.
- To the ladies' room?
You got big news for Mr B, don't you?
Mr B, Charlie's got big news for you.
- What news?
- What are you...?
Because of that donation, they'll hang
a picture of you in the monkey house.
- I'm touched.
- It's an honour.
It's not official - I have to run it by
a couple of guys. I can do that right now.
You two have a lot to discuss.
So why don't you just stay and...?
Listen, Charlie,
would you ever consider
- a mural, maybe?
- A mural.
We love it there. My mother's family
is from Tuscany so it's like going home.
That's so sweet.
You must come out some time. Our place
is at the edge of a magnificent vineyard.
Everything's at the edge of a vineyard.
It's Tuscany.
- Mrs Rueland.
- Hey, stranger.
Honey, you remember Celia and Tony.
We were telling Elizabeth
about our place in Italy.
- We meant to go on our honeymoon.
- Sydney wouldn't have stood the flight.
I promise you we'll go to Italy - eventually.
That's big.
If that's a promise, I'll take that.
- Where are you vacationing this year?
- We're going to a water theme park.
That'll be nice.
It's a joke, Celia.
I promised my wife that we'd dance
tonight, Tony, so if you'll excuse us...
- Certainly.
- It was wonderful to see you both.
Good night.
It's a little crowded out here right now.
Let's wait for the next song.
So really... how was I?
You were perfect. With the backlighting
you could see right through your dress.
No, you were wonderful. Really.
I'm so proud of you.
Don't be too proud. Poor Sydney's
still stuck in that small space.
Tell you what. If you promise you'll take
time off for a trip to Italy with me
I promise to build Sydney a new home,
with or without the rest of the funding.
Deal.
Come on. You can stand on my feet.
Return to me
Oh my dear, I'm so lonely
Hurry home, hurry home
Won't you please hurry
home to my heart
My darling
If I hurt you I'm sorry
Forgive me
And please say you're mine
Return to me
We got a female, 34, car accident.
Hit on the right side.
Head trauma, unconscious
at the scene, never regained.
Get Westfall into scrub.
- Name?
- Any allergies?
Sir? Her name.
- Sir?
- Eli-Elizabeth Rueland.
Sorry, sir. You can't go in.
You're going to have to wait here.
We're going to try to help her.
Return to me
Cara mia, ti amo
Solo tu, solo tu, solo tu, solo tu
Mi' amor
- Andiamo. Get that while it's hot.
- I got it, Marty.
- Aah, sure I'll get it myself.
- Suit yourself, baby.
Where's Sophie?
She got a perm today. Her scalp is
still burning. She went home early.
Oh, of course she did. Why did I ask?
Will you go find yourself a gondola?
Pick up.
Now then, Nancy darlin'...
It looks massive but you'll get through it.
Thank you.
Marty, how is Gracie doing?
Oh, fine, you know.
We... we're all waiting.
- Are you still keeping up the rosary?
- Every night.
- Give her our love.
- Oh, I will, of course. Of course I will.
I can do that.
Where are the three chicken Vesuvios?
- Already served them, Marty.
- Thank you very much. Grazie.
Oh, you've got it, haven't you?
You have? Thanks be to God
and all the saints in heaven!
Let me talk to her.
I'll be right over. Here's Angelo now.
Call everybody up now!
You got a heart, huh?
What, like an hour into it?
Someone will come out
and tell you intermittently. Excuse me.
He's here.
- You're here.
- Isn't she beautiful?
Grandpa, thank you for
always taking care of me.
And if I don't come out...
I love you so much.
You've got to come out.
If those tulips you planted come up
and see only me standin' there,
they'll go back into the ground again.
Thanks. Give me a kiss.
OK, folks.
- Here we go.
- Pray, Grandpa.
We'll take good care of her.
- I'll see you later.
- Yes.
I got to walk Mel.
I left the hospital a few hours ago.
I came by and took him to the park.
OK.
Thanks.
- I'm gonna stay.
- No.
I'll pick your parents up
from the airport in the morning.
Thanks.
OK.
If you need anything, you call me.
I'll be here in two minutes.
Thank you, Charlie.
She's not coming home, Mel.
Blessed Michael the Archangel,
who protects in battle,
and this is the greatest
battle of our lives...
My wife never thought much of you
but you were always my favourite saint.
Cos you're a battler,
you're a fighter. Well,
fight for us now, Michael. Fight for us.
In the name of the Father,
Son and Holy Ghost. Amen.
Adam Martin Dayton, what is that?
Cherry pop.
- Sophie, did you give him wine?
- Angelo...
Angelo, what are you doin' to me?
- It's... tranquilliser.
- Great(!)
So sue me.
Now they're drunk and disorderly.
Is that funny, Dad?
Stop it right now, both of you. Joe!
- Joe...
- What?
Help me out. Take the kids
to your mom's. It's one in the morning.
- Here, Emmett. Nourish yourself.
- Thank you.
Could I have milk?
Tyler, I want all your brothers up here.
I'll only buy more.
- Let's go.
- I wanna stay and see the new heart.
You'll see it when it comes home.
Come on.
No stopping anywhere.
You come straight back here.
- I'll stop at a lap-dancing bar.
- That's funny(!)
- Where's Marty?
- Dad, where's Marty?
In the chapel, honey.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee...
Want me to shuffle for you?
- Want to ante a quarter?
- Yes. I do.
This guy you're talkin' about,
he can't sing at all.
- How come he's got such a big band?
- To drown him out.
Wally, stay out of this.
How many famous
Polish singers are there?
I got two words for you: Bobby Vinton.
Bobby Vinton?!
Bobby Vinton, Bobby Vinton!
Well, what have you got?
The Irish Rovers?
I got three words for you.
Mr Bing Crosby.
He made a lovely priest.
But he beat the hell out of his kids.
Doesn't mean he couldn't sing.
Sinatra beat up everybody.
Frank did not.
His people did, he did not.
Look at Dean Martin.
The guy never hit anybody.
What about Jerry?
But he was askin' for it.
The point is: we got Frank,
we got Dean, we got Perry Como,
Vic Damone, Bobby Darin,
Mario Lanza, Luciano Pavarotti,
we got Beniamino Gigli,
we got the composers!
Verdi, Leoncavallo!
- Millions.
- That's right. A dynasty.
- I'm not bragging, but...
- You're not?
You're not bragging?
Christ, he goes on for a half hour.
Oh, come on.
- I'll take you to the doctor in my Caddy.
- No thanks, I'll take my bike.
- Let him take you. Suppose it rains?
- Then I'll get wet.
Then you'll be sick.
Gracie, settle this:
best male singer, dead?
Dean Martin.
- Frank!
- Bing.
Bobby Vinton!
Now, go straight to your appointment,
then you go to meet Megan.
If your plans change, telephone me.
I may stop off at the Pussycat Club.
One of their strippers quit.
Don't say strippers.
God's listening to you.
It's been over a year.
You can hardly see it.
Nice try, Angelo.
I just don't like all the questions.
Tell everybody you're
the luckiest girl in the world.
I know, Grandpa.
You're beautiful - and no one's
going to notice your chest.
Thanks a lot(!)
- I'll see you later.
- Bye, Grace!
Ride on the sidewalk, now.
Leave her alone.
Stop in at the church as you go by.
She's thanked God enough already.
You're going to be
a long while in purgatory.
Really? Well, I'll be with friends.
God's listening to that.
All right, guys...
Now, out of respect we gotta give
honourable mention to Sammy Davis Jr.
He only had one eye, so...
what else can I tell ya?
- He was Irish, you know.
- Are you blind? He was Jewish.
Whatever. Somethin' didn't fit.
This is hard for him.
Everyone he's ever loved has died.
I'm all he has, he's all I have.
- Morning, Grace.
- Hey, Alice.
Everything's looking very good.
How are you feeling?
- Good. Happy. Of course I'm happy.
- Good.
- What else am I gonna be?
- Well, we all have our days.
Add those to your morning meds.
98.6.
I don't feel like I should have "days".
I should be happy
just to be alive - and I am.
I'm alive cos someone else is dead.
I should just shut up and be happy, right?
Mm-hm.
You can get dressed. See you next month.
Say hi to your grandfather.
He's a great listener(!)
- What, honey?
- Nothing.
Tom, what the hell is goin' on?
- It's not my department.
- Whose is it?
- My guys worked 18 hours.
- At time and a half. I'm cryin' for ya(!)
- You got the best guys here.
- I don't give a shit.
I got to take a break.
You're on Wabash at 3 o'clock -
new beams goin' in.
Keep up.
- Mail it, Grace. You'll feel better.
- I know. I want to.
Every time I go to do it, I... I can't.
I don't know why not. It's anonymous.
It says you're grateful. I'd want to get
it if I lost someone I loved. Wouldn't you?
Yeah, but... it just seems so strange.
Sending a thank-you note for a heart.
It seems so...
..not enough.
- Won't you feel worse not sending it?
- Yeah. I mean, I always have it.
And it's been a year, so drop it in
and move on. I'm sure they have.
Yeah.
Let it go.
Everybody clap for Auntie Grace.
She just mailed a very important letter.
- Mom, look at the cool truck!
- Yeah. Oh, look at that.
- Look at their arms.
- Yeah. Wow!
OK, come on - gorillas.
Karson, your pants are falling down.
These are Adam's. He has your pants on.
That's all right. Come on, Laura.
Laura, stay in front of Mommy
all the time while we're here.
Aunt Grace, are you OK?
Yeah. Whatever it was, it didn't hurt.
Let's try it.
See if we can get him to come over.
- "H"...
- Here he comes!
Look, Mom, he likes us.
- Doesn't he remind you of Daddy?
- He looks bigger than Daddy.
- Do you see?
- That's kinda sweet.
Bob, don't go in there.
I just talked to 'em!
OK, guys, here's the deal.
My wife wanted this building up
years ago, so we're way behind schedule.
First of all, you:
artificial trees are not planted.
I'm asking for an additional 50 feet
to build aroundthe existing oaks.
And I will leave plenty of room
for your godforsaken souvenir shop.
If you don't approve, I'm taking my men
and it's over. I don't need the work
and I'm certainly not here for the money.
I'm here because of my wife.
Have you got it?
Good.
Thanks for yellin' and screamin'.
Now I gotta go in and clean everything up.
You want to get a drink?
Somethin' to shake this off?
- Come on! Let's go get a beer.
- Thanks, Charlie. No.
Well, if not tonight, Friday night.
Because I got somebody for you.
Charlie, no.
She's got a great body:
attorney, great body, intelligent...
You gotta start goin' out! She loves
animals - her cat was a patient of mine.
I'm a dog person.
I'm just trying to help you.
- Dan, you got 'em!
- It's the first time I'm wearing 'em.
- You look good.
- Feelin' good.
- Need some help?
- I think I'll be OK.
Look at you!
- Where are you goin'?
- I don't know.
Thanks. I took Mel out.
Put the mail next to the phone.
On the pile.
Thanks, buddy. See you later.
Come on, Mel.
Any calls?
You have no messages.
Wanna eat?
- Hi.
- Hi, Mr Rueland.
Hey, Mel!
- There you go.
- Thanks. See you tomorrow night.
- Yeah.
- Bye. Bye, Mel!
Come on. In the kitchen.
I got you some rice.
Here we go.
You're gonna eat in here today.
Good.
Come on. Come on.
I'm not doin' this any more.
We're goin' back to eatin' in the kitchen.
Goddammit, Mel, come on back here and
eat in the kitchen like a normal person!
Good boy, good boy. Come on, let's go.
To the kitchen. Let's go.
That's it. Follow me.
There's a good boy.
Good boy. You made it halfway.
You gotta snap out of it, buddy.
Charlie, it's Bob.
I'm gonna go out with you
on Friday, all right?
Yeah, you heard me.
Where?
O'Reilly's?
O'Reilly's Italian restaurant?
OK.
Where is that?
Ah, Marie
Ah, Marie!
Big finish, Grandpa!
I'm still trying to get them
to play "Danny Boy".
All right, I got a chicken Vesuvio and
a corned beef and cabbage - no butter.
All right, darlin'.
Now... don't eat that.
Oh, my God!
Save it for the Italians.
I know you love me.
Can we afford it?
Angelo says a true artist
must paint in the Pissa Navona.
Piazza Navona!
- You know, I... I could go over with you.
- Sure, yeah.
- Marty, let her go alone.
- Or... you wouldn't have to go at all...
- She'll be fine.
- I'm gonna go.
She's never before been on an aeroplane
and Rome is far away.
- She'll be fine. You paid for the ticket.
- We'll discuss it later on.
- Ange. Two more, hon.
- Sophie, he gave her the ticket!
You couldn't wait till I was here?
She had the same look on her face then
as she has now. Show her.
I miss everything!
Well, the customers out there
are missing you, so...
Can I at least look at it?
Here, look.
Don't touch it!
- Look how much it cost.
- It's so beautiful!
- You deserve it, sweetie.
- She does indeed.
- Oh, well. All right, let's go.
- Thank you.
All right, back to work.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Angelo, thank you!
How did you talk him into it?
My goodness! I'm so proud of him.
He loves you so much,
he's like an Italian mamma!
I can't wait to tell Megan.
She's gonna flip out.
I got another surprise for you.
- He is here.
- Who's he?
The guy I was telling you about.
He's at the bar, waitin' to meet you.
- Oh, Angelo...
- Don't worry. I told him everything.
- I told him you had your chest worked on.
- What?!
- Angelo, he's gonna think I had a...
- What?
Whatever.
It doesn't matter. He's a terrific guy.
In fact, he had a transplant too.
Coraggio - go on.
My doctors -
they say it's a solid transplant.
Look how natural it looks.
Go ahead, give it a tug.
- No, that's OK.
- Oh, come on, give her a tug!
Good evening, sir.
- Are you staying or leaving or what?
- I'm staying.
Thank you very much.
Bob!
My man, Bobby!
This is Marsha.
- Come on!
- I have bacon fat on my hands.
It's OK. I can wash it, shower in it, swim.
Come on, give it a good pull!
- I don't want to hurt you.
- It's OK! I'm fine.
- OK.
- Ow, ow!
- You picked a soft spot.
- Sorry.
Gracie, mind the four-top
over there, will you?
Yeah, I will.
OK, well, it was really nice to meet you.
- Good luck... with your hair.
- Thank you.
Hey, Patrick. Wanna grab on
with two hands and run for the door?
- No, Ralph. I don't touch men.
- It's women's hair.
And then I said, "It's Squeaker, my kitty!"
Everyone was laughing! Ah-ha-ha! Oh!
That's when I met Charlie.
He was the only vet open.
- Funny story.
- Where are the menus? What's going on?
Squeaker won't let
another vet touch him.
Yeah, well, I better not hear about
anybody else touching your squeaker.
I didn't mean to say that.
- I really like this place. It's nice.
- Oh, well, if you like this kind of place.
Everything here is good.
That's the beauty of it.
Oh my gosh, look at us, matchy green.
"Matchy matchy green squared!"
I'll take care of that.
Thank you very much.
Could you hang this up behind you?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
So, Rob, Charlie tells me
you work at the zoo.
Wait a minute - he doesn't work there.
Bob is there building. Bob's a builder.
The new building on State Street? Bob's.
- You own it?
- No. No, I designed it.
Oh.
Good evening.
No, no, no. Do you have bottled water?
Sure. Anyone else?
- May I have a wine list?
- Sure.
Do we know each other?
I think so. Have you been in here before?
- I'd remember an Irish-Italian restaurant.
- Yeah, you would.
Oh, my God - blah, blah, blah. My water?
I don't want Swiss water.
I got sick on that once, remember?
Ach, that was awful. That was so bad.
As long as it's not Swiss or tap water.
Preferably French, no bubbles.
I want it cold - no ice, no glass,
just the bottle and a straw.
Do you want to write it down?
I don't want Swiss water...
I'm pretty sure I got it.
I'm sorry. Can I get a coffee?
- Sure.
- No straw.
- I hate when they don't write it down.
- It will be wrong.
Maybe she'll get it right.
It's not gonna happen.
Nope, not me.
- Not me.
- No.
I think your ass is ringing.
I usually don't bring it.
Rueland.
Mike! Excuse me, I gotta take this.
What do you think?
Patrick, can you gimme an Aquafina?
That's good, Mike. The welder can work
four days for us and one day at the zoo.
Either way they get paid
under the original contract.
Who else is on the clock?
Um... no, no, that sounds good.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Hold on! Can you call me back in three
minutes and whatever I say, disregard it?
Thanks.
So the old man goes,
"How many times I gotta tell you,
I don't want no brown bananas?"
- Wine lists.
- That's a good one.
- I bet that's refreshing.
- Such a difference!
- Yes.
- There you go.
It's about time.
I'm doing a new food combination,
so I don't need something...
- Our specials are chicken Vesuvio...
- Please!
I'm around them all day.
I didn't mean to...
I'm a vet. You know?
And a corned beef and cabbage soufflé
and a spinach ravioli, my favourite.
- I'll have that.
- That sounds so fattening.
- Well, just order something else.
- Is every dish here cooked in oil?
No. Some we boil in Swiss water.
- We're gonna need another minute.
- OK.
- We should get that smartass fired.
- She's fine.
No, that is not fine. That was uncalled-for.
- Get out of the way, Patrick.
- We're getting compliments on the pasta.
Why wouldn't we?
Angelo's the best Italian chef in Chicago.
Angelo! Three more shepherd's pies,
if you please.
Oh, that's me. That's mine.
Rueland. Hey, Mike.
I'm just havin' dinner.
No. No, that's not a problem.
If I have to be there I have to be there.
See you in five minutes.
- Where?
- The Wabash building.
- They're working on a Friday night?
- Can you believe that?
- No.
- It's an emergency. I gotta be there.
- It was nice to meet you, Marla.
- Marsha.
- And Shari?
- Yeah, that's it.
I apologise, and... have fun.
Bye.
- Is everything OK?
- Oh, yeah. Fine. I just got called to work.
Oh, OK. Are your girlfriend
and friends staying?
God, that's not my girlfriend. It's not
even a friend. Not an acquaintance either.
Yes. They will be staying.
Oh. Hang on a second.
- Soph, what is that?
- Ravioli and a side cabbage for pickup.
Here you go, Mr... Atsuki.
It's... on the house.
Come back again.
Thank you.
Ticket, sir? Thank you, sir.
Buona sera, signorina, buona sera
It is time to say good night to Napoli
Though it's hard for me
to whisper buona sera
With that old moon above
and the Mediterranean sea
- What are you doin'?
- I got a call. I gotta go.
- You're already out. It's Friday night.
- I know.
Drink some wine. Enjoy the evening.
I can't. I gotta go to work. I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
- I know you're goin' home.
I'm not goin' home. I gotta go to work.
Yeah, yeah, right(!)
- Grace? Umbrella.
- Oh. Thanks.
Another set of keys. Oh...
I found this phone on the bar earlier.
Nice, huh?
Buona sera, signorina
Kiss me good night
Bob.
According to these plans...
are we only enclosing the one oak tree?
No, I got a newer set of plans in my office.
We'll work Saturdays.
- We are working Saturdays!
- I'll get the new set of plans.
I'll take this home. My kids love
colouring between the lines on these.
- Hey, Bob, could I see the new plans?
- Yeah. Sure. Right here.
- These'll be the last set, right?
- Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Did anybody call back about my phone?
Oh, yeah, the restaurant. They have it.
- Who called?
- The restaurant.
- No, I... who from the restaurant?
- I don't know. Some woman.
- Young or old?
- I don't know!
- I'll send one of the guys to go get it.
- No, I'll swing by there later.
That's cute.
Will you stop with the piano?
I'll go in the fall.
- Here's the baby pig pen.
- OK.
The mommy has ten baby bottles
coming out of her tummy.
That's cute.
Stop with the piano!
Megan!
- What? I'm not playing it.
- But you...
What else did you see at the zoo?
Then we went to see the gorillas
and mommy said it was you.
Oh, I did not! I did not!
- Did she take you to see the elephants?
- Watch it, Joe!
- Did you change him?
- Yeah, I'm gonna.
Get up and change him.
What have you been doing?
- I've been saving lives all day, honey.
- Very funny.
- I'll change him.
- No, Grace, I got it.
- Joe, get up and do it right now.
- I got it, Grace. I'll do it.
- Megan...
- What?!
I invited Rudy over. To meet Grace.
Father Rudy?
He's not a priest any more.
To me he always will be.
Joe, she'll meet someone on her own.
Where? She's here
on every one of her nights off.
- He's a nice guy.
- It doesn't matter!
It's not easy to dance
when no one's leading.
Now help me clean up the puzzle!
- Here's the barn. Barn's gone!
- What's goin' on?
Nothing. Joe invited somebody over -
like a blind date for you.
- What?!
- It's not a date.
He's comin' over for dinner, that's it.
- I gotta find my scarf.
- Better hurry!
- I already told him you've had work done.
- What?!
She's not a Buick.
He understands, he's OK with it.
He's a priest!
- A priest?
- Yup.
An ex-priest. What's the big deal?
He's never dated, you've never dated.
- Grace has dated.
- Who? Chooch Patucci?
- I never dated Chooch!
- That's a date?
You dated Chooch Patucci?!
Don't say that name in this house.
- It's all right, Megan.
- Do you hate priests, Aunt Grace?
- No, honey.
- Cos if you do you'll go straight to hell.
Your mouth!
- That's great, Joe. You taught him "hell".
- I did not. You picked it up from Mom.
- I never said "hell", you son of a bitch.
- Just back off.
Oh, shit! Father Rudy's here.
- Don't say "shit" in front of the priest.
- Shit! Shit!
Would everyone just calm down,
for the love of God and all that is holy?
Calm the hell down!
Stop playing that.
- Shut that thing off.
- No, no... Dad...!
Good night, Nurse!
For Christ's sake, he's just a man!
I'm not used to being without it yet, Joe.
Come on in.
- There she is.
- Oh, boy!
Dinner, I mean.
Hallelujah!
I'll call my friend and see where he's at.
Bobby!
Where you at?
You ran away last night,
you don't show up tonight...
I'm sorry, Charlie,
I'm just not feelin' up to it.
I don't know, maybe somethin' I ate.
I'm just going to... I'm gonna kick back,
take it easy, maybe go to bed early.
- What you doin'?
- Now? Watching the Cubs game.
- What's the score?
- The score? Oh, it's, uh...
Uh...
It's... the Cubs are losin'.
Mr Rueland?
Dan the man!
Bob the slob - just kidding.
Maybe you could clean up the place.
I don't think you could afford me.
How do I look?
Tall.
Tall, yeah.
Thanks.
Oh, Megan, it was fine.
You know... He was a nice guy.
- Well, at least we had a few laughs.
- Yeah, we did.
Did you notice how he was afraid
to even let me lift a plate of potatoes?
No, I think he was just being polite.
Mm-hm.
No, but it's like as soon as they know,
they think of me as broken.
I think they see you as a kind, loving
woman that's beaten unbeatable odds.
- That's the way I see you.
- Urrgghh!
OK, Tyler, come on!
The right guy will know. Trust me.
Can't have Joe helping. The way he
describes your surgery'd scare anyone!
Tonight. They're asleep. We can do it!
What did he say?
He's saying he's sorry about tonight,
so please forgive him.
Left. Step up. Good boy.
Daddy!
- Goddammit!
- Oh, dear.
- Megan!
I'm right here. Take it easy.
- Dad, I want some water.
- You can't have water.
- He can have water.
- He'll wet the bed and who'll change it?
- I do, damn it.
- OK, potty mouth's gonna change it.
Come on, honey, get up there.
You're going to sleep - for ever!
- Stop, it'll be in their heads all night.
- I'll put something in their heads!
- Dad, what are you doing?
- I'm trying to put Mom to bed too.
- Grandpa, you need some help?
- No darlin', not at all.
I'm blessed with work.
- Sweet dreams, Gracie Alana.
- Good night, Grandpa.
Best female singer.
- Dead or alive?
- Either.
- Ella Fitzgerald, easy.
- Now I can agree with that.
I agree.
- I still take Banks over Cobb.
- Don't be ridiculous.
You can't mix your dream team
from different eras.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org