[People chattering]
[Horse neighs]
[Boy yells]
DEFOE: I am a journaIist,
Robert, I assure you.
I have very IittIe interest
in your fIights of fancy.
ROBERT: You, DanieI Defoe,
are a writer.
It is your destiny as such...
to bring this
remarkabIe man's story--
a story of intense struggIe...
extraordinary friendship,
and undying Iove--
to the world.
Well done, well done.
Full of life, death, passion.
You could indeed
give up publishing...
for the stage, sir.
Tell me, though...
what relevance
has this fine story...
to an impoverished
scribe like myself?
Because, Daniel...
you are my favorite
impoverished scribe.
And what is this?
A recently-discovered journal
of one Robinson Crusoe.
Then this tale
you tell me is true?
Every word of it.
A travelogue
of a wayward seaman.
Read this journal, Daniel.
l am confident, sir, you will
find a great interest...
in the story he has to tell.
CRUSOE: And so
my story begins...
Iike so many other stories,
with a woman.
For as Iong as I can
remember...
Mary McGregor and I
had pIanned to marry.
However, as the McGregor famiIy
grew more prosperous...
So, too, did the fortunes
of the Crusoe famiIy dwindIe.
As a resuIt, the woman
whom I greatIy Ioved...
found herseIf betrothed
against her wiII...
To my dear friend
Patrick Connor.
CRUSOE: Though Patrick
knew of our IifeIong bond...
he refused to reIease Mary
from their arrangement.
lt need not end
this way, Patrick.
How, then?
Shall l cease the engagement
and disgrace my family?
[Both grunting]
Patrick!
We were friends once.
Does not that count
for anything?
[Panting]
We were friends, Crusoe.
But we are friends no longer.
Then we shall fight.
[Grunting]
[Horse neighs]
[Panting]
She is to be my wife, Robin.
lt is God's will.
You know Mary and l loved
each other since childhood.
MAN: Patrick!
PATRICK: This is not
your fight, James.
CRUSOE: You're not
Iike your brothers, Patrick.
Don't be like your brothers.
[Gasping]
[Horse neighs]
PATRICK: You wiII
never be together!
[Grunting]
JAMES: Patrick!
[Gasps and grunts]
No! No, no.
Dear God, forgive me.
[Groaning]
[Gasps]
[Panting]
MAN: He's dead, sir.
Murderer.
Take to your horse, sir.
l'll not leave.
Go, sir, now!
Murderer!
Uhh.
[Horse neighs]
[Panting]
MARY: Of course he knew
I did not Iove him.
l told him as much.
Yet he chose to fight.
You both chose to fight, Robin.
What are you saying, Mary?
Do you believe l would
willfully kill my friend?
l walked away.
You accepted his challenge.
Would a wiser man have known
better than to fight, huh?
His brothers
will seek vengeance.
Ah, they have already.
He was my friend, Mary.
l would never have wished...
such a terrible fate
on Patrick.
MARY: You must Ieave now.
It is not safe
for you anymore.
CRUSOE: WiII it ever
be safe for me, Mary?
MARY: Time wiII heaI
this wound, Robin.
I wiII expIain to
Patrick's famiIy.
They wiII come
to understand.
Go with the coachman.
You can trust him.
He wiII take you
to Edinburgh...
and arrange
for your safe passage.
Come back wiser
for the experience.
ln a year...l'll return.
Then we shall be wed.
lf it is 13 months, Robin...
then shall l marry another?
l love you.
l will always see
your face before me.
CRUSOE: A year.
No longer.
[Coachman speaks indistinctly]
[Neighs]
[Chattering]
[Sailor yells]
CRUSOE: And so I took
to the seas--
the one pIace where
I knew I wouId be safe.
[Sailor yells]
For many months we saiIed
the great oceans of the worId.
We docked at mysterious
scented isIands...
under the Southern Cross.
We swam with mermaids...
and we carried
fabuIous cargoes...
of siIks and spices,
jade and mahogany.
And once, even...
we carried
a human cargo of sIaves.
Providence had decreed me
a man without a country...
yet I was not
without a purpose.
Though I had formerIy
served in His Majesty's army...
it was my academic
background...
and my intimate knowIedge
of history...
that Ied the captain
of our ship to caII on me...
to chronicIe our journey
through the written word.
[Knock on door]
Enter.
Captain's compliments,
Mr. Crusoe.
Thank you. Shut the door.
CRUSOE: Though Patrick's death
brought about my exiIe...
it was the thought of Mary,
of the knowIedge...
that I wouId have her hand
in marriage upon my return...
that kept my spirit strong
as our voyage continued.
[Sailors chattering]
SAILOR: Aye-aye, sir.
CRUSOE: Our IittIe ship
had met and bested...
fouI weather and high seas
on 3 oceans.
Sometimes the storms
wouId Iast a week or more...
but I grew
ever more confident...
in the skiIIs
of our captain and his crew.
[Shouts overlapping]
CAPTAIN: Are ya
seeing the coast, yes?
SAILOR: Up ahead.
Put your back into it, sir.
[Grunts]
[Thunder]
SAILOR: CaIIing away,
caIIing away.
SECOND SAILOR:
Aft foIIow.
Batten down the hatches!
SAILOR: Aye-aye, sir.
[Crew yelling]
Get over here!
[Captain yells]
Ohh!
Oh, God!
[Yells]
[Yelling indistinctly]
Ohh!
[Grunts]
Oh, God.
[Glass shatters]
[Captain yells orders]
CAPTAIN: Get out!
Bring it around!
Aah! Aah!
Give me your hand!
Don't be fooIish, sir!
Give it to me now!
Give me your hand!
[Both grunting]
[Yelling]
SAILOR: Mikey, heIp me!
[Shouting and yelling]
Aah!
[Sailors screaming]
[Grunts]
Ow!
[Coughs]
Uhh.
Aah.
[Grunting and gasping]
CRUSOE: As I took
my first steps...
in that unknown Iand...
a dread came over me.
I began to reaIize in truth
how terribIe was my condition.
Hello!
[Grunts]
No!
CRUSOE: As I Iaid
my poor companions to rest...
I confess my thoughts
were for my own souI.
I did not know in what Iand
I had been cast...
in what country,
among what nation...
nor whether I might endure
a singIe night here...
Iet aIone a week...
or a month.
I spent that first night
not daring to imagine...
what dangers might prowI
or crawI beneath me...
and sIeepIess for thinking...
how I might survive
the next day...
without food or weapons
or human company.
But as the sun rose,
so did my spirits...
for then I saw
that the huIk of our vesseI...
had caught fast on the reef
where she had foundered.
On-board I might find food
and drink for my sustenance.
[Grunts]
And this gave me fresh hope.
Unhh.
[Dog whining]
Hello?
ls anyone there?
[Whining continues]
[Arf]
[Clank]
CRUSOE: I found that our ship
Iay so on the reef...
that onIy haIf of her
was fiIIed with water.
The forward parts were dry...
and there I found
powder and weapons...
and provisions.
I discovered
the carpenter's chest.
Being a gentIeman,
I had IittIe experience...
with the tooIs of the trade.
NevertheIess,
there and then I resoIved...
that I wouId Iearn.
[Whimpers]
CRUSOE: The ship's Ione boat...
had been dashed
to pieces by the storm...
but I found a part
of an upper deck torn away.
I used this
as a makeshift raft.
Thanks to an incoming tide
and a gentIe breeze...
my modest craft took me
straightaway to shore.
I began to feeI
not a IittIe proud...
of my achievement...so far.
And so I reckoned
my fortunes were on the up.
I had provisions
for a month or more...
tooIs and good timber,
even good company...
in the captain's oId dog
Skipper.
[Arf]
CRUSOE: There you go, Skipper.
That's it. No more.
From now on
you find your own food.
CRUSOE: I was now
making daiIy excursions...
away from the shoreIine.
Penetrating further
and further...
into the interior
of my domain.
I knew onIy that we'd
been saiIing some miIes...
from the coast of Guinea...
and I had in mind
the possibiIity...
that my soiI was somehow
connected to a mainIand...
where I may happen upon
some human civiIization.
[Panting]
l'm on an island.
CRUSOE: In order
to keep watch daiIy...
for the first ship
that wouId pass at sea...
I resoIved to situate myseIf...
as near the coast as possibIe.
The weeks turned to months...
and stiII no sighting
of a ship.
But I truIy beIieved
it must come to pass.
Some vesseI wouId saiI
by my shore...
sooner rather than Iater.
[Skipper barks]
[Arf]
[Woof woof]
[Woof]
Skipper!
Quiet.
Quiet, Skipper.
[Skipper barks]
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Ah.
CRUSOE: HeIIo! Come back!
Come back!
CRUSOE: I'm here!
l'm here! Come back!
Fire! Fire!
Fire! Come back!
Please! Please!
Please come back!
[Yells and gasps]
Come back! I'm here!
[Skipper barking]
[Barking]
Ah, ha.
[Laughing]
CRUSOE: It was
on that day I came to see...
I must no Ionger
reIy upon chance...
or fate or divine
intervention...
for my survivaI...
but soIeIy on my own efforts...
as a man.
CRUSOE: And I found,
as time went by...
I began to grow even fond
of my isIand kingdom.
[Chattering]
[Twitters]
[Chirps]
I have not been idIe
with my time on the isIand.
Even so, my thoughts
continuaIIy turn...
to the Iife I Ieft behind.
Skipper! Come here.
What you're about to hear...
is the sweetest sound
in the whole world.
Hmm? The spirit of Scotland.
[Panting]
[lnhales and plays]
[Skipper barks]
[Barking]
[Continues playing]
[Bagpipes blurt]
[Pants]
[Moans]
MARY: Come on, then.
[Mary laughs]
CRUSOE: My thoughts
of Mary inspired me...
for I knew that someday
I wouId return.
[Grunts]
I erected a monument
to mark my Ianding here.
Upon it I've been
scrupuIousIy recording...
the days of the week
and the months...
as they've passed since
my arrivaI on the isIand.
[Gasps]
One year, Skipper.
A whole year.
[Surf lapping]
[Bird crying]
Ho.
Ha.
[Grunts]
[Crusoe panting]
CRUSOE: How many wiId fantasies
tormented my mind...
as I made for the security
of my own castIe...
fancying every bush
and tree stump to be a man...
affIicted with such terror
that I couId imagine...
Satan himseIf
had taken human shape...
and Ieft his print
upon my shore.
[Wild yelling and ululating]
[Crusoe grunting]
From somewhere on my isIand
came sounds I beIieved...
I wouId never hear again.
Human voices, to be sure...
but voices unIike
I had ever heard before.
[Barking]
Stay! Stay here!
[Yelling and ululating]
[Yelling and ululating
continue]
[Man shouts
in native language]
[Yells in native language]
[Shouting and chanting
in native language]
[Hooting]
[Tribe yelling and shouting]
[Shouting in native language]
[Yelling and shouting continue]
[Victim screams]
Aah!
[Yelling and ululating]
[Crusoe loads weapons]
[Clicks]
[Moans]
[Panting]
Don't be afraid.
I'm your friend.
l'm a friend.
Ha.
CRUSOE: Ha.
[Panting]
[Yells]
Unhh!
Give it to me.
Come on.
[Rattles]
[Mutters]
Back!
[Bird squawking]
What do you think you're doing?!
l saved your life back there!
l want to be your friend.
How can l make you understand?
Friend.
[Deliberately]
l am your friend.
Food.
Right.
Food. Huh?
Food. Food!
[Grunts]
CRUSOE: Here you go.
A gift. Peace.
[Speaks native language]
[Man speaks native language]
Ah, you want the gun.
Oh, no. lt's very powerful.
And if you try to take this...
l will use this power
to kill you...
and l don't want to kill you!
You're my friend.
Food.
[Man shouts in native language]
Hey!
[Yelling]
[Man speaks native language]
No!
Blasphemy.
CRUSOE: How couId
I ever have imagined...
being a friend to this savage?
I saw now he was
from another worId--
one sureIy ruIed by Satan.
I, Robinson Crusoe...
wouId guide and protect
my kingdom...
against aII eviI.
Skipper! Skipper!
Prepare yourself.
lt seems we have
a very unfriendly heathen...
on the island with us.
[Skipper barks]
CRUSOE: LittIe did
this pagan know...
but his adversary was once
trained as a soIdier...
so he wouId be facing
one skiIIed in strategy...
in the miIitary arts.
[Ring]
CRUSOE: It is hard to describe
my confIict of emotions.
In aII these 2 years...
I'd Ionged for the company
of another human being...
and now we were enemies.
Hunter and prey.
And he was out there--
somewhere on my isIand.
Aah! Unh!
[Arf]
[Grunts]
Sha.
[Grunting]
Ahh.
Stay away from me,
you black heathen bastard!
Aah! Aish!
CRUSOE: Leave it aIone.
Leave the bIoody thing aIone.
You hear me?
That's right.
Blow your bloody brains out.
Go on.
Come here.
Give me that thing.
Give me that--
That's it.
Give me the gun.
Give me the bloody gun!
[Crusoe breathing heavily]
Aye.
Come here, come here.
l'll give you this.
Look. Look.
Aye.
Ha ha ha ha!
[Speaking native language]
Up.
All right, easy.
Do you understand danger?
Death?
Who are you?
Huh?
What are you?
Look.
Look!
[Fires]
[Screeching]
Aye.
[Screeches]
CRUSOE: That he was a savage
was indisputabIe...
and yet he seemed to be
a decent feIIow at heart.
In time, I might even turn him
from his pagan ways.
Perhaps this was my mission.
What's your name?
What about Hamish?
l had a brother called Hamish.
[Rooster crows]
What day is it?
Thursday?
No, it's not.
lt's Friday.
[Squawks]
Friday.
Master.
[Laughs]
Aye.
Friday.
You sleep here.
You sleep...
here.
[Sighs]
It's just untiI the morning.
Food.
[Bird squawks]
[Skipper barks]
Stay there.
F-food.
[Sets down]
Master.
Stay.
Stay. Stay.
Come here.
[Chains rattle]
[Sets down gun]
CRUSOE: I had wronged
this poor honest savage...
and I was truIy sorry for it.
It became cIear to me...
that I couId not have found
a better creature...
to be subject
to my benevoIent ruIe.
At Ieast...
that was how I saw it then.
[Barks]
[Rooster crows]
CRUSOE: Friday became
constant and diIigent...
in his work...
and proved to know
a great deaI...
about pIanting
and harvesting our crops.
Indeed, to my surprise,
he began to instruct me.
In turn, I made it
my mission...
to teach Friday
the King's EngIish.
And after 6 months...
I was astonished that
he Iearned the Ianguage...
with such great proficiency.
Yet other aspects
of Friday's education...
proved more arduous.
Friday, l have to talk
to you about God.
God?
Your Maker.
Your Creator.
God.
He made everything.
He made you.
Pokya.
Pokya?
Pokya God.
Look at that. Huh.
Before long time,
no land--only water.
That's in ''Genesis.''
Pokya live in the water.
He make Timpopo.
He make Tompopo.
He make the sun
and the moon. Right.
Mm-hmm.
Sun and moon marry.
They make baby--man.
Make all men.
Make me.
No. God made you.
Pokya.
You can't worship a crocodile.
Why not?
Teeth of crocodile.
CRUSOE: Does this crocodiIe...
this Pokya...
tell you to eat
the flesh of your enemies?
Make strong.
You eat fish, swim good.
You eat Iizard, cIimb good.
You eat heart, make strong!
This is pagan blasphemy,
Friday!
The true God is greater
and more powerful.
The true God is love.
He teaches us
to love our enemies.
Pokya...
is not God.
Show me God.
l cannot show you God.
l show you Pokya.
You show God.
You cannot see God.
He's in the spirit.
He's in the souI.
l see spirit in the trees.
l see spirit
in fish and animals.
l see everywhere.
Here.
Here is God.
Here is the living
proof of God.
His sacred word.
This is the living testament
to His love, His wisdom...
His divine plan--here.
Where? l see no God.
No, you--you have to read it.
Now look what you've done,
you heathen savage.
This blasphemy and your soul...
shall be damned
to eternal torments.
l no like your God.
l no like you.
Forgive all those
who trespass against us--
against You, Lord.
Against You.
CRUSOE: I knew I shouId come
to regret my harsh words.
Whether Friday was
the better for our meeting...
I do not know,
but I had good cause...
to think Providence
was sending him to serve me.
And so, I'm aIone again.
I manage weII enough
without him.
I eat weII enough,
I Iive toIerabIy weII...
but I find I begin
to miss him as a companion.
It's been severaI weeks now.
Our paths cross
from time to time...
but we do not speak,
do not communicate.
In my studies of history...
I had chronicIed
the reIigious wars...
that have pIagued mankind
since the beginning of time...
and how sad, I thought...
that in this universe of two...
reIigion had now put us
at our own war.
Yet something had to be done.
Friday!
[Spits]
We can't carry on like this.
lt's silly--
the two of us on
the same bloody island...
not talking to each other...
not sharing what we have.
l'm sorry for
all the things l said...
everything I did.
l was angry.
l apologize.
l want you to come back.
Good fish.
Eat.
CRUSOE: There she goes.
That's it. Come on, come on.
That's it. Come on.
CRUSOE: So now we were three...
and I heard once again
the sound of human Iaughter--
his and mine.
Come on.
FRIDAY: Ha ha!
CRUSOE: That's it.
[Both chattering]
There you go.
FRIDAY: Go sideways.
Sideways.
Go in the water yourself.
They'll go with you.
Let's get the big one.
Yours is bigger.
FRIDAY: Winner.
CRUSOE: I had not
forgotten who it was...
that had brought Friday
to my isIand...
nor the IikeIihood
of their return.
The Nemurs, it seemed,
were the dominant tribe...
on Friday's isIand...
and Friday had been offered
by his own peopIe...
as a tribute
to these savages.
Powder--
gunpowder.
This is it.
Power.
This is what the Nemurs
come for?
CRUSOE: This must be powerfuI.
FRIDAY: Oh, make great
warriors.
Then we'll come back.
CRUSOE: And so I determined
to be ready for them.
Like hunters
setting traps for animaIs...
we prepared our weIcome.
I expIained to Friday...
that this particuIar
white man's magic...
wouId ensure
that our enemies...
go to meet their god Pokya...
rather sooner
than they anticipated.
[Horn blows]
[People yelling in distance]
[Yelling louder]
[Crowd yelling]
[Drums playing]
[Barking]
Skipper!
[Yelling stops]
O dear Lord...
l thank you
for the time l shared...
with this
faithful creature.
He was my friend.
Skipper goes
to Crusoe's heaven?
Dogs don't have souls, Friday.
Only people have mortal souls.
Only people go to heaven.
Too bad.
Good dog.
[Softly]
Aye.
Friday ask Pokya...
to look after dog's spirit.
Pokya!
Pokya-ay!
[Speaking native language]
CRUSOE: The Iessons
of humiIity...
do not come easiIy
to a stubborn souI.
FRIDAY: Pokya!
CRUSOE: Once I had thought
mine was the onIy true path.
FRIDAY: Pokya!
CRUSOE: Now I was
no Ionger sure.
FRIDAY: Pokya-ay!
[Squawks]
The Nemurs will come back.
With new moon...
many, many warriors will come.
Want your magic.
Mmm. Well, we can't
fight them all.
We could build a boat.
Go away.
Go to your island.
No.
We cannot go to my island.
Why not?
Cannot go.
Can never go.
l am a dead man.
This island of dead people.
Aye. Well, we will be
if we stay here.
We build boat.
You go to your island.
Mmm. lf only l could.
My island's on the other
side of the world...
many, many moons away.
What name your island?
Britain--
Great Britain.
Brittany.
Yes. New Brittany.
You know Britain?
Not so long--
one moon, maybe.
You mean New Britain?
New Brittany.
Right name, Oamockapeet.
White men call it New Brittany.
Have you seen white men
before me?
My father told me
about white men long ago.
Not good.
White man,
he take much everything...
not give back.
Take land, take people--
Tonga people.
Make people slaves.
You're not white man, Master.
You're a good man.
But if your island
is close to New Britain...
we could build a boat,
and we could go there.
l cannot.
Do not ask me, Master.
My name is not Master!
My name is Robinson Crusoe.
Rob--
Robina Crus--
Crusoe, aye.
What name is Master?
White man.
l am slave to you?
No.
lt was a mistake.
l'm not your slave!
No.
No, you're not my slave.
We are friends, and
we can live as friends...
but we can build a boat.
We can build a boat
and leave this place!
You're going to build it!
[Choking]
[Catches breath]
You gave life.
l cannot kill you...
but l will kill myself!
Then stay on this island
and die...
but l will build a boat...
and l will live!
CRUSOE: So, my stupid
arrogance...
had Iost me my dear companion
for a second time...
and I was aIone again.
If what Friday said was true...
I was Iess than one month's
traveI from New Britain...
one of His Majesty's
coIonies...
off the coast of New Guinea.
But my time was short.
I had to Ieave before
the next fuII moon...
and the typhoon season
wouId soon be here.
[Wind blowing]
[Hammers]
[Thunder]
I knew I wouId have
to Ieave soon...
or miss my chance...
if I had not aIready done so.
[Thunder]
How I regretted
my thoughtIess words.
The chances were...
that I wouId
never see my friend again.
[Thunder]
l am not slave!
l know, Friday!
You're my friend!
[Thunder]
l tell you my spirit name.
Only spirit, me,
and Tonga big men know.
[Speaking native language]
Why are you telling me this?
Crusoe gave life.
Not say more.
[Thunder]
[Speaking native language]
Give power of bird.
Fly safe to landing.
[Thunder]
[Laughs]
[Speaking native language]
Quickly!
[Thunder]
[Goat bleats]
CRUSOE: Fearing that
this might be a tempest...
as vioIent as that which
cast me on the isIand...
we brought our Iivestock...
to what sheIter
we couId devise.
We waited together
to brave the storm...
which, indeed,
proved more fearsome...
than any before.
[Thunder]
[Snaps]
[Animals bleating]
[lnsects buzzing]
No time to build new boat.
Moon nearly big.
Nemurs come--
many, many warriors.
Yeah, well, there's
no place to hide.
We'll have to fight them.
We may die.
Dying not important.
All men die.
What matters is how you die.
Then we'll die like warriors.
[Click]
CRUSOE: At the time
of the Iast fuII moon...
I knew that severaI
of the Nemur warriors...
had escaped our trap...
so this time...
the enemy wouId know
we were there.
Our onIy aIIy
wouId be our ingenuity...
and what gunpowder
remained to us.
[Men shouting
in native language]
[Friday speaking
native language]
[Whispering]
Our Father, who art in heaven...
hallowed be Thy name.
[Friday speaking
native language]
Give us this day
our daily bread.
Forgive us our trespasses...
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
And Iead us not
into temptation...
but deIiver us from eviI--
for thine is the kingdom,
the power, and the glory...
forever and ever.
Amen.
[Whispers]
[Speaking native language]
[Drums playing in distance]
[Men chattering,
bagpipe playing]
[Playing]
[Chattering in native language]
[Bagpipe music stops]
[Men chattering
in native language]
[Man speaking native language]
Ahh!
[Gags]
Ohh!
[Speaking native language]
[Men speaking native language]
MEN: Aah!
[Speaking native language]
[Men speaking native language]
MEN: Aah!
Uhh!
Aah!
[Man hits ground]
CRUSOE: Uhh.
Ohh! Unh!
Uhh!
Uhh. Uhh.
CRUSOE: I do not know
how Iong I had Iain there...
whiIe Friday ministered to me.
I feIt IittIe pain...
but a coIdness
spread through every Iimb.
No, no, no, no.
[Shivers]
Uhh.
l don't want to die here.
[Shivering]
Will you stay with me until...
please, huh?
Then go back to your own people.
Cannot go--can never go.
You must.
Friday is a dead man.
l cannot go back from here.
l am dead to my people.
l am tanwuan.
This island of dead men.
No one ever leave.
l don't want to die here.
CRUSOE: Because he was
offered up for sacrifice...
Friday was considered dead
to his own peopIe--
In many ways,
a fate worse than death...
as he couId never again
be accepted...
amongst his own tribe.
IronicaIIy, this dead man...
was my onIy chance for Iife.
[Labored breathing]
CRUSOE: Friday.
Friday.
CRUSOE: Mary.
Huh?
MARY: Robin.
Robin.
Ha ha!
Mary.
Mary. Mary.
Mary, Mary, Mary.
No, no.
No, no, no.
You live.
No.
Friday take care of you.
[Mutters]
Unh!
Aah!
Friday...
take you home.
Aye, home.
CRUSOE: Having neither
the provisions...
Nor, in my case,
the strength...
to aim our saiIs
for New Britain...
Friday and I set out
for his nearby isIand.
WhiIe Friday beIieved...
his peopIe couId cure me
of my iIIs...
his own fate
was far Iess certain.
I couId not count the days
we were on the sea.
With God's grace...
we encountered
onIy fair winds.
And with Friday as our guide...
we saiIed safeIy
to his isIand home.
[People chattering
in native language]
[Crowd yelling]
Friday!
FRIDAY: You'II be better.
She has magic leaves.
Ohh.
Thank you.
Your wife?
Netwuana.
FRIDAY: Was my wife.
They think l dead
when Nemurs take me.
FRIDAY: Not come back.
She marry a new man.
[Speaking native language]
Ptt.
[Woman speaking native language]
Nabo.
Am l an evil spirit?
They think you are
a slave trader.
Ohh.
FRIDAY: Many times,
white men come...
and take many warriors--
many young men for sIave.
Take my son.
Oh, Friday.
They think l bring you here...
to make them slaves.
Ohh.
[Labored breathing]
lf l'm an evil spirit...
why does she help me?
You sick man.
Not good to kill sick man.
Bad mana.
[Necklace rattles]
[Men chanting
in native language]
He prays to the gods.
CRUSOE: Aye.
What are they saying?
We fight.
One of us die.
lf l kill you...
l can stay.
lf you kill me, you can go.
l cannot kill you.
CRUSOE: l will not kill you.
-FRlDAY: l am a dead man.
-CRUSOE: Ohh!
No wife, no man-child.
lt's better to die like warrior.
[Men chanting
in native language]
[Spits]
[Yelling in native language]
l will not fight you.
You must...
or they kill both of us.
[Men chanting
in native language]
Yaah!
Uhh!
[Chanting]
l cannot do this!
Ohh!
[Chanting]
AImighty God...
welcome me to paradise,
if l am worthy.
Kill me and live.
l cannot kill friend.
Do it!
Do it.
[Chanting]
Aah!
[Crowd stops yelling]
[Yelling]
Come on.
Go ahead.
This way.
Come on.
Ohh! Ohh! Ow!
MAN: Come away, me hearty.
These savages
can't harm you now.
No!
[Sobs]
[Crusoe sobs]
CRUSOE: And so,
fate had saved...
her harshest trick tiII Iast.
Just as a dueI had caused me
to fIee my native Iand...
so, too, did a battIe
between friends...
bring about my return.
I was to owe my freedom...
to the men
who had kiIIed my friend...
who had ravished
his peopIe and his famiIy.
MAN: Come on,
come on, mate.
CRUSOE: The sIavers
nursed me back to heaIth...
and then put me ashore
at Lisbon.
There, I was taken aboard
a merchantman.
6 years after my departure
from ScotIand...
I came home.
lt was he who gave you
the journal.
Yes.
Robert, l--l must write this.
[Taps desk]
You miss him, don't you?
He saved my life.
He brought you back to me.
A wiser man?
Mmm.
Perhaps.
[Both laugh]
Ohh.
CRUSOE: And so, Mary and I
settIed down to marriage...
and a famiIy of our own.
We were bIessed with
happiness and prosperity...
but...
for the rest of my days...
I wouId think often and Iong...
of the man who'd given me
the greatest gift of aII--
my Iife...
when I'd aII but Iost it...
and his friendship--
unto death.