Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
[Shutter Clicks]
- [Shutter Clicks]
- ?? [Men Singing]
?? [Singing Continues]
[Singing]
[Singing Continues]
[Man Speaking Arabic]
[Arabic]
Armed American marines,
they were shooting at his people.
They were just trying
to defend themself.
Is he saying
the marines shot first?
[Arabic]
Why were your police officers
ordered to abandon the embassy...
on the day of the riot?
[Man Speaking Arabic]
[Arabic]
It was a peaceful demonstration.
There was no reason to stay.
After the killing, were
any weapons found in the crowd?
[Arabic]
No. They picked up everything
that was left. No weapons.
[Man Outside
Shouting In Arabic]
[Arabic]
Hey!
No, look. Now, wait.
Wait a minute.
- [Shouting In Arabic]
- Wait a minute, fellas.
[Shouting In Arabic]
Hey. Hey!
[Panting]
[People Chanting
In Arabic]
[Chanting]
[Girl Speaking Arabic]
[Arabic]
[Chatter Continues]
Hi. Whats your name?
Do you speak English?
- You're a very pretty girl.
- [Gasps]
"Katchi"!
Is that your name? "Katchi"?
- May I help you?
- Yeah.
I was wondering
what happened to her?
She lost her leg.
Who are you?
I'm a lawyer with the United States
Marine Corps. What happened?
- A marine lawyer?
- Yeah.
Follow me, please.
[Flies Buzzing]
[Baby Crying,
Flies Buzzing]
There are hospitals like this
all over the city.
[Babies Crying]
Most of the people here
will die.
[Child Speaking
In Arabic]
[Crying Continues]
[Gunshot]
Sir? Do you want
something to drink?
Give me another one!
Open the goddamn door!
Whats wrong with you?
Get yourself a new lawyer,
you son of a bitch. You lied to me.
I could not find
one goddamn witness.
I couldn't find
one goddamn shred of evidence!
Not for our side
anyway!
You clearly opened up
on those people. What were they?
Rag heads, camel jockeys
or fucking gooks?
- You through?
- Yeah.
Get up.
- [Panting]
- Come on. Get up. Come on.
Look at you.
You went all the way to Yemen.
All you proved is
you're still a drunk.
You know what your problem is? You
never measured up to your old man.
- But I can't help you with that.
- [Grunts]
[Yells]
- [Yells]
- [Groans]
[Coughs]
[Groaning]
[Yells]
Stop this shit
before somebody gets hurt.
[Grunts]
[Coughing, Laughing]
[Coughing]
I lost every one
of my men at Ca Lu.
And I'll tell you
the first thing I felt.
Joy.
Elation.
Glad to be alive.
I was glad it wasn't me, and
I fucking hate myself for that.
That wasn't your fault.
We're in deep shit, bud.
Yeah.
Its fourth and 40, Hodge.
I need a Hail Mary.
[Sighs]
How?
[Sighing]
[Intercom Beeps]
Send him in.
[Door Opens]
[Door Closes]
I just want to make sure
we're on the same page here.
- Off the record.
- Of course, Bill.
Now, you didn't see any weapons
in that crowd, did you?
Well...
[Chuckles]
There was some shooting,
but I...
couldn't be sure exactly
where it was coming from.
Now, see, thats
gonna be a problem,
because we can't get on the stand
and waffle about the charges.
Waffle, Bill?
In your mind, Childers
was responsible, wasn't he?
I wasn't exactly there.
I had already evacuated.
You have to remember
he saved my life and my family.
This all happened after...
Does that mean the United States...
is gonna have to take the fall
for what he did?
I don't understand.
The investigating team didn't
find any weapons in the crowd.
Thats because they weren't
there until the following day.
The Yemeni government
cleaned up the scene,
but unfortunately thats
not something we can prove.
Nor can I testify about it.
It all happened afterward.
Yeah, but you can testify
about Childers' frame of mind,
his behavior
while you were there.
He saved my life.
Surely this will all come down
to what the tape shows.
The tape's inconclusive.
Hodges subpoenaed it,
of course, but, uh...
it was a faulty recording.
- I see.
- Do you?
If Childers isn't held
totally responsible,
then the United States
will be.
And just guess...
where the finger...
is eventually gonna point.
- Me?
- Where else?
You shoulïve known
this was gonna erupt.
And if you didn't,
you were asleep at the wheel.
Either way, your conduct
was inexcusable.
Now, do you want to face a
congressional inquiry over this,
put your career at risk?
Think about it.
Thank you, Bill.
[Door Opens, Closes]
[Retching]
[Panting]
[Toilet Flushes]
[Groans]
[People Chattering]
[Bailiff]
All rise.
Be seated.
Look closely
at this picture.
Why did a well-trained
fighting unit...
have to slaughter unarmed
men, women and children...
when their orders
were simply to protect...
and if necessary,
evacuate the embassy?
The answer is,
they didn't.
They were ordered to open fire,
and that order came from one man...
Colonel Terry Childers,
who stands trial
here today,
a day of sadness,
a day when America has
to accept responsibility...
for its failures and its
mistakes as well as its glories.
We will show you that the accused,
through his mind-set and actions,
ignored the rules
of engagement...
and went far beyond
the scope of his authority...
to intentionally order
the murder...
of 83 innocent people.
[Amplified Thumping]
[Clears Throat]
I was the last one to enter the
courtroom this morning. I was late.
I was late because
I was in the head.
And I was in the head
because... I was throwing up.
And I was throwing up
because I don't know if I'm...
able to handle this job.
[Chuckles]
I believe that Colonel Childers
is innocent of these charges.
I just don't know if I have what
it takes to make his case for him.
I'm simply not on the same page
as Major Briggs, uh...
Major Biggs here,
as a lawyer.
We all know that.
So why did I take
this job?
I took this case because
Terry Childers told me...
I would have done the same thing
he did if I'd been in his shoes.
I took the case because I know Terry
Childers. His word is his bond.
He told me he did
what he had to do.
Now, I hope
I don't let him down.
We sent Terry Childers out
on a very tough mission.
And when it went bad,
and he did everything he could
to save the lives of his marines,
save the lives
of the embassy people,
you turn around now and want
to blame the whole mess on him,
send him to prison possibly
for the rest of his life.
Thats not fair.
Its not right.
It is what made me sick
this morning.
It was a large crowd.
There was a lot of commotion.
The noise was very unsettling.
But it was
a peaceful crowd.
That is, until Colonel Childers
arrived and prevented me...
from pursuing
further avenues of diplomacy.
[Biggs] Did Colonel Childers
force you to leave the embassy?
Yes. He charged in.
He... started
pushing us around.
He physically restrained me
from doing my job.
[Biggs] What was his state
of mind at this time?
He was in a fury.
He was disrespectful
to me and my family.
Oh, thats bullshit.
It was almost, how should I say,
a murderous rage.
[Biggs]
Do you remember what he said?
I remember he said
something like...
"diplomacy is bullshit
at this point"...
and that "nobody fucks
with the American flag. "
- Those were his words.
- [Biggs] Thank you, Ambassador.
No further questions.
Do you believe...
that an American embassy
on foreign soil...
is sovereign
United States territory?
As a general principle, yes.
Do you believe Americans
have a right...
to defend that territory
if its attacked?
If it is, in fact,
attacked.
Would you have expected
Colonel Childers to surrender...
to the attacking crowd
or to fight them?
I would have expected neither.
The colonel should have let me
address the crowd,
then he could have withdrawn
his marines.
Would you have expected him
to hold his fire as he withdrew,
- even if he were taking casualties?
- To the extent possible.
So your order would have been,
"Hold your fire to the extent
possible, Marines.
And to the extent not possible,
fire away."
[Hodges]
Ambassador.
This photograph
is exhibit "C."
- What is that?
- Its a security camera.
Is it mounted
on the roof of the embassy...
and pointed down to where
the crowd had gathered?
- I would suppose so.
- Yes or no, please.
Yes.
- Is it in operation 24 hours a day?
- I suppose so.
- Yes or no?
- Yes.
Do you suppose there is a taping
system attached to this camera?
- [Biggs] Your Honor.
- [Judge] Colonel.
- Yes.
- Where's the tape?
It is my understanding
that if there were tapes,
undamaged tapes, they'd have been
sent to the State Department.
Undamaged tapes?
Well, there was
destruction and looting...
after the killing.
As you withdrew, did you remember
to take the American flag with you?
Did you remember to take
the American flag, sir?
- Of course.
- Where is that flag now?
I brought it home and returned
it to the State Department.
It was shot to shreds,
wasn't it?
By the snipers, yes.
[Hodges]
Yeah?
[Children Shouting,
Chattering]
Right! Go right!
Goal!
At ease, son.
Let me see. Which one
of you people is named Justin?
- Let me take a guess. How about you?
- No.
Then I'll have to make
another guess. I'll take, uh... you.
How'd you know?
Are you in the marines?
Yes, sir, I am.
Go on in the house, kids.
There are sandwiches in the kitchen.
Mrs. Mourain, I'm sorry
to bother you at home.
- I'm Colonel...
- I know who you are, Colonel Hodges.
- Is that your boy?
- Yes.
Can I talk to you
a few minutes?
I don't think
thats appropriate.
I don't believe your husband
is telling the truth...
about what Colonel Childers did
in Yemen.
Kids, go on in the house.
There are sandwiches on the table.
- Lets go! Come on!
- [Children Laughing]
[Chuckling]
You should take that up
with my husband, shouldn't you?
Colonel Childers risked his life
so you could be here, ma'am,
watching these kids play
out these windows.
Does that bother you?
I feel terrible about what
happened to Colonel Childers.
Can you tell me that he
manhandled your family?
Or that he prevented
your husband from doing his job?
Ma'am?
Can you tell me that?
No.
As far as I'm concerned,
he behaved quite honorably.
Will you testify to that?
- My husbanïs a good man.
- So is Colonel Childers.
I've been married for ten years.
You're asking me to throw that
away in an afternoon.
Your husband and you
and your son...
owe your lives
to Colonel Terry Childers.
We all have our priorities,
Colonel.
I can subpoena you, ma'am.
Please don't.
Don't put me up there.
I'm a very credible witness.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
You won't tell the truth
if I put you on the stand?
I don't know
what the truth is.
Colonel Childers is on trial for
what he did outside the embassy.
I wasn't there.
Were you?
[Door Opens]
- [Exhales]
- [Door Slams]
Captain Lee, you were in command
of the TRAP team...
and the second ranking officer
under Colonel Childers in Yemen?
- Yes, sir.
- And you were on the roof...
- of the embassy, were you not?
- Yes, I was.
Colonel Childers ordered you
to open fire...
immediately after Sergeant
Richard Krasevitch was shot.
- Is that correct?
- Yes.
But Sergeant Krasevitch was not
shot by the demonstrators, was he?
Objection. How could we know
the exact firing position...
of the bullet that killed
Sergeant Krasevitch?
[Judge] Sustained. Counsel
refrain from leading the witness.
[Biggs]
Did you at any time...
receive gunfire from within
the demonstration itself?
Captain?
I can't remember any fire
from the demonstrators,
to my knowledge that is, sir.
You killed the wrong people,
didn't you?
You shoulïve been firing
at the snipers across the way.
- Isn't that correct?
- I can't answer...
- Objection. Calls for speculation.
- Sustained.
You shot at people who
were demonstrating peacefully,
who were not using
deadly force.
Your Honor, thats not
in evidence here.
Sustained. Major, I'm not going
to warn you again.
Captain, what were the words
Colonel Childers used...
when he ordered you to fire
on the demonstrators?
I don't remember
the exact words, sir.
He ordered me
to open fire.
When you obeyed Colonel
Childers' order to open fire,
did you believe it
to be a lawful order?
Yes, sir.
Otherwise it would have been your
duty to disobey. Is that right?
Yes, sir.
When your men opened fire
on the attackers in the crowd,
did the snipers in the buildings
across the way cease their firing?
Absolutely, sir.
It went completely quiet.
It would seem, then,
that the two groups were
actually one working together.
Objection. Counsel is drawing
a conclusion for the witness.
Sustained.
Were you in a position
to observe Colonel Childers...
when everyone was evacuated?
Yes, I was.
What was the last thing
you saw him do?
- He went to the flagpole.
- Then whatd he do?
He took down
the American flag.
Was he personally
under heavy fire at that time?
- Yes, sir.
- No more questions.
Captain, prior to receiving orders
from the accused to open fire,
where was the point of greatest
concern for the safety of your men,
the crowd below or the snipers
in the buildings across the way?
- I'm not really sure.
- You're not sure?
Well, I guess...
Don't guess.
I'll repeat the question.
Was the point of greatest concern
the crowd below...
or the snipers
across the way?
I would have to say
the snipers.
Did you feel an immediate mortal
danger from the crowd as a whole?
- I don't understand.
- You don't understand?
- No, sir.
- Let me help you.
Were you more worried...
you'd be killed by these people
or by these people?
I wasn't thinking about that.
Have you ever been under fire?
You didn't see the crowd firing, but
you did take fire from the snipers.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Our clinic is not too far
from the embassy.
So I was one of the first
to arrive there.
Did you see any weapons
on the bodies of the dead?
No.
Did you remove any weapons from
the people you were treating?
No.
Not a single weapon
anywhere among the victims?
No, no weapons.
In your opinion, is Yemen
a training ground for terrorists?
Not at all.
We met in Yemen.
You encouraged me to tour
your clinic in order to witness...
the suffering caused by
Colonel Childers' orders.
- Do you remember that?
- Yes.
I found an audiocassette
on the floor of your clinic.
Its marked exhibit "R."
Do you remember that?
- Yes.
- I found another one...
inside the embassy.
In fact, I found several others.
They're all marked exhibit "R."
Will you translate the writing on
the outside of that cassette?
"Declaration
of Islamic Jihad...
Against United States."
These audiocassettes are used
for the purposes of religious...
and political propaganda due to
the high illiteracy rate in Yemen.
- Is that correct?
- Yes.
Will you translate
the words you hear...
on this audiocassette
for the court, please?
[Man Speaking
In Arabic]
[Stops]
Dr. Ahmar?
"We call on every Muslim
who believes in God...
and hopes for reward...
to obey Goïs command."
[Arabic]
[Stops]
Dr. Ahmar, does it say
what Goïs command is?
"To kill Americans...
and plunder...
their possessions
wherever he finds them."
[Arabic]
- Go on, please.
- [Man On Tape Continues]
"To kill Americans...
and their allies,
both civil
and military,
is duty of every Muslim...
who is able."
- [Tape Continues]
- To kill Americans is a duty.
- Is that what it says?
- Yes.
- [Tape Continues]
- [People Murmuring]
Do you recognize
the speaker's voice?
- No.
- [Tape Continues]
Dr. Ahmar, in your opinion,
is this propaganda...
representative
of that demonstration?
No. I'm not a member
of Islamic Jihad!
The crowd
was singing songs.
I heard them from my clinic.
What was your reaction when you
learned that Colonel Childers...
had been selected
to lead this mission?
I was very pleased. The colonel
had a distinguished record.
- He's a nationally renowned war...
- How did you define his mission?
We wanted to increase security,
but frankly,
if things got threatening,
we wanted an evacuation.
So you weren't looking
for confrontation?
No, thats what we wished
to avoid at all costs.
What was your reaction
to what happened?
I was stunned,
appalled.
Wasn't the severity of the problem
at the embassy understated?
Absolutely not.
We operated on the information
we had at the time.
I have here a State Department
report from Yemen.
Its exhibit "M."
Will you read the underlined
sections for the court, please?
Certainly.
"January 25.
Grenade thrown at police car.
January 27. Sixteen Western tourists
abducted by fundamentalist group."
- Go on, please.
- "February 6.
- A bomb explodes in a car..."
- You got today's Post?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Give it to me.
"Stun grenade thrown at newspaper
kiosk near a police station.
March 13.
A military officer...
is seriously wounded by
Yemen's first... donkey bomb.
Explosives were apparently
concealed under the saddle. "
[Hodges]
Thank you.
I have another State Department
document, dated 17 November.
Its from the ambassador
to you.
Will you read this
for the court, please?
"Dear Bill. Please, we must revisit
our previous conversation...
in that the security measures we
have taken are still inadequate...
for the protection
of our mission to Yemen."
You have to understand that
when I received this letter...
Thank you. Now, there are...
Well, are there... cameras...
- mounted on the roof of the embassy?
- Uh, yes.
Are they designed
to observe and record...
activities in the public spaces
outside the embassy?
- Yes.
- Where are the tapes?
Uh, its my understanding
the embassy was looted.
Maybe the cameras
were destroyed.
This is a photograph.
It is exhibit "D" for the court.
Its a picture of a camera
on the embassy roof.
Does it appear
to be damaged?
No.
- Where are the tapes?
- I don't know.
Don't you think
the United States owes it...
to Colonel Childers
for 30 years of service...
to find that tape
and produce it here?
Objection. We don't know
anything about any tapes.
- This is pure speculation.
- Sustained.
This is a shipping manifest.
Its exhibit "O."
It is a list of items removed from
the embassy during the evacuation...
and shipped
to the State Department.
Will you read
line six, please?
"Videotape from security
camera, VHS, one."
You too busy to look at those
tapes or you just didn't care?
Objection. He's badgering
the national security advisor.
Sustained. Counsel,
please proceed carefully.
- Where are those tapes?
- Objection! Asked and answered.
Oh. Yes, right. Right.
Don't you think its funny...
that a tape that could exonerate
my client is missing?
I don't think its funny at all.
Withholding evidence
is a very serious crime.
- [Biggs] Objection.
- Sustained. Counsel, rephrase.
Withholding evidence to frame
a United States Marine...
is no less evil than charging
my client with murder.
Where are those tapes?
Colonel, I turned over all
materials in my possession...
to Major Biggs.
If those tapes showed a happy
crowd of peaceful demonstrators,
we'd be looking at 'em.
Objection, Your Honor.
This is contempt.
Colonel,
this is your last warning.
It was a new security system.
The cameras were pointed down
at the crowd.
Tapes were recorded, and those tapes
were sent to the State Department.
Why are those tapes not here?
Objection, Your Honor.
I've seen no such tapes.
No further questions.
There are no tapes showing
the crowd firing weapons?
None that I'm aware of.
And the government has turned
over all of its evidence?
Of course.
Colonel Hodges has gone
to some length...
to have you read security reports
illustrating violence in Yemen.
- Yes, he has.
- Here is today's Washington Post.
Will you read these headlines
that I've underlined...
from today's Metro section?
"Agent, kidnapper killed in
rescue of businessman's son."
"Bomb threat evacuates
Muzeum of Natural History."
"Officer chases truck driver,
fires 38 times. "
"Husband shoots wife,
himself in street. "
Mr. Sokal, does this random,
unfortunate news mean we should...
allow Colonel Childers and his
troops loose in Washington, D.C.?
Don't answer that.
Thank you, Mr. Sokal.
Present arms!
Order arms!
[Bugle Begins]
Take deep breaths, sir! You're
almost out of here. Stay calm.
I hope you know
how to fold it, sir.
Thank you, Colonel.
I'll never forget this.
- [Shouting]
- [Yells]
[Explosion]
[Shouting]
[Screams]
Krasevitch is hit!
Corpsman!
Corpsman! Shit!
Goddamn it!
Engage hostile targets
as they appear!
- [Shouting In Arabic]
- Waste the motherfuckers!
Cease fire!
[Drill Sergeant]
Order arms!
I was proud of my marines.
They showed
remarkable discipline.
Why didn't you fire
at the snipers in the buildings...
instead of at the crowd below?
Because I believed we were
in greater danger from the crowd.
- Was that crowd firing at you?
- Yes.
The demonstrators in front of
the building were firing at you...
- in addition to the snipers?
- Yes.
Why didn't anybody else
see that crowd firing?
My men were
under cover on the roof,
except for Krasevitch
who was on an observation post.
And why isn't he here testifying
on your behalf today?
Because he was killed in action.
He died in my arms.
So you were the only man left in
a position to observe that crowd?
Yes.
Where else have you been
in combat, Colonel?
Vietnam, Beirut,
Panama, Persian Gulf.
Can you identify that blue and
white ribbon on your uniform?
Its the Navy Cross.
Do you remember the citation
that accompanied that medal?
"For conspicuous gallantry in
the face of great personal danger,
reflecting great credit
upon himself,
the United States Marine Corps
and the Naval Service."
Your witness.
Colonel,
you gunned down
more than 80 people.
You wounded
another hundred or so.
Could this have been motivated
by a desire for retaliation?
I was protecting my men.
Sergeant Richard Krasevitch was
shot only a few feet away from you.
- Is that correct?
- Yes.
And right after Sergeant
Krasevitch died,
you ordered open fire
on the crowd?
- Is that also correct?
- I was taking fire.
There were weapons
in that crowd.
Well, you wouldn't shoot
unarmed people, would you?
No, I would not.
Even in the heat of battle, you
wouldn't shoot an unarmed person?
No.
This is exhibit "F."
Will you please read
the following to the panel?
"Rules of engagement governing
ground conflict in urban areas.
One: If possible,
the enemy will be warned first,
then asked to surrender."
Colonel, did you warn
the enemy?
We arrived in helicopters.
We were standing on that roof armed.
Did you warn them, either with shots
into the air or by a loudspeaker?
Did you ask them
to surrender?
No.
I'm sorry, no, you did not
warn the crowd?
Yes. No, I did not
warn the crowd.
Continue, Colonel.
You seem to know them by heart.
"Deadly force
is the last resort."
- Go on.
- "Three:
When possible, try to arrange
for the evacuation of civilians...
prior to any U.S. Attack."
Did you do that, try
to evacuate the innocent people...
before you slaughtered them?
- Objection. That is inflammatory.
- Rephrase, Major.
Did you try, following Section C
of the rules of engagement...
for ground conflict in urban areas,
to evacuate innocent civilians?
- No.
[Indistinct Whispering]
Yeah, yeah.
I just have
one more thing, Colonel.
Did you have to repeat
your orders to Captain Lee?
- I'm sorry?
- You ordered Captain Lee...
to engage hostile targets,
and he advised you...
that there were women and children
in the line of fire.
- Is that correct?
- He couldn't see...
Yes or no, Colonel? Did he
follow your first set of orders?
I don't remember.
Captain Lee is on record
as saying he hesitated...
and mentioned the snipers
in the buildings.
- Is his testimony accurate?
- I don't remember.
Let me get this straight.
You evacuate
the ambassador.
You go back to the roof.
Two of your marines are K.I.A.
A third,
Sergeant Krasevitch, dies.
You give your captain
an order which he doesn't follow;
in fact, he questions.
And then you said what?
[Sighs] I don't remember.
You don't remember
what you said next?
It was combat,
not some training exercise.
A moment later,
your men were shooting.
What did you say
to make that happen?
I don't know.
You must have said something.
Captain Lee reversed himself.
- What did you say?
- I don't know the exact words.
- Let me help you.
- Your Honor.
You said, "Waste the motherfuckers,"
didn't you?
- No, no, no.
- You didn't say it?
- It all happened so fast...
- You're under oath, Colonel!
Let me refresh
your memory.
This is exhibit "Q," a tape
recording made aboard...
the U.S.S. Wake Island of all radio
communications received that day,
including your exact words.
Your Honor, with your permission
I would like to play this tape.
If you got it on tape,
then thats what I said!
They were killing my marines,
so, yeah, I said it!
"Waste the motherfuckers!"
- Are these "the motherfuckers"?
- Objection.
- Overruled.
- Yes!
- These?
- [Hodges] Objection!
Yes!
- These?
- [Hodges] Objection!
- Overruled.
- Yes.
Are these "the motherfuckers"...
- that you ordered to be wasted?
- Your Honor.
- Major.
- Yes!
The crowd in front of the embassy
had no weapons, did they, Colonel?
Objection. We found
no snipers' weapons either.
Yes, they had weapons!
You think there's
a script for fighting a war...
without pissing somebody off?
Follow the rules,
and nobody gets hurt?
Yes, innocent people probably died.
Innocent people always die.
But I did not exceed
my orders!
There are rules, and marines
are sworn to uphold them.
I was not going to stand by
and see another marine die...
just to live
by those fucking rules!
- [Gavel Pounding]
- Colonel!
Your Honor,
I request a recess.
Major.
The government is finished with
Colonel Childers, Your Honor.
[Judge] All right, Colonel,
you have your recess.
[Indistinct Chatter]
[Sighs]
Why didn't you tell me
what you said?
- I didn't remember.
- "Waste the motherfuckers."
Thats brilliant.
You didn't think that was important?
Why didn't you know
about the goddamn recording?
- You're supposed to know...
- I had a week to prepare this case.
I didn't realize
what a fuckup I'm defending.
- Well, now you know.
- Goddamn.
- [Sighs]
[Sighs]
- This is going to take us both down.
- How's that work?
You gonna spend the rest
of your life in prison too?
[Both Sighing]
- [Sighs]
- I'm sorry.
[Exhales]
- I really screwed up in there, huh?
- Yeah, you really did.
[Chuckles]
Whew!
- So what happens now?
- Shit, I don't know.
[Sighs]
I don't know.
Your Honor, the government
calls Colonel Bin Le Cao...
- as a rebuttal witness.
- Objection, Your Honor.
What are the grounds for
this rebuttal witness to be allowed?
Will counsel please
approach the bench.
- Who is Colonel Bin Le Cao?
- A North Vietnamese Colonel...
who fought against Colonel Childers
at the battle of Ca Lu.
What he has to say directly refutes
statements made by Colonel Childers.
- When was the battle of Ca Lu?
- 1968.
This is uncharged misconduct. It is
not allowable under military law.
How do you know this witness
is going to charge misconduct?
I'm assuming...
He knows because he was
at the battle of Ca Lu.
- Is that true?
- Yes, sir.
On what grounds are you
calling your witness?
Colonel Hodges made Colonel
Childers' combat experience...
part of his defense.
Furthermore,
Colonel Childers testified...
that he never shoots unarmed people.
My witness has an important
perspective on that statement.
I'm gonna allow
the witness.
[Biggs]
Do you swear or affirm...
that the evidence you shall give
in this case...
shall be the truth,
the whole truth...
and nothing but the truth,
so help you God?
[Cao]
Yes, I do.
Will you please state
your name for the court?
- My name is Bin Le Cao.
- In 1968, you were a colonel...
with the North Vietnamese army,
B3 regiment, involved in a fight...
with American marines at Ca Lu
in the Quang Tri province?
Yes, I was.
Will you tell the court
about that battle?
We were aware that
small units of Americans...
were near
my company of men.
We found ourselves
behind your forces.
This was lucky for us
because we were outnumbered.
Do you recognize
this man?
Yes.
Did he capture you and your
radio operator that day?
Yes.
Did he remove your weapons
and place you under armed guard?
Yes.
Did you consider yourself
a prisoner of war?
Yes.
Did he execute
your radio operator?
Yes.
You personally saw him shoot
a fellow prisoner of war?
Yes.
[Biggs]
Where did he shoot him?
[Cao]
In the head.
Thank you.
No further questions.
[Sighs] Were your men annihilating
that platoon of marines?
Yes.
Did Colonel Childers force you
to call your men off?
Yes.
Do you believe his actions
were calculated to save...
- the lives of American marines?
- Yes.
Would you have done the same
thing Colonel Childers did...
if the situation
had been reversed?
Colonel Cao, would you have shot...
a captive American radio operator
in the head if you thought...
it would persuade Colonel Childers
to spare the lives of your own men?
Yes.
No more questions.
[Judge] This court is in recess
until tomorrow at 0900.
- We will hear closing arguments.
- [Gavel Pounds]
- General, good to see you.
- Perry, good to see you too.
I want you to meet
my grandson.
Hi. Nice to meet
you, sir.
Thanks.
[Biggs] Colonel Terry Childers
is a decorated war hero,
a trusted leader
of American marines,
and I wish that was
all there was to it.
Unfortunately, there are
83 dead Yemeni citizens,
many of them
women and children.
Colonel Hodges would have you
believe that this crowd was armed.
He would also have you believe
that there is a videotape...
proving this to be true.
There is no tape
exonerating Colonel Childers.
There is no evidence
exonerating Colonel Childers!
Is Colonel Childers a man capable of
killing defenseless, unarmed people?
Is he capable of ordering
the execution...
of innocent
men and women?
Is he capable of executing
P.O.W. S with his own hand?
Unfortunately,
we have shown that he is.
You have heard the sad testimony
of Colonel Cao...
who witnessed Colonel Childers'
barbarism firsthand.
You've even heard
Colonel Childers' own admission...
that his desire was to "waste"
them, regardless of who they were.
Now, we are faced
with the difficult prospect...
of convicting
one of our own.
None of us wants to do this,
but you've heard the facts,
and it is unavoidable.
Colonel Terry Childers ordered
the senseless slaughter...
of a peaceful crowd!
Now, as marines,
we do not get the luxury
of covering up our mistakes.
We must air them,
thereby ensuring
that they never happen again.
Thank you.
Thats sovereign
United States territory...
as much as if it were
in Ohio or Maryland.
Colonel Childers didn't
volunteer to go over there.
He was ordered to go there because
he was the best man for the job.
We armed him.
We trained him.
We sent him over there to risk
his life to save other Americans.
And then ask him
not to return fire?
There are over 300 bullet holes
in this building.
Colonel Childers didn't open fire.
He returned fire.
And he waited until after three
of his marines were dead...
and another lay
mortally wounded.
He waited until he was
personally under heavy fire.
He waited until he saw
that crowd holding weapons.
Only then did he order
his men to return fire.
Under the rules of engagement,
a civilian pointing a weapon...
is no longer a civilian,
and the use of deadly force
is authorized...
in order to save lives.
Its not murder.
Its combat.
Colonel Childers is
the only man alive...
who was in a position
to see that crowd.
But the camera on the embassy
roof had the same point of view.
The government
would have you believe...
there's no tape
from that camera.
I have shown you that that tape was
delivered to the State Department.
Do you believe that tape
got up and walked out...
of the State Department
on its own?
By not producing that tape,
the national security advisor,
Mr. Sokal, has brought dishonor
into this court.
Without that tape, I cannot show
you that the crowd fired first...
and that Colonel Childers
is innocent.
But without that tape,
they cannot prove...
beyond a reasonable doubt
that he's guilty!
[Sighs]
Here's my case.
He's all I've got.
Thirty-two years of service,
thirty-two years of heroism
as a United States Marine.
Regardless of
what you decide here,
Colonel Childers'career
as a marine is over.
He will never again
command men in combat.
The ambassador and his family
are alive today because of him.
And I know how
the ambassador feels,
because Colonel Childers
saved my life too.
I'm alive today because of him.
My son is sitting in
this courtroom because of him.
I'm alive today,
and I have a son,
because of the heroism
of Colonel Childers.
To ask this man to risk his life
for his country,
to ask this man to watch
his marines die in his arms...
and call it murder
when he's defending himself,
call it murder for firing back
when fired upon...
To call it murder for saving
the lives of his countrymen...
under the most extreme
of circumstances, thats, uh...
My fellow Marines,
thats hanging him out to dry.
Its worse than leaving him
wounded on a battlefield.
That is something
you do not do...
if you are
a United States Marine.
And it is something that I pray
to God you won't do here either.
[Sighs]
- Whatd you think?
- You're pretty good.
Yeah. Yeah.
- Dad, you were awesome.
- [Chuckles]
Thanks, son.
I'm very glad that I don't
have to sit on that panel, son.
You made it
awful tough on them.
- [Ringing]
- [Indistinct Chatter]
- 15,000 to 25,000...
- Excuse me.
[Ringing Continues]
I said no interruptions.
[Woman] I'm sorry, Mr. Sokal.
Its very important.
Send him in.
Can we pick this up
after lunch, gentlemen?
Absolutely.
[Men Chattering]
[Door Closes]
Close the door.
What is it, Colonel?
No matter what happens
to Terry Childers tomorrow,
I'm not going to leave
this job until I find out...
- what happened to that tape.
- Good.
Think itll ever turn up?
No.
I don't either.
Well, then there's nothing more
for us to talk about, is there?
You ever had a pissed-off
marine on your ass?
Is that a threat?
Oh, yes, sir.
[Door Closes]
[Crowd Chatter]
- [Door Opens]
- [Bailiff] All rise.
Has the panel
reached a verdict?
We have, sir.
Colonel Terry L. Childers, this
court-martial finds as follows:
On the charge
of breach of peace,
the court finds
the defendant guilty.
On the charge of conduct
unbecoming an officer,
the court finds
the defendant not guilty.
On the charge of murder,
the court finds
the defendant not guilty.
This court-martial
is adjourned.
Sentencing will be conducted
at a time to be determined.
- [Gavel Pounds]
- Thank you.
[Indistinct Chatter]
[Sighs]
- I need one more favor.
- Yeah.
Teach me how to fly-fish.
You are well aware that I know
shit about fly-fishing.
Oh.
Colonel.
You realize in light of
Colonel Cao's testimony,
we'll be pushing for charges
on the Ca Lu incident.
That was 30 years ago.
You're going to have
a hard time finding witnesses.
I thought maybe
you'd be willing to testify.
I'll make you a deal.
If you can tell me right now
what the life expectancy was...
for a second lieutenant dropped
into a hot L.Z. In Vietnam in 1968,
I'll tell you everything
I remember about Ca Lu.
- One week.
- Negative.
Sixteen minutes, Major.
Sixteen fucking minutes.
And thats all I remember.
[Crowd Shouting]
[Together]
Sir.
[Soldiers
Shouting Drills]
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org