Here it is, folks, Russell Peters!
How are you?
See it, you dirty download era.
See this audience,
they are all there, great.
They are all there.
Obviously, we have here and Asia.
I saw the Honda Civic
parking lot, I know you're there.
I thought that record
Fast and Furious"3"or something.
Indian Scott, look at yourself.
Let me tell you, it is much
closed motels in town.
White, how are you? I'm glad to see you.
White guy with indian, super, my friend.
Its certainly very happy?
Behold the Indian white
woman, see balance.
I say, live American dream.
Or at least Indian dream.
"If I go to America and
find a white woman... "
"The horse I am. "
Are there Latinaca?
Well, six whole.
As if we are not in California
appeared only 6 Latinaca.
Blacks?
Look at that, you again tapšeš.
We have both the black and Latin.
The loan you certainly enormous.
It's funny when I say Asian.
Especially in America, when I say Asian
people automatically imagine...
Which is tricky, because India is a part of Asia.
And we do not have the same merit.
When I say Asian, people do not work...
And we bre Asians.
When God made
Asia, made the two types.
And you've chosen the first look.
I fucked us.
"We'll worry. "
"You take your noses and hair. "
My people are greedy. We heard
two,"It's a good deal or two. "
And noses and hair!
We did not know that you'll noses
be great and the hair on the body.
We are a hairy race.
In India it is very hot, and we're hairy.
Who is to come up bre?
I think that the God who made
Indians playing with the other gods.
"People, come to see. "
"Budo, drink and come down. "
"You see, I'll take these people here... "
"I put them in the warmest place in the world. "
"And just for fun... "
Prekriæu them"hair. "
It is warm, and we're hairy.
Both men and women.
Indian angry, pulling up his sleeves...
Scott,"I hate this. "
Now it's okay to fish
have hair. I can solve them.
I do not want them, and solve them,
there are various methods for downloading.
Waxing, electrolysis, hair cutting, epilation.
Now that I do not want hair somewhere...
And there's not.
Now they take off and ass.
How are you hairy was before all this?
You know what the fish's '80 worked to remove hair?
Blajhale them.
"Honey, we do not have a problem with the color of your mustache. "
Blue is nothing better.
The Asians are not hairy.
Their full head of hair, and nothing in the body.
You'll rarely see æelavog
Asians, but if it is not shaved.
When I say Asian...
People immediately think of Chinese.
"All Asians are Chinese, yes. "
Behold, how loud View your surname.
But the funny thing is that all people
think that only Chinese Asians.
Chinese"talk, look and it's them. "
That's not true, there are many types of Asians.
Of course looking
you can not immediately say.
That affects you, something is running out...
"Yeah, I know what you're Asian. "
But if you really want to
teach the difference among them
it can be seen by
how to speak English.
Just to acquire a feeling...
Is there a Vietnamese?
OK, a guy is hiding upstairs.
Is there a Korean?
Well, there are two indoor laundry.
Filipinos?
I knew that you are Filipinos because of the microphone
Stare like it's gonna be karaoke after.
"I hope this will speed up asshole from Bombay... "
"Because I want to sing. "
Chinese?
Fine.
You can tell by how speak English.
For example, Vietnamese...
Because when you speak, do so very quickly.
As you know it.
So fast-English speaking
it still sounds like Vietnamese.
Once I was frightened a Vietnamese.
"Fuck you, you fucking pušaèu kurca. "
Call me pušaèem kurca.
Someone you once called pušaèem kurca?
You are aware that when you call someone that,
there is not one good word to return.
Nothing gonna zvuèati great.
Pušaèu kurca"."
And you"."
That's why I love different cultures.
Different words, different means.
I am from Teran, there has
a Vietnamese restaurant.
It's called,"Pho Phúc Lie".
Pho Phúc"Lie".
As a kid I called just to type reported.
It sounds like a whole new level of lying.
"Hey, do not lie, it's a lie than 4 words!"
Pušaèu kurca"."
How Koreans speak English.
Sounds like you have lived.
As if they trèali marathon.
"I do not joke about zbijaj Koreans. "
I learned to count to 6 in Korean.
Not something, but better than swearing.
First you learn how to
foreign language is to swear by it.
And then angry because the first thing
have learned when it came to cursing.
"So rude, entered and said... "
"Hello, pederèino. "
But it is learned.
I learned to count to 6,
not much, but really I am.
From a woman who works in vešeraju,
I took the T-shirt and counted with her.
Here, count to 6
What are you, Jews?
When Chinese people speak English...
Sounds like you shred vegetables.
"Do not you say something".
Do what?
How to make brief word more kraæom?
I learned about the cultures for travel.
I had a show in Vietnam
a few years ago, it was great.
In Vietnam it's hot like hell.
When you say that Indian
it's hot, believe him, was warm.
Great place, nice people.
I did not know that in Vietnam,
scooter can be used as a van.
I did not know.
You can see the whole family on the scooter.
Dad sat down to this, leaving little space...
And there would be a village child.
And then another one stopped ahead.
Then the mom behind the village, with a hand like this.
And then another child faces like this.
And one way.
And three of the policy somersault while Dad drives.
If you can see here, it would be a circus.
"Do not try this at home,
These are professional circus performers. "
And six in a white car carefully.
In Vietnam, the whole family, Dad blowing...
Mom back, eat.
Vietnam is great, because if something
you should go, it's because of their money.
It's great, is called the dong.
So they called money, dong.
It pays to go only to you on the street, women ask...
"Sorry, sir, have you dong?"
"Yes, I have. "
"Will the penis with the dongle?"
Is not that word sounds disgusting?
These were invented by white people.
"Hey, buddy, I istresao penis. "
Penis, sounds wet.
I have no penis, I have a dick.
Comrade, the show is here.
I'm not a piece of meat.
Last year I
was in China, the Chinese, where are you?
And here, you're Chinese?
I'm sorry I was for it?
He said,"Yes".
"I keep doing this, but do not go. "
"I am a Pakistani. "
What's your name? - Vincent.
Vincent, and I just thought I
and video,"This guy,"it's Vincent.
And you have a Chinese name? - Yes.
How's it going?
Slow down, I'm not Chinese.
Me or you do not have proper to say.
Really?
Comrade, tell it again.
It's now made up.
Something is swallowing.
And you're Chinese, what is your name?
Catherine.
- Catherine, yes, of course.
You know those Chinese, Catherine and Vincent?
Catherine, and you have a Chinese name?
And yours is confused as Vincent, tell?
I love your what?
Cisse?
It sounds sexy.
With such a name
You can Tzimas buddies.
I fired one by name
Catherine. A friend says,"It hurts me ears. "
And when I say I was fired...
"He made you to somewhere?"
It is egzotièno!
Where are your family?
From the Bay area.
Bay, that's what I thought.
Before that?
Hong Kong.
China, mainland?
Which part? Do not you know?
So you accept?
"Mom, Dad,
where are you?"- "From China. "
"Which part?"
- "From the center. "
"Center, China, OK, Catherine, a lot of issues. "
You speak Mandarin or Cantonese?
Cantonese, then south China, see?
See how I managed?
Apparently, you too
Vincent speak Cantonese?
Your are from Hong Kong, I know the difference.
People do not know, say
that the Chinese speak Chinese.
Which is stupid, because China does not exist.
Like when my pride and ask,"Russell,
how to say Hi to India?"
Indian does not exist, I do not know what you ask.
Well", smart. "
"As in India, says Hi!"
Thus...
If you do not know, in China there are two languages.
Cantonese and Mandarin,
and a crowd of some village.
Even the Chinese say:
"I do not know what to talk. "
Cantonese spoken in Hong Kong.
Biggest part, and Beiðingu
and those parts of Mandarin.
If you think of someone to
speak Chinese, and it sounds funny
imagine Cantonese.
Cantonese is the funniest of them.
Those with long tones.
When I was in Hong Kong, I've heard people how
speak Cantonese, the funniest I have ever heard.
Sometimes, when you speak, as if falling off the cliff.
If you do not know the language, nor
do not know speak properly.
I do not know even whether mucaju while talking.
Can stuttering, we would not know.
Quotes To:
This story as"crazy. "
However, Cantonese is fun.
I remember in Hong Kong
I was in the hotel, woke up.
Teglio I was in the hallway, and obviously
said something in Chinese, I have no idea.
I walked i...
Yelled the manager of the hotel:
"Hey, asshole, do not swear at the hotel!"
Watch"dictionary, be male!"
But it sounds fun.
Mandarin, fluent in
Beiðingu, I went there last year.
I learned the difference between
kantonskog and Mandarin, I'll tell you.
Now that you know how it sounds Cantonese,
You'll immediately recognize Mandarin.
Is totally different, more relaxed.
Sounds a little more aggressive, as
to škrguæu teeth while speaking.
Particularly in Beiðingu.
"Of course, asshole!"
But it's just different.
Know when to use English
poštapalice until we find the right word?
Stupid word, like...
Words that we serve
until the next recall.
To odugovlaèimo.
In Mandarin, very like a
word for it, and in English is tricky.
You know what I'm saying,
the Chinese thought:"I know that word. "
You know I can not invent?
This is the word, in Bedding I always hear...
To their word!
Now, this is a true story.
The KFC in I Beiðingu.
Because I went to China that would
ate"Kentucky Fried Chicken.
I'm waiting in line, and in front of me in line, a black woman.
I have not put me there.
It was there, I swear, I do not invent.
I'm waiting in line in front of me a black woman
the only black woman in China.
I found the chicken, just tell you.
Not invent the stereotypes, but I see them.
I stand in line in front of me a black woman
and from Nigeria, I know it is
because they can not cope with the menu.
I keep looking at me.
"I do not know what to naruèim. "
"Look at the menu. "
"We should try popcorn chicken. "
And, we stand in line...
I uleæe little Chinaman with mom.
Stand at the cash register and looking at the menu,
trying to Skonto what's going to eat.
Mom standing there, a woman from Nigeria here.
Mom trying to say
what will, but not very secure.
And you just see...
And this from Nigeria looking at me
as if I have to isprebijam child.
"Why do not hit?"
I think is, here slamèica, fix it myself.
I had a great time in China.
Only it was pathetic that we
the airline lost her luggage.
On the way to China.
How to lose something on the way to somewhere.
I'm coming to China, I have nothing to do with them.
Because we have lost the case.
I'm coming to China, and I have only,
moron, I have only hand-luggage.
And it only DVD player, diskmen,
Some CDs, DVDs and magazine.
I thought that during the
times I want to have fun.
And will my underwear and socks,
èetkica and deodorant.
Deodorant.
Be the case that I will saèekati in China.
Who did not saèekao in China.
And to be honest, as well as Indian...
We need a deodorant.
Do not look at me, you know that you need.
"No, no, just a shower. "
No, no, you need a fucking deodorant.
Because rumors circulating.
People are already saying:"Indians stink. "
Let me tell you, you stink, let me explain.
Evaporate faster than others.
And after 25 hours of flight, I was totally evaporated.
So I smrdeo that me
Chinese airport, shouting:"You smrdiš!"
"You're from India. "
"I'm from Canada. "
So Kanaðani suck.
And, that night my show, I have no clothes.
I wear jeans, shirt,
kaèket, I dressed for the holiday.
Do not be such a stage, and I have to
shopping center in Beiðingu to buy something.
I did not know, but I
I am obviously in China Shaquille O'Neal.
Go to the store and ask...
"Do you have a shoe size 10.5 or 11?"
"We do not, may 8?"
"I'm not with you to discuss the issue of his shoe?"
A 36"pants?"
"36 is too big!"
"You're too fat. "
"Lose weight, fatso. "
"Back when you were 30, 32 the most. "
How come I can not find
clothes in China, does not make you all there?
All in all, great trip.
So much travel, passport
I ended last summer.
I had to renew it,
do not know about America but in Canada
Photos of the new passport
not allowed to laugh.
This is a new rule, their way
to fight against terrorism.
That's going to catch terrorists, you can not laugh.
This is the message, if you travel,
better you happy that you are not.
I did not know, I'm in a shopping center
I go to one place
where do passport photos
get inside and say that we need.
Guy says:"No problem, sit down. "
Popizdeli himself, because he was white,
and do not know what is so spoken.
I think I was fuck.
I sat, the type of pie I am
you ready, I say that I am
I need pictures, I am
gay guy and think, well.
I laugh, like this.
"Sir, lips must touch. "
Good.
"Sir, you can not laugh. "
Of course to do so or not.
They really think that
'll win by terrorism.
So you will not laugh.
Want to find a terrorist,
nateraj all to laugh.
Those who will not, Inspect them.
You watch CNN, and show
picture wanted terrorists.
And they are happy, never.
You have never seen a terrorist to do this.
There is no terrorist Rogue
with your thumb on the detonator.
"Pritisnuæu, I want, I saw that cvikaš."
I did not dare to laugh.
As it is not bad enough
I am Indian, I'm going to the airport.
Now that I give my passport, I look angry.
Pictures in my passport this.
Look at it and say:"Mr.
Peters, this way please, to talk. "
It is difficult, because the provision of
airport, like homemade, party
must learn the difference
between terrorists and the Indians.
We are not the same.
We are not the same part of the world,
do not speak the same language
do not eat the same food,
do not even hate the same people.
Terrorists hate Americans.
Indians, hate each other.
Terrorists will diæi airport into the air.
Indian likes to work at the airport.
"This is counter-productive. "
I know that many whites are now afraid of flying.
I understand that, but one said...
"No, do not fly. "
"You never know when you'll be up shit. "
"What, nothing worse will not happen. "
"Yeah, well, you never know. "
I understand, you little uspanièeni.
But think reasonable, logical.
Think of it that the company
fly, where ukcravate, where you fly
it affects all
your theory of terrorism.
I flew Jet Blue from".
You see,"Jet Blue"is funny enough.
I flew with Jet Blue"from"
Buffalo in New York for Langvardiju.
The aircraft with 30 seats.
My God, my Indian accent the back.
All pass through it.
I board the small plane that
flight of 45 minutes, we board
and he saw me bakuta white.
Grab the bag and says:"Oh, God!"
I used to think,"What?"
I think that terrorists in the fucking"Jet Blue"?
What am I, with terrorists
no self-esteem?
Yes, I do not want to kill a lot of us today.
Poèeæu with 30, and tomorrow,"East-West".
Just think logical.
I flew two weeks after 9/11.
I was sitting next to whites,
almost the ukenjao in gaæe.
I sat down a guy like this...
After half an hour, go for a bag type...
"God, no!"
Relax, kretenèino.
Just to get diskmen.
To obey instructions.
I'm glad to here
has Latinaca, full 6th
You're Latinac, mongrel, what?
Mongrel said, this is a mongrel.
Cut it.
How are you mixed?
Puerto Rican and black?
Not much different,
Parents are the ones from New York?
Huanes that?
Puerto Rico?
Puerto Rican and black, that's great.
In Canada, not Puerto Rican.
There are no Mexicans, whether they have here?
You, a guy works like this...
Clean Mexican?
Cool, what is your name?
Hose?
In case you did not believe him.
I like Mexicans, they're not in Canada.
There's not.
To see what our lawns.
Now you're suddenly oseæajni?
"It's all right, but not kenjaj for lawns. "
Funny how you defend...
Guarding these back.
No Mexicans, I'd love to have.
There are Latina, and those from South America.
Chile, Uruguay, they all fudbalerske country.
Now I live in LA, and there
a lot of Mexicans.
One of my friends is Jesus.
It's great to hang out with
guy named Jesus.
Who's your buddy? -"Son of God. "
I like to socialize with him.
Latins are generally proud people.
Do something Spanish
confused by them, is alarming.
As you must know how to say.
I tell Jesus to go on burrito...
It is said buriiito"."
OK, sorry.
Latins in Canada are trying...
One type of meksièkog
County of LA-ju, played by gangsters.
"To talk to you, but, idiot?"
Acting crazy, tense, are...
Even Jesus we pride...
"Race, to talk?"
"What did I do?"
"Nothing, just to tell. "
Jesus, relax.
Latini or those from South
America, posing as lovers.
Too, like all living want to seduce.
I go to a Spanish club...
"Race, I want you to meet Fernanda. "
Type of turn around and say...
"I'm Fernando. "
"Can you skloniš dick,
just want to shake hands. "
I am not for such entertainment.
But I like Latina, you know why?
They have najnormalniji accent in the world.
But as soon as I begin to mention the countries of South America
Sounds like they are second
just before getting off the ship.
Where are you from? -"Well, I am
... but here are mine from Ecuador. "
What happened to you?
And as many Spanish countries
mentioned, as if ogluve.
"I am from Ecuador,
my friend from Nicaragua. "
"He's from Guatemala. "
"Peru, Peru. "
I like names with the origin, are super.
I do not have it, and Indians to mind.
But my real name is Russell Peters.
Both my parents are from
India, and so they called me.
Russell Dominic... see jackasses!
Do you know you do history of India?
I do not know, you know how I know?
The British were there 400 years,
think that some of us are not pojebali?
If you already do all the gems that
we steal, we can also more important.
That is my name, both parents from India
and they called me Russell Dominic Peters.
Dominic, I got the Italian middle name.
Because my Italian works from India.
Calcutta. You know that part?
Do you have a problem, tell my.
Eric and Maureen.
And with his brother Julio.
I have Indian
name, I proudly wore it.
I do not have it, that I have, I would proudly wear.
What's your name, sir India?
Anita?
See, nice name.
Jose, this is your equivalent.
Anita Patel.
It's my brother Annecy Patel.
The older brother Aslab.
You know what your name means?
Do not you know?
I was not sure that my
means, but I do not know what is yours.
I know what I mean Russell is miserable.
You know what I mean? "Make noise. "
Crappy name.
I love Indian names, I think they are great.
They have a deep meaning, the history behind them.
How is your name, bro?
Prab Džolt?
No Prabdžolt?
That would be rude?
Meant to Prebfuck.
Preble Džolt.
Nice indian name.
I love them, you know what you mean?
You see, he knows.
What does that mean Preble?
Scent of God?
How do you call a sister, Flora Scent?
Sister"you smell great. "
"It's just grass. "
Herbal Džolt.
Scent of God, great.
I love Indian names,
I think they are mostly great.
The names of history are great.
But if you have one, and move to America
consider what means of
English before doðete.
How will affect your life.
For some Indian names are really cool.
Mean much, but they are good in India.
When doðete here, do not go well.
I met Indian, you know
it's name because the people from your.
Indian I met, I swear
is, his name is, smoke deeply.
Deep suck.
Imagine that you live with that name.
Someone asked...
You smoke Deep"?"
"Sometimes, if I must. "
"I just do not like. "
And obviously, in our country not so pronounced.
But if you turn it reads,
I read you so, Suck Hdeep.
H does not help.
Now it sounds just... Smoke deeply.
"Come on, smoke deeply. "
I thought it was the funniest
Indian name that I heard.
But a few months ago I
was in Washington, and met the Indian
and, not ft., type is called Hard Kita.
Hardik.
Hardik, who also called the child?
"Put on pants, it's not nice. "
Hardik.
How can you have a career in
porniæima when calling Hard Kita.
What if Keith and smoke Hard Deep
become best friends?
You're Indian, you know what I mean,
You crossed the border with the names.
I met a fish Deep Beat.
"Hey, give me deeply. "
Surely it does not say so but
Beat the fun when you say deep.
Just think...
I do not know why the Indians did not clear my name.
I do not know what is so hard, it's simple.
Just Read the Book
history, and all will be clear to you.
The Indians are always the worst response.
Russell Peters whites hear and say:"OK".
They do not have problems, I guess.
"Maybe it's from the south, I do not know. "
Christian is"You did not?"
Am.
- From the south?
No, I am of these.
I know what you think, not of these.
They changed their religion, I'm mixed.
We do not know when I'm involved.
Just happened, whether we are many.
Indians are the worst response.
You say my name, whites,
"Yeah, Russell Peters, I was pleased. "
Indians would immediately ask something.
And when they want any information, are terrible.
Not very convincing, always know when
Indian is trying something that you pulled.
Because when they do, look at you like you Kenji.
Really, do this...
"Race?"
They do not really convincing.
Parents are the worst.
Whites as parents are direct.
You have white parents, Hi, my friend.
What's your name?
Steve, just so.
Welcome to the night stereotypes.
Steve, Jose and Anita Patel.
Whites are direct, when
want the child to do something...
"Steve, ready room. "
Immediately say.
Indians believe that children should ubeðuju.
And if you do not make one face, izabraæe
one word, and thus try to convince you.
"Race, come on. "
"Come. "
It's their way, take the word and extend it.
You can imagine the agreed
Stan Stan the first couple of nights.
They have to sleep for the first time.
"It's gonna be sex?"
"Sex?"
Pseæi style"?"
Pseæi"."
Immigrant parents like
their children to be stupid.
Yes, do anything.
When family comes, then you shame.
You can pretend to Baja, but
When family comes, it is.
Filipinos me I guess.
You always do that.
Show"to sing, show. "
"June, come and show. "
Sing"."
"You see, is an excellent. "
The Indians do.
I remember, I played with 14 Breakdance.
Am.
I am constantly...
It's me, then.
I remember, with 14, all day I...
When family comes, I want to them.
Dad was saying,"Russell, uncle to play the show. "
Show uncle"to play. "
"I do not want. "
- "Show him. "
I stand there like a jackass.
The uncle will:"Great, retarded
is not to break. "
Just you obrukaju.
I'm tired.
Is there a British?
See, you import its white meat, fine.
Where are you from, you're from England?
Which part?
Bedford.
Bedford, as it is finely said.
Sometimes I love the British accent.
But I think it's only that you
make a funny face while talking.
"Good evening, I'm from England. "
"I'm from England. "
The British are OK, but sometimes very arrogant.
If you want to lug...
When you meet someone from England, and tell you
where it is, pretend you have no idea where it is.
Popizde.
"Interesting accent, where are you?"
From England"."
"Excuse me, where?"
"I've never heard. "
"For England?"
"Small Island, in addition to Europe. "
"It's close to Miami?"
"England, kretenèino!"
"I think I speak our language. "
"I speak English,
I have no idea what you are saying. "
England"."
It looks ugly, because I think
that the British do not reprove a lot.
Women do not like.
"What a wonderful feeling. "
"Awesome. "
"God, I'm coming. "
How much are you in America?
12, 13 years?
I obviously have not met
in England, because he is Indian.
I do not know if I know, but
England has the most Indians.
Really, they are all there.
The British were angry they are there.
Angry, so we have so many.
As an Indian, in London, I feel as gundam.
"Go home, brown Scott. "
I have been angry that so many Indians in England.
We are not guilty, the British, you've started.
You've gone to India, we are not called.
1600th just appeared.
Others are 400 years.
1947th they went, we were
fashion:"No, no, I go with you. "
"You can not just come and go like that. "
"What are you going to eat?"
"Let's go. "
Amerèki my white friends,
Steve, your are from America?
I married you indian?
How much are you married?
11 years, great.
Now it's, like 11 years
cool, before there were only 11?
Success?
Three children? A nice little cream children?
Super.
Indian are good, sexy, hot.
If krenes down, take glass of water.
My white American friends,
I want to tell you something.
I love you.
I do not say so, I have a good reason.
Because I think that the whites in the past
30 years done great things.
Just somehow pulled the line.
I am sorry, because whites...
All of us who are not
whites, whites are convinced
that they are racist.
So many are afraid to notice the color
to be afraid to describe
exactly a situation.
I worked in a club
one of my black friends
came a porter comes and says
"Race, there's your buddy. "
I wonder:
"Negro. "- "I do not know. "
"I have not noticed. "
"How do you?"
"What's it like?"
- "High said. "
Curly hair"."
"What's his name?"- "Leroy. "
Black"?"
"Maybe, if you say so, I do not know. "
We are so scared they
and convince them that they are racists, that's awful.
Because white people will never be a racist as we are.
No way.
Whites will never be such racists.
Indians, Asians, we are all racists.
Each group.
Whites will see Indians and say:"See
them, must have been as happy together. "
And you you go into society and say:
"Hey, you're from India, I am. "
"What part of, not that, worn, seljaèino. "
Each group will do it.
And Asians do.
"I am a Chinese, where are you from?"
"You're stupid. "
Obraæaj"I do not, idiot. "
Everyone is doing it, it's bizarre.
Whites do not have that problem.
When the encounter:"Where are you?"
- "In Tennessee, you?"
From New York"."
- "OK, let's go have a drink. "
It hurts your ear.
White, OK to be proud of themselves.
That's not bad.
Sometimes zanesete, and love
crosses and put the pointed hats.
But to pull the line somewhere before.
Whites have just changed
in the last 30 years.
Generously you let immigrants in their country.
I mean, the land which
you have taken, but, whatever...
Of course, you have a bad history.
Of course, you stole
neèiju country, strong thing.
You want to elete the whole
one race, no problem.
You brought people from Africa and sjebali them.
But forget all that.
Now we are in the 21 century.
It's time to move on.
I'm glad that you stole the land.
You know why, Christopher
Columbus was looking for my country.
You know, Christopher Columbus
the famous explorer.
He asked when India
discovered North America.
Jackass lost.
Not even was not in a good part of the world.
I knew that this was not India.
What do you think you are
natives called Indians?
He did not want to drop the stupid crew.
"Guys, it must be India. "
And that"Indians. "
We were burning and
standing and waiting for:"Where is the bre Chris?"
Scott"late. "
But white people are generous, open
the border, let immigrants.
They did not ask anything.
Immigrants"Come, stay with
Us USA. It's all right. "
We all came, and whites were great.
"Come, thank you for coming. "
"Of course, sit down. "
You were generous, you are not asked anything.
Never say:"Hey, what are you doing, get lost. "
Never, ever:"Come, sit down. "
And they did fine.
See immigrants and say:
"She saw them, I like you are there. "
I think about them, because they are smiling...
"Hey, Mr. Amer, how are you?"
"Good day, sir. "
And you realize that every
immigrant who came to this country
kenjao by you.
Each, where ever it is.
From Europe, Asia, Africa, it does not matter.
Come and talk behind the back.
I do not like it because I was born in
North America and it annoys me.
But doing it all, and they all speak one.
You are from England, and certainly
you have to say, and you belkinja.
You see, even white people do.
But every immigrant, you know what they say?
Americans have"culture. "
That said, my father used to say:
Fucking USA", no culture. "
I've talked to
have, have something of his.
What is theirs, which makes their culture.
Which means that they have.
"No, what their culture, show me, what?"
"What, hamburgers and horogovi not culture. "
"First, burgers and what?"
Horogovi"."
"What is the bre horog?"
Horog", you know ono. "
"You mean, a hot dog?"
"Do not sad to give it a fancy name, OK?"
But white people, it is not fair, USA, is not fair to
immigrants come and say they have no culture.
So what you have.
Black History is accurate.
When you look at, think,"Blacks
nothing more to prove. "
But white people are constantly prove something.
I'm here to tell you that
you have one, everything is reduced to the music.
When it comes to music, white people have their own.
And is not that we are not in fact enjoy, we are, but
you are more of us and has become your culture.
White people like certain songs, as well as
me, but whites were raised to another level.
White love songs that involve the audience.
They do not have much to do.
Radiæu"the same as the one guy. "
Because they already know that white people do not know how to play.
That's not true, it is not fair, they know.
Just play too dance at the same time.
There is a problem.
You can play salsa and
running man, do not look good.
But white people love the songs that involve the audience.
We love them and me. Makarena".
There was a Latin thing,
then it was the whites doèepali.
They made it his.
We all played Makarenu, but
the whites are raised to a new level.
And we recognize that this is your dance.
Good you are, enjoy.
I love to watch you so enjoy.
When you hear the music
love to see their joy in his eyes.
I love to watch when people enjoy it.
There are some songs, Makarena, Pileæi dance.
This is a song by whites.
You know Pileæi dance?
Farmers each.
Držaæemo the Pileæeg dance.
Pileæi I love dancing.
You went to the marriage of whites, when playing Pileæi dance?
When it starts to
played, the floor is open.
White people are crazy, young peel.
The song is tricky, is speeding up.
I do not know what's gonna happen.
I have a song for you
I think the national anthem whites.
I walked down Sunset Boulevard...
in Los Angeles.
And the club is noænog heard the song.
So loudly that èulo on the street.
Whites walked, passing
car, and then suddenly Koei
play"YMCA"
White people are crazy when you hear it.
Stop circuits
in the middle of Sunset Boulevard
out of the car, and not just play!
They play like this...
People Trumpet...
Attempts"to me, asshole, I play YMCA"
All are played, and I saw how happy.
And I was very pleased.
I so enjoy the video and thought...
"It's whites, have fun!"
I was glad for you.
Then I was sorry.
Not because of you.
Because me and my people.
And other Asians.
Because our alphabet...
not for these songs.
Will never be Chinese
version of YMCA
Thank you, San Francisco, good night.
Russell Peters, ladies and gentlemen!
Russell Peters!
I think that they want more, do you want?
I do not hear you!
Here it is, folks, Russell Peters!
Since this will izaæi on DVD
and records for Comedy Central.
I do not know whether he wants to be on this part
Comedy Central, but it'll be on DVD.
And this is probably the last time
I'll talk it, because povlaèim.
No, imaæete DVD, a miser.
Listen, when the DVD comes out
I do not want to place it on the net
and then download it for free.
I know what you are.
Please buy it.
When comes out, buy it.
There must be some protection.
Some of you Scott, the developer, for sure.
See it:"I am, I am!"
"It's me!"
Now I'll do this for you.
Whites, I hope you enjoyed it so far.
I've a lot of talk about whites
but, I have a little more, because...
I want to talk about what you're parents.
Whenever I see on the news, I get upset it.
Tucite children"do not talk to them. "
Let them"."
Tucite jerk, that I want to say.
White, please tucite children.
For colored beating their children.
Your æale is Puerto Rican, mother a black woman,
must be received beating like crazy.
"My son, come on. "
"Why?"
"I know you did something while I was not there. "
Mexicans...
Indians will kill children if necessary.
We are the second largest population in the world.
Reproduction is not a problem.
Æaletova theory was...
"If I get rid of one,'ll make more. "
"Then I'll tell you what the new
the jerk was the last. "
You must tuæi children, please.
I know that many whites
do not beat, and I do not know why.
Tucite them, if they have, and you beat them
when you get home tonight...
When you turn off the DVD,
I want to go to deèiju room...
"Comrade, how are you, O sleeper?"
Already is, prespavaæe.
You must, I'll tell you why.
Because white children
now go to school with black
and the Indians, and Asians.
They go to school with mixed children.
And they all get beaten.
I stajaæe the playground, the zabavljajuæi.
I prièaæe how they got the ass.
Æale"isprašio me. "
"I was me. "
"I got the ass. "
Want to have your child feels left out?
Tucite it, not to be the social surplus.
"I was sent into the room. "
"You have a room?"
Tucite them, please
I'll tell you why yet.
Because...
When a white kid hanging out with colored
seek advice from him.
I can die if they hear it.
How to deal with parents.
When I was 10 years,
I am associated with Ryan.
Ryan had never beaten.
Not even even shouted at him, everything is allowed.
And nothing he would not have worked.
But he was angry kid.
Once we are after
went to school with him...
"Ryan, prepare the room. "
"Fuck you, bitch!"
A mom's gonna:"What I'm with him?"
Kill him from the beating.
"Ryan, you can not so enticing. "
"I can, it is a jackass!"
"Do not say it, udariæe you. "
"It will not be. "
"What are you talking about, mate. "
"I am fighting. "
"Well, next time tell them to bugger off. "
I'm sure you"?"
"Believe me, I succeeded. "
I went home.
The last time.
Entered the house...
"Race, opera courts. "
"Fuck you, Dad!"
"What are we to say?"
"Lièim you to Ryan Mom?"
"Somebody's going to hurt. "
It was my father's threat.
Before you beat me.
Each time,"race, someone's going to hurt. "
I hated the threat.
You know why, because
they always said one.
Never it's you.
I mean, I know that I am.
But I had hoped...
"Race, someone's going to hurt. "
"One. "
"I will not say who. "
"I think I know him well. "
And I pray that my brother.
"Please, isprebijaj Julia. "
After a few days ago, I met Ryan.
"Your plan is almost killed me. "
"Sorry, mate. Something I
forgot to tell you. "
"If it continues, threatens social services. "
"Why?"
"If you call, your dad will take. "
Imaæe"problem, do not you
to call, just right. "
Usraæe"is. "
You've got 10 years, find out
how to scare æaleta.
It's like you found Kriptonit.
I tried, when he went æale next time...
"Do not. "
I'll call"social. "
You know when you break?
"What are you going?"
I'll call"social. "
"Really?"
"If you bring your phone, dude. "
What do you do"?"
"If you call, you're in trouble. "
"Maybe in a little. "
"But I know that they need 22 minutes to arrive. "
During this time,"... "
"Somebody's going to hurt. "
Thank you very much, good night!
Subtitle by Gattu1989