Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Neighbours heard them
screaming at each other...
Iike,for two hours.
Nothing new.
Then they heard the gun go off,
both barrels.
Crime of passion.
Just look at all
the passion on that wall.
Well, it's a done deal,
all but the paperwork.
The kid see it?
-What?
-The kid.
What kind of
fucking question is that?
We are all going
to be real glad...
when we get rid of you,
Somerset.
It's always
these questions with you.
"Did the kid see it?"
Who gives a fuck?
He's dead.
His wife killed him.
Anything else,
it has nothing to do with us.
Detective Somerset?
I'm Detective Mills.
Lieutenant,
I apologize for interrupting.
I get in town 20 minutes ago,
they dump me here.
Look, Mills?
I thought we might
find a bar someplace.
I'd like to get to the precinct,
if it's all the same.
Not much time
for this transition thing.
I meant to ask you something...
when we spoke
on the phone before.
-Why here?
-I don't follow.
Well, all this effort
to get transferred.
It's the first question
that popped into my head.
I guess the same reasons
as you had...
before you decided to quit,
yeah?
You just met me.
Maybe I'm not understanding
the question.
It's very simple.
You actually fought
to get reassigned here.
I've just never seen it
done that way before.
I thought
I could do some good.
It would be great for me
if we didn't start out...
kicking each other
in the balls.
But you're calling the shots,
Lieutenant.
Yes. I want you to look,
and I want you to listen.
I wasn't guarding the Taco Bell.
I've worked Homicide five years.
-Not here.
-I understand that.
Over the next seven days,
Detective...
you'll do me the favour
of remembering that.
Say it again.
I thought we moved here
to get away from tractor pulls.
Serpico's got to go.
You might want to get rid of
this little crusty eye, Serpico.
-Did you get it?
-Got it.
Good.
Coffee? No?
Nothing's been touched.
Everything's like I found it.
What time was death established?
Like I said,
I didn't touch anything...
but he's had his face
in a plate of spaghetti...
for about
forty-five minutes now.
No one bothers with vital signs?
Did I stutter?
This guy ain't breathing...
unless he started
breathing spaghetti sauce.
So that's how
it's done around here?
I beg your pardon, Detective...
this guy's sitting in
a pile of his own piss and shit.
If he wasn't dead,
he would have stood up by now.
Thank you, Officer.
Thank you.
I wonder...
What exactly was the point...
of the conversation
you were about to get into?
Don't know. How many times
has Barney Fife...
found dead bodies
that weren't dead?
Drop it.
Somebody phone Guinness.
I think we've got a record here.
"Better Homes and Gardens."
Who said this was murder?
No one.
His heart has got to be
the size of a canned ham.
If this isn't a coronary...
well, I don't know.
How about that?
We had this case once...
guy dead on the ground,
knife in his back.
Got to be murder, right?
Fuck.
Anyway, big insurance policy
involved, yeah?
The guy took
the tip of the blade...
stuck it in
his own shoulder blades.
Must've screwed up a few times.
There was multiples.
Could you please be quiet?
Wait a minute.
What?
-Got a bucket here.
-What's in it?
Oh, God! Fucking vomit.
Any blood in it?
I didn't see any.
Help yourself.
Are you thinking it's poison?
Wonderful. Very moody.
Are you thinking
it's poison, Somerset?
You girls have got
Forensics waiting outside.
I don't know
if we'll all fit, though.
There's room.
Light's the problem. Hi.
Detective Mills, would you
go help the officers...
question the neighbours?
What?
Send in Forensics
on your way out, please.
He's dead.
Thank you, Doctor.
You've seen my files, right?
Things I've done?
Well, I did my time
walking the beat.
I did that shit for a long time.
And?
My badge says Detective,
the same as yours.
Look, I made a decision.
I had to consider
the integrity of the scene.
Couldn't worry
whether you thought...
you were getting enough time
on the playing field.
Hey, man...
just don't jerk me off.
That's all I ask.
Don't jerk me off.
He's been dead a long time...
and I can tell you
it was not a poison.
Oh, man.
How does someone
let themselves go like that?
It took four orderlies
just to get him on the table.
How'd the fat fuck
ever fit out his front door?
Please.
It's obvious he was a shut-in.
Look at this.
See how big this stomach is?
And the strange thing
is stretches.
Look at the size
of the cardiac orifice...
where the food...
I see,
but that means nothing to me.
He's got lines of distension
across the duodenum...
and the interior wall
is ripped open.
This man ate till he burst?
He didn't really burst,
not all the way...
but he was haemorrhaging
internally.
There was a haematoma
in the rectus.
So he did die by eating.
Yes and no.
What about
these bruises up here?
I haven't figured that out yet.
Gun pressed against his head?
Pressed hard enough, sure.
Fuck, yeah.
Marks from the front side
flush with the muzzle.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have ourselves a homicide.
Killer put a bucket beneath him,
kept on serving.
Took his time, too.
Coroner said this could've
gone on more than twelve hours.
Victim's throat was swollen,
probably from the effort...
and there was definitely a point
when he passed out.
The killer kicked him,
and he burst.
Sadistic fucker, huh?
When you want somebody dead,
you drive by and shoot them.
You don't risk the time
it takes to do this...
unless the act itself
has meaning.
Come on.
Somebody had a problem
with the fat boy...
and decided to torture him.
Simple as that.
In the grocery bags,
we found two receipts.
That means the killer
stopped in the middle...
and made a second trip
to the supermarket.
So?
Hey, man, it's his thing.
I've been out
in the rain all day.
This is beginning.
We've got one dead guy,
not three.
No motive.
Don't start your big brain
cooking on this. Please.
I'd like to be reassigned.
What? What in the hell
are you talking about?
This can't be my last duty.
It's just going to go on and on.
You're retiring.
Six more days
and you're all the way gone.
Won't be the first time
you've left unfinished business.
Those cases were taken as close
to conclusion as possible...
and if I may speak freely...
We're all friends here.
This should not be
his first assignment.
Come on! I knew it.
This is not
my first assignment, dick.
It's too soon for him.
I'm here. You can say
that shit to my face.
It's too soon.
Captain, if we can just talk
in private.
This isn't working.
It's a personal thing.
Shut up, Mills.
I don't have anyone else
to put on this.
This is Metro.
You don't get to swap.
-Give it to me.
-Say what?
He doesn't want it, fuck him.
Sorry. See you later.
Have a nice time.
Give it to me.
No. I'm putting you
on something else.
Go on, Mills. Just go on.
I'm sorry, old buddy...
but it looks like you're stuck
cleaning up the fat man.
All right. Here we go.
Quiet down. Calm down.
Calm down. Quiet down!
Now, here's
how it's going to be...
I'll answer questions
for ten minutes only.
If those questions
do not come...
in a calm, sane,
and orderly fashion...
I'm on my way out.
Detective?
Can I have a moment
of your time?
I will not discuss the details
of this ongoing investigation...
so don't bother asking.
There he is.
That's the guy.
It looks like
we won't be eating dinner.
Who is this kid, anyway?
Hotshot.
What have you guys got for me?
Nothing yet, boss.
Why don't you guys
go get a coffee?
We have
this breaking story for you.
We're going live downtown where
defence attorney Eli Gould...
was found murdered this morning.
District Attorney Martin Talbot
is taking questions.
Conflict of interest
between your office...
That is ridiculous
to the point of being offensive.
There is no conflict
whatsoever...
and any claim there could be
is irresponsible.
Is it true you're far from
apprehending a suspect?
I've come from a meeting
of law enforcement officials...
and they've assured me
their very best men are on this.
This will be the very definition
of swift justice.
Pardon me, George.
Come in.
Have you heard the news?
Haven't heard.
Eli Gould was found
murdered this morning.
Someone broke into his law firm
and bled him to death...
wrote the word "Greed"
on the floor.
-Greed?
-In blood.
Mills is heading up
the investigation.
Excuse me.
Could you not do that, please?
Well, good for him.
What in the hell are you
going to do with yourself...
out there, Somerset?
I'll work, maybe on a farm,
fix my house.
Don't you feel that feeling?
You're not going to be
a cop anymore.
That's the whole idea.
I don't think you're leaving.
Hell, you can't leave all this.
A guy's out walking his dog,
gets attacked.
His watch is taken, his wallet.
While he's lying there
on the sidewalk helpless...
his attacker stabs him
in both eyes.
This happened last night
about four blocks from here.
I read about it.
I don't understand
this place any longer.
It's the way it's always been.
Maybe you're right.
You do this work,
you were made for it...
and I don't think
you can deny that.
Maybe I'm wrong.
The coroner sent
this down for you.
Found them in the fat boy's
stomach mixed with the food.
Looks like plastic.
Set them on the desk, please.
They were fed to him.
Oh, Lord.
This was found on the wall
behind the refrigerator...
at the obesity murder scene.
"Long is the way and hard...
"that out of Hell
leads up to light."
It's from Milton.
"Paradise Lost."
All right. I'm confused.
It means that this is beginning.
This was found behind
the same refrigerator...
written in grease.
There are seven deadly sins,
Captain.
Gluttony...
greed...
sloth, wrath, pride, lust...
and envy. Seven.
Hold on.
This is not even my desk.
You can expect
five more of these.
Now wait a minute.
I can't get involved in this.
He wanted it.
Damn.
I'm all over it.
Where you headed?
Far away from here.
Thanks, George.
How you doing?
I've got a few things
to look up.
Sit where you'd like.
How's everybody?
Hi there, Smiley.
Come on, George.
Your cards are getting cold.
Duty calls.
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
I'll never understand.
All these books...
a world of knowledge
at your fingertips.
What do you do?
Play poker all night.
We got culture!
We got culture
coming out our ass.
All right!
How's this for culture?
Smiley,
you really going to miss us.
I just might.
Fucking Dante.
Goddamned poetry-rhyming
faggot piece of shit!
Fucker!
Good work, Officer.
Thank you, Lord.
Sorry.
Be out of your way in a second.
You want your chair?
No. You go right ahead.
Phone.
It's a package deal.
It comes with the office.
Are you OK?
ls something wrong?
You dingleberry.
I told you
not to call me at work.
Yeah. Why? Why?
-It's my wife.
-Sorry?
She'd like to speak to you.
This is Detective Somerset.
Well, it's nice
to talk to you, too.
I appreciate the offer, but...
Well, in that case,
I'd be delighted.
Yes, thank you very much.
Hon, what...
-Well?
-Sorry?
I've been invited to
a late supper at your apartment.
-I accepted.
-How's that?
Tonight.
Hello, men.
-Hi, loser.
-Hi, idiot.
This is Tracy.
Tracy, Somerset.
Happy to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you.
Except, of course,
your first name.
It's William.
It's a good name, William.
William,
I'd like you to meet David.
David, this is William.
I'll be right back.
How are the kids?
Good.
They're in their room.
Come on in.
Oh, good dogs!
How are you?
-Smells good.
-What?
The...
Yeah. I mean, thank you.
Please, have a seat.
Would you like something
to drink?
No, thanks. I'll wait.
Just throw that anywhere.
Excuse all this mess.
We're still unpacking.
I understand you two
were high-school sweethearts.
Pretty hokey, huh?
You know something?
I knew on our first date
I was going to marry him.
Really?
He was the funniest guy
I'd ever met.
Really?
Well, it's kind of rare
nowadays, you know...
that level of commitment.
Don't worry.
I won't wear it
to the dinner table.
No matter how often
I see guns...
I can't get used to them.
Same here.
Why aren't you married, William?
Trace. What the hell?
I was close once.
Just didn't happen.
It surprises me.
It really does.
Anyone who spends a significant
amount of time with me...
finds me disagreeable.
Ask your husband.
Very, very true.
So how long have you lived here?
Too long.
How are you liking it?
You know,
takes time to settle in.
It'll be good.
You get numb after a while.
There are things to any city...
The subway.
It'll go away in a minute.
It's nothing.
That real-estate guy.
Fucking piece of...
Sorry, hon.
Shows us the place
a few times.
I think it's good.
Trace likes it.
Then I start wondering
why he only brings us here...
five minutes at a time.
We found out the first night.
The soothing, relaxing,
vibrating home, huh?
I'm sorry.
All right, laugh it up.
I don't know what
you're laughing at.
All right already.
The guy had to get
into the building...
before the office was closed
and security tightened.
Gould would have been
working late.
I'm certain.
Biggest defence lawyer in town.
Infamous, really.
The body was found
Tuesday morning.
The office was closed Monday.
The guy could have
gotten in on Friday...
Iaid low till
the cleaning crew left...
and had his way all day
Saturday, Sunday, maybe Monday.
Look at this.
Gould was bound,
his right arm free.
He was handed
a butcher's knife.
Check out the scale.
A pound of flesh?
"One pound of flesh,
no more, no less.
"No cartilage, no bone,
but only flesh."
-"Merchant of Venice."
-Didn't see it.
"His task done,
then he would go free."
That chair
was soaked with sweat.
Of course.
The killer would have
wanted Gould to take his time...
to sit and decide
which cut to make first.
Imagine it--
there's a gun in your face.
Which part of your body
is expendable?
How about the love handle?
Cut along the side
of his own stomach.
Let's take a fresh look
at these.
Even though the corpse is there,
look through it.
Edit out the initial shock.
The trick is to find
one item, one detail...
and focus on it until
it's an exhausted possibility.
I'm going to get another beer.
Beer?
Wine, please.
He's preaching.
He's punishing.
The sins were used
in medieval sermons.
There were
seven cardinal virtues...
and seven deadly sins
used as teaching tools.
Like in "The Parson's Tale,"
and what's-his...Dante.
-You read them.
-Parts.
Remember in "Purgatory,"
Dante and his buddy...
they're climbing up the hill,
checking out the sinners?
Yeah. The Seven Terraces
of Purgation.
Right, but pride comes first,
not gluttony.
Let's consider that the books
were the inspiration.
The sermons were
about atonement for sin.
These murders
are like forced attrition.
-Forced what?
-Attrition.
When you regret your sins
but not because you love God.
Because someone's sticking
a fucking gun in your face.
No fingerprints.
Totally unrelated victims.
And no witnesses of any kind.
Which I don't get because
the fucker had to get back out.
In any major city, minding
your own business is a science.
First thing they teach women
in rape prevention...
is never cry for help.
Always yell "Fire."
Nobody answers "Help."
Holler "Fire,"
they come running.
That's fucked up.
Must have left
another puzzle piece.
Know what? Thank you
for talking this out...
but I got to sleep,
walk the dogs.
This is to satisfy my curiosity.
I'm still leaving
at the end of the week.
Shit. Wait.
Gould's wife was out of town...
except this means
she saw something.
What if it's a threat?
I put her in a safe house.
She wasn't happy about it.
What if it isn't
something she has seen...
but something
she's supposed to see...
but hasn't been given a chance?
-What?
-I don't know.
But that's the one thing.
Sign us in.
We've got to see Mrs. Gould.
We want you to have
a phone line, but...
Mrs. Gould?
Mrs. Gould, I am sorry.
I truly am.
I don't understand.
I need you to look at each photo
very carefully.
See if there's anything strange
or out of place...
anything at all.
-I don't see anything.
-You sure?
Please, I can't do this
right now!
It's got to be now.
There may be something
we haven't seen.
-Wait.
-What?
Here.
This painting is upside down.
You sure your men
didn't move this?
No. Those shots were taken
before Forensics.
Nothing.
There's got to be something.
Moved the screws to rehang it.
What the fuck is that?
Switchblade.
God damn it!
Must be something.
He didn't paint
the fucking thing.
Now he's fucking with us.
That's what he's doing.
See this? This is us.
Just wait a minute.
Now Somerset's
climbing on the furniture.
Just wait a minute.
You're kidding me.
Call the print lab.
Oh, man.
Honestly, have you ever
seen anything like this?
I can tell you just by looking
at the swirl pattern...
they're not
the victim's fingerprints.
I don't know, man.
I'd say he's whacked enough.
Doesn't fit.
He doesn't want us
to help him stop.
Who knows?
Freaks doing evil deeds
they don't want to do.
"Voices made me do it.
My dog made me do it.
"Jodie Foster
told me to do it."
I've seen this take
three days to make a match...
so maybe you want to cross
your fingers somewhere else.
You meant what you said
to Mrs. Gould...
about catching this guy?
I wish I still thought
the way you do.
Why don't you tell me...
what the hell it is
you think we're doing?
Picking up the pieces.
We're collecting
all the evidence...
taking all the pictures
and samples...
writing everything down...
noting the time things happen.
That's all?
That's all.
Putting everything
into neat little piles...
and filing it away
on the off chance...
it will ever be needed
in the courtroom.
Picking up diamonds
on a deserted island...
saving them
in case we get rescued.
Bullshit.
Even the most promising clues
usually only lead to others.
So many corpses
roll away unrevenged.
Don't tell me you didn't get
that rush tonight.
I saw you.
We're getting somewhere.
Wake up, Glimmer Twins.
You've got a winner.
This guy goes by the name
of Victor.
His real name is Theodore Allen.
His prints were found
by Homicide.
He's got a long history
of serious mental illness.
His parents gave him a strict
Southern Baptist upbringing...
but somewhere they fell short.
Victor dabbled in drugs,
armed robbery, assault...
spent time in prison here
for attempted rape of a minor...
but his lawyer saw to it
that didn't last long.
His lawyer is Eli Gould,
the Greed murder victim.
We're going to finish
this today.
Victor's been
out of circulation...
but there's still
a residence in his name.
You're not buying all this,
are you?
-Doesn't seem like our guy.
-You tell me.
Our killer seems
to have more purpose.
You ever take a bullet?
Never in my thirty-four years,
knock wood.
I've only taken my gun out
three times...
with the intention of using it.
Never pulled the trigger.
Not once. You?
Yeah, but--
No, I never took a bullet...
but I pulled my gun once,
shot it once.
Really?
It was my first one of these.
Secondary unit.
I was shaky going in.
I was a rookie.
We bust open the door
looking for this junkie...
and the fucker opened fire.
One cop got hit in the arm.
Christ, what was his name?
Spun him like a top.
I mean, more like slow motion.
I remember
riding in that ambulance.
Well, he died right there.
Right there.
Christ,
what was his fucking name?
SWAT goes before dicks.
Here.
They love this.
Police!
Clear!
Good morning, sweetheart.
Get up now, motherfucker.
Now!
Get up, you sack of shit.
Fuck me. Dicks!
You want to come
take a look at this!
Dicks!
Jesus. Victor?
That's just Victor.
-Call an ambulance.
-A hearse, more like it.
Get your people out of here.
No one touches anything!
Some kind of freaking
wax sculpture or something.
"Sloth."
Oh, man. God damn.
This picture
was dated three days ago.
This must be
the first one. Look.
It's dated exactly
one year ago today.
I got a hair sample,
a stool sample, piss.
I got fingernails.
He's laughing at us.
You got what you deserved.
He's alive! He's alive!
That cocksucker's alive!
Calm down!
Emergency on that ambulance!
-He's playing games.
-No shit.
We have to divorce ourselves
from emotion.
We have to remain focused
on the details.
Man, I feed off my emotions.
-Are you listening?
-I hear you.
Excuse me.
Closed crime scene.
Get the fuck out.
I got a right.
Get out of here,
piece of shit!
I got your picture, man.
Detective Mills.
M-i-l-l-s! Fuck off!
-I'm surprised you can spell.
-Fuck you!
How do they get here
so fucking quick?
They pay police for
the information and pay well.
Hey, man, I'm sorry.
Well, he pissed me off.
It's impressive to see a man
feeding off his emotions.
A year of immobility
seems about right...
judging by the deterioration
of the spine muscles.
Blood tests show many drugs
in his system...
even an antibiotic to keep
bedsores from infecting.
Has he tried to speak
or communicate in any way?
Even if his brain
were not mush...
he chewed off
his own tongue long ago.
Doctor...
is there absolutely no chance
he might survive?
Detective,
he'd die of shock right now...
if you shined
a flashlight in his eyes.
He's experienced about
as much pain and suffering...
as anyone I've encountered,
give or take...
and he still has Hell
to look forward to.
Good night.
Hello, William?
It's Tracy.
Is everything all right?
Yes, everything's fine.
Where's David?
He's in the other room
in the shower.
I'm sorry to call you like this.
It's all right.
What can I do for you?
I...
I need someone to talk to.
Do you think
you could meet me...
somewhere
maybe tomorrow morning?
I don't understand.
I feel stupid calling...
but you're the only person
that I know here.
There's no one else.
If you can,
just give me a call.
I have to go now.
Good night.
It can be a hard place.
I don't know
why I asked you to come.
Why don't you talk to him
about it?
Tell him how you feel.
I can't be a burden...
especially now.
I'll get used to things.
I think I just wanted to talk
to someone who's lived here...
for a long time.
I mean, upstate...
it's a completely
different environment.
Really.
Did David tell you
that I teach fifth grade?
Well, I did.
He mentioned it.
I'm going around,
looking at schools...
but the conditions here
are horrible.
What about private schools?
I don't know.
Why don't you tell me
what's really bothering you?
David and I
are going to have a baby.
I don't think I'm the one
to talk to about this.
I hate this city.
I had a relationship once.
It was very much
like a marriage.
We got pregnant.
This was a long time ago.
I remember getting up
one morning and going to work...
just another day
like any other...
except it was the first day...
after I knew
about the pregnancy.
And I felt this fear
for the first time ever.
I remember thinking...
how can I bring a child
into a world like this?
How can a person grow up
with all this around them?
I told her I didn't
want to have it...
And over the next few weeks,
I wore her down.
I want to have children.
I can tell you now...
I know--I mean...
I'm positive I made
the right decision...
but there's not a day
that passes...
that I don't wish
I'd made a different choice.
If you don't keep...
the baby...
if that's your decision...
don't ever tell him
you were pregnant.
But if you choose
to have this baby...
you spoil that kid
every chance you get.
That's about all the advice
I can give you.
I got to go.
Thank you.
Victor's landlord said cash
was in the office mailbox...
the first of every month.
"I never heard
a single complaint...
"from the tenant
in apartment 306...
"and nobody ever
complained about him.
"He was the best tenant
I've ever had."
A landlord's dream...
a paralysed tenant
with no tongue.
Who pays the rent on time.
I'm sick of all this waiting.
This is the job.
Why aren't we out there?
Why sit here rotting
till the lunatic does it again?
It's dismissive
to call him a lunatic.
Don't make that mistake.
He's insane. Look.
He's probably dancing around
in his grandma's panties...
rubbing himself
in peanut butter.
How's that?
I don't think so.
His luck will run out.
He's not depending on luck.
We walked into that apartment
exactly one year...
after he tied Victor to the bed.
He wanted us to.
You don't know that for sure.
Yes, we do.
This note he left,
his first words to us.
"Long is the way and hard...
"that out of Hell
leads up to light."
Fuck him. So what?
He's right so far.
Imagine the will it takes...
to keep a man bound
for a full year...
to sever his hand and use it
to plant fingerprints...
to insert tubes
into his genitals.
This guy's methodical,
exacting...
and worst of all, patient.
He's a nut-bag.
Just because the fucker's
got a library card...
doesn't make him Yoda.
How much money you got?
I got fifty bucks.
I propose a field trip.
Come on.
We'll make a list.
We'll put "Purgatory,"
"Canterbury Tales..."
anything relating to
the Seven Deadly Sins.
What would he study
to do the things he's done?
What are his interests now?
Jack the Ripper?
-Where are we going?
-The library.
Coupons. Free coupons.
Discount coupons.
They must have had
fifty health violations...
during their last inspection.
Could you at least
sit across from me?
I don't want people
thinking we're dating.
Give me your money.
I'm giving you this...
but I ought to know
what we're doing.
Fuck.
Hey, Somerset.
How are you?
I didn't expect
a mnage  trois.
It's not a problem.
Sit down.
Only for you do I do this.
It's a big risk.
We're fair and square.
-It's a deal.
-All right.
About an hour.
Help yourself.
That was money well spent.
All right.
By telling you this...
I'm trusting you
more than most people.
Good, because I'm about
ready to punch you.
It's probably nothing...
but it's no skin
off our teeth.
The guy in the pizza parlour
is a friend from the Bureau.
Who? Stinky Man?
For years, the FBI has been
into the library system...
keeping records.
-Assessing fines.
-Monitoring reading habits.
Look, certain books are flagged.
Say, nuclear weapons
or "Mein Kampf."
Anyone who checks out
a flagged book...
has his library records
fed into FBI computers.
Wait. How is this legal?
Legal, illegal--
these terms don't apply.
You can't use
the information directly.
It's just a useful guide.
It might sound silly, but you
can't get a library card...
without an l.D.
and a phone bill.
-So they run a list.
-Precisely.
If you want to know
who's reading "Purgatory"...
and "Paradise Lost"
and "Helter Skelter"...
the FBl's computers
will tell us.
Could give us a name.
It could get a college kid...
writing a term paper
on Twentieth-Century crime.
At least you're
out of the office.
Get a haircut.
-How do you know all this?
-I don't.
Neither do you.
Exactly.
"The Divine Comedy,"
"The History of Catholicism."
There's a book called
"Murderers and Madmen."
"Modern Homicide lnvestigation,"
"In Cold Blood..."
"Of Human Bondage." Bondage?
Not what you're thinking.
-Marquis de Sharday.
-Marquis de Sade.
Whatever. Writings of
St. Thomas Aqua-something.
Saint Thomas Aquinas.
He wrote about
the Seven Deadly Sins.
Is that it?
Let's try it.
-Jonathan Doe?
-Whatever.
We're sure about that name?
You saw the list. John Doe.
You wanna go back,
I'll go back.
Let's take a look at him.
Talk to him.
This is crazy.
We'll just talk to him.
Excuse me, sir.
Are you, by any chance,
a serial killer?
You do the talking.
Put that silver tongue to work.
Have you been talking
to my wife?
This is retarded.
Charlie's fucking Angels.
Name off a computer.
You're hit.
He's going down!
Fifth floor!
Mommy! Mommy!
Police.
Is there a back exit?
Lock your door.
What's going on?
Get out of
the fucking hall, please.
Get down!
Get the fuck down!
Shit.
Shut the fuck up down there!
God damn it!
Fuck.
Taxi!
Get out of
the fucking way! Move!
-Are you OK?
-I'm all right.
-Where are you going?
-I'm going in.
Wait, wait, wait.
What are you talking about?
He fucking shot at us.
-We need a warrant.
-Probable cause.
How did we get here?
I can't tell anyone.
I can't tell about the Bureau.
We have no reason to be here.
-Listen to me!
-Get the fuck off me!
I'm sorry,
but just pay attention.
If we leave a hole like this,
we can't prosecute.
The guy will walk.
Is that what you want?
By the time we get the warrant--
Fuck that! No!
We need a reason
to knock on this door!
Think about it!
You're right.
I'm all fucked up.
Well...
No point in arguing anymore...
unless you can fix that.
You stupid son of a...
How much money we got left?
So, I noticed this guy...
going out a lot when the murders
was happening...
so l...
You called
Detective Somerset, right?
Right, so I called
the detective...
'cause he looked
creepy and shit.
And one of the murders
happened right over there.
OK. I told you the rest.
You got to sign it.
Good, good, good.
All right.
-You did good.
-I did what you said.
Here.
You get something to eat.
Everybody stay outside.
Victor.
Fuck.
-What?
-We had him.
What are you talking about?
It was the fucking photographer
on the stairs.
We had him,
and we let him go.
You're sure this is him?
Yeah. Good, good.
We've got nothing to go on.
No address books.
Just this receipt.
Then keep looking.
This was under the bed--
his only source of funds.
We got his money.
Fucking-A. Good work.
One more thing
you won't believe.
We haven't found
a fingerprint, not one.
I don't believe you.
Keep looking.
We could use some more men.
I'm doing the best I can.
What's all this?
There are 2,000 notebooks
on these shelves.
Each contains about 250 pages.
Forget it.
Anything about the killings?
"What sick, ridiculous,
puppets we are.
"What a gross little stage
we dance on.
"What fun we have
dancing, fucking...
"not a care in the world...
"not knowing
that we are nothing.
"We are not what was intended."
No, wait.
There's a lot more.
"On the subway today...
"a man started
a conversation with me.
"He made small talk...
"a lonely man
talking about the weather.
"I tried to be pleasant
and accommodating...
"but my head began
to hurt from his banality.
"I almost didn't notice
it had happened...
"but I suddenly threw up
all over him.
"He was not pleased...
"and I couldn't stop laughing."
No dates.
Placed on the shelves
in no discernible order.
Just his mind
poured out on paper.
Looks like a life's work.
Even with fifty men reading,
it would take two months.
I know, I know.
Where's that phone?
Phone?
People, quiet!
I admire you.
I don't know
how you found me...
but imagine my surprise.
I respect you law enforcement
agents more every day.
I appreciate that, John.
-I tell you...
-No, you listen.
I'll be readjusting
my schedule...
in light of
today's little setback.
I just had to call
and express my admiration.
I'm sorry I had to hurt
one of you...
but I didn't
have a choice, did l?
Will you accept my apology?
I would say more,
but I'd ruin the surprise.
I'll be readjusting
my schedule...
in light of
today's little setback.
Got it.
All right,
everybody back to work.
You were right.
He's preaching.
Yeah. These murders
are his sermons to us.
Look, we know him, him, him.
Who's the blonde?
Looks like a pro.
Maybe she caught John Doe's eye.
He collected it last night.
Last night? This man?
John Doe. Easy name.
He had a limp.
What was the job
you did for him?
I've got a picture.
One sweet piece.
I thought he was one of them
performance artists.
Sort of guy that pisses
in a cap onstage...
and then drinks it.
Performance art.
I think I undercharged him,
actually.
You made this for him?
I've made weirder shit
than that. So what?
They found the blonde.
The picture!
Fucking pigs!
Get the fuck
out of the booth, pal!
I've been in this cage
the whole time!
Come on. This way!
Can you do something
about this music?
We're working on it.
We're looking for the guy.
You from Homicide?
Better see this.
Stay still, all right?
God, get this thing off of me!
Get him out of here now!
Come on.
I want to hear it again.
Tell me again.
You heard nothing strange?
Saw nothing strange?
He asked if I was married,
and I could see he had a gun.
Where was the girl?
The what? What?
The girl. The prostitute.
Where was she?
Someone comes
to your establishment...
they want to go downstairs
to get a little whatever...
they got to come to you?
You didn't see anyone
with a package...
a knapsack,
something under their arm?
Everybody
that comes in there...
has got a package
under their arms.
Some guys are carrying
suitcases full of stuff.
She was just sitting
on the bed.
Who tied her down,
you or him?
Do you like
what you do for a living?
These things you see?
No. No, I don't.
But that's life, isn't it?
He had a gun...
and he made it happen.
He made me do it.
He put that thing on me.
Then he made me wear it.
Then he told me to fuck her.
And I did. I fucked her!
Oh, God.
He had a gun in my mouth.
The fucking gun
was in my throat!
Fuck!
Oh, God! God!
God, help me. Please.
Please help me!
This isn't going
to have a happy ending.
Hey, man. We catch him,
I'll be happy enough.
If we catch John Doe...
and he turns out
to be Satan himself...
that might live up
to our expectations, but...
he's not the devil.
He's just a man.
You bitch and you complain
and tell me these things and...
If you're preparing me
for hard times...
thank you, but...
But you got to be a hero.
You want to be a champion.
People don't want a champion.
They want cheeseburgers,
lotto, and television.
How did you get like this?
I want to know.
Well...
It wasn't one thing,
I can tell you that.
Go on.
I just don't think
I can continue...
to live in a place
that embraces...
and nurtures apathy
as if it was a virtue.
You're no different,
no better.
I didn't say I was.
I'm not.
Hell, I sympathize completely.
Apathy is a solution.
It's easier to lose
yourself in drugs...
than it is to cope with life.
It's easier to steal
what you want than earn it.
It's easier to beat a child
than raise it.
Hell, love costs,
takes effort, work.
We are talking about people
who are mentally ill...
people who are fucking crazies.
-No, we're not.
-Yes, today.
We're talking about
everyday life here.
You can't afford
to be this naive.
Fuck off.
You should listen to yourself.
"The problem with people
is that they don't care...
"so I don't care about people."
That makes no sense.
-You care?
-Damn right.
And you're going to
make a difference.
Whatever.
The point is...
is that I don't
think you're quitting...
because you believe
these things you say.
I think you want
to believe them...
because you're quitting.
You want me to agree with you
and say, "Yeah, you're right.
"It's all fucked up.
It's a fucking mess.
"We should all go live
in a fucking log cabin."
But I won't say that.
I don't agree with you.
I do not.
I can't.
I'm going to go home.
Thank you, though.
I love you, honey, so much.
So much.
I know.
Nine-one-one.
What's your emergency?
Could you repeat that?
I've gone and done it again.
What have you got?
Sleeping pills...
glued to one hand.
Telephone glued to the other.
You see what he did?
He sliced her up,
then he bandaged her.
Call for help,
and you'll live disfigured...
or you can put yourself
out of your own misery.
Come on.
Cut off her nose.
To spite her face.
He did it very recently.
I've decided to stay on
till this is done.
One of two things will happen.
Either we'll get John Doe...
or he'll finish
his series of seven...
and this case
will go on for years.
You don't have
to do me any favours.
Thank you, but...
Keep me as your partner
a few more days.
You'll be doing me a favour.
You knew I'd say yes.
Hey, we're here.
Your wife called.
Get yourself
an answering machine.
Detective.
After this, I'm gone.
No big surprise.
Detective!
You're looking for me.
Don't fucking move!
On the floor!
Keep away from him!
I know you.
Now! Get down!
Get down!
On your stomach!
You piece of shit!
Now! All the way!
All the way, fucker!
Down! Faster!
Faster, fucker! Now!
Nose on the ground!
Jesus Christ.
What the fuck is this?
I'd like to speak
to my lawyer, please.
God damn it!
He cuts the skin
off his fingers.
That's why we couldn't
find one usable print.
He's been doing it
for quite some time.
What about the trace
on his bank accounts?
So far everything's
a dead end.
No credit history,
no employment records.
His bank account's
only five years old.
It was started with cash.
We're even trying
to trace his furniture.
The only thing we know
about that guy right now...
is he's independently
wealthy, well-educated...
and totally insane.
Because he's John Doe by choice.
When do we question him?
You don't.
He's going to court now.
There's no way he would
just turn himself in.
It doesn't make any sense.
There he sits.
It's not supposed to make sense.
He's not finished.
He's pissing in our faces
and we're taking it.
You know what
I'm talking about.
For the first time ever,
we are in total agreement.
So what the fuck, man?
He's two murders away
from completing his masterpiece.
We'll wait for his plea.
My client says
there are two more bodies...
two more victims hidden away.
He will take Detectives
Mills and Somerset to them...
but only Detectives
Mills and Somerset...
only at 6.00 today.
Why us?
He says he admires you.
It's part of the game.
My client claims
if they do not accept...
these bodies
will never be found.
Frankly, counsel,
I'm inclined to let them rot.
We've got him downstairs,
locked up, done deal.
He'll get room and board,
cable TV.
Hell, my wife doesn't
even have cable.
Why are we having
this conversation?
Something stinks.
And this one here...
Yeah, you,
in your $3,000 suit...
and that smug smile,
dealing for that shit...
I am required by law
to serve my clients.
Jesus Christ.
And their best interests.
We don't make deals here.
My client says
if you do not accept...
he will plead insanity.
Let him try it.
I'd like to see him try.
With the nature
of these crimes...
I could get him off
with such a plea.
I'm not letting
this conviction slide.
If you do accept,
under his specific conditions...
he will sign a full confession,
plead guilty right now.
It's your case.
Make a decision.
Full confession. I'm in.
It has to be the both of you.
If he were to claim insanity...
this conversation
is admissible...
the fact he's blackmailing us
with his plea.
My client reminds you
two more are dead.
The press would have
a field day if the police...
didn't seem too concerned
about finding them.
If there are two more dead.
The lab report came.
Quickie on Doe's clothing.
They found blood from Doe
slicing his fingers...
blood from the woman
whose face he cut off...
and blood from a third party,
as yet unidentified.
You'd be escorting
an unarmed man.
Let's finish it.
If John Doe's head opens
and a UFO flies out...
I want you
to have expected it.
I will.
Man, if I was to accidentally
shave off a nipple...
would it be covered
by workman's comp?
I suppose so.
If you were man enough
to file a claim...
I'd buy you one
out of my own pocket.
I keep coming home late...
my wife's going to think
something's up.
You know...
What?
Let's go!
Spin it around!
There he is.
Late model black sedan
at ten o'clock.
Who are you, John?
Who are you really?
What do you mean?
At this stage...
what harm can it do
to tell us about yourself?
Doesn't matter. Who I am
means absolutely nothing.
You need to stay
on your left up here.
So where are we heading?
You'll see.
We're not just going
to two more bodies, are we?
That wouldn't be
shocking enough.
We've got newspapers
to think about, yeah?
Wanting people to listen...
you can't just tap them
on the shoulder anymore.
You have to hit them
with a sledge hammer.
Then you'll notice you've got
their strict attention.
But the question is...
what makes you so special
that people should listen?
I'm not special.
I've never been exceptional.
This is, though,
what I'm doing.
My work.
Your work, John?
I don't see anything special
about it, John.
That's not true.
No, it is true,
and the funny thing is...
all this work,
two months from now...
no one's going to give a shit
or remember.
You can't see
the whole complete act yet...
but when this is done...
when it's finished...
it's going to be...
People will barely
be able to comprehend...
but they won't be able to deny.
Could the freak
be any more vague?
As far as master plans go...
I can't wait for you to see.
It's going to be something.
I'm going to be
right next to you...
so when this big thing happens,
let me know.
I wouldn't want to miss it.
Don't worry. You won't.
You won't miss a thing.
Roger. Going south.
Keep two miles separation.
Roger.
What's so exciting?
It's not too far now.
I've been trying to figure
something in my head.
Maybe you can help me out?
When a person is insane,
as you clearly are...
do you know
that you're insane?
Maybe you're reading
"Guns & Ammo..."
masturbating
in your own faeces...
do you stop and go...
"Wow, it is amazing
how fucking crazy I really am"?
Do you guys do that?
It's more comfortable
for you to label me insane.
It's very comfortable.
It's not something
I'd expect you to accept...
but I did not choose.
I was chosen.
Whatever.
I don't doubt
that you believe that...
but seems to me...
you're overlooking
a glaring contradiction.
Meaning what?
Glad you asked.
If you were chosen
by a higher power...
and if your hand was forced,
seems strange to me...
you would get
such enjoyment out of it.
You enjoyed torturing
those people.
Just doesn't seem in keeping
with martyrdom, does it?
I doubt
I enjoyed it any more...
than Detective Mills would
enjoy time alone with me...
in a room without windows.
Isn't that true?
How happy would it make you
to hurt me with impunity?
That hurts my feelings.
You wouldn't only because
there's consequences.
It's in those eyes of yours,
though.
Nothing wrong with a man
taking pleasure in his work.
I won't deny
my own personal desire...
to turn each sin
against the sinner.
I thought all you did
was kill innocent people.
Innocent?
ls that supposed to be funny?
An obese man, a disgusting man
who could barely stand up...
who you'd point
out to friends...
so they could join you
in mocking him.
If you saw him
while you were eating...
you wouldn't be able
to finish your meal.
After him,
I picked the lawyer...
and you both must have
secretly been thanking me.
This man dedicated his life
to making money by lying...
with every breath
that he could muster...
to keeping murderers
and rapists on the streets!
Murderers.
Murderers, John, like yourself.
A woman so ugly inside
that she couldn't bear living...
if she couldn't be beautiful
on the outside.
A drug dealer...
a drug-dealing pederast,
actually.
And let's not forget
the disease-spreading whore.
Only in a world this shitty...
could you even try to say
these were innocent people...
and keep a straight face.
But that's the point.
We see a deadly sin
on every street corner...
in every home...
and we tolerate it.
We tolerate it
because it's common...
it's trivial.
We tolerate it
morning, noon, and night.
Well, not anymore.
I'm setting the example...
and what I've done
is going to be puzzled over...
and studied...
and followed...
forever.
Delusions of grandeur.
You should be thanking me.
Why is that, John?
Because you're going to be
remembered after this.
Realize, Detective...
the only reason
that I'm here right now...
is that I wanted to be.
No. We would have
got you eventually.
Oh, really?
So, what were you doing?
Biding your time,
toying with me?
Allowing five innocent people
to die...
until you felt like
springing your trap?
What was
the indisputable evidence...
you were going to use on me
before I walked up to you...
and put my hands in the air?
John, calm down.
I seem to remember us
knocking on your door.
Oh, that's right.
And I seem to remember
breaking your face.
You're only alive
because I didn't kill you.
OK. Sit back.
I spared you.
Remember that every time
you look in the mirror...
at that face of yours
for the rest of your life...
or for the rest of what life
I've allowed you to have.
Sit back, you fucking freak!
Shut your fucking mouth!
You're no messiah.
You're a movie of the week.
You're a fucking T-shirt,
at best.
Don't ask me
to pity those people.
I don't mourn them any more
than the thousands that died...
at Sodom and Gomorrah.
Is that to say
what you were doing...
was God's good work?
The Lord works
in mysterious ways.
Do you see
those high-tension towers?
That's where we're headed.
I see where he's talking about.
Follow the access road.
-Your signal's breaking up.
-Un-fucking-avoidable, sir.
We're in Powerline City.
Deal with it.
There sure as shit
is no ambush out here.
No fucking nothing out here.
Can't land near those wires.
They're coming up behind us
in about two minutes.
Go up, way up.
Thirty seconds, back east.
On my mark. Thirty seconds.
I'm getting him out.
We've got you in sight.
Get out...
slowly.
Stop.
Stay.
What do you got?
Dead dog.
I didn't do that.
What time is it?
Why?
I'd like to know.
7.01 .
It's close.
Well, let's go take a look.
It's this way.
Bird Two, close your distance.
They're moving away
from the car.
We got them, we got them.
Closing in.
Negative, negative.
Down, down, down.
Watch him.
There he goes.
It's good we have
some time to talk.
Stay on the guy in red.
Do not take the cross hairs
off him!
There's a van coming
down the road from the north.
Be ready for anything now.
Wait for my signal.
Wait for me.
Get out of the van!
Out!
Jesus Christ, man.
Don't shoot me!
Step away!
Turn around.
Put your hands on your head!
What the hell is going on?
What are you doing here?
I'm just delivering
a package, man.
I got this package
for this guy David...
Detective David Mills.
Get it...
slowly.
He's opening
the back of the van.
We've got him in sight.
This guy paid me 500 bucks
to bring it out here, man.
He wanted it here
at exactly 7.00.
Put it down.
We got a box.
We got a box!
Call the bomb squad.
We got a box.
Face the van.
Hands up.
Turn around.
OK. Go.
Off you go. Go!
I'm sending the driver
out on foot.
He's headed north
along the road.
Have him picked up.
I don't know.
I'm going to open it.
When I said I admired you...
I meant what I said.
There's blood.
You've made quite a life
for yourself, Detective.
You should be very proud.
Shut the fuck up,
you piece of shit.
California,
stay away from here.
Stay away from here.
Don't come in here.
Whatever you hear, stay away.
John Doe has the upper hand.
Here he comes.
-Throw your gun down!
-What?
I wish I could have
lived like you did.
What the fuck you talking about?
Do you hear me, Detective?
I'm trying to tell you
how much I admire you...
and your pretty wife.
What?
Tracy.
What you fuckin' say?
It's disturbing how easily
a member of the press...
can purchase information
from the men in your precinct.
What the fuck?
Throw your gun down!
I visited your home
this morning after you'd left.
I tried to play husband.
I tried to taste
the life of a simple man.
Throw it away!
It didn't work out...
so I took a souvenir...
her pretty head.
What the fuck's
he talking about?
What's going on over there?
Put the gun down.
What was in the box?
Because I envy
your normal life...
Put the gun down.
...it seems that envy is my sin.
Oh, what's in the box?
What's in the fucking box?
He just told you.
You lie!
You're a fucking liar!
That's what he wants.
He wants you to shoot him.
You tell me that it's not true.
Become vengeance, David.
She's all right.
Tell me.
Become...wrath.
Tell me she's all right!
If you murder a suspect,
David...
You can't throw it all away...
She begged for her life,
Detective.
She begged for her life
and for her baby's life.
Shut up!
He didn't know.
Give me the gun, David.
If you kill him...
he will win.
Oh, God!
Oh, fuck.
He shot him!
Set it down somewhere.
Come on. Set us down.
Holy Christ,
somebody call somebody.
Call somebody.
Well, we'll take care of him.
Whatever he needs.
Where are you going to be?
Around.
I'll be around.
Ernest Hemingway once wrote...
"The world is a fine place...
"and worth fighting for."
I agree with the second part.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org