Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
That's the ugliest thing
I've ever seen in my whole life.
It certainly is.
Who sent it?
That's strange, it doesn't say.
Who could've come from?
I don't like it.
It's staring at me.
It's probably one of
your uncle's jokes.
I don't think it's funny
at all.
Darling, I'm just going
to have a shower.
I'll be there in a minute.
Claudia, I told you not to leave
your toys laying about.
Good God, you are hideous.
- Claudia?
- What?
I had a bond with you,
young lady.
We had an agreement, didn't we?
Didn't we?
But daddy, I didn't
leave it there.
In a civilized society,
our word is our bond.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Just because it's your birthday,
doesn't mean you can...
Richard?
Richard, what was that?
You killed my mommy and daddy.
And now you're pissing your pants,
you're pissing your pants...
your pissing your pants!
Wake up!
You're pissing your pants!
And now,
ladies and gentlemen...
what you've all
been waiting for!
Shitface...
and the greatest ventriloquist
in Europe!
The psychotic Psychs!
Come on!
This grotesque abomination...
is not even anatomically correct.
Don't laugh,
it's a serious condition.
Six years ago, I found him in
a cemetery back in the US...
the little fucker tried
to rip me from hell.
I was trying to give you
a hug.
I don't know much
about myself.
I know I'm an orphan,
I know I'm a freak...
and of course,
I know that I'm Japanese.
But why do I have such
terrible nightmares?
Filled with rate and
blood and guts.
I'm not like that at all.
I would even hurt a fly.
There it goes,
back to his family.
I envy him.
Sometimes, I wonder about
my own parents.
Were they Zen masters?
Did they serve the emperor?
Sometimes I wonder what my mom
and dad were really like.
So, you don't believe
in Santa Claus.
Trust me honey, tonight
I'm gonna make you believe.
Wait to see what Santa is bringing
you, you naughty girl.
No, I can hear you fine,
you're not breaking up.
Sheila I just said,
You're breaking up with me?
Wait! You're breaking up
with me on Christmas's Eve?
Sheila, you've got to be
fucking kidding me!
That's just great.
I knew it!
You're not real!
You were never real!
You know what that kind of
disappointment can do to somebody?
You have any idea how that
can fuck with your mind?
Fuck with your mind?
Chucky broke again.
This is bloody ridiculous!
Cut! Cut!
Thirty-four, take 1.
- Don't help me.
- Tony, what was that?
- I'm sorry, it's...
- This is unprofessional...
- and I can't work like this.
- No Jason, I'm sorry! Wait!
We're here in Hollywood
where production is underway...
on the new horror flick
"Chucky Goes Psycho".
The film tell the urban legend
of Chucky and Tiffany.
Two dolls supposedly possessed
by serial killers.
The dolls were found in the scene
of real life murders...
which remain unsolved
to this day.
Guys, I think Tiffany's
left arm is loose again.
I'm looking for Jennifer?
Does anyone have a 20 on Jennifer?
Jennifer.
Got your skinny-quick.
We're ready for you on set.
- Jennifer, I'm so proud of you.
- For what?
- For sticking to your diet.
- Thank you.
What's going on
in the world today?
Julia Roberts is getting 25
million for her next film.
I'm so tired of hearing
about Julia Roberts.
You know, I should've
played Erin Brockovich.
I could've done it
without the WonderBra.
Julia stole that part right
out from under me.
You know how? She slept with the
director, that's what I think.
Jennifer, you know
that's not true.
How come I don't ever get
any of the good roles anymore?
How come nobody
takes me seriously?
- Nice tits.
- Thank you.
Look at me, I'm an Oscar nominee,
for Christ's sake...
and now I'm fucking a puppet.
Got no fan mail,
no paparazzi, no stalkers.
There must be something
I'm right for.
Let's see...
Hip Hop Superstar,
turned director Redman...
is still looking for the right
actress to take the female lead...
in his upcoming Bible epic.
That sounds good.
What's the role?
Virgin Mary.
- What's so funny?
- Nothing.
It's perfect! It's just what I need
to reinvent myself.
The Virgin Mary. I always loved
the way she wears robes...
her hair off her face,
kinda like this.
Joan, get Morty on the phone...
and tell him I need to have a meeting
with this Redman right away.
That's a wrap for Access Hollywood
reporting from Hollywood.
For as you can see, Chucky
and Tiffany are alive and well.
You can catch their movie in
theaters next Halloween.
Thank you, Chucky.
Fuck you very much.
I'm not orphan after all.
Well...
you were shit last night...
- you're gonna have to be more scary.
- Scary?
Let's rehearse, shall we?
Hello.
Look, you gotta learn tapping
your killer instincts.
Give in to your natural
impulses, or else I'll have to...
fire your arm?
Hey!
Come here! Come here!
Come here!
Mary, you're truly a vision
of solid innocence.
Unique among all women,
as pure as the virgin snow...
but I ask,
what is troubling you?
Joseph, husband,
there's been a miracle.
As I stand before you,
I must tell you...
I'm with child.
But Mary, how could this be?
In accordance with God's whishes,
we never lay together...
as man and wife.
Yes it is true, and I beg you
that you believe when I tell you...
I've never lain with
any man at all.
Do you believe me, Joseph?
Do you?
- Do you?
- Yes, yes I do.
- You're great. You're super.
- Thank you, Mr. Man.
Could I call you Red?
There's a whole lot different ways
I can do it, not just the way you saw.
I can do it faster, I can do it
slower, I could do it as a rap.
No.
You already showed me a side of the
character I've never seen before.
Thank you.
But I think I'm gonna have
to go with my first choice.
Thanks for coming by anyway.
I'm a huge, huge fan...
I really wanna work with you
one day, we should call you...
Excuse me, I hope you don't
mind my asking but...
- who is your first choice?
- Julia Roberts.
But thanks for
coming by anyways.
Listen Red...
I've been giving a lot
of thought to this project...
and I have a lot of interesting
ideas about the character...
and I was thinking maybe...
you'd like to discuss it in a more
intimate setting. Just the 2 of us.
Well, I didn't know you were that
passionate about the role.
Yes, very passionate.
So, shall we say, my place...
eight 'o clock?
Pardon me, sir.
Sorry.
Sorry, sir.
Don't mind me.
Excuse me.
Oh dear.
Mom?
Dad?
I've dreamed of this moment
all my life.
I know this must come
as quite a shock.
It's going to be an
adjustment for all of us.
Look, I still have the
necklace you left me.
I've always wanted to know,
what does this words mean?
Is it our family motto?
Please say something!
It's because of the way
I look, isn't it?
For pity's sake,
please wake up!
Wake up.
"Aguei Due Dambala. Awake!"
- Tiff?
- Chucky?
Who the hell are you?
Shitface.
Now what kind of a name
is that?
Where are you mother
and father?
Checking from that face,
my guess is they're hiding.
Shut up, you asshole.
Come on, it looks like the kid
fell off the ugly tree...
and hit every branch
on the way down.
You gotta feel bad for the parents.
I wonder what they must look like.
Oh my God.
What? No you didn't...
we didn't...
Sweet Face, come to mommy!
What's going on?
Where are we?
In Hollywood.
I saw you on the TV.
Chucky, wake up!
Look at us!
We've had a make over!
We're movie stars!
Shit! Barbie mode!
They're puppets. They don't
walk and talk by themselves.
Listen, if you want them to work,
I'm gonna have to take them apart.
Is mommy ill?
The courts thought so.
Heads up!
I'll stop believing that.
Hey, you're pissing your pants.
Chucky, she's just had
an accident.
You mean "he" had an accident.
Don't look at me.
See? What did I tell you?
- A beautiful little girl.
- What? Are you blind?
That's my boy!
It's just that he hasn't had
his growth spurt yet.
Don't worry about it, son.
You're a later bloomer, that's all.
And it's high time
that you had a real name.
Let's see, I'm gonna call you...
Glen.
Glen? What kind of name
is that for a girl?
Don't listen to him, honey.
From now on, your name is...
Glenda.
Run, Glenda!
Geez! What a mess!
There you are, mister good bar.
Jennifer Tilly!
Hello!
Oh my God!
You look so real.
You look so real!
You're cuter than
my last boyfriend.
I think we make
a lovely couple.
Jennifer! Mrs. Tilly!
Were you having an affair with him?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Pete Peters,
Celebrities Reveal.
- Jennifer, what did you see?
- You want me to draw a picture?
- Somebody give her a piece of paper!
- I'm not going to draw a picture.
Don't feel bad, you're an
actress, not an artist, uh?
What were you doing
when you saw the body?
No comments.
Jennifer, I love you.
Is it true that you and
Redman talked about...
you starring in his
new movie?
- Yes, as a matter of fact, I...
- Can I have your autograph?
Okay, sure.
We've heard about
your obsession with chocolate.
Hey, hold on,
you forgot the head.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Jennifer, how old
are you really?
- Paparazzi scum bag!
- What year were you born?
- I want the set of the film, okay?
- Sure.
What are you hiding?
- Are you okay?
- I am now.
So are you a pair
of ninja assassins?
Are you hit men for the Yakuza?
We're not from Japan.
We're from Jersey.
Just think. Jennifer Tilly
is playing me in a movie.
- It's absolutely perfect casting.
- But that voice?
I know, she sounds
just like an angel.
Now I've got it all
figured it out.
I'm gonna transfer my soul
into Jennifer...
and you're gonna transfer your
soul into Redman.
I'm down with that.
We'll diss these plastic bodies
once and for all...
and we'll be Hollywood's
hottest couple!
- What about me?
- Don't worry, Glenda.
I've got that
figured it out too.
You are going to be
a real life girl.
- Boy.
- How?
Well, I'm not getting pregnant
again, I'll tell you that much.
My mother always told me...
"once is a blessing,
twice is a curse. "
That would explain your sister.
The only sensible option
is a surrogate mother.
- I have something important...
- Hold on a second, sweetheart.
- Hello?
- What are you doing?
I'm busy.
- I do have a life, you know?
- Turn on the news.
We have discovered
the victim's body.
As of yet there's no
official confirmation...
as to whether or not
Mrs. Tilly is a suspect
- Jesus!
- Can you believe it?
Are you okay?
I've had better days.
Listen Joan, I need you
to do something for me.
I need you to get me
a bottle of champagne...
and bring it by my house.
What for?
I've got a big night tonight.
Tonight? With who?
Redman.
- Jennifer, what are you up to?
- Thank you, Joan.
Come on, Stan. It's just business.
He'll be outta there by midnight.
Oh my God!
She's a complete slut!
Good night, Glenda.
Sleep tight.
Leave it on.
Oh sweetie.
There's nothing to be scared of.
Your dad and I will be
right here.
Why do you kill people?
Excuse me?
Why do you kill?
It's a hobby, really.
It helps us relax.
Am I going to be a killer?
Of course! It's been a family
tradition for generations!
But violence is bad, isn't it?
They said so on TV.
Not violence. Violins.
Violins are bad.
That scrutchy music is gonna
ruin the godamn country.
Chucky, Glenda is right.
It's time we owned up to it.
We have a problem with killing.
I don't have a "problem"
with killing.
I like a little killing now and
then. What's wrong with that?
Killing is an addiction
like any other drug.
But we're parents now.
We have to set a good example.
Let's quit, Chucky.
Right now!
You have got to be kidding.
Promise me, Chucky,
no more killing.
- No.
- Chucky.
- No, no...
- No more killing!
- We can't do it anymore!
- No, no...
- We have the future to think of!
- No, no!
- We have a child!
Fine! Alright already!
I promise.
Thank you, doll baby.
You're a sweetheart.
Now we really will be
the perfect family.
Did you hear that?
Maybe you should forget the director
and fuck the exterminator instead.
So how do I look? Never mind.
Jennifer, this is beneath you.
Think about what you're doing.
What the people are gonna say?
Who cares what people will say?
- Don't you see how evil this is?
- I don't wanna hear it.
You're prostituting yourself
so you can play the Virgin Mary.
Joan, I don't wanna hear it.
This is so evil.
You're going to hell.
No, hell would be ending up
on "Celebrity Fear Factor"...
in a worm-eating contest
with Ann and Nicole Smith.
Which you'd win.
- He's here.
- Let yourself out the back.
And while you're at it,
leave your key on the counter.
- What are you saying?
- You think I'm so disgusting...
you think I'm going to hell.
I'm only trying
to survive here, Joan.
God knows I wouldn't wanna
drag you down with me.
I'm saying you're fired.
I'm gonna get that ass...
Now in artificial insemination,
timing is everything...
so you have to hurry. That
shouldn't be a problem for you.
Yeah, just don't let that player
get into her pants.
I don't want him touching
my woman...
- until I'm him, and you're her.
- Right.
Hey, aren't you gonna give me
a hand here?
Too tall.
Lesbos!
Done her.
Here we go!
Come to papa!
Cheers!
You know, I wasn't bullshitting
when I told you I was a fan.
That's so sweet, Redman.
Which of my films
is your favorite?
That movie where you and
that chick were making out.
"Bound".
Everybody likes that one.
- You're still in touch with her?
- Gina?
Yeah, we're friends.
Close friends.
Very close friends.
Maybe the three of us
can hang out together sometime.
- I'd really like that a lot.
- Okay.
- I'll see if I can make it happen.
- The bottom is up, baby.
Redman, I was wondering...
what's gonna take to make you
seem me as a Virgin?
Well, you tell me!
A masturbating midget?
Get it, Mini-Me!
Sweet Jesus!
God bless the little people!
- I don't know if I can do this?
- Why not?
- What will people say?
- Fuck what people will say!
You know what I'm saying?
This was meant to be, for real.
You know how I know? 'Cause
the man upstairs told me so.
- Really?
- Hell yeah!
Mel Gibson ain't the only one God's
been talking to in Hollywood.
And He personally told me,
that you was my Virgin.
What the hell?
Pig!
And you should be
ashamed yourself.
Where's your self-respect?
You know what my mother
used to say about dirty girls?
She said "You can always smell
it on the girls who sell it".
By the way, can I have
your autograph?
I'm a big fan.
What am I supposed to do
with this?
Mrs. Tilly, I know
you're frightened.
You're probably even wondering
if you've gone completely insane.
But I promise you, tomorrow
you're going to wake up...
and this will all seem
just like a bad dream.
In the mean time...
we can do this the easy way,
or the hard way.
It's really up to you.
No wonder the girl
is always in trouble.
Check it out.
Look at the size of his feet.
You know what they say.
Geez, she's fat.
I can't believe it, she's not
even pregnant yet.
Paparazzi scum bag!
Looks like you've got
everything under control.
I'll just leave you to it.
Motherhood is so beautiful.
No, no...
Sorry, just messing with you.
What time is it?
Time to get dressed.
We're gonna have our own boys'
night out, just you and me.
- How does that sound?
- Where are we going?
Hunting.
I can't see anything.
Maybe we should slow down?
Now, you're doing great!
Son of a bitch!
- Up yours, asshole!
- What?
Not you, son.
Come on, floor it!
Ops! I did it again!
Jesus Christ!
No!
- Oughta a boy!
- No, I didn't...
And I thought you
weren't ready, kid!
You're a fucking natural!
But he hit the shelf!
And don't worry about your
mother, it'll be our little secret.
Say "cheese".
Good morning.
Hi.
We must have really gotten
wild last night.
Redman, did we...?
- You don't remember?
- No, it's all blur.
- What about you?
- I remember you screaming a lot.
I seem to remember that too.
I have that effect on women.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Wait, I do remember.
I had the strangest dream.
I dreamt my guardian angel
came to me.
She had the sweetest voice
I've ever heard.
She told me
to respect myself...
and then she asked for
my autograph.
Let' see, step number one,
admit I have an addiction.
Okay, check.
Step number two, give myself
over to a higher power?
Whatever.
Here we go.
Step number nine:
The recovering addict...
must make amendments to anyone
he or she has harmed.
- Hello?
- Good morning. Is this Ruth Bailey?
- Speaking.
- The widow of Robert Bailey?
- Yes, who is this?
- Mrs. Bailey...
my name's Tiffany Ray.
You don't know me, but a few
years ago I killed your husband.
And I'm so very sorry.
Is this some kind of sick joke?
No, I'm completely serious.
But I want you to know...
I'm recovering now and
I've put all of that behind me.
I don't know who you are,
but...
Thank you Mrs. Bailey,
have a nice day.
I feel better already.
Good morning, Stan.
What is so important
you wanted to tell me?
Well, the things is, Jennifer...
I'm sorry, I don't know
what's got into me.
So you were saying...
- Forget it.
- Okay.
Now, let's see...
what should we do today?
I'm pregnant.
Redman, I said I'm pregnant.
Congratulations.
Who's the baby's daddy?
Don't even look at me.
I haven't slept with anyone else...
to advance my career lately.
- Who are you kidding?
- It's true, Redman, look.
I know I come off all sluty,
but that's for my image.
You think anyone would cast me
in these sexy roles...
if they knew I hadn't been
laid in a year?
I haven't even slept
with my driver yet...
and I think he really likes me.
That's all very touchy and shit,
but I'm telling you it can't be me.
Why not?
I had a vasectomy as soon as
I got to Hollywood.
I ain't no idiot.
- That's impossible, because...
- Hey, Jennifer.
I hate to break it to you...
but I can't hire you
if you're pregnant.
That's ridiculous.
The character is pregnant.
I know, but I have a very
specific vision of Mary.
What can I say?
She's gotta be hot.
That pig!
- Recovery Hotline.
- Yes, I'm in recovery.
And I'm afraid I'm going
to have a slip.
- Can you get to a meeting?
- No, it's really not an option.
- I just freak everybody out.
- Don't be so hard on yourself.
We're not here to judge you.
What's your name?
- Tiffany.
- Listen to me, Tiffany.
- I know what you're going through.
- You do?
Yes, I do. In fact, I'm gonna
let you in a little secret.
- Just last week I had a slip.
- Really?
Yeah, and believe me,
it was not pretty.
- It never is, is it?
- No.
In fact it took me three hours
just to clean up the mess.
Oh God, don't remind me.
But I'm not beating myself
over it.
- You know why, Tiffany?
- Why?
Because Rome wasn't built
in a day.
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
Hello?
Speaking. Who's this?
I understand who you are, I just
don't know how you got my number.
Because it's a private number.
Pete Peters?
Yeah, I saw him yesterday.
I don't have any relationship
with him.
He's a paparazzi who
started taking pictures of me...
in compromising positions.
Redman is a director...
Oh yeah...
he's a rapper too...
he's a rapper director, okay?
Bye-bye.
Jennifer.
Do you mind?
I'm on the phone.
There's been another murder.
What? I told where I was.
I was right here all night
with Redman.
What? I don't...
You're not telling me I'm
a suspect, are you?
Okay. Alright.
I'm on my way.
I'm leaving.
You can let yourself out.
By the way Redman,
drop dead.
Glenda, honey,
everything is okay.
It was just a little slip.
No need to tell your daddy.
It'll be our little secret, okay?
It's "D" day here
in San Quentin.
Who would've thought
it would ever come to this?
They're executing Martha Stewart
this morning.
I don't think I can take
nine months of this shit.
Silly Chucky. It's a voodoo
pregnancy. It's accelerated.
How accelerated?
It's 102,7 Kiss FM, LA's number
one music station.
Ryan Seacrest, Ally Kay "I don't
know if I can't take it" on the way.
We have bad weather on the way,
LA, Hollywood.
Bad weather? We're not
used to bad weather.
No, we're not.
I'm pretty sure it's gonna
affect my whole life.
I'd like to hear more reports
on the weather...
This is Joan.
Joan, I'm fat.
- You're not fat.
- No, I'm fat, I'm huge!
For the love of Mary,
I'm pregnant.
- Oh my God.
- No, I should've listened to you.
You said it was evil
and I was going to hell.
You're right and
now God is punishing me.
- My God. Is it Redman's?
- No, it's definitely not Redman's.
- What?
It's definitely not Redman's.
What an asshole!
- What makes you say that?
- Say what?
- That Redman's is an asshole.
- I didn't say, you did.
- No I didn't.
- So he's not an asshole?
- Yes he is.
- Joan, will you stop doing that?
- Doing what?
- Imitating, I don't sound like that!
Yes you do! I do!
Joan, shut up! There's something
wrong with me, I'm pregnant, I...
Jennifer, what's wrong?
Nothing, I'm fine.
I heard you scream.
I can still hear you screaming.
It's just, "Bound"
is on cable.
Gina Gershon is fingering me.
I love this movie, don't you?
Jennifer?
Yeah, that's really interesting,
but I gotta go. Bye.
Jennifer?
- Too tight?
- Yes.
Ain't no such thing.
What are you doing? Stop it!
What the hell is going on
in here?
She came on to me.
- Help me! Somebody help me!
- Shut up, asshole!
Somebody help me!
What the hell is this?
We had an agreement, Chucky!
We decided,
for the sake of our child...
we weren't gonna do
this shit anymore.
No, you decided!
Just like you decided
our son was a girl.
- He is a girl!
- He's a boy, godamn it!
And he's the most promising
killer I've ever seen.
You should've been there, Tiff.
You would've been
so proud of him.
- I want a girl!
- I want a boy!
You're tearing me apart!
What about what I want?
- What?
Doesn't what I want
mean anything at all?
Okay, interesting. Tell us.
What do you want, Sweet Face?
I think I want to be a boy.
Yes! In your face, lady!
But being a girl would be
nice too.
- Well, which is it?
- I'm not sure.
Sometimes I feel like a boy...
sometimes I feel like a girl.
Can I be both?
- Well, some people...
- No way!
But one thing I do know
for sure.
I don't want to be a killer.
Glenda, Glen, whatever.
I'm so proud of you.
No matter what happens...
we'll deal with it together,
as a family.
Okay, Tiff-san.
Wait a minute!
I'm not gonna let you poison
our son's mind...
with your touchy-feely
twelve-step bullshit.
If you two don't wanna kill
anymore, that's your loss.
But don't look down
your noses at me.
I'm not ashamed to be a killer,
I'm proud of it.
It's not an addiction,
it's a choice.
And it's not something that you
should have to hide in the closet.
- Oh dear!
- Oh God!
Well, well, well...
Looks like Ms. High and Mighty
ain't so perfect after all.
It was just a little slip.
Rome wasn't built in a day,
you know?
Besides, the fucker
really had it coming.
- And what about my body?
- I'll take care of it.
Jennifer, I love you.
I love you.
- This is Stan.
- Hello. It's Jennifer.
Baby, I need your body.
I'll be right there.
Jennifer, if anything happens to
me I want you to know...
They really do make a cute couple,
don't you think?
It's like my mother
always said...
Christ! Enough with your
mother already!
I killed that bitch twenty years
ago and she still won't shut up.
There, there, won't be
long now.
Jennifer!
- Who is it?
- Jennifer!
It's that nosy bitch Joan.
I'll take care of her.
I wouldn't want you to violate
your delicate sensibilities.
Jennifer!
Jennifer?
Oh my God!
Jennifer.
Look out behind you!
Joan!
Look, I'm not gonna
give you crap.
Nobody is perfect, Tiff.
I've got a few
skeletons in the closet myself.
See? Come on, Tiff?
How long did it take
to build Rome anyway?
Tiff?
Glen?
Guess again, daddy.
- Glenda?
- That's my name.
- Don't you ever hear?
- Oh shit!
- What did I miss?
- Nothing much.
I just fired Joan.
Looks like you win after
all, Tiff.
- Congratulations.
- You both win.
I'm a real lady killer,
if you catch my drift.
I'm a boned bonus baby.
Jesus Christ Chucky,
what did you do to him?
What did I do? At least I spent
time with the kid.
Glen, wake up!
Stop it, mommy.
You'll wrinkle my dress.
How do you like it?
I made it myself.
Like mother, like daughter,
right?
Like mother, like daughter.
Wake up! Right now!
Mom? Dad?
What am I?
Push, Mrs. Tilly.
Push!
I'm pushing,
you little star fucker!
Pay no attention to little
Mrs. Potty Mouth. She's hormone.
Oh my God! It's coming!
I can see it's little head.
What is it? What is it?
- It's a boy.
- A boy.
Thank God.
Give me my baby.
Chucky, we're not done
here yet.
- What?
- Jennifer isn't done.
We've got another one here.
Push, Jennifer. Push!
Push! Push it out!
What's this one?
It's a girl.
Chucky, it's time.
- Give me the power, I beg of you.
- Hold it!
Hold it. Chucky.
First he has to choose.
I beg your pardon?
Sorry, she has to choose.
We don't have time for this shit.
- Wait Chucky!
We have a son and a daughter.
Glen and Glenda.
Don't you get it?
Maybe they don't have to choose.
- Help!
- Hurry Chucky, do the chant!
- Somebody help!
- Chucky, do it now!
- Help! Help us!
- We won't get another chance.
What are you waiting for,
Chucky?
- Help!
- Do it! Do it!
Everybody shut up!
I've had it! That's it!
There's a limit
to how much I can take.
What are you talking about?
Look around you, Tiff.
This is nuts!
And I have a very high
tolerance for nuts.
If this is what it takes
to be human...
then I'd rather take my chances as
a supernaturally possessed doll...
it's less complicated.
- You can't be serious.
- As a heart attack.
Think about it. What's so great
about being human anyway?
You get sick, you get old,
you can't get it up anymore.
I'm not looking forward
to that.
Honey, I wanna be
Jennifer Tilly.
I wanna be a star.
And I don't wanna be
your chauffer.
As a doll, I'm fucking infamous!
I'm one of the most notorious
slashers in history.
And I don't wanna give that up!
I'm Chucky,
the Killer Doll!
And I dig it!
I have everything I want.
A beautiful wife.
A multi-talented kid.
This is who I am, Tiff.
This is me!
Chucky, I don't know what the
fuck you're talking about...
I don't know who the fuck
you are anymore.
But it's not enough for me.
I want more.
What are you saying?
It's over.
We've gotta get out of here,
Sweet Face.
I'm leaving you, Chucky,
and I'm taking the kid.
Nobody leaves me!
Nobody!
No! No!
Jennifer, I love...
Stan tell me, tell me...
Jesus!
- Oh my God!
- My babies!
I just wanna know
where they are.
They're fine, Jennifer.
They're in the maternity ward.
- Alright...
- The important thing for you...
to think about now is getting well
so you can get on with your career.
I don't care about my career,
I want my babies.
I'm working on it Jennifer,
but you're not making it easy.
I already talked to the cops,
they cleared me.
They know that you're
not a killer...
they didn't say you were
mentally competent.
What do you expect
after the story you told?
It's true.
I suggest from now on you
keep that to yourself.
We'll talk later.
Try to get some sleep.
Wish me luck, Sweet Face.
Mommy is gonna be a star.
I can't think of a thing to say.
Fuck it!
Give me the power,
I beg of you.
Switch! Switch! Switch!
Switch!
Nobody leaves me! Nobody!
What can I say?
Honey...
be a good girl...
or boy, whatever.
Don't make the same mistakes
your mom and dad made.
Specially your dad.
Let's go.
- Glenda?
- No, dad.
It's me, your boy.
Your chipper-filled block.
Are you proud of me now, daddy?
Are you?
Oughta boy, kid!
Oughta boy!
Glen, there, there.
It's alright. It's alright.
You're gonna be alright.
There, there.
Honey, it's alright.
Yesterday, she gave him a bloody
nose and took pictures for showing.
And I'm pretty sure she's been
taking money from my purse.
That's ridiculous.
Glen is an angel, an absolute
dream. But Glenda...
she's a bad girl, Mrs. Tilly.
A very bad girl.
I'm not listening to this.
- I hate that thing.
- Some of the kids wanna see her.
- Mrs. Tilly...
- What?
I'm afraid of her.
Fulvia, it's only a doll.
I was talking about Glenda.
Fulvia, just exactly are you
trying to say?
I can't work here anymore.
- What?
- I'm sorry, I just can't.
If you only saw the way she
looks at me with such... hate.
Alright Fulvia,
if that's what you want.
- We'll miss you.
- Thank you, Mrs. Tilly.
God bless.
Mom got her wish.
She's a bright shining star.
Now we're the perfect family.
I've learned a lot about myself.
I know I'm not alone.
I know I'm not a freak.
And even though we had
our differences...
I know my dad really
loved me.
Glen sweetheart,
come over here.
Sweetheart look,
here's another one.
- Who is it from, mommy?
- I don't know.
Let's see.
It doesn't say. Strange.
Doesn't say who it is.
Sweetheart don't run so fast,
you can trip.
So anyway...
he was on a movie,
he was gonna go after...
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org