Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Dishes off to Scootsie.
But look at this, Jackie Moon
blocks his own teammate's shot!
A loose ball on the court,
Vakidis gets it.
No!
God damn it, Vakidis!
Learn fuckin' English!
Corn dogs, Jackie!
Corn dogs for all these people.
The Tropics win,
and this crowd is going crazy.
Crazy for corn dogs.
And Jackie Moon gives us
a victory lap right out the door!
# Get up and dance to the music! #
Now, Scootsie, rotate up top.
Vakidis, flash to the high post.
No, to the high post, Vakidis.
Help him.
Good.
- At guard...
- # Dance to the music #
...formerly known as Clarence Withers...
- and "Downtown Funky Stuff" Malone...
- # Dance to the music #
...and Sugar Dunkerton.
- He's tryin' out his new name tonight.
Put your hands together for...
- # Dance to the music #
...Coffee Black.
Coffee Black!
# Dance to the music #
# You might like to hear
the horns blowin' #
# Cynthia on the throne, yeah! #
Now let's do it again. Jab.
Swing, back.
Good.
That's it.
# Dance to the music #
Here they come, the Flint Tropics
Ball Girls cheerleading squad,
keeping the crowd energized
through the timeout.
They've just got such big...
- What?
- Hearts.
- Yes.
- Big, bouncy, jiggly hearts.
Well, hearts don't really bounce...
so now I think you're talking
about something else, Lou.
- # Say it! Get up! #
- Yeah!
Downtown brings the ball up forward and
passes to Monix at the top of the key.
Behind his back to Doubleday.
Scootsie goes for the three-pointer...
and it is good!
Are you actually havin' fun out here,
Monix?
Hey, don't tell anybody.
# Dance to the music #
# Yeah, yeah, yeah #
Well, if it isn't
the toast of Flint, Michigan.
Shouldn't you be out signing
autographs somewhere or somethin'?
- Will you marry me?
- Shut up.
I'm crazy about you.
You know that.
Do I?
You came to one of our games.
Don't think I didn't see you
hiding in the upper deck.
- So?
- So let's do this, Lynn. You and me.
You know, like back in the day.
You know? I mean not then, because
I was an asshole. Better, right?
For real this time.
I need you.
Yo, Monix!
What's up, man?
Hey, check out the jersey. I'm you!
Yeah.
- Hey, Kyle?
- Yeah.
Can you do me a big favor?
Can you go get me a tube of Bengay?
Are you kidding me?
I'd be honored, man. I'll leave right now.
What do you think you're doing?
- Hey, Kyle?
- Yeah!
Listen, don't... Kyle?
- Don't go to the pharmacy.
I need one of those big tubes like
you get at Luger's out on Route 59.
I'm already gone, big man!
Hey, Lynn.
Forgot my stupid wallet.
That's it.
Yes.
# Baby, keep on #
# Come on, baby,
keep on doin' it #
# Right on #
# Right on doin' it #
# You got it together #
# Baby, keep on #
# Oh, you got it together, baby #
# Right on #
# Keep on doin' it #
# And I'll give you,
baby, all that I get #
- Kyle.
- # Keep on #
- Fuck!
- Monix!
You old dog.
- What the hell are you doin'?
- Nothin', man.
I'm just sittin' here watching...
and stuff.
I'm outta here.
Come on, man, don't be like that.
It's all cool.
No, man. No, believe me, it's not cool.
I'll call you.
OK.
He was talkin' to me.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen...
Jackie Moon has outdone himself
with this promotion...
as he prepares to jump
over 47 feet of Ball Girls.
- # Rollercoaster #
- # Say, what? #
The fact that Jackie's
never been on roller skates before...
appears to have done nothing
to diminish his confidence.
- # Rollercoaster #
- All right, folks.
Here comes...
- # Rollercoaster #
...Jackie!
Here he comes down the ramp.
- He is airborne!
- Shit!
- No!
- Lord!
- Jackie's up!
- # Rollercoaster! #
- Great job!
And everyone survives!
That was exciting!
- # Of love #
- That's an adrenaline rush.
# Rollercoaster #
Next time I'm gonna jump
even more girls.
- What?
- The Commissioner just called again.
- Commish?
- He's drivin' up here on Monday.
- He's comin' to Flint?
- Yes, he's comin' to Flint.
Shit. Crap.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
You know, Jackie, we need
2,000 fans in those stands.
We can't fake it this time.
We gotta do somethin'.
Look, it's no problem.
I'll take care of it.
Yeah? We've tried everything.
Look, I said I'll handle it, OK?
- I'll think of somethin'.
- All right.
Back in 30 seconds.
- How's your wife doin'?
- She's doing just super.
- She's gorgeous. Yeah.
- Really...
- Thank you, I think. I mean...
- I'd be...
...hands off.
- I'll try.
- OK.
- No guarantees.
Really?
I'd like a guarantee.
Are we back, Chuck?
We're back.
OK. Welcome back
to Tropics Weekly.
I'm joined by owner/player/coach
Jackie Moon.
Jackie, it is always an honor
when you can drop by.
Always enjoy our time together,
Dick Pepper.
Dick Pepperfield, actually.
Now, Jackie...
amazingly, you're two wins away
from getting your team to the NBA.
How do you intend to match up
to the Squires' strong inside game?
It's a great question.
Tomorrow, after the game,
I, Jackie Moon, will wrestle a bear.
Well, that's something...
but defensively, as a team,
how do you...
That's tomorrow night,
one night only...
watch Dewie the Wrestling Bear
attack me...
and he's killed people in public before.
Well, OK, that is some entertainment...
and you are known for
your creative promotions, Jackie, but...
You're not gonna
want to miss this, folks...
and if you're a small child, you creep
into your mama's bedroom at night...
and you lift about 40 bucks...
- outta your mom's purse...
- No, no, no.
...and you walk down to Flint
Fairgrounds Coliseum, eight o'clock!
There ya have it. Jackie Moon,
thanks so much for joining us.
Dewie's insane!
He could rip my head off!
I'm Dick Pepperfield, reminding you
there will be another night.
Good night, Flint.
Jackie, are you really
gonna wrestle a bear?
- Dick, you're the best.
- And we're clear.
- Let's go get some pussy.
- Gosh, I don't know.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- I shouldn't. You know, I shouldn't.
- But you want to.
Yes, I said I cannot say no to you. We
are gonna get some pussy, aren't we?
It's gonna be fun.
Come on!
I'm scared, Clarence.
It's a baby bear.
It's trained and everything.
I don't care. I'm terrified of those things.
I'm freakin' out.
Come on, get it together.
I'm startin' to feel really dizzy.
Break his neck! Come on!
- Wanna call it off?
- No! No.
OK.
I gotta give these people a show.
- Are you guys ready?
- Uh-huh.
- You have to give me your safe word.
- No, I don't need a safe word.
OK, I'll tell you what, if you feel
like you're in danger, just say...
spumoni.
No, I don't need spumoni, OK?
Let's get this show on the road.
Bobby Dee.
- Let's go!
- Go... Go... Go ahead, man.
What are you afraid of?
Hey.
We're both wearing red.
- Sorry, I'm not ignoring you. I'm just...
- That's stupid, Jackie!
...trying to deal with him right now.
How long you been
working with the bear?
Just like a day or so.
What?
But I've been working with cats
for like 12 years.
So I'm very familiar with animals.
Great.
- C'mon!
- Hey, Dewie.
Fuck that shit!
I'm outta here. Spumoni.
No, nope. No, no.
You can't quit now. We just started.
We got to give these people
a show, man.
- Yeah, you're right.
- That guy's a pussy!
Test him out.
I'm just gonna be right over here.
- Do something!
- Come on, Dewie.
You're just nothin' but a dumb bear.
Smack, smack. Yep.
Crazy fists. I'm comin' with crazy fists.
Yeah. This is fine,
he's not doing anything.
Flint, can you dig it?
Jackie Moon Flint...
Shit!
Dewie!
Spumoni!
One round. No spumoni!
Fuck you, Clarence! Spumoni!
Dewie, no!
Bobby Dee, help! Shit! Spumoni!
Watch my hair! Watch my hair!
The only thing I care about
is my hair! Watch it!
Dewie! My hair!
Spumoni! Spumoni!
How many times
do I gotta say spumoni?
- Somebody's got to do something.
- I wouldn't go in there if I were you.
Don't worry, Jackie!
I'm coming, Jackie.
I'm comin', Jackie.
Turn on the lights! Turn on the lights!
Good.
Nobody move. Nobody move.
Where are you, precious?
Dewie?
Everyone just remain seated.
I think he left.
Dewie?
Everybody panic!
My God, there's a bear
loose in the Coliseum!
There will be no refunds!
Your refund will be escaping
this deathtrap with your life!
If you have a small child,
use it as a shield!
They love the tender meat.
Cover your sodas, Dewie loves sugar.
- Hey, Jackie.
- Hey, Commish.
What do ya think?
Packed house, right?
I need to speak with you
and the rest of the team, Jackie.
OK. Locker room? All right.
This whole merger thing
has been really complicated.
It's taken a lot of my time
out of my life, away from my family.
Look, even if you beat the Spurs
on Saturday...
the Tropics won't be going
to the NBA next year.
Come on, man.
What the hell
are you talkin' about?
The expansion committee had
an emergency meeting in Manhattan...
and they decided that Flint
just isn't a big enough media market.
Well, tough shit!
We done made it this far.
And rules is rules.
Guys, it's over.
There's nothing I can do.
Jackie, I'm man enough
to admit when I'm wrong.
I never thought you'd pull it off.
But you did.
Good luck.
Right.
Jackie, this is the type of deal
you can work around, ain't it?
Yeah, you Jackie Moon. I mean,
you can just make a phone call, right?
Sorry, guys. I let you down.
I'm nothin' but a big phony.
Man, don't talk like that.
You ain't no phony.
Yes, I am. You know my song
Love Me Sexy?
Of course, yeah.
Yeah, everybody loves that song, man.
It was number one in the country.
I stole it.
No.
It's true.
My mom wrote it on a napkin three
weeks before she died, and I stole it.
That song bought me this franchise
and everything I have in the world...
but it's all fake.
Well, look, you can write another
song. I know it's in your bones. Right?
Don't be crazy. I can't write a song
as brilliant as Love Me Sexy.
You're right.
I just wish I could puke this all away.
Monix, can you punch me
in the jejunum?
Monix?
# Qué será, será #
In a new merger-policy shift...
it seems the Tropics will not
be playing for an NBA berth after all.
Saturday's matchup
against the first-place Spurs...
will be the Tropics'
final basketball game.
And in an act of great sacrifice...
Jackie Moon has helped
Tropics' superstar, Coffee Black...
realize his NBA dreams...
by trading him to the Spurs.
Clarence baby, you made it!
You made it, Clarence, you made it!
Yes.
# Qué será #
# Girl #
For Lou Redwood, I'm Dick Pepperfield
reminding you there will be another...
No, actually we're down to our last night.
Shit.
Sup, chief?
Hey.
What are you doing here?
If you ain't heard, I got traded.
Yeah.
Coffee Black headin' to the NBA.
Big time.
Yeah, I just wanted to let you know,
man, this year, you coaching us...
the way you did it,
you really made us feel...
No, no, no, no.
Don't.
OK.
Let me ask you somethin', Monix.
Yup.
You already played for the NBA.
Your knee is gone...
you couldn't give a damn about the
merger, you were gonna retire anyway.
What's the question?
What you playin' for?
I just wanna sit here
and have a beer in peace.
Yeah?
All right.
I just thought you'd wanna hear that.
Have a good one.
# Baby, are you ready
to lick me sexy? #
Jackie, where you at?
# I'm a big faker
and I stole this song-ly sexy #
# I wanna kill myself-y sexy #
# I'm gonna get an extension cord
and hang myself sexy #
Buddy. What are you doin'?
Right now I'm urinating on myself.
Listen, Jackie, I never thanked you.
- For what?
- For helpin' me find basketball again.
Now what is it... Don't eat that.
- What is that?
- Pancake.
- Has that been there?
- It's been here a while.
Listen, Jackie, I think
you should call a team meeting.
Why?
'Cause you're still the leader
of the Tropics. Can you do that?
OK.
You're a good man.
Should we...
I hate to see this go to waste.
This little bit.
It won't go to waste.
Save that for the next guy.
If I could have
everyone's attention, please.
Well...
I just wanted to take one last time
to say thank you to all of you...
for all your hard work
as part of the Flint Tropics.
My teammates, it was an honor
to be on the court with you.
You guys are the best.
Even you, Vakidis.
Goddamn dumb son of a bitch.
You don't understand
a word I'm saying, do you?
To the Tropic Ball Girls...
I always thought I was gonna sleep
with a couple of you...
but that didn't happen.
That'll teach me to procrastinate.
Bobby Dee,
you're like a son I never had.
The son who's exactly
the same age as me.
Well, kinda... You're like
a half-son, half-friend.
Friend. A son-friend.
No, don't talk. You'll just make it worse.
I don't want to cry and wet my pants.
I'm not makin'
a whole lot of sense right now.
- Jackie?
- Yeah?
- Can I say a couple words?
- Please.
Thanks.
So we all know
that Clarence got traded...
and we all know this game
doesn't really matter anymore, right?
I've been thinking...
We made it our mission
to win fourth place.
You know, fourth place is still out there
waiting for us to take it.
And we're this close.
Now I tried to pretend that
it didn't matter if we won fourth or not.
The truth is...
I never wanted anything
more in my whole fucked-up life.
This game does matter.
It matters...
because this is the last real game of
basketball any of us is ever gonna play.
Ever.
Saturday night, I say we leave it
all out there on the floor...
because there is nothing else
for us to save it for.
Clarence or no Clarence,
NBA or no NBA...
this is for us.
Yeah. Let's do this.
Jackie Moon, I believe you have
one more game to promote.
- That's right.
- Damn right.
- Gentlemen?
- Let's bring it in.
- Ladies?
- C'mon.
- Yeah.
- Let's go, Tropics.
- Let me hear you say, "Fourth place!"
- Fourth place!
Look, the Spurs may be
the number-one team in the league...
but come Saturday night
they're gonna have to prove it.
Turtleneck.
Mr. Moon, since this game
doesn't actually count...
what exactly is your motivation?
On Saturday, we're gonna be playing
for the Flint, Michigan Megabowl.
White pants.
Yeah, I don't know if I understand
what you mean by Megabowl?
It's a Megabowl.
What's not to understand?
This is history in the making.
You're gonna wanna tell your grandkids
and their grandkids and their grandkids.
And when they look back
in the annals of history...
they're gonna be talkin'
about three things...
discovery of fire,
invention of the submarine...
and the Flint, Michigan Megabowl.
Right, but still the game doesn't count.
The trophy's 12 feet high.
And it is glorious. I've seen it.
Yeah, and when
we win the game...
that big gun's gonna shoot off.
The cannon doesn't actually fire.
It's a relic.
We're gonna win the Megabowl.
Saturday! Eight o'clock!
Flint, Michigan Megabowl!
Fourth place! Fourth place!
The Tropics seem to have captured
every heart in this town of underdogs.
People have poured in
from around the state...
to root for this first Megabowl
championship.
- Fourth place! Fourth place!
- It's a wonderful night for Flint...
and a wonderful night
for the Flint Fairgrounds Coliseum.
Now, Flint will be playing
without Coffee Black, their top scorer...
as the Spurs have traded for several
new players from around the ABA.
I was excited to be here
till I saw your face, Coffee.
Why's it so quiet in here?
Somebody say somethin'!
Monix, what time is it?
It's time.
It is a sold-out crowd here
at the Flint Fairgrounds Coliseum...
as the Tropics walk onto the court.
I tell you what, Dick,
this makes a lot of sense...
this heroes' welcome
for this Flint Tropics team.
This is extraordinary.
Jackie Moon is Flint's favorite son...
and he has done more for this city...
than any human being
who's ever lived on this planet.
With the possible exception
of Henry Ford...
Jackie Moon has done a lot for this city,
you're right about that.
Good tip to the Spurs.
Behind the back.
And wow! A little "How do you do?"
from Markie.
That's a pretty impressive start
for the Spurs.
Running roughshod over the Tropics.
Vakidis passes to Doubleday.
Rejected.
Scootsie passes to Jackie.
Out to Twiggy, and...
Stolen by Rebenkoff.
He pulls up for a dagger...
and ouch, three points.
Yeah!
Yeah, I don't feel good about this.
I may not have brought enough Scotch.
Shit!
It's hard to say where the Tropics
are falling down worse tonight...
on defense or on offense.
And with Coffee Black on
the Spurs bench, the Tropics look lost.
You're goin' in, Coffee Black.
Coach, I've got back spasms.
I can't do it.
Lutz, you're in.
Jackie! C'mon. Jackie, Jackie!
Moon to Ellis.
Ellis to Munson.
Munson to Monix.
Three points! Monix responds!
But it will take more than one fancy
three to defeat these mighty Spurs.
This is easily the worst half
of basketball the Tropics have played...
since Monix took over as coach.
- Yeah, it's a shit-fuckin'-sandwich, Dick.
- Let's watch the F-bomb, Lou.
With time expiring in the first half...
Monix splits the screen
with a pass to Moon.
He goes up strong...
Gets taken out by Petrelli.
I don't think I've ever seen anyone
get taken out quite that hard before.
- This looks serious.
- Damn.
Monix, you gotta hit him in the nuts!
Father Pat breaking up what
could have been total pandemonium.
Come on. Jackie? Jackie.
- Come on, back to the bench.
- Jackie?
He's got a pulse.
Let's get the stretcher.
- We don't have a stretcher.
- Jackie sold it.
- All right, well, let's get him up.
- Yeah, come on.
Let's get him in the locker room,
guys. Hurry.
Come on, come on.
Jackie's teammates doing just
an awful job of stabilizing his spine...
as they carry him off the court.
Come on, Jackie.
Yeah!
Where the hell
do you think you're goin'?
- Coffee!
You walk away from this team,
you will never play in the NBA.
That's my son! That's my son!
- Go, Clarence! Go, Clarence!
- You hear me, Coffee?
Look at this. Coffee Black
is walking over to the Tropics.
This crowd is going crazy!
Come on, Jackie, wake up.
Jackie, come on,
it's me, it's Bobby Dee.
Wake up. Come on, open 'em up.
- Hey, you got any smelling salt?
- I think we do.
- Get up.
- Jackie.
- Come on, Jackie.
- Snap out of it. Hey.
Come on, baby.
Jackie.
Mom.
- I miss you, Mama.
- I miss you too, honey.
- Come on, little fella. Jackie.
- Jackie.
Clarence, what are you doin' here?
What it look like?
I'm wit' y'all. He a'ight?
Are you outta your mind?
You wanna lose your NBA contract?
I don't care nothin' about that, man. This
is our season and we gonna finish it.
So you're gonna blow the deal for this?
- Fourth place, right?
- Right.
- Let's get Tropical.
- Right on.
Come on, buddy. Come around.
Now, I want you to go forward...
and tell the others
what I have told you here today.
Do you understand me, son?
Yes, Mama. You're so kind.
I'm sorry I stole your song.
I forgave you for that a long time ago.
Jackie, it's time you forgave yourself.
I don't wanna leave this place.
It's so fluffy.
Now hurry up,
and don't forget what I said.
OK. Bye!
Bye, Mama. Bye.
Bye.
Hey... I threw up, Mom.
I know you did, sweetie.
I threw up all by myself.
- That's workin'.
- Here we go. Come on, Jackie.
A little eye flutter. Hello, fella!
- Hey there!
- Mornin', sunshine.
We missed ya.
This just in.
It sounds like Jackie Moon is up
and around the Tropics locker room.
Then fake the pass and go straight
to the basket. Twiggy, how hard is it?
He keeps throwin' elbows.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to stand up to him,
ya pussy.
Monix, wait. I gotta tell
these guys somethin'.
I had a dream.
I had a dream I was in heaven.
And my mother spoke to me.
She was wearing
this flowing white gown...
and she showed me
a brand-new way to score a basket.
She called it the alley oop.
She spoke to me and she said,
"With this gift, you will win fourth place."
We are back in action here
at the Megabowl.
Coffee Black is playing for the Tropics.
Jackie makes the start here.
In fact, it looks like
he's running the offense.
What was that?
I'm sorry, I don't know
what just happened.
A very unusual series of moves
just made the ball go in.
Damn.
Yeah, I don't know why, Dick,
but I just got an erection.
Foul. No, two fouls.
Foul?! I didn't touch anybody.
Look, Jackie, people can't just
go flyin' in the air like that.
Please. My mom
wouldn't cheat in my dreams.
- What?
- She's an angel!
Heaven wants us to win this game!
- I'll burn your house down!
- Hold it, hold it, hold it.
It can't be a foul without
touchin' another player.
And it can't be traveling without
first establishing a pivot foot.
- That's right.
- It's two points, Father Pat.
It is two points.
- All right, I'm gonna allow it.
- That's the gospel.
Two points, Flint.
Are you outta your mind?
- He was floating. Is this ghost ball?
- It's legal, Coach.
- What the hell is that?
Yeah!
It worked, Jackie!
Thanks, Mama!
Things are getting interesting
here in the second half.
It's the Spurs' ball
as Rebenkoff makes a shot.
Misses it.
Rebound Tropics.
There it is again.
Clarence leaping and forcing the ball in
a downward direction through the net...
off of a high arching pass.
- It's a great play.
- It sure is.
Hold on. I'm just being told
that this is called an alley oop!
Yes, that is easier to say.
Twig!
Monix passes to Jackie.
Jackie lobs to Clarence.
And then, yes! Another alley oop.
The Spurs don't know what's hit 'em.
I love the alley oop.
Yes! Yeah!
# I wanna take you higher #
Here comes the alley.
And there goes the oop!
Timeout, white.
In all my years of radio,
I've never seen anything like this.
The Tropics have fought their way back
from a huge deficit...
and now with 12 seconds left
in the history of this franchise...
they are down by two,
and, man, you can feel the tension.
OK, guys, listen up.
They've made adjustments.
We can't keep runnin' the alley oop.
They're keying on Clarence.
So we're not gonna run the alley oop.
- What the hell we gonna run, then?
- The puke.
The puke?
Don't tell me you've forgotten it.
I seared it into your brains.
- This will work, OK? The puke.
- Right on.
I was gonna say exactly the same thing.
Good call. "Let's get Tropical" on three.
One, two, three.
Let's get Tropical!
We're down to the last play.
Monix inbounds to Jackie.
Jackie passes right back to Monix.
Monix back to Jackie.
The Tropics have gotta
make a move here, Dick.
Yeah, they need to find a way
to the hole and fast.
Monix finds Bee Bee.
Back door to Jackie. He goes up strong...
- Fouled hard by Petrelli!
- Eat shit, Petrelli!
Don't you know
how to play basketball?
Father Pat struggles to keep order...
between these two tough,
competitive teams.
All right. Black. Four-two.
With the body. Two shots.
- Come on, Jackie!
- Jackie will shoot two free throws here.
His team down by two,
with two seconds left on the clock.
All right, gentlemen.
Relax on the first one, we got two here.
Come on, Jackie.
Don't worry, guys. I got these.
I'm very good at free throws.
Seriously, free throws are probably
the best facet of my game.
What the hell are you doin', Jackie?
What, you never see me
shoot free throws before?
He's shootin' granny style.
Let 'im do his thing.
Always has.
Shit.
Here we go.
Jackie Moon holding the fate of Flint
in his fingertips.
- He kisses the ball for good luck.
- Sweet sugar.
It's good!
- Yes!
- Never doubted you, Jackie. Come on.
The Tropics need one more
to stay alive.
Watch the lines. Move on the release.
One more, Jackie.
Flint wins the Megabowl!
- Fourth place! Fourth place!
- # Just move on up #
Go Tropics! Go Tropics! Go Tropics!
# And keep on wishin' #
# Remember your dreams
are your only schemes #
# So keep on pushin' #
Who's number four?
- Yeah, Scoots!
- God. We really did it.
Just a moment.
Just a moment, please. Don't...
- What are you doin'?
- # Just move on up #
- Fourth place! Fourth place!
- # And peace you will find #
Fourth place! Fourth place!
- # Into the steeple of beautiful people #
- Fourth place! Fourth place!
# Where there's only one kind #
Yeah!
- Hey, Coffee.
- What?
I've changed my mind. I think we could
use that alley oop of yours in the NBA.
Thanks, Coach! Mama!
The NBA!
- Hey!
- Yeah, baby!
- Way to go!
- Thank you.
# Move on up #
# And keep on wishin' #
- Yes!
- Yeah!
- We did it! Yeah!
- Jackie!
- Hey!
- Congratulations on the Megabowl!
- Thank you.
- Whatever that is.
- It's very exciting!
- Yeah.
- You're a hell of a promoter!
Yeah.
Listen, I'm gonna be working
with the Commissioner of the NBA...
and I want you to join me.
Me in the NBA?! Really?
My God, thank you.
Can I bring my son-friend with me?
- Jackie, you don't have to do that.
- Yes, I do.
Mark my words,
as long as I'm alive, you'll both...
Everybody panic!
It's just like the Titanic,
but it's full of bears!
# Yeah #
# Hey #
# When you wish upon a star #
# Your dream
will take you very far, yeah #
"Dear Dukes. I'm sorry it took so long,
but in this bag is 10,000 dollars, cash."
No way. Really?
Actually, it's only 2,300.
I'll be payin' you the rest
right after they finish my merger buyout.
Let's get Tropical. Jackie R. Moon.
# In the sky so very dear #
Bitchin'. Bitchin'.
- # You're a shinin' star #
- Let's get Tropical!
# No matter who you are #
# Shinin' bright to see #
# What you can truly be
What you can truly be #
# Shining star come into view #
# Shine its watchful light on you, yeah #
# Gives you strength to carry on, yeah #
# Yeah, make your body
big and strong #
# You're a shining star
no matter who you are #
# Shining bright to see
what you can truly be #
# You're a shining star
no matter who you are #
# Shining bright to see
what you can truly be #
# Shining star for you to see
what your life can truly be #
# Come on, girl #
# Yeah #
- # It's me, Jackie Moon #
- # Love me sexy #
# Don't gimme that look #
# That's right, let's get sweaty #
# Let's get real sweaty #
# I'm talkin' rainforest sweaty #
- # I'm talkin' swamp sweaty #
- # Love me sexy #
# Let's fill the bathtub full-a sweat #
# All right #
# Baby, who wants to love me sexy? #
# Love me sexy #
# Baby, are you ready
to lick me sexy? #
# Lick me sexy #
# Take off your shoes
and suck me sexy #
# Suck, suck, suck, suck,
suck me sexy #
# Baby, we're naked
and we're humpin' sexy #
# Humpin' sexy #
# I wanna do a little thing wit' you
I wanna do a little thing wit' you #
# When I say "love me"
you say "sexy" #
- # Love me #
- # Sexy #
- # Love me sexy #
- # Back it on up and showin' you #
- # I wanna do #
# That lovin' me sexy is the thing to do #
# Oh, yeah #
- # Your body says love me #
- # Love me #
- # Your mind says sexy #
- # Sexy #
# Love me sexy #
# Baby, who wants to love me sexy? #
# Baby, are you ready
to lick me sexy? #
# Lick me sexy #
# Take off your shoes
and suck me sexy #
and suck, suck me sexy #
# Baby, we're naked
and we're humpin' sexy #
# Humpin' sexy #
# Freak of the week #
# Are you in the mood #
# To fly to the stars
with Jackie Moon? #
# When I say "love me"
you say "sexy" #
# Yeah #
- # Love me #
- # Sexy #
# Our Zodiac signs are compatible #
# Clockin' that ass
from across the room #
- # Your body says love me #
- # Love me #
- # Your mind says sexy #
- # Sexy #
# Love me sexy #
# Baby, who wants to love me sexy? #
# Baby, are you ready to lick me sexy? #
# Lick me sexy #
# Take off your shoes
and suck me sexy #
and suck, suck me sexy #
# Baby, we're naked
and we're humpin' sexy #
# Humpin' sexy #
# That's right, girl #
- # Let me whisper in your ear #
- # Love me sexy #
# Baby, wake up #
# We're naked
and we're humpin' sexy #
For the last 15 minutes, baby.
That's what's been happenin'.
- # Love me sexy #
- # Yeah #
# Too late now, it's on #
# Baby, who wants to love me sexy? #
# Love me sexy #
# Baby, are you ready
to lick me sexy? #
# Lick me sexy #
# Take off your shoes
and suck me sexy #
# Suck, suck, suck,
suck me sexy #
# Baby, we're naked
and we're humpin' sexy #
# Who wants to love me sexy? #
# Is it you? Is it you? #
- # Love me sexy #
- # Are you ready to lick me sexy? #
# Is it you? Is it you? #
- # Take off your shoes #
- # Lick me sexy #
# And suck me sexy #
# Is it you? Or is it you? #
# Baby, we're naked
and we're humpin' sexy #
Where are you, precious?
Dewie?
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org