WOMAN 1: Thank you, sir.
Have a nice day.
Next in line, please.
FRANKIE: Ooh, a week in Hawaii.
All right, I'll fill in for you.
WOMAN 1: Are you sure?
Yeah. You take your little honeymoon
before I change my mind, all right?
Oh, thank you.
There you go, sir.
MAN: Thank you very much.
FRANKIE: Have a nice day, sir.
Next in line, please.
Hey, Darnell, I didn't know
you had an account here.
As a matter of fact,
I never even saw you out of the projects.
DARNELL: Shut the fuck up.
Empty the fucking drawer.
Empty the drawer.
WOMAN 2: Next in line, please.
I just have a straight...
Uh-uh, Darnell.
Darnell, don't do this.
Now, come on, Darnell. Stop playing.
DARNELL: What?
What playing? It's not a fucking game.
Empty the fucking drawer.
[SOBBING] Hell no.
I want nothing to do with this.
Everybody, get on the fucking floor, now.
Get the fuck on the floor.
Sit down. Don't stand up.
- Give me the money.
LORENZ: Get your ass down.
B. B: Give him the money.
Let's get this money, baby.
- Now.
Get your...
Give him the money.
Lay your ass down. Lay down.
Hurry up.
No. No.
Okay.
[GUNSHOT]...
...[WOMAN SCREAMING].
Now fill it up.
Give him the money.
And hurry up, goddamn it.
I said, hurry up.
Fill up everything.
Oh, my God.
DARNELL: Everything.
Hurry up.
Come on, man. Don't cry now.
- Hurry up.
WOMAN 1: Here, here, take it.
Oh, my God. No.
LORENZ: Come on, man.
DARNELL: All right, stay down.
[TIRES SQUEALING].
GUARD: Is everyone okay?
It's all right now.
[CRYING].
STRODE: Okay. Okay.
Why don't, uh...?
Why don't we take it from the top?
I thought we covered everything.
- How well did you know the perpetrator?
I've just known Darnell
from around the way, is all.
We live in the same projects.
STRODE: Frankie, will you do me a favor?
Just tell me one thing,
and we'll get out of here.
Sure.
STRODE: What's the procedure
when you're being robbed?
Look, sir.
FRANKIE: I'm aware that I did. I'm aware...
- Stop, stop. Stop now.
What's the procedure
when you're being robbed?
You pull the money clip...
...from your right-hand drawer.
And then you signal with the left...
- You signal with the left.
So you know the procedure?
Yes, like I said, the procedure
has been told to me over a million times.
But why is it
if that procedure's been told to you...
...why didn't you follow the procedure?
Because he had a gun.
And I went for my clip, but he shot her.
He shot her right in front of me.
I'm afraid, Miss Sutton,
we're gonna have to let you go.
The fact you knew the perpetrator
doesn't sit well with us.
Wait, wait. That's not right.
I haven't done anything wrong.
I can't help who I know.
Mr. Zachery...
...just last week you gave me a promotion,
and now you're gonna take my job away?
What happens the next time
one of your friends robs the bank?
How do we know you're not in collusion?
Collusion?
Let me tell you something.
I am here at 8:20 sharp every morning.
I work my ass off until quitting time.
Yesterday I counted $240,000
by hand for you.
That's how you should know.
I mean, come on, this is just not right.
I nearly got blown away
in your tired-ass fucking bank.
And you're gonna fire me?
ZACHERY: Calm down.
- You couldn't even wait.
You didn't even bother to ask me
if I was thirsty, sister.
STRODE: She's involved.
I want everything you have on her.
[LAUGHING].
I thought I said a '70s graduation party.
'70s, Halloween, what's the difference?
You the only one in the neighborhood
who'd give a '70s graduation party.
Anyway, T.T., Jajuan,
y'all look awfully groovy tonight.
You like it, girl?
- Thank you for following directions.
Simple directions.
Would you look at him? Ain't he fine?
Handsome as he wants to be.
- I know.
STONY:
Can you believe he's going to college?
Man, I remember
when you was just a little scrub...
...always trying to follow us around
and shit.
On that tricycle.
[LAUGHS].
Y'all always trying
to mess up somebody game.
Please. CLEO: Game?
What game?
WOMAN: Whatever.
You got a 10 I can borrow?
We need more chips. Stuff running out.
Come on, you're the one
that's gonna be making all the loot.
STONY: Yeah, college boy.
- You got to stop spoiling that boy.
Taking care of him
ever since your mama and daddy died.
[SIGHS]...
What you got?
- You ain't drinking none of this shit.
Stevie, what's the problem?
I'm not going.
I ain't going to college.
What?
All right, look, don't start tripping.
Okay, you cannot change your mind. We
got into UCLA, that's where we're going.
I ain't changed my mind.
I just didn't get a scholarship.
They didn't give you a scholarship?
- No.
We told them, only way we could apply...
- I know.
[SCOFFS].
All right, well don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
It's probably just because
I'm a January graduate.
How you gonna take care of it?
You can barely pay the bills around here.
I'll just get a job.
I'll just help around here until I can just...
- No.
Wrong, we gonna stick to the plan...
...and we are definitely getting you
up out of here.
I ain't here with this fool.
- Good afternoon, ladies...
...and gentleman.
All right, listen up.
Now, these good white folks...
...are out here trying to recycle all of
their glasses, plastics and aluminum.
And you bitches putting
all the shit in the dumpsters.
You got to recycle.
Who had 104?
I did.
You didn't empty the cans in 104.
I'm docking your pay.
That ain't right.
LUTHER: Who are you supposed to be?
Goddamn Mighty Morphing
fucking Power Ranger?
What you gonna do?
I'm docking her pay.
Speaking of pay...
...I thought you said
that you was gonna pay me under the table.
They're taking taxes out of my check.
I ain't got enough money...
...to pay for my babysitter.
- On this good earth...
...there are three peoples
I don't mess with.
The I, the R, and the S.
But I got my babysitter.
Look, if you don't like working
for Luther's Janitorial...
...why don't you just
take your broke ass home?
Otherwise, shut the fuck up
and get back to work.
Hey. You know, you're one
cold-hearted motherfucker, Luther.
Get back to work.
- You ain't have to talk to her like that.
STONY: Tisean, you have got to
learn to stand up for yourself.
Did y'all hear what happened to Frankie?
Our Frankie? TISEAN: What?
Lorenz and them robbed her bank.
STRODE: This kid's got 211s in four cities.
He has one at Nevada, Arizona.
I mean, shit he's damn near a professional,
and what's he, 21?
They're getting younger.
Yeah.
I want everything you've got
on his young ass.
Where he hangs out, who he knows...
...where his mother lives, everything.
I want it all.
WALLER: Look at that. Check that out.
His hair.
What is that?
AP?
What's that, a nickname?
Asshole Perhaps? Ha, ha.
- Perhaps.
Asshole Perhaps.
Oh, fuck off.
[LAUGHING].
Cleo, when are you gonna fix
this raggedy shit?
CLEO: Never mind my shit, fool.
- Ha, ha.
I heard what happened
at the bank the other day.
Keep your head up, girl, all right?
All right.
Up, up, up. Ha, ha.
You need to wash this motherfucker
or something.
That's all right. Your shit is original.
Damn right.
Don't worry,
one day my shit is gonna be tight.
Cleo, girl, you've been fixing up this car
since 7th grade.
[STONY & TISEAN LAUGHING].
Do you know Lorenz
and them got away with 20 grand?
Twenty G's, damn.
See, that's what the fuck we need to do.
Rob a bank.
No, that's crazy.
CLEO: Now really, though.
The four of us could take a bank.
[LAUGHING].
Look, if that crackhead, Darnell could
rob a bank, we could take the bank.
Twenty G's would save my life right now.
Stevie needs tuition.
Well, too bad we ain't some hard-up
crackhead motherfuckers...
...like Lorenz and them.
Then, sure, we could do some suicidal shit
like rob a bank.
But we ain't crazy, so we can't.
FRANKIE: So now you making the rules?
- Frankie, please.
Please, ain't nobody over here
gonna be robbing no bank.
FRANKIE: You're right.
We ain't gonna rob no bank. Mm-mm.
Let's just go in there
and blow it the fuck up.
[LAUGHING].
Here you go.
Can you believe after working
for that damn bank for two years...
...I can't even get a recommendation
for another job?
I'm gonna hook you up with Luther.
I know you ain't happy,
but you need a job.
Ursula. Ursula, come here.
STONY: How you doing, Ursula?
- Come here, Boo.
[FRANKIE GROANS THEN STONY SIGHS].
What's up?
What the fuck is up? She don't talk?
TISEAN: No, really.
What's up? You know better than that.
You've been gone all day.
Girl, next time I page you,
you better be calling me back.
Excuse me.
Drink, please.
What's up, girl?
That's a cute outfit.
- Want some?
- Mm-hm.
TISEAN:
Hey, Stony, look, girl. It's Nate Andrews.
Hey, hey.
Girl, didn't he want you
come work in his car lot for him?
STONY: Yes, and that's not all he wanted.
ANDREWS: Hey, Stony.
You going over there?
Yeah, I'm gonna see what he wants.
ANDREWS: Hi, what you guys doing?
[BOTH LAUGHING].
So how much money could I make
selling cars for you?
Oh, well, it depends. I mean...
Oh, you can make, oh,
2 G's a month on commission.
- I can make that much?
- Yeah.
I told you, you needed to get
with somebody who could help you.
Nate, before I come work for you...
- Yeah?
I need an advance.
There's a little problem that I need to fix.
- Ah.
Oh, I can do that.
Oh, yeah, yeah, I can do that.
But, I mean...
...Stony Newsom's gotta give me
a reason to do that.
You know what I mean?
And what would that be?
Oh, come on, now, you know.
[CHUCKLES].
Let's go for a ride, huh?
[ANDREWS GROANING].
Mm, mm.
So when do I get my advance?
Oh, I don't know.
Tomorrow, maybe the day after.
Look, Nate, before I do this,
I want my check.
Hey, whoa, whoa, look.
You're not getting no check from me
until I'm done, you understand?
This ain't right. It's not even worth it.
Shit.
I'm in a bind, Nate.
Some other time.
I really need this money, Nate.
[ANDREWS MOANING & GRUNTING]...
...[SOBBING]...
...[CRASH].
What the fuck is that?
It's Frankie, it's her first night.
What's wrong with you?
- Nothing.
Look at this motherfucker.
Bet you he ain't never held a broom
in his life.
And she ain't did no dishes
or wash no clothes.
This is a ugly-ass baby.
Yo, white people be having some old
water head, crying-ass, ugly babies.
Stony, I can't unload these things
without dropping them.
Frankie, relax.
How can you stand the smell of garbage?
- Girl, shit ain't that bad.
It ain't that bad?
Cleo, that's because you live in a garage.
- Girl, it'll be okay.
And you, stay out of it.
Damn, look at my nails.
Girl, you been bitching all night.
Stony back there
acting all stink-a-dink-dink.
[FRANKIE & CLEO & TISEAN LAUGHING].
That's all right,
I got something for that head.
[WOMAN LAUGHING].
FRANKIE: Ow, girl, that hurt. Girl.
Well, that's the only way
you get the knot out.
Yeah, I rolled this one good.
Blunt talking to a motherfucker.
Stop it, girl. Stinky.
Here.
Now, Cleo, I done told you,
I'm strictly dickly.
See I'm gonna tell Ursula.
- You won't tell nobody.
Hey, check out Stony.
Look at her. Look at her.
Chronic always get her ass all quiet.
Look at her sitting over there.
Hey, you fucked up, ain't you, girl?
[LAUGHING]...
...[BOTH LAUGHING].
What?
Why? What's wrong?
You know, every time we get high
you start looking like Sugar Bear.
For real.
Y'all are cold.
You do kind of look like Sugar Bear.
Fuck all y'all.
Ooh.
Old simple bitches.
Oh, Cleo, don't get salty.
CLEO: Damn.
Before they started laying people off...
...they was paying folks
$15 dollars an hour at that place.
TISEAN: Oh, man, that's good money.
Nigga, for $15 dollars
an hour, I'd be all:
'Full-ply radial. What I gotta do, sir?'
Ass motherfucker.
They'd have to pull me off that machine.
FRANKIE: Shit, I know that's right.
CLEO:
Overtime would be like 22.50 an hour.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
Now that Luther's
taking taxes out of my check...
...I'm making half as much as I used to.
Only way we gonna see cash
is we take a bank.
Now, see, I'm with that shit.
- Y'all niggas done lost your mind.
Might as well not even talk about this shit.
- Well, I'm talking about it.
Ain't nobody gonna stop me
from talking about it.
Well, talk is cheap.
Nigga.
[ALL LAUGHING].
Wake up, I mean, you know...
Frankie, you gonna get socked
dead in the eye.
Fuck it.
- Nigga, you're always talking shit.
First you wanna blow the bank up,
now you wanna rob it.
Frankie wanna blow up the bank. Oh.
Frankie wanna rob the bank.
Well, I ain't heard nothing about that.
No.
For real, though?
I said, hang up the phone.
You know who that is.
Yeah, I gotta go. I'll be over.
And don't drink up my champagne, man.
Peace.
Champagne?
Whatever, I ain't got time.
Look, did your sister come through for you
or what?
Where'd you get this?
- Don't worry about where I got it...
...ain't your business, look at the digits.
Look.
Stony, there's something I gotta tell you.
- Look, I know this is hardly enough money.
But I swear I will get every...
- No, no, no. Listen to me.
I didn't get into UCLA.
And I'm not going
because I didn't get accepted.
You didn't get in?
- Come on, Stony, don't go off on me now.
Don't you tell me not to go off on you.
Do you have any idea
what I had to go through?
Do you?
I'm not staying around for this.
You are gonna hang around for this
and don't you move.
Why did you have to lie to me?
Stony, you know how long you told me
that I had to go to college?
Well, I'm sorry, but maybe that life
is just not for me.
Shit.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR].
LORENZ: Who is it?
STEVIE: Lorenz, it's Stevie, man.
Come on, open up, man.
Hey, Lorenz, chill, man.
Hey, I heard you robbed a bank.
Rob no bank.
Heard your party was off the hook.
- Yeah.
You know why I didn't come,
because your sister don't like me.
She be tripping.
Here, Mr. UCLA.
Here.
You all right?
- Yeah, I'm straight, man.
LORENZ: Are you?
Hey, that AP is phat.
Acorn Projects, bro. Thought you knew.
No, what?
You want this, huh?
No, man, I'm straight. No.
- You want this?
You know your sister will whoop your ass.
My sister ain't gonna do nothing.
Tanika, hook him up.
He ain't even from Acorn.
Fuck all that. Hook his ass up.
Take your ass in the kitchen,
with your raggedy ass. You talk too much.
Come on.
LORENZ: Ain't nothing funny, man.
Go on, you too.
STEVIE: Yeah.
All right.
All right, man, cool.
Thanks for the champagne.
LORENZ: Yeah.
MAN 1: Freeze.
MAN 2: Get down on the ground.
Get down.
MAN 3: Get on the ground now.
Get on the ground now.
MAN 2: Get down.
Get him down.
MAN 4: Get down, down.
- Get down.
- Get down, asshole.
MAN 2: Get down.
MAN 5: He's got a gun.
Wait.
[STEVIE SCREAMING]...
Waller.
WALLER: Check apartment M, now.
Get me an ambulance. Get me a medic.
WALLER: No. He's up there.
- Move out.
- He's up there.
STRODE: Get me an ambulance now.
Come on, goddamn it.
Stay with me here.
Stay with me. You stay with me.
Get me a fucking ambulance.
Huh?
Oh, no.
No, no, no. Goddamn it.
A fucking champagne bottle.
MAN: Open it, quick.
Come on, move in.
LORENZ: Punk-ass pigs.
What you fucking with me for, huh?
Let all you fuckers...
MAN 1: Man down. Man down, get in here.
MAN 2: Get him covered.
MAN 3: Go, go, go.
MAN 4: Let's go.
[GUNFIRE].
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]:
- ... Twenty-eight. West Valley station.
Unit 5 clear.
1085 clear.
MAN: Stay back, folks. Stand back.
STONY: Stevie.
Stevie.
[CRYING].
WOMAN: All units tagged...
No. My God, don't let...
What have you done?
Excuse me.
Not this motherfucker.
If you need to talk,
if you have any questions...
...you won't hesitate to call.
There'll be a full investigation.
[STONY SCREAMING].
TISEAN: Stop.
- All right, all right.
Okay, okay, okay.
STONY: Fuck you. Fuck your investigation.
You fucking go to hell.
You son of a bitch.
CLEO: It's gonna be all right.
What do you got?
Stevie Newsom, no priors,
good student, headed for college.
I hear both parents killed in a
car accident four years ago.
Goddamn it.
Goddamn.
TISEAN: Damn.
Y'all she been throwing up for two days.
What we gonna do?
Let her get that shit out.
Somebody gotta stay with her.
I will.
[SOBBING].
I saw Stevie's hair in the bathroom.
I can't go... I can't go back in there.
I don't wanna go back in the bathroom
no more...
I never need to.
Oh, my, I don't wanna...
I don't wanna stay in here.
I can't stay in here no more.
- Okay, okay.
Stay with me. STONY: No.
No, I want out of here. All of it.
No.
FRANKIE: We can do this.
We can get some wigs,
some sunglasses and it's on.
TISEAN: Y'all are gonna have to do this
without me.
I keep thinking about Darnell getting
killed and Lorenz shot and Stevie...
That's because Darnell and them
were a bunch of damn fools.
They don't know half
of what I know about banks.
What if something goes wrong?
What if somebody gets hurt?
FRANKIE: Listen to me.
Damn, you're just scared, baby.
Ain't nobody gonna get hurt.
That's why this is the perfect crime.
I know this too well.
- What about all them folks money?
CLEO: Insurance.
Dumb-ass comment.
FRANKIE: Look...
...we just taking away from the system
that's fucking us all anyway.
You know?
Let's do it.
Excuse me.
MAN: Hi, how are you?
WOMAN: Hi.
MAN: Come on in.
Go right ahead and have a seat.
WOMAN: Thank you.
KEITH: How can I help you today, Miss...?
- Dorsey. Yeah.
- Dorsey.
I'd like to open up a new account.
Oh. Uh...
Right this way.
You can open an interest-bearing account
with a thousand dollar deposit, if you like.
A thousand dollars?
Yeah.
Uh, do you...? Do you have long lines?
No, no, not too bad. We usually operate
typically with about 14 tellers. Uh...
...[LAUGHING].
Actually, Miss Dorsey,
I'm a manager in corporate
banking upstairs.
I don't know what these folks do. But
when I saw you, I said to myself I said:
'Self, a woman that fine,
as fine as you are and you are that fine...
...needs to have her own personal banker.'
So I couldn't help myself.
[CHUCKLES].
She smiles, come on now.
Um...
Miss Dorsey, I'm new in town and I swear
to you I don't do this all the time.
I know you don't know me.
I don't know your plans...
...if you even have plans tonight.
Do you have plans tonight?
Are you asking me out?
Maybe.
Keith, well I see
you're in new accounts now, huh?
Come on, let's go.
- Nigel, thank you.
Thank you for your observation there.
These people are gonna kill me.
Now, can I have your number?
- No.
- No?
But I'll take yours.
Well, what were you doing in there?
I was just talking.
I thought we was coming here
to case the bank.
That's what I was doing.
He has an inside track. He works here.
Plus, he grabbed me.
Did he ask you out?
Maybe.
So you ain't gonna tell me, huh?
Well, maybe he can put a smile on my face.
[VACUUM CLEANER WHIRRING].
Tisean.
Girl, Luther is gonna kill you
if he see that baby in here.
T.T., what happened?
TISEAN: I had to bring him with me.
Hey, hey. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
T.T., no, no. Don't put him there.
Please, please. Put him over there.
Put him over there.
[JAJUAN CRYING].
CLEO: Come on.
STONY: Come on, move it.
You're gonna be all right.
- We can't waste time.
- Hold the elevator.
- Hurry up.
Open it up. Hurry up.
- All right, it's all right.
I think your son
is going to pull through just fine.
- Oh, yes.
- Can I see him?
You need to speak to Ms. Wells
with the Child Protective Services.
No, no, no.
I know you ain't fitting to take her son.
Wait, now, hold the fuck up.
That was a accident.
I mean, we was right there.
We was looking right at him.
Wasn't even like two seconds...
- I need to talk to the mother alone.
- Cleo.
- Go on, T.T.
WOMAN [ON PA]:
Donna Kilmen, please call extension 453.
Miss Williams,
the boy has been severely poisoned.
I'm sure it was an accident.
But we're gonna retain custody just to be
sure the child isn't suffering from neglect.
That's my son.
I would die for him.
He was in an unsafe environment.
He shouldn't have been at the workplace.
Well, I didn't have a choice.
I don't have money for a babysitter.
You're gonna have to prove
you can take care of him.
But kids get into poison every day.
WELLS: Not in the workplace.
To us that spells neglect.
Now, Jajuan will remain in our custody
until you can pay for proper child care.
Well, what if I can't come up
with the money?
Like I said, you will get a court date.
At that time,
the judge will decide what will happen.
No. No.
Please, you can't take my baby.
I'm gonna die without my baby.
STONY: Tisean, come on. Come on.
TISEAN: I'm gonna die without my baby.
- Look, now, T.T., we gonna handle this.
TISEAN: Oh, God.
STONY: Come on.
Fuck this shit.
You know what you got to do.
You know.
You in? STONY: Can't we just...
Come on, T.T.
FRANKIE: Cleo, take the note to the
merchant teller. She will have 20 grand.
On Wednesdays, Sears
makes a big deposit,
so she could have 35,000.
Can I give her the note,
tell her not to give bank money?
Cleo, you gotta tell her not to draw
from the right-hand clip.
If she draws from the right-hand clip,
she's setting off the alarm.
I say, 'Don't give me bank money.
If you come out with that clip,
my gun is going in your mouth.'
That's what I'm talking about.
Let's go through plan B.
CLEO: Plan B?
The fuck this planning shit.
Why can't we just get buck
with these motherfuckers...
...go in there and take the money?
Why can't you just listen for once?
Plan B, Frankie.
FRANKIE: All right, plan B.
Stony, when Cleo goes to the teller,
you start to survey the line for the cow.
Cow?
There's gonna be a cow up in there?
Stop smoking weed.
Cleo, the cow is just a small vault
on wheels.
They push it from window to window
depending on which teller needs cash.
All right now, if the cow is there,
it'll be open...
...and we'll have at least 50,000.
[GUN COCKS].
CLEO: Look here, let me talk to Black Sam.
Black Sam, she wanna talk to you.
Goddamn.
Shit.
How you doing?
So, what you need?
I need a favor.
Yeah, so, what else is new?
Come on, Black Sam.
After all them cars I just stole for you,
before you got into this gun-running shit.
You owe me.
Oh, we going there, right?
All right, check it out.
Y'all can roll with that right there.
Man, we ain't robbing stage coaches.
I need something I can set it off with.
Damn, y'all ain't bullshitting, huh?
We want them guns we were shooting.
Y'all can't afford them guns.
That's why it's a favor.
I'll bring them back with interest.
With interest, huh?
Check this:
So hook me up with your homegirl, Frankie.
[CLEO CHUCKLES].
Interest, that's it, Sam.
BLACK SAM:
All right, this is what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna let y'all use my shit, right,
but if y'all get caught...
I'm already knowing.
I'm knowing.
BLACK SAM: Yeah, all right.
I'm coming back for that Uzi too.
Yo, Bruce, go on and hook them up.
- The right shit.
- All right.
[CAR ALARM WAILING]...
...[CAR ALARM SILENCES].
Come on, baby.
[CAR STARTS].
All right, yeah.
What do we got here? Bullshit.
Bullshit, bullshit.
Fucking bullshit.
Yeah.
[RAP MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO].
Now, that's what I ride to.
Y'all ready?
- Y'all okay?
- Okay.
Okay, wait. Okay, wait a minute.
Let's just wait.
Let's just wait a minute.
Okay, let's just wait. Just for a second.
What's wrong?
I can't do this.
Frankie, she's right.
We didn't case this bank.
We cased Downtown Federal.
They're all pretty much the same.
I ain't feeling this, Frankie.
This ain't right.
Okay.
Everybody get down
on the ground right now.
Put your hands up. Move back, everyone.
STONY: Everybody stay down. Stay down.
CLEO: Don't touch that fucking gun.
Get on the ground.
Go, go.
STONY: Okay, all right, okay.
Turn around.
All of y'all, turn the fuck around.
Don't move. Don't move.
- Move back. Move back.
STONY: Okay.
Turn around, what the fuck you looking at?
FRANKIE: Give me the money, the drawer.
- Put that phone down. Put it down.
Put your arms up. Hey. Hey.
You'd better lay down.
Lay down. Lay down.
Lay down. Don't move.
CLEO: Y'all just be cool.
Don't move. Don't move.
- Stay there.
- Come on.
What are you looking at?
I'm a bitch with a gun.
Two.
STONY: We're taking too much time.
FRANKIE:
Take the money. Don't try and be a hero.
STONY: All right, here we go.
FRANKIE: Come on.
- Here we go. Yeah.
- All right.
STONY: Move it, we're almost to the door.
Almost to the door. Come on, come on.
Yeah, slow it down, slow it down.
CLEO: Got it. Got it.
Yeah.
FRANKIE: Whoo. Get up y'all.
Come on, move, move, move.
[TIRES SQUEALING
AND CAR HORNS HONKING].
Now, that's how you work it.
That shit was brilliant.
Frankie, we robbed a bank.
Aah. Whoo.
Listen to me, that is a lot of money.
Are we gonna get away with this?
What do you mean are we gonna get
away with this? What does this look like?
Is it ours?
Yes.
- Whoo.
- Shit.
Did you lock that door?
And where have you been?
I caught the bus.
Yo, we weren't ready.
You know we weren't ready.
FRANKIE: Look.
If I didn't set it off, we'd be casing
banks for the next two months.
I had to push y'all.
It worked, didn't it?
CLEO: Ha, ha.
Look, Tisean, it's over.
We got about...
- What?
- About 12 G's.
Twelve thousand dollars in 60 seconds.
Why don't you come over here
and sit down beside me.
Okay? Come on.
TISEAN: Twelve thousand dollars.
- Whoo.
- Aah.
STONY: Cleo, sit.
Vehicle stolen here today was lD'd as the
getaway car in that South L.A. bank job.
Oh yeah?
I want prints on all these.
See if anybody shows up.
Yeah, all right. Dust everything.
STONY: Frankie.
Cleo.
Moi and T. T.
T.T.? She ain't getting a cut.
Look, Frankie,
I ain't for your shit tonight, all right?
T.T. needs it more than any of us.
- She didn't do anything. She walked out.
Who the fuck cares?
- She was there.
- No, fuck that.
She didn't do nothing,
she ain't getting nothing.
Forget it.
Frankie, I don't want your money.
If you wanna kick my ass,
come on, let's just get it over with...
...because I am sick of your shit.
I need that money.
It ain't you I'm mad at.
Damn.
I'm sorry I was tripping.
You my girl.
I need this.
You are so special, Frankie.
Still ain't do shit.
[LAUGHING].
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]: Ten-eleven, roger.
STRODE: Hey, Waller?
WALLER: Yeah?
STRODE: Anything on Francesca Sutton?
WALLER: Who?
The teller suspected of being in collusion
in the Pan Pacific robbery.
Nothing, clean as a whistle.
- Nothing?
- Nothing.
Here, run this again for me.
And in what may be a first
for Los Angeles...
...three women have robbed the branch
at South Los Angeles Bank.
Getting away
with an estimated $90,000 dollars.
Ninety thousand?
BOTH [IN UNISON]: Insurance scam.
[FRANKIE LAUGHING].
This is the 25th bank robbery
this year in Los Angeles...
...the bank robbery capital of the nation.
And now on to national news.
[KNOCKING]...
...[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]...
- Hey.
- Hi.
Wanna come in for a drink?
- No, thank you.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
All right, hold on. Let me get my jacket.
Could've come and pick you up,
you know.
Oh, no, I needed the exercise. Thanks.
- You look great.
- Thanks.
What?
- What?
- Nothing, I just...
I've just never been out
with a guy like you before, that's all.
A guy like me, a guy like me.
What does that mean, a guy like me?
Oh, I see. You must be used to those
roughneck types. Ls that what it is?
So where we gonna eat?
I don't know. I was thinking maybe...
...you could show me
someplace in your hood.
- In my hood?
- Your hood, yes.
You ain't trying to flow like that.
- I might be trying to.
You're probably from Harvard and all.
As a matter of fact, I am.
I still gotta eat.
And I'm still very hungry
so could we please feed a man.
Give him some nourishment
or some sustenance.
That's all I'm asking...
...Miss You-Need-To-Starve
Because-You're-From-Harvard.
KEITH: This is really a nice restaurant.
It's black-owned, I like that.
Do you come here often?
No, I've never been, I just heard about it.
- So where are you from?
- D.C.
- Have you ever been?
- Nope.
KEITH: Mm.
No, but that's where the mayor
got popped basing up, isn't it?
[CHUCKLES].
Yeah, well, nobody's perfect, right?
It's a great town, though.
I miss it. I really, really miss it.
Anyway, I came directly from New York.
Have you ever been to New York?
- No.
KEITH: Ever been outside Los Angeles?
When I was in New York, I was working
on Wall Street and before that B school.
STONY: B school?
- Business school, I'm sorry.
I wanted to go to business school.
- Really?
What, financing, uh, marketing?
No, typing and bookkeeping.
[CHUCKLES].
Oh, I'm sorry.
Is that not professional enough?
It's hard for me to believe that you're
this hard when you're so beautiful.
And so tough.
I'm not tough. I just don't think
we have anything in common.
Stony, I don't want anything from you.
I really don't.
I have no expectations, no demands.
I am quite content...
...just listening to you.
Sitting here.
Staring into those beautiful,
pretty brown eyes.
Are you cross-eyed?
No, your head is just small. Ha, ha.
KEITH: Ha, ha.
My head is small.
Makes my eyes go this way:
Because I have to focus in on your little peanut.
No, I'm just kidding.
KEITH: Oh, my peanut.
[KEITH & STONY LAUGHING].
KEITH: This is it.
It's not much but, it's home.
I took the lease over from my brother
who brought me to L.A.
STONY: Do you feel free?
KEITH: Hell, yeah, I feel free.
STONY: Hmm. Hmm.
Well, I don't feel free.
I feel very much caged.
Caged. Hmm.
What are you doing about it?
- What do you mean?
This cage,
what are you doing to get out?
What are your plans? I mean, where do you
see yourself, say, in five years, Stony?
I don't know.
See that's...
That's what I'm saying.
We don't plan for the future, as a people.
We never... Have you ever thought about it?
I mean, really put serious thought
where you see yourself in the future?
Well, I worked really hard to keep
a roof over me and my brother's head.
To keep clothes on our back.
[SIGHS]...
And I planned on sending him to college.
- That's great.
Then he should go to college.
He'll go on and accomplish things...
...and he'll be great and wonderful,
like his sister.
He's dead.
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't realize.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not.
No.
I'm dealing with it.
You are, aren't you?
Tough lady.
Ls that a Cabernet or Merlot?
- Damn.
MAN 1: Take care of it.
MAN 2: All right, I'll follow it up.
The next time he has a problem...
- Captain Fredricks, sir?
Do remember the bank robbery
where four people were killed...
...and the arrest of the perp
where a young man was killed?
We're still getting bad press for that.
Sir, I'd like to bring in his sister.
I think she's one of the robbers.
What you got?
- I've got a girl named Francesca Sutton.
She's a teller at the Pan Pacific Bank.
I'm certain she was connected to the thing.
Go on, go on.
- Francesca and Lida are best friends.
Right, that's a big coincident, okay?
There's also physical likeness...
- Wait, do you remem...
They're real suspects.
- Do you remember the headline?
'Innocent student killed by cop.'
- I remember.
You bring in his sister based on the fact
that she knows someone...
...who may be friends with a robber?
- Right.
What the hell's wrong with you, Strode?
No way.
Can I get a tail on her, sir?
What part of 'no'
don't you understand, Strode?
The N or the 0?
[CHUCKLES].
Up. We go... Oh, shit.
Now watch it. Watch it.
Aah. Fuck them niggas now.
[LAUGHING].
Watch it. Watch it, honey.
Here it come now.
CLEO: Oh, now. Oh, shit, girl.
What is you doing?
Cleo, how come you
ain't been to work in a week?
Because look what I got here.
I bought my baby some new things.
Check them out.
Luther said you fired.
STONY: Cleo. Cleo.
We gotta act like nothing's different.
Now, you need to get to Luther's
and get your job back.
Man, Luther can kiss my ashy kneecap.
- Money got you tripping.
I know you out of money by now, Cleo.
Now what you gonna do?
Rob another goddamn bank.
What the fuck is y'all thinking?
Hold on, we said once, Cleo.
To get us change to get us up out of here.
And that's all it is, Stony.
We need some real money.
I don't know how far out of town
you plan to get, baby sister.
But you ain't getting far on 3 grand.
Oh, really?
All right, Louise, you
take Thelma over there...
...and y'all go rob another
bank if you all that.
CLEO: Fuck you.
I know you ain't fitting to back down on us
now that we need you.
I want some more motherfucking money.
Cleo, you are real high...
...and you acting real stupid.
You need to get that gun off my face.
Oh, shit.
- Don't you ever raise a gun to me again.
CLEO: Or what? Or what? What? What?
Are you gonna hit me, motherfucker?
Stony, we go back to first grade.
You've been my peeps for 20 years.
- Cleo, come on.
Get off of me.
You know what?
I ain't fucking with you no more.
STONY: Yeah, well, fuck you too.
Fuck you, fuck you. Fuck you.
Fuck her.
[HUMMING]...
...[LATIN MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]...
...[SPEAKING IN SPANISH].
Come on in.
How you doing?
- I'm all right.
- You sure?
All right, now,
I hope you like Mexican foods.
We have fajitas, enchiladas, special sauce.
You have a seat right there.
Now, you say you don't travel a lot.
This is what we're gonna do, Stony.
From here on out.
I cook, we eat, you pick the country,
starting with Mexico.
And now sit back, relax,
load off your feet.
Smell the aroma of Mexico and the sounds.
What?
I just got a lot on my mind.
You wanna talk about it?
No.
Okay.
What do you think
about friends and money?
[CHUCKLES].
I think they don't mix, why?
I just had a very big argument
with one of my best friends...
...about a money situation.
And I don't think
we're gonna be friends anymore.
Don't you lose that friend over money.
It's not worth it.
Money you can replace easy.
Friends, real friends, you can't.
Don't sweat it.
You have the answer to everything,
don't you?
No, I wouldn't say that.
I'm just sharing my experience with you.
Who do you think you are?
I'll be your genie if you let me.
Your every wish is my command.
Cleo, you know you was wrong
for what you did to Stony.
Fuck her.
Fuck Stony.
We'll do this without her.
- Now, wait a minute.
Now, suppose Stony put a gun in your face,
what would you do?
I would've slapped you too.
Oh, come on now,
you know I wasn't gonna shoot her.
You know how I get when I'm faded.
You still was wrong.
So T.T., what's my girl gonna do?
Girl, you gotta step to that judge
and prove you got some coins in the bank.
I ain't doing nothing without Stony.
Stony.
I don't wanna give that ho no ride.
- Stop acting like a baby.
STRODE: Bingo.
Come to me, baby.
Oh, yeah, grand theft auto.
I love to see it.
- Hey, Waller?
- Yeah.
Tell me something.
Yeah.
- Did I or did I not say...
...all these women run together?
WALLER: Hmm.
Do you feel me?
I thought that you would.
Work with me, baby.
Look, I'm sorry.
You're sorry.
Let's just put it all behind us.
Come on.
We've been through worse.
Apology accepted.
But you know
you need to come back in with us.
You ain't got enough money
to get out of town.
You're right about that.
But I want more than that.
I mean, is this the only way?
See, I wanna be somebody
who doesn't have to do this crap.
You know what I'm saying?
[CHUCKLES].
Stony, you can go to suburbia
and start a new life.
But we ain't nothing but hood rats.
Now, I can live with that, you can't.
The hood is where I belong.
I mean, what am I gonna do in Hollywood?
Or Thousand Oaks or some shit?
[LAUGHING].
Man, shit.
Why we gotta roll over
and accept that though?
We gotta have a plan.
What does our future look like?
Where do you see yourself
five years from now?
I don't know.
And I don't care.
But I ain't thinking
about five years from now.
I'm just trying to get through the day.
LUTHER: What the hell?
Cleo, I know you didn't come to work...
...ain't been to work
and don't call nobody.
I'm broke, Luther.
I know you gonna give me my job back...
...because nobody take shit
the way I take shit.
Now, shut up before I stick
that mop up your ass, Luther.
You better save that for
your little girlfriend.
Well, get to work...
...ladies and gentleman.
[ITALIAN ACCENT]
There's been a rift in this family...
...and that is not good for business.
See, we wanna play it like it was.
Back to work, see?
If only Tisean and Stony
will come rob the bank with us.
We started as a gang of four.
We must always be four.
Don Stony from the Bronx.
What is your opinion?
Should we rob the bank?
[ITALIAN ACCENT]
The only way I can return to this family...
...if we do this one more time...
...we do it right.
[LAUGHING].
We get enough money
to get us up out of here for good.
T.T., you agree?
Cleomenza.
No more funny looking underwear
for your little girlfriend.
[ITALIAN ACCENT] Cleomenza, no more...
...fancy cars.
Shopping sprees.
Cleomenza.
Can you respect our conditions?
Can you live with the terms
that your dons have set forth?
[ITALIAN ACCENT] Yes, Godfather.
Tisean Scullino from Detroit,
are you cool with all of this?
I am.
And you...
...Don Stony from the Bronx.
Can you accept your godfather's terms?
All right then. We're back in effect.
Next stop, Balboa Savings and Loan.
CLEO: Whoa, right down there. Okay.
Yeah.
TISEAN: Think you can do that?
FRANKIE: Hurry up.
[CLEO GRUNTS]...
...[CLEO GRUNTING].
STONY: You got it?
[CAR STARTING].
STONY:
Come on, Cleo, what are you doing?
CLEO: Hey, pass me a tape.
STONY: No, let's go.
CLEO: Come on, I ain't going nowhere
till you pass me a tape.
STONY: Take that shit and let's go.
[RAP MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO].
CLEO: Ooh, yeah, it'll work.
Can you help me out?
WOMAN: Please don't...
- Come on, lady.
I've been out here all night.
WOMAN: Sir.
I'm sorry.
Come on,
just a couple of bucks or something.
- I'm sorry, ma'am.
- Come on.
Sir, please. WOMAN: Thank you.
Stop, you're annoying our customers.
- Come on, man.
I'm not hurting anybody.
- You are annoying our customers.
Now, I'd like you to move down the street
and leave our people alone.
I've been asked to come out here...
- Come on, man, I'm not hurting anybody.
GUARD: Look...
MAN: No, I'm not. No, I'm not.
What's your problem?
GUARD: Fuck, lay on the ground.
I didn't do anything.
Everybody get the fuck down right now.
Move it. You, down.
FRANKIE: Hands up and move back away
from the drawer.
That's right. You, move back. Get down.
Open the drawer and you fill it up.
Let's go.
Did you hear what I said?
FRANKIE: Give it up.
That's right.
- Back up, back up, back up.
You, up, let's go.
STONY: Hey, down, that's right.
TISEAN [SOBBING]: Oh, please.
Oh, please, mama.
Oh, please.
- Bitch, would you shut the fuck up?
STONY: Nobody move.
- What's going on?
- Talking...
Talking to the lady,
I'm not bothering anybody.
- Come on.
- Listen.
What's happening?
A minute and a half.
Get your money. Don't be a hero. Let's go.
- Okay. Okay.
You, open up the cow.
STONY: Everybody, do what I say.
Some backup over here. We got
a vagrant that's drunk and disorderly.
Uh, would you send another unit?
Come on, let's make it. Move it.
Let's make it, come on.
- Cover me.
Don't make me get ugly up in here,
ladies and gentlemen. Not today.
Don't look at me. Turn around.
Hey, you keep your hands down.
FRANKIE: Let's go.
STONY: Everybody, face down, face down.
FRANKIE: Let's go, let's go.
Keep him in line, girl.
Keep him in line. Down.
Hey, come on, let's make it.
[BREATHING HEAVILY].
Don't do it. Do not...
Where's Cleo?
[TIRES SQUEALING]...
...[GASPS]...
...[WOMEN SCREAMING].
Hey, come on, get in.
Shit.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on, come on, come on.
Yes.
- Come on, let's go. Goddamn it.
STONY: You are crazy, damn it.
[ALL SCREAMING]...
- Come on, let's go.
- Move it.
Move.
[ALL SCREAMING]...
...[CAR HORNS HONKING].
Yeah. Yeah.
We did that shit.
Wow.
The way you busted through that wall.
[ALL SCREAMING].
We did it. We did it.
I thought it was over
with the cops outside the bank.
Where was you going?
I don't know.
I was coming to get y'all asses.
Now, what about T.T.?
The way she got the drop on the cop.
You think of anything else,
you give us a call today.
This the girls?
- Took off in the Suburban.
Apparently the getaway car was blocked.
It's still out there.
Car theft report's
from near the 21 st Street garage.
They're getting in way over their heads,
aren't they?
They don't fucking know it.
Man, counting money is harder
than working for Luther.
I'm getting dizzy up here.
Two hundred and ninety-six thousand,
Stony, and counting. Whoo.
So, what's that?
- Seventy five thousand a piece.
Whoo.
Seventy-five thousand dollars a piece.
That's a lot of money.
I'm rich. Aah.
Ooh, look at all of this, okay.
Look, this is what we do.
We're gonna keep scrubbing floors...
...like we been doing, nothing's changed.
We're get Jajuan.
And in three days we are out of here.
I'm gonna miss y'all.
- Oh, T.T.
What happened? What'd she do?
Girl, you coming with us.
I got money. Ha, ha.
STRODE: Hey, Waller.
WALLER: Yeah?
STRODE: Run the CD's from the garage?
WALLER: They're clean.
Give these a try.
- Right.
- It's all connected.
All right, we'll get these dusted now.
[DRILL WHIRRING].
CLEO: Damn.
Cleo, how come we putting
all the money here instead of at home?
If the police track us
that's the first place they gonna look.
- Oh. Okay.
- All right?
All right.
[DRILL WHIRRING].
Stony, I'm substituting for my boss tonight
at a cocktail party...
...for the National Association of Bankers
at the Biltmore.
And I'd like you to accompany me.
- Aah. Damn it.
- Hey.
That would be really nice.
Great. Well, listen, be here early.
Don't know what time the limo's coming
since you won't let me pick you up.
Limo?
Yeah, black tie, limo, 6:00.
I'll see you then.
STONY: Y'all are real rude.
I know you heard me on the phone.
What phone?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR].
KEITH: Hey.
Do you like it?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, you look great.
No, you don't.
No, it's... it's colorful.
Colorful?
We're late. I'll be right back.
Great, Frankie,
I look like a box of crayons.
[SIGHS]...
...[KNOCKING ON DOOR].
KEITH: Stony, could you get that for me?
Yeah, can I help you?
OFFICER: You know, sir, a blue Lexus was
stolen from the garage this afternoon...
...from the space next to yours.
We wondered if you saw or heard it.
KEITH: No, no, I just got home myself.
Okay, thanks. Sorry to bother you.
KEITH: Not a problem, not a problem.
Are you okay?
I just don't like cops after what happened
with my brother, that's all.
All right, well, listen, car will be
right here, make yourself at home.
So you like?
It's real nice.
You got a bar, you got crystal.
Stony, we've been spending time
together lately. It's been nice.
We've been real straight forward
with one another and honest.
But I have lied about one thing.
What have you lied about?
Let's take a little detour.
Alex, do me a favor.
Change of plans.
Take a right at the next light.
And I'll tell you from there.
WOMAN: it's good to see you.
MAN: Fantastic. How are you?
Shall we go?
Hello.
You're doing great, lady.
- Enjoy yourself tonight.
- Okay.
- Champagne?
- Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
Are you nervous?
- Yes.
- Don't be.
You are the most beautiful lady in the
room, don't you ever forget that.
Okay. NIGEL: Keith, hey.
- Hey, Nigel.
- How you doing?
- Good. Patrice.
- Hey, Keith.
Thank God you are here.
I was getting sick and tired
of making banter with Rossman all night.
Yeah.
- Hello, I'm Nigel.
- Hi.
You are Miss New Account.
Keith, your follow-up, it's impressive.
I have taught Keith everything
he knows about banking.
Nigel, Patrice, I'd like you to meet my...
- Lady.
- Lady. Stony.
- Hi, I'm Patrice.
Nigel, nice to meet you.
KEITH: Stony.
There are some heavy hitters here.
Michigawa from Sanwa.
- I saw Strolman from Citibank over there.
Check this, if a terrorist
were to come and blow this place...
...the banking systems of Japan, Europe
and the United States would never recover.
Right.
- I thought a roomful of dead bankers...
...meant that, uh, the world
would be a better place. Ha, ha.
- Yeah. My wife.
- Yeah.
So, uh, Stony, are you in banking also?
- No.
- Yes, in a way.
Wells Fargo, B of A, Chemical?
Well, I prefer to create
my own personalized portfolio...
...which reflect an original diverse taste
in funding sources.
Well.
KEITH: Always got me into trouble,
always raiding the sororities.
Yeah, he hadn't grown up
but we're working on him.
STONY: Right.
He seems like a nice guy.
No, he's terrible.
- I hate him.
- Ha, ha.
He's a good guy.
I want you to know...
...that this is one of the best nights
of my life.
I've never felt so special.
Do you feel free now?
Well, for now, but it's not my life.
I'm just borrowing from pieces of yours.
Borrowing's not such a bad thing.
As long as you return the favor.
Look at all your friends.
They all own banks.
Where I'm from,
you're lucky to have a bank account.
[BLOWS].
I just wanna get out of here.
Have you ever felt like that?
Like you just wanted to get up and go
and move forward and you can't?
Baby, you don't have to go anywhere.
Stay with me.
For a little while.
And then you decide
if you wanna stick around.
You think about it.
Okay?
Your fine self.
[BOTH MOANING]...
...[BOTH LAUGHING].
You crazy.
Hi, I'm, uh, Pete Rodney.
I'm taking over for Luther.
Where's Luther?
He ain't cleaning this building no more.
He got out of the business.
You gotta be...
- Hi.
- How you doing?
Oh.
CLEO: This motherfucker
better not have touched that money.
FRANKIE: Rip it.
Come on, come on.
FRANKIE: it's gone.
- This mother...
Kill this motherfucker, come on.
Yo, Sam, you got company.
Hey, um, Sam, you seen Luther?
Yeah, Luther came by here earlier.
Looked like he came upon some dollars,
you know.
Had his shit all permed up.
Why, what's up?
We got twisted, man.
Our money and your interest.
Oh.
That's why that fool was acting crazy.
See, now you're fucking
with my money though.
But I know where he at.
He at a hotel over there on 55th.
Fifty-fifth and 9th.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Got a little something for that ass, baby.
[LUTHER & WOMAN MOANING].
CLEO: Climb out the pussy for a minute.
WOMAN: Aah.
Oh, God. WOMAN: What are you...?
Find it.
Go around this room.
Tear it up if you have to.
Think you slick, huh? Check her stuff too.
You slick, right?
You better be here
for a good goddamn reason.
Oh, my money is a good goddamn reason.
Now, where is it?
Money? What you talking about, money?
- I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Just one more time. Where's my money?
I told you,
I don't know nothing about no money.
You don't know what I'm talking about?
You don't know...
What the fuck is this, huh?
Look at this shit.
Watches and Cristal and shit you done
bought with my motherfucking money.
Oh, let's see what you got here.
What is this?
My money.
All right, bro.
[GUNSHOT THEN WOMAN SCREAMS].
WOMAN: Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
CLEO: Luther?
Oh, fuck.
WOMAN: Oh, no.
Alissa Lions, 483 Moorpark.
You didn't see none of this, right?
Right? ALISSA: Right.
All right,
it's a little fucking insurance, baby.
Just a little insurance.
Now, where did Luther hide that money?
I don't know.
- Where's the money?
CLEO: Don't give me that.
You know where that money is.
- I just met him.
Come on, come on.
Let's get up out of here. Let's go.
Come on, T.T.
- I'll call you.
- I hope so.
This weekend, ltalian.
[SIGHS].
I'll call you.
I ain't trying to hear this today.
Which one of you girls
smoked Luther, huh?
I'm thinking it was you Cleo,
you're the only one with any priors.
Don't know what you talking.
- I'll tell you what I'm talking.
We're gonna take a ride.
[WHISTLES].
Man, I ain't do shit.
You ain't got probable cause.
- All you're doing is a lineup.
And for the record, having a witness
is a lot better than probable cause.
Get in the car.
Today.
Take this home, call the girls.
ALISSA: You sure they can't see me?
WALLER: No, no.
Just your imagination.
It looks like everyone looking right at me.
- Do you see her?
Hmm?
The person that killed Luther Morris?
- Take your time and concentrate.
Hmm?
Face right.
You see her?
The person that killed Luther Morris.
No, it's not her.
Be sure now.
You see her.
The person that killed Luther Morris?
No.
STRODE: Look at her.
- Get a real good look.
Real close, right there.
See her?
The person that smoked Luther.
Nope.
Can I go now?
You're real cute.
They got Cleo
and y'all fucking killed Luther.
He wouldn't give up the money.
He was about to kill Cleo,
so Tisean shot him.
And now I got Cleo in trouble.
- Damn it.
- I'm sorry, Stony.
Look, they gonna be after all of us.
We gonna take that bank downtown.
Are you in?
No, I ain't in. Hell no.
You ain't got no fucking choice.
And you don't tell me
what fucking choices I have, Frankie.
There's armed robbery and there's murder.
You said we weren't gonna hurt anybody,
Frankie.
Stony.
Girl, I got to have money
before my court date. I have to.
And I can't go to jail for killing nobody.
I need you.
I really need you.
Cleo.
FRANKIE: Cleo, what happened?
STONY: Are you all right?
- Baby, go pack our shit.
The motherfuckers was all over me.
But I represented.
Now, the problem is,
they on our ass now.
And we got to do two things:
Rob another bank
and get the fuck out of here.
Or be in jail by tomorrow morning.
- I say we hit Downtown Federal.
That's where the most money's at.
I'm telling y'all.
We could get 500,000.
Fuck it. We hitting that shit.
Simple as that.
Look, Stony.
We hot.
We're all facing a murder rap.
Does it have to be Downtown Federal?
What the fuck is that?
What, you gonna play us?
Over that buppie at the bank?
Fine.
[GUN COCKS].
It's on.
- WOMAN: Miss Harris?
- Yes.
- How are you?
- Oh, very good.
I know you have a court date
tomorrow. Good luck, Tisean.
Thanks, Miss Wells.
You think everything's gonna be okay?
I'm sure it is.
Come here.
WELLS: Everything's gonna be just fine.
Come on, let's go. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
WELLS: Let's go. Yeah.
Okay.
Let's go.
STONY: All right?
WAITRESS: Okay, ladies. Will that be all?
- Some more coffee.
TISEAN: Cleo.
I don't think you should be drinking
so much coffee.
You're making me nervous.
How the fuck is my drinking coffee
making you nervous?
TISEAN: I don't know, it just is.
- Okay, okay, listen up.
Nobody has ever successfully robbed
this bank.
I wish you would stop saying that.
I'm saying that because the nearest freeway
is a mile away. We gotta stick to the plan.
All right?
I know y'all sick of wearing them wigs.
- What you got?
Okay? I got some other stuff in the car.
WAITRESS: Thank you, ladies.
Cover my share
till I finish robbing this bank.
I'm broke.
Don't look over here. I am too.
Y'all, we don't have enough money
to pay the bill?
Hey.
[CLEO GRUNTS].
We're in.
CLEO: Bullshit.
What the fuck is this?
- What are you doing?
Trying to find some mood music.
Fuck it. Radio.
[RAP MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO].
Look at that.
Yo, what's up with that dress girl?
You going dancing or something?
What you got?
CLEO: One for you.
One for you.
Check it out.
WALLER: There has been a rash...
...of these robberies in
the Los Angeles area...
...as far east as Pasadena,
as far north as the San Fernando Valley.
They seem to know
the inner workings of each bank.
Wigs and sunglasses
aid them in their disguise.
Their M.O. is in and out.
Please do not be mislead by the fact
that these four bandits are females.
It's not gonna be,
'Stick them up and give me your dough.'
Your lives are going to be in jeopardy,
and that's a fact.
These girls are the real deal.
They've gotten good at casing out
the banks that they knock off.
Yes, Keith Weston, please.
- What the fuck are you doing?
STRODE: They seem to
know the intricacies...
...of bank security systems.
More importantly,
they know how to get around them.
They may even have a contact to the inside,
so please be aware.
WALLER: Obviously, they don't appear
this way when they're on the street.
We have photographs...
KEITH: This is Keith.
Keith, listen to me.
I need you to meet me at the restaurant...
...that you took me to, in five minutes.
Baby, why?
[STAMMERS].
I'm leaving right now.
You be there.
Come on, let's do this.
T.T.
Detective Strode.
STRODE: Is there a question?
KEITH: Are we done here?
Actually, we're just wrapping up.
We'll leave a copy for your further review.
Thank you.
- I'll show you out the back.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
Please be safe, please be.
FRANKIE: All right. Y'all do your thing.
[SCREAMING].
CLEO: Get down and don't move.
Get the fuck down. Get down.
STONY: Get down everybody. Don't move.
Don't. No. CLEO: Get down.
Stay down.
TISEAN: Don't move. Don't move.
CLEO: Get the fuck on
the ground. Back up.
Get down. Right now. You, you.
Get down.
TISEAN: Put your hands up. Put your
hands up. Put your hands up. Get down.
STONY: Don't move.
TISEAN: Put your hands up.
Don't.
Don't fuck with me today.
CLEO: Just stay calm.
TISEAN: Put your hands up. That's right.
Put your hands up.
Down.
- Can I get you anything?
- No.
WOMAN 1: So I'm just gonna call her up.
WOMAN 2: Call her.
WOMAN 1: Sure, why not? And then the...
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]: All units,
silent alarm Downtown Federal Building.
Proceed with caution.
Suspects armed and dangerous.
WALLER: Can you believe this? Shit.
- Goddamn it.
STONY: Don't move. Don't move.
Do not move. Let's make it.
Put that fucking drawer in.
Don't move. We got a minute and a half.
Let's make it. Let's make it.
You, down. You. Don't move.
STONY: Don't move. Don't move.
- Get some more money.
No. Don't be greedy. Let's go now.
Shut it now.
You.
- Let's go.
- Let's go. Go.
STONY: Don't move. Stay down.
- Okay, okay.
STONY: Put your hands out in front of you.
Come on.
Let's go. Make it.
Thank you. Don't move.
Don't make me hurt nobody.
That's right, ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you for your cooperation.
There we go. Move it.
There we go. Nice and smooth,
ladies and gentlemen. Nice and smooth.
Stay down. Don't move. Don't move.
STRODE: Lida Newsom.
Shit.
- CLEO: Fuck.
- Stony.
Don't do this.
Put the gun down. Put it down.
Don't do this. Cleo.
No. CLEO: Fuck you.
No, no.
Stony.
Now, I know the deal, I do.
And I'm sorry about your brother.
I'm sorry about Stevie.
I'm sorry he's dead, I swear to God.
But don't do this.
Stevie was enough.
He was enough.
No more killing.
Put the weapon down.
Stevie was enough.
Stony, put it down.
Come on.
There you go. Cleo, come on.
What are you doing?
[TISEAN SCREAMING]...
...[SCREAMING].
Motherfucker.
[TIRES SQUEALING]...
...[CAR HORNS HONKING].
STRODE: Cleo.
STONY: Here, baby. Hold on.
Come on, baby. Come on.
TISEAN: Aah.
[GUN COCKS].
CLEO: Come on, come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
STONY: Help me out.
Come on, get inside now. Tisean, hurry up.
Come on.
Back it up. Back it up. Back it up.
[TIRES SQUEALING].
- STONY: Okay?
- Okay.
Come on, Frankie.
- Shit. Shit, shit, shit.
What happened?
What happened to her?
Drive this.
She's gonna be all right.
I need you to drive this car really fast
and get us to the hospital, okay? Go.
This is not gonna make it.
We gotta switch cars.
All right. Do what you gotta do.
Listen to me. You listen to me.
Okay? You are gonna make it through this.
- Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
- You understand me?
- Okay.
It doesn't hurt. We've been
through a lot together, haven't we?
You okay? That's what I wanna hear.
I wanna hear you're okay.
TISEAN: Yeah, I'm okay.
- Yes, I know you okay.
Okay? Please hold on for me, baby, okay?
Come on, Frankie, man. Drive this car.
You'll be okay.
You better tell them to hurry up.
- Okay.
Come on, you guys.
TISEAN: You know what?
Keith.
He gonna be mad at you.
- Ha, ha.
You don't worry about Keith, okay?
You worry about that tattoo
you gonna get over that hole.
- Okay.
You know what I can use right now?
I can use a banana flambé.
Remember those banana flambés
we had that time at that restaurant?
They were so good.
Remember?
Stony, we got it started.
Come on, let's get her.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
We're sorry, T.T.
STONY: Frankie, we can't stay. Let's go.
[HELICOPTER APPROACHING].
Come on, let's move it.
MAN [ON TV]:
Suspects are coming closer now.
Police reports indicate
that the women are from Los Angeles.
They've been identified...
...as Lida Newsom, Francesca Sutton,
Tisean Williams, and Cleopatra Sims.
You've just seen these
alleged bank robbers...
...avoid a blockade on
the 1 st Street Bridge.
However, the police
are still on the suspects' tail.
We'll try to follow the
action as best we can.
I'm going.
- You've got to drive faster.
FRANKIE: Come on, they're on our ass.
They're right behind us, Cleo.
No, no, no. Hold on.
STONY: Watch out.
Watch out.
[ALL SCREAMING].
Oh, my God, we lost them.
Go, go, go.
Come on, go.
FRANKIE: We gotta find a car.
MAN [ON TV]:
That was a close one. Here we go again.
The suspects barely getting away this time.
I don't see any police vehicles
in pursuit at the moment.
But the L.A.P.D. helicopter next to ours
has clearly got a beat on them.
I just checked with the L.A.P.D. liaison...
...he's reporting
that this 1962 Chevy Impala...
...has approximately 40
minutes of fuel left.
FRANKIE: Go, go, go.
- I'm going.
- Ls it our light?
FRANKIE: Damn.
Come on.
[TIRES SQUEALING]...
...I think I lost them.
STONY: Yeah, you lost them.
- All right.
- You're good.
Okay.
MAN: We have visual contact with
suspects' vehicle in 2nd Street Tunnel.
- STONY: Shit.
- Damn.
STONY: Damn it.
What are we gonna do?
- What are you doing?
Okay. Think, think, think.
- Come on. Fuck.
- Okay, okay.
- Okay.
Okay, let's think, let's
think, let's think.
All right. Get out. BOTH: What?
Get out. STONY: What?
Look, I want you to get out
and lean up against the wall.
And in 60 seconds,
I want you to run that way.
Cleo, fuck no. Hell no.
- Stony, shut up. We gotta split up, okay?
We gotta. Look, I'll catch up
to y'all later. I promise.
What we gotta do about the money?
- Just hold onto it.
Come on.
Come on, let's go.
[TIRES SQUEALING].
All right, motherfuckers.
MAN: Suspects are on the move.
You want it? Here it go.
Here we go, me and you.
Me and you. MAN: They're on us.
[POLICE SIRENS WAILING]...
Yo, we gotta dump these clothes.
- Okay.
FRANKIE: Oh, God.
- You be careful, okay?
- Okay.
FRANKIE: Okay.
And now the police
are all over the suspects' tail.
We'll try to follow...
- Ain't that your girls?
Hell, yeah.
Damn, that's fucked up.
OFFICER: It's them.
Hold your positions.
MAN: Step out of your vehicle
with your hands in the air.
Step out of your vehicle
keeping your hands in the air.
MAN [ON TV]: We've just had...
...a horrible moment here.
This our greatest fear
as for what would've happen today.
This is the most...
...tragic culmination of the day's events.
Damn.
Oh, God.
MAN: We're not late, are we?
MAN 1: Freeze. Drop the bag,
get your hands where we can see them.
MAN 2: Slowly turn around.
MAN 1: Get your hands up.
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]:
- -Tampa Avenue, pick up.
Wait.
Wait. Wait now. You wait. Waller.
You wait. Goddamn it, you wait.
Francesca. Frankie.
Listen to me. I'm taking it off here.
I'm not carrying.
Okay?
Okay? I got nothing. You wait.
[GUN COCKS].
Frankie...
...Tisean is dead.
Cleo's dead. She's dead.
All you got is you.
And now you gotta save you.
Do you understand me?
Now, I need you on the ground.
Frankie, I need you on the ground.
Wait.
- So, what's the procedure...
...when you got a gun at your head, huh?
What's the fucking procedure
when you got a gun at your head?
It's over.
[GUNSHOT].
MAN: Oh, my goodness.
[STONY SOBBING]...
...[BOTH LAUGHING].
TISEAN: What you all laughing at?
- Ha, ha.
We did it. We did it.
[CRYING].
Whoo. Whoo.
[GUNSHOT].
STONY: Cleo, sit.
CLEO: Man, I remember
when you was just a little scrub...
...always trying to follow us around.
[PHONE RINGING].
KEITH [OVER PHONE]: Hello?
Hello.
Stony, I'm glad you're safe.
I am.
Thank you.
[CHUCKLES].