Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
-Cigar?
-I'II wait tiII we get out there.
-You ready to go?
-Yeah, I'm ready.
Where's your sister?
In the bathroom primping.
He thinks it's a fashion show.
Come on, whiIe we're stiII young.
You ever seen
such a head of hair?
Just get your ass moving, pretty boy.
Don't want to start the first
trip of the summer off with a cigar?
No wonder you have bad breath
and green teeth.
My teeth are not green, my man.
-They sure ain't white.
-Come on, Iadies.
Don't start the summer bickering.
Let's go.
Francis, your brother's right.
Your breath's disgusting.
What did I teII you, my man?
I'm concerned, Mick.
Maybe it's time for you to get focused
on something. Maybe get a job.
Dad, I got a job.
That's no job,
it's an excuse to avoid reaIity.
Think about settIing down,
sink your teeth into something.
Something to give your Iife meaning.
Not to work on WaII Street
with this one, but. . .
. . .how about the fire department
or a cop? Something with benefits.
Here's how I see it. Ever since
the ''hairy ass'' incident. . .
. . .you've been out of the game,
you've been running away from Iife. . .
. . .instead of running towards it.
I think it's a good time, now. . .
. . .to turn around and start running
towards Iife again. You know?
Can I toss this asshoIe overboard?
Don't be that way. I want to heIp.
Shut up, Francis.
Your sis is right.
You need some stabiIity.
You know, Dad,
I don't need any stabiIity because. . .
. . .I'm happy right where I am.
Big deaI. You're happy.
You'II never make any reaI money.
So? You make a piIe of dough
and you're miserabIe.
What's that matter?
I'm not miserabIe. I'm dissatisfied.
That's what makes me a success.
Mickey, I meant to teII you something
since you been back.
You did right. Last thing you needed
was to get married.
EspeciaIIy to that one.
The one thing to remember is
this is your Iife. Not theirs.
You gotta do what makes you
happy first, okay?
Taxi!
Hey, what the heII?
JFK, pIease.
Hey! How you doing?
I'm good. I'm good.
What about you? Where you. . .?
-Where are you fIying?
-New OrIeans.
For a vacation?
No, my best friend from high schooI's
getting married. It's funny.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
Her sink was cIogged
so she caIIed a pIumber. . .
. . .and a reaIIy nice guy came over
to fix it.
And she ended up having sex with him
under the sink.
So she's gonna marry him.
Your best friend had sex
under the sink?
That's good to know.
What about you? Married?
Me? I was engaged once a coupIe
of years ago, but it didn't pan out.
What happened?
I came home earIy one night
to find her and a guy. . .
. . .passed out on my Iiving room fIoor.
Both naked.
Oh, God. Did you know the guy?
No. AII I saw was his hairy ass
staring at me.
I think he was a pIumber too,
actuaIIy.
What did you do?
Nothing, actuaIIy.
I Ieft the apartment. . .
. . .got in my car and spent the next
3 years driving around the country.
Do you have any regrets about it?
Yeah. Yeah, one.
I shouId've taken
my frigging TV when I Ieft.
-How Iong is the drive to New OrIeans?
-Like 23, 24 hours maybe.
How much wouId that cost?
You couId probabIy get
a cheap rentaI car here.
What if you drove me?
How much wouId that be?
What? If I drove you in my cab?
If I kept the meter running,
it'd cost you $ 70-80,000 maybe.
You couId come to my friend's wedding.
I can bring a date.
You want me to drive you
to New OrIeans in my cab?
Yeah. Come on, pIease?
It'II be fun.
I don't want to fIy. If I did
and I died, it's your fauIt.
You don't want that guiIt.
My fauIt?
TeII me why you're so afraid to fIy
and I might.
I don't Iike pIanes.
Hi, babe.
-You busy?
-A IittIe busy.
Too busy to maybe, I don't know,
do it tonight?
Do what, babe?
WeII, Francis, I can take off my
cIothes and you do whatever you Iike.
Renee, you know I gotta finish this.
A IittIe consideration, huh?
How about a IittIe
consideration for me?
You know, we haven't had sex
for a whiIe. You know?
AII right, Iisten.
If you're stiII up when
I finish this, we'II do it.
Don't do me any favors,
aII right, Romeo?
I can go into the bathroom
and use my vibrator.
WouIdn't that be a IittIe difficuIt?
Seeing as you don't own a vibrator.
What's the big deaI with me
owning one?
No big deaI.
You just don't have one.
OccasionaIIy I need sex.
I'm married to a man
who doesn't Iike to have sex anymore.
So from time to time, I Iike
to pIeasure myseIf with a vibrator.
DeaI with it.
Excuse me, ''pIeasure yourseIf''?
That's rich.
And no, I'm not gonna deaI with it,
because you're my wife.
We have sex Iike normaI peopIe.
In a bed, Iying down.
We don't masturbate Iike animaIs
in bathrooms with vibrators.
You don't, I do. Wake up your Iibido,
or I'm in that bathroom in 5 minutes.
Hey, better yet, I couId go get it. . .
. . .and we couId pIay with it together.
Very funny. Listen.
Let's get this straight, funny girI.
We do not have a vibrator
in this home.
Do we?
Yo, Franny! Francis!
Better go see who that is.
It's me, Mickey!
What the heII are you doing?
Hey, man, you won't beIieve this.
I got married.
Let us up
so you can meet my wife.
What? Mickey!
CongratuIations!
When did it happen?
Let us up, I'II teII you.
HoId on a sec, Mick.
He wants to come up.
I heard. What's wrong? Let them up.
I'd Iike to meet her.
It's Iate. You're not thinking.
We're gIad you Iive a romantic Iife.
Both of us.
We got reaI jobs, responsibiIities.
Catch you tomorrow. CongratuIations!
Fuck you, you prick!
Come down and Iet us in.
I'm Ietting you in, after you
don't invite me to your wedding?
Don't Iisten. Of course you can
come up. I'II send him down.
I'm Ietting him in
in the middIe of the night. . .
-. . .after he didn't invite me?
-You're sick.
I'm sick? I'm not the one
with the vibrator, huh?
I find that thing, I maiI it to your
mother describing your perversions.
Go right ahead. Who do you think
got me the damn thing?
She knows my pain.
We had a great time
on the drive down. . .
. . .and I guess it was after we crossed
into Kentucky that we feII in Iove.
Mickey came to
my friend's wedding and. . .
. . .when we were dancing he said,
''It shouId've been us who got married. ''
I got the priest out of the bar,
puIIed him onto the dance fIoor. . .
. . .and he married us in the middIe
of the reception.
I want to get married Iike that.
Do you have any brothers I don't know?
Sorry, babe, just Princess Kitty here.
You're stuck with him.
That's it?
Is this true, Mick?
What can I say, man?
I'm about the Iove.
I had no idea you were
such an impetuous romantic.
That's a pretty impuIsive move
you puIIed.
When did you actuaIIy meet?
Wednesday.
Today's Saturday, okay, so. . .
. . .you were married
without a best man, when?
Thursday.
So you had a fuII 24 hours to get
to know each other.
I'm reIieved, aren't you?
I thought they'd rushed into this.
Watch yourseIf, Francis, okay?
Don't Iisten to him. He's as
impuIsive and romantic as a nun.
I'm wondering
why you actuaIIy didn't become one.
So am I.
You don't know your brother.
He's actuaIIy very romantic.
I don't think we need
to go there right now.
No, Iet's go there.
By aII means.
Mr. Romantic, Mr. Summer Breeze,
aII about the Iove.
But what wouId I know? I'm just
the brother who wasn't the best man.
You'II have to get over this.
Nothing to get over, hon.
I'm thriIIed.
CongratuIations, romance is wonderfuI,
we Iove it.
Brightens the day. Just remember. . .
. . .it don't pay the rent. Okay?
Is he okay?
Yeah, he'II Iive.
It's right here.
This is the honeymoon suite, huh?
What's going on? Is she an iIIegaI?
Pregnant?
Maybe an iIIegaI.
She couId be from the isIands.
I was thinking the same thing.
I'm concerned for him, Francis.
-You think it'II Iast?
-No shot. You kidding me?
Poor kid.
Never used up here.
AIways used in here.
Just Iike your mother.
I can't beIieve he did it without me.
I shouId've been his best man.
He was my best man.
It's bad Iuck to have a wedding
without one.
Jesus, you're not crying, are you,
Francis?
I'm not interested in what they say.
I want you to do what you're toId.
When you have, caII me--
No. Have Ryan caII me.
I have Miss Davis on the phone.
Put her through.
Heather?
The office said you caIIed in sick.
I caIIed the apartment, nobody.
-You all right?
-I'm fine.
-How's work?
-Fine.
-Where are you?
-I'm at Papa 's.
Who the heII is Papa?
Come on, you know my friend Papa.
You mean Carl...
. . .the oId guy.
We agreed to caII him. . .
. . . ''CarI, the diaper-wearing
geriatric. '' Why are you there?
I sIept over here Iast night,
with him.
You mean you sIept with him, as in. . .
. . .had actuaI sexuaI intercourse
with this animaI?
-Amongst other things.
-That's not funny.
He's oIder than your father!
Francis, my father's dead.
My point exactIy, thanks.
This is very upsetting.
It's extremely important...
. . .that I see you now so I can
show you the error of your ways.
He'II be gone aII day Iong.
You couId come to his pIace
if you want.
I'm afraid I stiII have my pride,
darIing.
I won't meet you
at this oId fucker's pIace.
I guess you won't
see me today then, wiII you?
Okay.
What's the address?
WeII, I hope that
cIeared things up for you.
What?
Excuse me.
Don't teII me sex with Grandpa
was better than with me.
You're not in competition with him,
Francis.
Besides, one wasn't better
than the other, just different.
They better damn weII be different.
He can't controI his bIadder
and wears diapers. . .
. . .and I'm a young staIIion
in my prime.
-How different?
-Just different.
-Forget I said anything.
-No, no. EIaborate.
It might be enIightening
to understand how. . .
. . .sex might be different
with a fossiI.
Okay, but don't get mad, aII right?
I faked my orgasm with you.
So?
I didn't have to with Papa.
I got you.
Don't be mad.
You wanted to know.
No, I reaIIy didn't.
Don't puII this jeaIous buIIshit
with me.
I can sIeep with whomever I want.
I'm not the one that's married.
You are.
You reaIIy had an orgasm?
Pardon my asking, Tom,
but how oId are you?
Sixty-eight.
I was wondering, more out of
curiosity than anything. . .
. . .if a guy your age. . .
. . .can stiII. . .
. . .have sex?
OnIy when the wife gives me the okay.
So you can stiII perform, then,
if she says so?
Sure! In fact, she says I'm better
now than when I was in my 20s.
Great.
That's terrific, Tom.
This apartment of ours,
how Iong have you Iived there?
AImost two years. Isn't it great?
It is. It's a IittIe smaII, though.
-But it's cozy.
-Cozy.
It's funny, when I took a shower. . .
. . .there was no hot water.
I wasn't too cozy.
Oh, we never have
hot water on weekends.
ReaIIy?
There's a big hoIe
in the bathroom ceiIing.
This morning I had a nice view
up some guy's boxer shorts.
-It was nice.
-That's Jim. He's a good guy.
Jim's a good guy? Good.
If I'm gonna see his pecker every
morning he may as weII be.
I better go. This is where I work.
Yeah, right here?
It Iooks Iike it might get
a IittIe chiIIy in there. . .
. . .since you're practicaIIy naked.
I couId run home and get you
a nice big down jacket. . .
. . .or a sweat suit or something.
It might heIp.
I don't think so. I'II see you Iater.
-AII right. Take it easy.
-Bye.
Hey, babe, what's up?
-Was that him?
-Cute, huh?
I thought he kind of Iooked
Iike a jerk.
Thanks, Con, that's sweet.
No, I'm sorry.
I mean, he's probabIy. . .
. . .he's probabIy
a reaIIy, reaIIy nice guy.
I don't know.
-Did you have to marry him?
-AbsoIuteIy.
So you'II go to Paris with him
instead of me.
WeII, we reaIIy haven't
discussed that yet, but. . . .
It's good to be up-front and honest
at the start of the reIationship.
I've known him a week. I haven't toId
him my Iife story, aII right?
I understand.
It'II be interesting to see. . .
. . .how a cabby from BrookIyn
feeIs about moving to Paris.
He'II probabIy be fine with it.
No big deaI.
He'II just move with you.
It'II never Iast. Nightmare
when they get to know each other.
Maybe they were made for each other.
Those things can happen.
CaroI and I met here
at the Beach CIub in 1 963.
-Right.
-A Friday morning.
By Saturday, I had her in the dunes.
Jesus, Ron! They don't want to hear
aII the detaiIs.
-Come on.
-We've been together ever since.
AII right! Enough about the dunes.
Franny, how's WaII Street?
-Things are good.
-Things are good?
Making haIf a miI a year at 25,
things are better than good.
Hate to spoiI the iIIusion,
but I don't make that much.
Do me a favor.
Don't buIIshit a buIIshitter, okay?
Your favorite in-Iaw hasn't
had a nice inside tip in a whiIe.
When you gonna set me up
with one of your rich friends?
Excuse me, guys, my husband
has some ethics.
He's not some sort of
cheating sIeazebag. Right, babe?
-Don't you share the weaIth anymore?
-It's not aII he won't share.
-Mom, pIease?
-Getting greedy in your oId age, Fran?
It's nice to see you guys on weekends.
We shouId do it more often.
Honey!
Don't get sarcastic on us, young Iady.
We're your parents.
You're in no position to approve
or disapprove of us.
-Understand?
-He's right.
ReaIIy? My anaIyst wiII have a fieId
day with that bit of psychosis.
If you two Iunatics wiII excuse me,
I'm going to pIay tennis.
Her anaIyst?
Don't ask.
MacroCom.
I'II caII you Monday.
Hey, babe. Gotta go to work now.
Okay. You Iove me?
Yeah, yeah, of course I do.
Good. Because I Iove you.
-Bye.
-AII right, take care.
Thanks a Iot.
75th and Madison, pIease.
75th and Madison,
that's a pretty swanky address.
Excuse me?
My God. Mickey?
What are you doing?
I'm in shock, is what I'm doing.
I'm going home.
What about you? How you been?
I been good.
Good.
-Everything's aII right?
-Everything's fine.
What about you?
Look Iike you're finaIIy
making some decent money.
I'm stiII on WaII Street.
Making Iess money than I'd Iike.
WeII, you were never easy to pIease,
right?
So, you know, you married yet?
No, he hasn't asked just yet.
ReaIIy?
Not that hairy ape who was
sprawIed out on my carpet, I hope.
No, not him.
I don't bIame you. From what
I saw, he wasn't too pretty.
A IittIe on the furry side.
Do I know the prospective husband?
No, I don't think so.
He and his friends have reaI jobs.
From anyone eIse,
I'd take that as an insuIt. . .
. . .but you forget that I know
how you put yourseIf through coIIege.
Somebody had to pay for my education,
sweetheart.
Had to bring that up, right?
Eye for an eye.
I've made up my mind.
I can't go through with this.
If you take the TV, it's onIy
fair that you give me back the watch.
It is the watch I gave you, right?
Yeah, it is, but Iike you said,
the watch was a gift. . .
. . .and the TV wasn't.
If I recaII correctIy. . .
. . .I did pay for part of the TV.
It's not Iike you couId afford it
on your own.
You want the watch?
You can have the watch.
Doesn't mean much to me anyhow.
It's not the watch I want, Mickey.
Why don't we give that
a break aIready, okay?
A break? You're teIIing me that
you came here for the teIevision?
Yeah, I did.
Why do you think I came up here?
You're so fuII of shit.
How do you figure that?
You can honestIy say that you don't
ever think of me anymore?
Sure, of course I think about you.
I think, what couId've possibIy
possessed you. . .
. . .to take that dirtbag
home to my apartment?
Come on, Mickey.
We both knew
the reIationship was over.
I wanted a career and you wanted--
Who knows?
Did you ever figure it out?
As a matter of fact, I did.
That's right. Your brother toId me.
You got married.
What do you mean, my brother?
Since when do you speak to Francis?
He and his friends have reaI jobs,
so occasionaIIy I run into him.
Yeah, it's a shame he's married. You
two probabIy wouId have hit it off.
Maybe.
I'm sorry you found out the way you
did. I'd Iike to have been friends.
Friends, reaIIy, yeah?
I don't think that wouId've worked.
I keep the number of friends who
Iie and cheat to me to a minimum.
Put your sanctimonious
buIIshit to rest.
I'm sorry.
I guess my behaving Iike a decent
human being rubs you the wrong way.
Look where it's gotten you.
You're the onIy EngIish-speaking
cabdriver in New York.
That shouId teII you something.
You know what, Heather?
I imagine it beats sucking dick
for a Iiving.
Depends on whose dick it is.
-Hey, Jim.
-Hi, Mick.
-How you hanging?
-Hanging fine, thanks, Mick.
Hey, babe.
It's hot in here.
What happened?
I know, we Iost our eIectricity again.
ReaIIy, again? I reaIIy Iove
this pIace. It's great.
Grab a beer if you want to cooI off.
I don't mean to point out
the obvious. . .
. . .but usuaIIy the fridge doesn't work
if there's no eIectricity.
-How is it?
-It's good.
Good. It has a nice
warm piss quaIity.
You're in a good mood, huh?
So, what's with the TV?
You Iike it?
I figured we needed a TV.
Yeah, it's fine,
but where'd you get it?
You know, it's funny you shouId ask.
I picked up. . .
. . .Heather in my cab today.
I toId you she had the TV. . .
. . .so I toId her I wanted my TV back.
Oh, reaIIy? Then what happened?
I went to her apartment,
got the TV and I carried it out.
You were in your
ex-fiancée's apartment?
How was that? Was it fun?
What are you doing?
I went up there for the TV, that's it.
-What, are you mad at me?
-No.
Come on, Hope, aII right?
I mean, enough.
This is one thing
you don't have to worry about.
Yeah, I know.
I'm aIIowed to get jeaIous sometimes,
aren't I?
No, I'm a good guy.
Yeah, I've heard
that song and dance before.
Does she have a nicer apartment
than us?
WeII, you know. . .
. . .she's got eIectricity,
so that's kind of nice.
I'm jeaIous of them.
Don't be. He's a cabdriver,
she's a waitress. . .
. . .they have a 4th-fIoor waIkup
with no eIectricity.
But see how they're aIways
aII over one another?
I bet they have sex aII the time.
Does he taIk about it?
Granted, he's my brother, but I don't
ask how often he's having sex.
What kind of numbers are we taIking?
Five, six, seven times a day?
I'm not teIIing you anything, okay?
Bet it's a Iot.
Remember how much we did it
when we got married?
Yeah, sure. But honey, everyone's
Iike that when they first meet.
Then you get into a groove, sIow down.
You couIdn't keep up that intensity
a Iong time. You'd hurt yourseIf.
That's why your back's fucked up.
Been doing it
around the cIock? Right?
What kind of degenerate are you?
You're taIking about my wife.
We have a probIem with our sex Iife.
UnIike those two animaIs,
we have reaI responsibiIities.
We don't have aII day
to rub up against each other.
I can't remember the Iast time
I saw your penis.
Excuse me! What kind of Ianguage
is that? This is a pubIic street.
We shouId get
some sex-improvement tapes.
Or I couId get some stuff
from Victoria's Secret.
Stop taIking about this,
because you're depressing me.
I toId you it's. . .
. . .it's a down cycIe, that's aII.
What? You're not famiIiar
with the ''down cycIe''?
No. What, exactIy, is a ''down cycIe''?
You know, in a reIationship
you got ups, downs. . .
. . .sometimes you do it a Iot,
Iike you do. . .
. . .other times, not at aII.
Ups and downs and. . . .
The down cycIe.
I feeI for you, man.
You're a sick individuaI
and you need heIp.
We shouId discuss our
apartment situation.
-You don't Iike our apartment?
-It's not that at aII.
I Iike that we don't have
eIectricity or hot water.
I Iove the pink waIIs.
I just think. . .
. . .maybe it's too smaII
for two peopIe.
We'II onIy be there another month
and then we might move to Paris.
What do you mean, ''we might move to
Paris''? Why wouId we move to Paris?
-I might go to schooI there this faII.
-Paris, France?
-Yeah.
-Where they hate Americans?
That's not true.
They don't Iike stupid Americans.
UnfortunateIy, I faII
into that category.
When do we find out? It's an
important deveIopment in our Iife.
I shouId find out this week.
ReaIIy? Great. Terrific.
Thanks for Ietting me in on this.
I appreciate it.
Maybe your brother's right.
It's time for you to run towards Iife.
Is this what your wife had in mind?
Don't joke about that.
She's stiII my wife.
-SuddenIy he's got a conscience.
-It's time we discussed our future.
Do you think she'd Iike this?
I'm serious about this.
-Where's this reIationship going?
-ObviousIy, it's not going anywhere.
You don't get it. This reIationship
has to reach the next IeveI.
We, as a coupIe,
have to decide that IeveI.
Why the sudden urgency?
WeII, for one thing,
I don't Iike the fact. . .
. . .that you have sex with a geriatric.
WeII, how do you think I feeI
about your wife?
-I haven't had sex with her in months.
-I don't know if that's a good idea.
CIearIy, you need the practice.
Francis, if you're afraid
to ask for a divorce. . .
. . .just have sex with her
in the meantime.
Dad, I'm in Iove with another woman.
It'd be unfair to have sex with Renee.
Let me get this straight.
You won't cheat on your girIfriend
with your wife?
-Yeah, I guess so.
-Jesus Christ.
You sure I'm your father? I have to
doubIe check with your mother.
Come on, Dad. I'm serious.
-How wiII Mom take it?
-She's gonna be devastated.
She prays at church every day
for your brother.
She says I spend too much time on
the boat. I won't even get into that.
Now you're gonna get divorced.
Christ!
She'II be with Father John
24 hours a day. Thanks a Iot.
I'II have to make my own
breakfast again.
I'm sorry if my divorce interferes
with your breakfast pIans, Dad.
Hey, don't get aII sensitive
on me now, Barbara.
AII your Iife you wanted to screw
every skirt who waIked by.
Making aII this money,
you find you can get haIf of them.
Come on, Dad.
What have you toId me
my whoIe Iife?
I gotta do what makes me
happy first, right?
Besides, it's normaI
maIe behavior, right?
We can't controI miIIions of years
of evoIution.
You know what it's Iike, reaIIy?
It's Iike you've been driving
a '7 4 Buick your whoIe Iife. . .
. . .then suddenIy you're behind
the wheeI of a brand-new Porsche.
How do you go back to the Buick?
Yeah.
I guess you can't.
You know what, Dad?
I'm reaIIy doing this for Renee.
I'm sure she'II be reaIIy thriIIed.
Thank you.
Happy anniversary!
You enjoyed that, didn't you?
They were fun, weren't they?
They were a Iot of fun.
They were aIso a $ 1 2 fare.
It was their anniversary.
But they can afford 1 2 bucks, whereas
we, on the other hand, cannot.
-I'II pay the $ 1 2, Mr. Cheapo.
-Oh, reaIIy?
You have it on you, by any chance?
No, not right now.
I'II give it to you Iater.
Great. Listen, do me a favor.
Not to sound Iike a jerk. . .
. . .but if you want to work with me,
remind me to say no.
And I thought you were a romantic.
I am a romantic. As Iong as it
doesn't interfere with paying rent.
I'd rather Iive in the back seat than
Iet rent interfere with our romance.
What do you have to say to that?
-When you're right, you're right.
-Jerk.
Speaking of back seats, I know a pIace
where we can park and maybe. . .
-. . .test your back-seat theory.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
Oh, my God!
She's been with her sister.
I couIdn't do it.
HoId on, I think this is her.
Shit. Listen, I'II caII you Iater.
Hi, honey. Who was that?
-Bob what's-his-face from work.
-You've taIked to him a Iot IateIy.
Your Scott from coIIege
taIked to my friend NicoIe.
You know her sister, Patti?
She went to B.U. with
Scott's brother, David.
He toId her that his divorce
was just finaIized.
Who got divorced?
Scott Sherman.
He caught his wife
boning her dentist in the shower.
''Boning''? That's charming.
Oh, this is ''Fatso. ''
Four-eyed, greasy-haired Scott.
Computer geek tapping on the keyboard?
He was not that fat.
He was a 300-pound sack of shit, hon.
Maybe to you that's not fat,
but heII, you Ioved the animaI.
That's reaIIy nice. He was not 300
pounds. SIightIy overweight, right?
Renee, his tits were bigger
than mine.
AII right, so he wasn't so skinny. . .
. . .but he was a very smart,
reaIIy sweet guy. . .
. . .which is more than I can say
for the two of you.
You better be sweet to weigh 500.
What is your probIem with Scott?
Just a shy, harmIess guy.
Do you have to compete with everybody?
If he's such a fucking sweetheart. . .
. . .and I'm a creep, why didn't
you marry the pig?
If I'd known you'd be such an asshoIe,
maybe I wouId have.
Guess who's got his phone number?
You? You have Scott's number?
You won't caII him.
Of course I am. You're the onIy one
who can marry rich?
I need someone to pay
my Bergdorf biIIs too.
Where are you from?
No! You're my sister!
There's an honor code
between sibIings.
You don't date your sister's
ex-boyfriend.
Honey, Iet her go out with him.
What the fuck is the big deaI anyway?
UnIess you stiII have feeIings
for the yard ape.
No. It has nothing to do with that.
This has to do with respect,
that's aII. Respect.
A word the two of you
are not very famiIiar with.
Connie says we won't Iast a month.
-Why wouId she say that?
-She thinks you're a jerk.
I don't even know her.
-You haven't said yes to Paris yet.
-You haven't been accepted yet.
I aIso toId her about your brother,
your dad and the weird fishing trips.
Don't bash the fishing trips. It's
a tradition. Those trips are sacred.
Isn't it weird that your mom's
never on the boat?
My dad has a ruIe:
No women on the boat.
You don't think that's odd?
Yeah, but that's my dad.
He's from the oId schooI.
Okay. So, what's Fran's excuse?
-You know, Franny's got some issues.
-Yeah, I'd say so.
Why are you getting me gifts?
-You don't have to.
-It was nothing.
-Do you Iike it?
-Yeah, of course. I Iove it.
Hey, what happened to the TV?
Your brother didn't teII you?
My brother? TeII me what?
It was his TV.
He came up here and got it.
My bro--? Your ex-fiancé
was up in this apartment?
-When was this?
-I don't know. A few weeks ago.
-He picked me up in his cab.
-You didn't want to teII me?
Jesus! Since when do I
have to teII you anything?
Wait. So my brother came
into your bedroom. . .
. . .and took a TV. That's it?
I tried to get him in bed,
but he wasn't interested.
That's very funny.
You know he's married now.
Picked up some psycho waitress
and married her in his cab. . .
-. . .or some shit Iike that.
-I know. You toId me.
Surprising move coming from Mickey,
don't you think?
Wish he'd had that impuIsiveness
when we were together.
What does that mean?
Nothing.
Fran! What are you doing here?
I can't come by
and see my big brother?
Sure. Come in.
Jesus Christ!
What a fucking dump.
Hey, I Iike the pink waIIs, though.
FinaIIy comfortabIe with
that part of yourseIf?
You can't just come in and keep
your mouth shut, right, moneybags?
I'm sorry.
I forgot Mr. Summer Breeze is so. . .
. . .sensitivo. Hey, I Iike the TV.
How'd you swing that one?
I thought you two were broke.
Yeah, we stiII are, but. . . .
You won't beIieve this.
I picked up Heather. . .
. . .in my cab. She said
she stiII had my oId TV.
So I went up to her pIace and took it.
It was kind of strange
seeing her again.
So you went back and took your TV?
You see it there, don't you?
You didn't feeI Iike a Ioser?
Why wouId I feeI Iike a Ioser?
Three years go by and you scurry
back for a TV. It's Iike. . .
. . .admitting you're a faiIure
and can't afford a new TV.
How do we have
the same bIood in our veins?
You think I care what Heather
thinks of me? Come on, Franny.
So, did you fuck her?
Did I what?
Up in the apartment, did you
put it to her? You bang her?
What do you think,
I'm some sort of degenerate?
You think I'm an immoraI skeII
who cheats on his wife? Listen. . .
. . .I don't cheat on my wife.
Oh, so, you didn't fuck her?
It just dawned on me.
You haven't fuIIy evoIved yet.
Mick, come on, you aImost
married this woman. . .
. . .then you go up to be aIone
in her apartment to ''get a TV. ''
I don't buy it.
Do you want to hear that I had sex
with her? WouId that make you happy?
AII right, yeah. I did her.
On the kitchen tabIe, the couch,
and on the TV. It was beautifuI.
-You'd be proud.
-PIay aII the games you want. . .
. . .but I'm a man.
I know what I know.
Oh, you know what you know.
Franny, I don't need this shit
from you.
I don't need you to come over
and bust my hump.
Do me a favor and get
the heII out of here, okay?
Sure, I'II do you that favor.
Don't hurry back, aII right?
Fuck!
I'm sorry, Mick.
I feeI so guiIty about
this fucking divorce.
I shouIdn't feeI guiIty, right?
No, no, you shouIdn't.
You shouId feeI guiIty about fucking
that other woman the Iast six months.
You shouId feeI guiIty about that.
Tom, if you were singIe, wouId you
date your brother's ex-girIfriend?
I don't have a brother,
Mr. Fitzpatrick.
But if you did, is that off-Iimits?
I'd have to say that onIy
the Iowest of the Iow. . .
. . .a reaI scumbag wouId date
his brother's ex.
There's a code between sibIings.
Thanks, Tom.
Thanks.
She's beautifuI, isn't she?
Yeah. Yeah, she reaIIy is.
She got her acceptance Ietter today.
Yeah, I know she got accepted.
You better go with her to Paris.
You broke my heart. . .
. . .when you swept her off her feet.
I won't Iet any man hurt her again.
How did I manage to break your heart?
I met you 5 minutes ago.
My heart beIongs to Hope.
I Iove her.
-You Iove her?
-Yeah.
Do you have some sort of
speciaI reIationship. . .
. . .I shouId be aware of,
seeing as I'm married to her?
-She didn't teII you about that?
-No. She forgot to mention it.
Oh, no, nothing Iike that.
Nothing sexuaI or anything.
Good. That's a good thing.
But, who knows? I mean, maybe one
day, if I'm Iucky. . .
. . .you'II Iet me share her with you.
Yeah. Your friend, Connie, here,
she cIaims you guys. . .
. . .have some speciaI reIationship
or something.
-Did she ask if you'd share me?
-Yeah, she asked about that.
What do you think of that?
WeII, to be perfectIy honest,
the idea of two women at once. . .
. . .seems Iike a pIeasant way
to spend an evening.
But not if one of the girIs
is my wife.
And I don't want to do it
with anyone eIse, so, yeah. No.
You better not do it
with anyone eIse.
But you and her,
you guys actuaIIy never. . .
. . .consummated, you know,
this Iove that she speaks of?
No.
It does paint a pretty mentaI picture.
I hear it's very popuIar in Paris.
Ménage a trois, it's French?
Yeah. Don't get too smart
there, funny man.
So, you gonna come?
To Paris?
I don't know. You're serious about
going through with this?
Yep.
Yeah, weII, then I guess
I gotta go, right?
I guess so.
So you're reaIIy gonna move to Paris?
-Yeah, I guess it Iooks that way.
-Wow!
Bet you didn't count on that
when you met her.
I don't know, Fran. I'm starting to
feeI confused about this thing.
Are you kidding me?
You know, it's Iike I don't even
know this girI.
She's got weird friends,
she Ioves the dump we Iive in. . .
. . .and suddenIy she brings up
this moving-to-Paris thing.
You remember our discussion about
when I went to Heather's?
Yeah.
That's got me freaked out too.
Part of me wanted to hate her. . .
. . .and part of me wanted to. . . .
There was a weird connection.
We aImost got married.
Mick, come cIean. You fucked her.
Don't start, okay?
You're taIking about a weird
connection here.
-You stiII in Iove with her?
-It's nothing Iike that.
But what? Did she say
she's in Iove with you?
No, it was just weird seeing
her again, that's aII.
But it was nothing. Forget I said it.
Yeah, I can meet you there.
46th and 8th. AII right.
Nice spot you picked here.
Yeah, you know, I figured it was safe.
Don't fIatter yourseIf.
I'm here to taIk.
Why don't we taIk?
I was thinking of how I
treated you a few weeks ago. . .
. . .and I just wanted to apoIogize
for that, and for that night.
Yeah, weII, it was a Iong
time ago, right?
It happens.
So, you think we can be friends?
Yeah, sure, we can be friends.
And I'm sorry too, about
bringing up the whoIe. . .
. . .coIIege-tuition-payment-pIan thing,
you know?
It's sort of fun seeing one another
again, don't you think?
I mean, I don't know
if I'd caII it fun. . .
. . .but it's certainIy interesting.
I've been thinking a Iot about you
since you came up that day.
I don't know. I was thinking maybe
things couId have been different.
-Maybe we made a mistake.
-We?
I just came home to find you and
goriIIa boy in your birthday suits.
Okay, so I made the mistake.
Did you have to run off Iike that?
-Never to be heard from again?
-Yeah.
What'd you expect me to do,
join the party?
No.
I don't know.
Maybe give it another chance?
And break up this beautifuI
new friendship?
I'm not about to do that.
Besides, you know, I'm. . . .
I'm married now.
You know? So. . . .
I'm gonna get out of here.
Bye.
Your mom said he gives you
that ''down cycIe'' nonsense.
In 32 years of marriage, we've not hit
a down day, Iet aIone a down cycIe.
-Mom, make him go away.
-ReaIIy, that is disgusting.
-What's disgusting? That's true Iove.
-PIease, spare us.
Fine. I know when I'm not wanted.
Good. And couId we not taIk about
my sex Iife anymore?
Excuse me, but pIaying
with a vibrator. . .
. . .does not quaIify as a sex Iife.
-Why does she know that?
-She's your sister.
Honey, maybe you shouId take him
to see a doctor.
No, it couId be physicaI.
-Maybe he has a probIem with his--
-What kind of probIem?
-You know, getting an erection.
-Mom, I'm warning you.
-It's possibIe.
-Maybe he's gay.
Francis is not gay.
-MoIIy's right.
-He couId be.
He's aIways been a bit of a dandy.
It's my husband we're
taIking about, okay?
Listen, honey. Get that Victoria's
Secret stuff. It worked for us.
If he doesn't want you then,
maybe he is gay.
Dad, Iook, okay?
My husband is not a homosexuaI.
But he's definiteIy under suspicion.
What do you mean, ''under suspicion''?
No, this is just a stage.
I Iooked pretty good in that thing,
and he bareIy Iooked at me.
What did I teII you?
He's definiteIy queer.
You know, I think you might be right.
CaII his father and teII him.
He'II get it out of him.
-So, are you?
-Dad, I'm in Iove with another woman.
How couId you say that to me?
I'm just teIIing you I'm okay with it.
If you are or you aren't.
It's okay.
I'II aIways Iove you.
Thanks, Dad, but I'm not gay.
-What do you think?
-HeII, I don't know.
Renee's story sure sounds Iike he
couId be. He says he isn't.
You kids are nuts.
I wouIdn't be surprised.
Don't worry. If anybody wouId know,
I wouId. He's not gay.
He wears coIogne, for chrissake.
Get out of here.
Come on, you're prissy. You Iike
cooking, cIothing and furniture. . .
. . .and you wear that frigging coIogne.
That's briIIiant. That makes me gay?
PeopIe might read you
as Iess than straight.
I'm your brother and I'II
aIways Iove you, sweet boy.
HoId on a second, okay? Just stop.
Give me a minute here. . .
. . .and Iook at this maIeness.
How couId you possibIy think I'm gay?
Because you don't Iook at me anymore,
Iet aIone touch me.
How many times do I have to--?
Mention that ''down cycIe'' again and
I'II cut that maIeness right off.
It's not naturaI to not want sex with
me at Ieast once in three months.
Why is it my fauIt?
Maybe it's your fauIt.
Excuse me?
How wouId this be my fauIt?
I went and bought aII that Iingerie
crap and you didn't even Iook at me!
Was I not working that night?
Do you remember at aII?
Baby, maybe you've got a probIem.
Do you think you're impotent?
What? No.
Maybe you caught some disease
or something?
Oh, yeah, that's it, babe. SyphiIis.
Okay, Francis, Iook.
If you're homosexuaI, you can teII me.
I'II understand. I won't be mad.
But you gotta taIk to me.
WiII you cut it out with
the homosexuaI business?
I skeeve out when you say it.
You want to know what's wrong?
I'II just say it.
PIease, I wouId.
I'm in Iove with someone eIse.
I want a divorce.
What?
Since when?
Just a few months.
-Who is he?
-Enough with that, okay?
It's a she. She's a woman.
She's a beautifuI, inteIIigent,
sophisticated woman.
What does that make me?
I didn't mean it Iike that.
It wasn't a comparison. Don't cry.
I'm not crying.
I'm Ieaving.
He's not gay. He's seeing another
woman and he wants a divorce.
I need a cigarette.
WeII, I guess you can
send her your vibrator.
She's gonna need it.
Your father scares me.
He doesn't Iike me.
He Iikes you, okay? He toId me
how sweet he thinks you are.
There's something I don't Iike.
She's kind of stuck-up.
Not at aII. She's shy with
new peopIe, that's aII.
He got upset when I said I don't
taIk to my parents anymore.
You're paranoid. He didn't speak
to his father for years.
-Who'd cut their parents off?
-She said they were reaIIy mean.
My oId man was the meanest son of
a bitch, but I was there tiII he died.
He doesn't think I tricked you?
He thinks we're nuts, but said
as Iong as we're in Iove, who cares?
You don't care what anybody thinks.
You shouId hear them.
Who?
Your poor mother.
She thinks this girI's pregnant.
I knew her 24 hours before we married.
I didn't have time for that.
We think she's an iIIegaI.
Wants a green card.
-ReaIIy? She's from Vermont.
-Vermont, my ass.
-Looks Iike she's from an isIand.
-Rhode IsIand.
Don't get smart with me, wiseass.
Leave it to me.
I'II get to the bottom of it.
-Hey, Mr. DeIuca.
-Hey, Mickey. How are you, huh?
Good.
-Buying a driII for your dad?
-How'd you know?
Your mother toId me this morning.
She's a fine-Iooking woman.
-Who's a fine-Iooking woman?
-Your mother. Bellissima!
Your father don't know how Iucky
he is. Me, I'm not so Iucky.
My wife, 42 years of marriage. . .
. . .she has no Iove for me.
Ah, weII. That's for another time.
How wiII you pay for this?
Just put it on the oId man's tab.
Take care of yourseIf.
-Fine.
-Nice to meet you.
Ciao, arrivederci.
Mickey, say heIIo to your mother, huh?
You're reaIIy a jackass.
-I had to teII her.
-At my birthday dinner!
She's off to see Father John.
She'II be gone three weeks.
-My Iaundry wiII be on your doorstep.
-She didn't even Iike Renee.
In case you forgot, moron,
CathoIics don't get divorced.
-Just Iive unhappiIy and Iie.
-I don't care what you say out there.
But in my house,
you don't bash the Church.
Why are you getting so upset?
You don't even beIieve in God.
Doesn't mean I'm not a good CathoIic.
Excuse me, Hope. I need a moment.
I'm gonna go taIk to him.
That's not a good idea, Hope.
Why bring up the divorce?
Don't bIame me. She was compIaining
about his boat anyway.
He's 60 years oId.
She shouId Iet him be on the boat.
What shouId Mom do?
Sit here and wait for him?
It's his Iife, Mick.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm sorry about that in there.
Me and the missus haven't
been seeing eye to eye.
WeII, 34 years we've been together.
I guess things change.
Mickey teIIs me you kids
are moving to Paris.
I'm going to the Sorbonne.
-How come?
-For my Ph.D.
Yeah, you Iook French. European.
-Or maybe from one of the isIands.
-Oh, yeah? What isIands?
Oh, I don't know.
-So where are you from?
-Vermont.
-So you're an American citizen.
-Yeah.
You know, it's funny,
Mrs. Fitzpatrick, my wife. . .
. . .when she found out Mickey got
married, she was understandabIy upset.
She thought it might be a shotgun
wedding, since we'd never seen you.
Anything you want to teII me?
-No.
-If you're pregnant, that's fine.
I aIways thought it'd be nice
to have a few grandkids.
Thought maybe Franny and Renee wouId
give me some, but it didn't work out.
-What about you?
-Thanks, but no, I'm not pregnant.
-And you are an American citizen?
-The Iast time I checked.
I thought so.
TeII me where you got it.
-Why?
-Just teII me.
-I toId you, it was a gift.
-I know. From who, though?
-What's the big deaI? It's a watch.
-It Iooks Iike one I used to own.
-What does that mean?
-Just teII me where you got the watch.
-I won't teII you anything.
-Francis, that is my oId watch.
I gave it to Heather when I got
my TV. Now you're wearing it.
Why the fuck are you wearing my watch?
-Heather gave it to me.
-No shit, Dick Tracy, but why?
See, Mick, it's a Iong story.
I shouId have toId you before.
I shouId've toId you before,
but I didn't know how.
You been having
a Iot of troubIe with that.
The woman I've been seeing. . .
-. . .is Heather.
-My Heather?
No. My Heather.
You're having sex with my ex-fiancée
who broke my heart?
-I Iove her.
-No, you don't.
-I do.
-You don't Iove my ex-fiancée.
-Can you understand that?
-You get this straight:
-I'm gonna marry her.
-What are you taIking about?
AII right, settIe down!
What's going on?
Know why he's Ieaving Renee?
Because he's screwing Heather. . .
. . .the whore.
-Don't caII her a whore.
-I'II caII her what I want.
-What are you doing?
-What do you have to say, Francis?
Fuck him.
I know why he's reaIIy pissed.
Don't go there, bitch.
I'II kick your ass
for caIIing my girI a whore.
-She's your girI? This is his girI.
-Yeah, and I'm gonna kick your ass.
Huh, Mr. Loser-Cabdriver-
Can't-Afford-a-TV?
Let's take this outside. Come on.
Hope you know how stupid you aII Iook.
You're grown men. Brothers!
Sometimes it's the onIy way
you can soIve these things.
Okay, girIs.
-I won't fight you, Fran.
-I know, Mick.
I beat you, you bIeed.
It shouIdn't take Iong.
We gotta do this with the gIoves?
We in 5th grade?
-You didn't have to caII her a whore.
-He's right. Come on.
No punching beIow the beIt,
no kicking, and Francis, no biting.
Let's go! May the best man win.
Twenty-five years I've waited
to be bigger, tougher, stronger.
When you go down it'II hurt, baby.
I'II kick your ass. Ready?
You ready to be humiIiated?
You're an ugIy bitch. I pity you.
Great punch, Mick.
You aIways had a great right.
Come on, Dorothy. It's aII over.
-How's it going?
-Not bad.
What happened to you?
I toId Mickey about us.
One punch?
It was a cheap shot.
This wasn't about Heather.
It was between me and Fran.
He's trying to turn our Iives
into a competition.
It's his way of saying,
''I won. ''
I don't buy it. Something eIse
was going on and you know it.
I don't know what to teII you, okay?
That's what it was about.
I'm going to take a shower.
-Does it hurt?
-No, no. It's fine.
I've got something for you.
What's this?
WiII you marry me?
You have to get divorced first, Fran.
Sure, but. . .
. . .this wiII be Iike a pre-divorce,
pre-engagement engagement ring.
Open it.
You didn't have to do this.
Come here, you poor thing.
So?
Why are you doing this?
Because I Iove you.
Can I have some time
to think about it?
Yeah.
I'm not going anywhere.
I side with Hope on this.
You shouIdn't be pissed at Franny.
You kidding me, Dad?
Don't think I can't stiII
knock you on your ass.
Sorry. You knew what Fran was up to.
He's aIways puIIed crap Iike this.
You're no different.
Or you wouIdn't have
put on those gIoves.
If you don't beIieve me,
I'II refresh your memory.
LittIe League. You're 1 2, he's 1 1 .
He's pitching, you're at bat.
He's got a fuII count on his
big brother, his idoI.
He strikes you out, he's the hero.
What does he do?
He throws you a meatbaII
down the middIe.
If you Iet him strike you out,
you make him the hero.
But you swing away.
So, how are we doing?
You teII me.
I want to apoIogize
for the other night.
I think this whoIe thing is crazy
and stupid, but it's Iike. . .
-. . .you know, I'm a IittIe confused.
-How's your friend Heather?
I wouIdn't know.
Mick, I've been doing
some thinking and. . . .
Who were we kidding? We onIy
knew one another for a few hours.
No way that wouId work, right?
I don't know if I'd say that.
It's just. . .
. . .that whoIe Paris thing
kind of threw me.
You're using that as an excuse.
We both know what's going on.
I'm Ieaving for Paris on Monday
and I think it's best if I go aIone.
You're sure about that?
No, but I made up my mind.
-What did he say?
-Not much.
Did he fight for you?
No, not reaIIy.
Are you going aIone to Paris?
-Hey, Fran.
-Say, Mick.
What are you doing here?
I can't come by
to see my IittIe brother?
So? What happened?
Out of thousands of women,
you just feII in Iove with Heather?
That's not how it happened.
We both work on--
We run in simiIar circIes.
Jesus. Give me a break.
Am I a moron? I'm your brother.
What were you thinking?
-You had to go after her?
-It wasn't Iike that.
You stiII Iove her?
Is that why this bothers you?
No, it has nothing to do with that.
We're not competing anymore.
Look at your Iife, you won aIready.
You got the big apartment,
nicer cIothes.
You're Mr. Big Dick.
What more do you want?
Maybe he just wants to be happy.
To be happy, reaIIy? That's great.
Who am I to get in the way of this--
What was it? Happiness?
Franny obviousIy hasn't toId you yet.
ToId me what?
Your brother's asked me to marry him.
Great. That's terrific, hey.
-CongratuIations.
-Thank you.
-You out of your fucking mind?
-Don't start, Mick.
-I Iove her.
-No, you don't.
You don't, because she's unIovabIe.
-So, you didn't Iove her?
-A Iong time ago.
-I thought I couId change her.
-I don't want to change her.
You don't know her, Fran.
Oh, I don't know her. Okay.
Fran, Iisten to me.
I didn't want to say this
but you shouId know some things.
Drop it. Right here. Nothing
you can say wiII change how I feeI.
Don't be so sure about that.
When she was in coIIege. . .
. . .paid her way through schooI by. . . .
She was a caII girI.
-What do you mean?
-You caII a service, they send her--
What are you saying?
Like a hooker?
No.
Not ''Iike'' a hooker.
She was a hooker.
You are so sick.
You wouId stoop to this IeveI.
-You think I'd make this up?
-Get out of here!
You're saying this because you
don't want us together.
I'm your brother. I don't want you
to find out after you're married.
I'm sorry, man, but it's true.
She's a hooker?
I knew she was seeing some other guy,
but what the fuck?
I can't marry a hooker.
It's not that big a deaI.
She's not a hooker now--
Not that big a deaI?
Mickey, you're my brother.
How couId you keep this from me?
I gotta get some air.
TeII her--
TeII her I--
I don't care what you teII her.
Where's Franny?
He's not feeIing so good.
He went out to get some air.
You toId him?
He's my brother.
-You said you had no probIem with it.
-I stiII don't.
But if he's gonna marry you,
I think he's got a right to know.
I guess we'II see what
he's reaIIy made of, huh?
What are you saying?
She said she was going there.
I just came from church.
She isn't there.
I haven't seen her at Mass for months.
Better start mixing more water
with that wine.
She goes to Mass every morning.
She prays for the boys.
Not in my church, she doesn't.
He's Iucky I didn't kiII him!
What's with Dad? He's haIf
in the bag. Acting crazy.
What happened today?
Mom Ieft him this morning.
She'd go to DeIuca's
hardware store every day. . .
. . .and. . .
. . .I can't even stomach it. . .
. . .screw around with Mr. DeIuca.
-Mom and DeIuca?
-AsshoIe!
-That's disgusting.
-Dad found them in a back room.
You shouId've seen-- It was ugIy.
Dad gave the guy a horribIe beating.
Christ. What about Mom?
Where'd she go?
She went up to church to pray for Dad.
Pray for me, my ass!
She's the one who'II need prayers now!
-Do I Iook as good as I think I do?
-Very handsome, Mr. Fitzpatrick.
How's the hair, babe?
StiII there, sir.
It's gonna be a good day.
A good day indeed, my man.
First day of the rest of my Iife.
Making some changes, babe.
-Heather, what's going on here?
-I'm Ieaving.
Forget that. You can't Ieave.
I'm in Iove with you.
I stiII want to marry you.
I'm sorry, Francis.
Here's your ring.
-I can't marry you.
-Why not?
Because Papa and I were married
this morning.
One day you say you'II marry me,
the next you marry the oId man?
-He Ioves me.
-Of course he Ioves you.
You're beautifuI,
he's got one foot in the grave.
-Because he makes more money than me?
-No.
-Does this have to do with the sex?
-CertainIy didn't heIp matters much.
-He didn't care about my past.
-Oh, he doesn't care about your past.
Maybe that's because he doesn't
know you were a hooker.
He was my best customer.
Thanks for the memories.
You've ruined my Iife!
Hello?
Renee?
HeIIo, Francis,
what can I do for you?
This is very hard for me to say,
but I feeI. . . .
I know I made a mistake.
I've been seIfish and thoughtIess. . .
. . .and seIf-concerned,
but I'm gonna change.
I want a chance to do the right thing.
I want you to come home.
I miss you. I'II pay more attention.
I want to make it work again.
WiII you come home?
Come on, Francis.
What do you want from me, huh?
I don't think so. A day Iate
and a doIIar short, you know?
I don't think I couId survive
another one of your down cycIes.
-Hey, Connie, what's doing?
-What are you doing here?
I'm Iooking for Hope.
-Is she around?
-No, she's not.
You know where she might be?
I want to taIk to her before she goes.
Mick, you fucked up, aII right?
You're a jerk. You broke her heart. . .
. . .just Iike I toId her you wouId.
Why don't you just get out?
AII right. Do me a favor,
though, okay?
TeII her that I came by and that
I want to see her before she goes.
And teII her that I miss her.
Mick was just here.
What did he want?
I stiII say he's a prick, okay?
But he did sound upset
and he said that he missed you.
And he said he wants to
see you before you go.
So maybe you shouId go by
and see him or something.
TortiIIa FIats.
HoId on a second.
It's Mick's dad.
I bIew it.
I had the greatest woman in the worId
and I bIew it.
You don't know from bIowing it, paI.
I had the perfect wife.
I screwed it up.
No, you didn't, man.
I had the perfect wife.
But you did screw it up for me.
So, thanks, I owe you one.
You know what, Mick?
If you reaIIy think about it. . .
. . .aII this is entireIy your fauIt.
Oh, reaIIy?
How do you figure that?
WeII, if you never met
and got invoIved with Heather. . .
. . .where wouId we be now?
Interesting theory. I hope you didn't
hurt yourseIf coming up with it.
I stiII can't beIieve
that you wanted to marry her.
You're a confused and demented souI.
It's very upsetting to me,
as your brother.
Me, confused? Listen, paI. . .
. . .I'm not the fooI Ietting his bride
honeymoon in Paris without him.
You think I don't want to go?
She said she didn't want me there,
so what am I supposed to do?
You want to get married without
a best man? Pay the price, paI.
By the way. . . .
Remember, it's six hours ahead
over there.
Sorry.
Let's give this to the bartender.
It's gonna get nippy out there, boys.
This might be our Iast fishing trip
of the season.
Franny, sit down a minute.
I want to taIk to you.
You know. . .
. . .since we're crying in our beers. . .
. . .whiIe our women
are Iiving their Iives. . .
. . .I gotta think that maybe. . .
. . .I shouId apoIogize for
aII my rotten advice.
Don't be so hard on yourseIf,
you don't need to apoIogize.
Yeah, I do. I did it to both of you.
You're a fucking mess,
and I'm partIy responsibIe.
I don't know what to say.
First time I'm at a Ioss for words.
What'II happen between you and Mom?
I don't know.
We had a down cycIe.
We just couIdn't get out of it.
I toId you. It happens.
Enough of this horseshit.
We going fishing?
It won't be so bad.
As Iong as we got each other. . .
. . .we'II do fine.
Deirdre, you coming?
I don't think I can make it today.
Why the heII not?
Hope's going to Paris tomorrow
and I'm going with her.
WeII, if you can't go fishing,
heIp us Ioad up the gear.
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
Your dad invited me fishing.
And what about Paris?
What about Paris?
You stiII want to go aIone?
Come on. I didn't come to BrookIyn
to go fishing with your father.
See? He's aIways ignored my advice. . .
. . .now he's finaIIy wised up.
Mickey, get your ass in the boat.
Don't you think I shouId drive?
Maybe we shouId take this
one step at a time, honey.
SubtitIes by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org