Hey, look up there.
We got him now. Yes, sir.
Idiot!
Come here, stupid mutt.
You go down there and get that coon.
Go! Go!
Flea-bit hound!
Come back here. Come on!
I wouldn't shoot you.
Here, boy.
Come on.
Suit yourself.
Here, boy.
Here, girl?
Forget it.
Come on, boy.
See? I wouldn't hurt you.
Oh, man. What happened to your eye?
Where do you come from?
Come on, boy.
Come on.
Hi, Mrs. Wallace.
- You been rolling in the mud?
- No, I slipped.
You know better than to bring
that thing in here.
Sorry.
- Marty, what's new?
- Not much, Doc. Looking for a job.
Not much to do around here.
You know, Sam does the sweeping up.
There's nothing else.
Wait. Sam and Marty
can collect bottles.
I'll take them down to
the recycler myself.
You've said that for months.
- Sam and Marty can do it.
- I don't think Sam wants to.
I'd love to.
Eight houses, three bottles.
I'm going home. This was a bad idea.
- Maybe there's another job.
- There's no jobs here.
This place is dead.
- Why do you need to work so much?
- I want a bike.
Dad says if I want it,
I gotta pay for it.
- We'll figure something out.
- No, we won't.
I'm never getting a bike.
Mrs. McCallister needs
some yard work done.
Forget it. I'll see you later.
- Want to do something tomorrow?
- I gotta help my dad.
- You want me to come with you?
- No. I'll see you around.
What do you keep
following me around for?
Well, you can't come home with me.
Look, I can't have a dog.
I'll already be in deep
because I'm dirty and wet.
Please go home, boy.
It's all wet.
Come on.
It's gonna be okay.
Hold on.
- What happened to you?
- I slipped.
Take it off.
This is damp, honey.
Are you following
your grandmother to the grave?
You know how fast pneumonia sets in.
- Listen, there's this dog...
- Honey, the shirt.
- Whose dog is that?
- What dog?
- In front of the house.
- It followed me.
- Where did you find it?
- In Shiloh, across the bridge.
By the river? I bet
it's Judd Travers' new hunting dog.
- Great.
- Judd got a new hunting dog?
- Why don't he treat it right?
- Whose dog?
We don't know.
- He ain't treated right?
- Look at his eye.
He's cut bad. How it acts.
- Scared to pee, almost.
- Watch your mouth.
- Sorry.
- Just because his eye is cut...
...don't mean he's been hit.
- Don't have to mark a dog to hurt him.
- Pay him no attention, he'll go.
- Carry me.
- Did you help Mama today?
- Did she?
- No.
Fibber.
Poor little Shiloh dog looks tired,
doesn't he?
Shiloh.
You gonna eat that meat
or play with it?
- Not hungry.
- Don't give it to that dog.
- What's the dog gonna eat?
- Nothing here.
Eat your food.
- He doesn't want it.
- Eat your dinner, Marty.
- I don't feel like it.
- You got a problem?
How can you be so mean
about that poor dog?
He's hurt bad.
That dog is going back
when I've finished eating.
If that's Judd's dog, he won't
have sense to get back by himself.
We'll put him in the truck
and drive him.
- What's that?
- I said, "Yes, sir. "
Eat your food.
There you are. Good dog.
I got something for you.
Let's go.
- Maybe we can keep him one more day.
- Please. Get in the truck.
- It has ticks, though.
- So? Judd will take them off.
- What if he doesn't?
- That's his concern, not yours.
It's not your dog. Get in the truck.
Judd cheats people.
He got Mrs. Wallace so frazzled,
she gave him change for 20, not 10.
He kills deer out of season. Remember
the buck he hit with his truck?
I saw the buckshot.
How do you report someone
who don't treat his dog right?
He's one out of 50,000 mistreated.
This one came to me for help.
That's why he followed me.
I want to make sure
he's treated right.
Get this out of your head.
No mind of ours how he treats it.
What if it was a child
and it was shaking like this dog?
It's not a child
and it's not your dog.
I want you to quit going on about it,
you hear?
- You hear?
- I hear.
- Ray, how you been?
- Hey, Judd.
- You getting out?
- No.
I want to make sure
he belongs to Judd first.
- Nice day.
- Yeah, sure is.
- How's your mama?
- Not so good. Thanks for asking.
What brings you here?
Forgot to deliver some bills?
No, it seems that my boy
found this beagle.
- Thought it might be yours.
- Thought I'd lost that hound.
Show him the dog.
- That's him.
- Bring him on down, boy.
Come on, don't take all day.
Where you been?
- Don't kick him!
- He needs more than a kick.
It's the third time in three months
he's run off. He is fast.
Well, you got your dog. We'll keep
an eye out if he runs off again.
If he does, I'll shoot him.
What happened to his eye?
I don't rightly know.
- You better not hurt him, or else.
- Or else what?
Whatever it takes
to make him a good hunting dog...
...and keep him from running off,
I'll do it.
If you treat it right,
it won't run.
These are working dogs.
This is my livelihood.
If I ain't got meat
to sell the butcher in Sistersville...
...I got nothing.
Well, I guess you know your business.
Certainly your dog.
Come on, boy.
If you find him
wandering around again...
...you best do the right thing
and bring him back to me, all right?
- I'll bring him back.
- If he wanders off again...
...I'll whup the living daylights
out of him. Guaranteed.
- You touch him...
- Get in the truck.
Thank you, Ray.
A dog is a man's property.
We did what we had to do.
- I was thinking about that dog...
- The answer is no.
- I know, but...
- No more talk about it.
What about that bike?
You were looking for a job.
If I get a job it's to
buy Shiloh from Judd.
- It has a name now?
- I found him on the Shiloh Bridge.
It's not your dog to name.
I'm not gonna wait
until I find him dead on the road.
How do you propose to feed the dog?
I'll find a way.
When your grandma got sick,
I had to remortgage the house.
I do my part.
I take care of Becky and Dara Lynn.
The bank owns this house.
Until we own it, there will be no dog.
I hope if your mama was sick,
you'd also take care of her.
- Morning, Marty.
- Morning.
Hi, princess. Oh, I'm late!
You help Mama, all right?
- Bye, Dad.
- Bye, honey.
- What's up with you today?
- I don't know.
Just look for a job, I guess.
Let me brush your hair.
- You got that dog on your mind?
- Thinking don't cost nothing.
I'd love a dog.
- You know he won't budge.
- Maybe you could say something.
There's nothing to say about it.
It's not that he doesn't want a dog,
he's worried about money.
I need to get a job too.
If you love something, you
take care of it. Like Grandma.
It's not a toy, it's a living thing.
Dad won't change his mind,
and you won't stand up to him.
Don't talk to me like that.
Sorry.
You want a dog instead of a bike.
How much will he cost?
Jeez, I don't know.
Probably 20 or 30 dollars.
- You won't make that from bottles.
- I guess you're right.
I know how you love that dog.
I found a stray cat.
Mangiest thing you ever saw.
Grandpa said no way,
but Grandma said I could keep it.
On account of my parents
had just died.
Anyway, I loved that cat so much.
- I called her Blackie, she was black.
- What happened to her?
She got run over and killed.
We buried her in the garden.
Grandpa cleaned up the street.
Man!
- What are you doing with those bugs?
- Letting them go.
They don't deserve to be locked up.
I gotta get going.
Where are you headed?
Mrs. McCallister's.
See if she'll hire me for yard work.
- Make sure you make it secure.
- Yes, ma'am.
- What are you doing?
- Sorry, I had it backwards.
Be careful. I don't want to fall.
- Is it straight now?
- Yes, ma'am. Thank you.
- That's a very good job, Marty.
- Thank you.
Here you go.
- Hey, boy.
- How come you ain't out hunting?
I got work to do.
I'll hunt Friday. Possums.
- How are the dogs?
- Good.
But they're all chained.
- I'm training the beagle you found.
- Where is he?
He's caged alone
until he learns how to behave.
- Can he come out?
- No, I'm training him.
- That ain't right, locking him up.
- I fed him, so he don't starve.
That's no way to keep a dog
from running off.
- What do you know about it?
- A dog is the same as a kid.
You don't treat a kid right,
he'll run off too.
You know, if that was true, I
would've run off when I was 4.
As long as I can remember,
Pa took a belt to me.
Had welts on my back so raw
I could hardly put my shirt on.
I didn't run off.
Didn't have no place to go.
I turned out, didn't I?
Turned out how?
You trying to get smart with me?
No, I was just asking
how you turned out.
Somebody who was beat
since they was 4.
I'd feel real sorry.
Well, don't go wasting
your sorry on me.
Ain't nobody ever felt sorry for me.
And I never felt sorry for nobody.
Sorry is something I can do without.
- What's his name?
- He ain't got a name.
Don't name any of my dogs.
Dogs one, two, three, four, five.
That's what I call them.
When I want them, I whistle.
When I don't, I kick them.
"Get out! Scram! Idiot!"
That's their names.
His name's Shiloh.
- What do you want?
- I'll work this summer.
Saving up to buy a dog.
Maybe you'd want to sell me Shiloh?
Fat chance.
That'll be the best hunting dog I got.
I'll pay you good. What did he cost?
I got him cheap. 35 dollars.
But after I'm through training him,
I won't get rid of him.
You wouldn't sell him for any amount?
Well, everything has a price.
No way you'll ever
have enough to buy him.
What are you doing?
Your grandpa paid me two bucks
to sweep the porch.
- How much is it so far?
- Seven bucks.
I wonder if Judd would sell Shiloh
if I had $100.
He has so much spite in him.
If Shiloh messes up,
he'll shoot him.
How did he get so mean?
My dad said that Judd's dad was so
mean, nobody went near their house.
- Sounds as mean as Judd.
- Yeah, worse.
If you find a real stray,
you won't have to pay for him.
That's not the point. Shiloh needs
me. I never had anybody need me.
- What about me?
- Don't be gross.
I wonder what he's doing.
Get 'em, boy!
Come on, boy. Go!
Go!
Move, dumb mutt!
Get back here, boy. Come on!
What are you doing here?
- What's the matter?
- I thought I heard a dog bark.
Probably Baker's shepherd.
- Marty, everything all right?
- Just going up the hill, Dad.
You know, Marty should be
spending time with friends.
I saw Mr. Howard the other day.
I think Marty and David...
...should spend time together.
Sure. I'll call Celia about it.
You're gonna
have to stay here tonight.
I'll get some stuff to clean this up.
Judd Travers isn't gonna
hurt you again.
This'll be your house
till I figure out what to do next.
Be still. I'm gonna pull it out.
Stay.
Good boy. Stay.
- What's the hurry, son?
- Just getting the. 22.
- What for?
- Shoot some cans.
Isn't it late for that?
Why don't you call David Howard?
You can get together tomorrow.
I don't know.
I have a lot to do around here.
Why don't we make hot chocolate
and watch TV? There's a mystery on.
I was about to put the cans out.
Can't that wait?
- Okay.
- Good.
Where are you going?
To the bathroom.
This is the kitchen.
- Hey, Marty!
- Yeah?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- We won't be long. Be good.
- See you, Mom.
Girls, let's go.
Bye!
Shiloh, got some more food for you.
Marty!
Hey, Sam. Here I am.
- Is that Judd Travers' dog?
- Yeah.
Look, Sam.
You can't tell anyone, okay?
Come on, boy.
Let's go to the creek
and get some water.
His name's Shiloh.
What do your folks say about Shiloh?
- Nothing.
- You mean, they don't know?
- No.
- Wow, it's like a real big secret.
I hope it stays that way
until I've figured things out.
Thanks. I gotta fix up that shed.
- Can I help?
- Sure.
Perfect.
Come on, Shiloh.
- Don't your folks come up here?
- No, hardly ever.
Sometimes Dara Lynn and Becky
watch me shoot at cans.
- Will they tell on you?
- Yeah. They wouldn't mean to...
...it would just slip out.
I don't know. I hate lying,
but I promised Shiloh.
Besides, he'll be in the shed
if anyone else is home.
What if Judd Travers looks for him?
I have $10 so far.
If I keep working, I'll have enough
that he can't turn me down.
What if Judd finds out you have Shiloh
before you have the money?
I don't know.
I can't give Judd the chance
to hurt him again.
You might just be the best boy I know.
Sam, why did you have to do that?
- Morning, Judd. How are you doing?
- Just fine, Mrs. Wallace.
- Morning, Doc.
- Morning.
I'm looking for my dog
and was wondering if you'd seen it.
The other night I saw a stray mutt.
No, this is a beagle, purebred.
About a year old.
A little banged up,
got in a dog fight.
- Maybe you're better off without him.
- He could be a fine hunting dog.
How about you?
You seen my dog?
No.
Maybe you could put a sign
in your window for me?
I guess we could do that, sure.
My pleasure.
Well, thank you.
I hope you find him.
I'm not putting up any signs.
Okay, Ma.
Mom, do you mind if I take
some biscuits for Mrs. Young's?
No, not at all.
You have a funny appetite these days.
Saving everything for later.
- Hey, everyone.
- Hey there. What's your hurry?
I ran to see how fast I'd get here.
Marty, you want to
go down to the creek?
- Sure.
- Can we come too?
You have that appointment
at Sue's, remember?
See you later.
- Bye-bye.
- See you.
I knew they'd be friends.
- I bet they're kissing out there.
- Oh, stop.
Judd Travers came to the store
asking about Shiloh.
What did he say?
He said he's valuable
and he wants him back.
- What did you say?
- Nothing, except I haven't seen him.
Mrs. Young's gonna pay me
five bucks to paint her fence.
Then I'll have 15.
I'm gonna need about 50 bucks.
Probably.
I buy the base and then
I custom blend the colors.
And I have other ones as well.
I can sell them to you
for $1.70 a bottle.
$1.70? Well, let me think about it.
You know, the ladies
are real happy with Sheffield's.
Yes, but they cost
over 2 dollars a bottle.
Let me check it out.
I'll give you a call.
And if Joan really marries that guy...
...you've got the manicurist's job.
Wonderful. Thank you very much.
- I'll leave a sample, if it's okay.
- Sure. That'll be nice.
Hi there.
I just wanted to give you a treat.
Thank you.
Girls, let's go.
- Hi there. How are you?
- Everything okay?
- I'm great. Thanks, Sue.
- Bye-bye.
I'm gonna do something with that hair.
You've done a marvelous job.
- Looks good, doesn't it?
- Sure does. Here.
Thank you very much.
If you could recommend me,
I'd be grateful.
- I'll make a point of it.
- Thank you.
I made $5 getting rid of cans for Doc
and $5 for Mrs. Young's fence.
- I've saved $20 so far.
- That's terrific.
- Will you buy us something?
- That's Marty's money.
- What are you gonna spend it on?
- I might just save it for a while.
You know what
I've been thinking about?
- A dog.
- Louise, please, not you too.
I know how badly he wants a dog.
I was a boy once.
A dog isn't a one-purchase thing.
There's shots, vets, toys and food.
When I sell the nail polish,
we'll have extra money.
We'll talk about it later.
It'll still be no.
Excuse me, but this is a family,
we all have a say.
You all can say whatever you like.
I say, "no dog, no way. "
Can I be excused?
You got something to do?
I just want to walk around.
You should spend time with a friend.
Sam is a friend.
Sam is a girl. This is a boy.
I want him to have a pal
and not be lonely.
You got to make a daily plan for
the rest of the summer.
Why are you being so tough on him?
He's a big help to me.
He worked at Mrs. Young's...
...he was picking up cans.
I've said my piece.
You know where I stand.
I'm going to go practice my aim.
- Why don't you go with him.
- I got the news in five minutes.
I wonder who that is.
- Evening, Judd.
- Evening.
What can I do for you?
Have you had dinner?
I can heat something up.
I ain't looking for a meal,
I'm looking for a dog.
That new dog run off again?
Haven't seen him on my route.
If I find him this time,
I'm gonna break his legs.
Come on. A dog with
four broke legs ain't no dog at all.
How about you, boy?
I bet you seen him.
Your dog? I haven't seen a dog
around this house all day.
You must've seen him.
He likes to follow you around.
- Maybe you just don't know it.
- No way, I would've seen him.
Here, dog!
When you went to recycling...
- ... did you see him?
- I saw the Baker's shepherd.
He gets loose, but I didn't see
any beagles on the road.
You keep a sharp eye out.
If you see him, don't get any ideas.
Throw a rope around him
and drag him over.
You hear?
You hear what he said?
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Wouldn't the sheriff get on you
if you hurt that dog?
The law never told me
what I can't do with my dogs.
They won't start now.
It's like the Bible says.
Animals were put here for us.
They got no other purpose or feelings.
Have a nice evening.
What are you doing here?
Come on.
Oh, boy, Shiloh.
You know, Shiloh?
Some day you're not gonna be a secret.
Even if I have to run away with you,
Judd's not getting you back.
Really, my folks are nice.
We just can't afford a dog right now.
I gotta get home and sleep.
You stay here like a good boy.
Don't run off.
Lie down. Stay.
Stay, stay.
- Bye, Dad.
- Bye, honey.
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Quit it.
Quit it.
- You're no fun.
- You're no fun!
- Quit it!
I'm going to the creek.
I'll be back soon.
- I want to go too.
- I'm looking for a snake stick.
I'm looking for a snake stick.
It must have a long handle
and a strong fork.
- Why?
- It was the meanest snake ever.
- What snake?
- The one I saw on the hill yesterday.
Must've been four, no, five feet long.
Looking for a leg
to wrap itself around.
Kill it. Blow its head off!
You've been watching
too much stuff on TV.
Let's get in the house.
Come on. Hey, buddy. How you doing?
Yes, yes. I got the food.
I know you're still hungry.
So am I. That was half my breakfast.
We'll play later on.
Go back in the shed.
Go. Good boy.
- How are you doing?
- Hey, Doc.
Can you sell me some old cheese or
lunchmeat for 50 cents?
I don't want your money.
I'll try and find
something not too bad.
Don't want your family
to get sick.
It'll be fine.
They all have strong stomachs.
- Why are you selling that old food?
- It's not old.
Don't keep that cheese
more than a couple of days.
- Thank you.
- Tell your mama...
...if she's behind in her bills that
she has an open account here.
It's not like that.
You don't have to explain.
You're embarrassing him.
Please don't say anything
to my mother about this.
- Thanks.
- You want me to walk with you?
You better finish
your work here first.
I got stuff to do at home.
- I'll see you around.
- Bye.
How could you do that?
Do what?
Just because they're hurting is no
reason to sell them spoiled food.
I think they're okay.
No, it's all over town.
That boy has been asking for food
and a job all summer.
I'm afraid the Prestons
really are hurting.
Honey, I don't understand.
Mrs. Roper makes that turkey
and gives it to us. Why?
What do you mean?
You do a good job for her.
What about the tuna sandwich
in Mrs. Kingle's mailbox...
...and that half cherry pie
in the Saunders'.
Used to be Mrs. Ellison
would leave me banana bread.
What? Do I look thin or something?
Maybe you're the best mail carrier
they ever had.
- You ever think of that?
- You think so?
Really?
Here you go.
That's to keep it cool and fresh.
And that's to keep the raccoons out.
One last bite.
Come on.
Let's go.
Good boy.
$20 so far.
Judd says he won't sell you, but when
I stick $50 in his face, he will.
I gotta go home.
Be a good boy and stay here.
What are you doing?
Have I got frown lines on my face?
Tell me the truth.
I don't see any.
You don't see any lines
here by my chin?
All I see is a pretty face.
Why, thank you.
Give me a kiss.
I'll have some of that squash later.
Finish up for me.
I'm gonna check on the girls.
- Watch out.
- I'll get that, Mommy.
I'll throw one from here.
I'll watch from here.
Becky, you throw one in.
I'll toss you one.
How are you doing?
How long have you had
this dog up here?
A few days, I guess.
You've had Judd's dog up here and told
him you didn't know where it was?
I didn't say I didn't know.
Just that I hadn't seen him
in our yard.
Will you help me
find a way to keep him?
- We have to tell Dad.
- No, we don't. Not yet.
I'm not used to keeping secrets
from your dad.
- Please don't tell him.
- I've got to.
If he finds out that I knew and
didn't tell him, he won't trust me.
He'll make me give him back.
I know he will.
What else can we do?
If Judd comes to our house,
he'll have to fight me to get him.
Promise me one night you won't tell
Dad so I can figure things out.
You won't run off with the dog,
will you?
Look at me.
Don't ever run away from a problem.
Now, I can promise
not to tell your dad tonight...
...if you promise not to run off.
I won't run off.
- Then I won't tell him tonight.
- Or in the morning.
I gotta have at least
one day to think.
His name's Shiloh.
Hello, little puppy.
Marty, take a flashlight.
Get out of here.
Please don't die, Shiloh.
Take the gunnysacks on the porch...
...and put them on the floor
of the truck.
Don't take him back to Judd.
- He'll shoot him.
- Get the gunnysacks like I said.
Honey, get the keys to the truck.
- What is it? What's he got?
- A dog.
- Here. Is he alive?
- Barely.
Sorry, Shiloh.
I'm so sorry. It's all my fault.
Dr. Wallace!
- What's up?
- Got a dog here. Hurt real bad.
Easy.
He sure is bleeding.
First we make sure
he doesn't get infected.
Hold that for me.
How did it happen?
Big old shepherd got him.
I promise, he'll feel better.
He won't feel any pain.
Here we go.
Easy, easy.
Thank you.
Whose dog is he?
- He's Judd Travers'.
- Where did you find him?
- I had him.
- You what?
I had him.
- Uh-oh.
- Uh-oh is right.
Judd doesn't deserve him.
Marty treats him good.
- He's dying because of me.
- Let's go to the other room.
No, I'm gonna stay with Shiloh.
Not a bad job, if I say so myself.
Tell you something,
this guy's a fighter.
Will he be okay?
Come by tomorrow
and we'll see how he's doing.
- What do we owe you?
- One of your wife's cherry pies.
I'm serious.
My boy will pay for your time.
I will. I promise.
It's gonna be okay, boy.
- Is he gonna be all right?
- I hope so.
- Can't thank you enough.
- Thank you, sir.
You're welcome. Any time.
Marty loves that dog so much.
I wish Ray could talk
some sense to Judd.
After all, they were boys together.
Nobody can talk sense to Judd.
What else don't I know?
- What?
- You hiding Judd's dog.
- What else are you keeping from me?
- Nothing.
- How do I know that's not a lie.
- It's not.
Your saying so doesn't make it true.
That's the problem with lying.
What should I have done?
Let him wander around so Judd can beat
the living daylights out of him again?
- Did you want me to do that?
- Do what's right.
What's right?
You got to go by the law.
Man that pays money for a dog,
owns that dog.
- You don't like it, change it.
- What if there's no time?
He could be dead
the way Judd treats him.
You think Judd is the only one
hard-hearted toward animals?
Open your eyes to yourself.
How many times do you see a hungry,
chained-up animal in a yard?
How many times do you think about
how unhappy that dog is?
You're face to face with an animal
that pulls at your heart.
All at once you have to change things.
There's gotta be a first time.
You're right about that.
It's the first time you lied.
If Shiloh is okay, I gotta keep him.
You don't have to do anything.
I promised Shiloh I wouldn't
give him back to Judd.
We'll go to Judd tomorrow
and tell him the truth.
But I've saved up some money.
If I can make a deal,
you won't stop me.
If you keep this up
there'll be trouble.
What if Judd Travers finds out?
If Doc doesn't say anything,
nobody would know.
I can make a fence
so the Baker's shepherd can't get in.
Please.
Just till Shiloh's better.
Judd will take one look at Shiloh
and shoot him!
We have to get him better, Dad.
I'll pay Doc's bills, I promise.
You can have my money for the next
three years. I'll deliver the paper.
Please.
We'll keep him till he's well.
That's it.
Then we take him back to Travers.
- I just found out myself.
- You're keeping secrets from me.
People are trying to give us food.
Like I can't feed my family.
- Judd mentioned the dog and he lied.
- He loves the dog.
- Now he's got you on his side.
- He's our son.
I know.
- What?
- Where's the doggy?
Doc Wallace's.
- You want some breakfast?
- No, thanks.
I'll head over to the Wallaces'.
Here's a sandwich
if you want it for later.
Thanks.
I'll take the bandages off
in a couple of days.
- I don't know what to say.
- You don't have to say anything.
- I saved up, it's only $20.
- I don't want your money.
Please, Doc. Take the money.
Tell you what. I'm gonna give you
$20 worth of dog food.
What's wrong?
I gotta give him back to Judd. When
he sees him hurt, he'll shoot him.
You really love that dog, don't you?
You must find a way to keep him.
You don't know
what I've been through.
You feel like the whole world's
against you.
See that picture up there?
That's Sam's parents.
Eddie, the father. Clara, the mother.
And that little itty-bitty thing,
that's Sam.
I never saw a picture of them before.
Clara was...
...my princess.
We were babysitting Sam...
...the night of the accident.
I'll never forget social services.
They jumped all over us.
They said we were too old...
...to raise a child and we didn't have
financial stability.
I thought it was a joke, I've been
practicing medicine for 40 years.
- But you were able to keep her.
- Yes, after a fight.
The love of Sam gave us our strength.
We would have sacrificed anything...
...to keep her.
Sometimes...
...the greatest test of love...
...is how much you're willing
to fight for it.
You think about that.
This dog is gonna need a lot of love.
Go get him.
I love you.
This will do just fine.
Let's put him over here.
Nice and gentle. That's it.
There you go. Nice and gentle.
Girls, be very careful with his leg.
I'll sleep on the couch tonight.
Keep an eye on him.
He's licking my hand.
Will you come pet this dog?
No good getting attached to a dog
we gotta give back.
Stay. Stay.
Judd won't sell the dog.
- Besides, with Doc's bills...
- Marty settled that.
Don't go guessing
another man's business.
The Doc has every right
to charge us full rate.
You know he won't.
Watch what he does
when I put a sock under his face.
Let me try it.
It's Judd.
Girls, go on upstairs.
Ray Preston, Mrs. Young told me
you got my dog.
He's right there. He's hurt.
We've been taking care of him.
I'll be danged. I can't believe it.
Somebody knows my dog is missing,
takes him in...
- ... and don't tell me.
- Nobody wants to hear it's been hurt.
We wanted to make sure
that he pulled through.
Tell Judd how the dog come to be here.
Go ahead.
He come here
because you been mistreating him.
The second time I hid him
in the woods. Dad didn't know.
The Baker's shepherd got loose
and hurt Shiloh.
- Who?
- Shiloh. That's what I'm calling him.
Shiloh got hurt really bad.
It was my fault because
the shed wasn't safe.
Doc Wallace patched him up.
Boy, put the dog down.
Look what you done to my dog.
I never mistreated my dogs.
I never caused an injury like this.
It wouldn't have happened
if you'd brought him back.
He was wrong to hide the dog
and he will pay Doc Wallace.
As soon as he's strong,
we'll drive him over to you.
Let us keep him until then.
Excuse me, Judd?
Marty's got awful attached
to that dog.
How much do you want for him?
This dog is not for sale.
I paid good money
to get a hunting dog...
...and this is the best
I ever had.
If you want to take him
till he's better, that's okay.
You got him tore up
and you will pay the bill.
- But I want him back by Sunday.
- You'll have him back by Sunday.
I don't believe
you allowed this to happen.
I'm not giving him back.
What are you gonna do?
First thing in the morning, I'll go
talk to Travers and settle this.
Look, Judd. I love this dog
and I'm not giving him back.
I've saved up some money and...
Oh, yeah?
Go ahead and try.
You can beat, punch and kick me.
I'm not giving up the dog.
What do you think you're doing?
You could get shot sneaking up
on somebody like that.
I was on my way to see you.
You caused me to miss my shot.
Sounds like the day
might not be a total loss.
Rabbit ain't in season.
What are you? The game warden?
There's a $200 fine
for killing rabbit out of season.
I didn't kill no rabbit, did I?
What about this?
You set this trap?
Boy, are you trying
to stir up trouble?
Don't you know that I can put you
in your place real quick?
What are you gonna do? Shoot me?
Like the dog I found
with a bullet in its head?
I know whose bullet that was.
I told Dad.
If my folks find a bullet in
my head, they know whose it is.
Come on, simmer down.
I got lots of game up here.
I'll let you keep that rabbit. Don't
tell me your mama wouldn't like that.
I don't want the rabbit.
I want Shiloh.
Set that rabbit free.
You came here to set me up.
It's Sunday, the day
you told me to bring your dog back.
You'll have to fight me first
to get him back.
I mean to keep that dog.
If you expect me to keep my mouth
shut, you'll make the trade.
Let me get something straight.
You're telling me
that if I let you have my dog...
...you'll keep your mouth shut?
You gotta do more
than keep your mouth shut.
You gotta promise not to come up here
spying on me.
I ain't gonna spy.
You know it's wrong.
I'll tell the warden
to watch out for illegal game.
Ain't you something.
Wait a minute.
I paid $35 for that dog.
I want $40 for it.
I'm working hard.
I'll get the money to you by and by.
I don't want any money by and by.
I want something right now.
You're gonna have to work for it.
You got a bargain.
You gotta work for me four hours
a day, five days in a row.
I'll do it.
- Keep your mouth shut.
- I will.
How do you get her out of this?
Boy, if you ain't a mess.
Look out.
When will you clear all these traps?
I'm not. That will be your job.
Start by picking
that one up right now.
I want that wood split, stacked.
I want the weeds cut.
Whatever I think of to be done,
that's what you'll do.
No, put it over there.
Hang it on the nail.
- I want you here starting tomorrow.
- I'll be here.
I want it in writing that
after I do 20 hours of work for you...
...Shiloh belongs to me.
In writing?
You stay right there.
Put whatever you want on the back.
My hands are dirty.
It's my hunting calendar.
"Beagle hunting dog... "
Sign it.
- I'll be here tomorrow.
- Wait.
If you ever tell anyone
about that rabbit or them traps...
...you're gonna be one sorry boy.
You got my word.
- Where you been?
- Went to see Judd Travers.
- I'm buying Shiloh.
- Judd said he wasn't selling his dog.
I talked him into it. He needs help.
If I work 20 hours it'd be worth
the $40 he wants for Shiloh.
I don't believe it.
- Shiloh is your dog?
- Not yet, but he will be.
That's wonderful! Ray?
Judd said he wasn't selling his dog.
What went on?
I told him I wasn't
giving Shiloh back.
- You said that to Judd?
- Only thing I hadn't tried.
It must be because Shiloh's hurt.
- He's getting rid of a lame dog.
- That's what I figured.
Well, puppy, are you a new member
of the household?
I brought in 10 traps.
That's all I can find.
That's all there were.
- Any catches?
- They were all empty.
You see that patch of land?
I want you to clean this mess up.
Then I want you to work the ground.
I mean to plant some corn on it.
What are you waiting for? Get to work.
Come here, boy.
Come here!
Move that stuff from there to there.
- But...
- Don't question me.
After you're through with the garbage.
Before you do that,
get the couch in the house.
Bring me a beer.
Don't touch it, then I can't read it.
I'm not sick.
It's 100 degrees.
I don't think you should go tomorrow.
I'm going. I've gotta stick
to my promise.
For Shiloh.
All right. Tell Judd to take it easy.
Work inside the house, okay?
Here we go.
I'm telling you.
See that big piece of wood?
I want you to roll it over there...
...take this wedge, drive it in it...
...then you hit that wedge
with a sledgehammer.
You get pieces small enough
to fit into my stove.
Got that?
You're sure doing a lot of work
for nothing.
Shiloh's something.
You don't think
you'll get my dog...
...because of some handwriting
on a piece of paper?
That paper ain't worth nothing
except to blow your nose on.
- It ain't got a witness.
- What do you mean?
You don't know what's legal
and what's not, do you?
You show a judge a piece of paper
without a witness signature...
...he'll laugh you
out of the courthouse.
Someone has to sign it
who saw you strike a bargain.
Ain't nobody here except my dogs.
What are you, boy? Some kind of fool?
What are you breaking your back for?
I want that dog.
There he is.
I want to check his leg.
It's healing pretty well.
Dad, what's a witness?
Someone who sees something happen
and swears it's true.
If you make a bargain,
do you need a witness?
If you want it legal, I guess.
Why? What are you thinking of?
Just thinking about selling things.
Land and stuff.
You're not thinking of selling my land
to buy Shiloh?
- Let's have a look.
- I'm all right.
Does it feel good to be in your room?
Did you get the job?
Yeah, I got the job.
And you are my first customer.
All I can do is stick to my side
of the deal and see what happens.
- You should tell your folks.
- It's between Judd and me.
I don't want Judd mad
and having bad feelings.
Or worry about Shiloh
while I'm at school.
I'm the one to square this
and I'll finish the job.
What do you think?
Paint it again.
That's about it.
- Kind of tired.
- You couldn't have worked me harder.
You done everything I asked too.
I'll take good care of Shiloh.
You ain't keeping him.
- But...
- I told you. The deal's off.
But we made a bargain.
You can't go back on it now.
What time you want me
to pick up my dog?
You come for Shiloh,
bring the sheriff.
Get on home, boy. Get on home.
Get on home. Scram!
Keep away!
- Pick up no stick to me, boy!
- You're never getting Shiloh back!
I'll whup the daylights out of him.
You'll never have enough to buy him.
What are you? Some kind of fool?
What do you want?
- Where are your folks?
- Dad's on his way back.
- You got something that belongs to me.
- No, I don't.
I worked hard for this dog.
I ain't giving him up.
I want my dog back.
Get off my property.
I want you to take this leash...
- ... and put it around his neck.
- No.
Go on, Shiloh.
- Leave my dog alone!
- What are you doing?
Keep away from me, just keep away.
You all right?
- Better control your boy.
- Get out of here, Judd!
- Dog is my property.
- We had a deal.
Maybe it won't make legal sense, but
you and I know we made a bargain...
- ... and you lied to me.
- That makes us even.
Why don't you and me
discuss this man to man?
I'm through with discussing, Ray.
That dog is mine.
Judd, you can't take Shiloh.
You take Shiloh...
...and you have forever
made an enemy of me.
Don't mess with me.
I'm in the right.
And you know it.
He's gonna kill Shiloh!
Stay here.
Wait, Judd. Wait.
All I had was your word.
Ain't that worth something to you?
Shiloh, huh?
Go on! Get!
You know what, Marty?
I think you got yourself a dog.
I got myself a dog.