Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
The time has come
to go to war again.
Not with Iraq, international terrorists,
or what was once Yugoslavia...
but with the medfly...
a potentially devastating insect...
that has chosen to make
California its new home.
Despite assurances that spraying poses
no significant health risks to the public...
the public is not convinced.
People sense they're being
kept in the dark purposely.
Furthermore, there is
no consensus...
as to whether the objectives
are even realistic.
Is this a war that can be won?
Some say no.
Are we just going through the motions
so certain people can cover themselves?
- Honey, it's on!
- Some say yes.
- Okay, I'm coming.
- How is this war fought?
It's like fishing.
We use bait.
Actually, the bait is spread over
our city at night, like a glaze.
This is very discriminate bait...
- Do you have to wear your glasses on TV?
- like smart bombs...
that destroy one thing,
but nothing else.
The bait attracts the hungry,
newly hatched medflies...
and poisons only them.
The war's objective is clear.
To destroy the medfly before
it has a chance to destroy us.
All right.
Look over there.
Marian, what's so interesting?
- Isn't that Alex Trebek?
- Alex Trebek? Where?
Over there, next to the woman
with the white hair.
Is that Alex Trebek?
Yes, I'm sure it is.
Who's Alex Trebek?
Marian.
Please.
...taken their time adopting a policy
of coexistence with the medfly...
'cause that's the only
realistic course open to us.
Oh, Andy, you're
a long ways away.
I'm in L.A. Can you
hear the helicopters?
What are you wearing?
Already?
That was fast.
If you're looking for a rainbow
You know there's
gonna be some rain
One minute you're
filled with happiness
Next minute there's
nothing but pain
When you're a prisoner
And I'm a prisoner
I'm a prisoner of life
One day your man is here
The next day
he's walked out and gone
But no matter what happens
You simply somehow
gotta carry on
When you're a prisoner
And I'm a prisoner
I'm a prisoner of life
What are you doing here?
Just give me some coffee,
will you, babe?
- Are you working, Earl?
- Yeah.
- You got somebody in the car?
- How come you got 'em here?
- They're passed out.
It's one of those
drive- arounds.
You're not drinkin', are ya?
Just give me
some coffee, baby.
I come all the way down here to see you.
I'd think you'd be happy to see me.
Life's good
It's bad
It's somewhere in between
But it's the unexpected
and the uncertainty
That keeps us goin'
You know what I mean
Yesterday you owned the world
The next day the world owns you
One day everything's a lie
The next day
you swear it's all true
That's what happens
when you're a prisoner
And I'm a prisoner
I'm a prisoner of life
You okay?
I told you I canceled
the Times, right?
Stopped the mail.
All you have to do is come in and
check up on everything and feed the fish.
I'll write... I got it all written down.
Didn't I put it on the, um, fridge?
- Yeah, she wrote it down. I watched her.
- I got it written...
- Just come back tomorrow morning.
- Okay.
- You are gonna...
- I... Your fish are gonna be fine.
What about the lionfish?
Feeding the lionfish?
- That was just a joke, honey!
- No, no, no, no. No, no.
- Lionfish like goldfish.
- That's what you wrote down.
- Yes. You feed them live goldfish.
- I thought you were joking.
- No!
- You do that.
Earthquakes, water shortages...
fires, mud slides...
Crime, gang warfare,
massive overcrowding.
"His mother's name was
Speckled Hen. She looked..."
What will our lives be like if we
have to share space with the medfly?
Gene! Gene, the helicopters
are here! Shut the windows!
Watch your brother. Okay?
Watch your brother.
Suzy! Come here,
my good little boy. Yes!
Sandy, shut the windows
for me, please.
What are you doing?
The dog stays outside.
I've told you a hundred times!
Don't put Suzy outside. The spraying...
It's gonna give him cancer!
It's not gonna give it cancer!
Don't you get environmental on me, Sherri.
Have you listened to
the news lately? It's dangerous!
They wouldn't be doing it
if it was dangerous!
Come on, kids!
It's all right! Come on outside!
It's all right!
It's safe! Come on!
Oh! Oh, yeah! Yeah, go on!
Get cancer!
- Gene!
- Get the dog out!
- Leave the dog alone!
- Stupid...
The dog stays out.
The dog drives me out of my mind.
- Where you going, Gene?
- Out of here.
This is the third night
this week, Gene!
Why don't you start
smoking again?
How about Friday?
Are you free this weekend?
I don't get back till Saturday, but if you
make it Sunday, I'll bring fresh trout.
Marian, why did you do that?
- What?
- Invite them to our house for supper?
I didn't. You did.
- No, I didn't.
- You said, "Let's set a date".
No. I had to say "Let's set a date"
because you invited 'em to our house.
That was just
a comment, Ralph.
What's his name again?
He's some kind of a doctor.
I think he's a dentist.
Her name is Marian.
- Marian, we don't even know them.
- Just relax.
Okay? Just... relax.
Any of those medflies
get on you today?
Ow! I got one.
Do you want me to
describe myself for you?
I'm a blonde...
36-24-34.
You don't do that.
- What do you do?
- Oh, yeah?
These countries
ship their food...
Oh, yeah? But I'm not
gonna suck it yet.
Come on. Let's go
play in your room.
Come on.
What if all this is telling us...
that every expert...
before every expert...
Can you speak up, honey?
I can barely hear you.
Yeah, baby. Ooh.
My panties are
getting a little wet.
Well, I'm on my bed, and
I'm on my hands and knees...
and my mouth is
so close to your balls...
Can you hear that?
Can you feel it?
Don't you want me
to lick your balls first?
Mmm. Mmm.
You taste so good.
Ooh, your cock is
getting so big in my mouth.
So big.
Oh, yeah, baby,
I'm just gonna lick it...
Life's good, life's bad
- You don't like the music? You wanna go?
- We've got an early flight to catch.
- Oh, then let's go. Come on.
- And the uncertainty that keeps us goin'
You know what I mean
Yesterday you owned the world
And the next day
the world owns you
One day everything's a lie
- You wanna drive?
And the next day
you'd swear it's all true
When you're a prisoner
And I'm a prisoner
Yeah, I'm a prisoner of life
- The medfly is already established in L.A.
- Mom?
- Baby?
Shit.
Honey, what's the matter?
Did you have a bad dream?
Come on, sweetie.
Let's watch Daddy on TV.
- We'll all snuggle.
- What happened?
- The helicopters scare you?
- I thought it was an earthquake.
- This is Howard Finnigan...
- He was just frightened.
With thoughts
to make you think.
Go ahead, shut it down.
I gotta go make a phone call.
It's my wife's birthday.
Okay, guys, gather 'round.
Get in line. Specimen time.
That time of the month, guys.
Fill it up.
- Yvonne!
- Hey, sweetheart.
- Cheers!
- You need some help?
- There you go.
- We just spray the stuff. We don't drink it.
You need a magnifying glass
and a tweezers to help you out?
Hey, sweetheart.
Okay, you two.
Y'all haven't been
taking anything, I hope.
Don't let anything run on the sides,
okay? 'Cause that gets real nasty.
- Hello?
- Chad!
What are you doing
up so early?
- It's Mommy's birthday.
- Hey, that's right!
- Did Mom ask you to remind me?
- No.
- I'll bet she did.
- No, she didn't!
- I'll bet she did. You can tell Daddy.
- Give me that.
- She did not!
- Go back to bed, young man.
- Stormy.
- Yeah!
How'd you know?
Two more hours. Please!
- Who else would call me at the crack of dawn?
- Hey, who was that? Chad?
What do you want, Stormy?
I just wanted to see
what was on the agenda.
I got Chad tonight, you know.
Wanna join us?
Whoops. Sorry, sweetie.
I really like the Wymans.
Don't you?
Who?
The doctor and his wife.
Marian.
And Ralph, I think his name is.
You know, the ones from the concert.
He seems, uh, kinda lofty.
Off to work early, huh?
Well, I got two birthdays today.
He's a doctor. Remember?
- And she's an artist, I think.
- Oh, yeah? What kind?
What kind? She's a painter.
You know.
She paints pictures.
- There's Vern.
- They really want us to come to dinner.
Well, we'll see. I'm off.
What does that mean?
We already agreed to go.
We made a date.
Bye.
Close the door, Stuart!
Sorry.
Got it.
- Oh, Christ.
- I think it's broken.
The little thing didn't come up.
Fuck!
Why'd you let me sleep?
- How am I gonna explain this?
- I don't know.
- What, is it broken?
- Yeah.
Is your kid awake?
I don't want him to see me here.
Is he?
He won't, baby.
He's still asleep.
'Cause kids shouldn't see
that kind of thing.
Jesus, how am I
gonna explain this?
Jesus. Okay.
Kids. Crack.
Kids... Kids on crack.
Okay.
- What?
- Fucking dog.
Fucking dog knows. I know.
That fucking dog.
- Hey. Ruff! Ruff!
- Just can't live with all this.
I need to... What are you
gotta smoke in the morning for?
No, I told you I don't
wanna do that anymore.
Honey?
Honey? You home?
Make me some coffee!
Oh. Something hit me
in the fuckin' head last night.
Hello.
Shut up.
These you can mist.
Water them once a week.
Harriet, we're running
behind schedule.
- I'm gonna bring the bags down to the car.
- Okay. All right.
- Yeah. So those you can mist. Right.
- So these are the same...
Jerry? Saturday's
Casey's birthday party.
The plan was to swim.
Howard's nephew's a lifeguard.
We were gonna pay him to watch the kids.
But...
I don't know now.
Maybe you should drain
the pool, change the water.
Won't the "methalanon"
contaminate the water?
They sprayed again last night.
It's safe, Mrs. Finnigan.
It's only toxic for a few hours.
The water actually
dilutes it, so...
water's probably
the safest place to be.
So irresponsible. Casey has allergies.
The slightest thing sets him off.
I wouldn't worry about it,
Mrs. Finnigan.
Well... why don't you
come again Saturday?
When's your next
regular day?
Tuesday.
I can't make it Saturday.
- Hi.
- But really, I wouldn't worry about it.
I was wondering if your guy
could treat my pool. Can you?
Can I what?
Whatever you put in it
to kill the bug spray.
I'll pay you.
I'm afraid to go in.
- I only have time to take care of
my regular customers, ma'am. I'm sorry.
- Hey, Jerry, can I help with the pool today?
- Casey, get back in the house.
It's still dangerous out here.
- Well, maybe I'll become a regular customer.
- Get ready for school.
- Have you seen my wallet?
- Oh. It's next to the phone.
- What's it doing there?
Oh, I was ordering something
from this catalog.
- Will you at least come over and look at it?
- Not now, ma'am!
I... You know, I might be able to
swing back by in a couple of hours.
I'm late. We'll talk about
your bearded iris tonight.
Hey, Jer!
How goes the war?
Bad guys are winning, sir.
Yeah, well,
thank you very much.
Now, see, these bugs...
This Humphrey or this Royal Coachman...
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
"Doreen".
Is that your name? Doreen?
- That's it.
- Hey, Gordon, isn't that your first wife's name?
- Darlene.
- Oh.
- Are you sure?
No.
- So, where we going, anyway, guys?
- An hour outside of Bakersfield.
- Then we're gonna walk.
- How far?
Four or five hours.
There's nobody there.
- You say it's good, right?
- Yeah. Is the fishing good?
- It's gorgeous.
- Oh, good.
You've never seen anything like it.
They want to be caught.
They're desperate
to be caught.
What's that for?
I thought I might have
to examine you later on.
Where'd you get it?
Some doctor left it in my web.
- Better take it to the lost and found.
- Yeah.
What's the menu like, babe?
The Greek's watching. Don't order
anything you can't pay for.
Daddy's home!
Pow! Pow! Pow!
Daddy, you gonna take us
to the park today?
Off me! Off me!
- Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!
- Quiet!
Cut it out.
Quiet! Quiet!
Get in the house.
- Did you do this?
- No. The dog did!
Mommy, Mommy, Daddy's home!
Daddy's home!
That's really exciting, sweetheart.
Please finish eating.
- Bang! Bang! I saw Dada!
- Please don't point that gun at me.
Who gave the dog my belt?
This is completely destroyed.
Completely ruined.
It's a piece of trash.
It's a $35 belt!
Shut up!
- That dog has got to go.
- Wanna talk about where you were last night?
No, I don't.
Not in front of the kids, I don't.
I don't want them to hear about all the
"ain-pay" and "isery-may" I saw last night.
If you would like to hear
about kids on C-R-A-C- K...
you can come in
the other room.
Whose crack are we
talking about, Gene?
I got a list here.
Um, I canceled the 'Times'.
I stopped the mail.
Just check up on the fish...
Harriet! Enough about
the fish. Let's go.
- Okay, okay.
- Which one takes the, um, goldfish?
These are the lionfish,
and these are the goldfish.
- Come on. I don't wanna miss that plane.
- Okay.
Just feed the other fish
regular food.
- Hey, sorry. You guys are running late, huh?
- Yeah. She keeps running her mouth.
Uh-huh.
You need a hand with those?
- I gotta go. Jim's gonna have a fit,
and I gotta make sure I have the tickets.
- Have a good time in Memphis.
Thank you.
Have you got the keys?
- And, um, that's it.
- All right.
- Say happy birthday to your mom.
- Bye.
Bring us back some
of that country ham.
- You're not gonna smoke in my house.
- I'm sorry.
- Thanks. Bye.
- Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, Harriet.
- Come on.
- They are so full of shit.
They've been good to us.
Don't smoke, Bill.
They brought us to a jazz bar, gave us
a couple of drinks. And what do we do?
We're taking care of their apartment free
for a month. They're taking advantage of us.
- Don't you have some classes or something?
- I don't punch a time card. I'm not in high school.
So, what are you
gonna order?
Uh, let's see, baby.
- I can't read this.
- Honey, put on your real glasses.
Let's see.
- Tuna melt.
- Tuna melt? It's breakfast.
- Have a steak and some eggs.
- Not if I have to pay for it, baby.
You're not drinkin', are you?
- Is that what's startin'?
- No.
Very... Ohh!
Suddenly there's God
so quickly.
My goodness.
Gordon, how about that ass?
I've seen better.
I just saw what
she had for breakfast.
Where have you seen better? Penthouse?
I say that's money in the bank.
- What do you think, Stuart?
- Not for breakfast.
- Excuse me, honey.
- Yeah?
Uh, could we have...
What was it in the bottom drawer
over there you were getting?
- What, butter?
- Yeah. Could we have more butter, please?
Here you go. Oh, hey,
is my tuna melt workin'?
Well, I'd say this trip's
off to a pretty good start.
Yeah.
I say the tuna melt works.
- Cup of coffee.
- Yeah, okay.
You know what we need?
More, uh, you-know-what.
Uh, could we have
some more butter, please?
Oh, yeah. Okay. Butter.
Coming up.
Is that your face,
or your neck just threw up?
- We're out of butter.
- Out of butter.
Ask for margarine.
Well, then what did he do?
He walks in at
7:30 in the morning.
The kids are screaming. They're
happy to see him. Same old story.
Sits down. He's acting
like nothing's happened.
I have no explanation.
Nothing.
- So he's out having breakfast with her.
- Are you serious?
Yeah! I mean, I tried
to ask him where he was, and...
he gave me some...
- I'm going.
- Where's he going?
- He's going to work. Okay.
He gives me some ridiculous
excuse like... like crack kids...
- Who you talking to?
- I'm talking to Sherri.
- And, um... And, um...
- Bye!
And now I'm not even supposed to
say the word "crack" in front of them.
Now tell me about
the Alex Trebek thing.
Did he flirt with you?
- Who?
- Alex Trebek.
No! Oh, no. I mean...
- Shut up!
- What's so threatening about that?
- Nothing.
- Sherri, where are my keys?
Will you get out of here?
Sherri! The dog pissed
on the bed again, Sherri.
Shoot him, man!
Shoot him! He's crazy!
Who are you
talking to, anyway?
Yeah, in those nice, tight pants he likes
'cause it makes his dick look big.
What? I can't hear you.
The dog's barking.
I'm talking to my sister.
Yap, yap, yap.
Yap, yap, yap, yap, yap!
- Yap, yap, yap, yap, yap!
- Where are you going, Gene?
I thought you had
some time off this week.
I gotta check on my work.
Quality control.
Uh-huh.
How about tonight, Gene?
- Oh, God.
- Sherri.
- Just a minute.
- Okay.
You know what kind of
work I do, right? Look at me!
You know it's dangerous...
and you know there's things you
can't know for your own safety, right?
I was just asking
about dinner.
Don't you worry your
pretty little head about it.
- He's out of here.
- All right, kids.
What is he talking about?
- The king is gone.
- Come on, Suzy. Come on.
Close the gate when you go!
I don't want Suzy to get out!
He might get run over!
Casey?
You are gonna be late
for school, young man.
- Now, do you want me to drive you?
- No. I'll walk.
You sure?
All right, kisses. Okay.
Oh, my God.
Honey! Honey, you all right?
- I... I'm fine.
- Wait, wait, wait!
Let me get your stuff.
Here. Wait, I'll...
- Come on, let's get in my car.
- No, I- I'm fine.
My mom doesn't want me
to go in a car with strangers.
No, wait a minute. Let me give you
a ride home, make sure you're okay.
I'm... I'm fine.
For sure.
No, no. Look.
Come on.
How old are you?
I'm eight.
My birthday's tomorrow.
I wanna see your mom and dad.
I wanna make sure you're okay.
My mom said
I can't talk with strangers.
Hey, bye.
- Have you got ready-made birthday cakes?
- Yeah. They're right here.
- Have you got one with "Betty" on it already?
- Just what you see here.
I can do something special,
but not for today.
Yeah. Well, all right,
I'll take that one. What is it?
- It's a lemon cake.
- Can you maybe put her name on it?
- I can't do it today.
- All right. Well, how much is it?
It's 14.75 with tax.
Mrs. Schwarzmeier, can you box this up?
Jawohl, Herr Bitkower.
Mrs. Schw... Could you maybe...
Could you just write "Betty" on here?
"Betty"? No. No.
- Hi.
- I'd like to order a birthday cake.
- Sure. What kind?
- Birthdays. They keep adding up, huh?
- Here is your cake and your change.
- Thanks.
Oh, I've got a couple
ideas here.
Okay, this is what I'd like.
What's that say?
"Happy Birthday, Casey"?
- Oh, excuse me.
- Yes. Casey.
- And is that supposed to be a baseball bat?
- Hi, Mrs. Schwarzmeier.
Yes, that's a baseball bat.
I don't draw very well.
- I came to pick up the cake
for Debbie Eggenweiler.
- Are you sure you want this?
Because I have some
very nice baseball designs.
- I think it's prepaid.
- Yes. Yes.
- If you like this, I can do it.
- No, I like this.
He's, um, he's starting Little League,
so we're real excited.
That's really sweet. His name
is Casey, and he plays baseball.
- Down, down.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Beautiful shot, man.
Hey. Casey. What's up?
How come you're
not in school?
- Let him go.
- Hey, Casey, you wanna see the dribble?
- Come on, Joe!
- Hey! Heads up!
- Come on. We're ahead too.
- Let's go.
Pass you. Pass you.
Yo, good pass, good pass.
Take a right
down by that tree.
- That's all?
- Okay. I got it, I got it.
Goddamn back seat.
Hey, Doreen.
Paul Grossman got me
more than $1 million.
Call me. Paul Grossman.
I'll be your attorney too.
Call toll-free. We'll come to your
home or office anywhere in California.
1-800-462-5555
Once a year, the P.B.A.
Touring pros join forces...
in doubles competitions.
What's the door doing
standing wide open?
Hey, you...
you hungry, honey?
What are you doing, anyway?
How come you're not workin'?
You're not gonna lose
your job again, are you?
You'd better give that back.
Some doctor's gonna be looking for it.
I got London broil from the Greek.
You want me to fix it? Want me to freeze it?
Doreen, Doreen
the question queen
Stole a London broil
thick and lean
Hey, how 'bout a fruit plate?
Somethin' light?
How 'bout a
short skirt, Doreen?
Short enough so I can see every
inch of your ass. How'd that be?
- What are you talkin' crazy for?
- Yeah.
We don't wanna talk
about that, do we?
We just wanna talk about Earl.
Let's hear more about Earl.
How 'bout cops, baby?
I bet they love
those short skirts.
I know fishermen like 'em!
- Whoa!
- No, man, wait a second.
What happened?
- Aw, Christ!
- What happened?
That's half my supply.
- Okay? Let's do it.
- All right. Let's go.
- Watch your step.
- Man, I'm thirsty already.
Well, we only got
3 hours and 59 minutes left.
Well, I don't think
it's gonna rain.
Casey?
What are you doing home, honey?
Why aren't you at school?
Honey? What happened?
I got hit by a car.
What? What do you mean,
you got hit by a car? Where? How?
Casey, now you tell Mommy
exactly what happened.
I got hit in the back
and knocked down hard.
- Well, how did you get home?
- Walked.
Well...
Casey, let me look at you.
Ohh. Now, um...
What about this car?
How fast was it going? Who hit you?
She was a lady.
She was nice.
Listen, honey...
today...
something terrible happened.
I hit this little kid with my car.
- Oh...
- He didn't get hurt. He was okay.
- But, Jesus, it scared the hell out of me.
- Oh, Jesus. All right, were the cops there?
I told you, he wasn't hurt.
Okay. All right, listen.
Did they get your name?
I told you, nobody was there.
He's all right.
Okay. All right.
I just don't wanna get sued.
No, it was just a
stroke of luck I didn't kill him.
I'm glad somebody's
luck's holdin' out.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Howard?
You have a phone call.
It's... It's your wife.
I think you've got time.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
Excuse me.
Jerry, we've got some great stuff,
good footage coming in on the satellite.
- Hello.
- Howard?
- Yeah?
- Casey got hit by a car.
He's all right, though.
What do you mean,
hit by a car?
When? Where is he?
Well, h-h-he's here.
He's home with me.
He's... He's all right.
He's not hurt.
Annie, calm down,
start from the beginning,
and tell me exactly
what happened.
Well, I put him in bed, and...
he fell fast asleep.
He's all right, I'm sure.
Why'd you let him go to sleep?
You shouldn't have done that, honey.
Jesus Christ! I mean, wh...
Who hit him? How did this happen?
I don't know!
I came home and he was here.
I... He went to sleep.
I should let him sleep, shouldn't I?
No. No, you wake him up...
and you take him to the emergency room.
You gotta get him looked at right away.
Call Bob Winslow.
No, wait, I'll call him.
Um, just hang up the phone.
I'll call you right back. Okay?
- All right. I understand.
- Okay. Don't worry.
Everything's gonna be all right.
He's gonna be fine.
Casey?
Casey, we're... we're gonna
get up and have some milk now.
Casey? Casey, um...
Casey, Daddy's coming home.
Casey.
Casey. Casey, wake up!
Casey, wake up!
Accidents happen every day.
Fortunately, most are harmless.
But some are very serious.
He's eight years old.
I asked him.
Tomorrow's his birthday.
Such a close call.
Everything could have changed.
Our whole lives could have changed.
Yeah, well, I wish somethin'
would come along and change our life.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Oh, nothin'.
Look, maybe I'm just sick and tired of
watching you show off your ass at work.
Oh, you're drunk. And you lied to me.
Get the hell out of here.
You want me out of here?
You got it.
You told me you weren't gonna lie no more.
That was the deal... no more lies.
Okay. Watch me go, baby.
You know, a lot of guys don't like a big ass
in their face when they're trying to eat.
Oh, pick a fight. Go ahead.
Pick a fight with me.
Tell you something...
I don't know who you think would wanna
look at your sad, middle-aged ass anyway.
Don't you talk to me like that.
And don't you come back here.
I'm not taking you back no more.
You understand? No more!
- No more I'm not taking you back!
- I'm not coming back!
- Slobberin' all over Honey like that.
- I never touched Honey!
I didn't say you touched her!
I said you slobbered on her!
How come you don't wear your
wedding ring to work anymore?
Oh, you're such
a bullshit artist.
You're the one chippin' away at
our mansion of love, baby, not me!
Why don't you go get drunk
and pee on Irmadine's drapes again!
I'm gonna
go get drunk!
I'm gonna get drunk
right now, goddamn it!
Look how stupid you're acting.
What if I'd killed him?
Then what?
Oh, Pat! What are you lookin' at?
It's nothin' new!
Have a nice day.
And now back
to 'Captain Planet'.
It's as much fun poaching
Planeteers as it is poaching elephants!
I have had enough of this!
- Betty! Chad! It's me!
- Your dad's here.
Come on. Let's go.
All right! I'm coming!
- Let's go.
- Give me that.
- Betty, the key doesn't work!
- Yeah!
Listen, don't you have any fun.
Stay up really late. Okay?
- Give me a kiss.
- Okay.
You changed the lock.
Happy birthday!
- Look at this helicopter I got! Isn't it neat?
- Cool! Come on. Make a wish and blow.
And there's a net
to catch the Planeteers in it.
It's really neat. And there's
Verminous Skumm inside.
He's one of the Eco-villains. Not a good guy.
I don't really like him very much.
- But it's neat.
- You're not all blown out, are you?
Hey, how come there's
only one candle?
Mommy's 29.
- Sure she is.
- Shut up.
That's what she told me.
I'm just trying to get Mommy used to
one big candle instead of a lot of little ones.
Is that a joke?
Come on. Blow!
Wait till you discover...
the rest of my surprises!
- Ohh!
- You got your wish!
- What'd you wish for?
That the two of you
would get the hell out of here.
Oh, Betty, you gotta
keep this wound.
It's your clock, Stormy.
You take it and keep it wound.
I want you gone when
I'm out of the shower.
Suzy, come on, boy.
All right, now, you go run away.
We don't want you anymore.
Go ahead.
Hey, hey, hey.
Sniff this.
Mm-mmm! Look at that.
It's a bone. Mmm!
All right, go get it.
Make sure they do the
neuro checks every half hour.
And diligent suctioning.
Mr. Finnigan.
- Yeah?
- He's resting comfortably.
That's good. We'll let him sleep.
That's the best thing for him right now.
The medfly editorial.
Not too sure about
that malathion.
Nurse, can you get me
some aspirin?
- Sure, Doctor.
- It's for me.
He's got a small blood clot,
a little brain swelling,
but it probably
won't require surgery.
He's aspirated, but we're
not too concerned about that.
- Aspirated? What is that?
- He's got some fluid in his lungs.
Listen, we'll keep
a close eye on him. Okay?
He knows what he's doing.
It's gonna be all right, honey.
- I, uh...
- Three more.
Damn shame you can't feel safe
driving in this city no more.
His vital signs are good. We're just
gonna have to wait till he wakes up.
Is there something we could do?
Something we should do?
You can wait. There's a
waiting room down the hall.
There's smoking out on the porch,
if you want to smoke.
He may be waking up soon.
You'll wanna be here when he does.
Yeah, well, uh, listen, how...
how long you think it'll... it'll be?
You never know with
these things. I just...
want you to do whatever
makes you feel comfortable.
Come on, come on, come on!
- You made it.
- Yeah!
I hope you don't have to
put too much chlorine in.
It's bad for my voice.
The pool's around the back.
Jonathan, that's you, babe!
Go up, go up!
- Right here, right here, right here!
- Zoe!
Excuse me.
Um, see how
that bruise is... is...
it's intense,
but it's not glowing.
So you'll wanna work on that.
Let's take a look at yours.
This is good. I like that. Yeah.
The bruise is really good.
Um... I want you to put
a little bit more blood in there.
Oh, on the...
on the, uh... on...
Yeah, blend off
that one edge.
- And take the brush out of your mouth.
- Sorry.
Filter? What's the filter
got to do with it?
Well, if your filter ain't workin', and I don't
think it is, there's not much I can do.
How dangerous is
this malathion?
Well... How long
have you had this system?
Came with the house.
Yeah? Well,
I hate to be the one to tell you,
but I think it's on its last legs.
Oh, no. Don't tell me.
- So, Ace, what's up tonight?
- I don't know. What do you wanna do?
I mean, with Mom. Is she celebrating
her birthday alone, or what?
Uh, with Gene.
Jean, huh?
Jean.
Well, who's she?
He's a friend of Mommy's.
May I see your license
and registration, ma'am?
Did I do something wrong,
Officer?
Take your
sunglasses off, ma'am.
You know, this clown
is detachable.
I, um... I have
a permit for it.
It's to code. I've been stopped before.
There's never been a problem.
- Phone number, ma'am?
- 504-0361.
I'm gonna let you go with
a warning this time, ma'am.
You were driving too slow.
Just as dangerous as driving too fast.
Please refrain from
doing so in the future.
Can I go now?
No, ma'am.
I have one more question.
What's that?
How many clowns
can you fit in this car?
I beg your pardon?
How many clowns can you
fit in this car, ma'am?
Why'd you take
my phone number?
Well, you never know when you might
need the services of a clown, ma'am.
- You have children?
- No, ma'am.
I, uh... I can use some cheering up
from time to time myself, ma'am.
Being a cop isn't easy.
You have a nice day now.
If there's anything I like
more than being mean...
it's being sneaky.
It's a trap!
- Of course it's a trap!
- Gene?
- Is that you?
- Affirmative!
With the Planeteers
out of our way...
Chad left the TV on.
Man dares to go where
only cows have gone before.
Bandini is the word
for fertilizer.
Oh, my God! Chad,
what are you doing here?
- Where's your dad?
- He had to go somewhere.
He had to go somewhere
without you?
He said he had
to do something.
- Something came up.
- Yeah.
I'll bet it did.
I'll bet something came up.
So, what'd he say
about you?
He said we'll have
to do it some other time.
Hey.
He's a son of a bitch.
- Now?
- Bring in the...
Jerry Kaiser.
- Hey, buddy, it's me.
- Hey.
Listen, I'm walking around
with a fuckin' serious chubby.
Listen to what's going on.
There's this girl
at school here...
She's 18, she's got a body to kill for,
beautiful face, and she asked me...
- Why are you whispering?
- to do her body makeup for this...
I'm not whispering. I'm just...
I'm... I'm throaty. I'm excited.
So I gotta do full-body makeup
on her. That takes an hour.
That means I'm rubbing base
up and down the insides of her thighs...
like, right around her puddy...
and I'm just like, "Oh, man!"
I gotta run it up and down, up her...
on the inside of her elastic...
and inside her perfect ass.
I'm just, like...
I'm losing it, man.
I was, like, rubbing some on her titties and
she looked at me and said, "What's your name?"
I said, "My name is Bill."
She said, "Bill, you're
giving me a nipple boner."
I said, "That's right."
And I was just, like... I was about
to drop my brushes and just fuckin'...
Oh! It was amazing.
What do you think about that, man?
Pretty amazing... Jerry?
Jerry? Kaiser?
Oh... Uh, d-did you
get a good grade?
Yeah, they gave me
an A-plus, baby.
- That's great.
- Why are you whispering?
- Shh! Shh, shh.
- What? What are you doing?
I told you! I'm working.
You don't sound like you're... What are
you doing, waiting for some rich dame...
Okay, I gotta go.
I'll call you back later. Bye.
I wish you wouldn't do that.
You're not fooling me,
you know.
Hey Stuart, nothing counts against first,
most or biggest unless we're all fishin', man.
Yeah, I'm just settin' up
this new line. All right?
What about somebody...
What about setting up the camp here?
Somebody's gotta dig the hole.
I'll do that! Just give me
a couple of minutes here!
I'll help you.
Just let me take a leak first.
Hey, don't piss
on any firewood!
Yeah, and don't piss
in the water!
Shit.
What are you
pissin'in the water for, Vern?
I kinda like the way it sounds.
Hey.
Hey, Stuart, Gordon!
Come here a second.
What the hell is this?
Stuart, come here!
Gordon, get over here!
Holy Christ!
It's a dead body!
Look at that. Jesus!
Who do you think it is?
- It's a dead body, isn't it?
- Yeah, it's a woman, huh?
She's dead, isn't she?
Yeah, dead. I'll say.
Look at her.
I wonder how.
We gotta pull her out.
Pull her out?
What are you, crazy?
I don't think we should
touch her. Should we?
No, we should call somebody.
I think we should call the police.
I don't think we should touch
anything until we call somebody.
Great idea. How we gonna do that? You got
a portable cellular phone or something?
We can't just leave
her there, can we?
Well, I know what
I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna have a drink.
Uh, I think Vern
has the right idea.
Hey, wait...
wait a minute!
Why don't you go home,
get some rest?
I'll call you if there's
any change.
No, you go. I'll stay. You go rest up.
You've got things at the station.
I'm all right.
I could make some calls.
Probably a good time.
Look, I'll take the number
of the pay phone here.
- That's a good idea.
- Yeah.
Sometimes it takes forever
to get through here.
Uh, could you bring me some...
shoes, some flats,
and a sweater?
And maybe some mail?
Magazines or something?
It's gonna be all right.
Bye.
- Marian?
- What? What's the matter?
Something horrible's happened.
This has been the worst day of my life.
Oh, my God.
What happened, Sherri? Tell me.
- Suzy ran away.
- Oh, Jesus.
I thought you were gonna say something
happened to one of the kids, or to Gene.
- It's Gene's fault. He's the one who let him out.
- Oh, I'm sure you'll find her.
- Him.
- Yeah.
I've been going up and down
the streets all day trying to find him.
- Kids are going nuts!
- Did you call the pound?
- Dad, Suzy's gone!
- I called everyone I could think of.
- Honey, he's out running around. Don't worry.
- No, Daddy, he's really gone!
Honey, he'll come back
when he's ready. Don't worry.
Daddy, we looked and looked.
Sweetheart, Suzy will be back
as soon as he gets hungry.
Daddy, I want Suzy back!
Daddy, we can't find Suzy!
Listen to me, all of you.
Suzy will come back... sometime.
- What if she doesn't?
- Well, then we'll have to get another dog.
- We'll get a puppy this time. How's that?
- I don't want another dog. I want Suzy!
I want Suzy!
- Tell me how much you want it.
- Put those on my side.
Why should I, Big?
Still got three fingers
in your ass?
Slut. I should make you
get an egg.
You got an egg
in that refrigerator?
No, you don't got an egg?
- What about a candle?
- Candle.
What about the rubber bands
I told you about?
I don't think you got 'em
tight enough. Snap 'em!
- Good.
- Okay. Geez!
Okay, take the rubber bands
off your dick.
I'm gonna suck your dick now.
I'm gonna introduce
your dick to my tonsils.
Sit back down.
Joe, now!
- Baby...
- How long you gonna stay on that phone, Lois?
- Sit down. Look at the cards.
- Say, "Please, mistress."
- Sit down.
- I didn't tell you to come!
So tell me, how did it feel?
Next time I'm gonna make you
get a Q-Tip with some aftershave...
and I'm gonna make you
stick it up that dick of yours.
3:30 Wednesday.
Call me, bitch.
Bend the card!
They don't want another dog.
- Well, neither do I.
- Neither do I.
- Neither do I!
- I! I! I!
I!
I don't even see
what the difference is.
They're not even gonna know
who Suzy is in a week.
Let's take the kids, put them in the car,
drive around and see if anybody's seen him.
- Can't do it. I got plans.
- Oh, Gene, come on!
Sherri, I told you
a week and a half ago...
I got the leadership...
council thing on the... crack kids.
What you should do is,
you should go out with the kids...
put up some signs, offer
a reward... not too much.
- Remember, it's a dog.
- Who's Claire "The Clown" Kane?
What are you doing
looking in my pockets?
What are you doing with her
driver's license and telephone number?
You wanna know?
I'll tell you.
Claire Kane, a.k.a.
"The Clown"...
is a bunco artist
wanted in three states.
I have her phone number because I'm
running a sting operation. Now you know.
And now, unfortunately...
I have compromised your safety
and the children's safety.
Are you happy now?
There is a...
a hard, heavy physicality...
in my new paintings.
In part because I've executed them
on large panels of wood...
but I'd say that
they're tempered by the...
- Oh. Sorry.
- Sorry.
Um, tempered by the
ephemeral use of color.
You could almost say that
it's beyond natural color.
What are they about?
Well...
I think they're about seeing...
and the responsibility
that comes with that.
- Okay.
- And call next week.
- Thanks. Thank you very much.
- Bye.
Bye-bye.
Who was that? Sherri?
No, that was David...
at the gallery.
Oh. David at the gallery.
I'm hoping to get
a show there.
Is this "David at the gallery" going to be
another Mitchell Anderson in our lives?
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, that's the sort of stuff you two
used to blather on about, isn't it?
What are you talking about?
The lousy painter. The one who never
sold anything. Mitchell Anderson.
Just because he never sold anything
doesn't mean he was a lousy painter.
So you've said.
Well, it's true.
You know,
scientifically speaking, Marian...
there's no such thing as
"beyond natural color".
I don't know why we're sittin'
around here actin'like it was our fault.
We didn't have
anything to do with it.
Yeah. Suppose we'd never
come up here in the first place.
When would she have
been found? Maybe never.
Nothing we can do to help.
She must have been murdered.
I mean, she's naked and everything.
Nothing we're gonna do
about it tonight, anyway.
Suppose it floats away.
Then it's out of our hands.
Maybe that's what we oughta do...
kick it loose and let somebody else find it.
Ah, I don't know.
I think...
I think we oughta tie it up
so it won't float away.
Then we can, uh, you know,
deal with it in the morning.
What do you say about that?
I say we got 2 hours of prime trout
time left. That's what we oughta deal with.
Hey, let's take a vote.
All right by me.
Fish now,
or deal with the body.
I say fish now.
Suppose the current
takes it away.
Then it's not our problem.
The Planeteers are trying to save
the planet and the environment.
Uh, they're all
wonderful characters.
- Tell Gene where he comes from.
- The tropical rain forest.
- This one?
- This is Ma- Ti.
And his power is heart.
Let's see. Where is his ring?
They all come with little...
Stormy did this to me on purpose.
I'm gonna kill him.
Let's say he points his ring
at, maybe, Earth, and...
Chad, you know what?
I think that it was really nice
that Gene brought us here tonight...
and I think we should
say thank you.
- Don't you?
- Mommy, can I go to the bathroom, please?
Yeah.
- Wait. Where is it?
- Uh, excuse me, miss.
Where's the restroom?
- For him? I'll take him.
- Thanks.
Come on. I'll show you.
What's that?
- What?
- That.
Happy birthday.
What is it?
An alarm clock?
It's pretty.
My marriage is breaking up.
Oh, honey, really?
Really.
I can't think of
anything but you.
Not at work,
not about the trial.
Just you.
I think I'm, uh...
I think I'm, uh,
getting serious.
Oh, honey, I wanna be
with you too.
- Hello?
- Mrs. Finnigan, please.
Uh, sorry, she's
not here right now.
- Who's this?
- This is Mr. Bitkower.
She placed an order today, and I just wanted
to make sure I was clear about what she wanted.
Her drawing's a little messy.
Well, she isn't here right now.
Call her back next week. All right?
Hello.
I don't appreciate
being hung up on...
when I'm calling
about your order.
I need to know whether Mrs. Finnigan
wanted a bat or a mitt. May I speak to her?
No, you may not. Whatever it is,
just cancel it and stop calling here.
Now, we've got
a problem here.
We don't need the line tied up
with unimportant stuff!
Either you give me
an answer now...
Look, fuck you, asshole.
Fuck you!
Jesus.
Goddamn it!
All right, tomorrow night
we'll get a motel room.
- When?
- Tomorrow night.
Oh, no, I can't.
I'm going away for the weekend.
- What?
- Goin' to Tahoe, see my sister.
- Tahoe? When did that get decided on?
- I don't know. Last week.
Your sister? Thought your
sister lived in Michigan.
That's Phyllis. This is Bunny.
- Bunny lives in Tahoe.
- Bunny? Who's Bunny?
You never mentioned
her before.
- Yes, I did. She's my half sister.
- Half sister?
And besi... Gene, you were always
with your family on the weekend.
How was I supposed to know
you could get away?
Oh, well...
I don't know what
to think, Betty.
Huh.
So, is B...
Who is Bunny?
- Bunny...
- Bunny... Who's...
- Bunny is my half-stepsister.
- These your mother's kids or your father's kids?
- My dad's wife's kid.
- Oh, yeah.
We have been planning to
get together for over a year.
- Oh, yeah? Well, what's she do in Tahoe?
- What?
What does she do in Tahoe?
She work? Is she married?
- Tahoe's a fancy place to live, you know.
- Gene, stop this.
I'm going away for a few days
to visit my sister.
Don't try to make me feel
guilty about nothing.
You're making mountains
out of molehills.
- Come on...
- Shh. Kid's back.
There's this really
neat camera up front.
- It's not a real camera.
- Did you find the bathroom okay?
Uh, yeah. There's a man
throwing up in there.
- Oh, my God. How awful. Is he all right?
- Chad.
- I don't know.
- You going to visit Aunt Bunny this weekend?
How about those peas?
Let's eat up some of those peas.
Bunny?
He's too young to
remember Bunny, okay?
Does not remember Bunny.
Eat 'em up.
Anyway, it squirts water...
It looks like a real camera. Please?
I really want it. Come on.
Daddy would buy it for me.
You boys have obviously not heard
of the Joe Robbins legend, have you?
- What can I get you, pal?
- Same, Jay.
Are you laughin' at me?
- No one was laughin'at you.
- Go ahead.
Next to my cell,
a big Spanish brother.
6'4", 6'5", Eddie Valdez.
We called him "Big Ed."
I said, "Big Ed, yo, listen.
Don't fuck with me."
Cat fuck with me. I get my hands
on about 30 feet of rope.
Now, you may wonder
where I get rope in prison.
Like I told you, I'm Joe Robbins.
Inside or out.
It's all in my cell.
How you doin'?
Good.
Here's a song I want
to sing for myself.
I lay low, like a black cat
in the shadows.
And I wait for this big Spanish
motherfucker to come moseyin' down.
As soon as he
crossed my path, boom.
- I'm tired
- Flies on shit...
So tired
Around his neck so quick, then
pushed him over the fucking guardrail.
The rope snaps tight.
His fuckin' head pops off.
His body keeps plummeting
downward, and he falls...
neck hole first
into the ground.
My point is...
Big Ed pissed me off
just a little bit.
You wanna keep it down
so the lady can sing?
Wait.
Hey, come on.
- I made a mistake, all right?
- Yeah, you made a mistake.
- See, my shit's live.
- Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up.
Where was I?
I was tellin' a story here.
But I won't be sorry
If you won't be
And I don't want your pity
Or your sympathy
But with $45
I can make it
- Hi.
- Hi. How's he doin'?
- You wait and see
He's still asleep.
He really hasn't moved.
What's, uh...
What's all this?
I don't know.
Dr. Wyman ordered it.
Any change?
- Well, he says the numbers look good.
- Yeah?
I don't think it's good he keeps sleeping
like this. I don't think that's a good sign.
He's okay.
He's gonna be all right.
He'll wake up soon.
I talked to, uh, Bob Winslow.
He's in Hawaii.
And he knows this... this Wyman fellow.
He says we're in good hands.
- He knows what's what.
- Good.
I'm gonna go get
a cup of coffee.
- You stay with Casey.
- Okay.
Oh, God.
Why won't he wake up?
It isn't as if
I was just anybody
On Broadway I danced
For that senator
They know me in London
And they know me in Paris
- Hmm.
- I'm only talking
'Cause you looked like
you needed a friend
Here. Gimme that. Gimme that.
I'll tie it around the wrist.
Never thought I'd be
doing anything like this.
- Yeah, me neither.
- What's she feel like, Stuart?
- Oh, God.
- Feel her tits?
You know, I just realized...
there's probably a thousand guys in L.A.
Who'd be ballin' her right now.
Will you shut up!
I'm just trying to lighten things up
a little bit, all right?
Yeah, let's get the hell out of here.
Come on. Tie that up.
Man, if you'd have told me I was
fooling around with a dead body up here...
- I'd have told you you were full of shit.
- Yeah. Okay, let's go.
- Stop stealing.
- Bill, God. What'd ya sneak... Bill.
- I'm sorry.
- You scared me.
- You want to make up?
- Why did you sneak up on me?
- What time are your classes, huh?
- I'm ditching.
I wanna see you.
It's true.
- You've got to go to class.
- Are you snoopin' around?
- All you're supposed to do is just feed the fish.
- Look at this one, though. Look at this one.
- Look it, that's a lionfish, honey.
- Oh, really?
- He is. Go on. You should go to classes.
- Okay.
- These are strange people, honey.
- I know.
- What's in here?
- Bill... Don't snoop, Bill.
- Don't snoop.
- Why not?
You respect their privacy.
Why not snoop around with
their "Hot Fudge" videos out?
Their sick, dirty pornography.
These people are creepy.
They're creepy.
Use an ashtray
when you smoke in here.
- That's a rule. That's a rule.
- Why? There's no...
- Oh, you brought my ashtray.
- Our ashtray.
See, on the list it says
it's good for the carpet.
- Oh, Bill.
- How long are these creeps gonna be out of town?
A month.
You know what?
- I think we should move in here.
- No.
- And really... Yeah!
- We can't do that.
It's the only respectful
thing to do.
- Nah, that wouldn't be right.
- Why not?
'Cause that's not right, Bill.
- Okay.
- She's right.
- So, I'll see you around 6:00, okay?
- Yeah. I'll come home.
But you know we're gonna do
the right thing in their bed tonight, right?
Oh, uh... I don't know.
Whoo-hoo!
Hey, Vern!
- Hey!
- Look at here!
- How big?
- It's about three or four pounds.
I got it!
Hey! Didn't I tell ya?
It's Moby fuckin' Dick here!
Look at this!
Come on, baby. Come on!
Come to Papa.
How long are you gonna do that?
Do you know what time it is?
Do you have to play so loud?
That's Chick's fault. He was always
hot for the string players.
I always thought
they were weird.
- String players and girl singers.
- How come...
That was his weakness.
I don't remember him.
Well, mainly because
he wasn't around that much.
Hell, he exploded
when you were barely six.
Get me another
"Veggie Mary," will ya?
Talk... Talk more about Dad.
Not much more to tell, baby.
He was a prick.
That's the long and the short of it.
- Wanna get the door?
- Mommy, Daddy's here.
- Hey!
- Go to your room.
Finish up what I told you to do.
What do you want?
I came to get
my mother's clock.
- What's wrong with you?
- Well, it is my clock, isn't it?
- Finish. Do what I told you.
- Oh, Betty.
What you did to your son
is unforgivable.
What, he didn't tell you Daddy's been
flying nights, bombin' the dirty medflies?
Get it and get out.
- This house is half mine, you know.
- Liar!
- I pay for it.
- Take what you think is yours...
and get out of my life!
New sheets.
Jungle theme, huh?
- Goin' somewhere?
- Yeah, I am.
- Yeah? Where?
- None of your business.
Your... condom
file drawer is open.
Going with Gene?
Going somewhere
with Jungle Gene?
Get your fucking clock
and get out of here!
Oh!
Goddamn it, Zoe!
What was that?
Thank you.
- What was the patient's name?
- Eh, the boy's name is... is Finnigan.
Uh, h-his father is
Howard Finnigan, if that helps.
Excuse me.
I'm Claire the Clown.
I'm here to do a party
in the pediatrics ward.
- Yes. I'll call the head nurse.
- Uh... excuse me. Uh, Claire?
- Do you do tricks in your, uh, routine?
- Yes. Uh- huh.
Oh, I've got something to show you.
I brought this stuff along.
I wanted to do this trick
for my grandson.
He's a patient in there.
I used to do this for his dad
when he was just a kid.
Now, I am going to move
that egg from this glass...
into that glass
without touching it.
You say to me, "How could you
possibly do that?" Go ahead.
How could you possibly do that?
I'm going to show you.
I-Is that a touch of terrific?
It's yours!
Thanks. It's good for bars,
but I don't think it's a children's trick.
- Claire.
- I'm here.
The Finnigan boy's
in Intensive Care, sir.
- But I think that's his mother over there.
- Oh.
Dr. Wyman, it's Claire.
Claire Kane. Remember?
From the concert.
Um... This is what I do.
I'm doing a chil... I'm... I'm a clown.
I'm really looking forward
to dinner.
- Stuart's bringing the fish. Remember?
- Right.
- Who's that?
- I have no idea.
Ann? Ann Finnigan?
Oh, good. The girl said that
she thought you were...
Yeah, I just didn't want to walk
into the boy's room alone, you know.
- Do I... Do...
- Oh, I'm sorry. Paul Finnigan, huh?
Howard's dad.
- Howard's dad?
- Yeah. Yeah. Howard's dad.
I was just passing
through L.A., and I, uh...
Well, actually, I've been living
in Riverside for a number of years.
Olla filled me in on what
was going on around here.
- Olla?
- Yeah, Olla.
How's the boy?
Well, he has a head injury...
a little clot and some swelling.
But they don't have to operate. We're
a little worried because he won't wake up.
- Oh.
- So you're Howard's dad?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Well, it was very thoughtful of you to come by.
Yeah. Oh, hey, hey.
I was gonna come by...
but I just heard about this now.
You know, I've never even seen him.
You know, uh, Kevin... It's, uh...
- Casey.
- Casey, yeah. Yeah, Casey.
- Howard's doing real good, isn't he?
- Well, we're...
We're very worried. You know,
he... he... he won't wake up.
Uh, but other than that, he doesn't
have any broken bones, so...
No, I mean, Howard's
doing real good.
- Oh.
- The TV editorials, you know.
Yeah.
- Hello?
- Who's this?
- Well, who's this?
- Let me speak to Betty.
- Give me that phone.
- No, she's not dressed right now.
- Give it to me!
- Honey, put your panties on!
- Who is this?
- Give me that phone! Who is it?
Give it to me! Give it to me!
- Have a nice weekend!
- Get out of here!
Hello! Hello!
Hello? Betty Weathers.
- Take it easy with him.
- What is it?
They're gonna operate again.
He's gonna be all right. Thank you.
- Now, don't bump him!
- Keep that hallway clear.
You're not gonna believe this,
but your father's out there.
My father?
You mean Paul?
Yes!
He was always
such a good kid.
- Who's Olla?
- Olla? That's my aunt.
That's who your father
talked to.
What happened
to the Willis boy?
He's in surgery.
So, when did you last...
So, when did you
talk to him last?
He lives in Riverside.
That's not that far away.
I don't know. This is as much of a
urprise to me as it is to anybody.
I mean, I haven't seen him
in years. I haven't...
talked to him since
the divorce.
I wonder why he picked now.
- Hi, Dad.
- Hey, son. Ah!
Oh, you are lookin' good.
Hey, oh, I'm sorry to hear
about what happened to, um, uh...
- Casey.
- Yeah, the kid. Oh, I'm sure he's gonna be fine.
- We're praying.
- Yeah.
- You, uh... You... You've met Ann?
- Oh, sure. Yeah. Yeah, sure.
I seen you a couple of times on
television there. You're a real authority.
- Huh? Huh?
- Yeah.
So, uh... uh...
It's a bit of a surprise seeing...
- Yeah.
- How'd you find us?
Olla. Yeah.
So, uh, how you been?
Pretty good.
You know. It's...
Well, I'm gonna go back with Casey.
It was nice to meet you.
- Yeah, wasn't it?
- I'll see you back there, honey.
Well, at least
he came home last night.
That's more than
I can say for the dog.
Why don't you say
something to him?
Tell him what you think.
Oh, he'd just deny it.
If I start to get specific
about things...
he starts screaming about
what kind of job he has.
He's a pathological liar.
To tell you the truth,
I'm more worried about the dog.
- Mm-hmm. I know what you mean.
- Hi, Sherri. How are the kids?
They lost their dog.
Suzy ran away.
That's a shame.
She'll probably be back.
I wouldn't worry about it.
It's a he. Suzy's a boy.
Yeah, yeah. That's...
That's what I meant.
What are you doing home?
You're not supposed to be home now.
Oh, we have... we have
that thing with the, uh...
You know, the, uh,
the husband and wife?
- Kanes.
- Who are the Kanes?
They're these people
that we met at the concert.
They have tickets next to us.
It's not tonight. It's tomorrow night.
Remember? He's going fishing.
We're gonna eat his fish.
Tomorrow? Oh, shit!
Excuse me, Sherri. Um...
I told Sherri I'd go home, have dinner
with her and the kids. They're really upset.
Ralph, you're welcome to come.
But Gene's not gonna be there.
I don't think you want to come, honey.
You don't want to come, do you?
You don't want
to come, do you?
No. No, I-I-I can't.
I've got, uh, work.
Some lemons.
I will for a little bit.
Maybe he'll wake up if I'm not here.
Yeah. Well, when you get home,
just sit and rest...
or get something to eat,
or just have a bath.
And let's try to, uh, just, uh,
forget about it, okay?
- Everything's gonna be all right.
- Oh, yeah.
Uh, excuse me. I think... Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were asleep.
I think your son is in the room
next to my grandson, you know?
At least, I assume it's your son.
I'm not from around here.
I'm just here because
the kid got hit by a car.
Uh, are you the father of
that newsman on Channel 9?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah. Well, I'm Knute. This is my wife, Dora.
- Oh, hi. Paul Finnigan.
Oh, that's your wife?
You two...
- I'm sorry to hear about your grandson.
- Yeah, he got a cracked skull...
- and a concussion.
- Oh, no.
No, he's gonna be all right.
But they said he's in shock right now.
- I... I...
- Well, our son, Brian...
- Well, he's been operated on twice.
- Twice.
- No kidding.
- Somebody shot him on the freeway.
- What?
- Yes.
- Just driving along, minding his own business.
- Driving along, minding his own business.
- And somebody shot him.
- Oh, my God. What's the world coming to?
I don't know.
Nobody knows who did it.
Jesus. Well, ours was like
a hit-and-run too.
A recent graduate of
Seton Hall University...
he drank every day
of his college life.
- Beer and Jack Daniel's.
- Mom?
- Yeah, I'm in here.
- Not necessarily together.
- He still loves to get buzzed.
- Hi.
He doesn't do it
quite as much.
But he's not about
to give up drinking.
- Hi.
- Shh. I'm watching.
- What are you watching?
- Don't call it a disease.
- Why do you like that guy?
- Phil? I love him.
- Got you something.
- Huh?
- Look.
- Oh, cute. Goldfish. Haven't seen those in years.
Aren't those nice?
- I'll set it up for ya.
- How you feed 'em?
I'll show ya.
Jesus. Ma, it smells
like a bar in here.
Well, Earl's startin' on another one.
I don't know if I can take it anymore.
He gets so mean.
Didn't use to.
We used to have a good time
when we drank.
How long you gonna
let that guy ruin your life?
Mom, what are you doing smoking?
You said you quit.
I can't quit smokin' when I got
a lot of other stuff goin' on.
Why don't you think
about yourself for a change, huh?
I got to think about Earl.
Mom, he is a... he is a pig.
Do you know that?
He's a drunken, stupid pig.
I don't want you to talk that way
about your father.
He's not my father.
Well, he's my husband.
Don't you forget it.
He's an asshole.
I know, Mom.
- Believe me, I know. He's a...
- You don't know.
I don't want to
hear that anymore.
You told that story
one time too many.
Look at me. He was
drunk anyway, and you know it.
He's all I've got.
I need company.
We're addicted to addiction.
Honey, yesterday I hit a kid.
- What?
- I hit an eight-year-old kid.
He wasn't hurt. I just kind of
brushed him, knocked him down.
But it was so close.
He's such a little sweetie too.
I tried to give him a lift to his house.
He told me his mom and dad told him...
never to get into the car with anybody
unless they said it was okay.
Oh. You're very lucky,
you know that?
If I'd been going faster,
I would've killed him.
Imagine.
How could you get over that?
You couldn't.
I came home. I told Earl
our whole life could change.
Earl tells me
to go on a diet.
That's all he could
think of to say.
Hey!
I tell ya? Did I tell ya?
That's the best fishing
I've ever had.
Yeah, but I lost four
of those motherfuckers.
Yeah, but tell me it wasn't worth it. I mean,
even four hours of walking is worth this.
Yeah, but what
are we gonna...
do about you-know-what?
I'm gonna take
another picture.
Okay. Uh, right there, bring it down a little bit.
Right on the cantabile. A little bit down.
Zoe, is that bothering you?
- It looks terrible.
- Oh, no.
- Can we start right...
- How did you do that?
Um, I fell carrying
my mom's lunch tray.
- Can we start right at... at...
- By the way, how is your mother?
- Is... Is she all right?
- No.
I don't think she's got much time left.
I can see her change right in front of my eyes.
It's a cruel disease. Can...
Can we start at number six?
Okay. Number six.
Ah.
- Hello? Howard?
- No, this is not Howard.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Who are you calling?
Casey.
I want to talk about
that little bastard Casey.
Casey? Who is this?
Hello?
This is good. Is that Suzy?
Is that her tail?
That's nice. I really like that.
- Marian.
- Okay.
- Don't let the kids see.
- Why?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org