Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
We're not breaking anything!
Come on, please?
- Ow, ow, ow.
- Did you get it?
Ow! Got it! Oh!
It's locked!
Now, let's go!
- Are you crazy?
- I've got to know.
Well, go on.
Well, is it our ball?
Does it say "Tigers"?
Come on, Joe.
What's it say?
- It's-lt's not fair.
- Joe?
- Joe!
- It's not fair!
It's not fair.
What the hell's
the matter with you boys?
Baker fail you
in phys ed or something?
- Simon didn't do anything.
This is all my fault.
- I helped you break in.
- No, he didn't.
- You couldn't have done it without me.
- Shut up, will ya?
- Nice try, Joe.
Now, the way that
I figure this,
you can either do hard time
right here in prison,
or you can do
community service.
Community service.
That's what I thought.
And I've already
called the reverend,
and he'd be just delighted...
to have the two of you help him
with his Junior Lamb's Winter Retreat.
But that's over
Christmas break.
Yeah, we don't want to babysit the
stupid third graders at some dumb camp.
Fine! I'll just go out there in the
back room and get your prison uniforms.
- Okay, okay! We'll do it.
- Good.
Now, Joe. I'm gonna call your
grandmother to come and pick you up.
- Oh, she doesn't drive.
- Well, I've got to have
somebody pick you two up.
I've only got two men on tonight
and they're both out in the field.
- What about my parents?
- Joe, do you have any other relatives?
- No, sir.
- Did you call my parents?
Yes, I did.
What did they say?
They said that...
maybe that we should leave you
here for the night.
I guess they thought
it might teach you a lesson.
Anyhow, I gotta get
you guys outta here.
Do you know anybody that might come
down here at this hour of the night?
- Yeah.
- Who?
Yeah, who?
Just about
to land in WGV. Let's click on
the turnstiles on our wax files.
- Ben?
- Yeah?
- Are you mad?
- No.
Well, baffled,
but not mad.
I assume you had a good reason
for doing what you did.
- The reason is that Joe went psycho.
- Shut up, Simon.
That's a good reason as any.
- It is?
- Sure.
Everyone's got to reserve
the right to go a little nuts
every now and then.
- Life isn't always so easy.
- Or fair.
Oh, it's certainly not fair.
Hey, you guys want to go get,
uh, some pizza
or a hot dog or somethin'?
- You want to take us for pizza?
- Yeah, it's 9:00. Aren't you hungry?
It's not that.
It would be like...
rewarding us
for bad behavior.
- But if you really want to.
- No, Joe.
It wouldn't be right
to take advantage of Ben like that.
No pizza for us.
Okay.
Ice cream?
So, now I don't know
if I'll ever find out who my father is.
Maybe she figured
you weren't ready for the truth.
Ben?
Do you know the truth?
No. I guess your mom was just
gonna tell me when she was ready.
But if you did know,
would you tell me?
Yeah.
Yes, I would.
Ben?
Did Miss Wenteworth
ever talk about me?
All the time, Simon.
Everybody talks about you.
That's how we keep
from gettin' bored.
- Did she tell you about my destiny?
- Simon!
What do you mean?
- I'm going to be a hero.
- You are?
Pretty vague job description,
isn't it?
- How you gonna do that?
- I don't know.
I keep waiting for God
to show me a sign.
Like the burning bush
in the Ten Commandments.
But I guess he doesn't go in
for that kind of thing anymore.
Well, uh, you know,
you got to be a little patient.
I have been patient,
but I'm running out of time.
Simon, you're
12 years old!
You've got all the time
in the world!
I don't think so, Ben.
Time is a monster
that cannot be reasoned with.
It responds like
a snail to our impatience.
Then it races like a gazelle
when you can't catch your breath.
Simon and I were in such a hurry
to get to the answers at the end...
of the road that we never took time
to read the signs along the way.
How could we have known that everything
was working together for a reason?
And so I expect
each and every one of you...
will lend a hand
in making this...
the best Christmas
pageant ever.
So, now, are there
any volunteers for roles,
- or shall I just choose?
- Well, I'll play Joseph!
Good for you, Eddie.
- Looks like I got the lead.
- What lead?
It's the Virgin Mary, Eddie.
What does Joseph
have to do with anything?
All right, now.
Any volunteers for Mary?
Beautiful, beautiful
Mother Mary.
Mary, Mary, Mary.
Who will it be?
Marjorie?
Would you like to be
our Mary this year?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Good girl!
All right, now.
Which one of our...
future stars
would like to be the Three Wise Men?
Hm?
Three Wise Men.
Who's it gonna be?
All right.
Gary, Allen, Matthew,
you will be the Wise Men.
Now let's see what we've got.
Ah, well, we've got
the shepherds,
but they don't have
a lot to do.
Miss Leavey
always tried to downplay...
the role of the shepherds,
but we weren't fooled.
We knew they were the plum roles
because all you had to do...
was stand around with a staff
and try not to laugh...
at the poor saps that got stuck
with the speaking parts.
All right.
Hands-Hands down. Hands down.
Uh, Joe, Melanie,
Ming, Tommy.
You will be
our shepherds.
All right.
Now, let's see what's next.
We've got...
Oh, the angel.
Yes, the angel.
The wonderful angel
of the Lord...
suspended high, high above
everyone else...
the wonderful, magnificent angel
of the Lord.
Aww!
- I can't! I'm afraid of heights!
- Well, then, this will be...
the perfect chance
to face your fears.
- Can't I be a donkey or somethin'?
- You're an angel.
You have your own special pillar
of light for all the world to see.
- Well, I'll switch with Howard.
- No!
- Yeah!
- I could be Joseph. Joseph does nothing.
- Told ya.
You are going to make
a wonderful angel, Howard.
- But...
- Thank you.
- Psycho.
- What about me?
Well, Simon, you know what?
- You have the most important
role of all.
- No.
Without you,
there would be no play.
I'm not playing the baby Jesus,
so just forget it!
- You're the only one
who fits into the manger.
- I won't do it!
Come on, Simon.
It'll be fun.
Easy! It says swaddling clothes.
Swaddle it!
Simon, that is so cute!
I look like a burn victim.
- You made her laugh.
- She's laughing at me.
What's the difference?
She likes you.
Everyone likes
the swaddling baby Jesus.
- It's great!
- You really like it? Well, thank you.
Why does Ming get
all the girls?
But, uh, things
will be different...
once God makes you
a hero, right, Simon?
- Right?
- Huh?
Oh, yeah.
I guess.
You! You, you, you,
you, you, you! Okay, okay. Come on.
So, is everybody ready
for dress rehearsal?
- No.
- What now, Simon?
What are those?
- They're turtledoves.
- They look like
they're from outer space.
The audience won't know
what they are.
They're doves, Simon!
The audience knows what a dove is!
They're giant doves!
They're as big as half a donkey!
They're actually
kind of frightening!
Oh, look what I found
wandering off. A turtle.
Oh! A little turtledove! Look at that.
Oh, so how's
the rehearsal going?
Help. Please! I'm gonna strangle him.
I swear to God! I'm gonna strangle
that little granite mouse...
if it's the last thing I do,
with my bare hands!
- I'm gonna strangle him!
I'm a little fragile right now.
- Simon.
- Hey!
- You'll get these back
after the pageant.
If you can stop yourself
from ruining our play.
Understand?
Any questions?
Does God have
a plan for us?
I like to think he does.
Me too! I think God made me
the way I am for a reason.
Well, I'm glad that, um,
that your faith, uh...
helps you deal
with your, um,
you know,
your-your condition.
That's not what I mean.
I think I'm
God's instrument.
That He's gonna use me
to carry out His plan.
It's wonderful
to have faith, Simon,
but, uh,
let's not overdo it.
God's instrument.
Hey, kid. You okay?
- Hey, kid.
- Hi. What's wrong?
My dad's makin' me go
on a retreat tomorrow.
- Why are you crying?
- I'm scared of all the other kids.
They're a lot
bigger than me.
- Not all of them.
- Are you going too?
And I'll make sure
nothing happens to you. I promise.
Now get over there with those other
flying monkeys where you belong.
We're turtledoves.
Quack. Quack.
- You're good with him.
- Little kids always listen to me...
because of the way I look.
- Too bad Marjorie isn't six years old.
- Not funny!
The star of Bethlehem
is not a pinata.
Marjorie! Marjorie!
You spit that gum out right now!
The Virgin Mary
does not chew gum.
Where are we going?
You get down from there!
Get down from there now!
It's not safe!
I've got half a donkey here.
What good is that gonna do me?
I need a cigarette.
Monsters.
Oh! Oh, hello, Agnes.
Hello, Reverend. Hi.
Ah, ready for tonight?
Absolutely.
# Joy to the world #
# Miss Leavey's dead #
# They guillotined her head #
# We took it from her body #
# And flushed it
down the potty #
# And watched it go round and round #
# And watched it go round and round
and never saw it go down #
# Joy to the world
Miss Leavey's gone #
- Oh, Agnes.
- Oh! Oh!
# She's buried
in the lawn #
Psst! Psst!
Thank you.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas to you too.
- Merry Christmas.
Go, go.
Be not afraid.
For I bring you great joy.
Be not afraid!
For... F...
- For...
- Simon.
Are you okay?
For I bring you great...
joy!
Oh, man! Oh, man!
Oh, oh, man!
Simon, what is it?
Boobs!
- Get her, Simon!
- Holy shit!
Oh, shit!
- Let go of me!
- I'm trying to help!
Uuh!
Ohh!
- I don't feel so good.
- If you vomit on this stage,
I swear I will leave you
up there...
- till next Christmas!
- Hold on!
Uh-oh.
Yeah, yeah! Get it!
I'm gonna kick your ass,
you little perv.
Hey, leave him alone.
Pick on someone your own size.
- Okay.
- Oh!
- I told you this was a bad idea.
- Fight! Fight!
Oh, shit!
I'm gonna honk!
- Oh, no.
- Simon!
Oh, no!
Can I get down now?
Congratulations, Simon.
You've just given us our first
full-contact Christmas pageant.
Well, do you have
anything to say?
- Can I have my baseball cards back?
- No you may not!
Oh, Simon.
- What happened tonight?
- I don't know.
Sex makes people crazy.
That may be, uh... That may be true.
But, uh, that is
no kind of answer.
Simon,
you spend more time sitting
alone in a corner downstairs...
than you do
with the other children.
You, uh, frighten them
with your stories...
- about being an-an instrument of God.
- They're not stories.
And you interrupt my sermons
and you refuse to apologize.
I'm out of ideas, Simon.
I can't speak
to your parents because,
well, they don't
attend church.
And I-I can't speak
to Rebecca because...
because, uh...
um...
Simon, what I'm trying
to say is that...
all of us around here...
Well, we need a break from you.
So, once this all simmers down,
and Marjorie Albright's father
accepts your apology,
we'll talk about
you coming back.
- What about the retreat?
- Joe will go alone.
And it's about time
I had a talk with him too.
Simon, I'm sorry.
but, as the Bible says,
"There is severe discipline...
for him who forsakes the Way."
"To impose a fine
on a righteous man is not good.
To flog a noble man
is wrong."
Proverb 17, Verse 26. That's, uh,
very good, Simon.
But perhaps you know this one
as well: "Folly is bound up
in the heart of a child,
but the rod of discipline
drives it far from him."
- "Good sense makes a man slow to anger,
- Simon.
- and it is glory
to overlook the offense."
Simon... what do you
want me to do? Hmm?
What do you want me to say?
I want to know that
there's a reason for things.
I used to be certain,
but now I'm not so sure.
I want you to tell me
that God has a plan for me.
A plan for all of us.
Please.
Simon...
I can't.
Okay, you grabbed her boobs
and ya pulled her into the manger.
Big deal. It could have
happened to anybody.
Well, maybe not anybody.
Who cares what
Reverend Russell says, huh?
Him and his wife, they're the two
most miserable people we know.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Where are ya goin'?
- Home.
- Why?
It's Christmas.
I could go get the bike.
I'll walk.
Simon?
Simon!
Simon's sick.
- How sick?
- He's just sick, all right?
But I've gotta see him
before I leave on the retreat.
You can see him
when you get back.
But can't I just come in
and see him for a couple seconds?
Go on, now.
Simon's sick.
- I know.
- So was I when I heard
what he did last night.
The whole town's
talkin' about it.
What a little screwup.
Hey! Your son is not a screwup.
He's a hero.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I said he's a hero.
And you don't deserve him.
I want you to know that.
... six, seven,
eight, nine,
- ten, eleven,
- Thank you. And God bless you.
twelve...
Uh, is that it?
- We're one short.
- Is that
supposed to be a joke?
Have fun. Okay?
- Please tell me you're coming.
- I just came to say good-bye.
But what are you
gonna do without me?
Well, first, I'm gonna sneak
into Reverend Russell's office
and get my baseball cards back.
Sounds like trouble.
Sorry I'm gonna miss it.
Well, I bet you boys are going
to be very sad to know that...
Miss Leavey has taken
a leave of absence.
She's going to spend some time
with her mother in Connecticut.
Okay, Joe. Let's go.
Simon, you should be home resting.
You better go.
Yeah.
- So, uh, I'll see ya
in a couple days, right?
- Sure.
- Get better, okay?
- Okay.
I wish I could
remember every detail of that weekend.
Even now, I'll sometimes sit
and try to remember the colors,
the sounds, the faces.
But it only comes back to me
in bits and pieces.
If only I had known,
I would have paid closer attention.
But you're never prepared for
the moment that changes your life.
Whoa. Hey. Hey, you okay?
Yeah.
- Take it slow.
- You're very good with them, Joe.
You should see Simon.
He's the one they really listen to.
Don't tell me you miss him
already. It's only been one day.
- He's my best friend.
- Yes, I know.
Gotcha!
- Miss Wenteworth.
And how did you end up...
with Simon Birch
as your best friend?
I don't know. Maybe it's because we both
know how it feels to be an outsider.
Teased or...
whispered about.
- They tease you?
- Yeah, you know, the Wenteworth bastard,
and stuff like that.
Well, people-people can be
very unforgiving at times, Joe, uh...
I'm sorry.
- Joe!
- Looks like somebody needs me.
Joe.
You can talk to me...
anytime.
God, no wonder
she kept it such a secret.
You're sure we're doin'
the right thing, huh, Simon?
We promised him, Ben.
You promised him too, remember?
You're right. I did.
Reverend Russell?
Reverend?
Uh... I need the keys...
to the kitchen.
Reverend?
A lefty.
Just like me.
What do you mean?
I met your mother 13 years ago.
I was coming to Gravestown
to interview at the church.
- No.
- She was going to the city to
buy a present for her mother.
Stop it.
I'd never seen anyone like her, Joe.
And I fell in love.
- Right there on
the Boston and Maine.
- Joe! Joe!
Simon.
Did you hear what he said?
He's lying, right?
Joe...
Joe!
Let him go, Reverend.
Joe.
A bastard.
I wish I never knew.
I wish I'd never found out.
- I must sound like a baby, huh?
- No.
- Big goddamn baby.
- No, you don't.
- I wish I could go home again.
- I know.
Back to the way things were.
I know, pal.
I guess Simon's gonna ride
on the bus with Joe.
- He'll be all right.
- Ben, it was a mistake.
I wanted to take care of her,
but she said she didn't need that.
- Well, that sounds
a lot like Rebecca to me.
- Yeah.
Haunts me every day
of my life.
Wish I could take it back. l...
I just wish it never happened.
Well, there's a beautiful kid over there
who wouldn't be here if it hadn't.
Ben?
... eleven,
- twelve,
- and he ranks thirteen.
- Hey, you came.
- I told you I'd be here. Come on.
Up we go.
Thanks.
You okay?
I was thinking.
Maybe this was
your destiny.
To help me find my father.
Yeah. Maybe.
...that our boys should be returning
home in just a matter of weeks.
- Come on. Give it back.
- You started it!
Calm down, guys.
Watch out!
Oh, God!
- I can't... I can't stop it!
I can't stop it!
- Oh, good Lord.
- Oh, no!
- Oh, my God!
Oh, good Lord!
Oh!
Reverend Russell!
I can't sw- I can't swim!
Hey, where are you going?
Come back.
Okay, everybody, just stay calm.
Okay. We're going to get out of here.
Hey, come on. Calm down.
Just listen to me.
Stop it!
I'm not going to let anything
happen to any of you. Understand?
Now, the current is very strong.
So I'll take you to Joe... one at
a time, and Joe will help you on shore.
- Go!
- Okay.
You first, now you.
You're after him.
Don't worry. It'll be okay.
I got you.
Now, you. Come on.
Let's go. You're next.
Well, that's it. Come on.
Simon, let's go.
Wait. We're missing one.
Simon!
Joe!
My foot's stuck.
I'm scared.
Hang on.
- Aah!
- Come on. I got ya.
Come on, Stuart.
It's okay.
I got him.
- Where's Simon?
- He's inside. I'll get him.
- No, no! Let me.
- Simon!
Get him. Get him, Joe.
Pull him through the window.
Pull him out, Joe.
- Joe!
- Simon!
- No, no, no, Simon!
Simon!
Let me.
Joe!
Simon!
Okay, Joe.
Keep his head above the water.
Hmm. Hmm.
- Get 'em up to the road.
- What about Joe?
We got him. Joe!
Come with me, boys.
Here. Down here.
Here. Hurry!
Come on.
Come here, children.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Come on, Joe.
Simon.
Don't leave me.
I want to see Simon.
Father Russell,
I'll see you on Sunday.
He's got a visitor.
Simon...
I heard what you did
for those kids.
The whole town's
talking about it.
I just wanted
you to know...
that I think what you did...
was really brave.
And you're a hero,
Simon Birch.
Jesus, Simon,
you look like shit.
Hey.
Are the kids okay?
Yeah.
They all made it?
Even Stuart.
Did you see how
the children listened to me...
because of the way I looked?
Yeah.
That window
was just my size.
Extra small.
Extra, extra small.
That was
over 200 Mississippi.
Nobody likes a showoff.
Promise me.
Yeah.
- You'll take my baseball cards.
- No.
Take them and share them
with Ben. Please?
Okay. I promise.
Simon?
Yeah.
You're the best friend
I ever had.
I know that, stupid.
- Joe?
- Yeah.
I got to go now.
Okay.
See you later, alligator.
Timber-r-r!
One year good luck.
Winter left its icy chill behind.
And soon it was spring
and summer again.
Grandmother passed away
that June...
following a stroke.
And because Hildie was always
so content to just follow her lead,
she had a stroke of her own
and died in July.
We buried them
side by side.
It's the way
they would have wanted it.
Ben Goodrich legally
adopted me...
just two days
before my 13th birthday.
Not a day goes by that I don't
thank God for bringing him into my life.
With Simon's help,
I'd finally found my real father.
There is a prayer
I say for Simon Birch.
It's the same prayer
that he said at my mother's grave...
that night I found him
in the darkness.
Into paradise...
may the angels lead you.
Dad?
Dad! I'd love to stay here
in the graveyard all day,
but I've got a game, remember?
Okay, Simon.
I'm coming.
You know, I was just thinking
about that.
Last year, you played
in the squirt league, right?
- Yeah. So?
- This year you're a peewee.
So, what do they want you to do,
play soccer or urinate?
Anyway...
I was just thinking.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org