Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Who is she? - The recently
deceased Harriet Gould of Astoria.
No surviving relatives.
She's perfect.
- She even has a bun.
- That's her.
Dr. Marie Charles.
Oh, my God.
Every bull
begins a relationship...
with certain cards
up his sleeve... aces.
Tools of seduction
by which he lures a new cow.
One of the most
notorious examples...
is the current cow
sob story.
Allow me to deconstruct
the essential elements.
You're so easy to talk to,
not like my current cow.
This is key to understanding
the myth of male shyness,
for though you think
he is flattering you,
he is actually
flattering himself,
showing how open
and sensitive and honest he is.
I just try so hard and...
Well, I'm sure she doesn't
mean to be such a cold cow.
Just in case you're starting to think he's
a coldhearted, home-wrecking womanizer,
he'll throw this in just to prove
he's putting his current cow...
out to pasture for good reason,
and that he's actually tormented with
guilt at the thought of abandoning her.
What's that thing they always say
about the love of a good woman?
That, once offered,
it's guaranteed to come back...
and bite her in the ass.
- Enter case in point.
- Hey.
- Thought you were with what's her name.
- Didn't work out.
- You have a little saddle sore on that white horse of yours?
- Okay, so what happened?
- Just lost interest.
What do you mean,
you lost interest?
How exactly?
Christ, Jane, do we really have
to have another postmortem?
I'm just curious is all.
So you went to a movie,
then back to her place?
Then what?
So we're in the kitchen
getting a drink,
and suddenly, she starts
looking for food.
We had dinner right after the
movie, but... I don't know.
She was still hungry.
She's always hungry, it seems.
And that's bad,
Women who eat?
Okay, so you're in the kitchen,
she's hungry again, inexplicably,
then what?
So she takes out a pint
of Haagen-Dazs... a pint...
and just starts eating it
right out of the container,
and there was just something
about it that turned me off.
Was the refrigerator door open?
- Why? - Answer the
question. Open or closed?
It was open, I think.
Would it have made a
difference if it were shut?
Would that have made the act of a
nonfat woman eating ice cream...
a little less revolting to you?
What if she'd not had dinner?
What if she were legitimately hungry...
before she shoved her face
into a trough of Haagen-Dazs?
Would it have repulsed you less
if she used a dish?
- Good night, you psycho!
- Good night, neophiliac!
- Are you sitting down?
Oprah read the article
on her show today.
The audience went so crazy for it,
she called us personally,
begging for Dr. Charles
to appear as her guest.
- What?
- I told everyone in P.R. A different story.
She's vacationing in Hong Kong.
She's at a conference in Tangiers.
- Oh, this is bad.
- No, no, no. This is all good.
Okay? Trust me.
I've got it all under control.
This won't come
anywhere near you.
"And so, while the male
may often seem shy...
"with all his Uriah Heep hand-wringin'
and 'aw, shucks' toe-kickin',
"he's actually a narcissist...
"because this apparent shyness belies
the more deeply rooted feelings...
"of unworthiness
and fear of rejection.
"And this is what compels him
to constantly seek attention...
from new cow after new cow
ad nauseam, ad infinitum. "
This is such great stuff.
It obliterates any sentimentality
we might have...
about what
noble creatures men are.
This right here is what we've been
looking for. It's-It's provocative.
It's clever. It's got mass
appeal written all over it.
There's just one problem. Nobody
can seem to find this woman.
The Today Show's tried.
Oprah's tried.
- Yeah, and have you tried?
- Eddie?
- Uh, well, no.
- Well, get on it!
Do you realize what
we're talking about here?
- The ungettable get?
- Yes!
I don't care what it takes.
You find that Dr. Marie Charles...
and bring her here
to my studio.
Let me get this straight. Your best
friend works at M magazine...
and she has no idea
where this cow doctor is?
That's what she said.
I don't buy that.
Why are you holding out on me?
I'm not!
I told you she's working on it!
- Just give me her number.
- I'm not gonna give you her number.
- Why not?
- She's working on it!
- Besides, you'd never reach her. She's at Jivamukti.
- Huh?
- Yoga.
- Yoga what?
- Jivamukti.
- Jiv...
- Manhattan. Jivamukti.
- Eddie!
It's a yoga place.
Eddie, don't be a jerk!
Eddie, come on!
- This is so ridiculous.
- Ohhh!
Hey, hey, you have
to leave your shoes in here.
Liz?
Excuse me.
Jerk, she is my best friend.
I would certainly know if...
- Jane?
Stay!
- Bring your leg up higher.
- Excuse me, sir, you're gonna have to leave.
Gee. Sorry. I know.
I'm just looking for a friend.
Oh.
- Sorry. You okay?
- Eddie.
How you doin', Becca?
I'm good.
What are you
doing here?
I, uh... I-I don't know.
Come, class. Let's forget
about this disturbance.
It's okay. Everyone,
let's come on up.
Get back to your spaces
and let's prepare for lion pose.
Hey, inhale. Exhale.
Open your mouth.
Stick out your tongue.
That was Rebecca?
Eddie, talk to me.
There's nothing
to talk about.
- Hi, Liz.
- I cannot believe it.
- Hey, Janey!
- Hi! Hi, guys!
Eddie, this is my sister Alice
and my brother-in-law Stephen.
- You're... Eddie.
- Yeah. Hey.
- Are you two taking yoga class together?
- No.
- We were just... I... It-It's stupid.
- No, no, it's not stupid.
- We don't think it's stupid.
- No. We just started the pregnancy class.
- Oh, yeah. Congratulations.
- Thanks. She's a great breather.
- Listen, I gotta go.
- Hey, it was really nice to meet
you, Eddie. - Bye-bye.
Eddie preferred
to leave things unsaid...
and went back to grazing
in greener pastures.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, everyone.
- I'm getting out of here.
- Okay.
- Uh, two champagnes, please.
- Yes, sir.
Shouldn't that be a champagne
and a Shirley Temple?
- Sorry.
- No, you're not.
- So where'd you meet her?
- She's Emily's roommate.
Emily that I made
coffee for last Sunday?
Uh-huh.
Isn't that complicated?
It's never complicated, Jane.
Thank you.
Evening, sir.
What can I get you?
- Scotch, please.
- Yes, sir.
Did you hear Diane's
joke about the reindeer?
Funny!
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
I miss you, Jane.
Am I... Am I supposed
to walk away now?
No.
Can we get away from this?
Can we do something?
Get together for lunch,
dinner, Friday night.
Friday is New Year's Eve.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
You probably have
some, uh, plans.
- Don't you?
- Yeah.
Yes, I do.
I have...
No.
I have none.
Could I call you?
Would that be okay?
Yeah.
Merry Christmas, Jane.
- Yee-haaaw!
Well, you can't stop now.
We'll do it together.
You're syndicated
in over 300 newspapers.
Talk radio is having
a field day with it.
Clearly the world
is one giant used-cow lot.
- Look, I just want to think about it, okay?
- What's there to think about?
You don't want to be
a post-feminist icon?
Come on. Let's get something great to
wear for Julian’s New Year's Eve party.
I meant to tell you that...
I kind of made other plans.
I mean, it's nothing major.
It's not a big...
- Well...
- What are you talking about?
- Ray asked me out.
- Ray?
As in Ray Brown?
As in devil incarnate?
No! No, I forbid it!
L- I-I thought you
were over this.
I think I'm having
second thoughts.
Oh, so now... Dr. Charles
is having them too.
- Done yet?
- You got a hot date?
- No, I just have to pee.
- Be my guest.
- What's this, party Viagra?
- Huh?
No, it's nicotine gum.
- When did you quit?
- Oh, since Daphne told me she wanted to marry a smoker.
Here.
Thank you.
Why don't you put on a dress
and come out with me tonight?
Why, so I can
trail after your harem?
- I'm flying solo. I thought I'd keep my options open.
-
Yeah?
Although
that may be for me.
- Hello.
- You're home.
Does this mean you've
come to your senses?
No, and I only have
an hour to get ready.
So quit worrying about me.
Go out. Have a good time.
I'm going to wear that red lipstick
you gave, and I'll call you tomorrow.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
Why are you doing this
to yourself?
- Doing what?
- Ray.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Okay.
- Well, if you change your mind, this is where I'll be.
- Oh, thanks.
I think I'll...
jump into my pj's,
probably
watch a little TV...
- go to bed early...
- Happy New Year.
- Same to you!
Now, back to our special New
Year's Eve coverage with Hugh Downs.
To recap, it was
less than 48 hours ago...
that Ray Brown called
to confirm his plans...
to take Jane Goodale out
this evening,
a clear indication
that he was, indeed,
regretting his decision
to terminate their involvement.
So the question remains,
why hasn't he shown up yet?
By all accounts, it would appear
that Mr. Brown is sticking firmly...
to his September sanctions.
Nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four,
three, two, one!
Happy New Year!
Jane!
Whoo!
Ahh...
Ohh...
Jane!
Happy New Year!
- Jane?
- Don't even bother.
- L-I need to talk to you.
- Shh...
Excuse me. Why didn't you...
Why didn't you return my calls?
You mean the calls that came
after the call you didn't make?
L...
This is not true.
It's so true.
Will you stop
for just a moment?
- Hey, Jane.
- Listen, I know it was inexcus...
- Good morning!
- Hi, Jane. Ray.
- There's a reason I didn't showup that night.
- I'm sure there is.
And you know what?
I couldn't possibly care less.
So let's forget about it.
Okay!
I don't suppose you're
interested in hearing me out.
You know what, Ray?
The truth is...
Hi!
You did me a favor.
Any delusions I may have still
had about you, they're gone now.
It was a gift.
You released me.
- For the first time in months, I feel great.
-
- Staff meeting in my office in two minutes.
- Okay, be right there.
Uh, what's wrong?
Diane's wearing your shirt.
The shirt I bought you
on the sidewalk.
So, does that mean
that the, uh...
- the two of you are...
- Seeing each other again.
- Yes. That's what I've been trying to explain.
- Wait. Stop.
Did you say, "Again"?
I should have told you
a long time ago,
but Diane insisted
on keeping it quiet.
- We got back together right
before New Year's and...  - Oh...
and we went away for a couple of days, and
it was terrible of me to not call, but I...
Ray, I've got
Tony Robbins on line three!
- Ohh! Go on.
- I'm really sorry, Jane.
Hey, what is it?
- "D... " She's "D."
- I'm not following.
Di... Di... "D."
Diane is "D."
Yes. "D" is for Diane.
"E" is for Eddie.
Ray's "D."
She's the one!
I mean, she was... She
is the one. I mean, she...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa.
Just breathe. Breathe, Jane. Breathe.
Now, let me get this straight.
Ray and Diane are together?
- Back together. Together
again. - All right. I get it.
- Let it go. Ray and Diane?
- Yeah!
Okay. Shh...
It doesn't matter.
That chapter's over, remember?
Now we got to go in there,
so pull it together.
Do you hear me?
Don't cry.
Don't cry, please. You're gonna be fine.
- Okay.
- We're gonna go in there.
- Good. You all right?
- Okay.
Jane, where are we
for next week?
Uh, we're-we're all set with
Gerard Depardieu. Right, Jane?
Oh, good.
New movie?
Am-Amazing.
Amazing.
I- I actually, uh...
I saw it. It's, uh...
about a man whose whole
marriage falls apart and...
I mean, it's brutal,
actually. I mean...
You know, they show
the whole love story first.
You see that this woman means...
everything to this-this man.
In fact, there's this-this...
this one scene...
where he actually sits
in just a... a dark... uhh...
It's very touching. He's sits
in a dark room, and he just...
You just start to see
the-the tears and stuff.
I mean, the man is completely, you
know, broken, and you feel it.
You really feel it, and it's
devastating. It's a devastating...
Is this a joke?
N- No.
What do you mean?
I mean...
I mean, is this a joke?
- No, I saw it two nights ago.
- What's so funny, Jane?
- Oh, can you believe this guy?
- I know, I...
So sensitive... So...
So devastated when it comes to
some chubby French guy, but, oh!
Stomp on somebody's heart in real life,
and where's his sorry-ass pity then, huh?
Nowhere! Why?
Because he doesn't get it!
He never gets it!
Someone please
explain it to me.
Because I don't know
what you are talking about!
- Evelyn, is she free?
- Yeah. She is.
Thanks.
I'm sorry, Diane. I... I don't
know where that came from.
Well, I do. I know
exactly where it came from.
You do?
Some guy crushed you
under his boot heel,
and you lashed out
at poor Ray as being...
representative of the prick
that did that to you.
- I'm right, aren't I?
- More or less.
Well, you can't do it, Jane.
- I don't care how much it hurts.
- I know.
No, you don't know.
Now, sit down and listen to me.
I'm gonna let you in
on a little secret.
About six months ago,
my boyfriend tried to leave me.
Well, he did.
He left.
And I was devastated. I was
destroyed. Did you see it?
- No. I-I-I didn't. No.
- Right.
Do you know why?
Because if I fall apart,
everything around me
falls apart...
everything that I have worked
my entire life for.
- Do you love him?
- Wh-Who?
- Him. The guy.
- I don't know.
Of course you do.  Now, have
you talked to him lately?
No. No. Not ex...
Not exactly talked.
Do it. Do it.
Talk to him.
I used to feel that if I
kept my heart to myself,
If I never let him know how much I needed
him, that he would never leave me.
Well, guess what?
He did.
And I lived in a private,
pathetic puddle...
until I couldn't
stand it anymore,
And so you know what I did?
I showed up at his doorstep...
with two corned beef sandwiches
on rye, lightly toasted,
and I told him that
I was lost without him.
You said that?
Pretty progressive, huh?
And I'm happy. Go figure.
I never thought
I'd be happy.
And you believe her?
This is true love?
This is what we all should be looking for?
That is the most tragic thing
I've ever heard.
We're talking about a woman whose boyfriend
was screwing you in order to get away from her.
And she's the authority
on romance?
The only reason she believes
that crap is because she has to.
She's an old cow.
Truth is all we need to do
is adjust our radar a bit.
You know, learn to be attracted to
men we're simply not attracted to.
Whoa. Hang on.
What are you talking about?
Well, for example, normally...
I might be attracted
to a guy like you.
But thanks to Dr. Charles, I've learned
to control my passion for testosterone,
and now I can proudly say...
that I no longer find you
in the least bit desirable.
Oh, gee.
That's swell.
I need a drink.
Does she have any
idea that she's completely insane?
No. She's right. Diane is an old
cow. He cannot go back to her.
Okay, that's it.
Jane, these are people,
not cows!
Hello.
I should have known
you would take his side.
This isn't about sides, Jane.
It's about dealing with reality.
- And you need to get a grip.
- Oh, that's rich...
coming from an emotional moron who's
whoring his way through Manhattan,
using women
like A.T.M. Machines.
Oh, that's great.
I get dumped, sleep around, and I'm a moron.
You, you get dumped
and become the disciple...
of some crone-slash-quack
behavioral scientist...
who can't tell the difference between
quadrupeds and bipeds, and you're normal.
- She is not a crone. And she is not a quack!
- How do you know?
Who gives a shit?
You know, while you were out there buying
these theories about the horrors of men...
And why guys like Ray won't ever come back,
deep down inside
you're hoping he would.
Men are evil. Men are scum.  But please,
Ray, won't you make a liar out of me?
Well, you got
what you asked for, Jane.
He did go back. He just
did it with the wrong girl!
It's over! Over.
- Why can't you just let it go?
- Because.
- Because why?
- Because I can't.
- Why?
- Because I was happy.
Because if this...
theory is wrong,
men don't leave all women,
Eddie, they leave me.
I know what
it does to you. I know.
Maybe that's why
we hold on as hard as we do.
We just can't believe that such a
miracle can ever happen to us twice.
And...
But it can.
Someday you'll
find it again.
- I promise you.
- Look at me.
- A mess.
- I'm looking at you.
And you're beautiful.
Hey, you are beautiful.
You're intelligent... and real.
And Ray is not the last man
you're ever gonna love.
I promise you he's not.
Shh. Shh...
Oh, my God.
Oh...
Mmm...
Hmm...
Hi.
Uh... listen.
- L...
- No, no, no.
No. No.
No, you're not going
to analyze this one, Jane.
- I'm not?
- No. No.
You're so hell-bent on making sure things fit,
you miss out on all the fun when they don't.
- Eh? Oh...
- Well, I...
No? Right now you're trying
to rationalize last night.
Yeah? Worrying about
what might have happened.
Me, I'm just getting a kick
out of the fact that I, uh,
spent an entire night
with you in my arms,
and I didn't even cop a feel.
Well...
maybe one.
- Whew!
- What?
Well, I'm relieved.
I mean,
for a second there, I...
I thought maybe you
thought last night was, um...
You know, or that you would...
think...
That would've really blown your
Dr. Charles out of the water, huh?
Temporarily maybe, but you would
have shown your spots eventually.
- My spots.
- Oh, come on, Eddie.
Men never fail to do
what's in their nature to do.
And what is that, Jane?
Disappoint you?
Abandon you?
Hmm?
What's really behind
these theories, huh?
What are you hiding?
Nothing.
Sorry. What you see
is what you get.
Is it?
You know, this is not about my
nature, Jane. This is about yours.
- Hello.
- Janey?
Listen, Stephen.
Can I call y'all back?
Your sister's in the hospital.
We lost the baby, kiddo.
Hey, Janey.
Did you see Stephen?
I saw him in the hallway...
- Getting water.
- Getting ice.
Good luck.
God love him.
They break so easily,
don't they?
Last weekend,
he woke up in a panic.
He said that he had to go
shopping for the baby.
You know how anal he is. I thought
he was gonna come back with...
thermometers and baby blankets
and safety gates.
When he walked in the door,
all he had was this little, tiny bag...
and inside was this...
this perfect little
baseball mitt.
He got it in his head that
it was going to be a boy.
Janey.
Okay, I've got ice.
I've got blankets.
I've got magazines.
Look at my wife.
Have you ever seen
anyone more beautiful?
You're nuts.
Diane, it's Jane.
I found Dr. Charles,
Okay, is everybody ready
to have a good time?
Now, come on.
You're going to have to do a lot better than that.
Okay, let me explain how everything
on the show's gonna work.
- It's a really informal show...
- Yo, Ray! Do we have her on the line yet?
Two minutes. The magazine's
putting her through.
- All right!
- Two minutes.
- Diane, two minutes.
- So, Diane's going to come out.
The first guest is going to come.
We have about a 15-minute segment.
Our first interview is gonna be
on the telephone, okay?
- Dr. Marie Charles.
I'm going to ask you one more time.
Are you 100% sure you want to do this?
I'm sure. I'm sorry
to put you in this position.
Don't worry about me.
I just want to make sure you haven't lost your mind.
- Maybe I have.  -
Here she is, Ray.
- Dr. Charles.
Welcome. Rarely have I
had the honor to host...
such a distinguished
and extraordinary guest.
Today, Dr. Marie Charles
speaks out for the first time...
since the publication
of her searing article...
Network says we've already
had 20,000 hits on the web site.
- Holy cow.
The reclusive Dr. Charles...
has agreed to an exclusive,
live telephone interview.
And I consider it
a rare gift...
from someone whose work has meant
a tremendous amount in my life,
- as I'm sure yours.
- Dr. Marie Charles
Hello, Dr. Charles.
Are you there?
Can you hear me?
- I'm getting nothing.
- Where the hell is she? Where's the feed?
- Excuse me.
We seem to be having
some technical difficulties.
If you'll just bear with us,
I'm sure we'll get it repaired.
Tell them to patch it through
on the other line.
- We can't. We only have one dedicated line.
- Shit!
Okay, take us to commercial.
Uh, she's here.
She wants to go on.
Ho-Hold that.
Hold that. Hold that.
- She's here.
- Well, ladies and gentlemen,
it seems that the reason we've
been unable to get through...
to Dr. Charles
telephonically...
is because at this moment
she is right here in our studio,
having decided to do
the interview in person after all.
- Holy shit.
- So let's not waste any more time.
Join me in welcoming
Dr. Marie Charles!
- Makeup?
- Stop. Stop.
Show yourself, Dr. Charles.
Wake up!
Jane, what's going on?
Where's Dr. Charles?
- There is no Dr. Charles.
There never was.
- I invented her, Diane.
- You...
- I invented her because...
I had something to say,
and... somehow...
I thought if...  if-if-if it were
coming from a 65-year-old Ph. D.,
that you would
see it the way I had...
as a truth, as a legitimate,
scientific truth.
But it isn't.
It's completely ridiculous.
And...
I lied to you all,
and I lied to myself.
Because
the real truth is that...
I was heartbroken...
and lost.
You know, and I just wanted
to understand it somehow.
I wanted it to be...
about them.
So everything I thought I had figured
out was completely upside-down.
I thought this bull had gone on
to another new cow,
when, in fact, she was an old cow
who had become a new cow again.
I mean, what was
I talking about?
I was comparing
men to animals,
- which... okay, let's face it... sometimes they are.
-
But sometimes they are not.
Sometimes
you open the barn door,
or the hospital room door...
or the bedroom door and...
you find the real thing.
You find a guy who...
can sit with you when you
are at your absolute worst,
when you are knee-deep in Kleenex, and
your face looks like a punching bag,
and you are a complete
and total mess.
And he...
can still look at you
and tell you...
that Ray is not the last man
you're ever going to love.
- Eddie! Oh, my God.
Hey, are you all right?
All right.
There you go. Late edition.
Eddie!
- Oh, Eddie!
- Eddie! Eddie!
Stop. Stop.
Whew.
So, what you see
is what you get, huh?
Minus a few gray hairs
and a Ph. D., yeah.
I'm really sorry, Eddie.
You should have told me.
I should have told you
a lot of things.
You were right.
It was about my nature.
Out of all the things
you said to me that night,
what scared me
the most is...
that I would find it again.
Because I have.
Would you please
say something?
No.
So you're saying?
What do we got to lose?
- Everything?
- Exactly.
Ripped by:
SkyFury
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org