Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
The day after the one
nuclear disaster in Texas,
... United States were
in a very delicate situation.
Third Guerra
World cup had begun.
The conflicts in the Middle East
that you began they implanted...
... new access restrictions
to the petroleum for United States.
The alternative sources of fuel you
they transformed into a very lucrative business.
America faced the terrorist threat
and in
the forests didn't face the same enemy.
EXPANSIBLE PATRIOTIC ACTION
Those were increased
military points of checkup.
To travel to other states
it was required to be civic.
The prisons increased.
The presidential elections of the 2008
they would opt for the vote of a state.
The Republic dedicated everything in
to assure the state of California.
Not it happened this way from 1988.
June of 2008 Boxer 27
Santeros a significant character...
... in Republican Party
he/she disappeared without leaving rake.
Two days later discovered it in the one
desert of Nevada with the erased memory.
The government made the possible thing
to take it out of California,
but the circumstances of their return
to Southland, they are still a mystery.
One of our soldiers
it was wounded yesterday in Iraq.
Because of a thrown granda
for another member of their unit.
The revelation was given to Jesús
Christ, for everything that made.
What was made belonged
to the past, and it was high...
for the angels in a sacred trip. As
testimony of God and of Jesus Christ...
And all that saw and all him
that this writing will remain,
... this way for all those that
they believe, for the whole time.
My name is Paulie Aveline...
... and I am a veteran one
of the war in Iraq.
I will count them the history of Boxer Santeros
in their trip for the not taken highway.
This is the way in
that the world ends.
Not with one winter, the time changed.
The search of Boxer continues Santeros,
... their wife Madeleine Frost daughter
of Kennedy's former vice-president...
Bobby Frost has not made comments.
The government to red on code for the visas
interstate for the matter of possible terrorists...
this weekend and the freeway of Those
Ángel will be closed indefinitely.
The government prepares measures of
security for the festejos...
... of the 4 of Julio since are completed
three years of the nuclear attack.
HISTORIES DE SOUTHLAND
The government decided that it could not take
to end a war against the terrorism...
until the space not
federal low control was
USIDent was the I celebrate controller
of Republican Party.
Welcome to USIDent.
A colossal form of protection
false to the patriotic actions.
I took a trip less to see this
and you have marked the difference.
They know, Bobby and me
we are so proud.
That we can develar the first
institution of IDent here Southland.
She said it. And they will have more!
Boxer Santero came out of the one
desert with amnesia.
Alone with god it is their skin.
Their name was Kristy
Kopawski and together they wrote,
... a libretto that predicted
our future destruction.
Does it care? The power.
The machines of war you
they were without fuel.
And there was not alternative...
Until one day in that it arrived
a scientist with the cure.
He would create one giant it schemes
that it was in the ocean...
... and it generated a liquid
call Flows Karma.
and a great net that toward
to move big you scheme,
... you scheme that he/she never went to
to be stuffed with fuel.
It invented something to make this
does it scheme generating perpetual?
The ocean is one it schemes
generating perpetual.
Flow Karma it is a simulation
of the workers that come here.
While waves exist
, it will exist you Flow Karma.
Quantum Telexportación.
Explain the mechanism
it is all that I ask.
Flow Karma it works with movement
quántico the particles move and.
The atomic program that of the administration
of the civil defense it was seen by June Callway.
Taenia that to see the program
atomic, not alone as reporter,
... but as representative of those
men and American women.
I am Kristy, Kristy Now, and I am
here in Malibú today with my invited ones.
Unite to us to discuss on those
problems that affect to the society of nowadays.
Problems like the abortion,
terrorism, crime,
... poverty, quantum telecuantismo,
I already made my decisions
now you take his.
... I believe that it is hour that
let us look at ourselves in a mirror.
Once you already make it
you cannot stop to make it.
That should be condemned,
it is totally antiético.
You believe that to throw you to the floor and ching...
Good...  the violence is not anything good.
They know that, I like that me hard chingue.
The violence is a problem
that it affects the society nowadays,
that it is to reason for the
that I am this way, I am anal.
Not wise that were this way.
All those that know something of
history knows that the changes,
... social they are not possible
without the feminine wickedness.
It continues making fun of my profession.
But all well inside want
to be a star of the pron.
Seriously?
Your bisexual nature
that he/she lives in negation.
Everything for a heap of idiots that,
... 15 disembarked in the century and
they undid that the sex was embarrassing.
The only thing good that made it was
to give the freedom to the Indians.
Have you been lying me?
You have to trust my,
I am here to protect you.
Of the one who?
People there out wants to destroy you.
I remember that that day kristy taenia a lunch
with a cinema directress Cindy Pendzeki.
When I made my first six
movies were single Kristy...
but then, to be distinguished of the other ones
Kristys that are in this business put on Now.
Wow.
Good, everything rotates around
what happens now. in the 2008.
Non tomorrow, neither next week.
If you want to go to bed
with me, you can make it now"
Wow, that it is the name of
your program of TV, Now?"
It is a reality show
of debate and discussion.
Jewels, government, lines of perfumes...
... good it is a very ambitious business.
Can you keep a secret?
Of course.
I am catching to a
very important man.
Wow
The search of Boxer
Santeros was organized,
And their mother-in-law directed it,
the wife of the one
vice-president Bobby Frost.
May Frost.
Antigua graduation queen,
and directress of NSA.
May Frost, please confirm.
Identified, Welcome Sra Frost.
Thank you
the things are very jodidas.
Does he/she want to abandon?
No.
We know that Bóxer crossed
the frontier with California.
Not we have found neither a print.
We know that somebody is hiding it.
That devils toward in Nevada?
We know that it was kidnapped
of a Hotel in San Pedro.
Somebody stole the information,
we know that it crossed the frontier,
... he/she comes toward the computer for
to show him/her what we have up to now.
these videos were
taken by the kidnapper.
Is that Boxer?
If
The last time that was seen was.
If.
Is this fume?
If
Somehow a began
fire, had somebody inside.
What?
If, he/she was a
cadaver almost in ashy.
- Did they already identify the cadaver?
- Not that it is known.
Venice Beach was the headquarters of
that that you toward undercover.
An entire market of strange things.
here we go, I joust on time.
This is Fortunio Belducci...
their better new friend.
Trafficker of drugs, pretty, now
he/she walks after some mysterious project,
It has been with Fortunio in
Manhattan Beach the whole week.
Kristy me to engaged a marriage
I murder, and maybe some murderous elections.
Boxer has not spoken with its wife in one
week, her this in the military mapamenteto.
You doesn't imagine where the one has been.
The stupid senator's family
and of their dog Grandma handcuffs May.
People in Washington
already this commenting.
It is the last news of the century.
It hurts that it is in time of elections.
Anything that a magic ball, a star
pron and a tattoo cannot fix.
Revelation 6.8: Admire
a white horse
and the one will be sat down in
the, their name will be Death.
All the violence of the one
world this in this car. If
Does he/she hear, is that a bazuka?
No that what you really want is?
I need bullets of salvo of 9 mm.
That more needs besides the 9 mm?
It is everything.
here this your 9 mm and the bullets.
That shit this is?
Not you do accept personal checks?
No, I don't accept checks.
veto of my truck, crazy dog.
Dilo again, dilo again.
That what you said was?
I don't hear you, dilo, dilo prostitute son!
Imbecile!
I want to talk about the narcotic
that it is injected in the neck...
... these they are human beings
You this experiencing with soldiers,
it is a
fact that one knows and nobody says anything in this respect.
They call it Rum Taverner,
and it was one of their activists in a
I play political dangerous of extortion.
Roland, could you hurry sky?
My reflection takes a long time.
That they told him/her?
The head was hit in the desert and it returned with amnes
These things seem real.
Ronald? They said that they would vibrate.
They drugged you and they kidnapped two
official, that is against the law affection.
If he/she comes here we will make it together.
he/she needs to be calmed.
The calm helps to face the fears.
Promise me that they won't be harmed.
We promise it.
Neo had taken a hostage
that he/she would help them to expose
all the wrongs of USIDent.
Their mission was to spend
for their twin brother.
but their heart was
full with scorn.
- Official Rum Taerner.
- Hello, as these?
When you returned of the desert?
Non memory exactly.
That doesn't care, your these well.
And your you need somebody that
play police's part.
If exactly.
Him but important it is that you
it develops in the near future.
Ok. The scientists are saying that
the one
future will be worse of that than it had been predicted.
Him but important, I play the part of a
police of The Ángel that is not what seems.
It is a paranoiac esquizofrénico.
With a supernatural don, you see the death.
And it feels a change.
The world this arriving to their end
and the one is the only one that
he/she can see the truth.
Which the truth is?
My character realizes that those
crimes in the world are to cause...
of the deceleration of the Earth.
The earth stops to a speed of
.00000006
miles per hour every day...
... what develops
chemical imbalance,
... in the human causing brain
of the criminal behavior.
As he/she is solved the problem
of global deceleration?
Oh, the he/she is not able to him
to solve, single God can.
But New York Cheats
he/she said that God was dead.
So at the end, they die a
shooting in downtown...
while I whisper my theory to Dr. Muriel
Fox the specialist oceanólogo in disasters.
Astrophysicist!
Oceanálogo specialist in disasters!
My character's name
it is Jerry Cocaine.
Let us prove.
Roland that comes you and the
do mention when you kill a man?
Crossing the streets without humanity,
it is an elimination process
that he/she puts to think.
The person that this inside
he/she is the true suspect.
Or we all are innocent
and we wait to be caught
and thrown to the arms of the wolves.
I believe that we all are civic.
we speak the same language,
Not you believe that the emotions
are they the cause of the crimes?
It depends of like respond to
a state of certain humor.
Good, there is a cause.
I know it, tell me I know honest.
To be honest those
black they are the cause.
The black ones? If
Each word.
These joking? No, I am not joking.
Alone I am you jodiendo.
It is a good joke.
If, he/she said black.
Not I am sure, maybe
let us should erase this.
Ask him/her on their wife.
Then that he/she thinks your
does it handcuff of your new girlfriend?
My wife? If
She had to swallow you that left it
for a star pron. Not I am married.
He/she could swear that you were married
with the senator's daughter Bobby Frost.
good but not. And not
I have idea of who is.
For that make all those questions,
alone I want to speak of my movie.
Let us speak of your movie.
That it really tries?
Among all the things
he/she hides a secret.
A young couple leaves the one
hospital with their he/she drinks newly born.
While it lapses one week the one
he/she drinks and the one drinks he/she begins to get complicated.
Maybe the one drinks he/she has a cold.
No, it is a he/she drinks very special.
This drinks it processes the energy
in a different way.
The Revelation 11 speak of of
two men that appeared in...
... Jerusalem to speak Preposition
of the humanity's sins.
Finally they die because of
those tormenting prophecies.
Not you can doubt, the type is a shit.
That it happens if this writing in the Bible
or if not this writing in any place.
Not this writing in the Bible
but it is the law of the nature.
All the dirts of the world
even that of the animals.
And they like it, you want it
to make, do they have voice?
If I believe that they like.
My answer is not.
We will never agree
, we should stop to discuss.
We should make many things
and we should leave of here.
Look who arrived.
You arrive late.
the shit is big.
Did they already see to the type of USIDent?
If of course.
Boy, when this he/she wakes up, him
you inject with that that this there inside.
Neo workers recruited this boy
of USIDent to work hidden.
Miss, can it return me my coat?
Thank you
But their misfortune was to trust
in their colleague, Starla Vann Loved.
The senator Bobby Frost beginning
their campaign to collect funds,
Also, the campaign will be good to tranquilize
to the protectors of the environment,
... that they oppose you to the new fuel
for their environmental repercussion.
... in order of increasing the votes that
they are made with the print dactilar...
for the next elections.
Sacred God!
the information to those
adolescents are not a crime.
Mr., I believe that it is worse.
How devils can it be worse?
This arrived inside a box with a
sender not identified call: DPro2
good we discover who are.
Who are and that they want?
We are DPro2, the dog this of
turn and he/she has Boxer Santeros,
... engraving in positions
compromising.
A million dollars cash
and revoke the proposal 69.
Srta. DPro is the senator Bobby Frost,
I watched their movie and I believe that it is a garbage.
Therefore we won't negotiate
with terrorists and,
... if he/she believes that it will take money out of this him
I will say that he lacks a lot to still travel.
Ok that doesn't go a long way the one
panic, we will pass to the plan B.
Which the plan is B? Not me
you said there was a plan B.
Well, not and without offending we are trying
of stopping the result of this election.
Proposal 69, for Kristy that
number taenia a single meaning.
For all the other ones that number was a mean
to stop the oppressive power of USIDent.
My parents didn't stop to pay taxes,
we will never get rid of this terror, NOT vote.
I believe that the conference of
it presses had concluded, thank you.
Always the rich idiots.
They are a pile of imbeciles that nobody
he/she chose.
They are a handful of hollow heads.
Don't tell me what I should
to make with my body ok?
I have a question
for the supreme court,
... what it happens when a woman has sex
in a flight of London to The Ángel?
The airplane comes out in the morning of
London then crosses the Meridian,
... and it arrives the morning
before the elections.
The soldiers arrested to
a group of Marxist neo
The plan B was in he/she practices,
a
long shot of destroying USIDent.
Inject me again he/she drinks.
Not I see for that this is
necessary...  it was not part of the plan.
I will tell it to you again, Deon and
I am icons of the culture,
If I already see, reciting poetry
they renovated the idea of the American dream.
If, at least we are not
comedians of second.
Alone because it is high not
he/she means that it is amusing.
I will forget what dog said,
sometimes a dream one can,
Already leave that! When we will be clever?
,they will be here in one hour.
That of the teeth was a great idea.
Thank You Saura.
There is a punetera barricade, now
same east place is a madness.
No, I told you that him
I attempted with the countersign,
... good you already heard me they are 15
minutes to destroy the barricade.
That you joda! And do you know what?
Nany Mae Frost can die.
Kill him.
Salt of there!
No
He/she hears it I won't make, and it won't leave.
Eliminate it
Awake, awake, let us go!
Who are? I don't know it
Take it to you.
He doesn't know who is.
Promise me that you will find it! I promise it
Ok, veto for the window.
I had a crazy dream.
Count me
I wake up and in a tank of
garbage and the walls are of sand...
... while I walk slowly
toward a source of light...
... and to see somebody that
he/she was waiting for me. Who?
Your.
At some time you have felt that there is as
1000 people contained inside you?
Sometimes.
But your memory maintains them meetings.
Evita that all those
people fight to each other.
Maybe in the bottom it is all it that
we have left it,
the gospel of the memory.
Do you excuse me one second?
If
The Small world of the books
He/she Is the Doctor Inga Baam West
Charmed
He is a very good specimen
Divine
What happens now from now on
it will be your responsibility.
We read your terror work The Power."
As they got it?
Very afraid Sr shines. Santeros.
It is exactly as you imagine.
This is the way in that it is the world.
Without a bank.
These making the
surveillance of the bathrooms.
LAX
Partner is worried for
Starla takes making...
... the surveillance of those
bathrooms already a time ago.
Starla had lowered a copy of the movie
of Santeros from the place Web of Kristy.
So obsession took it to one
spiritual transformation.
She assumed the paper of Dra. Muriel
Fox
and alone she could solve the mystery.
Does official Taverner, copy me?
Ahead.
Possible fight tames in
14000 Lonleyplace, does it copy me?
Received.
Will we catch a suspect?
so seems
Transform, he/she breathes.
He/she dreams
Jodete! If your also!
I caught it very rich. Did you like it?
I loved it! Your prostitute!
Also me chingué yesterday!
Your shit prostitute.
Don't aim me with the finger. I will kill you!
If you kill me I call to the police!
As, as?
You will be dead!
I know people!
They are some professionals!
Shhhh!
I hate you!
I also hate you!
Not you can be my wife!
Not I want a damned one
I engage he/she likes to suckle penises!
Oh, looks, another official of the law.
Holitas!
That you make outside of your jurisdiction?
Not I believe that there are jurisdictions!
We all are with all.
Boxer Santeros? Good afternoon official.
I am making investigations
for my movie.
I find that you will need support.
I believe that I can manage this.
No, I believe that you needed
some support.
Imbecile idiot! Oh God!
Not you can if to have sex! What?
Jódete! Not I can believe
that I married you!
That carajo passes them! Is that Roland?
He/she listens this pig: The Fascists not
they will dominate me, the Revolution will be made,
... of the their subjective elections
my vagina won't depend.
That is an original poem of Dream.
oh shit!
The game finished. My tears run.
That sounded high and I miss.
They were inoffensive.
This is now my matter,
this way
that you release yourself of here Santeros.
Not these here really. Who I am?
Not it is your problem,
now release you of here.
It was double an inspiring idea, a
murder made by a policeman...
... of range recorded in tape by one
movie star with a political record.
But nobody could advance the stormy one
arrival of official Bart Bookman.
Shit!
Hello Jerry Cocaine Is?
If, Dr speaks to him/her. Muriel Fox, I have decoded
the information of all the generators.
A corrosion in the layer has produced a
desbalance in the space of continuous time.
My resurrection? It was in the desert
,You are as me and there is more.
But I cannot speak here
They are listening.
Record this number,
310-691-6496.
Treer Saltair of the one
2008 will arrive soon.
Thank you, it is a great honor and a
I privilege to be here, thank you...
What I have just seen was
two cars having sex?
Certainly.
That was unpleasant.
It is that European way
of seeing the things. Ohh.
Already never more we will bury
the spirit of the nets,
Never but no idiotic neo will deny
the mejestuocidad of our ocean.
Hello Jerry Cocaine speaks to Him/her.
What? Jerry Cocaine speaks to him/her.
Boxer? Who speaks?
Where you are?
I Am in Venice
Beach, I don't know in that leaves.
Boxer, listens you go to Low Tavern,
this the end of the channel of Venice,
... in Boulevard
Washington, is a restaurant.
Stay there until the one
senator will look for you.
You go to Low Tavern in
the channel of Venice, quick.
We have it.
Shit!
It is an urgent matter
with respect to Boxer Santeros.
That you mean with which not
this available one? Not it is true!
You tell Vaughn Smallhouse
that he/she doesn't enter with DPro2.!
As carajo they want
that he/she sends him/her an I chant,
... to a star of but if not
I can talk with the one on the phone!
Allow me to tell you something Terry, when the
shit has fans all they smell equally.
It is true!
Not you what you/they have made but they have me
that to promise that he won't come out wounded.
Not it is person's type
that they think that it is.
Sr. Santeros!
That good, they have the head of the one
neomarxista Tony Brown and their girlfriend,
... that it was made call Dream,
name real: Veronica Thousands.
Deon and Dream are dead.
He are not, they were pretenders.
They were not it! If!
We made two pretenders.
It seemed that they were dead!
If, that is what you leave! That he/she spends?
You have been lying me
the whole time Saura!
You these returning paranoiac Rum.
I am listening to boys.
I believe that I want to leave home because
I don't want to be wrapped in this.
Ok, Ben vetoes good luck.
If it stops
you also, keep the skates.
Consider them a gift. Take care.
Release you of here.
Revelation 22: So that never but it is
darkness again doesn't have little light...
... because the light of God
it will be shining on them.
They will reign for always.
Two residents of Venice
they were discovered dead today,
... after having had one
look domestic dispute.
Verónica Thousands an artist
that you toward calling,
The well-known couple as John
and Joko of Venice underground...
Excuse Mister, he/she has a
cellular that can use?
Local call? If.
Thank you
Official Roland Taverner?
The revelations 12 and 13 count
the history of a pregnant woman,
... a dragon and two beasts.
Boxer Santeros has arrived.
They are the antichrist's mascots.
That...  do you have amnesia?
Your you are my wife!
God!
Oh...  I am so happy
that you are alive!
Did you get the tape?
When you will pay me?
Soon he/she drinks.
I am cheap but I don't leave. I already see.
They will pay us a lot of money.
To destroy it.
These very jodida without that movie.
Look for it and bring it to me right now.
We think that a group
Marxist neo kidnapped you.
Cockroaches!
Care with what says Mister.
If
Ms. Kristy had arrived Mister.
Not I can wait to know it.
Sexual games who
does carajo make this shit?
He/she hears, she has just taken out
their pop own album.
This not this well, mantén the one
heart and the opened mind.
Her this developing their own one
reality show, their line of clothes,
... perfume and their own one
energizing drink...
... that I proved and he/she knows very well.
Thank you.
Can I see the sexual games?
No, you don't see that one has put on
trap?
Were they made some video together?
If
If there is one.
Ok, we have to give him/her to
this prostitute what she wants.
That you find a million dollars
and we accept the proposition 69.
Is your also of DPro2?
Not I am in that movie.
Dad, we have to give him/her what she wants
to have that DVD and it will be closed case.
This is extortion affection.
A million dollars are a lot of money and
we don't negotiate with terrorists.
Sexual games 2! If this comes out to
the light the elections ended.
It is a year of elections Bob...
It is true Bob we should pay
although DPro 2 can be silenced.
Remove him/her their bank bill we have
agreement prenupcial, and you know that... ?
Perhaps be good moment to tell you
that I am pregnant of your son!
This pregnant one? If you will be grandfather.
Srta. Kristy somebody involved it
in this? If, the he/she made it!.
He paid me so that he/she brought to
Boxer of the safe and sound desert.
Barry, is this certain? No.
Not begin. All of the same one are
side.
Barret would never sabotage the campaign.
In who you will trust Bob a Prize
Nobel in sciences or in a pron star?
Not him you dad, would not trust the because it is
famous in the movement of the neomarxistas.
What? As you dare? Those clowns
they know less than Karl Marx that of your mom.
No, your you have been sabotaging this
campaign privately from inside.
Have much care with
who point with the finger...
because recently I knew that
these pregnant of Brandt,
... and I have the tests
of blood that they prove it.
Mr. Takahashi has accepted
the terms of the treatment.
We have to reach an agreement with
DPro 2. Brandt, can you come a moment?
I love you Jerry Cocaine.
Hello. Jerry Co?
If
You go to the base of the chapel you Santa Mónica,
there you will find that that these looking for.
These are the shades of the light of the
tomorrow,
shades of the sun of the afternoon,
... and to illuminate the shades one.
Go before it is very late!
The boss speaks, cut the energy.
That it is this way.
What the gentleman says is the true.
He appears without reason.
There are not them
helped before without you be requested it?
He has the life in their hands.
Shake hands him/her and feel their force!
And he/she will curse them for their sins.
Barrtr had been experiencing
with soldiers in Iraq.
Flow Karma, the elixir of God.
Infected in the neck.
Alone for a
fuel comes home to live eternally.
He/she Says that the Flowing Karma
it is safe but you rehúsa...
... to publish the report of the impact
environmental of this fuel.
The search of global dominance
of Barret it was almost completed.
The negotiations with the Prime minister
of Japan they were to be carried out.
Takahashi was willing to change one of
their fingers for the shortcut to the Flowing Karma.
Bastard!
You said a finger I don't flow it!
Really? Your lawyers not
they read the whole contract.
It specifies a margin of six inches
of error in the court radio.
Please make an impression in
brass of the hand of Mr. Takahashi,
The temperatures in the one
desert continues increasing.
This type is not a joke
so don't waste their time.
Marvin has arrived.
Is a can? It is medicinal.
I have seen all your
movies are very good.
Already you that I am good,
tell me something that doesn't know.
My dad is his plastic surgeon.
Are you my surgeon's son? If
Don't tell me, as these?
Send greetings to your father.
Tell him/her that I will call it. If
He/she hears, let us return to the businesses. That it happens?
It is Flowing karma. Me and my
boys are very well with that.
You forgot all that
dirt of the marijuana,
... and everything the rest. The blue new dream.
When you take this languages with God.
If to say a word, you hear their voice.
And angels appear
using black parasols.
Ángel that you will see to
measure that the time passes.
My face in one of those dreams.
Per centuries the behavior patterns
that they existed in the ocean they were the hunt,
It was this way as the life
it arrived at our planet.
The city this full with enthusiasm and longings
for what will open up in any moment.
These majestic ones scheme activated
with what we call Flowing Karma.
Hello Kristy. Saura
Ahead.
For that have it.
It is alone a situation.
That what you want is?
I will make a party to celebrate the beginning of my reality sho
Do you have drugs? Clear.
The box of Pandora stayed
exposed to curious eyes.
Where you got this?
He/she hears they come here. For that have mystery it is?
I have the tape of the movie
of Boxer in my wallet.
That you will make with her?
This would rot joder the elections.
There is one it paginates in
Internet...  you show the tape,
... people will protest in front of the headquarters of
USIDent
and the government won't have as remaining silent them.
And like I can enter and the central net?
Not him you, speaks with the neomarxistas
they have a net for the whole city.
Avelaine is one of the suspects
terrorist that you/they put the bomb in Texas.
Give me the gun.
I need your help.
I need you to help me to
to find my brother. Ok
Put on your belt.
Good, DPro 2 imagine.
Is the only copy?
Non work in distributions,
yes it is the only copy.
Oh please, would like me
to ask him/her some questions.
Ahead, ask.
As you can sleep at night?
Because I sleep very well, thank you.
Until I heard screams in the neighboring house.
Because
USIDent this putting an end to my neighbor's house.
Because you listened some
false informations, for one of their friends.
Maybe you are not afraid of
a terrorist attack because me if.
Maybe this doesn't collide to you Sr. Smallhouse
but I lost two people in Abelaine.
Two of my former one
- husbands.
That you will make with all that money?
I will distribute my documentaries...
... I will help some women in the Mean
Guide to drink some civil freedoms.
He/she knows what you/they mean those
two words, Civil rights?
You have made them disappear.
Bo knows that, your you will go Cindy below
Pinzeeky. It is this way I know your name.
Not I believed that he/she had to make this
but I feel very generous today,
Do I like" that is? A
electrified in their eggs.
You should know that
there is another tape somewhere around.
Many but that incriminate to their friend
Boxer Santeros in a double murder.
He will find difficult but of a million
to put their hands in that.
Because nobody jode to Cindy Pinzeeky.
Jodete, he-goat.
Wow, if!
It is a dog, Kristy, he/she stole the
It will put it and all they will see it. Her
he/she probably thinks that it is another thing.
I will kill her.
That, you this returning madwoman.
You believe that their personal prophecy is but
important that my to protect to my family?
If the government not those
it stops I will make it.
Vote it doesn't stop the proposal 69.
The president was received
with a warm welcome
There is big bad hidden that you
they practice the human beings.
The president's conference
it began with the price ascent...
... of the fuel that you/they threaten
the economy of California.
Big earthquakes are reported
in Santa Mónica's coast.
They grow in magnitude. The seismologists
they notice on a great earthquake...
I sit down a premonition.
The danger is close.
To their health.
Shit Boxer Santeros.
These well?
The information that
I obtained it can kill me.
But it is a risk that he/she takes.
THE destination of the world depends on you.
If.
You should approach the magazepellin.
The secret that you look for this hidden one
in the secret camera of Barrent.
Which is the secret?
There is a dead body
that they brought of desert.
They found it in your room.
Do kill somebody?
They are listening, seeing.
If he/she is successful, remind me
my love, my name.
I will make it.
I want to suck you it.
If you don't allow me to make it, I will kill myself.
He/she waits, he/she waits.
Take off the pants
now, or I will kill myself.
- Take off them.
- ok.
Ok, Jerry Cocaine
I will make your dream reality.
And it will transform you into a woman.
He/she rents a room in Shudders, I like it.
Well, we are in problems.
They are in silver truck.
Look for in the interview with Krista.
Alias Krista Now, blond, medium.
He/she has a tape that is the objective.
There is a car.
Well this lit one, we go.
I want a real one as a movie.
As a television show
but it is a movie.
Because the new ones
technologies are the best.
Specially now
that all this so strange one.
- Well.
- If, it is this way.
Mr., she wants to kill me.
Salt of the mean.
All care.
Krista, I will kill you stupid prostitute.
Fascist pig.
We go.
- hello.
- where these?
I am close.
Ok, well.
Fortunio was always
in it nominates it of Barrens.
Their you order they were to surrender to the one
specimen before the evening.
Not there is returned now.
You are a good friend.
Cindy taenia a ticket
for the fair Jenny West.
Unfortunately not
a guest could take.
The darkness key on the city.
The neomarxes bandages
they appeared in the center.
They celebrated the festivities
with a concert in the center.
Elliot anger with their family.
While Frost anger to the one
launching of the megazepellin.
It will consume their lives.
There he/she can see a car bomb
that it exploded he/she makes moments.
Why did you want to kill yourself?
They recruited me.
I have to go to Iraq, it is difficult.
Not I can with that, well
I kill myself quick and simple.
- Fallujah.
- Were You in Iraq?
How did you leave man?
He/she is not interested.
A boy crosses the frontier of
Mexico, there I and my brother go.
Not you have a visa.
You said something when you slept.
You dressed the tomorrow's shades.
Shades of the sun of the night.
And between the shades and the light, they unite.
- What does he/she mean?
- 3 days.
The ends.
Everything finishes today.
It will be tremendous when they see me today.
Well made.
Will it be well?
As they say alone the time will say.
What does this mean?
There is a road to finish
our suffering.
You should take it.
Did You Take the DVD of Deep Throat 2?
Affirmative, I go live in tonight.
How long it will be active
the Web before they knock down it?
That you speak to me, don't worry,
he/she enjoys the rest of the party.
Alone we look for to the black ones.
This is now mine, Santero.
- Santeros has arrived.
- Well.
How do I happen?
Taenia a check.
I dreamt last night with which you died.
Mr. Santeros, him
they request in the suite, alone.
I won't leave.
Welcome.
Revelation 22.
We will see each other again.
He/she brings each man's recompense,
of agreement like he/she deserves it.
Mr. Santeros,
Welcome to the fleet Marx.
Among please.
Is it deaf or stupid?
I told him/her that it lowers that.
There he/she has, well among.
You are about winning the elections.
California this very close...
Ok, like say affection.
- Why not this here?
- Not he/she left the position.
It is time of a surgical incision.
I can smell it from below.
Not now, Denis.
The neomarxistas has infiltrated
the buildings, he/she has to leave.
Ok, this whole first floor control.
- he/she has to leave of there.
Gentlemen, I present them Megazapelin.
The project calls you
Serpentine fairy of dreams.
The generator inside Utopia 3,
... it has achieved movement
perpetual feigned.
The impact of this, it has reduced
the speed of the planet,
... at a level that certain
environmental anomalies happened.
One of those which, he/she was discovered
at the beginning of this year.
It was a rupture in the fourth dimension.
A space rupture
and time, far from here.
Outskirts of Lake Meade.
If.
As I imagine it in their libretto.
And what we made when
do we discover the rupture?
We send monkeys toward the one.
Alone the humans can survive that.
The soul of the monkey is not able to
to survive the dimensional threshold.
That learned and in that
moment the they Sweep he/she decided,
... that the first human
that I will travel for the rupture,
... serious a movie star.
Why me?
For their fame and the political bonds.
They were an irresistible combination.
As they show those
picture at 10:51 o'clock to. m.
... and this is before 69 minutes
that I go by the rupture.
A copy of you appeared.
I travel 69 minutes toward
behind in the time.
And in that moment its me
future and that of the past,
... they faced.
Am I then that of the future?
And am the one that I travel for the rupture?
And this is all it is him of its me past.
This body, this device,
.. this existent jewel of an unique soul.
It could decipher the one
I secrete of the creation.
Of the humanity.
Not I understand, never consider to kill me.
I am a pimp.
And the pimps don't make it.
Not we know that it would happen if
two human identical souls,
... and the recipients in
that they travel they would be.
Of where you took out this?
Welded Avali.
Have you bled?
Your friend, pilot.
That I pass in Fallujah,
it was not an accident.
They called it fire friend.
And the soldier Taverner not
that is forgiven that made me.
To where we go?
To the center.
Tenesmo that to go there.
We have to look for a truck.
I can feel it.
Will you enter?
He/she takes what you can, while you can.
We need...
Welcome.
He/she says that the transition this refused.
What do I make?
We will take ourselves the cashier to Mexico.
Stop for the hymn.
I present to Rebecca of the River.
Teverner, how these?
The truck of the ice cream.
Terri.
You were too far.
This alive one?
It was always this way.
You made sure that Taverner
he/she went with me to the rupture.
And you destroyed the trucks for remote.
What means
that I don't commit suicide.
You are a pimp, and they don't commit suicide.
There you are right.
Roland Taverner and its
is twin the same one, not?
Two identical souls,
wandering for the earth.
Coexisting, killing unconscious.
What would it happen, if they were shaken hands?
The fourth dimension would collapse.
Stupid dog.
The ocean has the control.
And this is the tower of the fire.
We have to evacuate.
Of what do you speak?
No.
We go.
These well?
Well made soldier.
He/she takes this, you cannot fail.
Vámonos.
Gentlemen I present them...
Taenia that to be this way. Him you.
- He will die.
- One cannot make anything.
This is an orgy or something
this way? What devils do they make?
Evacuate the atrium, go to the tip.
No, all of turn to their seats.
Or I kill myself, I swear him for heaven's sake.
I will make it.
We have to come unfastened.
- Not I can.
- Come unfastened.
If the truck falls, both die.
Allow me to kill me.
- You won't make it.
- I swear him to you.
Gentlemen the party you ends up.
It lowers the weapon.
This is the end, I can already shoot,
... and to wake up and all this finished.
Our mission is
to destroy the ambivalence.
To dethrone to God.
Official Taverner, they are the same one.
Don't you remember?
- Of Fallujah?
- I remember everything.
Gentlemen, it is this way like the world finishes.
Not without style but without vanity.
But there is hope that at the end,
... we can make sure
for an undeniable truth.
Nobody mounts a polla like Krista.
And I say nobody.
That type this lunatic, take out me of here.
NOT it was our blame.
It was not it.
Allow me to shoot.
- I forgive you.
- Fire friend.
I forgive you, I forgive you.
Revelation 21.
And God you clean those
you cry of their eyes,
... so that the new Messiah
he/she could see new Jerusalem.
Their name was Official
Taverner, of California.
My best friend.
He is a pimp and,
... and the pimps don't commit suicide.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org