Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Typewriters, transcripts,
anything missing?
The key to the ladies room.
Where was the fecal material found?
In the corner.
You'll know when you're near it.
- This was mailed to me.
- Just a minute.
If you don't have a telephone,
bring in a gas bill.
We need proof that you live
in the district.
I'm Jaime Escalante.
I'm supposed to teach Computer Science.
We don't have computers.
We were supposed to get computers,
but there's no funding for them again.
I'm Raquel Ortega,
chairman of the math department.
We'll be working together.
You don't understand.
I was supposed to teach computers.
- Where were you last night?
- Where was I?
"Where was I?" I was waiting.
You the new teacher?
Please find a seat.
What are we doing today?
Will everyone please try to find a seat?
If you can't find a seat...
...stand against the wall.
Let's put our desks in a circle
and discuss our feelings.
One body to a desk.
Could we talk about sex?
Then I'd have to give sex for homework.
Stand back everybody, please.
I can get you fired for saying that.
What'd he say?
¿Entienden inglés?
Sometimes.
Please move forward
if you do not speak English.
All the first row, stand up. Move out.
I was the first one here.
I'll find you another seat, okay?
Be careful.
This is Math 1-A.
I don't need math. I got a solar calculator
with my dozen doughnuts.
The bus is exact change. No big deal.
Quiet!
Everyone back in the classroom!
Everyone back in the class!
It was a premature bell. Back in the class.
That was a premature bell.
Premature bell?
We're not supposed to discuss sex in class.
Sit down! Stop talking!
They rigged the bell.
Those little bastards.
She's looking good, Joe.
When are you coming aboard?
I get seasick in the rain.
- Have you seen my boy?
- He was riding around here somewhere.
I hear your company's pushing
whole hog into PCs.
I don't work there anymore.
Jaime's teaching high school now.
Here's your thingy.
If you got laid off,
why didn't you come to me?
We pay kids right out of college $30,000.
I didn't get laid off. I want to teach.
High school teacher.
Well, good. That's great.
This is your job.
I was going to do it.
Why do you think I hurried home?
You're not even breathing hard,
you're hurrying so fast.
Have a good night, Joe.
I want a burger, hold the French fries,
the onions, and the pickles!
You look like Julia Child.
What you got?
It's an apple.
How much?
What do you mean?
What have you got?
Half.
Good.
Excuse my German accent.
What have you got?
Missing 25 percent.
- What?
- It's missing 25 percent.
That's right. Missing 25 percent.
Is it true intelligent people
make better lovers?
What you got?
I got a core.
You owe me 100 percent.
I'll see you in The People's Court.
Everyone please open your books,
Chapter 2, Page 26.
Multiplication of fractions...
...and percentages.
25 percent...
...50 percent...
...75 percent...
...and 100 percent.
Who's calling the shots, ese?
Have you got a slip?
You got a slip?
You'll have to stand in the back
until I can get another desk.
You sit right here.
Everyone please read
the first paragraph for a second.
- Where's your equipment?
- Don't got any.
Got to come to this class prepared.
Do the work in my head.
You know the times tables?
I know the one's...
...two's...
...three's.
Finger Man. I heard about you.
Are you the Finger Man?
I'm the Finger Man, too.
Do you know what I can do?
I know how to multiply by nine.
9 x 3. One, two, three. What do you get?
27!
6 x 9. One, two, three, four, five, six.
What do you get? 54!
Do you want a hard one?
How about 8 x 9?
What have you got? 72.
Wait a minute.
Please make sure you do problems
1 through 20. Page 26.
Can I have my book, Mr. Escalante?
Don't bring it to class again.
Don't get excited.
Cut me a D like the other profes.
I'll read my funny books...
...count the holes in the ceiling...
...kick back.
First thing, I can teach you some manners.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Lose a finger, I can't count to ten.
We've seen vatos like you before.
You'll be hurting soon.
Ponte trucha.
I was so worried the kids would know
more than me, I'd wake at 5:00 a. M...
...down my coffee and hit the math text.
I finally get every chapter down...
...and now they change the book on me.
Math, you either love or hate.
You got problems, come see me.
Thanks, Jaime. See you later.
You're in love? Which one? Let me know.
No, that's all right.
- Come on, Johnny, don't be afraid.
- I'm not "Johnny."
I know, Tito. Tito Grande.
Angel!
Go get a teacher!
It's Frank Garcia.
When I say García, you answer, okay?
Are your friends auditing?
I audited them to come with me.
I'm El Ciclón from Bolivia.
One-man gang.
This is my domain.
Don't give me no gas.
I'll jump on your face,
tattoo your chromosomes.
This is basic math,
but basic math is too easy for you.
So I'll teach you algebra,
because I'm the champ.
If the only thing you can do is
add and subtract...
...you'll be able to do one thing: Pump gas.
Ripping off a gas station is better
than working in one.
I'm a tough guy.
Tough guys don't do math,
tough guys deep fry chicken for a living.
You want a wing or a leg?
Who ever heard of negative
and positive numbers?
Negative numbers are like unemployment.
Ten million people out of work,
that's a negative number.
We'll need lots of Kleenex 'cause
there's gonna be bloodshed.
Have you ever been to the beach?
Have you ever played with the sand?
Finger Man!
You ever dig a hole?
The sand that comes out of the hole,
that's a positive.
The hole is a negative.
That's it. Simple. Anybody can do it.
- 2 + 2 =...
Net Head?
Answer it.
Come on, you know the answer.
- 2 + 2. Fill the hole.
If I had that on my hand,
I wouldn't raise it, either.
- 2 + 2 =...
Anybody can do it. Fill the hole.
Just fill the hole.
You can do it.
Don't let these burros laugh at you.
- 2 + 2 =...
I'll break your neck like a toothpick.
0.
0? You're right.
Simple. That's it.
- 2 + 2 = 0. He just filled the hole.
Neither the Greeks nor the Romans were
capable of using the concept of zero.
It was your ancestors...
...the Mayas, who first contemplated
the zero. The absence of value.
True story.
You burros have math in your blood.
Kimo sabe todo.
The man knows everything!
Parenthesis means multiply.
Every time you see this, multiply.
A negative times a negative
equals a positive.
"A negative times a negative
equals a positive." Say it.
equals a positive." Say it!
"A negative times a negative
equals a positive."
Again!
"A negative times a negative
equals a positive."
I can't hear you.
"A negative times a negative
equals a positive."
Louder!
"A negative times a negative
equals a positive!"
Louder!
"A negative times a negative
equals a positive!"
Why?
My point is I don't want
to be the principal...
...of the first school in the history
of Los Angeles to lose its accreditation.
I'm the last person to say that
this math department couldn't improve.
But if you want higher test scores...
...start by changing the economic level
of this community.
The purpose of this meeting is to review
the recommendations for accreditation.
Any suggestions?
I don't think
I should be teaching math next semester.
I was hired to be phys. Ed. Instructor.
As I said before...
...we lack the resources to implement
the changes the district demands.
Mr. Sanzaki,
you must have at least one comment.
This may not be the right time
to say this, but...
...I'm sorry, but I won't be coming back
after Christmas.
I got a job with aerospace.
How much money?
We have the remainder of the year
before we're put on probation.
- If we fail, we lose accreditation.
- If we fail?
You can't teach logarithms to illiterates.
These kids come to us
with barely a 7th grade education.
There isn't a teacher in this room
who isn't doing everything he possibly can.
I'm not. I could teach more.
I'm sure Mr. Escalante
has good intentions...
...but he's only been here a few months.
Students will rise to the level
of expectations, Señor Molina.
What do you need, Mr. Escalante?
Ganas. All we need is ganas.
What's ganas?
We will begin each class with a quiz.
There will be no free rides, no excuses.
You already have two strikes against you.
There are some people in this world...
...who assume that you know less
than you do...
...because of your name
and your complexion...
...but math is the great equalizer.
When you go for a job, the employer...
...will not want to hear your problems.
Neither do I.
You'll work harder
than you ever worked before.
And the only thing I ask
from you is ganas...
...desire... a haircut.
If you don't have the ganas,
I will give it to you because I am an expert.
Today is Monday,
tomorrow is Wednesday...
...Friday is payday, the weekly test.
There will be no diagonal vision.
Keep your eyes on your own paper.
You have 10 minutes to finish.
If you finish early, start the assignment
on the board. No questions? Good.
¡Angel, vámonos!
I was said to go here.
Nice knowing you.
Have a good day. Arrivederci!
You're in luck. Take the seat.
Relax, take Sominex.
Don't sleep in my class.
I take that as an insult.
Kimo, I want to talk to you about the class.
You ain't got a seat. Don't give me no gas.
I know about that. It was a mistake.
I'm gonna fly straight, but I got a problem.
Yeah, me.
Seriously. Books.
The homies can't see me
haul them around.
You don't want anyone to think
you're intelligent.
Maybe I can have two books,
keep one stashed at home.
I'll cut you a deal.
I'll give you three books.
Take one home. One for your class.
This one is broken.
One for your locker,
so nobody sees you carrying it around.
Easily understood?
What do I get?
Protection, Kimo.
Protección, understand?
I understand.
That's the only reason
I'm still in Kimo's class.
Don't tell her that you dig her.
That's the worst thing you can do
with a woman.
I'm fed up with this pelón we got
for a teacher.
Escalante has a bug up his ass.
He's from South America.
He's probably a Nazi come out of hiding.
Don't you know?
Garfield can't get accredited.
Only teachers who act like assholes
will keep their jobs.
What if we all decide not to take this test?
He can't fail the whole class.
Mutiny. That's cool.
See you guys later.
Camejo thinks she's hot
because she dates gabachos.
If we don't do better today, heads will roll.
I've never gotten lower
than a B+ in my life.
Because you take those
Mickey Mouse classes.
Always get an A.
Here you have a chance for a solid D.
You got 10 minutes.
Here he comes.
Watch this.
What's wrong with you?
I'm not taking the quiz.
You didn't turn in your homework.
My goat ate it.
You don't do your homework,
you don't get a ticket to watch the show.
Give her the chair!
Shit.
Chair! Chair! Chair!
Shut up!
Get back to your tests.
You've got less than nine minutes.
Now you're the show.
What's the matter with you?
Are you the dumb student? Come on!
3:00.
You'll have to do it anyway.
Kids go to bed?
Papa go to work?
Can I fix you something to eat?
Mija, could you please turn off that light?
Orale, homeboy.
Teacher time, ese.
Tell Kimo I say, "¿Qué hubo?", ese.
Oh, shit man!
Green light, red light?
Anybody?
Late! Late, Angel!
- Go see the counselor.
- Come on, Kimo.
Go to wood shop, make a shoeshine box.
You'll need it.
You're the man, you know.
Why don't you put them in college, huh?
So dumb taco benders like me...
...can pick their vegetables...
...collect their garbage...
...clip their poodle's toenails.
I may be a sinner...
...but I'm willing to pay for my sins.
One-shot deal. Go sit down.
See you at 3:00.
Go to hell.
I got more bad news for you.
What I'm going to say will trip you out.
Mr. Escalante, I forgot my pencil.
He can have mine.
Today is my last day.
Did you enjoy your taquitos?
Except for one thing.
Someone doesn't know how to add.
She should be back in school.
Papa, this is Mr. Escalante,
my math teacher.
Can you sit with us?
Anita, bring us a couple of beers.
You should get another waitress.
Ana can be the first in your family
to graduate and go to college.
I thank you for your concern.
Her mother, sisters,
and brothers work here.
This is a family business. She is needed.
She could help the family more
by getting an education.
She'd probably get pregnant.
She wouldn't finish college.
Anita, go help your mom in the kitchen.
She talks about going to medical school.
I don't think so.
She should make her own choices.
She'll just get fat.
She'll waste her life here. She's a top kid!
I started washing dishes
for a nickel an hour.
Now I own this place.
Did I waste my life?
I washed dishes too
when I came to America.
Good!
Put on an apron and give us a hand.
Your husband comes
to my restaurant, eats...
...then insults me.
Excuse my husband, Mr. Delgado.
He just wants what's best for Ana.
She could go to college,
then teach you how to run the place.
Professor?
I don't want your money
and I don't need your business.
Skip it. Tip.
He puts hot chili in his dip
to sell extra beer.
Dog, dog, dog, dog!
Everybody look at the board.
Will someone please read for me
what's on the board? Anybody.
Juan has five times as many girlfriends
as Pedro.
Carlos has one girlfriend less than Pedro.
If their total number of girlfriends is 20...
...how many does each gigolo have?
Late! Late!
How many girlfriends does
each gigolo have? Anybody.
You think you got it, Einstein?
Juan is x. Carlos is y. Pedro is x + y.
Is Pedro bisexual, or what?
I have a terrible feeling about you.
5x = Juan's girlfriends.
You're good now...
...but you'll end up barefoot,
pregnant and in the kitchen.
Can you get negative girlfriends?
No, just negative boyfriends.
Please forgive them,
for they know not what they do!
Carlos has x - 5 girlfriends, ¿qué no?
"Que no" is right. Que no.
The answer to my prayers!
May I go to the restroom?
In 10 minutes. Hold it.
Hit it.
It's a trick problem, Mr. Kimo.
You need to know how many girlfriends
they have in common.
It's not that they're stupid.
They just don't know anything.
I'm wrong?
X = Pedro's girlfriends.
5x = Juan's girlfriends.
X - 1 = Carlos's girlfriends.
(x + 5x) + (x -1) = 20.
So, x = 3.
Good to see you.
This makes no sense unless we see
how it works in the real world.
Could I get a couple of gigolos
for a practical demonstration?
No, no. Just kidding.
What kind of math is this?
The one that's up right now is calculus.
You'll get it in college.
My daughter uses this program
in her high school.
I want to teach calculus next year.
Boy, that's a jump.
That's ridiculous.
They haven't had trig or math analysis.
They can take them this summer.
Our best students in summer school?
From 7:00 to 12:00.
Every day, including Saturdays.
That would do it.
Summer classrooms are reserved
for remedial courses.
To turn this school around,
start from the top.
Mr. Escalante, don't lecture us.
Our kids can't handle calculus.
We don't even have the books.
If they pass the Advanced Placement Test,
they get college credit.
There are some teachers here...
...who couldn't pass
the Advanced Placement Test.
You think you can make this fly?
I teach calculus or...
...have a good day.
If this man can walk in here...
...and dictate his own terms,
over my objections...
...I see no reason to continue
as department chair.
Don't take this personally.
I'm thinking about those kids.
If they try and don't succeed...
...you'll shatter what little
self-confidence they have.
These aren't the types that bounce back.
Have a good day.
Kimo, it stinks like last year in here.
Somebody give Claudia an orange.
Okay, okay! Sit down!
You think I want to do this?
The Japanese pay me.
They're tired of making everything.
They want you to pull your own weight...
...so they can go take vacations
on Mount Fuji.
Kimo, I thought this room
was supposed to be air-conditioned.
You should think cool.
Think...
Cool.
Cool!
I get this letter saying
I'm fired because of Proposition 13.
I'm down to $936.
I invest $100 in resumes and buy this suit.
I hit every insurance company in the city.
My wife wants us to move
into her parents' rec room.
Two weeks later I get another letter
telling me to go back to work.
How do you like the suit?
- Fabulous.
- How about the color?
Welcome back, pelón!
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Sure?
Yes! I said I was fine.
We will go step by step, inch by inch.
Calculus was not made to be easy.
It already is.
Remember the good times we had
last summer?
Remember when things were
really jumping good?
That's Gone With tAhe Wind.
Now it's The Good, the Bad and the Ugly.
Come on, a contract?
You mean you can't trust us by now?
Those of you who commit will be preparing
for the AdVanced Placement Test.
Have this signed before class tomorrow.
We come in an hour early, take your class
two periods and stay until 5:00?
Believe it or don't.
We have to come on Saturdays?
And no vacations?
Pass the A.P. And you get college credit.
- Big deal.
- We're seniors. We get to slack off.
Can you make it Saturday morning
after playing in your band Friday nights?
I know you love scaring us into doing stuff.
But that gets old real fast.
Hey, Kimo.
You proud of me? I'm the first dude here!
What's calculus?
Calculus is math
that Sir Isaac Newton invented...
...to figure out planet orbits.
But he never told anybody about it...
...until this other scientist
claimed he had invented calculus.
But the guy was so stupid
he got it all wrong...
...so Newton went public
to fix his mistakes. Isn't that neat?
For a genius, Newton was an idiot.
If I invent something,
I'll make sure to get paid.
I hope this isn't an excuse
to stay out all hours.
Trust me, Mom. Sign it.
Boys don't like it if you're smart.
I'm doing this so I don't have to depend
on some dumb guy for the rest of my life.
Thank you.
You don't have it signed,
you don't have a ticket to watch the show.
Thank you, Mr. Kung Fu.
Mr. Blue Eyes, thank you.
Elizabeth, my Taylor!
Sophia, my Loren.
Get a haircut.
How many times I got to tell you?
Red, get a new jacket.
Clint, forget your gun?
Unfold it.
Hey, you didn't...
Get out of the way.
- You didn't sign it.
- I'm putting school on hold.
Go back until you sign it.
My uncle offered me a job
operating a forklift weekends.
So what?
Two years in the union
and I'll make more than you.
The money I'll be making
will buy me a new Trans Am.
Wouldn't you rather be designing
these than repairing them?
You can't even do that.
They got fuel injection.
- You're going to strip my gears.
- What's the problem?
Don't panic, Johnny.
Just watch out for the other guy.
- Right or left?
- Where are we going?
- Right or left!
- Go right!
All you see is the turn.
You don't see the road ahead.
Open the gate. We're going to be late.
Why are you here so early?
We're going to Mr. Escalante's class.
Wake up. Drink some coffee.
One, you got the graph right here.
Two, this is the most important part.
Right here.
The radius of rotation.
That's it. Anybody got any questions?
Anybody can do it
if you remember one basic element:
The element of surprise.
Stay awake! Wake up!
Wake up! Bring toothpicks
to pinch open your eyes.
Do you understand, Johnny?
I was swimming with dolphins,
whispering imaginary numbers...
...looking for the fourth dimension.
Go back to sleep. That's very good.
Any questions?
Yes? No? Nothing? Okay.
You should have it by now.
What's the answer? Anybody?
We're going backwards.
You're fooling around too much
on the weekend.
This girl's got to do some work
from the neck up.
We'll have to stay late again.
We can have pizza delivered.
We can get fried chicken, cheeseburgers.
Donations? You owe me money.
You don't deserve the grades you get.
Are you late for another date?
She has more boyfriends
than Elizabeth Taylor!
I don't appreciate you using
my personal life to entertain this class.
Everything is falling apart.
My boyfriend is freaking out!
School sucks.
I'm in that classroom all day, Kimo.
Look at my clothes and my hair.
I can't even comb it. I hate my life.
So what's the problem?
You're going to have to bring him in.
I'm not a doctor, Ma'am.
There's no way. I don't do diagnosis.
Are we going to see the doctor
before next week?
Hold on. ¿Seguro?
Medi-Cal?
How are you going to pay for this?
If we could pay for it,
we'd go to a regular hospital.
My grandmother will
get pneumonia waiting.
Take a seat and we'll call your number.
You have to bring him in.
There's no way around it.
I understand that,
but you have to bring him in.
Try the shortcut.
This is easy. Baby stuff for Boy Scouts.
My mind don't work this way.
Tic-tac-toe. It's a piece of cake,
upside down. Watch for the green light.
I've been with you guys for two years!
Everyone knows I'm the dumbest!
I can't handle calculus!
They have a better chance
on the A.P. Test without me.
Don't laugh!
Laugh! You're breaking our hearts.
Don't do this.
He'll sacrifice himself to benefit the team.
Do you have the ganas!
I have the ganas.
- You want me to do it for you?
- Yes!
You're supposed to say no!
I'm going to have to get tough.
We'll have to work
right through Christmas break.
The counselor was just here
looking for you.
Something about cosmetology classes.
He says, there's three different levels.
One for boys, one for girls and one
for I don't know what. Go find out.
Kimo, listen. It's cool.
- My grandmother...
- Clock out.
Game's over. You lose.
You never listen to nobody, man!
Adiós. Why don't you...
...send me some postcards?
Or call me on the phone, let me know...
...how you're doing? We love you.
Kimo Sabe this, cabrón!
Pancho, that guy has a bigger problem
than you.
Tic-tac-toe.
Simple.
No. She's a little sloppy
with her homework.
Dad, get off the phone so we can eat.
No, she's a top student.
You're father works 60 hours a week,
then volunteers to teach night school.
Merry Christmas to you, too.
Now he's visiting junior high schools
in his spare time.
Corn and potatoes?
What happened to the lomo montado
pica a lo macho?
Jaime, I don't want you to teach
this holiday.
No teaching.
I don't understand this problem.
His own son has problems with math.
Give me that book.
- No books at the table.
- Go wash your hands.
I'll get it.
You see what I mean?
I've seen you do a lot
of underhanded tricks...
...but bringing your abuelita
to my house at Christmastime, come on.
I need calculus to take me
to a good career, Johnny.
Something smells good.
"On the first day of Christmas
A cholo came to me"
This is what's given.
We're looking for the area
in the first quadrant bounded by the curve.
What are the limits? Anybody.
0 to pi/2, sir.
Wrong. Lupe.
0 to pi/2?
What is wrong with you? This is review.
I checked my work twice.
Check it again.
I got the same answer as the gordita.
Don't call me gordita, pendejo.
It's 0 to pi/2, sir.
Yeah, I got the same thing.
You should know this!
What is wrong with you? This is review!
You act like a blind man in a dark room...
...looking for a black cat that isn't there!
I don't believe it. It's giving me a shot
from the back! No way!
Kimo finally blew a head gasket.
It's a pen.
It's a pencil.
It's a chair.
It's a light.
It's a window.
It's in the room, on the table.
It's 10:00.
Un momento, por favor.
One moment, please.
Page 456, please.
Come on, Page 456.
Shut up and sit down.
We told him to take it easy.
It's our fault.
We sit back and watch him burn in.
It's "burn out."
The man brought it on himself.
He was asking for trouble.
How can you say that?
You wanna-be cholo asshole.
That's disgusting!
You want me? I'll kick your ass!
It's Molina!
Break it up! Pancho, just break it up.
Settle down.
- Later, dude.
- Settle down, Angel.
Mr. Escalante is okay.
He had a mild heart attack
and he's under observation.
Mr. Schloss is your substitute.
Out of respect to Mr. Escalante,
please give him your undivided attention.
I don't want any more trouble
from this room.
Pancho, you come with me.
Angel, let's go.
Tito, take your seat.
Mr. Molina has informed me that...
...you have your A.P. Calculus exam
in two weeks.
To be honest, I've never taught calculus.
I'm really a music teacher.
Are you mad at me, Mommy?
If I thought it would help, I would be angry.
The doctor says no stress.
No job-related activity for at least a month.
I want another doctor.
I have to go.
I left Fernando with a neighbor.
- I'll stay with Dad.
- No, go with your mother.
Don't forget to take out the trash.
What time do you get off work?
I'm still alive! I'm a hard-dying guy.
Shouldn't you be in the hospital?
No, I should be here with you.
Bulldogs!
Dog, dog, dog, dog.
Thank you for baby-sitting my canguros.
Have a good day.
How are you?
You should take it easy.
Go back to bed, man.
No, I should be here with you.
You already forgot to stand up!
Everybody!
No, against the wall like a snake! Hurry!
We've practiced for this all year.
You're the best!
You guys are the best!
This will be a piece of cake!
Upside down.
And...
Step by step.
You got it now. Open your eyes.
Y = In...
...(x - 1). What is the domain?
X > - 1.
No! End of the line!
I'm gone two days and you forget.
What's the domain?
All real numbers greater than one. X > 1.
I told you, you could do it. Okay!
Be sure each mark is black
and completely filled-in.
If you make an error...
...save time by crossing it out
instead of erasing.
It is not expected that you will
answer all multiple choice questions.
When you're told to begin,
open your booklet.
Tear out the green insert and start work.
You may begin.
Let's go!
I like to keep my pants dry.
The water is great! Come on!
Okay, fine!
This is so stupid!
I'm coming!
Orale, Grandpa!
We, being teachers...
...know the Advanced Placement Tests
are very difficult...
...especially in mathematics.
Less than two percent
of all high school seniors nationwide...
...even attempt
the Advanced Placement Calculus Test.
You've been drinking!
I am proud to announce...
...that no other high school
in Southern California...
...has more students passing...
...than Garfield High School.
No, he just walks like that.
Eighteen students took the test.
Eighteen passed.
We have an announcement to make.
We, the A.P. Calculus Class...
...would like to present this plaque
to our teacher...
...Jaime A. Escalante.
Yes, this is Guadalupe Escobar.
Is this some kind of joke?
Who is this?
For real?
What?
You're crazy, man.
"Tests are graded with the identity
of the student concealed.
"Only after irregularities were found
was it determined...
"...that all the students were
from Garfield High." You all got this?
"Based upon the unusual agreement
of incorrect answers...
"...E.T.S. Must question the scores...
"...of all students with
such unusual agreement."
What does it mean in English?
They think we cheated because
we all had the same wrong answers.
We're too stupid
to know how to cheat correctly.
Let's sue them.
"The board doubts the grades are valid
because of these unusual circumstances."
These people are human.
They can make mistakes.
Kimo, these people are calling us cheaters.
This is where we keep
all confidential material...
...S.A.T. And A.P. Tests included.
Only my secretary and I know
the combination.
This controversy is officially
between the E.T.S. And the students.
It does not reflect upon your school
or its administration.
We'd like to resolve this
with as little publicity as possible.
I'd appreciate that.
You think they got the test ahead of time?
Claudia was having emotional problems.
Pancho was way behind.
Do you really think anyone cheated?
No.
But my father does.
Damn shit!
Look at this shit!
If I'd taken that job with my uncle,
I'd have a new car by now!
It's all right. You can fix it.
You can fix it. Just relax.
I didn't know you two were a thing now.
Just something for the summer.
You're an asshole, Pancho.
Shit!
Lots of stars up there, homey.
Not too polluted.
The stars aren't really there, ese.
What you're looking at
is where they used to be.
It takes the light...
...1,000 years to reach the earth.
For all we know,
they burned out a long time ago.
God pulled the plug on us.
He didn't tell nobody.
The stars are out there, homeboy.
I don't care what you say.
Hey, homeboy!
Throw me a kiss, baby!
That's right! That's all you know.
Can't you afford a knife?
Use a pencil, go to jail.
You've got a tough mouth.
You better watch yourself.
Mucho gusto, officer.
That was real smart, ese!
Get away from my ride!
Get up!
Where are you going?
Come back!
Well, does anyone have anything to say?
I've known your family for years.
Tell us the truth.
Nothing happened.
- Don't lie to me.
- Nothing happened!
Leave her alone.
She didn't do anything wrong.
Then tell us who did.
We're not cops.
We're not here to put anybody behind bars.
If you cheated,
let us know so you can go home...
...and enjoy the rest of your summer.
I come from this neighborhood.
I know that sometimes we're tempted
to take shortcuts.
Tell me the truth. What happened?
We're busted. Let's admit it.
How did you do it?
I got the test ahead of time
and passed it out.
How did you get it?
The mailman.
I strangled him.
His body's decomposing in my locker.
No sense in continuing
if they won't cooperate.
Do you know how this got in my box?
A letter of resignation.
Anonymous.
My guess is that it has something to do
with the mess this school is in.
Do you think the students cheated?
Mr. Escalante, you put these kids
under an awful lot of pressure.
They would have gone to any lengths
to please you.
You didn't answer my question.
Every night I watch the news on Tv.
I see a lot of people go on trial.
They deny everything or their lawyers say
they were insane when they did it.
A lot of them get off.
But I believe most people
who get caught today are guilty...
...don't you?
Yep, I know what you mean.
Have you seen my car?
Do you need a ride home?
No, thank you!
Kimo, let me take you home!
Want to talk about it?
I may have made a mistake trying
to teach them calculus.
Regardless of whether they passed
that test or not...
...they learned.
They learned if you try real hard,
nothing changes.
Quit.
If that's all you have left to teach...
...quit.
What kills me...
...is that they lost the confidence...
...in the system they are now
finally qualified to be a part of.
I don't know why I'm losing sleep over this.
I don't need it.
I could make twice the money
and less hours...
...and have people treat me with respect.
Respect?
Jaime, those kids love you.
Hey, Kimo!
Check out your ride!
We fixed it up for you.
It's going downtown
to take action on those E.T.S. Boys.
Dad, check out your new car!
We got to talk about the payments,
though.
I'm Jaime Escalante. I'm the A.P.
Calculus teacher from Garfield High.
I'm Dr. Pearson...
...and this is Dr. Ramirez.
I feel I have a right to know
why you think my students cheated.
I'm sorry you drove all the way out here...
...but we're not at liberty
to discuss the controversy.
I'd just like to see the test, that's all.
I understand what you're going through...
...but the problem is between the E.T.S.
And the students.
I'd just like to see
what kind of mistakes were made.
I'm their teacher. I know my kids.
Mr. Escalante, have a seat.
No, thank you.
There were some...
...unorthodox, even illogical, computations
for students of this caliber.
Mistakes in simple math.
Because they have the same teacher
teaching them the same program.
I taught them step by step,
all the same way.
Your students averaged fewer than
four wrong on the multiple choice...
...where other schools average
14 to 18 incorrect answers.
Most of your kids finished
with time to spare.
They should be rewarded, not punished.
The Educational Testing Service...
...does not act capriciously.
Every major university in the US
subscribes to our service.
I'd just like to see proof of wrongdoing.
I'd like to see the tests.
There is no proof of wrongdoing,
only a suspicion of cheating.
In this country...
...one is innocent until proven guilty.
Not vice versa.
If you are so confident of their abilities,
encourage them to retest.
Why?
If they don't,
everyone will assume they cheated.
Everyone will assume
they cheated if they do.
I want to see the test!
Mr. Escalante, we are psychometricians,
thorough to the point of boring.
We're not out to get anyone.
Wait.
A situation of two students
cheating is one thing.
This blanket accusation is saying
there was a conspiracy.
Every conspiracy has a leader.
Who better qualify to be the leader
than the teacher?
Nobody is accusing you here of anything.
Not only me, the school, the parents,
the entire community!
Scores this high would be questioned
regardless of the school.
But if this was Beverly Hills High
they wouldn't have sent you to investigate.
I hope you're not insinuating
that we haven't earned our position here.
No one has given me a damn thing.
You are letting your emotions
get the best of you.
If no one gave you a damn thing,
you shouldn't take away from my kids!
The identity of the students
was concealed...
...until it was determined
that irregularities existed.
No one would have questioned the scores
if my kids didn't have Spanish surnames...
...and come from barrio schools!
All right. We've explained our position
and heard your complaints, but now...
...our conversation is over.
Something is going on
that nobody is talking about.
And you know what it is!
No one has the right to accuse me
of racism. No one has that right!
I know well how to spell discrimination!
I thought this was over long ago.
Why do this to my kids?
There are two kinds of racism,
Mr. Escalante.
Singling out a group
who are members of a minority...
...and not singling out a group
who are members of a minority.
My kids could teach you
a thing or two, Johnny!
I'll call security
if you can't control yourself.
Do it!
You didn't prove anything.
My kids didn't do anything!
I'll prove you guys wrong.
I hope you do
because this is not between you and me.
Maybe not.
But if I catch you on the street,
I'll kick the shit out of you.
This is Guadalupe Escobar.
I'm going to take the test again.
You're kidding!
Kimo, we only have one day to study.
8:00 a.m. On Tuesday. Thank you.
You didn't let me talk to them.
Call collect. Stick them with a big bill.
Thought I'd seen this place
for the last time.
We'll have to review the whole course
in one shot.
- In one day?
- Can't do it in any less.
Maybe they'll give us the same test.
It will be harder. You can count on that.
Just go step by step and play defense.
Don't bring anything.
No pencils, no erasers, nothing.
Don't wear clothes with too many pockets.
Don't let your eyes wander.
No spacing out.
Don't give them any opportunity
to call you cheaters.
You are the true dreamers.
And dreams accomplish wonderful things.
You're the best.
Tomorrow you'll prove
that you're the champs.
Start with Chapter 1.
Kimo, what you making there?
You like brains? Good. I was afraid
you guys wouldn't appreciate it.
This food lasts for 24-hours.
You're afraid we're going
to screw up royally tomorrow.
Tomorrow is just another day.
I'm afraid you'll screw up
the rest of your lives.
I'm fried. I don't care
if I don't pass that test.
- Sit down. We got a lot of work to do.
- I'm going home.
Sit down.
I'm tired and I'm going home. Okay?
- Do you know what you're doing?
- I'm going home, that's what.
It's almost ready. Who wants some?
Let's order out, man.
Just kidding.
I had to see you.
You can't expect me to be your girlfriend
at your convenience.
I'm an asshole.
Sorry.
I'm sure you're all familiar
with the procedure.
You have 90 minutes to complete
the multiple choice section.
Do not fill in answers by guessing.
Wrong answers will be counted
against you.
You may begin Part 1, now.
Okay, pencils down.
You have 90 minutes to complete
the free-response section.
Do not spend too much time
on any particular answer.
Credit will be issued for partial solutions.
Open the booklet, begin Part 2. Good luck.
- Finished?
- No, I can't finish the test.
I have a scholarship appointment at U.S.C.
- Can't that wait?
- No, it can't.
Did you fill out your ID card?
Okay, pencils down.
Did you hear the news?
We got the computers.
Yep, that'll do it.
They want to go over the test again
so that there's no misunderstandings.
I'm on my way to the faculty meeting.
Misunderstanding again?
Call Dr. Ramirez. He'll help us.
He'll tell me the same thing.
All right, I'll call him.
This is Mr. Molina calling again.
Can I speak to...
Yes, I did.
You do?
Yes! I'd like that very much.
One moment.
Yes, I'm aware of the scoring.
Three is a passing grade,
five is a perfect grade.
I'm ready. Go ahead.
Diaz, Maria, four.
Sinfuentes, Mark, five.
Narvarra, Jose, four.
I want the original scores reinstated.
Santos, Daniel, four.
Escobar, Guadalupe, five.
Camejo, Claudia, four.
Ana Delgado, four.
Garcia, Francisco, three.
Fuentes, Rafaela, four.
Javier Perales, five.
Guitaro, Armando, four.
Angel Guzman...
...five.
Tell them to hold the meeting.
We have great news.
Pernajas, Juliana, five.
Hernandez, Alejandro, four.
Castro, Monica, four.
Done by (c) dCd / November 2008
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org