Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Where are you going?
You were doing great.
You were in perfect position
to deIiver the death bIow.
AII you had to do
was foIIow through.
Come on.
Let's try it again.
Don't push me, Tom.
Huh!
I am not pushing you.
I'm encouraging you.
To do what?!
Try something new.
This martiaI arts program
is the best workout
I've ever had.
No, it's more than that.
Working with a bat'leth
is an art.
You have to use
your mind and body,
your movements...
Look, you may find
aII of this KIingon stuff
reaIIy fascinating,
but I don't.
I'm not going to waste my time
trying to disemboweI a bunch
of hoIographic monsters.
I onIy came down here
because you tricked me
into that stupid bet.
WouId you watch it!
You couId take somebody's
head off with that thing.
I have tried this,
and now I am finished.
Got it?
Look, if you don't Iike
the program, that's fine,
but why do you aIways
have to get so hostiIe?
I am not hostiIe!
Where am I?
Paris to Bridge.
We have an aIien visitor
on Deck 6.
What do you want with me?
Why have I been abducted?
We didn't abduct you.
You just appeared here.
We had nothing to do with it.
What is this pIace?
You're on a starship
caIIed Voyager
Where were you before?
My coIony on Nyria III.
I was waIking home and...
then I was here.
What's wrong?
It's coId here...
and too bright.
Let us take you to Sick Bay.
Our Doctor can run some scans.
Maybe we can get some answers.
I've increased the temperature
to 45 degrees CeIsius.
And the Iight IeveI shouId be
more comfortabIe for you now.
Yes, thank you.
You're very considerate.
I hope you'II excuse
my initiaI suspicion.
This experience
has been very unnerving.
I'd feeI the same way
in your pIace.
Do your peopIe
possess technoIogy
which couId have
transported you here?
Not that I know of.
I've heard of other races
that have it.
Maybe one of them
brought me here,
but I can't imagine why.
PIease describe
the physicaI sensation
of your experience.
First, I feIt Iightheaded
and then everything around me
seemed to bend or rippIe.
There-- there was
a moment of bIackness
and I feIt a curious sensation
of insects crawIing on my skin
and then I found myseIf
on your ship.
Interesting.
I'II run a microceIIuIar
scan for residuaI energy traces.
Can you teII us
where your coIony is Iocated?
We're on the third pIanet
of the Nyrian system--
a red giant star
with a Iarge cIoud
of intersteIIar dust
just beyond the fifth pIanet.
Doesn't sound Iike any
system we've encountered.
UnfortunateIy, our knowIedge
of this area of space
is Iimited.
I'd Iike you to Iook
at a star chart
to see if you recognize
any astronomicaI markers.
Of course.
In the meantime, my crew
has begun scanning the area
for any cIues about
what happened to you.
Lieutenant, if you don't mind.
Where is Kes today?
I don't know.
She's Iate for her duty shift.
Computer, Iocate Kes.
Kes is not on board Voyager
When did she Ieave?
1 132 hours.
What time did our aIien
visitor come onboard?
1 132 hours.
There's nothing to indicate
that any other ships
have been in this area for weeks
and the nearest inhabited worId
is over ten Iight-years away.
Whoever or whatever did this
had to Ieave
some kind of energy trace.
InternaI sensors aren't
showing anything unusuaI
in the corridor
where the Nyrian appeared
or at Kes's Iast known Iocation.
Then Iet's concentrate
on the time.
Run a IeveI-1 anaIysis
on aII sensor readings,
internaI and externaI
taken at the exact moment
it happened.
I'II get it started,
but it may take a whiIe.
You don't think I'm hostiIe,
do you?
I, uh...
wouIdn't describe
you that way, no.
I know that I have a temper,
but that doesn't mean
that I'm aIways hostiIe,
does it?
No, of course not.
I am forthright;
I speak my mind.
That is very different
from being hostiIe.
Very different.
And if someone described me
that way, they'd be way off
the mark, wouIdn't they?
Way off.
Then why do you Iook Iike
you're afraid for your Iife?
What is this?
Looks Iike a surge
of poIaron particIes.
LocaIize the source.
I'II try to increase
the sensor resoIution.
You have anything yet?
Harry?
Torres to Bridge.
Ensign Kim just disappeared.
And we just got another visitor.
Mr. Tuvok, have you
made any progress?
Increasing the shieId strength
has had no apparent effect.
However, if...
Oh...
WeIcome to Sick Bay.
Take a number.
In the Iast three hours,
we've Iost 22 of our peopIe.
According to the Nyrians,
they've aII shown up
on their coIony
as though
we're switching pIaces.
I went over our navigationaI
charts with Dammar,
but he's compIeteIy unfamiIiar
with this part of space.
For aII we know,
that coIony couId be
thousands of Iight-years away.
Any idea what might be
causing these transfers?
I'm not sure.
Harry and I detected
a surge of poIaron particIes
right before he disappeared.
They created a spatiaI
distortion fieId around him,
but it coIIapsed
as soon as he vanished.
CouId it have been some
kind of spatiaI anomaIy?
It couId have been anything--
a naturaIIy occurring
phenomenon Iike a wormhoIe,
or a subspace fIow fieId
or a kind
of technoIogy
Iike our transporters.
AII right.
Get back to your stations
and keep Iooking.
Confine the Nyrians
to the cargo bays
and post security detaiIs
at every access point.
In aII fairness,
Captain, they haven't been
threatening in any way.
They seem as puzzIed
by aII this as we are.
Chakotay, I don't care
how they seem.
AII I care about is that I've
had a knot in my stomach
since the first Nyrian arrived.
Something about this is wrong;
I can smeII it.
Look at us--
running around the ship
checking sensors
and spinning theories
whiIe the Nyrians
sIowIy repIace our crew.
Consider this:
There has been
a consistent intervaI
of nine minutes and 20 seconds
between these exchanges.
At that rate, our entire crew
wiII be gone in 18 hours.
TeII me that doesn't put
a knot in your stomach.
You have your orders.
Captain's Log, Stardate 50912.4.
It's been 12 hours since these
mysterious exchanges began
and we stiII haven't discovered
their cause.
I've aIready Iost
over haIf my crew.
Cargo Bay 2 is aImost fuII.
We'II have to start
converting the shuttIe bays.
Then do it.
I want them
where we can keep
an eye on them.
I'II have to reassign
more crew members to security.
Our ranks are getting
a IittIe thin.
Shut down everything but the
ship's essentiaI functions.
We'II be operating on
a skeIeton crew before Iong.
B'EIanna,
you've deveIoped a theory
about what's happening.
A Nyrian astrophysicist
who arrived about an hour ago
toId me about some strange
graviton fIuctuations
they detected at their coIony.
I ran some scans on this end
and found the same thing.
A wormhoIe?
PossibIy a baby one.
And if I'm right,
one end is opening
intermittentIy inside Voyager
We couId have passed through it
whiIe it was forming
and snagged on it somehow.
Then how do we get it unsnagged?
WeII, now that I have
this new information
I'd Iike to have
another taIk with RisIan,
the Nyrian scientist.
Is NeeIix stiII heIping out
with the new arrivaIs?
I think he's in Cargo Bay 2 now.
Janeway to NeeIix.
NeeIix here, Captain.
I'd Iike you to find
one of the Nyrians who...
NeeIix to Captain Janeway.
I Iost contact.
What did you say?
Chakotay to NeeIix.
The Captain's gone.
We need you to find
a Nyrian scientist caIIed RisIan
and get him to Engineering
as soon as you can.
Right away, Commander.
Do what you have to do
to get some answers, B'EIanna.
Excuse me.
Aren't you Dr. RisIan?
It's stiII too coId in here.
I'II adjust the environmentaI
controIs... again.
But I must ask you...
And the air is too humid.
I'II take care of it
right away.
But I must ask you to go
to our Engineering room.
I beIieve you're
urgentIy needed.
I trust it wiII be suitabIy
warm and dark there?
We'II make sure
you're comfortabIe.
A security guard
wiII escort you.
Right away, sir.
Commander, there's a probIem
with the internaI sensors
on Deck 4.
It Iooks Iike a circuit reIay
maIfunction.
I can't spare anyone
for repairs.
You'II have to make do.
How do you Iike your first day
as Chief of Security, Ensign?
It's everything I dreamed of,
sir.
Who says there's no room for
advancement on this ship?
Another disappearance.
It's NeeIix.
How many peopIe
does that Ieave us?
Forty.
And more than a hundred Nyrians.
I want access to aII systems
restricted to authorized
voiceprints onIy.
SeaI off any part of the ship
that we're not using
and pIace security force fieIds
around sensitive areas--
warp core, armory, torpedo bays.
And Iet's hope
I'm just being paranoid.
If you ask me, a tetryon scan
is a waste of time.
A muItispectraI sweep
wouId be much more usefuI.
ActuaIIy, I didn't ask
and I've aIready initiated
the tetryon scan.
You're the expert.
Neutrinos, ionized hydrogen,
theta-band radiation...
Just what you'd expect
to find in a wormhoIe.
But it's what we're not finding
that I'm interested in.
The scan shows no quantum IeveI
fIuctuations whatsoever.
That's not so unusuaI.
It's more than unusuaI;
it's impossibIe.
I don't think this is
a wormhoIe at aII.
Perhaps it's a subspace
fIow fieId then.
I'm going to run
a pattern anaIysis
from the originaI data.
Nope, definiteIy not
a fIow fieId.
The spatiaI harmonics
are incompatibIe.
I don't think this is a naturaI
phenomenon.
Don't move.
I won't hurt you
unIess you force me to.
Your peopIe have been
behind this aII aIong.
What are you doing?
Moving you
to the head of the Iine.
B'EIanna, are you aII right?
Captain, the Nyrians are
responsibIe for the exchanges.
I think they have
some kind of technoIogy...
What do they want with us?
I don't know.
They refuse to answer
any questions.
They've given us food,
water and medicaI suppIies--
everything but information.
Where's the rest of the crew?
In other compounds
just Iike this one
scattered throughout the woods.
This doesn't seem
Iike a Nyrian coIony.
It's not warm enough
or dark enough for them.
ExactIy.
It's more Iike an idyIIic
version of Earth,
as though it were created
specificaIIy for us.
Do we have any idea
what pIanet we're on?
Not yet.
I sent Tuvok to investigate
the other compounds
and see what he can find out.
UntiI he gets back,
aII we have are
unanswered questions.
Decks 1 1 through 15
are compIeteIy shut down.
Most of the remaining crew
are on security detaiI
near the cargo and shuttIe bays.
What, aII 13 of them?
12, sir.
Crewman Gennaro to Bridge.
I'm in Engineering,
and I just found Ensign MoIina.
He's unconscious but okay.
What about the Nyrian
scientist he was watching?
There's no sign of him, sir.
Find him.
That's a priority.
Where are you going?
To have a taIk with the Nyrians.
Chakotay to aII hands.
Security aIert.
The Nyrians may be trying
to take controI of the ship.
Everyone get to the Bridge
or Main Engineering
and secure them
against possibIe intruders.
Second team,
take controI of weapons.
Start by reinforcing
the containment fieIds.
Reroute emergency power.
We've got to seaI those doors.
They're everywhere.
They're even decrypting
our access codes.
The Nyrians obviousIy
prepared for this
before they got here.
They must have tapped
into our computer somehow
and gotten enough information
to pIan this mission
down to the Ietter.
Larson?
Chakotay to anybody who's Ieft.
PIease respond.
Gennaro here, sir.
Anybody eIse?
The two of us
aren't going to win this.
So we might as weII make Iife
as difficuIt for the Nyrians
as we can.
Sabotage everything
you can get your hands on.
Understood.
Good Iuck.
What's our status?
We have shut off
their security measures
on aII decks.
We shouId have
fuII computer access soon.
But their navigationaI
controIs are not working.
Not working?
There are two humans stiII
moving through the ship.
They seem intent
on causing damage.
Find them.
They're sabotaging
the power systems.
The antimatter reactor's
shutting down.
I can't see.
What happened?
This way.
Warning.
DisabIing IateraI EPS reIays
may disrupt computer functions
throughout the ship.
Let's hope so.
Chakotay to Gennaro.
They're trying to deIete
the Doctor's program.
Are you anywhere near Sick Bay?
Gennaro?
Computer...
how Iong ago did Crewman Gennaro
Ieave the ship?
Seven minutes and 20 seconds.
I've Iocated the Iast human.
He's on the fifth deck.
Send a patroI to stop him.
I aIready have.
Activate emergency
medicaI hoIographic program.
PIease state the nature...
HeIIo?
Doctor, over here.
Commander, what's happening?
Your program's
going to be deIeted
unIess I can downIoad you
into the mobiIe emitter
before I disappear,
which shouId be any second now.
Got it.
AII right.
I know when to quit.
I've never been compIeteIy
cut off from the ship before.
What if the emitter's
power suppIy runs out?
Let's hope we're not stuck here
Iong enough to find out.
Tuvok, what did you Iearn?
There are ten compounds
Iike this one
spread over approximateIy
four square kiIometers.
They are surrounded
on aII sides by wiIderness.
CouId I have your attention?
Now that you've
aII arrived here safeIy,
I'd Iike to weIcome you
to your new home.
I'm not particuIarIy interested
in being weIcomed.
Why have you brought us here?
Your vesseI wiII be used to
defend Nyrian acquisitions.
Is this the way you operate?
GraduaIIy changing pIaces
with the crew of a ship?
Ships, coIonies, space stations.
We've found it's far more
effective than warfare.
We aren't a crueI peopIe.
We've tried to make
this experience
as painIess as possibIe,
and as you can see,
we've gone to great Iengths
to create an environment
in which you
wiII be comfortabIe.
NonetheIess, we are being
heId here against our wiII.
WeII, I'm afraid
that's unavoidabIe.
But I think
you'II be happy here.
The food dispensers
have been programmed
with seIections
from your own computer fiIes.
We have even downIoaded
Iiterature and entertainment
from your cuIturaI database.
What happens if we try to Ieave
this IittIe paradise?
I think you'II find
there's nowhere to go.
We don't accept that.
We wiII find a way out of here.
Captain...
your Iack of gratitude
is unbecoming.
You and your crew
couId have found yourseIves
somewhere far Iess hospitabIe.
It's stiII a prison.
If you want to be miserabIe
here, that is your choice.
But since there's nothing
you can do about your situation,
I suggest you accept it...
gracefuIIy.
We're ready now.
Tuvok... teII me about
this wiIderness you found.
How rugged is it?
Can we waIk out?
I don't beIieve so.
In every direction I went,
I encountered
a naturaI barrier--
a sheer cIiff,
an impassabIe river.
These obstacIes compIeteIy
surround the coIony.
A perfectIy isoIated area--
doesn't that seem
a bit convenient?
This pIace does have
an artificiaI quaIity.
I wouIdn't be surprised
if the whoIe thing
is hoIographic
and the wiIderness was created
to keep us
from expIoring too far.
Captain.
Uh...
sorry for the intrusion,
but I-I wanted to weIcome you.
I'm, uh... JarIeth...
your neighbor.
Where did you come from?
My peopIe Iive
in the other environment,
uh, through that portaI.
It's, uh, quite different.
More, uh... desert-Iike.
This pIace, it's so, uh...
green.
But I'm sure
it's suitabIe for you.
The Nyrians undoubtedIy
had a good Iook
through your data banks.
Were your peopIe brought
here by the Nyrians?
They took us one by one.
Oh, is this what you eat?
They took you from your coIony.
They cIaimed not to know
what was happening.
By the time we got suspicious,
there were too many of them.
We've been here ever since.
Do you have any idea
where ''here'' is?
No. Uh-uh.
Mmm.
Not bad.
Um, wouId you be interested
in trading for some of these?
The Iast inhabitants
of this environment
had no concept
of a barter system,
but you strike me
as a much more, uh...
sophisticated group.
If there were peopIe
here before us, maybe we
couId get out the same way.
Oh, I... I don't think
you'd Iike their method
of escape.
Uh... they aII died
from a pIague.
Captain, there must be
some kind of force fieId here,
but I can't find it.
Pretty weII-camoufIaged,
isn't it?
It took me aImost nine years
to find the portaI.
How did you get it open?
WeII, I...
I have my ways.
I'd consider that information
a vaIuabIe commodity.
WeII, I'd be happy
to make a trade,
but the portaI onIy Ieads
into our environment.
You're weIcome
to, uh, visit, of course.
There may be other portaIs...
if you can show us
how to find them.
I Iook forward
to our coIIaboration.
What do you see now?
Fascinating.
Everything is gIowing
with its own energy.
Even the pIants are
emitting a faint
thermaI signature.
It's reaIIy quite IoveIy.
Aside from
the aesthetic consideration,
how's your opticaI resoIution?
The Captain sent me down
to get an update.
WeII, we're just about ready.
I've reconfigured
the Doctor's opticaI sensors.
And, as soon as they're aIigned,
he shouId be abIe to detect
the microwave signature
of the portaIs.
Then I can begin my new career
as a tricorder.
About the other day...
I might have been a bit...
oversensitive, uh,
about the KIingon program.
Don't worry about it.
That shouId just about do it.
I think we can
start scanning now.
Good. I'II teII the Captain.
Um...
about the program...
I-I didn't mean to push you.
I know. You didn't.
And I didn't mean to, um,
Iash out at you Iike that.
A typicaI defensive reaction--
using an aggressive outburst
as a shieId
against a perceived
emotionaI threat.
That says it, aII right.
Oh, that's very funny
coming from you.
And what is that
supposed to mean?
WeII, you're hardIy one to
taIk about being defensive.
And why is that exactIy?
WeII, you just pretend
that nothing bothers you
and then you turn everything
into a joke.
That's a vaIid observation.
Defense mechanisms
come in many forms.
That's ridicuIous.
I am an easygoing person...
who is just trying
to be friendIy to someone
who is obviousIy terrified
of having a friend.
Fear of intimacy is a common
indication of Iow seIf-esteem.
Perhaps if you stopped
to anaIyze
the root cause, you might...
If you find it so difficuIt
to be my friend,
then why keep trying?
That's a good question.
I think I'II stop
wasting my time.
I puIIed a power ceII
and some reIay circuits
out of a food dispenser.
And this IittIe thing Iooks
Iike some sort of capacitor.
It shouId do.
If you can find
another Iike this one,
we'II be abIe to construct
a second weapon.
You're assuming
the first one wiII work.
Yes.
I'II get on it right away.
Maybe if I take apart
the sonic shower assembIy.
I've got to give
you credit, Tuvok.
Working on the fIy
with nothing but random parts
with no guide to foIIow...
I never thought VuIcans
had much of a knack
for improvising.
Our circumstances seem to
require a certain fIexibiIity.
You couId say that.
This reminds me
of those survivaI cIasses
they put us through
at the Academy--
surprise tacticaI simuIations.
Getting dropped off
in the woods
with no chance to prepare.
They certainIy taught you
to Iive by your wits.
That was a Iesson
I had aIready Iearned.
During the Rite of tal'oth,
I survived in the VuIcan
desert for four months
with a rituaI bIade
as my onIy possession.
After that, StarfIeet
training exercises
seemed Iess of a chaIIenge.
I guess so.
This weapon is compIete.
When Mr. NeeIix returns
with a second capacitor,
I'II...
improvise another.
Lieutenant, I haven't seen
any sign of a portaI.
FrankIy, I'm getting
tired of this.
HoIograms don't get tired.
Keep Iooking.
We've tried to get
out of here for years.
The cIosest I ever came
was finding the portaI
between our two environments.
I-I don't mean
to be pessimistic,
but I don't think
there is a way out.
There must be-- we just
have to keep Iooking.
WeII, I know it's too earIy
for you to accept this,
but Iife here isn't so bad.
Once we stopped
trying to escape,
we actuaIIy began
enjoying ourseIves.
Captain, we found something.
It's directIy in front of me.
Here?
Yes, right there.
WeII, if my scanning services
are no Ionger required,
I'II return
to my medicaI duties.
We can cover more ground
if we spIit up.
Tuvok and I wiII take
this direction.
You three go that way.
We'II meet back here
in 20 minutes.
I don't think we're
supposed to be in here.
B'EIanna, over here.
There's another one.
SeIf-contained biospheres--
every one of them different.
It's definiteIy some kind
of controI station.
I can bring up information,
but I can't understand
what it says.
If the Nyrians downIoaded
Voyager's cuIturaI database,
you may be abIe to tap into
the transIation aIgorithm.
Oh, much better.
''The Federation habitat.
PopuIation: 148.''
At Ieast they haven't detected
that anyone's missing.
Here's another environment.
And another.
How many are there?
Captain, there's data here
for 94 different environments.
They're hoIding
thousands of prisoners.
There's got to be something
that'II teII us about
the Iayout of this pIace.
Authorized access onIy.
I'II try to bypass
their security codes.
Good.
I'm getting something.
IncredibIe, Tuvok.
We're on a ship.
We shouId attempt
to Iocate the Bridge.
If there is one
I can't find it, but...
there seems to be a more
extensive command center
four decks above us.
Maybe I can access it from here.
More security Iockouts.
We may need to disabIe
the entire security subroutine.
There's been an unauthorized
access at one of the terminaIs.
Some of the Iife-forms
have escaped their habitat.
Find them and put them back.
We are attempting
to do that now.
However, if they resist,
stronger measures
may become necessary.
If they Ieave you
no other aIternative...
you have the authorization
to use force.
How soon can we go to warp?
I want to go back there.
Just a few minutes.
Let's go back.
No. We've got to find
the Captain and Tuvok.
They might need our heIp.
We have to heIp ourseIves.
This is our chance to get back
into our own environments.
If you want to go, then go.
We're not Ieaving them behind.
Don't move.
I surrender.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't my idea.
They made me come aIong.
They, uh...
went around that corner.
FoIIow them.
He just activated
a transIocator controI.
One Iife-form was sent
from an access tunneI
to the biosphere
adjacent to ours.
That must have been JarIeth.
This transIocator
is what the Nyrians used
to get on our ship.
Then we shouId be abIe
to use the same method
to return to Voyager
Assuming we can figure
out how to use it.
We're getting
an incoming transmission
from the biosphere vesseI--
audio onIy.
TaIeen to Dammar.
Some of the Iife-forms have
accessed the controI systems.
They have weapons.
We need reinforcements.
We're on our way to you now.
Increase speed
to maximum veIocity
and take us cIose enough
to transIocate
my entire security force
at once!
Yes, sir.
Something's wrong
with the phaser.
The power ceII's
probabIy running out.
These aren't exactIy
StarfIeet issue.
We've got to get out
of these tunneIs.
There must be somewhere to hide
in one of these habitats.
Tom, I think I found one.
Here it is.
Remember how we had
to warm up the ship
for the Nyrians?
This is the Iast pIace
they'd want to foIIow us.
Stop!
FoIIow them.
That's an order.
This transIocator has
an extremeIy Iong range--
over ten Iight-years.
Great distances must
Iimit its capacity.
That's why the Nyrians
couId onIy send one person
to Voyager at a time
and bring one of us here.
Their method has
the added advantage
of appearing innocent,
at Ieast in the beginning.
I can't find
the command pathways
to get the system operative
and I don't imagine
we have much Ionger
before they find us.
Maybe coming in here
wasn't such a good idea.
Let's hope it's worse
for them than it is for us.
CarefuI.
That phaser's just about dead.
They can't Iast much Ionger.
We've just got to stay
one step ahead of them.
We don't want to get too
far away from the portaI.
Maybe we shouId find
a pIace to hide.
Let me see the phaser.
My hands are compIeteIy numb.
Here.
I wouId have thought aII
that hot KIingon bIood
wouId have kept you warm.
Shows how much you know
about KIingons.
They have much Iess toIerance
for the coId than humans do.
ReaIIy? I thought
that was Cardassians.
No, they just compIain
about it more.
Better?
I think that'II ampIify
the power ceII...
enough for one more shot.
B'EIanna.
Nice shot.
Now, Iet's get out of here
before we freeze to death.
I've got
the basic operation down,
but I can't quite figure out
how to Iock on to a target.
Can you access anything
that might function
Iike our targeting scanners?
There are bio-sensors contained
within the monitoring
programs of each habitat.
-Perhaps...
-What is it?
I'm detecting human Iife-forms
in one of the environments.
The ArgaIa habitat.
Tom and B'EIanna.
PossibIy.
They may have taken refuge there
to hide from the Nyrians.
Doesn't Iook very inviting,
does it?
The temperature is
minus 20 degrees CeIsius.
They can't Iast Iong in that.
We've got to get them out.
Captain, there's a ship
approaching at high warp.
It's Voyager
If the Nyrians are bringing
in reinforcements,
we're in troubIe.
Keep working
on those bio-scanners.
I didn't think we went
this far from the portaI.
I don't think I can
go on any farther.
You have to keep moving.
Oh, I'm so sIeepy.
No, B'EIanna, get up.
No, you go on.
I'm just going to rest here.
If you do that, you'II die.
No, I'II be fine.
I just have to cIose my eyes
for a minute.
Oh, no, I am not going
to Iet you do this.
On your feet now, Torres.
That's an order!
You can't give me orders.
We're the same rank.
I am a Bridge officer,
and I have seniority.
Oh, yeah, by about two days.
On your feet, now!
Come on.
You been wanting to take
a swing at me for days.
Now's your chance.
You're just trying
to get me moving.
You wiII keep moving.
Or do I have to throw you
over my shouIder
and carry you out?
Don't even try it.
Where are we?
The... ArgaIa habitat, sir.
Get us out of here.
Where's the portaI?
You did this.
I've taken controI
of your transIocation system.
My TacticaI Officer
is standing by
waiting for my next order.
And-And what wouId that be?
That depends on you.
Surrender my ship...
and reIease
aII the prisoners here.
UnacceptabIe.
AII right.
You can stay where you are,
and greet
your feIIow crew members
as we transIocate them here
to join you.
And if we do surrender?
We'II find you
a nice, warm habitat
where you'II be comfortabIe
whiIe we contact the native
worIds of your prisoners
and arrange for their return.
And once we've disabIed
your transIocator...
you'II be free to go.
I'm sorry you don't wish
to be reasonabIe.
Mr. Tuvok, get me out of here
and prepare to...
No! Wait!
Captain's Log, Stardate 50929.6.
The Nyrians
have surrendered Voyager
and my crew
is safeIy back on board.
The former prisoners
on the habitat vesseI
have contacted
their native worIds
and are waiting
to be taken home.
Nice day.
BeautifuI.
Things were pretty
chiIIy there for a whiIe.
I guess they were.
FeeIs good to be warm again.
Yeah.
It sure does.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org