Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Hey, watch where you're
going, you old klutz...
- Sorry. Sorry.
- You gonna pick that up?
Pervert.
You're late. l've been
looking all over for you.
l slept right through the alarm clock.
That baby kept me up all night.
- What baby?
- l don't know. Our neighbors have a kid?
Our neighbors are 90 years old.
You want to try and get
the paint on the canvas.
l like it messy.
Oh, yeah?
l gotta go.
Hey-
l just start drinking
and doing a lot of,like, pills.
'Cause then it just kills the pain,
and then l can just deal with it later.
l'm just saying- l'm not
telling you to go drink.
l know you go to meetings.
l'm just telling you what works for me, okay?
lt's hard to deal with those feelings.
Well, drinking kills feelings. That's why.
lt's gonna hail this afternoon.
You think?
Looks pretty sunny to me.
Who the fuck are you?
l'm Dr. Sam Foster.
You must be Henry.
Where's Dr. Levy?
Didn't she get in touch with you?
No.
Oh, l'm sorry.
She's away for a while.
- l'm covering for her.
- She's away where?
She's not feeling well.
She'll be back in a couple of weeks.
What are you-
a substitute shrink?
l guess you could call me that.
Oh.
This is her office.
Yeah, we share it. l'm only here
a few hours a week. Please take a seat.
Oh, l see.
So you treat the, uh...
depressed investment bankers,
paranoid housewives all week?
Come up here to do
a little pro bono work?
lt's the other way around.
The bankers are paranoid,
and the housewives are depressed.
Now,you're a junior at the college.
ls that right? Majoring in fine art?
She passed me off to you, huh?
You get the hard cases.
Does it make you uncomfortable
that l'm filling in for her?
She was trying to help me.
l'll try and help you too.
She afraid of me?
ls that why she's gone?
Did l scare her?
Should she be afraid of you?
l've read your file.
And can l read your file?
Tell me why you're here.
l thought you read the file.
You torched your car.
Why?
l don't remember.
l just woke up...
and l was in the car,
and it was on fire.
ls that something you do-
set fires?
l didn't mean to hurt anybody.
Who did you hurt?
l don't know.
l'm gonna go.
No. Please, sit down.
We have more time.
No, l, uh- l'm gonna go home
before this hail starts.
The king of Poland goes hunting
in the woods with one ofhis assistants.
And they're looking around...
and suddenly on the other side
of the clearing a farmer walks by.
Hold still.
And the king raises his rifle,
and the farmer yells...
''l'm not a moose.''
The king shoots
and kills the guy...
and the assistant's shocked.
And he says...
''Sire, the man said,
l'm not a moose.''
''Oh, says the king.
l thought he said, l am a moose.''
lt's a joke.
No, l'm just trying
to figure out...
if l'm the king or the farmer.
You're the moose.
- l'm the moose?
- Yeah.
Well, l appear to be the moose.
- lt's shit.
- lt's not shit.
lt's not shit.
Still there.
Sometimes l forget.
They're from another life.
Oh, my God.
l love this song.
l know you. Psych 221.
Professor Azzopardi?
You did that presentation on psychosis
and Tristan Reveur, right?
No smoking on the train.
Look at the sign, fella.
No smoking.
Capisce? Put it out.
''Capisce''?
Put out the fucking cigarette.
You oughta be locked up,
you asshole.
Beth? Sam. l hope
you're getting some rest.
Look, l met with your
patient today- Henry Letham.
l'd really like
to talk to you about him.
Give me a call, okay?
l wanna hear your voice.
You don't think it's a little odd-
predicting a hailstorm like that?
So he watches the Weather Channel.
No. l looked in the newspaper.
There was nothing about hail today.
How's Beth?
l don't know.
She hasn't returned any of my calls.
She always kinda
liked you, didn't she?
What, are you jealous?
Of Beth?
- l'm just faking it.
- Your students love you.
My students love me
'cause l give 'em all A's.
l mean, what the fuck do l know?
This kid could be the next Rothko.
Tell me l'm good.
You're good.
Tell me they'll remember me.
Who's ''they''?
The world.
ls that what you want?
The world will remember you.
Now take off your clothes.
Hey.
Who did that?
My girlfriend.
Where'd you get that?
This? l bought it.
Henry, what are you
doing here? l-
l wasn't expecting you.
l have someone coming in.
So, have you considered
a career in meteorology?
Hmm?
The weatherman
said something about hail?
The weatherman?
No.
You know, l can't even
listen to him anymore?
l don't understand a word
that comes out of his mouth.
You don't understand
the weatherman?
No.
But you do?
Sure. He says rain,
l bring an umbrella.
Henry, give me something.
l'm good at what l do.
Well, l'm hearing voices now.
Voices?
They come and they go,
but when they are there-
You're hearing them now?
Okay.
Can you write down
what they're saying?
- Yeah?
Hey, Dr. Foster. lt's Frederick.
Can you read it to me?
- Hmm?
- Can you read it to me?
Uh, yeah.
''Hey, Dr. Foster. lt's Frederick.''
This is-This voice isn't in your head.
This is a real voice.
Okay. Well, l don't know.
Maybe you could show me
how to tell the difference?
Go on.
l don't know.
''l didn't move him.
l know you're not supposed to move 'em.''
''l can't watch anymore.''
''Stay with me, Henry.
Stay with me.''
Hey, guys. Sorry
to interrupt, but, uh-
Hey, Frederick,
can you give me a minute?
- l've got a conference call at 11:00.
-Just a minute. Thank you.
Yeah, okay.
Where's this from?
Oh, l burned myself.
You burned yourself? Why?
Practicing for hell.
Why do you think
you're going to hell?
Um...
'cause of what l did.
What l'm gonna do.
What are you gonna do?
You're gonna try and kill yourself?
And how seriously should l take that?
Saturday at midnight
is when l'm gonna do it.
You gotta know that
everything just changed.
lf you talk to me about suicide,
l'm required to take certain actions.
Hey, look.Just wait a second.
Wait a second.
Just, you know, deal with him...
and, uh, we'll talk
about it next time.
There's a next time?
Yeah.
Yeah, we got three days.
He's coming! He's coming!
l am not a monster, goddamn you!
Get off of me!
Nobody's calling you a monster,
Daisy. Come on now.
Please! You said you would-
l don't deserve this!
Well, if you'd just remember to take your pills,
you wouldn't have to go through this.
- l'm not a monster. l'm lovable.
- l know you are.
l'm lovable. Stop!
- No, please! l'm lovable.
- Very lovable.
He's coming!
l oughta know he's coming!
l'll be good. l'll be good!
l don't want to- No!
- Hey, Sammy.
- Hey.
He's just a kid!
Okay, now.
Let go, Daisy.
He's just a kid!
Sorry about that.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah. l'm used to dealing
with neurotic stockbrokers.
Neurotic stockbrokers pay better.
So, uh, what brings you
to Club Meds?
l have a student
threatening to kill himself.
Christ. Well, tell him
to take a number.
Look, you know how it works.
lf he threatens to hurt
himself or someone else...
then we can take him in,
but we can't hold him here forever.
He said he's gonna
do it on Saturday.
lf you take him in now,
he'll be out by then.
Organized kid.
He's got it all scheduled.
Saturday, midnight.
That's what he said.
We can pick him up Friday,
hold him for the weekend.
As you can see, it's
not a real fun process.
Anything you could do to avoid it?
- What have you got him on?
- He won't take any meds.
Where's my man?
You know what l've
been craving all day?
Something to drink.
What's the matter?
You're looking a little tense.
lt's nothing.
So tell me about nothing.
l'm just tired.
Let me make a call,
and then we can take a bath together.
Beth, it's Sam again.
Um, l hope
you're getting some rest.
Everyone's been asking about you.
Look, give me a call.
l want to speak to you about Henry Letham
and find out how you're feeling, okay?
Bye.
You sound like you're talking
to one of your patients.
- ls she sick?
- She's exhausted.
Exhausted?
Come on. We live in New York City.
Everyone's exhausted.
- What, is that a code word?
Yeah.
Yeah, l guess it is.
How's the kid with the hail?
Ever heard of
doctor-patient privilege?
What's the prediction
tomorrow? Locusts?
He's confused.
Confused?
ls that like exhausted?
l don't want to get
into this right now.
You told me about the lawyer
who thought her cat was talking to her.
l shouldn't have.
He wants to kill himself.
That's it, isn't it?
That's why you won't talk about it.
- He has a right to confidential counseling.
- Come on, Sam.
He wants to kill himself
on Saturday night.
At midnight, like it's a date.
What's so special about Saturday?
l didn't have time to ask.
Look, we can talk
about it, you know.
lt doesn't scare me.
- lt scares me.
- Yeah, l know.
But you have to trust me.
l do.
- Up slow,Jerry.
- Got it.
- Looking good, Mikey.
- Not  - Not so fast.
- Stop that swaying.
- Come on, Mommy. Faster.
Easy. Easy. Hold it!
Stay clear, you guys. Quick.
Wait! Wait! My balloon!
Sorry, kid.
lt's gone to balloon heaven.
Oh, that's okay, sir.
We're gonna get another one at the park.
- Go ahead, honey.
- Promise, Mommy?
All right, you guys.
Comin' your way.
Tristan Reveur once said...
''lf we cannot see the wind,
we can see the wind's will.''
Here, Pradilla Ortiz forces us
to imagine the wind...
by showing its effect
on the smoke...
the candle flames
and Dona Juana's veil.
Only the victims' faces are
visible in Goya's masterwork.
Our eyes are drawn
to the brightest spot on the canvas-
the white shirt of a doomed man
pleading for his life.
Behind him, the hill closing in...
refusing a path to escape.
- The Dead Toreador was originally
part of a larger painting...
lncident in a Bullfight.
After the painting was mocked
by critics and viewers...
Manet angrily sliced it in half...
removing the fallen hero
from his arena...
and accidentally creating
one ofhis most enduring works.
- Hey.
How are you doing?
Oh, you know.
l didn't know if you'd still be coming
to class after what you told me.
Yeah, well, where else
am l gonna go?
Have you got a minute?
Sure.
Are any of these yours?
Ouch.
What?
Well, these are bad, so-
- Oh.
Do you know that Tristan Reveur quote
about bad art?
lt's ''Bad art is more tragically
beautiful than good art...
because it documents
human failure.''
Why'd do you want
to do it on Saturday?
lt's my 21st birthday.
l think the tradition
is to go out and get drunk.
Well, um, Tristan started
a different tradition.
What did he do?
He died.
What about your parents?
What about 'em?
Don't you think they care?
No.
Do they live around here?
They're over in Mahlus Gardens.
Mahlus Gardens-
Where is that?
lt's a cemetery in Jersey.
- l thought you read the file.
- l'm sorry.
l did.
lt didn't mention that.
lt's a little out of date.
Do you have any other family?
No.
Girlfriend?
You talked to her?
No.
Who is she?
No, you're not talking to her.
l thought you were talking
about this waitress...
in this diner l used to go to
over on Canal Street.
Tell me about her.
When she filled up my cup of coffee,
she would ask me how l was doing.
Waitress things, you know.
lt doesn't really constitute a girlfriend.
Did you ever get her name?
Yeah, it was Athena.
l was gonna marry her.
You were gonna marry her?
Yeah. l bought her
a ring and everything.
lt looked just like the one
that you got your girl.
l didn't steal your ring,
Henry, okay? l promise.
Yeah, l lost it.
Anyway, she's gone.
- She's gone?
- Yeah.
- Or she's somewhere else?
- What do you mean?
There is no somewhere else.
He's not going to make it.
- lt's beautiful.
- No.
lt's like the crap
tourists buy on Fifth Avenue.
- You talk with your student today?
- Mm-hmm.
Still wants to do it?
l don't feel right talking about it.
Talking about it with me, you mean.
You stopped taking your pills.
l've been counting.
You haven't taken one in weeks.
l don't need 'em anymore.
Well, that's a decision
we should've made together.
l can't paint on meds.
l can't.
- Well, it makes me nervous.
l'm not happy
you did this in secret.
Well, l'm not happy
you're counting my pills in secret.
We have to trust each other.
Hey, look at me.
l can't make them disappear.
l wish l could.
l made you a promise.
l gotta go.
l'll see you at home.
Henry?
Forgetting something?
- What's the matter?
- You just called me Henry.
- Baby, l think l know your name by now.
- Yeah, but you called me Henry.
Sam, l know who you are.
l promise.
Sorry.
Okay.
Do you get nervous?
lt's a great part,
but she should resist more.
- She just takes his abuse and walks into the river.
- You should use that.
- All without a fight.
- Can we come and see you?
- Henry, that would be nice, wouldn't it?
- Yeah, Mom.
We could all go together.
King's rook to E-3.
Mm-hmm.
How's Lila?
She's good. Oh,
l got something for her.
- Mm-hmm.
- Give me your hand.
Ah.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
l hear she's a beautiful girl.
How long have you
been carrying that around?
A while.
What are you waiting for?
The fear to go away, l guess.
Mm.
How do l know she won't try again?
You don't know, Sam.
Does she make you happy?
Oh, yes.
Well, here's something that won't.
Knight to C-3.
Check.
- Oh, shit.
Do you remember the dream
of the burning boy referred to by Freud?
- Vaguely.
- Vaguely meaning no?
- Right.
- Yeah.
Well, he describes a man
whose child is dying.
The father sits by the boy's bed
night after night...
and after the boy is dead,
they give him a wake.
And they set up a circle of candles
around the boy's body.
And the father's exhausted.
He falls asleep.
And he dreams that his son
is standing beside him...
holding his arm
and whispering...
''Father, can't you see
that l'm burning?''
- You have a visitor?
- Henry.
- l can come back.
- No, no. You're all right.
- l don't mind.
- Do you know Dr. Patterson?
- No.
- Pleased to meet you.
What's the matter, Henry?
What the fuck?
What are you doing here?
We're playing chess.
You're dead.
- Sam?
- l watched you die.
Sam, we'll finish this game later.
Sure.
- Where are you going?
- Henry, take a seat.
- Why'd you come back?
- Do you know Leon?
What did he say to you?
Did he say something about me?
No, he didn't say anything about you.
l don't think Leon even knows you.
That's my father.
He knows me.
Now, listen, l've known Leon a long time.
He doesn't have any children.
Don't say that! Don't
fuckin' say that to me!
What are you doing?
Do you think l don't
recognize my own father?
- You told me your father was dead.
- He is dead.
He's dead, and that's him
walkin' out the fuckin' door!
The man walking out the door
is alive and well.
What's happening?
l saw all the blood,
and l watched him die.
l did it.
lt's my fault.
Maybe you hurt someone,
but not Leon.
Who did you hurt?
Your father?
l don't remember.
Sometimes we don't want to remember,
but l think you have to try.
Fuck you! What the fuck
do you know!
You don't know anything!
Everything you know is a fuckin' lie!
- All right?
- Okay.
Tell me what the truth is.
Your troubles will cease,
and fortune will smile upon you.
Yes, Henry.
Henry?
Henry!
Henry, are you there?
Here we go.
Trouble.
- Henry, listen.
Stay with me, okay?
Listen to my voice, Henry.
- Stay with us here, all right?
- ls that your voice?
l didn't leave that message.
Probably someone who
sounds exactly like you.
So what do we do now?
Not much we can do
at this point.
We don't have the resources or the manpower
for a stakeout or anything like that.
l'll notify the police,
but they won't do anything.
Why not?
Because they've got more important things
to do than look for depressed college students.
Then l'll find him.
Well, if you do,
give me a call.
We'll pick him up for you.
But do me a favor, Sammy.
The kid hears voices
and carries a gun.
Watch your back.
Mommy, is that man
gonna die?
Come on, Bobby.
We're gonna be late.
You shouldn't run away from me like that,
you little monkey.
But is he gonna die?
Listen to this.
''Henry Letham has a fertile,
powerful imagination.
lf he maintains his concentration,
he will create new worlds with his art.''
Jim O'Shea?
Professor O'Shea, yeah.
How'd you know?
'CauseJim wants to fuck
every cute boy in his class.
- Did you ever hear of an artist
named Tristan Reveur?
- Yeah, of course.
- Do you like his work?
- l've never seen it. Nobody has.
He burned all his paintings
before he killed himself.
- He killed himself?
- Mm-hmm.
When he was 18, he told everyone
he'd live three more years...
then go to New York
and kill himself.
And that's exactly what he did.
Left a one-line note:
''Un suicide elegant
est l'oeuvre d'art finale.''
''An elegant suicide is
the ultimate work of art.''
Ah,Jesus.
He's Henry's favorite artist.
Of course he is.
Let me talk to him.
Talk to him?
First l've gotta find him.
He'll find you. He knows you can help him.
That's exactly why he keeps coming back to you.
Well, even if he does,
l can't let you talk to him.
l'd violate every rule in the book.
So violate them. You have something, Sam.
This kid trusts you.
But you've never stood where
he's standing right now, and he knows that.
Yeah, but l treat people every day
with conditions l've never experienced myself.
You know, the day l did it...
l took two razor blades
to the bathtub.
You know why?
Because l knew that
once l started to bleed, l'd get weak...
and l didn't want to drop one blade
and leave myself half done.
Can you imagine that?
Can you imagine hating
your life so much...
that you want to bring
a backup razor?
So what do l tell him?
There's too much beauty to quit.
Tell him that.
There's too much goddamn beauty.
Eat something.
l'm not hungry.
Eat your fortune cookie.
lt's yours.
''Your troubles will cease,
and fortune will smile upon you.''
Not a moment too soon.
What's the matter?
- Beth, it's Sam.
-  l didn't touch him.
- Beth? Beth?
- l know you're not supposed to move-
Beth?
lt's me.
Are you okay?
l'm gonna turn on the light, okay?
l know Leon's been trying
to get through to you.
And Toni.
Oh,Jesus.
- Beth, are you gonna talk to me?
What do you want to talk about?
How are you feeling?
What do you really
wanna talk about?
l'm worried about you...
and l wanna know more
about Henry Letham.
l didn't touch him.
l know you're not
supposed to move them.
What does that mean?
l wanna kiss you.
Do you want to play a kissing game?
Beth.
No. You're loyal.
You're a good dog.
Good, loyal dog, Sam.
What's her name?
Lila?
You should've let her
bleed in the bathtub.
- She had the right idea.
- What are you talking about?
lt's highly inappropriate.
You're not supposed to fuck your patients,
even the pretty ones.
You know the rules.
- You can't drink while you're taking these.
- Mm. Apparently l can.
No, you can't. Come on, Beth.
l want you to come take a shower.
Bathe the corpse.
We won't really be corpses
though, will we?
lt will be more
like a memory of nothing.
What happened to you, Beth?
- l need to sleep, please.
- No, you got too much crap in your system.
Are you okay to shower?
- He's watching us.
- No, we're alone.
- He's watching.
- Are you still talking to him?
- Do you know where he is?
- Ask the mother.
- The mother's dead.
- ls she?
Ask anyway.
Hello? Hello? Yeah.
This is Sam Foster,
Dr. Sam Foster.
l'm a psychiatrist. Yeah.
l'm calling about a student
named Henry Letham.
He is?
This is very strange, Mrs. Letham.
He told me you had passed-
Hello? Hello?
- Damn it.
This is it.
l won't be long.
- l've been waiting for you.
Mrs. Letham?
l'm Dr. Sam Foster.
l'm sorry to bother you at this hour.
l thought you'd never come.
l would have come earlier.
l didn't know you were here.
lt's easy to forget about me...
all alone up here.
Your son's not well.
That's why l'm here.
l'm trying to find him.
l'm sorry to say he's threatened
to commit suicide.
You came to see Olive,
didn't you? Not me.
Olive?
There she is.
She's been lonely.
Me and Olive
keep each other company.
We've been alone in this house
for a thousand years.
Hey, Olive.
How are you doing, girl?
She doesn't remember you.
- Are you hungry?
- No.
Do you know
how to contact your son?
Are there any relatives or friends
he might have gone to see?
Let me fix you something to eat.
You stay with Olive.
There's some leftovers in the fridge.
Most days l don't say
a single word.
Sometimes l'm silent so long,
l forget how to speak.
Mrs. Letham,
we have an emergency here.
You-
Do you hate me?
You must hate me.
ls that why you did it?
No, l don't hate you.
l'm here because
your son needs help.
l knew you'd come eventually.
lt's been quiet without you.
Lonely.
Mrs. Letham, who do you think l am?
Don't play games.
Not anymore.
Who am l?
You think l don't
know you, Henry?
recognize my only son?
Oh, Lord, l've missed you.
l've missed you so much.
l know you never
meant to hurt us.
- Mom?
- Yes, baby.
How did l hurt you?
lt doesn't matter anymore.
l could never stay angry with you.
What do l do on Saturdays?
When you were a boy,
you used to go to the zoo.
Remember? You loved
to watch the walrus swim.
But l'm older now.
lt's my 21st birthday tomorrow.
What'll l do for my birthday?
Who knows?
You don't tell me anything these days.
l guess you tell Athena
your secrets now.
Athena?
Do you remember where Athena lives?
Dogs are a big responsibility, darling.
- Look at the mess l'm making.
- l just have to clean it up.
- Let me see your head.
- You don't want to see.
- Mrs. Letham.
You didn't mean to hurt anyone.
You know you didn't.
Let me look at your head.
That's a serious wound.
- Don't look at me, darling. Don't-
- Olive, off!.
Let me fix you something to eat.
You're a bleeder, huh?
Here, maintain pressure on that.
Dr. Foster?
Could l have a word with you?
Yeah,you got bit up pretty good.
- Get your rabies shot already?
- Yeah.
Look, l'm, uh-
l'm Sheriff Kennelly.
Now, l-l know you already
spoke with Deputy Carlyle...
but l just wanted
to confirm a few things.
You said the, uh- the assault took place
at 9625 Rickover Street?
- That's right.
- The home belonging to the Letham family?
Right. Her dog attacked me,
and... she needs some help.
She has a severe head wound.
She should be in a hospital.
l went to high school
with Maureen Letham.
Oh, yeah? Maybe you know her son, Henry.
He's a patient of mine.
l remember Henry.
Pale, skinny kid, always drawing pictures.
- Yeah, that's him.
- He kind of gave me the creeps.
What's strange, Doctor-
What l'm trying to figure out is...
who you were speaking with
over there at 9625 Rickover Street.
l'm sorry. l thought we already
established Maureen Letham.
She told you her name
was Maureen Letham?
Yeah. We were talking
about her son.
She wasn't entirely coherent.
She needs medical assistance.
But why did you want to talk
to this woman at 1:00 in the morning?
Look, l'm treating her son.
lt's an emergency situation.
The- Sheriff, she needs help.
She's lost a lot of blood.
l told you l went to school
with Maureen Letham.
l also went to her funeral.
She's been dead for months.
Car wreck-
her and her husband.
As far as l know, that house is empty still.
The family's trying to sell it.
l spoke to Maureen Letham
an hour ago.
lt's probably just
someone's confused.
So how long they keeping you here?
l don't know. l gotta head back into the city.
Look, 9625 Rickover Street.
l was there.
Henry's mother was there.
All right, Dr. Foster.
We'll be in touch.
l've got your number.
Sheriff?
- Uh-huh.
- Mrs. Letham-
Did she have brown eyes?
Oh, no, sir.
Bluest eyes in town.
No, no, no, no, no.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org