Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
Always saying goodbye.
So I learned to be alone.
But with street dance,
I could step out in front of any crowd,
into any street dance battle,
and for one moment, be the hero.
And then, being alone didn't matter any more.
I was able to show off my moves,
taking on the local legends
in street dance battles.
And legends, they don't come
any bigger than this crew.
Two-times Final Clash Champions
and on their way to Paris to make it three.
Invincible.
Named after the biggest ego in street dance.
Vince.
Vince! Vince! Vince! Vince!
This was the moment,
right here in London.
The moment to take on the legend.
This was the moment to be the best.
This was my moment.
Or not.
Yeah, yeah. Is that all you got?
Some nerdy little popcorn boy
who can't even stay on his feet?
You got two months, Europe,
till the Final Clash.
Y'all better rustle up some new ideas.
Or we will kick ass.
You got that, Popcorn?
I was just trying to see the show.
Easy, easy, easy. Easy!
- What? You come to have a laugh too?
- No. I wanna be your manager.
I'm gonna help you put a crew together
for the Final Clash.
Right now is not a good time.
You know, you jumping in there
and falling on your arse was really, really...
I know. Really stupid.
No, inspiring. You showed a lot of courage.
- Thanks.
- Look, someone needs to stand up to Vince.
And that's why I think I'd be a top manager.
I can get you all the top dancers
you need to beat Invincible.
- Who are you?
- Hi. I'm Eddie.
Look, Eddie, thanks for your offer,
but Invincible are just that, invincible.
- Look, you're impulsive.
- I'm impulsive?
Yes, and you need to learn a bit of patience.
- Taxi.
- A bit of discipline.
- I could be your Yoda.
- Yoda?
Secondly, you're American and I'm European.
So you could use someone local.
Someone who understands the culture.
Like a tour guide.
Et trois, the Final Clash is in Paris.
And I speak fluent European.
Ooh-la-la, garcon, baguette,
fromage, croissant.
♪ Voulez-vous coucher avec moi?
♪ Ce soir? ♪
Okay, Yoda, what's the great plan?
We've got eight weeks before the Final Clash.
If we've got any chance
of beating them in Paris,
we need to get the top dancers in Europe.
- The mavericks, people like us, loners.
- Genuine freestylers.
People with their own moves
and their own styles.
We have to track them down
and convince them to join us.
Invincible think they've seen everything.
But what we've gotta do...
- We gotta show them that they haven't.
- Exactly.
If we wanna pull this off,
we need the best of the best.
La creme de la creme.
Do you have anyone in mind?
Eddie!
Next.
How about it?
You wanna take down Invincible?
Told you.
On my time? With my crew?
- So I guess that's a no?
- Damn right it is.
Seriously? You need to get yourself
a real manager.
Breakin' Point. Still hurts, doesn't it?
Police!
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Sorry.
- Oh!
- Ciao.
Whoa!
You, my friend, are wasting your talents.
We'd done it.
The perfect crew in the City of Love.
One big happy family.
- Ash, the food is disgusting.
- Yes, and nothing is halal.
The room sucks, the food sucks, and we
can't get sleep because of Tino snoring.
- Oi! I don't snore.
- Yes, you do.
Come on, Ash.
You're our mighty leader, right?
- Do something.
- Guys, guys, leave Ash alone.
- You want food?
- Yes.
Fill your boots.
If there's a problem,
I'm the manager, come see me.
Problem 101.
- Toilet's blocked.
- Yeah, he's right.
- Disgusting.
- Okay, Okay. Guys, quiet.
- ...is dirty.
Look, I understand conditions
are really rough.
But we've got a place to stay, we've got food.
- Yes, but...
- I'm working on the halal.
But we've only got six weeks
before the Final Clash.
So we've got to pull together as a crew
so we can win this.
- You still wanna win this, right?
- Yes!
- Yes, we wanna win.
- Let's eat.
I can't even believe that we got
every single person that we wanted.
- We are so on the money.
- Exactly, so on the money.
Now we got all the right ingredients
to take down Invincible, I'll tell you that.
All except one.
- Really funny.
- We've gotta think outside the box.
Well, there's outside the box
and then there's a whole other planet.
You'll see.
Please get us a drink.
Excusez.
Can I have une biere
et une Manu special, s'il vous plait?
Deux, trois, cinq...
Seize. Seize!
While Eddie struggled
with his terrible French,
I struggled with how on earth
Latin was going to help us beat Invincible
in a street dance battle.
And then I saw.
Hey! Oh, come on, help us out.
We're only a few Euros short.
Tell you what, if you can stay in the ring
for one dance with her,
I give you the drink.
- You speak English.
- Better than you, my friend.
- Wait, what do you mean, "stay in the ring"?
- If you can keep up with her for one dance.
- Like a battle?
- If you like.
Don't spill my drink.
Oi!
I'm sorry.
Best of luck.
Okay.
I'm sorry, I didn't catch your name.
Eva.
- You're absolutely amazing.
- I'm kind of busy.
That's what I call a battle.
Lucien, bye.
- I'll see you tomorrow. Bye!
- Okay.
Wish me luck!
Hi, again.
Hi.
I wanted to ask you something.
No, thank you.
You don't even know what it is yet.
Yeah, but I don't drink
and I'm not hungry, so good night.
Why do you dance?
I mean, I dance to have a good time,
have a laugh, show off.
But I made a real fool of myself recently
in front of a lot of people and...
- Should I start playing the violin?
- No.
'Cause my story has a happy ending.
I met you.
You know, I've heard some
cheesy pick-up lines in my time,
but this one beats them all.
Join my crew.
- Quoi?
- My street dance crew.
We're going to the Final Clash.
It's the biggest battle in Europe.
I'm happy doing my own thing.
We could come up with a whole new style,
like a fusion of Latin and street,
something that nobody has ever seen before.
So you want me to join a street dance crew,
dancing a style that hasn't been invented yet?
- Pretty much, yeah.
- You're an escaped crazy guy, right?
I prefer dreamer, but sure.
I tell you what, you bring me
this great crew and I'll think about it.
- Is that a promise?
- No, that's a "think about it".
That's good enough for me.
You were right, she is absolutely perfect.
With her and those moves,
Invincible won't even stand a chance!
Let me just get this clear.
This is a Latin-street-dance fusion
we're talking about here,
not an Ash-Eva fusion.
- Eva. That sounds really beautiful.
- Focus, Ash.
- We've still got to convince the crew.
- But they'll love the tango!
- Salsa!
- Salsa, tango, whatever.
Look, we'll show her the crew,
she'll love 'em, bam, we're unbeatable.
Bonjour.
It's that crazy guy again.
And my crew.
Oh, mon Dieu. This is not a refugee camp.
- Uncle, it's okay.
- We're closed.
It's okay.
You said you'd think about it.
Well, let's see what they can do.
♪ And now I feel like
I'm the reason I should last
♪ I move like my ish don't stink
♪ But I'm all in a trance, no hit, no assist
♪ This is all from the heart, intro, no script
♪ I'm just about writing it down
♪ So now I don't sleep, man
I miss those nights
♪ I take planes like trains
I don't miss no flights
♪ I'm the type of guy that will have no life
♪ Just so I can shine like this gold life
♪ And that sounds sad but I'm happy
♪ And the only plans to stay scatty
♪ Yeah, unorthodox,
I made the bar so I call the shots
♪ We don't follow no crowd, they follow us
♪ Don't follow no sound, it follows us
♪ Go sit in hell, look down that wishing well
♪ Unorthodox, we call our own shots
♪ Yeah, I got a good vibe
♪ I ain't trying to be bait with my hook lines
♪ I had a feeling I could fly
♪ Before I hopped on a plane or a new sky
♪ Yeah, I'm a good guy
♪ And if you heard otherwise, it's a true lie
♪ I'm hype, I don't do shy
♪ I bark up every tree and I do bite
♪ Psych, I'm only playing
♪ You all got freedom of speech,
I'm only saying
♪ I ain't got time for beef, I'm on the way in
♪ So the eighth day
of the week's my only lay in
♪ That sounds sad but I'm happy
♪ And the only plan's to stay scatty
♪ Yeah, unorthodox,
I made the bar so I call the shots
♪ We don't follow no crowd, they follow us
♪ Don't follow no sound, it follows us
♪ Go sit in hell, look down that wishing well
♪ Unorthodox, we call our own shots
♪ No one can hold us down again
I need an answer.
This is something we could be a part of.
"We"?
Me and my dance partner.
Lucien.
♪ We don't follow no crowd, they follow us
♪ Don't follow no sound... ♪
All right, playtime is over, thank you.
- Ciao.
- Listen up.
We've only got six weeks to get ready
for the Final Clash.
And if we want to win this, we gotta
come up with something that is so different
that Invincible won't have an answer.
Eva, Lucy...
Lucien.
Right. Lucien.
Take the floor.
Stop.
That's it.
I don't want to dance for these idiots.
- Ooh!
- Ciao.
That's granny style.
This is ridiculous, Ash.
I'm a B-boy.
Don't try and make us look stupid.
That went very well.
Eva, please.
Give us a chance.
Your friends have no manners.
I know, I know.
But they're good guys. It's just...
Street dance is all about front and reputation.
They just don't want to lose face.
But they don't...
They don't know what you do yet.
Well, go figure it out.
You see, a good idea is just an idea...
Until you make it work.
We're here to battle.
The crew couldn't understand
why I wanted the best street dancers
in Europe to do Latin.
But I wasn't giving up without a fight.
You guys are so stuck on what you know.
I had to persuade the crew to come back
to the club with me one more time.
All right?
Latin dance is vicious.
We hear you, man.
Thank you.
Well done.
I think we're definitely on again.
What makes you think
I want any more to do with you?
Well, you liked what you saw earlier
and you can see how this might work.
Pretty sure of yourself, aren't you?
I gotta be. I'm the leader of this thing.
Teach us some of it.
Then I want you in bed.
Your first lesson starts at 9:00.
In the morning.
If we were going to beat Invincible
at the Final Clash,
Eddie's Latin idea had to work.
For the first time in my life,
I was going to have to learn
how to dance with someone.
One, two, three and step.
Fingertips.
- One, two, three...
- Stop jiggling your shoulders.
Turn me a little bit slower.
No, okay, stop. You're showing off.
I'm just dancing.
No. You want to look good.
Get applause from the crowd.
But listen. You're not dancing with them,
you're dancing with me.
Again.
No. Reach out your hand.
Good.
This is a tough crowd.
Listen, salsa is not about
the choreography or the steps.
It's about the passion.
You have to feel it, mean it.
Yeah?
- Feel it?
- Yes.
Okay.
And one, two, three.
Good.
Now cross-body lead.
What are you doing?
We don't have that much time. I'm just...
Just teach me one of those tricks
that I can use against Invincible.
The basics first.
You've got a battle to prepare for.
If I can't trust you with the simple stuff,
how am I gonna trust you with the tricks?
I'm sorry.
Relax.
So I guess dinner is out of the question?
Good...
Good. Now cross-body lead.
Good.
Better.
Two times. And... Yeah.
Okay, good. Let's leave it there.
Um, Uncle, remember Ash?
Hard to forget.
Ash, Manu.
- Hello.
- Hi.
I'm going to be working with him.
It's okay to practise here, right?
Yeah, of course.
And his friends too?
They're practising in their hostel.
Sure. Why not?
- Thank you. I really appreciate that.
- My pleasure.
Well, I should probably head back
- and tell them the good news.
- Mmm.
- I'll see you out.
- Thank you.
- Eva's really incredible.
- Mmm.
You're gonna have to come down
- and see her in the battle.
- Mmm-hmm.
If you hurt her, I will break your legs.
Five, six, seven, let's go.
♪ If you wanna get with me
There's some things you gotta know
♪ I like my beats fast, and my bass down low
♪ Ba-ba-bass, bass, bass down low
♪ Bass, bass, bass down low
♪ I, I, I like my beats fast
And my bass down low
♪ Bass, bass down low
♪ Bass, bass, bass down low
♪ Bass, bass, bass down low,
low, low, low, low, low ♪
All right, everybody, take a break.
Take a break. Get some water.
- Can you please show me that step?
- Sure.
One, two, three and four.
- One, two, three and four.
- Yep, that's good.
Yo, Ash has been giving you
extra lessons, huh?
Well, I've been giving him extra lessons.
- Oh.
- So you like him?
As much as any of you.
- Oh.
- Yeah, right.
Let us know when you gonna find his tattoo.
Okay. Well, can you show me that step again?
- Okay.
- One, two, three and four.
Thanks, Steph. Take five.
Take a break. Come on.
You look great out there.
And your body is absolutely...
Perfect. For hip-hop.
And technical work.
Yep. Ca va.
Ca va.
Uncle, this feels great. It's amazing.
There's no rules. It feels free.
Well, listen, you be careful of him.
I know guys like that.
I was guys like that. Ooh!
Three weeks to the Final Clash,
and things were finally coming together.
Just one problem.
Shh! Wait, wait.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
♪ What's wrong with waking up everyday
♪ With great expectations?
♪ And grabbing all this life you can take
♪ With no limitations
♪ What's wrong with
giving in to your dreams?
♪ What's wrong with living them to extremes?
♪ Yeah, oh, yeah
♪ Yeah
♪ I want to get too much till I can't get enough
♪ I want to live it up
♪ Because I want to
♪ Don't want a little sip, I want to drink it in
♪ Every little bit
♪ I say, who says you can't
♪ Have it all
♪ Get what you want
♪ I've got a big dream, I want a big life
♪ Life's like a cake, I'll take a big slice
♪ Yeah
♪ Who says you can't have it all?
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
♪ Who says you can't have it all? ♪
- Try and relax a bit.
- I don't have time. I gotta own this thing.
Sorry. Let's just try it again.
Dance with your heart, not with your head.
You're still thinking like a soloist.
I want to try something.
It's an exercise in trust.
Do I get a last request?
People think tango is only about sex.
But it's about so much more.
It's about channelling your passion.
It's about precision,
control,
discipline.
Follow my movements
until you begin to sense them.
Tango is a shared language.
There are no secrets...
Careful of the tree! Stop!
No lies...
Just the dance.
Good.
Remember how that felt next time we dance.
I'll never forget.
I'm sorry if I've been a bit...
Unfriendly?
Over-professional.
Maybe we could have dinner.
It wouldn't hurt our dancing
to get to know each other a little better.
Smells great.
He is a one.
No, Uncle, he is a two.
Definitely a one.
Would somebody mind
explaining to me what's going on?
Uncle has a way ofjudging men.
It never fails.
He can tell what sort of man you are
by how many chillies you eat.
You are a one.
- So how many chillies do you usually have?
- Four...
- Serve it up.
- Ash? Seriously.
- Bon.
- He'll take two.
- Four.
- Ah!
- Ash, you don't have to prove anything.
No, no, no. No. I like hot food.
- I actually love hot food. It's great, yeah. Bon.
- Bon.
Merci.
Bon appetit.
It's really nice.
Oh, mon Dieu.
Are you okay?
Excuse me for a second.
Oh...
I like this man. Oh.
Oh, I like.
Sit down. Have some chilli.
Ai-ai-ai!
Whoo!
Junior!
Ole! Arriba!
Un, dos, tres.
Come here. Come on.
And... Boom-cha, boom-boom cha.
Oh, stop. Stop!
You think you're so funny, huh?
Listen. We are all street dancers.
Mambo, tango, salsa...
All started in the street.
But you... You have problem. Hmm?
You are afraid of your partners.
Boo.
Ah, yes, you joke. Yes, very funny.
Ha-ha-ha. Oh, yeah.
No, you hide. You hide behind your attitude.
Oh, you're so cool. Ah!
I dare you to get naked.
I'm not getting naked with you.
Not your body, but...
Maybe a little piece of your soul, hmm?
When I offer you this,
I don't just invite you to dance.
I ask you to trust me.
It's all right.
Come.
Remember, you're holding the most perfect,
the most beautiful creature in the world.
Now, the rhythm.
Ba-da-bah, ba-da-bah, ba-da-bah.
A man's job is to make the woman
look wonderful...
Let her shine,
so that the other men are envious.
They want her but they can't have her.
- Oh.
- Oh, yeah!
Yeah!
Thank you.
You try it.
Zut alors!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven...
♪ Come
♪ Together as one
♪ Let's come together as one
♪ Come
♪ Together as one
♪ Let's come together as one
♪ Together as one yeah!
♪ Come
♪ Together as one
♪ Together as one ♪
Only a couple of days till Final Clash.
I think we've nailed it!
I think we've got the crew to beat Invincible!
I couldn't have done it without you.
Shut up.
I see you've been
working your magic with Eva!
I did not. It's strictly professional.
- Strictly professional?
- Yeah.
You mean a strictly professional date,
under the strictly professional moonlight
in the most romantic city on Earth.
We'll just have dinner
and we're gonna talk about the routine.
Talk about the routine.
You know, just imagine Vince's face
when you and Eva drop that Latin fusion.
Trouble was, I could imagine
Vince's face, all too clearly.
I knew he'd be in Paris by now,
preparing for the Final,
and I couldn't shake the memory
of my popcorn humiliation.
You're quiet tonight.
I'm just thinking.
What if people don't get it?
I mean, our street Latin fusion.
Dancing when it's just us is one thing but...
In a street dance battle, I just don't...
Do you really wanna do this?
Yes.
Then you shouldn't back away.
I'm here because I believe in it...
And you.
Come dance.
- Come!
- No.
- Please.
- No!
Please!
Come on, come with me.
Okay, you win.
- Come on.
- All right.
♪ Let us make amends
♪ We're not overly good friends
♪ But it's not heaven
♪ Without you
♪ You can have it all
♪ We'll see mountains fall
♪ But it's not heaven
♪ Without you
♪ Let us make amends
♪ We're not overly good friends
♪ But it's not heaven
♪ Without you
♪ It's the symphony distorting
♪ When we're not talking
♪ But it's not heaven
♪ Without you... ♪
Think I get it now.
With me it's always been my time to shine
and my big chance to show 'em all but...
Dancing with a partner, it's all about...
It's all about sharing the moment.
From now on we share.
Hey, nice tattoo, by the way.
- Hello?
- Yo, Ash, guess what?
I bumped into our old friends The Surge
and they've challenged us
to an underground battle.
The Surge wants to battle, mate.
I... I don't know.
I think we should focus on the Final.
- We've only got...
- We're on.
- We...
- Hang on,
is that Eva?
It's the perfect opportunity
to practise our fusion!
We've only got two days
before the Final Clash.
Okay, Eddie, where is it?
Come on!
Yes!
Move. Forward!
Whoo!
Hey, look, it's Popcorn Boy.
Hey, yo, Popcorn Boy, fall on your ass again.
Make us laugh.
Go into the B section!
Five, six, seven!
Way to go, Popcorn Boy.
I guess we'll be seeing you in the Final...
That is if you still have a crew.
Eva! Eva, wait!
Just wait a minute! Wait, wait.
What happened to sharing the moment?
Why did you leave me hanging back there?
I can't explain it.
Well, try!
It just felt wrong to throw
the couples thing at them.
You got scared.
No, no. I just wasn't sure, okay?
It was a street dance battle,
and we were winning.
Look, the Latin thing was a great experiment.
I just don't think that it's gonna work.
An experiment? Latin thing?
Is that what I am to you,
a little Latin experiment?
I didn't mean that.
I let you into my world,
my uncle's world.
Where we shared things with you.
You throw it back in my face!
I didn't mean...
Work out what you do mean, little boy!
So what the hell happened last night?
Latin was your idea
and now you're just dropping it!
- And what about Eva?
- She and Manu are like family.
First you drop her, then who's next?
Him, me, or her?
Seriously, you can't just do that
without telling us!
We are a crew! Next time we decide together!
There won't be a next time.
- Huh?
- What?
It's over.
You guys said this was a bad idea
from the start and you were right.
- For what it's worth, I'm really sorry.
- What?
- Just gonna give up?
- We could have kicked ass.
- So what are we supposed to do?
- Go home.
- Go home?
- What?
I thought you said he was a champion!
You know, I never figured you for a loser.
She left.
You made her.
♪ I am the midnight caller
♪ Waiting on the line
♪ I need to be your lover
♪ I need to get into your life
♪ I'll be yours
♪ For ever more
♪ Make me yours
♪ When the feelings suffocate me
♪ And nobody is there
♪ All alone I turn to you to you to you
♪ I am the midnight caller
♪ Are you ready for me now?
♪ You know there could be no other
♪ And your time's running out
♪ I'll be yours
♪ For ever more
♪ When the feelings suffocate me
and nobody is there
♪ All alone I turn to you to you to you
♪ I'll be yours
♪ For ever more
♪ Make me yours
♪ For ever more ♪
Ah, Eva.
Voila. Voila
I know, Eva.
Eva's not here.
No, thank you, I'm good.
I really messed up.
I knew that you would.
I really need her.
For what? For yourself
or for the competition tonight?
I quit the competition.
It's not about the competition.
Wake up! You let Eva down
and now you're going to let everyone
else down because you are afraid!
- I don't need this.
- Oh, I don't need this.
Why do you come here, hmm?
You want me to speak to my niece?
You want me to say,
"Oh, poor Ash, he's very sad"?
Where are your balls?
You want something, you have to take risk!
And who are you to dish it out?
I never quit, never!
You're a quitter! Go, I don't want to see you!
Go, you're a quitter!
Go, go on.
You...
Look, Manu, I didn't come to fight. I just...
Manu!
Manu. Oh, no. Oh, no, no, no, Manu.
Manu! Come here.
They've done some tests.
Should be able to let us know soon.
So you can go now.
Look, if there's anything that you need,
I'm gonna be...
Just go.
I'm sorry.
Go.
Go and win.
Ash.
Thank you.
You also should go.
I am not leaving you.
How is he?
He's tapping his feet.
That's good news.
So, what's the plan?
We kick ass!
♪ We will we will rock you
♪ Buddy, you're a boy
make a big noise
♪ Playin' in the street gonna be
a big man some day
♪ You got mud on your face
♪ You big disgrace
♪ Kickin' your can all over the place
♪ Singin'
♪ We will we will rock you
♪ We will we will rock you ♪
Yo!
Ladies and gentlemen...
Your champions...
Invincible!
So what now?
Guys, I got an idea.
Are you not entertained?
You seen it with your own eyes, people!
Invincible by name
and invincible by nature!
Is there no one...
No one here who can challenge us?
So here we are.
This is it.
Popcorn Boy?
This is right now.
This is the moment.
And the Popcorn Crew!
This is our moment.
This is too sweet.
Bring it!
Yo, the Final Clash is done!
- Done! You can't just come up here...
- Shut up.
Because I say when it's over!
I crushed you once, Popcorn!
And I can do it again.
And again!
It's on!
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
it looks like you've got yourself
a bonus battle!
Are you ready?
Thanks, Eddie.
For what?
Putting your trust in a guy
who fell on his ass.
Just don't do it this time.
All right.
Let's do this!
♪ No bad boys
no champagne
♪ No false love
no mind games
♪ No scandal
no boxes, no labels
♪ Labels
♪ No ice-cream, no candy
no too-hot-to-handle me
♪ No cigarettes, just alcohol
sliding easy down my throat
- ♪ No French kiss, no ooh-la-la...
- Whoo!
♪ My fake tan, my Shangri-La
♪ No chit-chat, no slap on the back
♪ Show me, show me who you are
♪ I like you
♪ I feel your love on the dance floor
♪ Rubbing on my...
♪ Oo-ooh!
♪ Bow wow wow
♪ Give that dog a bone
♪ Is that love on the dance floor
rubbing on my...
♪ Oo-ooh?
♪ Bow wow wow
♪ Give that dog a bone
♪ No labels labels
♪ I drop girls like jive
♪ I'm faded I'm unstable
♪ But my two-step's just fine
♪ And I like girls that like girls
♪ You Nicki Minaj that's fine
♪ And I'm crazy but look baby
if you give me...
♪ I'll shine
♪ Okay she got the moves like Jagger
make you wanna dagger
♪ Wanna pay, boy
I hear ya
♪ My bank balance hits high notes
like Miss Aguilera
♪ I MC
I can dance too
♪ Twice flawless dance grooves
♪ It's Bodyrox and it's big chip
and here's a song you can dance to
♪ I feel your love on the dance floor
♪ Rubbing on my
♪ Oo-ooh!
♪ Bow wow wow
♪ Give that dog a bone
♪ Is that love on the dance floor
rubbing on my...
♪ Oo-ooh?
♪ Bow wow wow
♪ Give that dog a bone
♪ This time I want to get it get down ♪
That's Popcorn's round.
These two crews are really going in!
Make some noise for these crews right now!
♪ Just first place
♪ Never settle for less
♪ What's the point in trying
if you ain't trying your best?
♪ They wanna see me six feet under
but I'm watching my steps
♪ Now everybody watching me
like Jay-Z watches the Nets
♪ Don't see myself on a skateboard
but I stay on my grind
♪ Aiming for the top and I won't stop
till I cross that finish line
♪ I see it like the deaf
I listen like the blind
♪ So if I can't hear them scheming
I still see the signs
♪ I never count the days
I make the days count
♪ They wanna take my crown
so I swim when they wanna see me drown
♪ Smile when they wanna see me frown
stand up when they wanna see me down
♪ New and improved attitude
you don't wanna see me now
♪ They said I can't do it but I did it
♪ Now they love me all over the world
cos they say that my style is so prolific
♪ If I said it I live it the black Scott diss it
♪ Fresh haircut and a brand-new suit
lift up the trophy and kiss it
♪ Whenever you feel like letting go
♪ And you've got your back against the wall
♪ Hold on
♪ Just hold on
♪ Cos you're gonna take a few low blows
♪ And I know you feel those broken bones
♪ But hold on
Oh.
Invincible!
♪ Cos you're undefeatable... ♪
Oh, they're one-one.
It's the last round. Winner takes all!
Sorry, I dropped the ball. It's my fault.
No. Don't apologise.
- You gotta get your head in the game.
- We've got this!
This is a real battle right now!
Okay, are you ready for the final battle?
All right? Let's do this!
♪ Make your Lady Gaga
and party like a rock star
♪ Party like it's TV
but I wanna see it in 3D
♪ Take it to the crib and see if she
♪ If she can ride my beat
♪ Ride my beat
♪ Beat beat
♪ If she can ride my beat
♪ Ride my
♪ Ride my beat
♪ Ride my beat beat beat beat ♪
Ha-ha-ha!
Make some noise!
Oh, you see that?
Popcorn, last throw down!
You hear me?
No playing.
On this one right now.
What now?
What's this?
What's going on?
So,
you think you can keep up?
Popcorn going in!
Whoo!
I'm loving this mix-up right now!
Dosey doe!
Whoo!
Oh!
Whoo-hoo!
In your face!
Whoo!
Oh!
Well!
Well, let me get to the result on this.
Okay, my judges,
on the count of three, show me what's good.
Three!
Two!
One!
♪ Am I dancing on my own?
♪ I don't know
♪ Am I walking all alone?
♪ Cos you
♪ You just come and go
You just come and go...
♪ Like a beat echoing...
Oh, my days! Worthy champions!
♪ Fast forward and rewind
♪ Play it all again
♪ Play it all again and again
♪ When does it end?
♪ I get up
♪ I fall down...
Popcorn!
♪ I hit the roof and land on the ground
♪ Come near
♪ And shut up
♪ You rock my world a little too much
♪ How am I going to let him go?
♪ The boy's got me high and low
♪ How am I going to let it go?
♪ Kiss somebody turn out the lights
♪ 'Cos this room is spinning around
♪ I find it hard not to like
the way you mess me around
♪ So it's the official run-around
♪ Should I go
♪ Or get a rope to tie you down?
♪ Cos you
♪ You just come and go
You just come and go
♪ Like a beat like the same song on the radio
♪ Fast forward and rewind
♪ Play that song again
♪ Play that song again and again
♪ When does it end?
♪ High high high
♪ Low low low
♪ High low
high low
♪ I get up
♪ I fall down
♪ I hit the roof and land on the ground
♪ Come near
♪ And shut up
♪ You rock my world a little too much
♪ How am I going to let him go?
♪ The boy's got me high and low
♪ How am I going to let it go?
♪ High high high
♪ Low low low
♪ High low
high low
♪ High low ♪
♪ When I go in when I go hard
♪ There's nobody else on my level
♪ When I go near when I go far
♪ It's over over
♪ Since I've been going in
scared of coming out
♪ I hit 'em with a hit the blood's rushing out
♪ I feel like I'm the ish
♪ But still it's unannounced
♪ So when I top the charts
I ain't coming down
♪ And my drive ain't driven by numbers
♪ I'm from the underground
Seen the best deprived buskers
♪ They ain't got a piece of the pie
♪ So we should think about the cake
next time we're buying custard
♪ Yeah the hunger in my belly
could have turned my knees to jelly
♪ Now my vision gets channelled
through the telly
♪ Ain't give up the fight
♪ I know wrong from right
♪ I'ma keep it tight
♪ Where the darkness I can find
a light was shining bright
♪ Cos I know when I go
♪ When I go hard
♪ There's nobody else on my level
♪ When I go near when I go far
♪ It's over over
♪ I came to shut it down
♪ Until there ain't no trace of doubt
♪ When I go in when I go hard
♪ There's nobody else on my level
♪ When I go near when I go far
♪ It's over over
♪ Cos I came to shut it down
♪ Until there ain't no trace of doubt
♪ When I go in when I go hard
♪ It's over over♪
♪ Mama won't you please
Mama won't you please
♪ Mama won't you please let me
♪ Yo, coming in with a sound
fresher than cut grass
♪ Fun starts
♪ Second that we enter if you must ask
♪ Rush past
♪ Like you've forgotten your mind
♪ Drivers all up in your face
can I see your bus pass?
♪ Nah
♪ We just wanna lickle rhyme, bruv
♪ Call me what you want
but you should not call it a night, love
♪ And I mightjustjoin the mile high club
♪ Only problem being
that I couldn't give a flying
♪ Yeah, yeah
I love that sound
♪ What?
♪ Yeah, yeah
I love that sound
♪ So flick your fag butts
at once on a mad one
♪ Like, yeah
your mama can hump
♪ Mama do the hump
mama do the hump hump
♪ Mama won't you please
let me do the hump hump
♪ Mama do the hump
mama do the hump hump
♪ Mama won't you please
let me do the hump hump ♪