Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
All rise, please.
The Court of California
is now in session.
The Honorable Judge Lundstrom,
presiding.
Please be seated.
Mr. D'Ambrosia?
This case is a travesty!
You have no evidence whatsoever
linking the accused to the murder.
The gun found in his car was obtained
as the result of an illegal search.
In the eyes of the court
it does not exist.
The search was illegal
because Inspector Callahan...
...and this is an old story...
...did not have sufficient probable
cause for detaining Mr. Hawkins.
The gun is inadmissible and
the charges against the defendant...
...are dismissed!
Mr. D'Ambrosia...
...be assured that I will discuss
your case-preparation techniques...
...with the district attorney.
Bailiff, next!
How many times, Callahan?
You can't bust them
because you think they're dirty.
"Psychic" don't cut it.
Hey, Callahan.
Don't look so puked-out.
Better luck next time, fool.
Listen, punk.
To me, you're just dog shit,
you understand?
Many things can happen to dog shit.
It can be scraped up with a shovel.
It can dry up and blow away,
or be stepped on and squashed.
My advice:
Be careful where the dog shits you.
Class act, Callahan.
A real class act.
Loretta.
You did real good with that cop!
Now, I want everything.
Money, watches, rings, everything!
Quick! Move!
Come with me.
We'll have a little party!
What are you doing,
you pig-head sucker?
Every day for the last 10 years,
Loretta gives me a black coffee.
Today she gives me a black coffee,
but with sugar in it.
A lot of sugar.
I just came back to complain.
Now, you boys put those guns down.
Say what?
We're not just going
to let you walk out of here.
Who is "we," sucker?
Smith and Wesson...
...and me.
Go ahead...
...make my day.
Call D'Ambrosia in the D.A.'s office,
ask him if coffee is psychic.
- Ernie.
- What?
Look who's going into the hotel.
Is that who I think it is?
Shit!
Why me?
A nothing detail!
A lousy peeper tour!
So, what do we do now?
Call Captain Briggs, let him decide.
May I have your invitation, sir?
I don't understand,
inspector Callahan.
You know the number
for San Francisco General?
Yes, I do.
Why don't you call,
have them send an ambulance?
Tell them there's two assholes...
...with multiple contusions
and sundry broken bones.
- Inspector Callahan.
- I want to talk to Threlkis.
At his granddaughter's wedding?
On what business?
- To help him catch the bouquet.
- They have harassment laws.
Sit down. Please.
Champagne? It's imported.
Men, like wine, should grow finer,
more civilized.
They should mellow,
become more worldly.
But not Callahan.
Callahan is the one constant
in an ever-changing universe.
Linda Doker?
Fished out of the bay a month ago.
Her breasts were slashed.
Her feet burned.
Her face smashed to a pulp.
I read about it.
A hooker.
A very expensive one.
In fact, her specialty was making
old scumbags mellow and worldly.
She had a special customer
who said lots of things.
You are a fool, Callahan.
She may have been clever
and written them down.
Maybe she made a copy of it.
Maybe she didn't tell
when she was being tortured.
What will the scumbag's bosses
say when they find out?
Or his family?
Maybe his ass is in a wringer.
You fucking...
Someone help us.
Call an ambulance.
Sorry, inspector, but captain...
What happened?
Someone grabbed their chest.
Must've seen the bill.
Oh, my God.
Stand back, please.
Harry, wait till you see this.
Some stiff got himself
a. 38-caliber vasectomy.
Harry, you don't look so hot.
Bad night? All nookied out?
Gang hit? Screwed-up drug score?
Unlucky john?
Or an unhappy love affair?
Don't tell me this shit's
getting to you.
Not Harry Callahan. Say it ain't so.
No, this stuff isn't getting to me.
Shootings, knifings, beatings.
Old ladies getting bashed
for Social Security checks.
Teachers being thrown out of windows.
- That doesn't bother me a bit.
- Harry, take it easy.
Or this job, wading through
the scum of the city.
Being swept away by bigger and bigger
waves of corruption and red tape.
That doesn't bother me.
You know what does?
You know what makes me sick
to my stomach?
Watching you stuff your face
with hot dogs.
Nobody, I mean nobody,
puts ketchup on a hot dog.
What the hell you talking about?
Having our fingers in the holes and
the whole dike is crumbling around us.
Lt. Donnelly says to get your... self
to the commissioner's office.
Swell.
- Leah, can I speak with you?
- Jennifer, what marvelous timing.
I'm giving your work
the favorite positions.
I'm afraid you'll be wasting
good selling spots.
Nonsense.
They're the jewels of the exhibit.
Don't be discouraged
if they don't sell immediately.
They're intense. People need time
to get used to them.
I'm just getting used to them myself.
How can such a howl of anguish
come from such a sweet girl as you?
I'm leaving town.
- When?
- Today.
But you'll miss the exhibit,
the opening.
I'm better at painting
than receptions.
Can I give you an address
to send the paintings to?
Think positive. It's money
we'll send from the sales.
- Where are you going?
- North, to visit someone.
Look at the blond baby!
Mama, check it out.
How you doing?
She wants to play.
- Need a lift?
- Sure, baby.
Then shove a jack up your ass.
Puta.
In 30 years of police work,
this is the most outrageous...
...transgression of authority ever.
- What the hell were you doing?
- My job.
It's your job to harass and incite
an old man into a heart attack?
My job's to investigate homicide.
That old man is the
biggest crime lord in the West.
How did I know
he would vapor-lock?
You hoped he would.
The Doker case is mine.
It's stuck. I broke it loose.
- With threats and intimidation.
- Any way.
Are you aware...
...that you've destroyed
months of surveillance work?
Thousands of dollars.
Hundreds of man-hours.
Investigations is busting its ass
to build a case on Threlkis.
He would've snaked out of it.
Maybe we saved the taxpayers money.
I ought to bust your ass
down to Traffic.
Or better, kick it off the force.
You're a dinosaur, Callahan.
Your ideas don't fit today.
What ideas are these?
Murder's a crime,
it shouldn't be punished?
Don't lecture me, you son of a bitch.
You know who you're talking to?
You know my record?
You're a legend in your own
mind.
- Goddamn you, Callahan.
- Gentlemen, enough.
Inspector, your methods are
different. But you get results.
Often your successes
are more costly to the city...
...in terms of publicity and
destruction than most failures.
The press will have a field day
with this fiasco.
There may be legal repercussions.
There could be attempts at retaliation.
I think the inspector
should take some time off.
You're suspending me?
I'm suggesting you vacation
until it's calm.
I'm not up for vacation.
Callahan, I'm not fencing with you.
Take a few days off.
Harry, a couple of days.
Think things over, Callahan.
Get with it.
It's a new ballgame these days.
Funny, I never thought of it
as a game.
I examined your sister Elizabeth,
and I tested her again.
There are no changes.
The computerized tomogram
shows no evidence...
...of chronic subdural hematoma.
Physically, she's in good shape.
She remains in a vegetative state
that we can't penetrate.
Not even a primitive startle response.
We'll keep trying,
we're always hopeful.
You should be too.
Hi, baby.
It's me.
Jen.
I missed you.
Beth?
I saw one of them.
He just appeared on the street
in front of me.
At first I thought I was having
some horrible vision.
But no. He was there.
Older and uglier.
I followed him.
For days I watched him.
Then I bought a gun.
I followed him to a bar.
I let him pick me up.
Let him drive me to a deserted spot.
Let him think...
It was like I was outside myself.
Above me, looking down.
Then he touched me.
And I killed him.
Beth?
I love you.
- Hell of a way to have a night off.
- You in on the act?
No, for Christ's sake.
Back off a little.
I worry about your ass.
It'll be shot off or kicked out.
What else is new?
They're not a bunch of junkies.
To them, you killed Threlkis,
same as shooting him.
They'll keep coming after you.
Good, we'll know where they are.
You're incredible, Callahan.
You're also on vacation
as of right now.
- I'm not up for vacation.
- You are, I just put you up.
Go get some R and R
and stay out of trouble.
You hear me, Callahan?
Peace and quiet!
Good morning, Horace.
Sweet Sister Sadie,
where the hell did you get that?
I've had it a while.
Thought I'd get used to it.
I heard about the car.
Fabulous, coming after you in tanks.
Yeah, they're making those now, for
sheiks and business executives, hoods.
- Impregnable to anything but artillery.
- Well, you got that covered.
Not bad.
My ass! You have to strain
the remains for the fingerprints.
Well, this is the. 44 Magnum Auto-Mag.
It has a 300-grain cartridge...
...and, if properly used,
it can remove the fingerprints.
I got just the place for you
to go on vacation.
- You got that wrong.
- You've no choice.
I think I do.
- You thinking about quitting?
- I might.
Look at the field.
Look what you did there.
Not quite good enough.
You can't quit, that's what.
Okay, jamf?
What's the brass going to do?
Who are they going to complain to?
And the PR men kissing ass,
ass that you kicked.
You're nothing but a cop.
That's all you've been
and all you'll be, jamf.
Thank you, doctor.
Listen, when you get cut,
you'll bleed P.D. Blue, jamf.
What the hell's a "jamf"?
- That means you're a jive-ass mother...
- Forget I asked.
Almost there.
l hope the house is suitable.
It's a bit deserted out in West Cliff.
I thought you'd appreciate
the solitude as you seek inspiration.
The house is lovely.
I've left the fridge stocked for you.
And there's firewood for a fire.
Let's see, here are the keys...
...for the carousel house.
Everything you need should be here.
But if you have any additional wants,
we have an account in Dunstan's.
Thank you.
I can't tell you how happy we are...
...that you're doing this work
for the Historical Society.
Because your work is so impressive
and so impeccably authentic.
I do my research.
It must give you great satisfaction
to make old, ugly things right again.
Yes, sometimes it does.
Like what I brought you, baby?
I like you, yeah.
Tell him that you like it.
Don't forget,
l get my shot at the other one.
Come on, Alby.
What are you, queer?
There he is.
- We'll show you dog shit, Callahan!
- Come on. Let's go kick some ass.
There he is! We've got him!
That's your idea of rest and
recreation? What's wrong with you?
Briggs is berserk and
the commissioner's on my ass.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Can't you do anything the easy way?
- Am I on the job or not?
- You are.
Good. Then I'll get to it.
It's not what you think.
Remember that cock-shot stiff
by the Cliff House?
He's been here a few years,
but in the shade.
He looks small-time,
but maybe he was never caught.
And?
He came from San Paulo,
born and raised.
I want you to go there
and find out about him.
- What is this crap?
- It's a murder case, Harry.
- You're shipping me out?
- I'm doing you a favor.
You are a walking combat zone.
People seem to die around you.
I don't want civilians
taking the fall.
You want to work?
Fine.
You got your assignment.
Get the hell out of here.
Take all the time you need. Maybe
the salt air will agree with you.
Any comments?
Swell.
Freeze!
Around the corner!
What's the matter?
You trying to kill someone?
Excuse me.
Police officer in pursuit
of a robbery suspect.
- Shag his ass!
- Get that sucker!
Nail that son of a bitch!
Is he all right?
I guess I'd better
read you your rights.
Best damn day trip I've had
since they put me in that home.
Holy mackerel.
So, you're the famous Harry Callahan.
I'll make this short and sweet.
I'll only say it once.
We don't need a hotshot to show
us dumb yokels how to do our business.
We know how to do our business,
so you keep your nose out of it.
You read me, Harry?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org