Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
The last time I was done counting,
was learned that 53 million
people died each year.
150 thousand each day and 107 every minute.
That is in normal times.
Now, every one of those dead
gets up and kills a person,
and each of these is
up and kills again.
addition, suicide,
murder, mayhem, and we ...
guards ....
should help with
body counts, but ...
... this did not work.
Bring him here. Move.
dead returned to life.
We should fear them, but we did not.
They were too easy
kill, except when they were ...
... your partners.
It's time.
The command in this hole.
You killed D.J. and
now he will kill again.
The fucked up, Lou.
You could not handle it,
but you can do the right thing
I can not.
No.
Everything is there.
- What happens?
- This sucks.
We heard gunshots.
I enlisted for this shit.
You'd better streets.
What the hell is it?
Respond.
Lou and I saw how
died elsewhere.
We became assailants.
Stopping people
on the road ...
- Hello.
- ... taking what they had.
- It's nice to see them.
- These were some boys who were filming ...
... A documentary about themselves.
- What about this camera?
- We're making a movie.
Ah, that is.
That damn movie annoyed me.
- Millions of hits.
- Where is the star?
I earned a very bad reputation ...
- ... between all actors.
- Turn off the camera, son.
I made a fortune with this.
Turn it off.
We turned us against the world ...
- Now.
- ... or were looking for a world where ...
... Not have "them."
The Survival of the Dead
PLUM ISLAND, NEAR THE COAST OF DELAWARE
SIX DAYS AFTER THE
WALKING DEAD START
Well, that's another that does not
we will have to worry.
Amen.
I would just say a
Amen to end all this.
That too would like.
Are you with me then?
- Yes
- Yes, Captain.
You're right.
I'm asking.
Are you with me?
You are being too
strict, as it always has been.
Being strict is the
curse of a father.
Rather, the curse of a
daughter, if you ask me.
What if I die?
Would you enough
strict as to finish?
- What if you die?
- Do not be so.
No, I'm serious. What
if you die and you get up and walk?
Would we be enough
stringent as to kill again?
There would have to,
I shoot myself.
Change a few things.
Death does not change
a person's feelings.
All you can do
is to remember dead
what used to be and
try to do the same.
We go next.
We were alone at home.
We listen to what happened later.
Patrick O'Flynn decided
that the living would
better if the dead
stay dead.
They made a detour around the island
trying to clean things up.
Not everyone was on their side.
Come on.
The army warned that if someone is
forced to fend off an attack
attack to ensure his brain.
Any news of the people?
No.
I'm sitting waiting.
What, a miracle?
Something has to happen, you
believe what the books say.
Does it say what to do?
I'll fix it.
No scandals.
I do not think anything happen.
Patrick O'Flynn.
00:06:09,252 -> 00:06:10,195
Matthew Muldoon.
I know that does not concern me, but ...
Where are your children?
Up there.
They're sleeping.
You came to me because one of them had
had an accident a couple of days
Yes, the girl he fell
the bike, so ...
"And the child?
- Why do you ask?
- I hit a car.
Is the child either Matthew or not?
I believe what I say.
- He is ...
- Maybe I should go to see for myself.
It will not go up there.
Beth, I have to do this.
You do not have to do
this, enjoy it.
No, I promise that it is not.
Do not want to get up there. I do not want
see what we have become your children. "
He has not become nothing.
It remains only my son.
Do not do that.
Beth.
Oh, my God.
You are stupid. You could
have stopped this.
I could've told the truth.
What will you do now? "You will be taken
up there and lie down in bed?
No, I will have to do.
If you give me the means.
Get rid of them.
I will, I a.
But I would give my soul
who can do it for me.
Nobody is going to help.
Not this time, not just children.
Been sufficient
deaths for a day.
It appears that your kids
I have heard.
I said that was enough deaths.
These back belong
initially to O'Flynn.
Now, listen.
I am seeking a safe place
where men can
proud to live your life.
We can keep it that way
but only if we
what to do.
Killing our species,
as if we belonged.
Putting the dead sleep,
before we do so to us.
I have faith.
Judgement Day will forgive me
and prove that I have reason.
You're wrong, Muldoon.
What will you do with them?
Son of Muldoon, my turn to save them.
You can not save a
person who is already dead.
May not be dead.
Maybe they have some kind
disease or something.
Someone will find
the cure for this.
It might take 100 years, but
someone will find a cure.
The only families who believe
in it are yours and mine.
So far there has been no stranger.
For me now are
strange, Patrick O'Flynn.
and safe ...
Is everything clear?
Outside, everyone.
What will happen to him?
If I'm not going to the opposite ...
... I'll let you be killed himself.
Shamus.
He is my father.
I need to get rid of him.
This island needs to get rid of him.
You can put in a pot.
Who's coming with me?
I've been with you a long time, Captain.
So I'll keep at his side.
Is that all?
We like it here, Patrick.
We believe the best way
overcome this is here in Plum.
Come on, Janet.
I like it here too, Dad.
"You're leaving now?
I'm not leaving.
You're the one who does.
If you continue to emerge
convicted, none survive.
THREE WEEKS LATER
Why are zombies
good at oral sex?
Why zombies are good
in oral sex? I do not know.
Because they eat any
thing he put forward.
Did you like that?
Why Zombies
politicians eat?
I do not know.
Professional courtesy.
- What?
- Anything is funny.
There was no able to receive
no signal for several days
so now I can.
It sucks, people
wrong are those who die.
Only fools are still alive.
Dead heads, and call them now.
The world is going crazy.
Hi, mommy.
Forget it, okay? You're exciting.
Can not stand me here
and not doing anything.
Just give me 5 minutes.
You'll change your life forever.
I have no 5 minutes, man.
No one has lately.
Too bad.
What is bad is that
if another bitch in this place.
I was walking around,
but no one there.
Turn off that.
That's funny.
Shut it now.
I heard something.
Not far away, come on.
Check this out.
Perhaps there is money inside.
The money does not make sense anymore.
Money always
will be money, my friend.
If you have a lot of money
at the end of the world
is possible that you can
buy a nice condo.
Let's ambush.
We will find four
positions from there.
Make some noise.
- Come on.
- Here.
- After all he had.
- Do you leave it there?
I would stay, but did not.
- Certainly not.
- He almost gets your property.
Who is she, your mom?
Shit.
How many are you?
They have enough weapons.
Lay down arms.
You'll have to force me
to lower, Mandrake.
Oh, shit.
Anything else you want
venture to sign up?
That's good.
I do not like shooting
people do not know.
Oh, maybe we should know.
Who the hell wants to meet you?
- Two.
- Even I can tell you better than that.
- Three.
- Three is company, sir.
- Four.
- Four is a crowd.
Oh, shit.
What the hell was that?
Oh, that.
That is something that we have fun.
"Fun?
There are zombies out there.
We were following.
Oh, God.
Why did you do that?
They came after us, like I said.
We were following
so we kill them.
That's right.
There are many ways to kill someone.
For example, if I shoot
in the head, I would use this.
If I wanted to cut you in
bits would use this.
Or you want to bust.
If you would like esparcirte through the woods ...
... Would use one of these bad boys.
But you know one thing
I do not want
do on a rainy day.
It is likely that you do ...
Do not shoot, please. Not
I am one of them, I swear.
Kenny, stop.
Just coming up the road.
Too crazy
around to walk alone.
The bad people have bad people.
Are not they yours?
"People scoundrel?
- No.
- Yes
I'm not demanding.
You have to finish your work.
You're dangerous, man.
But not as much as me.
You come with us, eh?
Just give me a minute.
What are you doing?
- Did you steal their things?
- No, my stuff, they'd have been stolen.
What do you think?
Maybe we should take this.
It is better to walk in Jeeps.
I need the keys.
One of those dead
the back there should have.
Not anymore.
It makes no sense.
Who would be
stupid enough to
leave a bundle of money
in the middle of nowhere?
"Those guys looked like you geniuses?
One million three hundred
thirty-three U.S. dollars.
- Are you told?
- No, I knew what I had.
Can you give us the key?
You can have this key.
To start the truck.
I meant that.
I think not.
Well, we can not take the
things to this boy. Let's go.
Drive.
Hey, Cisco wants to know where we go.
We have two options, "North or south?
South.
- Who made you king?
- Single suggest.
Do not make any suggestion, OK?
To the north, Cisco.
Did you ask why I can?
Go North gives us a good
possibility of obtaining things.
A nowhere.
We do not want anywhere.
We want somewhere
where there is so much shit.
Like what?
As an island.
Where will we find an island?
Let me see ... Maybe in the ocean?
Do not get smart, kid.
Sorry.
Have you ever heard
of Captain Courageous?
Who?
It is a type.
Are you going to look on the computer?
PC sucks.
I think it's great, everything is there.
That's not great, it is.
Friends, I will
so that simple.
Who is the sailor?
... I know many who have
come up with many questions.
They are cannibals.
They can come and join us.
Come to Plum.
It is an island near
the coast of Delaware.
Move out to our island.
It has beautiful scenery
and a prodigious beach.
If they come over here, we
I promise I will be welcome.
It is a small place
small and under control.
This sounds good.
Think about it.
Come here.
It is a trap,
What else can it be?
So this type found
a place to escape.
No zombies who fall behind.
Yes and if we find it, let's start
to call people to join us.
All right. What can we lose?
I thought we agreed with
we were better on our own.
Thank God that is far, right?
I do not want to enlist with anyone, Kenny.
What we agreed on, man.
Shit.
Shit. Shit. Shit.
That was not good.
You should think about something else boy.
I never joined up with you
never did with me.
We are together because we know.
I get a shot of yours,
you receive one of mine.
No one will give me a bullet.
Sergeant, the people of this island
is blessed by Uncle Sam.
Maybe it's just ...
... A smart thing.
So where do we go? "North or South?
South.
And find the path to the beach.
Oh, I caught a big one.
What the hell was that?
Someone is coming, Captain.
No one around here.
When a place seems so empty.
... It is not at all.
Hello.
- Do you see what I mean?
- Nice truck.
They must have a lot of money there.
There's nothing here that we.
We find this
truck on the road.
Another person had already cleared.
It's awful liar, Sgt.
We want to get to Plum Island.
They have come to the wrong location.
We only have one boat
with oars and a motor.
How much you want for the boat motor?
- How are you?
- How much for the other?
- Shit.
They are just old-fashioned thieves.
Attract people here
to steal what they have.
We did well until
who showed you.
Dead.
If you do not go now, I'll fly brains.
While we are here,
you will not be able to do that.
Why do not we go from here?
Do not think of leaving here,
TNT road is mined.
Damn.
You can be crazy, but
was not lying.
What do we do?
Yes, there it is.
We can leave that.
I just want the money.
It has never been money,
it's about staying alive.
This tank gives us
opportunity to stay alive.
The truck may be our
savior, but are not on the water.
Someone is going to have to go there ...
... Or me, and turn on that boat.
What if no light?
What if no fuel?
We would have tremendous bad luck
Cisco, driving to the rim.
Cisco, I told you back.
I know how to handle a boat.
Do you know how to handle a boat?
Yes, I can try.
No need to try.
Lord, the two and this woman.
Soon will I gain from this.
You have more chance to catch you
Ferry that kept pushing me to me.
-5 Minutes dear.
- Yes, yes. Forever changed my life.
Cisco, no.
It is swimming to the ferry
How did we get there?
There must be something better than this truck.
Shit.
Let me see if I can.
I think I could get used to this.
Shit.
Those damn things
are leaving the fund.
Guys.
Shit. Get in the truck.
Oh God.
He did, Captain.
Come, take this. Toma.
Toma.
- How did you get here?
- Swimming, just like you.
And your gun? It was wet, right?
You should thank me.
It is better to try now.
Try it now, Cisco.
Do you want to do all the work?
You never know.
Sometimes fires and sometimes not.
You're awful cowboy, Pancho.
Come on, we have
try to get out of here.
Okay.
Turn on the telegraph.
- What is the telegraph?
- That there, put it to the fullest.
The boat moves, Captain.
You should not have much fuel.
Move the truck, Tomboy. Let
addressed.
Tomboy.
Where the hell is Tomboy?
How can we get this truck
in a boat if nobody is driving?
What do you think, boy?
Jesus, what the hell was that?
I do not look at me. Begin
shoot these bastards.
Tawdry.
I have you!
I can not believe, no.
Shit.
My children, give them some
seconds before you blow them up.
Thank you.
Okay, I have you.
Come on.
You're looking at me.
If any of the
others would have left him drowning.
In this case I am very lucky.
- Where is Plum?
- This, to the east.
The man says to the east.
Towards the east? Thither
is the Atlantic Ocean.
Yeah, well, hopefully
there is something in between.
Everything is ruined.
Except this.
You remind me of my daughter.
Yes? Is she pretty?
As it concerns me.
Yes? Then it is a matter
so I would like to know.
Oh, you're ...
Oh, yes.
I am ...
- Any problem with that?
- None, none.
You.
I can not help this time.
My name is Patrick O'Flynn.
Leave that tried to kill us.
Well, there is always
resource that can be used.
I could kill you right now
if you wanted.
I also I can kill.
Yes, you could, could.
I think just about
Who pulls the trigger first.
Why I like him?
Well, I have said this several times.
We are all on the same side.
The land of the living.
- I'm on your side.
- Yes, but you are.
Just do not know it yet.
First things first.
We must ensure that there are no more
of these errant chick on this ship.
I'm not in charge of
you all the time.
Grab.
Want something to eat shit?
Are you okay?
Yes, yes, perfect.
Do not bite when
were swimming, right?
No, I do not bite.
In fact, I ended up with one myself.
One of those things
and I tried to catch me ...
... Tore off one of his fingers.
Did you take blood?
No, I do not.
A little water, but ...
... Blood, I do not.
Tomboy, come hither.
Come as quickly as possible.
What we have here?
This is dead in different ways.
I have one here.
It has become intelligent.
"Intelligent?
That thing has reminded
how to start the car.
Yes, but I do not give
Driving License.
I think we've cleaned up.
Thanks for your help.
Is there any gain
to kill dead people?
That island that were selling.
Have you been there?
Of course, it's a lovely place.
Very charming.
But I'm not welcome.
Why? What did you do?
Nothing to deserve that.
It was not a thief.
But these days there
nothing more than thieves who earn
wages to be tremendous
intelligent in his profession.
Never won a wage.
I always did for fun.
Thank God
never had Internet.
There are no good thieves.
I can not believe that we are ignoring
a guy who is devoted to kill zombies.
Land in sight.
Throw the anchor.
Pull the anchor "? Are not we far away?
Not here. No water
deep near Plum.
Protect the Ferry is better.
Nobody is going to see enter.
Shit.
What did I do?
We gotta go.
We need to get
before dawn.
Enter illegally.
Do not think it's good.
It is better to take it
the wrong way.
They do not like outsiders.
You're not a stranger.
Oh I'm worse, I'm sure.
Especially now.
Veras, an unusual number of strangers have
Plum been arriving for weeks.
in boats that I have provided.
Launch the network.
Why do it?
Has a gentleman to trouble
believed to be the owner of this place.
And believe it or not, to help people
to find a better place to live.
What happened between that gentleman and you?
We had a little disagreement ...
... About expanding or not
the cemetery of the island.
Come to the front.
Hey, it respects a little, old man.
It's not you, is part of the River.
I refer to this river.
This part always
belonged to the O'Flynn.
The other side ...
... Well, I'm sure you know
someone on the other side ... soon.
This year the company expanded
a pest species.
I hope my daughter is here.
I had a kind of
disagreement before leaving.
But she remains one O'Flynn.
It seems that you had
disagreements with the whole world.
Hey.
If a place looks so empty it is likely
it is not at all, is not it?
See what I mean?
It's only the postman.
It takes several days delivering the mail.
Look.
And there.
See what happens?
Keep them with you, he says.
But in reality they are not.
Not if you keep them chained.
Those are them.
Give me a gun.
Shoot him the bastards.
What bastards?
- Who shot them?
- The Muldoon.
There is only one up there.
Kenny crouch.
Oh, God.
I have it.
Shit.
You said you would receive no
never a bullet from anyone.
That is very easy to say.
You're just an old-timer.
Kenny.
Hey.
Shit, Kenny.
No, no.
Why do you dress?
I'm so sorry, man.
I'm sorry.
Why did you dress me?
Damn.
I had to do, you know it well.
You son of a bitch.
- She is beautiful.
- It's dead.
It's my daughter.
Is your daughter?
It was.
Can you hold, please?
Hey, you're right.
How will I be?
I got shot, for heaven's sake.
Given the fact that you
fired, are you okay?
Yes, I think.
Mother of God.
In my property.
All this ...
... Used to be mine.
The land around us.
Even the pine down there.
and anything that was swimming in the river. "
nothing happens on the river now.
Many of them.
These people were killed by
head and then shot them dead.
That woman did not have to be dead.
He asked me not to send here.
After you steal
his last $ 30.
I put on a ship and sent it here.
I never thought I would die.
Bastard.
I should not let it
away with it.
That bastard.
What bastard? Who is this guy?
Shamus Muldoon.
We had quarrels
since we were kids.
Does anyone give me more
bullets for this gun?
What will you do?
I have to shoot that son of a bitch.
Not if I come first.
My best friend is lying there dead.
My shoulder seems to burn in
fire and there are plenty of
innocent people dead because
someone decided to do so.
If this someone is the Muldoon
which has been talking ...
... I want a part of that.
I knew we would be on the same side.
Sooner or later.
I'll get to some friends.
I'll go with you.
No, no use.
I'll get some of my team.
There is a cottage half a mile from here.
Wait there, I'll go look
before nightfall.
Bullets.
This is good.
Thank you.
I feel sorry for her daughter.
It serves no purpose.
Shamus.
Lem, Christ. What are you hiding
smelling like a raccoon in the trash?
I was not snooping, Shamus.
Mr. Chuck sent me.
Stud says that is not right.
It is best to come see.
Damn, what does a man do
to have a moment of peace on this island?
Chuck, you're here.
What else
thought I was going to be?
Lem said you were
having problems.
Oh, yes, I'm trying
prevent these types eat me.
A little more upset than usual.
No sir.
Not my hat.
Damn.
No more than usual.
They say he is the son of Timothy.
Timothy Skyland.
How long there?
This is her third day.
I should have made some progress already.
Puts his head around and bites everything.
If I did not have a shot
head, resembles a man.
But do not just do nothing
to eat that pig.
Maybe not like pork.
Lord, it is no disrespect ...
... But we say we want
keep these people alive
and lately we shooting
like mad dogs.
I think it's necessary.
What about those people?
They are strangers.
Homeless.
We have an obligation to protect
their souls, that's what we do.
Protect what is yours,
that is mine, what belongs to everyone.
I provide the security people.
I hope you are the last
to question, Chuck.
I helped you when you came out of the bottom.
I left work in a place of respect.
I have left to work this
ranch like yours.
Not mine.
It is not so easy.
I've helped with everything he has done.
Do not bother me when I
began to care for these stalls.
But that was when the
barn was a barn.
Are you still with me, Chuck?
Or do you want to go?
I do not want to go.
Lem, get rid of the boy
and brings home the pork.
Let's make a good dinner.
Go find another
dead head with Chuck.
That no other
those idiots you bring.
All are fools.
When a man dies
becomes stupid.
I have a dead woman in mind.
One that is intelligent enough
to ride a horse across the island.
You mean the daughter of Patrick O'Flynn.
We must learn from it
to know how he did it.
She could be the chosen one, Chuck.
It could be.
The strange, right?
Yes, it did not work.
It seems that nothing works.
Craps.
Hey.
"Medicine?
Thank you.
I have a needle
Do you want the thing?
I do not think that works.
- You are a fool.
- I told you it was okay?
Tremendous asshole.
"Cisco?
Cisco.
The dead are everywhere.
This is no different.
I do not know, man.
I do not know why we still here.
Domination.
"Doom?
It reminds me of my birth.
In the crap out of Alabama.
In a small town.
All the time people
was sniffing ...
... Wanting to know what
were doing every minute of the day.
And to top it off you went out in the
newspaper columns.
When things were you
well you threw the dog.
I like small towns but
small towns
are small people.
But you are not a small person.
How tall, 6.2 feet, 6.3?
6.1 half last time.
And I do not think there
finished growing yet.
Who knows?
Might become taller than you.
Do you know, son?
You'd better prepare for growth.
Me.
Cisco, Jesus.
Leave me alone.
- Cisco.
- Leave me alone.
It's beautiful, right?
It is a beautiful place to live.
Not to die.
You know what you're
happening, eh, darling?
Yes.
Then go back to the others.
Just say goodbye.
No, Cisco.
Okay, if you want to watch.
No.
My God.
You can not kill yourself.
If you do, you'll burn in hell.
That is something that your God does not forgive.
Finally did, Cisco.
I finally changed
life forever.
I'll never forget.
Who the hell are you?
Better than you I am.
Apparently there is a person
you'll want to know.
Lem.
Come on.
No.
No, fuck off.
Are you all right.?
I think I need to check this.
Take the first-
aid that is there.
Psamelo.
Shit.
According ...
Damn.
Okay.
Shit.
You forgot the gun.
You're an idiot.
Too high.
Oh, Jesus.
Patrick.
William and I brought my son.
We want to do what you said
we should from the outset.
My Susan was murdered too.
It was bad.
Thanks for coming.
Help!
Bastards.
She did not eat with us?
Women and children have their place.
The children quietly in their beds ...
... And women in the kitchen.
Some people do not
would agree with that.
How did you get here?
On a boat.
Did you come alone?
Yes, yes.
Well, it's funny.
Because two of my rancheros
went to the other riverbank.
Only one returned.
He told me that they got
in a shootout with ...
... 6 outsiders.
One was a boy.
4 were dressed like you.
The number 6 was Patrick O'Flynn.
I'm sure
I filled bastard
bad head
thoughts about me.
Well, I was born to be a Muldoon.
At school, my
Muldoon was a teacher.
The good man who brought me
the ranch was a Muldoon.
My priest, which I have the
name, Father Shamus Muldoon.
Please note that all persons
these pictures look a little evil.
That's because all the pictures
were taken after death.
We feel the need
keep them with us.
Just as I am trying to do now.
All I continue to pray for ...
... Keep them with us.
All my life I have led
by the word of the Good Lord.
In their practices.
Everything I do is what
he demands of us.
I will try to urge you ...
to help me exercise
what the Lord asks.
Okay, okay.
I have you, I have.
Come here.
All right.
Okay, baby.
It's me, Jane.
Me.
Guys.
Guys, come here ...
Come here.
You're dreaming.
Wake up.
It's her, she is.
You have to wake up.
Arise!
They are two of them.
The one saw was my twin sister.
Jena and Jane, we called the two
Jenas whenever we traveled separately.
Of course there must be more
easier now that Jane is dead.
Where is he now?
My father.
He left.
A little while ago.
To do what?
To meet some friends.
Oh, my God.
What happened to Cisco and a Tomboy?
I do not know.
I have not seen since ...
My father is a liar.
Maybe not a liar.
but my father sees the world in a
one way, against Muldoon.
Both would do whatever
to go to the opposite.
Well, I'm from your old man.
Why?
For many reasons,
should too.
- What reasons?
-'s Your father.
never, never was an appropriate parent ...
and is now back with
you and all your weapons
and is about to begin
World War III.
Hello, daughter.
Hi, Dad.
You do not have to come with us.
It has never been your fight.
Come on.
Right now?
Right now.
- We are waiting for Cisco.
- And Tomboy.
Muldoon has.
Not sure, but it could ensure
also has to that of Mexico.
Are you sure you want to do this?
There is no reason
to do otherwise. Come on.
Dad.
She is very good, huh?
You are very young and I am very old.
She has her trouble, boy.
- We'll see.
- Dad, please.
Come back, baby.
You can not kill. It is the only
why you are still alive.
What?
Be right with you. James.
I always wondered.
Why do not you shoot me this
night when they had a chance?
It was you.
You spoke on my behalf.
And why?
Now you will die
Anyway he.
Shamus Muldoon spat on
the floor that was sacred.
I did 100 times.
And I made the funeral
and I cut the wood and I
bury your wife when
you did not want to see anyone.
On the other hand was Jane, always
Jane was the one in your heart.
She was the only girl in the house
and I the only one who had grown up.
Listen to yourself, you're so
willed as I am.
Of course I loved Jane.
But you too I love you.
Or maybe more, because you are another me.
Return to the house, Janet.
See you there after or not.
Why should we stop
here? Let us cross the bridge.
I have a hunch.
I think there's someone here.
We are waiting
right here, Patrick.
Go away, kid.
Go to the boat, takes the money
of safe and go to live.
Remember this?
Now, get out of here.
Do not shoot, guys.
Not necessary, it is good meat.
I dead head by
and then I take care of the rest.
Yes, and Muldoon kill your friend.
No.
I owe something to that girl.
Lay down your guns, boys.
"You look at me?
Come across the bridge.
All of you. Leave behind their weapons.
Hurry.
- Hey, you okay?
- Yes
- Where is Cisco?
- Is in Heaven.
Telling the Virgin Mary
you can change your life.
This may interest you. Patrick.
Look there.
We tried this with
many dead heads.
Lord.
We have been fed
rabbits, hares, pigs.
This time we
try something bigger.
Because you are now here, Patrick,
I thought maybe you could
to understand
I've been trying to do.
Trying to keep
the fallen with us.
I could not do so unless
that may have something to eat.
It is important ...
... Not just for us
but for the rest of the world.
God will send us all to
hell and the devil is possible
we back again
if we do the right thing.
Chuck, bring them out of the barn.
Let them see what happens.
Who knows? You may learn something.
Guys.
Oh, Christ.
Look at this, Patrick.
Your daughter will not take even a
bite of this animal.
Admit that I have
right after all.
That's what I always wanted.
Admit that I have right ...
.. and you're wrong.
You have that and you and your kids can go.
Thanks for the offer, Shamus,
but I can not go.
Not without having resolved
what brought me here.
What?
Well, first ...
... I have not killed yet.
I imagined a little different.
Well, well.
I will sit down to enjoy
eyes and see what happens.
What would you do with a million dollars?
My sister never will
do anything on that horse.
What can we do?
I brought this. The left thrown away.
But I do not want to start a war.
I do not want, I just want
have some answers.
What happens there?
It's me, Chuck.
I brought up arms again.
What did you do now?
Now, we all have guns.
The first to pull the trigger
will cause a river of blood.
- Very fast.
- Let it go.
No.
I do not want to go.
It looks like your father
determined to stay with me.
As I have determined
stay here with him.
Nobody here is going to kill anyone.
With or without you.
Hey.
You will not want to
start shooting.
We have this.
Shit.
Well, Mr. Muldoon
Looks like someone is hiring me.
Chuck.
Chuck, where are the hell are you going?
Nobody challenges me.
She wants something.
To me.
She knows me.
Jane.
Bitch.
Fucking bitch.
I've been bitten, Dad.
This is your fault, Muldoon.
He escapes, stupid.
Come, come, come.
You can not stop this.
I can kill now.
For nothing in this world.
Come to me.
This way.
Over here.
Come on. This is for you, Muldoon.
Son of a bitch.
Come on.
This is your fault, Muldoon.
Let's go, guys.
Stop already.
I've got one bullet, Muldoon.
Come on, I'm waiting.
I've got one too.
Say you were wrong.
Say you were wrong and
I've always been right.
Reasons?
Does any of this sounds good?
Dad.
I have seen all dying around me.
Now I'm dying.
I can not believe that you also die.
Shamus, I mean several
things about how I think.
Now if you'll excuse me, I
spend time with my daughter.
No.
Bastardo, Muldoon.
It's over.
Come on.
Move.
She did.
I've got one bullet.
Wait, wait.
It happened.
What happened?
My sister, she ...
She said I would not be
strict enough.
She was all I had.
I did.
Was it not so?
Are you okay?
Well, good luck.
Come on.
Here is a boat.
Look.
There is a world out there
and no money.
The reason why
came up here because
we thought we'd
than anywhere else.
Although it can be.
What makes you think that there
end up like these idiots?
Yes, who knows?
You and I can finish
firing at one of these.
Yeah boy, that will
when you are done growing.
was from
O'Flynn from the start,
so I could only see
Muldoon as the enemy.
I've always wondered.
decided to take the money and go.
I still question that.
What if we could achieve that
dead eat something other than human?
What if Muldoon was right?
I think that I'll never know.
this damn world,
someone puts a flag and
else puts theirs.
01:24:09,023-> 01:24:11,399
Soon begins a
war and nobody knows who
was the one who started to put
those stupid flags.
Translate by wellburnthesky
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org