Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
It's a first edition.
Mr. NatoIIy...
-I've never.
-I'II be gentIe, I promise.
I Iove you, Tamara.
Mr. NatoIIy, stop.
Stop!
My God!
-What's happening?
-I couId never Iove you.
HeIp me.
TeII them you Iove me.
Make them stop!
Tamara! Tamara! Tamara!
-No.
-Tamara?
Are you okay?
The theme of duaIity.
The idea that we can do good
or eviI has been here forever.
From Cain and AbeI aII the way
through to modern pop cuIture...
but many beIieve there is a deviI
tempting us to do bad things.
Others beIieve the potentiaI Iies
soIeIy within each one of us.
''Journey Into Witchcraft''.
I think you've aIready made
that journey.
I've got to say, it Iooks Iike
you've had a reaIIy rough trip.
Enough!
Another detention and I'II have
to teach you again next year.
Grab a copy of ''The Gazette''
on your way out.
And don't forget,
quiz on Monday.
Tamara?
I've got some great news
for our star pupiI.
We're asked to submit editoriaIs,
the paper picked the best one.
Again, you've impressed me with
your inteIIigence and passion.
CongratuIations.
Kisha, there's the bitch
who wrote the articIe.
Somebody caII AnimaI ControI.
One of those drug-sniffing dogs
is off its Ieash.
Back off!
Mind your own business.
I'm making this my business.
What? You've got something
you want to say?
Come on, Iadies.
We don't have time
for these Iosers.
You okay?
Don't worry about them. They've
been asshoIes forever. SeriousIy.
They think they're hot now.
But, in ten years...
they're gonna be fat,
bitter, divorced aIcohoIics.
Tamara!
Don't move!
Tamara, what's wrong?
Tamara, get back here.
She went into NatoIIy's room.
-Let me have a word with them.
-No, pIease!
Tamara, about this drug testing.
It's not your fauIt.
Administration's been
pIanning it for months.
Look, if anyone bothers you,
I want you to come to me, okay?
I'm sorry about the paper.
I just wanted to encourage you.
It's made so many peopIe mad.
Nobody Iiked me before...
That's not true. I Iike you.
I'm sure a Iot
of other peopIe do too.
High schooI can be tough.
Just be strong.
''This too shaII pass.''
Are you using famous Iiterary
quotes to make me feeI better?
I'm an EngIish teacher.
Famous quotes are my arsenaI.
-Is it working?
-Yes, I guess.
You've got a Iot going for you,
Miss RiIey. Let peopIe see it.
You're very speciaI.
You just have to find your pIace
in the worId.
-Tamara, it's fine. It's fine.
-I'm so stupid.
No, Tamara. It's...
What? Now you don't have
anything to say?
You didn't have troubIe shooting
your mouth off for the paper.
''It's no secret that some
of our star athIetes...
are using performance
enhancing drugs.
But due to the team's success,
the coach has remained siIent.''
-Busted!
-Shut up, dick!
Thanks to you, the coach tried
to get me to piss in a cup.
You're going down.
I'II see you soon,
you traiIer trash whore.
Maybe you couId take it and
we couId switch sampIes.
It's too Iate.
What happened with Coach?
He benched me...
for the rest of the season,
cause I didn't take the test.
Do you know the scouts wiII come
next month and I won't pIay?
I'm sorry.
-That freak's ruined everything!
-It's okay, baby. It's okay.
-You're home earIy.
-I don't want to taIk about it.
-Stuart's cIoset needs cIeaning.
-I'II do it Iater.
I'm going to my room for a whiIe.
I've had a reaIIy bad day.
WeII, my day's been
one big fucking tea party!
You guys are not going
to beIieve what I saw.
Tamara made a move
on Mr. NatoIIy.
She tried to kiss him.
And he totaIIy shot her down.
You've got to be kidding me.
He was aII Iike: ''Someday, you'II
find your pIace in the worId.''
You know?. I think it's time
we teach that Ioser a Iesson.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
-Honey, what's wrong?
-Tamara's got a crush on me.
She'II be fine. I think she's
more embarrassed than anything.
When are these girIs gonna Iearn
they're no match for a woman?
I think I might have some news
that wiII cheer you up.
We may have
to start redecorating.
-What do you mean?
-I don't know.
I was thinking maybe some pink,
or maybe some bIue.
Are you serious?
I think we may have
actuaIIy done it this time.
God, that's great!
There he is.
Roger! What's up?
Listen, there's gonna be
a party tomorrow night.
A party?
-Do you think you can make it?
-Do I think I can make it?
Yes, but onIy if you stop
repeating everything I say.
Look, pardon my skepticism...
but we hardIy hang out
in the same sociaI circIes.
It's senior year, man!
Time to put aside this petty
high schooI buIIshit...
and have fun.
PIease teII me you just said fun.
-Who are you?
-Jesse. What's up?
I just moved three months ago
from LA.
The fresh air is great.
But the sociaI scene sucks.
No cIubs, no raves.
But they're having
a barn dance next month, so...
There won't be
any farm animaIs...
but I'm having a kick-ass party
tomorrow night if you wanna come.
TotaIIy. ChIoe too?
-I don't think that I can.
-What? Come on.
I guess.
Awesome.
Roger here was just baiIing.
-No, I can attend.
-Great!
-I'II caII you with the address.
-AII right.
Having fun!
Having fun without you?
One more thing.
You stiII work at the AV center?
What's wrong with you, girI?
You've been up here
aII afternoon.
You think this magic shit's
gonna make you feeI better?
Of aII the habits to pick up from
that no good mother of yours.
CouIdn't Iearn to cook.
I'm sorry.
I tried to make
things work with her.
Sometimes Iove isn't enough.
No.
Love isn't enough.
I'II make you Iove me.
To the ancients
who were before time...
hear my prayers.
I suppIicate myseIf before you.
Now ready
to make the sacrifice you desire.
To the old ones, endowed with
powers of Iove and attraction...
bind my fate
to that of the one I desire.
BiII?
And Iike this fIame,
Iike a phoenix from the ashes...
let me rise anew to claim
aII that shouId be mine.
Honey?
With a touch, grant me the power
to sway others to do my bidding.
And destroy those
who stand in my path.
For this, I offer up my heart...
my souI...
my bIood.
I spiII it in your name.
Yes, some witch.
What are you doing?
HeIIo?
Tamara?
What? I can't hear you.
lt's my cell. Reception's bad.
It's BiII.
l had to call you.
l've thought about what you said.
And l want you to know
that I care for you too.
This isn't Mr. NatoIIy.
l told you that someday you'd
find your pIace in the worId.
l'd like that place
to be with me.
-But what about Mrs. NatoIIy?
-We're having problems.
l don't want to talk about it
over the phone.
Can you meet me tonight?
Yes!
Come to the Capri Motel.
Room 39. 1 7h30, okay?
Tamara, l've been dreaming
about this for a Iong time.
l'd love to spend
the night with you.
I'd Iike that too.
Great. l'll see you then.
I Iove you.
It worked.
You are just so crueI.
What is taking him so Iong?
With aII the freshmen he's done
here, he shouId have a Iine.
We got both the rooms.
Phase one is compIete.
Why are we getting two rooms?
Have you ever heard
of exotic dancers, Rog?
I mean, of course.
Just heIp me
unIoad this video gear.
Hello?
Are we earIy?
No. It's gonna be a smaII party.
Yes, my foIks are going
out of town soon.
That's when we're having
the big bIow-out at my house.
''PatrickpaIooza 5'', baby.
-What's up, man? How you doing?
-How you doing?
AIright, it's shot time, peopIe.
Let's make it happen.
It's okay, I got us some wine.
So, she is tough to go or what?
So, about the Iocker room.
I'm sorry.
I'm gIad you couId come.
No probIem.
But you reaIIy shouId give Tamara
a break. She's a cooI girI.
AII right, cheers.
-Now that's one quaIity Iibation.
-You know what I'm taIking about?
Shawn, phase two?
Yes, I'm just going
to the car to get some more beer.
BiII?
-Is that the dancer?
-It sure is.
-What is this?
-A Iate night entertainment.
You guys know how to party, man!
-TeII me you Iove me, Tamara.
-I Iove you.
WeIcome to reaIity TV, bitch!
You didn't say it was her.
My God!
I can't beIieve you actuaIIy
thought he wouId sIeep with you.
You Iook Iike a cheap ugIy whore!
TeII me where she is right now!
That fucking dress.
You fucking Ioser.
Tamara!
You?
It's not what you think.
-I trusted you!
-No, wait!
Tamara!
FiIm that!
Tamara! Tamara!
Somebody shut her up!
Stop! Stop! Don't hurt her!
Don't hurt her!
Tamara, pIease, stop.
Bitch!
Tamara?
Is she aII right?
-I can't feeI a puIse.
-Move! Move!
She's dead, isn't she?
-Isn't she?
-No. No.
Wait. Let's think about this.
What's there
to think about? She's dead!
I know. There's nothing
we can do for her.
We can figure this out.
-Just caIm down.
-CaIm down?
-We kiIIed her.
-Shut up!
No one kiIIed her.
It was an accident.
I am not throwing my Iife away
because of this Ioser.
If we aII keep our mouth shut,
everyone wiII think she ran away.
No one has to know.
-Are you out of your mind?
-Listen, you IittIe shits!
You aII struggIed with her.
CaII the cops.
And I'II teII them that you
and your boyfriend set this up.
That you were fighting
with her when she feII.
It'II be your word against mine.
I've aIready got a record.
I'm not going to jaiI.
No way.
Roger?
I didn't know.
God.
-You're not Iike them.
-This is so wrong!
But I have a schoIarship
and I guess...
I can't beIieve I'm hearing this.
ChIoe?
She scratched me.
You too.
They're going to find
our skin under her naiIs.
Your hair's in her hand.
It's five against one. I've got
videotape to back up my story.
Who do you think
they're gonna beIieve?
AII right.
So, what's your fucking pIan?
We never taIk about this. Ever!
Let's finish it
and get out of here.
Wait.
This is reaIIy wrong,
burying her out here Iike this.
We can stiII caII the poIice.
It's not too Iate.
We've aIready decided. Let's
finish it and get out of here!
Leave him aIone!
I'm afraid it's too Iate.
I'm done. Can I go
to the bathroom?
Watch it!
You Iook a IittIe paIe.
Is something wrong?
Sorry, I'm Iate. Rough weekend.
I aImost died getting here.
You'II have to take
a make-up test.
Time's up peopIe.
Hand everything in.
Is something wrong, Jesse?
Thank you.
Can I taIk to you for a sec?
Sure.
About Friday. I was
just feeIing a bit vuInerabIe.
It's okay. Are you aII right now?.
As you can see, Mr. NatoIIy,
I'm better than aII right.
I'm perfect.
-What's up?
-It's Tamara. She's aIive.
-She just waIked into cIass.
-But how?.
She must have been unconscious.
No, she was dead.
ChIoe and I checked.
-ObviousIy, we were wrong.
-Did you guys taIk to her?
HeII no, I didn't taIk to her!
I was busy shitting my pants.
Then, we'II go to her and say,
''We didn't mean to hurt you.''
I'II make sure
she keeps her mouth shut.
We tried it your way
and buried her aIive.
I'II taIk to her.
What about how she Iooks now?.
Come on. She'd give HaIIe Berry
troubIe in the hottie department.
Tamara?
She was into aII that magic shit.
What if she reaIIy is a witch?
And what if you reaIIy are
a fucking moron?
We messed up.
That's aII. She wasn't dead.
AII right, we've got
to get to cIass.
Like I said, I'II taIk to her.
Gotta get a score
in this period. Set!
And the pass is good...
Tamara? Tamara?
Somebody shut her up!
Stop! Stop!
Don't hurt her!
Tamara, please, stop!
Bitch!
Tamara?
ls she all right?
-l can't feel a pulse.
-Move! Move!
She's dead, isn't she?
I don't know. Am I, Roger?
-Tamara?
-In the fIesh.
But... I... How?.
Do you reaIIy care how?.
Aren't you just gIad to se me?
God, yes.
Look, I'm sorry
for what happened.
You didn't mean
for me to get hurt.
-No, I swear.
-Things just got out of hand.
Yes. But you're okay.
And that's aII that matters.
Do you reaIIy think I'm okay?
You buried me, Roger.
I'm sorry.
Look, we thought that you.
Do you have any idea
what that was Iike?
-No. I...
-WeII, Iet me show you.
Scholarship... Scholarship...
But I have a schoIarship.
Imagine waking up in
the coId, wet ground.
Scared. AIone.
You don't know where you are.
How you got there.
You cIaw at the ground untiI
your hands are bIoody and raw.
You try to scream,
but dirt fiIIs your mouth.
And you feeI the bugs and worms
eating at your fIesh.
God.
God. Make it stop!
Now do you understand
what I went through?
AII because you were
too scared to stand up.
God.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
I guess everyone's right.
You are a Ioser.
And what wouId they think
if they knew the whoIe truth?
That you're
such a sad IittIe boy that you...
You thought you couId
bIeed the pain away.
But it's stiII there,
eating at you.
You know what your probIem is?
You never finish what you start.
Good afternoon, Hafton High.
l know a lot of you may view me
as just some Ioser video geek.
This weekend, l did something
horribIe. It made me reaIize...
you're right. I am a Ioser.
Although l can't change the past,
I can stiII make things right.
I can accept my punishment.
But first l want to offer you all
a IittIe advice.
Never be afraid
to stand up for what's right.
Don't just sit back
and aIIow yourseIf to.
Hear no eviI.
Roger! Roger!
Speak no eviI.
Roger!
See no evil.
I can't beIieve
he kiIIed himseIf.
If he wouId have known Tamara was
aIive, maybe he wouIdn't have.
-I shouId've toId him right away.
-It's not your fauIt.
Yes. He took the easy way out.
WouId you Iisten to yourseIves?
You are so busy...
trying to cIear your conscience,
you don't get it.
This is our fauIt. AII of it.
Don't be so hard
on yourseIves. Accidents happen.
ActuaIIy, I want to thank you.
Because of you, I'm not that
scared, insecure girI I was.
Now I know what I want.
Tamara, we need
to taIk about what happened.
We didn't know what they pIanned.
They said it was a party.
Yes, it was Patrick's idea.
-Dick! It was yours.
-It doesn't matter. It happened.
And what we did after
was inexcusabIe.
-I don't want excuses.
-What do you want?
You'II see.
You guys,
what did she mean by that?
What was that shit
about it being my idea?
Shut up.
Maybe she just wants
to forget aII this.
You seriousIy beIieve that?
Why not? You and I
were aIways nice to her.
Yes, untiI we buried her
in the woods.
How do we even know it was
reaIIy her? I mean, Iook at her.
-What if that magic...
-Don't start with that again.
You know, enough!
Something happened
in those woods.
I'm gonna find out what.
Here it is.
What if she's stiII here?
She dug herseIf out.
Why didn't she suffocate?
No! No!
-What is it?
-She's here!
-ChIoe, it's empty.
-I saw her.
Come on, it's aIright. Look.
See?
What is it?
It's a speII. But there's so much
bIood, I can't make it out.
See? I toId you.
She's a fucking witch.
Dude, keep it up
and I'm gonna bury you.
Maybe he's right.
Tamara, what are you doing here?
The door was unIocked.
I needed to taIk to someone.
-WeII, AIison's at schooI.
-I can wait.
I don't think that's a good idea.
PIease, Mr. NatoIIy?
I've been through so much IateIy.
And now with Roger.
Okay. She shouId be home soon.
You know?. I've been thinking
about what happened between us.
Nothing happened.
But, I'm sorry if I misIed you.
Did you?
-I didn't...
-Look at me, Mr. NatoIIy.
-Look, it was a misunderstanding.
-Look at me.
It's getting wet.
What?
The tabIe.
Are you gonna drink that?
So, do you Iike my new Iook?
I Iiked you the way you were.
This is me, Mr. NatoIIy.
Not that pathetic weakIing
you feIt sorry for.
I've never feIt sorry for you.
And you shouIdn't change
to pIease peopIe.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org