Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Thanks to
www.opensubtitles.org
God said to Abraham,
"Kill me a son."
Abe says,
"Man, you must be putting me on."
God say, "No."
Abe say, "What?"
God say,
"You can do what you want, Abe,
but the next time you see me coming,
you better run."
Abe says,
"Where do you want this killing done?"
And God says,
"Out on Highway 61."
The Serbs have taken over this Albanian
village. They're killing everyone in sight.
It's not a war,
it's a slaughter.
The Serbian commander,
he's in that mosque.
This is the third village
in a week he's destroyed.
We are to identify
and neutralise him.
We will proceed
under cover of NATO air strike,
commencing...
right about now! Move!
I'm in the nest.
Copy that.
Reagan is in the nest.
Cover fire, on my mark.
Three... two...
one!
- Sgt First Class Aaron Hallam.
- Yes, sir.
It is my privilege
to present to you the Silver Star,
one of our nation's
highest awards for valour.
Your bravery, judgment and outstanding
resolve are an example to all soldiers.
Your actions are the bedrock upon which
peace and democracy have been built.
Congratulations, Hallam.
What happened to you?
You stepped on a snare, didn't you?
Easy.
Take it easy.
Be still.
All right,
let me have that...
nasty thing.
All right.
Next time you see one of these,
you go the other way.
Okay, here we go.
You're good.
All right.
Now, get out of here.
Anybody here with the initials JW?
Yeah?
- This yours?
- Yeah.
What the...
No more snares on wolves, guys.
I got him.
- He was down there.
- What?
I saw him.
You need all that equipment
to kill a deer?
That's how we
make sure they're dead.
You guys
don't look like deer hunters.
When you kill with your own hands,
there is irreverence.
Is that right?
There is no reverence in what you do.
Where's your weapon?
Holy sm...
You're not here for the deer.
What's that?
Think you can
hunt me with those rifles?
Your rifles against my knife.
What are you, nuts?
What do you think?
Well, don't push it, asshole.
Where the fuck are you?
Come on, baby.
Get off!
God!
A little antifreeze with that?
- It's not that cold out.
- Maybe not to you.
- Thought you were on the wagon?
- Wheels fell off.
You running a fever?
I'm tired of the goddamn cold.
Not too crazy about the thaw, neither.
Get a hot water bottle.
Keep you company at night.
I don't want one. I want to
go to California for a few weeks.
Get some thoroughbreds,
do some fishing.
The Yellowtail jump into the boat
this time of year.
Yellowtail are not lying
Hello, Ted.
LT. How'd you know it was me?
I saw your pigeon-toed tracks.
What are you doing this far north?
Van Zandt wanted me
to show you something.
Personally.
- Been a few years.
- Okeechobee, 1 996.
Your agents got so scared of alligators.
One guy shit in his pants.
- Mike Handy.
- That was funny.
- You disappeared after that.
- I worked a few more, then quit.
Been in Portland for three years now.
We reached out for you
a few times.
- Let me ask you something.
- Yeah.
What the hell
are you doing out here?
Working for the Wildlife Fund.
You went to a lot of trouble
to get up here.
- You're a hard man to find.
- No, I'm not.
How hard am l to find
if you found me?
Van Zandt thinks it's important.
- He thinks everything's important.
- This one's different.
I don't do
that kind of work any more.
Why don't you have a look?
I really don't want to go back there.
All we're asking you to do
is take a look, LT.
Can we get prints off that paper?
- We sure can.
- And the door handles.
I'm concerned
about the number of squad agents.
I want to take these guys alive.
We need to deploy men
on the other side of the canyon.
I want to contain this area
and establish a parameter.
It's your call, Abby.
We're here to help.
You all right?
No, l hate those things.
I'm afraid of heights.
I'm Abby Durrell,
I'm the ASAC here.
I'm not sure how much
Harry told you about the...
Tell me what he told you
and we'll take it from there.
The two men were found
a half mile from here.
They were killed with a hatchet,
then gutted in a ritualistic fashion.
Every vital organ was cut.
I got a deputy
talking to the Paiute chief.
There's no Paiute ritual
for gutting a human body.
The dead men were dressed and
quartered the way you'd quarter a deer.
The Paiute are upset...
A Paiute wouldn't quarter
deer hunters unless...
What?
He's gonna eat 'em.
There were two men killed the same way
last week in Washington State.
They were forest service rangers,
which is how we got jurisdiction.
Where are the bodies?
We sent 'em to the lab yesterday.
- You need to see 'em?
- No.
You got too many men and horses here.
All these tracks, it's chaos.
You have a deer stand
or any coolers for packing meat?
Not within a five mile radius.
- No camp site?
- Still looking.
What do you know
about the victims?
As far as we know,
a couple businessmen from Mifnard.
- What else can we do for you?
- Nothing.
- Get everybody to fall back.
- Let's get everybody out of here.
Everybody, let's go.
Let's fall back.
Let's go!
Yeah, everyone!
- This is him.
- Who?
The guy who did it.
We're not sure
how many killers there were.
- One.
- How do you know?
He left his signature on that tree.
The deceased were able-bodied men.
They had rifles
with sophisticated scopes.
One of them had a 9 mm handgun
in his jacket.
It seems unlikely
one man with a hatchet...
He used a knife with a serrated edge
on one side and filet blade on the other.
One guy with a knife threw it
at this tree and killed those hunters?
Yeah.
He wore a size ten shoe with no tread,
like a slipper. Like this one.
He's out there.
- You're not going alone.
- That's the way l work.
- Take this.
- I don't need it.
Humour me. The battery's fully charged.
Please leave it on.
Okay.
- You don't have a gun?
- I don't like guns.
- How much time do we give you?
- If I'm not back in two days, I'm dead.
LT.
Remember me?
No.
You taught me.
I taught a lot of people.
How come you didn't
answer my letters?
How come you chopping up
all these people?
Did you see the scopes
they were using?
They weren't hunters, LT.
They were sweepers.
You're gonna have to come in, son.
Move up.
- He's down.
- Down, he's down!
Don't touch him.
I'm on the weapon.
Bring him in.
LT.
You did a hell of a job.
- He's one of yours?
- Yeah.
He's our man?
- Any idea why?
No, that'd be your job.
Coffee?
No, thank you, ma'am.
You don't have to talk to us
if you don't want to.
I understand that.
How about telling us your name?
We could start with that.
He knows my name.
Why don't you tell me
what happened in the woods?
Did you know 6 billion chickens
will die in slaughter houses this year?
What does that
have to do with what happened?
What if there was a species
above us in the food chain?
How do you think you'd feel
if that species lost respect for us,
and started slaughtering us wholesale?
I don't know.
But it's very interesting.
Do you understand it?
Oh, yeah.
Good.
What is it you want to tell Mr Bonham
you don't want to tell me?
I'd like to talk to him
about Operation Black Eagle...
Wanna get yourself killed? His name
is Sgt First Class Aaron Hallam.
You remember me.
- They're recording this.
- Good, there'll be a record.
And it'll never say what you want.
Then what am l doing here?
Mort, you've got to help me out here.
Is this our guy or not?
I know. There are always variables.
But we can't indict a variable.
Boss?
We understand you have a man named
Aaron Hallam in your custody?
How much do you know
about Mr Hallam?
Born in 1 968.
Raised in Burl County,
West Virginia.
High school equivalency.
Although he scored
off the charts in science.
Joined the Army at 1 8.
That's the strange part.
What's that, sir?
It doesn't really tell us
any more about him.
The record's incomplete.
Not even a date of discharge.
Sgt Hallam is unofficially listed
as Missing In Action...
Sir.
Unofficially?
That's a cover.
That means
he's still doing work for you.
We're here to take possession
of your prisoner, sir.
This is not a military base.
Your man very likely killed
and mutilated four hunters
on federal land.
I think you should
take a look at this, sir.
Unless we've been invaded by a foreign
power and are officially at war,
you don't have any authority here.
I know you wanna get out of here,
but we're waiting on the blood results.
Ever use that thing?
- Did l ever shoot anyone?
- Yeah.
- Would you ask a guy that question?
As a matter of fact, l have.
Do we have to go into it?
- No.
- Okay.
Not a great view of the city.
It's a wilderness.
What's your relationship to Hallam?
- I trained him.
- To do what?
Trained him to survive.
I trained him to kill.
I trained a lot of people like him.
The "best of the best."
I pulled your file.
- You were never in the military.
- No.
- You just work for them?
- Yeah.
- Like a contractor?
You don't like to talk about it, do you?
No.
My father was an Army colonel.
When my brother
was killed in Vietnam,
he decided we wasn't going to lose
another son to that particular war.
Dad was a tracker
before he joined the Army,
and l learned what l do from him.
What about Hallam?
He's unusual.
He can kill anybody.
Without regret.
Most people he killed never knew
he was in the same room with them.
How'd you feel about that?
I don't know.
I never had to kill anybody myself.
I just taught people how.
In many ways,
Hallam is a fine warrior.
After a tourin Kosovo, he was given
another sensitive assignment.
Off the books.
H.e went too far.
A lot of innocent people
lost their lives.
Hallam's battle stress
has become so deep
it is a part of his personality.
And it's impossible to reverse.
He's a killing machine.
There is no way he can be indicted,
or tried in open court, or any court.
He cannot be processed,
interviewed,
charged with a crime,
or cocked out as a psycho.
His picture cannot appear
in any newspaper.
As far as the world
is concerned, sir,
Aaron Hallam doesn't exist.
He's one of them.
They'll handle it.
You know why you're here, Aaron.
You wandered off the range.
This is way too messy.
You're supposed to be precise.
They weren't his family.
They were soldiers, Dale.
There was no backup,
no way for me to get out.
I was set up.
That's bullshit.
You fucked up.
Your actions resulted in the injury
and death of unarmed civilians.
They had weapons.
That's the problem.
You can't tell the sharks
from the guppies any more.
That's what they're using now?
Supposed to be painless.
Course, he never used it on himself...
Release him.
Release him now!
- Flying to Vancouver?
- Yeah.
Then a connecting flight?
No. I drive.
Takes about eight hours.
That's right, you don't like flying.
Must be worth it.
It's a special place. You ought to
come up sometime. You'd like it.
You don't have to wear two guns all
the time. Your posture would change.
It's an open invitation.
Is it painless, Dale?
- We need paramedics!
- It's gonna explode!
- See if you can help...
- No, l can't!
Does anyone know
what's going on?
Is anyone on their way?
- Paramedic! Paramedic!
- You all right?
I'm okay, I'm okay!
My buddies are in there.
Get 'em out, get 'em out!
Somebody call an ambulance.
You're okay.
Get 'em out!
Shit!
- You go over there.
- Okay, yeah.
One, two...
three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten.
Ready or not, here l come.
We have a breaking story.
We're going to
our correspondent
who is live outside the tunnel
to Forest Park. Jeff?
We have just arrived on the
scene of a terrible accident
outside the tunnel
in Forest Park.
This is some sort of van
that was transporting people.
We can tell you there are...
I will teach you how to kill.
Quickly, accurately,
efficiently.
It will become a reflex action.
You will learn how to enter a
combat zone and evaporate into shadow.
You will learn
how to survive.
Or you will not.
Ready...
Arm! Hut!
Reverse your grip.
Bring your knife
from the inside of his arm,
sever the connecting tissue, pulling
his finger away from the trigger.
Come around his shoulder,
grab the strap, choke him.
Come into his heart, to the top of his
sternum and bring him to the ground.
Arm throw, heart, leg,
leg, arm, lung. Good.
Slice through that thigh,
into this thigh and that femoral artery.
You'll notice this arm
is in your way.
The only thing this arm
can do to hurt you
is block the lung puncture
you're about to do.
Push this arm over in front of his face.
Go into his lung.
Now, arm, neck,
heart, leg, leg, lung!
One, two, three,
four, five. Six!
One, two...
three,
power assist four,
five, six.
One, two, three,
four, five, six!
...two, three, four,
five, six.
One, two, three,
four, five, six.
Make this cut
a good power assist.
You're looking for his backbone.
Here we go.
Go.
There we go.
Once again.
LT,
I don't think l can do this any more.
The nightmares
are getting worse.
I think I'm losing it, LT.
I need to talk to you.
I don't know if you've
been getting my letters, LT.
I need to hear from you,
or talk to you.
You've been like
a father to me.
Please write.
Once you are able to
kill mentally,
the physical part
will be easy.
The difficult part...
is learning how to turn it off.
At this point,
all we know for sure
is we have three
confirmed fatalities.
We don't know
if there were other passengers
inside this van
when it crashed.
Access is limited.
We have no new information
from either the police or the FBI.
However, the van appears
to be a military vehicle.
possibly the type used
to transport prisoners.
We'll try to get confirmation.
Once again,
information very sketchy.
Rescue crews still on the scene
along with FBI agents and technicians.
We're getting no comment
from agents on the scene.
- What happened?
- Hallam's loose.
Hello, Irene.
Aaron.
You scared me.
It's good to see you.
I'm not listening to you.
Everything you told me was a lie.
I've never lied to you.
Where have you been
the last six months?
- Doing stuff for the government.
- That's a damn lie!
Get out of here.
I don't want to see you again.
Aaron?
- Aaron, you're back!
- Hey, Loretta.
It's good to see you!
l missed you so much.
- How's my big girl?
- Where have you been?
Loretta, l need you
to do your homework.
Can l visit with Aaron some more?
You can visit later.
- Are you staying for dinner?
- Go do your homework.
Don't think you're just
gonna step back into our lives.
I understand, Irene.
I don't even know
what you do for a living.
Did you look in my locker?
How could l do that?
You got four locks
on that thing.
What track is that?
- A squirrel.
- That's right.
Where is the next one?
- Um...
- Bring it down.
Where's the next one?
- I can't tell.
- Hold it flat.
See? Every nine inches.
That's the gallop pattern.
- Every nine inches.
- Oh, yeah. I see.
- What's this one?
- A racoon.
How come
you never see any?
They hide, to survive.
Men don't respect animals any more.
They run 'em down or
kill 'em any chance they get.
I think that's sad.
That's only Kitty.
Here, Kitty.
You don't want
to bother him now.
Why?
He's hunting, too.
Does he know we're here?
- He knows.
- How?
He can sense it.
She's so happy to see you.
Sit down.
What's this?
You got to leave here.
You got to get out of Portland.
- What?
- You're in danger.
- Why am l in danger?
- You and Loretta.
And they'll come here
and burn this house down.
What are you talking about?
We got visual.
Copy that, stand by.
See you later, Dad!
All right, sweetie.
You wait for me
after school,
I'll be there
to pick you up, okay?
- Is everything okay, Mommy?
- Everything's fine.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
- See you later, alligator.
- Bye.
- ..approaching.
- Roger that, we got her.
Irene Kravitz? Agent Durrell.
Is that your little girl?
Loretta, is it?
That's right.
- We'd like to talk to you.
- About what?
It's just routine,
but it'd be a lot easier inside.
If you make us come back with a warrant,
it won't be routine any more.
Going somewhere, Mrs Kravitz?
No, I'm just cleaning stuff up,
trying to get organised.
We're looking for a man named
Aaron Hallam. Have you seen him?
- Not for a few months.
- But you know him?
This have to do
with his government work?
When's the last time
you saw him?
I don't remember.
A few months ago, he sort of took off.
That's the way he is.
Is he here, Irene?
What's this about?
What's Aaron done?
Please have a seat, Irene.
Nobody said he's done anything.
FBI wouldn't be here
if he hadn't done something.
When did you and Aaron meet?
Eight months ago, maybe. Stayed here
awhile, then he just took off.
He tell you where he was going?
Is he still here?
I said l ain't seen him in months.
How many times
do l have to say that?
Excuse me, sir.
Where are you going?
You wouldn't be doing him
or your daughter any good.
What do you know
about my daughter?
Don't worry...
We really just want
to talk to you.
That's all we want
to do here.
Just sitting here
having a talk, that's all.
You shouldn't worry.
You want someone around for her.
But you have to look out for her safety.
Is this the right guy
to have around your daughter?
What has Aaron done?
We just want to talk to him.
Did he kill somebody?
Come in.
You care about
these people here, Aaron?
You're gonna get 'em hurt.
- You here to sweep me, LT?
- You know l don't do that.
How do l know that?
They are coming for you.
They've been coming for me
for a long time, LT.
You have to answer
for what you've done.
I have to live with what I've done.
You can say
whatever you want.
I don't trust you, LT.
If you cross this line,
you better be ready to kill me.
Don't move.
Put your hands on your head
and get on the floor.
I said get on the floor. Now!
Get down.
That's his Silver Star.
That is a sketch
l made for a knife.
It's addressed to you.
"LT, those guys you trained
to come and kill me,
they're not soldiers.
They're... robots."
We've got a positive ID
at the river front construction site.
We're headed there, over.
1 0-9 that location.
This is agent-in-charge Van Zandt.
Agent Moret. Site foreman Hank Hooker.
Our guy saw him
pull up near that tunnel.
- How many men work down there?
- Three dozen.
We need an exact count
and blueprints.
This is an overview of the site.
There's four major sections.
He probably went down here
in the red section.
- How far does this thing extend?
- 1 2 square blocks.
We'll cover the red section.
Only our people.
Show me the other three entrances.
He went in there.
There's three other entrances.
Make sure
they're completely blocked off.
FBI. Step away from the column
with your hands up.
Let me see your hands!
7-20, this is number one.
I need backup right now.
Red section, tunnel A.
Did you hear me? l said,
step away from the column now!
Step away from
the fucking column.
My radio's dead.
Shit.
Jesus Christ.
Bobby!
Leave it in, don't touch him!
Open his mouth.
Keep pressure on the wound!
Command post.
We have an agent down.
Sector red, sector red!
Get me them EMTs now!
ASAP!
Bobby?
Bobby, listen to me!
Subject spotted.
East bound, number 2 lane.
- Close off both ends of the bridge.
- Two SWAT teams on their way.
Get everybody off the bridge.
Leave that car!
Excuse me.
- Get down! Leave this between us.
- Don't get in the way!
Get everybody down on the floor.
Get down!
He's on the tower!
Target of opportunity.
He's on the tower! Fire!
Cease fire!
Hold your fire.
Captain, l need two or three
of your officers on each bridge.
Sweep the western sea wall,
and shut down the bike paths.
I need recon teams
on both sides of the river.
Sniper units to cover
each team's advance.
The currents are strong enough
to carry him and he swims like a fish.
This is our show, Bonham.
How many people you willing to lose?
He will kill as many of you as he can.
Decide now on an acceptable body count.
- Knock it off.
- You'll get more dead bodies
if you let these guys
declare war on my boy.
I made him what he is
and l can stop him.
We've lost two of our people.
Best agents l ever served with.
Hallam belongs to us.
If he's alive, he won't come in.
Right.
- Hallam!
- Get on the ground!
God said to Abraham,
kill me a son.
# There's a man goin' round
# Takin' names
# And he decides who to free
# And who to blame
# Everybody won't be treated
all the same
# There'll be a golden ladder
# Reaching down
# When the man comes around
# The hairs on your arm will stand up
# At the terror
in each sip and in each sup
# Will you partake
of that last offered cup
# Or disappear
into the potter's ground
# When the man comes around?
# H.ear the trumpets,
hear the pipers
# One hundred million
angels singing
# Multitudes are marching
# To the big kettle drum
# Voices calling,
voices crying
# Some are born
and some are dying
# It's Alpha and Omega's
kingdom come
# And the whirlwind
# Is in the thorn tree
# The virgins are all
trimming their wicks
# The whirlwind
is in the thorn tree
# It's hard for thee
to kick against the pricks
# Til I Armageddon,
so shalom, no shalom
# Then the father hen
will call his chickens home
# The wise men
will bow down before the throne
# And at his feet,
they'll cast a golden crown
# When the man W??????Rund
# Whoever is unjust,
let him be unjust still
# Whoever is righteous
# Let him be righteous still
# Whoeveris filthy,
let him be filthy still
# Listen to the words
long written down
# When the man comes around
# H.ear the trumpets,
hear the pipers
# One hundred million
angels singing
# Multitudes are marching
# To the big kettle drum
# Voices calling,
voices crying
# Some are born
and some are dying
# It's Alpha and Omega's
kingdom come
# And the whirlwind
# Is in the thorn tree
# The virgins
are all trimming their wicks
# The whirlwind
is in the thorn tree
# It's hard for thee
to kick against the pricks
# In measured hundred weight
# And penny pound
# When the man comes around #
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org