Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Bling-Bling.
(Laughs)
Bling-Bling, baby.
Yo, what took
you so long, ese?
Stuff isn't easy to find
this time of night.
What's up, 'Seel?
(Screams)
That's some good shit.
Yeah... Now I can eat
my Fruity Flakes.
(Surf music playing)
I'll be right back.
(Groaning)
(Knocking)
Hey, Blue Crush,
where you been?
Catching some waves.
I'm a total hard-Core
surfer chick.
At night?
In the middle of Texas?
I told you... I'm hard-Core.
What's that?
I'm writing
my local congressman,
Because I'm worried about
the rapidly decaying future
Of Social Security.
During a party? Why?
Because everyone's
labeled me rebellious,
So I'm rebelling
against the rebellious label
By being conscientious
in rebellion.
Duh.
Michelle, I can't stop
thinking about you.
That night when we kissed,
and I...
Bobbled your boobies...
I don't want to talk about it.
Why not?
Why won't you give me a chance?
(Gentle music playing)
Because if we went out,
You'd pick me up, we'd
drive out to the lake,
Have a little picnic,
some wine,
We'd lay out on
a blanket and ball.
And ball, ball,
ball, ball, ball.
We'd do it over and over
for hours and hours.
And I would ride you so hard
You wouldn't be able
to walk for weeks.
We'd do it every day.
All the time.
Always trying new things
And different positions.
Then we'd get married,
Move into a nice house
and have kids.
Two vacations a year.
One on a beach, and one
most likely in Europe,
With the occasional
Africa or Asia.
Second home on a lake,
early retirement.
Never tiring of
each other's bodies
Or lessening
the frequency of sex.
Well, excuse me.
But that is not the type
of life that I would want.
That sounded pretty good to me.
Especially the balling part.
Hmm.
You know what, Michelle?
I bet, under that tough
exterior of yours,
Under all that self-Tanner
and macrame bikini,
There's something
very warm and soft.
And pink.
Probably smells a little bit,
but not too much.
I am not going to let you
sweet-Talk me, Lance Truman.
Fine.
(Muffled music plays)
(Loud music plays)
(Girls giggling)
I hope you are kidding me.
A study group.
Please tell me
This is some kind of a joke.
Calculus.
Shakespeare?
You all signed a contract.
What are you trying to do?
Ruin your season
before it even begins, huh?
No, Coach. We're simply
trying to keep up our G.P.A.S.
Oh, is that what you call it?
Mm-Hmm. You make me sick,
all of you.
Now, I was hoping...
That you kids would
have the gumption
To do this on your own.
But, apparently,
I'm gonna have to
take you by the friggin' hand.
You won a football game!
Everybody knows that after
you win a football game
You're supposed to consume
alcohol at a dangerous rate!
Ah!
You should be
popping ecstasy, man!
Oh, yeah,
and huffin' some paint!
What's the color?
Good times.
(Sniffing)
Yeah.
Look at me now, man.
Yeah, I brought all these
illegal drugs to the party...
In my fake Louis Vuitton bag
that's chock-Full
Of pirated DVDs
I got down in Chinatown.
Who cares, man?
I'm just having some fun,
because I won a football game.
Yeah! I'm a huge
drug-Pushing drug guy.
Check me out.
(Bong water gurgling)
Gotta have some more of that.
(Groaning)
That's the right spot.
(Trumpeting)
Now I'm crazy wasted
with a bunch of minors
And I'm taking off
all my clothes.
(Whimpers)
Yeah, it's cool, man.
I'm a football player.
That's what we do!
Ow!
It's the cops!
You'll never take me alive.
(Yelling)
Freeze, tighty-Whities!
(Electrical buzzing)
Ah! Right in my Reggie Bush!
(Grunts)
(Buzzer sounds, groaning)
Oh, come on.
You have got to be kidding me.
You can do it! Come on!
Get it! Get it!
Get it!
(Groaning)
Aw! I'm sorry, Clint.
I couldn't get it
unstuck either.
Well, thanks for trying.
I should just ask for another one,
- But that piece goes so well with the room.
- Mm-Hmm.
It does coordinate nicely
with those throw pillows.
- Wanna have sex again?
- No, I'm good.
(Lock buzzing)
- Who are you?
- I'm the warden.
You can go free
If you beat me in hoops...
- One on one.
- Hoops?
Me likey.
I feel I should warn you.
I was the leading scorer
of the Jewish community center
Bitty-Boy's Basketball League
three years straight.
Well, I think I'm gonna
spare you the humiliation
And just wait to be bailed out.
(Chuckling)
(Lock buzzing)
Psst!
Are you sure you
don't want to cuddle?
NARRATOR:
And so, Coach called the only man
He knew he could
always count on.
The man who had been by his
side through everything.
The only man he knew
he could trust.
His partner, his rock, the wind
beneath his wings-Me.
Thanks for coming, Freddie.
How long before
you can get me out?
I'm not going to be
able to do that, Coach.
What? Why?
It was right about then
that Coach Fields
Realized something was afoot.
His old friend Freddie
had betrayed him
And orchestrated a most
nefarious scheme
- That would allow Freddie...
- Why you talking like that?
Ooh, my bad.
But now you know, Coach.
The reason why I wanted you to
be head coach of the Comebacks
Is because I'm head coach
Of the Lone Star State Unbeatables.
Coach of the number one
team in the conference.
Yeah. Yeah.
And I want it to stay that way.
See, I knew the Comebacks
had a shot this year.
And I also knew, if I could
talk you back into coaching
They'd sink like a stone,
Because that's what you do, Coach-
You lose!
(Crying):
You bastard.
How could you?
Freddie decided
it was time to go.
As for Coach, he had
bigger things to worry about.
Why, just this morning,
He banged the wife
of the guy sitting next to him.
Come on, Turbo.
That's impossible.
I'm in here with you.
I'll get you for this!
(Laughs)
Send a message to the warden.
I'll take him up
on his little offer.
Your interpersonal skills are horrible.
And you're a terrible gossip.
Everybody knows that.
People talk about you.
You cheat at checkers.
Oh, why resist it? Aah.
Oop da. Yeah, easy.
That's right.
(Rap music plays)
(Soft rock music plays)
(Grunts)
Make it, take it, be-Yotch.
(Rapid hip-Hop
scratch intro plays)
Yeah! Come on!
Is that all you got?
I hope you weren't
planning on leaving today.
(Grunting)
(Music continues)
FIELDS:
Get that shit outta here.
It's called skills, junior.
And I guess I got some. Whoa.
(Music continues)
(Laughing)
Change of rules.
Even if you win,
you're still gonna stay here.
(Grunts aggressively)
What you looking at?
I'm not getting it.
Fine.
- I'll get it.
- (Lock buzzing)
I got it.
Hurry up!
(Tires squealing)
Shit.
(Lock buzzing)
All right, gang, today we play
the Friday Night Lights.
They're one of the best teams
in the conference.
I'm not going to lie to you.
There's a lot of drama
going on over there.
Just found out that
Rick fell off the wagon.
He's drinking again.
And Lyla is cheating on Jason
With Tim, if you can believe that.
Smash can't
control his temper,
And I just found out
That last night,
Billy and Tyra
Had a pre-Homecoming party
And it got broken
up by the cops,
Which means, for us...
Automatic victory-
They're not gonna make it!
(Cheering, whooping)
Rock n' roll!
(Whistle blows)
(Rock song playing)
Blue, 22! Hike!
(Baby crying)
(Rock song continues)
(Yelling)
(Needle buzzing)
(Rock song continues)
(Cheering)
- Hey.
- Hey, Coach.
- How's it going, Coach?
- Good game, guys.
Thanks
(Song fades)
(Sighs)
Oh, for the love of the game.
(Glass shattering)
(Chain clinking)
(Gears whirring)
NEWSCASTER:
We all remember that touching story
Of the autistic
high school boy
Who was finally
given his chance to play.
This amazing story
has inspired people
From all different
walks of life.
Last night,
at Cleveland General Hospital,
Dr. Edmund Grand allowed Billy,
a longtime orderly,
A chance at his dream.
Touching story
out of Cleveland.
Time of death- 8:05.
(Door opens)
There you are.
Well...
(Loudly sighs)
Tonight should be the greatest
night of my life, Barb.
But those kids,
they still just don't get it.
Who's that?
Who's who?
That guy in the
bed with you.
Right there.
Oh... um...
I didn't think
you'd mind.
We-We took in a foreign
exchange student.
He's a foreign
exchange student?
Uh-Huh.
Where you from?
I'm from, uh...
Banging-Your-Wife-Istan.
Where is that?
It's, uh...
It's a little south of, uh,
Doing-Barb's-Fine-Ass-Yvania.
All right, Coach, all right.
I... I just couldn't
take it anymore.
You were never here,
and I am a woman
- In her sexual prime.
- Yeah.
Don't try to stop me, Coach.
I have finally found a man
who gives me what I need.
There isn't a Doing-Barb's-
Fine-Ass-Yvania, is there?
Is there?
(Whistling)
Big story developing
out of Plainfolk, Texas.
Heartland State head coach
Lambeau Fields
Is taking an unusual stance
against academic excellence.
He has locked his team
out of practice all week,
And now the squad is in danger
of forfeiting the upcoming
Conference championship
at the Toilet Bowl.
(Groans)
You sure got to have some
big clankers to come in here.
Go ahead. Do your worst.
My wife left me.
Aw, hell.
It's my fault.
I forgot she was there.
Boys, if you find
that perfect gal
That has all
the little things,
And, yet, she's willing
to enhance them surgically
Into bigger things.
And she doesn't mind
showing them to your friends
At a New Year's Eve party,
That's a gal.
- Yeah.
- That's the gal.
Well, don't take it so hard,
poon cheeks.
We've all walking in
on a loved one
Getting barn-Doored
by a half rack of bird doggers.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, we sure have.
(Sighs):
Ow.
Hell, I remember
when my Dorothy left me,
And I did everything
I could to get her back.
And when I did, I made sure
that she'd never leave me again.
How'd you do that?
I treated her like a queen-
Like an Egyptian queen.
Mummified and entombed her
in the basement.
Her shrieks of help
like music to my ears.
It's all about communication, fellas.
My Jeanie, she used to wag
her finger in front of my face
And bug the bejesus
out of me.
But, well, we sat down
and when we discussed it
In a mature manner and-And-
And now sh-She'll never,
Never wave this finger
in front of me again.
(Mumbling):Amen to that.
Hey, you know what?
I'm gonna tell you something.
It's about compromise.
Now take Salamander here.
Now we get up in each other's
rifle racks now and again.
But then we make up and talk
about it. We bangity-Boo.
You know what I'm saying, Coach?
Solid advice, fellas.
You're good people.
(Chain rattling)
It's still locked.
(Horn honking)
(Latin music on radio)
What's up, guys?
It's time to do something
we should have done long ago.
Get in the back.
(Whooping, cheering)
Let's go.
Let's do it!
(Whooping)
I think we're gonna need
a bigger truck.
I can't believe you, Dad.
Haven't you put
the team through enough?
They did it to themselves, Michelle.
I finally found someone
that I care about
And you're taking
away his dreams.
Sweetie, Trotter
only cares about himself.
I don't like Trotter anymore.
There's somebody else.
Someone kind and sensitive.
Someone who
Loves to laugh and...
Makes me feel wanted and alive.
Michelle, I'm your daddy.
I'm talking about Lance.
Oh... Oh, good.
He's a good boy.
He has a future.
This could be the real thing.
I want what you and Mom have.
Herpes.
No!
True love.
Oh...
(Sighs)
Well, if you find it,
hold on to it tight.
Look at me. I blew it.
I promised your mother
I wouldn't let this job
Get in the way of our family,
and I failed her.
It's not too late, Dad.
You can change all of this.
All you have to do
is win the championship.
Can't I lose by just a little?
No, Dad. You have to win.
You've spent your
whole life losing,
And this is your last,
and actually first chance,
To prove everyone wrong.
I know you're scared.
But you have to remember,
There used to be a...
A big, big man inside of you.
There's a reason for that.
I was in prison,
I didn't have a choice.
No, uh...
What I'm trying to say is that...
I believe in you, Dad.
Oh...
And Mom does, too.
Sweetie...
Thank you.
Well...
Then I better take care of business.
And when I'm done, we're gonna
win that championship.
(Rock music plays)
What the hell
is going on here?
Hey, Coach.
Buddy Boy smashed a whole
12-Pack over his forehead.
I Pod's doing body shots
out of his belly button.
And Jorge, he's been
dancing like this
For the past six hours.
And Jasminder,
she made 300 bucks.
And I think that Randy
lost his cherry
To Gwen Stefani over there.
And our signed contracts.
I have never been so proud
of a team in my entire life.
ALL: Yes!
Who do you play for?
ALL: Comebacks!
Hello, everyone.
Al Michaels, along with
John Madden, and welcome
To Odessa, Texas, home of
the second annual Toilet Bowl.
MADDEN'S VOICE: And-And this is
the place you really want to be, Al-
I mean, right in the middle
of the Toilet Bowl.
I mean, there's no place
in the world I'd rather be.
(Cheering)
(Ominous music plays)
What's this, Freddie?
Your players look like a bunch
of thankless thugs and thieves.
That's because they are.
They're my gridiron gang.
So, you want to forfeit,
Save yourself a lot of
embarrassment and pain?
Why would I start now?
Lance!
Michelle.
I left something
for you in your locker.
For good luck.
I know.
(Whispers):
I'm wearing it.
What?
The lace bra and the...
Crotch-Less panties.
No. I left you a note.
Oh.
A note saying that I'm sorry
For the way that I treated you.
That I was afraid
of a real relationship.
That I'm not afraid anymore.
That I am dying to let
you know how much I love you.
Nope, I never got that.
Oh. Okay, well, check.
Maybe it fell into the back
of your locker or something.
Yeah, I'll... okay.
Lance.
Wait.
There's something else
that I wanted to give you.
This.
(Pop music plays)
(Music fades)
Well, isn't that sweet?
Trotter...
We'll settle this on the field.
Woo! Michelle!
Got your letter, baby.
You and me after
the game, mama.
(Grunting rhythmically)
Woo! Yeah.
(Groans)
John, the excitement is so thick
In this stadium,
you could cut it with a knife.
MADDEN'S VOICE:
A-A-And there's two things
That I love to cut with a knife.
One of'em is turkey,
and the other one is excitement.
And if you're a Comebacks fan,
You got to hope
they're not the turkeys.
MICHAELS' VOICE:
But you have to believe
The Unbeatables will be
the guys with the knives.
Take a look down there-
It's unbelievable what's going on.!
(Air horns blowing)
Believers coming through!
- That's right! Get up!
- Get up!
- That's right. What's up?
- Come on. What's up!
What's up, eighth row?
Uh-Uh!
MICHAELS' VOICE:
And the team captains
Take the field, ready
for the ceremonial coin toss.
Call it in the air.
And when I say "it,"
I do mean the coin.
(Exhales sharply)
Where is it?
Now where is it?
It's right here in your ear.
(Kiss)
Call it in the air.
We'll receive.
(Crowd cheering)
(Loud rock music plays)
(Crowd roars)
(Loud grunt)
Yeah, baby! Yeah!
Okay, ready... hut!
MICHAELS' VOICE:
Unbeatables back to pass.
He's wide open.!
The bomb.!
He could go
All the way...
To Mexico.!
(Reggae music plays)
(Players clap, shout)
Green-20!
Hut!
(Grunting)
Nah, you take that!
You take that!
(Grunting)
Ooh!
Like you took my girl!
Personal foul.
Cock blocking.
Look, it's nothing personal, Trotter.
I'm in love with her, man.
Man, only thing you love
is taking my girl from me.
JORGE:
Man, would you guys shut up?
This game's bigger
than the two of you.
Football taught me
how to cope...
With anger, with life.
This team's all I got.
Without it, I have nothing.
Back on the skreets.
Dude,
Your parents
just bought you a house.
A condo.
A junior one-Bedroom.
Where am I supposed
to park my Prius, dawg?
All right, all right.
Pro-Right-94, on one.
On one. Ready?
Break!
Hut!
How about a flag, ref?
My guy's getting mugged out there.
(Whimpering): Don't take
my Gold Card, man. Come on.
That's ridiculous.
How much is he paying you?
A 1,000 dollars a call.
Twice the going rate.
(Exhales sharply)
Where is it now?
Hut!
(Grunting)
(Gunshot)
(Grunts)
Come on, ref!
That's attempted homicide!
You gotta call that!
(Groans)
What are you guys, blind?
(Dog barks, whines)
MICHAELS' VOICE:
Unbeatables up the middle
For an easy touchdown.!
They're running
all over the Comebacks,
Who are more than overmatched.
JIM ROME'S VOICE:
Jim Rome here, and this is a ridiculous
Half-Time score:35 to nothing.!
BOTH (chanting weakly):
We believe. We believe.
(Long sigh)
We believe.
So, you ready to give up?
Almost.
MADDEN'S VOICE:
Hey, hey, my favorite part of the game-
The half-Time show.!
Janet Jackson and Justin
Timberlake couldn't make it,
So instead, we present you
with this wholesome salute
To American values.
(Piano plays brief intro)
#The weekend's here #
# The weather's nice,
two football teams are playin' #
# I put your
favorite beer on ice #
#But the couch
is where you're staying #
# The game is
on the plasma screen #
#Got deep-Fried snacks
for munchin' #
# Rootin' for
the home team #
#Oops, wardrobe
malfunction #
(Rock music playing)
(Music ends)
MADDEN'S VOICE:
I mean, I mean,
It started out where she
was wearing
A lot of clothes,
then she wasn't wearing
and then boom, I got a chubby.
Take a knee.
Listen up.
I've been a loser all my life.
I came into this world ass-First.
I was raised as a girl till
my walnuts dropped at age 13.
I didn't lose my virginity
until I was 22.
That was by accident.
I didn't know
I was gonna have to pay for it-
I thought it was a date.
I've destroyed everything
I've ever touched,
Chased away everyone
who's ever loved me.
I am...
...a failure as a husband
And a father and a coach.
And a human being.
(Fields sobbing)
(Quiet sobs)
Um... Coach?
Isn't this the part
Where you turn
your personal tragedies
And shortcomings
Into a rousing,
inspirational rally cry?
Huh?
Oh. That's a great idea.
You're a real asset
to the team!
Well, thanks, Coach.
Does that mean I can play
in the second half?
No, absolutely not.
All right.
I don't think
I have to tell you all,
The scope
of the second half is to...
Aim high.
And I...
Pledge... to all of you.
That you will be
Showered...
By the cheers
And shouts of joy...
From your fans.
It depends...
...on you now.
Remember...
Your preparation
H...
And you can all be...
Champs!
(Shouting)
Yeah, champs!
All right, let's close our eyes
and bow our heads.
(Closes zipper)
Okay, you can open
your eyes again.
All right, let's go get 'em!
(Shouting)
MICHAELS' VOICE:
Second half just under way,
And despite the score,
it seems the Comebacks
Are even more fired up.!
MADDEN'S VOICE:
And nobody wants this
More than Coach Fields.
That's the way!
Hope you had a good rest, Oprah.
Actually, Coach gave
a very inspirational spee...
Wait a minute, what'd you say?
Oprah. I'm saying you're
as fat as Oprah, you fat ass!
(Seething): Are you
saying Oprah's fat?
Oprah's an incisive
and charitable lady,
You miserable piece of shit!
(Vicious growling)
MICHAELS' VOICE:
The toss to Trotter...
(Loud grunt)
Ooh.! And Truman lays
a huge block.!
Go, go!
(Whistle blows)
Yeah!
That's the way!
(Groans)
Truman scrambling.
Nowhere to go.!
Oh, look at that, Trotter
takes out two Unbeatables.!
MADDEN'S VOICE:
I mean, I mean,
Looks like he's
gonna score, Al.!
The Comebacks are finally
starting to play like a team.!
Yes! Yes! Yes.
(Grunts):
Oh!
(Grunting)
- Yeah!
Nice block.
Thanks.
Nice run.
(Quiet music playing)
Hey, Lance.
Be good to her, man.
Be good to her, too.
(Sighs)
Not all about winning, is it?
Hey, cameraman!
I hope you're
watching, Barb.
MICHAELS' VOICE:
John, it looks like Coach Fields
Is holding up the sign,
"I heart you. "
Oh, he loves me.
Like chili fries
and the smell of his own burps.
BOTH (chanting): He loves you, Barb.
He loves you, Barb.
(Crying)
Why can't I have that?
It's so beautiful.
Aww.
Hey, Coach!
Suppose I can get in the game?
Hey, guys, look who's back.
- I'm a quick healer.
- Hey, gang.
The cavalry's arrived.
And he goes by the name of-
ALL: Aseel Tare.
Okay, I got it. ACL Tear,
get out there. Let's go.
Not you Randy. Not you.
Set!
Brown-88! Hike!
MICHAELS' VOICE:
Aseel Tare with the carry.
Look at that.!
He's got the entire defense
on his back.
The pile is clearing, John.
MADDEN'S VOICE:
Yeah, yeah, it is. And take a look at that.
(Chuckling)
He got ripped into pieces.
Oh!
(Aseel groaning)
No worries!
I'm a quick healer. Whoo!
Yeah!
MICHAELS' VOICE:
John, what we're seeing here
Is a definite shift
in momentum.
MADDEN'S VOICE:
I mean, we-we really are, Al.
I mean, y-You take a look
at what's happening
And they were down by a lot
And now they're not down
by as much
And-And pretty soon
they could erase this deficit.
(Chanting alone):
Randy.
(Others join in):
Randy! Randy!
(Crowd joining in):
Randy! Randy! Randy! Randy!
Randy! Randy! Randy!
Randy! Randy!
(Chanting continues)
They're calling your name, son.
Get out there!
Randy! Randy!
(Chanting continues)
Go! Go, Randy!
MICHAELS' VOICE:
Would you look at this.!
Randy Randinger is making
His first appearance ever
for the Comebacks.!
Randinger's wide open.!
(Grunting)
(Yells)
MICHAELS' VOICE:
He scores!
Unbelievable!
(Excited shouting, whooping)
(Music grinds to a stop)
(Glass shatters)
Blue-Ten!
Hut!
(Yells) Ooh!
(Groaning in pain)
Randinger with
a block out of nowhere.!
You are not gonna believe this.!
The Comebacks score.!
(Cheering)
(Panting, whimpering)
How was it, son, everything
you'd hoped it would be?
Hey, thought you
might want this...
Get away! Get away!
Get away!
Aah!
Blue-22! Blue-22!
Hut!
(Loud grunt)
Yes!
He knows our playbook.
What? How is that possible?
Freddie knows all my secrets,
Where I get all my plays.
What are we gonna do?
Someone else has
to call the play,
Someone Freddie
wouldn't expect,
Someone who thinks
outside the Xbox.
I Pod!
I Pod. Hey, there, little buddy.
How would you like
to call a play, huh,
Help us win
a championship?
What do you say?
What do I say?
Man, I been waiting all season
for you to ask.
Dude, I have been humping legs,
Carrying this...
Stupid cord all over
the damn place,
And now, fourth quarter
of the last game,
You come and ask me for...
All right, all right!
Just call the play, will ya?
Get out of my...
Watch yourself, watch yourself.
All right, everybody, come on.
974-Wing bandit.
- Let's go get 'em!
- Let's go get 'em! Let's go!
(Electronic rock music plays)
I POD:
Audible!
Let's switch it up!
LANCE:
Shift!
KICKER:
What the heck is that?
That... is the
I Pod Shuffle.
(Crowd cheering)
Hut!
MICHAELS' VOICE:
Trotter... back to Truman...
...back to Trotter...
(Cheering)
Who scores!
MADDEN'S VOICE:
I mean, that was incredible!
ROME'S VOICE:
Phenomenal!
MICHAELS' VOICE: Coach Wiseman
has got to be feeling the heat
As the Comebacks only trail
By one touchdown.
It's fourth and goal.
With just seconds remaining,
the fate of the Comebacks
Lies in the hands
of quarterback Lance Truman.
Ref! Time out!
(Whistle blows)
I can't do it, Coach.
What's the problem?
What if I drop the ball?
And what if you don't?
Damn!
(Fans cheering)
Give me your hands.
Aw, geez!
Lance.
Yeah?
Do it for me.
Okay.
We can do this, guys.
Yeah!
(Loud cheering, whooping)
Let's do this! Oh!
- Yeah, Lance!
- Come on!
Set!
Hut!
(Loud grunting)
Hold on to it, Lance.
(Quiet burbling)
(Grunts)
(Grunting)
(Whistle blows)
Yeah!
(Cheering, whooping)
(Moaning, panting)
Get out there, Jiz!
Wait.
We're not playing for the tie.
I say we go for the win!
(Shouts, cheers)
Get out there!
They're going for two?
Don't worry.
I got one more page
in my playbook.
Set!
MICHAELS' VOICE:
Looks like the Unbeatables coach,
Freddie Wiseman, has entered
the game at middle linebacker.!
Time out, Comebacks.
John, something weird seems to
be going on down on the field.
MADDEN'S VOICE:
Yeah, it looks like Lambeau Fields
(Laughs): Was suiting up.
I think he's gonna go
For the two-Point
conversion himself.
BARB:
Coach!
It's me, honey! I'm here!
(Whooping loudly)
(Dramatic, exciting music playing)
FIELDS:
I'd give anything for one last shot.
FREDDIE: Because that's what you do,
Coach, you lose!
MICHELLE:
I want what you and Mom have.
FIELDS:
Herpes.
LANCE:
Set! Green-20!
Green-20! Hike!
(Freddie roaring fiercely)
(Grunting)
(Whistle blows)
(Cheering)
Yeah!
MADDEN'S VOICE:
The Comebacks did it!
Coach Fields
has finally done it.!
The Comebacks win!
MICHAELS:
Do you believe in miracles?
MARVALBERT:
Yes!
MADDEN: How long
have you been waiting to say that?
ROME'S VOICE:
The Comebacks have won.!
They beat the Unbeatables.!
Phenomenal.!
(Cheering)
(Whooping)
BOTH:
We did it! We did it!
(Cheering, shouting)
My shit goin'
to Disney World, baby. Yeah!
- Dude, guess what!
- What?
My parents just said we
could use the beach house
In the Hamptons for
the week to celebrate!
- No way! Oh, my God!
- Yeah!
And I get a real tattoo!
(Cheering continues)
I love you, Dad.
-(Choked up): My boy!
-Dad!
Coach! Coach!
(Squealing)
(Barb screams)
(Grunting)
I'm okay.
(Gasps)
Barbara!
Coa...
(Loud thump)
Oh!
Barbara!
(Grunting):
Oh, God! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Barb!
(Disgusted groan)
(Yells)
Barb!
(Fierce grunt)
Get out of my way!
Coach! Coach!
Oh! I'm so sorry.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
I'm a winner, Barb.
(Laughs)
I'm hanging up
my whistle for good.
I'm never gonna
let sports come
Before you and the
kids ever again.
(Swooning sigh)
MAN:
Uh, Coach Fields?
Coach Fields, excuse me?
Name's Gabe Low.
I'm looking for a new
head basketball coach
At Sequel University,
And I think you're
just the man.
(Chuckles):
Well, mister,
I sure don't know anything
about basketball...
(Swooning sigh)
...but I'll take it!
-Coach Fields!
Coach, how does it feel
To finally win
a championship game?
Um... to be honest,
it really hasn't hit me yet.
(Laughing)
(Groans): I thought
it would feel better than this.
(Groans loudly)
(Drum riff plays)
(Rock music plays)
(Woman screams)
(Angry grunts)
(Grunts)
You guys are ripping me apart!
(Music continues)
(Blowing whistle)
Let's do it!
(Whooping)
I think we're gonna need
a bigger truck.
(Blabbering)
All right, huddle up!
ALL:
Break!
FIELDS:
Lend an ear, take a knee.
(Loud slap)
FIELDS:
Clock's running down.
The game is on the line.
No time outs left.
Not gonna go for the tie.
(Shouts gibberish)
This time I'm gonna win!
See an open door!
Gonna walk right in!
(Music continues)
Nobody shed a tear
for old Freddie.
At least, not after he...
"Borrowed" $200,000
from the school's Booster club,
Moved his athletic ass
on down to Mexico
And entered into a consensual
polygamous relationship
(Chuckles): With two
fine-looking young ladies.
Adios, y'all.
(Laughing)
(Taser strikes, clicks)
Aw, Scruffy!
I think we nailed it!
(Rock music playing)
(Music fades)
Thank you! Good night!
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org