Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I never thought of that.
Since you may not die,
While we most assuredly will...
There must be a reason for that, no?
Perhaps you are an expert.
Uh, that's it, mr.
Oldman. Have a good one.
Thank you. You too.
Or are you a vampire, john?
Even an unknowing one.
Do you stand alive and tall
In a graveyard that you helped to fill?
Dan: that's going too far.
Bored, perhaps lonely,
because your heart
Cannot keep its treasures.
Is that what you're doing?
Have you led a wrongful life?
Well, then, perhaps...
It is time to die.
Wait a minute, now.
Look, i don't know what john is doing,
But i sure as hell don't
like what you're doing.
Give me that gun or i'm
gonna break your goddamn arm.
You sound like our football coach, dan.
What do you think, john?
A shot to the arm?
Perhaps we could watch it heal.
A bullet in the head-
What exactly will happen?
I have papers to correct.
As much as i dislike that job,
It'll be preferable to this.
I leave you with it.
Jesus christ.
What the hell was that all about?
Where'd he get a gun?
He had you on the ropes, john.
Are you really so damn smart?
It's not like will.
Mary passed away yesterday.
Who?
His wife.
She had, uh, pancreatic cancer.
Will!
I didn't know about mary.
I'm sorry. I can see how
this might have hit you.
Please, permit me to
be infantile by myself.
Will, please.
What the hell were you thinking, art?
Oh, come on. Something had to be done.
I have to say i agree.
And he's our friend.
Whatever else on earth is going on,
He's our friend!
You sure about that?
Why are you being so hard on him?
One of my favorite
people has disappeared.
Can you get alzheimer's at 35?
Maybe i'm trying to wake him up.
Maybe i'm too sad to cry.
What i said about myself hurt him.
He struck back expertly-
That stuff about stealing life forces?
I've always wondered about the reasons.
Well, we still have an
afternoon to kill, right?
Charades?
No. John?
I have a charade, and
it is just for you.
Sandy, come here.
Come on, come on, come on.
Okay, this one's for you.
Ready?
Ooh!
Uhn.
My first wedding?
There you go.
There you go!
Very good, and i bet at least one of us
Is your direct descendent.
And i didn't even send a christmas card.
Christmas card? What
about a birthday card?
And don't even get me
started on the candles...
With the blowing and the
For years with the blowing.
Yeah, all right. I tried.
Well, uh, call me underdeveloped,
But i'd like to hear more.
Me too.
More.
You double-Damn swear
this isn't some cockamamie
Science fiction story or...
You're pulling on us?
Next question.
You-You-You
realize
This is an invitation
To men in white suits with happy pills.
Dan: think about it-
A mechanism allowing survival
For thousands of years?
Run out of room even faster.
Then we'd have to go to mars as a colony
As we expanded, as we'd have to.
I'd like that.
On a planet of another star.
I envy you.
Did you have a pet dinosaur?
They were a little bit before my time.
At least something is.
No doubt you could give us
a thousand details, john,
Corroborating your story,
From the magdalene to the buddha to now.
Ten thousand,
And you could stay out of the books.
Oh, it's getting chilly.
Here, come over here. Join me.
That, uh, raises an
interesting question, john.
Could there be others like you
Who escaped the aging
process as you have?
Representing something terrific
We don't even know about biology.
We're learning all the time.
Yeah, but how would he know?
He doesn't wear an i. D. Badge
saying "yabba dabba doo. "
There was a man in the 1600s.
Where were you in 1292 a. D.?
Where were you a year ago on this date?
Anyway, it was the
1600s, and i met a man,
And i had a hunch that he was...
Like me, so i told him.
Ah. See, you said this was a first.
I forgot.
A crack in your story, john?
A touch of senility.
Anyway, he said yes,
But from another time, another place.
We talked for two days.
It was all pretty convincing,
But we couldn't be sure.
We each confirmed what the other said,
But how do we know if the confirmation
Was genuine or an echo?
I knew i was kosher,
But i thought, "maybe he's
playing a game on me. "
You know, a scholar
of all we spoke about.
He said he was inclined
with the same reservation.
Now, that's interesting.
Just as we can never be sure,
Even if we wanted to-
I mean, if we were sure,
You couldn't be sure of that.
We parted, agreeing to keep in touch-
Of course, we didn't-
And 200 years later i thought i saw him
In a train station in brussels.
Lost him in the crowd.
Oh, what a shame.
I
- I mean, if it were true.
Okay, here's one for you.
What do you do in your spare time?
Every 50 years or so,
When i wanna get away from the rush,
I go down to a primitive
tribe in new guinea
Where i'm worshipped as an immortal god,
And they have a huge statue of me.
It's a big party.
Yeah, i've got a lot of pictures of it,
But i've already packed
them up. I'm sorry.
I won't make the obvious nasty
crack about more unwashed cavemen.
Actually, bathing was the style
Until the middle ages
when the church told us
It was sinful to wash away god's dirt,
So people were sewn
Into their underwear in october
And they popped out in april.
You said you just happened.
I don't believe that.
If your story's true,
Why did god allow you to happen?
That makes an interesting point.
Are you religious, john?
I don't follow a known religion. No.
Ever.
Long time ago i did,
Like most people.
Some just never get over it.
Do you believe in god?
As laplace said,
"I have no need of that hypothesis. "
He may be around, though.
He's everywhere. We just can't see him.
Pfft. If this was the best i could do,
I'd be hiding, too.
And creation...
It's here-I'm not so
sure it was created.
Edith: what then?
Maybe it's just accumulated,
fields affecting fields.
What about the source
of the field energies?
Wouldn't that imply a prime mover?
I'd wonder about the
source of the prime mover,
Infinite regress, but that
doesn't imply anything to me.
Back to the mystery.
It's a very old question,
But there's no answer
except in religious terms.
If you have faith, it's answered.
Did you ever meet any person
from our religious history?
A biblical figure?
In a way.
Who?
We should skip this one.
No, no, no skipping. Come on.
Next question.
No, come on!
Come on, spit it out!
Good lord! You were one of them!
This is going in a direction
that i-I didn't expect.
I hoped it wouldn't
- We... call it a night.
Come on! You were someone
in religious history?
Yes.
In the bible?
Someone we know?
How could we not know
someone in the bible?
I mean somebody important.
You may think you know him,
But it's mostly myth.
The entire bible is
mostly myth and allegory
With maybe some basis
in historical events.
You were part of that history?
Yes.
Moses.
Moses was based on misis, a syrian myth,
And there are earlier versions-
All found floating on water,
The staff that changed to a snake,
Waters that were parted so followers
Could be led to freedom
And even receive laws
On stone or wooden tablets.
One of the apostles.
They weren't really apostles.
They didn't do any real teaching.
Peter the fisherman learned
a little more about fishing.
How do you know that?
The mythical overlay is so enormous...
And not good.
The truth is so, so simple.
The new testament in 100
words or less: you ready?
I don't think i wanna hear this.
Harry, will you take me home?
No, not right now. I
do want to hear this.
Sit down, edith. You
act like you believe him.
It's sacrilege.
How can it be sacrilege?
He hasn't said anything yet.
The new new testament is sacrilege.
There are a dozen new new testaments,
From hebrew to greek
to latin to tyndale,
All the way to king james,
All revisionist,
And all called revealed truth.
I mean a new new testament in 100 words.
I can give you the ten
commandments in ten words:
Don't. Don't, don't, don't,
Don't, don't, don't,
don't, don't, don't.
don't.
The commandments are just modern
updates of more ancient laws.
Hammurabi's code.
That's right, they
weren't the first, right?
Edith, i was raised on the torah...
My wife, on the koran.
My oldest son is an atheist.
My youngest is a scientologist.
My daughter is studying hinduism.
I imagine that there is room there
for a holy war in my living room,
But we practice live and let live.
Why don't you sit down.
What is your preferred
version of the bible?
The king james, of course.
It's the most modern, the
work of great scholars.
Modern is good.
All right, john, hit
us with the short form.
Guy met the buddha, liked what he heard,
Thought about it for a while-
Say 500 years, while he returned
To the mediterranean,
Became an etruscan.
Seeped into the roman empire.
He didn't like what they became-
A giant killing machine.
He went to the near east thinking,
"Why not pass the buddha's
teachings on in a modern form. "
So he tried.
One dissident against rome?
Rome won.
The rest is history.
Well, sort of. Lot of
fairy tales mixed in.
I knew it.
He's saying he was christ.
Oh, no. That's the medal
They pinned on jesus
to fulfill prophecy.
The crucifixion.
He blocked the pain
as he had learned to do
In tibet and india.
He also learned to
slow his body processes
Down to the point where
they were undetectable.
They thought he was dead.
So his followers pulled him
From the cross, placed him in a cave...
His body normalized as
he had trained it to...
He attempted to go away undetected,
But some devotees were standing watch.
Tried to explain.
They were ecstatic.
Thus, i was resurrected,
And i ascended to central europe
To get away as far as possible.
You don't mean a word of this, john.
My god, why are you doing this?
Let me see your wrists.
I don't scar.
Besides, they tied me...
But nails and blood make
better religious art.
all the
speculations about jesus.
He was black, he was asian,
He was a blue-Eyed
aryan with a golden beard
And hair straight out
of vidal sassoon's,
He was a benevolent alien,
he never existed at all.
Now he's a caveman.
The christ figure goes all
the way back to krishna-
Hercules, of course.
Harry: hercules?
Born of a virgin, alcmene.
A god for a father, zeus.
The only begotten.
The savior
- The greek? Soter.
The good shepherd, the prince of peace,
Bringing gentle persuasion
and divine wisdom.
He died, joined his father on olympus
A thousand years before gethsemane.
How can you compare pagan
mythology to the true word?
Pretty damn closely, i'd say.
The early christian leaders,
They threw away hebrew manuscripts
And borrowed from pagan
sources all over the place.
Do you realize how...
Inconsiderately you're
treating my feelings?
About as inconsiderately
as we're treating john's.
Well, he doesn't
believe what he's saying!
Sandy: do you believe literally
everything in the bible, edith?
Yes!
Before you say it,
I know it's undergone a lot of changes,
But god has spoken through man
To make his word clearer.
He couldn't get it right the first time?
We're imperfect! He had to
work to make us understand.
He couldn't get us right
the first time, edith?
Dan: taken alone, the
philosophical teachings of jesus
Are buddhism with a hebrew accent-
Kindness, tolerance, brotherhood, love,
A ruthless realism acknowledging
That life is as it is here
on earth, here and now.
The kingdom of god, meaning goodness,
Is right here, where it should be.
"I am what i am becoming. "
That's what the buddha brought in.
And that's what i taught.
But a talking snake
make a lady eat an apple,
So we're screwed.
Heaven and hell were peddled
So priests could rule
through seduction and terror,
Save our souls that we never
lost in the first place.
I threw a clean pass...
They ran it out of the ballpark.
This is blasphemy.
It's horrible! Who else were you?
Solomon, elvis, jack the ripper?
It's been said that buddha and jesus
Would laugh or cry if they'd known
What was done in their name.
Harry: and if there is a creator,
He'd probably feel the same way.
I see ceremony, ritual, processions,
Genuflecting, moaning, intoning,
Venerating cookies and wine,
And i think...
It's not what i had in mind.
But that's vatican flapdoodle.
It doesn't have a thing to do with god.
As you said, john,
everywhere, religions...
From exalting life to
purging joy as a sin.
Rome does it as grand opera.
A simple path to goodness needs
A supernatural roadmap.
Supernatural...
A stupid word, i mean...
Anything that happens,
happens within nature,
Whether we believe in it or not.
Like a 14,000-
Year-Old caveman.
I- I-I drove
for a while,
And then i sat for a while.
I'm so ashamed.
and i'm freezing.
Well, come inside.
I still don't believe you, of course.
You need help.
Everybody needs help.
Yes, well, some more than others.
From the buddha to the cross,
I have always imagined
both as entirely mythic-
But i would like to hear more.
May i lie on the couch for a moment?
I'm not as young as i used to be.
Ohh!
So, you were jesus.
Well, perhaps somebody had to
be, for better or for worse.
The jury is still out.
When did you begin to
believe you were jesus?
When did you begin to believe
you were a psychiatrist?
Since i graduated harvard medical school
And finished my residency,
i've had that feeling.
Oh, i sometimes dream about it.
Have you acted upon this belief?
I had a private practice for a while,
And then i taught.
Nothing unusual-
Oh, until one day, i met a caveman
Who thought he was jesus.
Do you find that unusual?
Very. I would stake my reputation
He as sane as i am,
So why does he persist in such a story?
There must be a reason, though.
Unless i imagined it all?
Is that possible?
I think you're as sane as he is.
Oh, god, i-
no.
Did you ever find it
prudent to worship yourself
Rather than be thought a heretic?
That would be something.
Other times, christianity
was considered heresy.
I had to pretend other faiths.
And what does jesus have
to say to those present
Who find it difficult to believe in him?
Believe in what he tried to teach,
Without rigmarole.
Piety is not what the
lessons bring to people.
It's the mistake they
bring to the lessons.
Well, it's getting to be night.
I still have stuff to carry
And a long drive.
I'll help.
Dan: john, do you have
a destination in mind?
Never mind.
I won't ask.
John: thank you.
Anyone mentally ill can imagine
A fantastic background-
Even an entire life-
And sincerely believe it.
The man who thinks he is napoleon
Does believe it.
His true identity has taken a backseat
To his delusion and the need for it.
If that's the case with john,
There is a grave disorder.
Organized brilliantly.
He's got an answer for everything.
It might involve
rejection of his father,
Of his entire early past,
Replaced by this fantasy.
He says he can't remember his father.
Precisely why?
You said he was sane.
Did i?
Do you think that perhaps our caveman
Has a monkey on his back?
Drugs?
No, no, no, no.
I've done a lot of consulting
work with narcotics.
I've seen people tripping, strung out-
Whatever's up with john, it isn't that.
I've looked for signs-None.
Could cavemen really talk?
We think that language
came into existence
60,000 years ago.
The structure of stone age culture
Is evidence of the
ability to communicate-
Verbally.
Oh, shut up.
Maybe it'd be easier if i were.
Crazy?
No.
That is fascinating, isn't it,
A brave attempt to teach
buddhism in the west.
It's no wonder he failed.
We're not ready for it.
Edith: you're talking
as if you believed him.
Well, it is possible, isn't it?
I mean, anything is possible.
Look, we have two simple choices.
We can get all bent out of shape
Intellectualizing or
bench-Pressing logic,
Or we can simply relax and enjoy it.
I can listen critically,
But i don't have to make
up my mind about anything.
But you think you do?
Well, unfortunately, there's
no authorities on prehistory,
So we couldn't stop him there.
Edith: there are experts on the bible.
Harry: dream on.
Yeah, thus the lost years of jesus.
He didn't exist until john put on a hat.
I don't believe in angels and the
nativity and the star in the east,
But there are stories about
the childhood of jesus.
History hates a vacuum.
Improvisation, some of it very sincere,
Fills the gaps.
It would have been easy
To falsify a past back then-
A few words, credulity
- Time would do the rest.
Now you're talking as
if you believed him.
Art: well, look at the
popular myths surrounding
The kennedy assassination
in a few short years-
You had, uh, conspiracy, mafia, cia-
That's a mystique that'll never go away.
It's always been a small step
from a fallen leader to a god.
I don't think anybody
will deify kennedy.
We're more sophisticated than that.
Dan: we are?
We are.
Harry: well, you're finally fulfilling
One prophecy about the millennium, john.
John: what's that?
Here you are again.
You like the fire, john.
Everywhere i've lived,
i've had a fireplace.
Childhood fixation, i guess.
Helps me to feel secure.
There are predators out there.
One thing i didn't pack...
I thought i might need it.
Wouldn't sacre du printemps
be more appropriate?
What?
You've got...
Four men of science
completely baffled, my friend.
We-We don't know what to make of you.
Did you know voltaire
was the first to suggest
That the universe was created
by a gigantic explosion?
I think paul would agree.
And then goethe was the first to suggest
That spiral nebulae were
swirling masses of stars.
We now call them galaxies.
It's kind of funny how
often new concepts of science
Find their first tentative
forms of expression in the arts.
So did beethoven do physics on the side?
He spent most of his
time lying on the floor
In front of his legless piano
Surrounded by orange
peels and apple cores.
Now we're on the floor
listening to beethoven.
Full circle.
Did you have, um...
Any religious beliefs,
Or did you give it much thought?
You can't get there with thought.
You have faith?
In a lot of things.
Do you have faith in
the future of the race?
I've seen species come and go.
Depends on their balance
with the environment.
We've made a mess of it.
There's still time,
If we use it well.
Christianity has been a worldwide belief
For 2,000 years.
How long did the egyptians worship isis
Or the sumerians ishtar?
In india, sacred cows wandered freely
As reincarnated souls.
In a thousand years,
they'll be barbecued
And their souls will be in squirrels.
You weren't jesus!
Oh, edith.
if
it rains... it won't.
How do you know that?
I don't smell it.
Were you...
I guess... a medicine man?
I was a shaman a few times.
I revealed some truths
to eat a little better.
You think that's all
religion is about...
Selling hope and survival?
The old testament sells fear and guilt.
The new testament is
a good code of ethics,
Put into my mouth by
poets and philosophers
That are much smarter than i am.
The message is never practiced.
Fairy tales build churches.
What about the name "jesus"?
Did you pull that out of a hat?
I called myself john.
I almost always do.
As tales of the resurrection spread,
The name was confused
with the hebrew "yochanan,"
Meaning "god is gracious. "
My stay on earth was seen
As divine proof of immortality.
That led to "god is salvation"
Or hebrew "yahshua,"
Which in translation
became my proper name,
Changing to late greek, "iesous,"
Then to late latin, "iesus,"
And finally medieval latin, "jesus,"
And it was a wonder
to watch it all happen.
Then you didn't claim
to be the son of god?
Began as a schoolhouse
and ended as a temple.
I said i had a master that
was greater than myself.
I never said he was my father.
I wanted to teach what i learned.
I never claimed to be king of the jews,
I never walked on water,
i never raised the dead.
I never spoke of divine
except in the sense
Of human goodness on earth.
No wise men came from the
east to worship at a manger.
I did do a little healing
With some eastern medicine i'd learned.
That's it.
The three wise men began as a myth
About the birth of the buddha.
John, i should be home,
uh, kissing my wife.
We're all here, trapped by your story...
Hoping for a...
revolution? I don't know.
Are there any, uh...
More revelations for us?
It's just like old times.
You weren't jesus.
Quote the sermon on the mount.
Which one?
Darby, king james,
new american standard?
Do you know them all?
No one knows the one, not even me.
I...
I did some teaching on a hill one day.
Not that many people stayed.
But you...
Biblical jesus said,
"Who do you think i am?"
He gave them a choice.
I'm giving you one.
Were you?
If i said no, could you ever be sure?
Turn that off.
Please.
This has gone far enough.
It's gone much too far.
These people are very upset.
I don't believe you're mad,
But what you're saying is not true.
That leaves only one explanation.
The time has come when you must admit
This is a hoax...
A lie.
Isn't that true, john?
If you don't drop
this now- If you can-
I'll be convinced
That you need a great deal of attention.
I can have you committed
for observation.
You know that.
I ask you now-
I demand it-
That you tell these people the truth.
Give them closure.
It's time, john.
Please.
End of the line. Everybody off.
What?!
It was a story.
It was all a story.
Good god!
Another fairy tale?
All of it? But what-
What in the name of heaven...
John, you had us wondering
whether you were sane or not,
And it's just a story!
Where'd you come off with such
a half-Baked, asinine idea?
At least you're relieved i'm not a nut.
I'd prefer you were!
You gave me the idea.
All of you.
Come again?
Edith saw my fake van gogh.
You could have just told me.
You commented that i never age.
You gave me the book on early man.
Dan, you spotted the burin
And you said, "if stones could speak. "
I knew it.
I got the notion, i ran it past you
To check your reactions,
and i took it too far.
Too far?
Check my reaction.
You asked if i was a figure
from religious history,
If there were others like me,
If i'd created future identities.
We were chasing our
tails around the maypole,
Enjoying the mystery,
the analytical stretch.
You were playing my game!
I was playing yours.
Oh, man, you know, you
had us going, right?
You were good, man.
You know those chinese boxes,
One inside the other inside
the other inside the other-
I feel like i'm in the last box.
You son of a...
Bitch!
How could you do this to us?
I was worried about you.
I know, i was tempted
to cop out many times,
But i couldn't resist
seeing whether or not
You could refute what i was saying.
I had the perfect audience-
Anthropologist, archaeologist,
Christian literalist...
A psychologist.
Okay, i've had enough of this.
I'm outta here. You
wanna come? Let's go.
So, john.
Are you gonna write the story?
If i do, i'll send you copies.
Don't bother with mine, okay?
You are absolutely certifiable.
I don't know you!
It was nice seeing
you again, dr. Oldman.
Your name's a pun, isn't it?
Old man?
Did that help you with your story?
Art: linda!
Bye.
Well, art was half right.
Which half?
Well, at least i don't
have to throw away half
Of what i know about biology.
Which half?
It's a beautiful idea,
So rich, so full of possibilities.
Perhaps you should write
a paper on it, doctor.
Maybe i will.
I'll interview you in the rubber room
For further details.
You may still need help, my friend.
My ass.
I thought it sounded pretty good.
They believe you because they have to.
But the one thing that i know about you
Is that you would never use people
Or abuse their goodwill and intelligence
Like they think you've
just done to them.
Psych 101?
No, it's woman,
one-On-One.
So you're a pretty fast liar, mr. Ugg,
But i wanna know
- What's your real name?
Believe it or not, the
sound was always john.
Why'd you cave to gruber?
What happened was enough.
Just-Just needed to stop.
I shouldn't have expected it to work.
Fourteen thousand years old.
I bet that's a lot of women.
Are we counting?
Maybe.
Well, i'm taking edith home.
Sandy?
I'm gonna stay.
Are you sorry for some
of those things you said?
I'm sorry i said them.
Well.
Like a good christian,
I... oh, john.
Oh! Well.
You did a terrible thing,
But we're all so
thankful you're all right.
Even art-He just hates
things he can't understand.
You're a sadist, john,
But i admit i got a kick out of
Chasing my tail around your maypole...
Even if that is all i caught.
Good luck to you.
Wish you the best. Thank you.
Ready?
Harry: later on.
Sandy: okay, good night.
Mm-Hmm.
Mmm.
I don't know, man.
Something about this...
Something about you, john.
The more i think about it,
The more i'm no longer
in that chinese box.
I sense... space.
A kinda latitude of what
we happily call reality,
In which, as everybody keeps saying...
Anything's possible.
Yes. No, no. No, no.
No-No more words.
I'm gonna go home,
And i'm gonna watch star trek
For a dose of sanity.
Good luck to you, man,
Wherever this may lead you.
You drop me a line sometime.
Let me know how you're making out.
I will.
Mm. Mwah.
So, john oldman.
What other pun names have you used?
Lots.
John paley for john paleolithic,
John savage-
Got really crazy about 60 years ago.
When i was teaching at harvard,
I was john thomas partee.
John t. Partee-
Boston tea party-
I get it.
Yeah, i know.
Wait, wait, wait.
Boston?
60 years ago?
J
- John partee?
You did not teach chemistry!
I do not believe you!
Your mother's name was nola.
No. Yeah.
No.
Yes, nola.
my mother!
I reject this!
My-My-My
dog's name.
We had him before i was born.
Woofie.
Woof, woof, woofie...
Gruber. She remarried?
She said you abandoned us.
Sorry, i had to move on.
You know that. I left enough.
I left enough. I'm cold.
Chilly willy, always cold.
Never could stand the cold.
wait, you
- You had a beard.
Yeah, you used to tug on it
To see if it was real.
Agh! Will!
God.
911, now!
Come on, will.
Will.
Come on, buddy.
You'll stay in touch, dr. Oldman,
In case there are any questions.
I'll be back for the funeral.
Miss.
You never saw a grown child die.
No.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org