Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
-What can I get for you?
-Just a burger and a drink, pIease.
How do you want that burger done?
It doesn't matter.
Okay, that'II be 4 bucks.
-You want that for here?
-No.
Okay, we'II bring that right out to you.
Mommy, why does that girI's face
Iook Iike that?
You eat your food, honey.
-Did she get into an accident?
-Yes. Eat your food.
Stop Iooking at me! Stop Iooking at me!
I know what I Iook Iike.
You think I chose to Iook Iike this?
You think I chose this?
The Han dynasty, during their ruIe,
wouId sometimes Ieave their enemies aIive,
disfiguring them
in a most grotesque manner.
It was a message to aII those
who wouId oppose their ruIe
that you wouId die,
or carry the scars of your defiance.
They understood the psychoIogicaI effect
this wouId have on the masses.
There was a price to pay for your actions.
By the time they were through with you,
death wouId be a weIcome friend.
Have your daddy pick me up a sIushy
when he gets off work, okay?
Make it a cherry one.
BradIey, I've toId you a miIIion times,
Ieave Ravi aIone and find another seat.
WeII, as I entered the cIassroom,
this was the onIy seat avaiIabIe.
Then switch with Bernard.
Continuing on, taIking about the
importance of the Chinese ancient mindset
that they were into this whoIe idea
of cosmic retribution.
I got us the hottest costumes for the party.
They scream,
''We Iove sex, but not with you.''
-We're so vain.
-I'm totaIIy okay with that.
-So, who's throwing this party anyways?
-ProbabIy Stephanie.
She keeps trying to win us over
so that we'II be her friend.
She's such a Ioser.
Awesome, so we'II drink her booze,
trash her pIace and stiII ignore her ass.
You reaIize
we're aII going to heII someday, right?
And we'II be the hottest bitches there, too.
That's the pIan.
Oh, my God.
There's that IittIe bitch, EmiIy.
Let's fuck with her.
Hey, sexy girI.
-So, going to the costume party next week?
-No.
Come on, it'II be so much fun.
Maybe you can even
get your cherry popped.
-Yeah, some guys Iike freaks.
-Yeah, EmiIy, don't you want to have fun?
-I wasn't invited.
-What?
You mean,
we were invited and you were not?
I don't understand. I mean, Iook at you.
How couId that be?
Why are you aIways so mean to me?
I've never done anything to you.
We're not being mean. We're being honest.
You know, I think you'd actuaIIy Iike me
if you just gave me a chance.
I doubt it.
Oh, my God, you're not gonna cry, are you?
-Oh, my God.
-Don't go. Be our friend.
Howdy.
Hey, is WorkIey around?
Passed away about eight months ago.
I'm his nephew.
He Ieft me the house in his wiII.
WeII, I'm sorry for your Ioss, son.
My name's Parker.
-I'm Dane.
-Dane. Nice to meet you.
Eight months. Don't that beat aII?
You know, he and I were both in Vietnam.
We shared a Iot of stories.
So, you and your friends doing some work
around the grounds?
Yeah.
Yeah, just getting the pIace ready.
It's a mighty fine picking.
WeII, if you need anything,
I'm just a miIe or so down here.
Thanks. Appreciate it.
You know,
I don't mean to stick my nose in it,
but that pIan of yours,
it's never gonna work.
-Sorry?
-Trap.
The tops are too sturdy.
They'II waIk right over it.
What you need are cage traps.
I got pIenty of them.
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe. Thanks.
Just offering.
Hey, Ravi.
Yeah, I'm watching it now.
I think it's...
Gruesome, disgusting.
It's perfect.
We'll pick up the partiers in the truck
and bring them to the house.
TripIets wiII be on ATVs in the woods
wearing the same costumes as us.
-Nobody escapes.
-I think it's briIIiant.
I mean,
aII the years of watching horror fiIms,
what can be better than to put it aII to use?
I think I know the perfect way
to use Jack's banjo skiIIs.
Dude, what? Can you smeII it?
Can you smeII it?
You're kiIIing me.
-Dude.
-He's fucking coming over here, man.
-Trying to come over here?
Go back to India, bitch.
Bernard, I beIieve this is yours.
Thank you, come again.
-Sorry.
-Go back to your seat.
We have no hummus here for you.
Don't worry about it, man.
-Yo, my peopIes, what's up?
-Hey, Kurtis.
Check it.
I just got my first commerciaI TV gig.
You're Iooking at the new face
of Yums shoes.
Video shoot over at their spot on Friday.
I want you guys to come check it out.
-That's great news.
-Hey, you never know.
Next time you guys see me,
I'II be at the Oscars
accepting my award for best actor.
Ravi, I remember you got that sweet camera
for your birthday.
Can I get you to, you know, shoot
some behind-the-scenes stuff for me?
-HeIp me out?
-Yeah, sure.
Nice. AII right, so I'II see you guys there?
CooI. AII right, y'aII.
-I Iike Kurtis.
-Me, too.
-Make sure he doesn't make the party.
-Yeah.
He's not one of them.
-What's up, man?
-What's up?
What's up? Hey, Iook, I want you guys
to come out. I'm doing a video shoot.
Look.
Oh, my God.
I cannot wait untiI the party next week.
-What?
-You're fucking Tommy.
-Who toId you that?
-It's in your ceII phone, stupid.
''I can't wait to taste you again.''
You bitch. Give me that.
-That is so shitty.
-Take it easy.
We've been besties since grade schooI.
Can't beIieve you didn't teII us.
He made me promise not to teII anybody,
and you can't either.
You know, we have to keep it quiet
since he's stiII dating Nadya.
-I'm gonna go see him tonight.
-We're just pIaying. We won't teII.
Besides, Tommy's kind of hot.
I hate that Russian bitch anyways.
I'm gIad you're fucking her man.
AII's fair in sex and high schooI.
''I find that I am quite content.
''I have peace in my Iife,
''and I am not afraid.
''For the first time, I am not afraid.''
Yeah, Mom?
What's with the boxes?
I noticed you packed up some things.
Just cIeaning up a bit.
Is everything okay?
You've been very quiet IateIy.
-Yes, everything's fine.
-Okay.
''One night.
''One finaI night.''
I just... Look, I reaIIy appreciate
you guys coming, man. It means a Iot.
-Anytime, man.
-Man.
Now, Iet me cIean the Iens off reaI quick.
-I'II be right back.
-AII right.
You must be pretty nervous, huh?
A IittIe bit. I'II find the courage, though.
Snap!
What do we have here, son, huh?
If it isn't the Slumdog Millionaire.
What's up, bin Laden?
-I'm Indian, not Arab.
-My bad. I'm sorry.
-No, it's a dot.
-Like it fucking even matters.
-What do you got there, sunshine, huh?
-TechnoIogy.
Give it. Give it.
Sunni's doing a IittIe recon
for his terrorist ceII. What you think?
-Joke's over.
-Joke's not over.
Just give it back.
-Looks Iike we got ourseIves a terrorist.
-I caught me a terrorist, BiII.
-I got him. I got him.
-How'd you get him?
WeII, he was Iooking
at my Iockstock funny.
-You remember state?
-Fuck, yeah.
So cIose.
BradIey's at the 30! The 20!
-The 10!
-Go, go, go!
-Touchdown, BradIey.
-And the crowd goes wiId.
-Why'd you do that?
-Easy, missy.
-'Cause I feIt Iike it.
-These things happen.
-Don't be so down.
-Ravi, they're starting.
-What's going on?
-Three peas in a pod.
-Just teIIing stories and hanging out.
-What happened to your camera?
-What happened?
-Did you guys break his camera?
-Is it busted? Did it bust?
-Hate to think, yeah.
-I remember.
-No, you...
Yeah, I did. I busted it.
The question is, what the fuck
are you gonna do about it, huh?
What the fuck are you gonna do about it?
I'II teII you what. I'II teII you what.
You kick my ass, I'II buy him a new camera.
How's that sound?
I can't beat you.
You can't beat me?
I know you can't beat me.
You know why?
'Cause you're a coward.
That's why.
You know why it is
that I do what I do to you?
Do you know? I do it because I know
that you can't stop me.
Get the fuck out of here.
-Let's Ieave these pussies.
-I beIieve this is yours.
Soon.
IndividuaIIy, these chemicaIs are harmIess,
but mixed together
form a compound which is caustic
and can eat through metaI.
It is actuaIIy quite dangerous.
So, your homework assignment is to find
two chemicaIs that share that property.
Man, I'm sorry.
I couId not get the camera to work.
Man, don't trip, aII right? It's not your fauIt.
You didn't do nothing.
It's about time somebody
put them fooIs on notice.
The time is now.
Yo, BradIey, Iet me hoIIer at you.
-What's up?
-Look, man, you better Ieave my boy aIone.
You better watch it.
You wiII not be afraid.
When the time comes,
you wiII not be afraid.
Can I heIp you, Dad?
Dad, I Ieft a Ietter in my room
expIaining everything.
You don't have to worry about me.
I'II be okay.
I know you'II be mad,
but I did what I thought was right.
Anyway, I know you'II be fine,
and Mom, she'II be okay with you there.
Okay, then. Bye.
-How's this?
-Perfect.
-How many RSVP'd to the party?
-Everyone.
I knew we couId use their egos
to our advantage.
It's gonna be a night they'II never forget.
-We'II be Internet Iegends.
-Yeah.
Hey, come check this out.
-Sweet mother of Jesus.
-Check this.
That is hard core.
I think I know what heII is.
HeII is waking up every day
beIieving that the suffering
you're doing in Iife has meaning.
That somehow, if you endure it,
you gain vaIuabIe Iessons.
The truth is, sometimes you just suffer.
There is no meaning.
We're just pawns
in a sick game of random chance.
Chaos.
My heII, siIence.
The kind of siIence
that makes your ears ring.
Be gIad for it.
Mine's Iistening to my mom and dad
fight day after day.
Crashing pIates.
Screeching tires.
Crying.
I fucking hate the crying.
I couId use some siIence.
Think we're going to heII?
No.
We've suffered enough.
We're doing God's work,
as far as I'm concerned.
Bring some justice into the worId.
I can't wait.
I've been more at peace
ever since we first taIked about this.
We'II aII be at peace tomorrow.
Amongst other things.
-I'm not gonna go.
-Why?
Because I don't feeI good and I feeI fat.
Heather, you're such a drama queen.
You Iook great.
WeII, yeah, but I reaIIy don't feeI good.
-And my stomach hurts.
-I toId you not to eat that burger.
Red meat is for peopIe who don't care
how they Iook, not hot chicks Iike us.
I think I'm gonna die.
If you don't go, we don't go.
Come on, you'II feeI way better
after a night of drinking and hot sex.
Okay, but if the party's Iame,
we can Ieave earIy, right?
Honey, that's what the dream poIice do.
We break up bad parties.
Come on, Iet's go turn some heads.
Crap, I don't see anybody.
I know we're at the right pIace.
It's Edgar and Matty.
Hey, Nadya.
-What's up, guys?
-Tommy, what's up?
How's it going? Pirates, huh?
Lord,
we understand what we're about to do.
And with one sign from you, right now,
we wiII caII off our pIans.
We offer you this finaI chance.
So now you know, Lord, the fate of
those who are about to come here tonight.
And we leave their lives in your hands.
Man, it's too bad Riggs couIdn't make it.
Man, that boy's got his priorities
aII jacked up, aII right.
First of aII, if it was me, I'd quit that shit job
a heII of a Iong time ago, aII right?
Tonight is what? It's time to party, right?
-It's time to party, baby!
-HeII, yeah!
Party our asses off.
You know what I'm saying.
-Fuck.
-Shit.
Fuck. RoII down the window, man.
-Shit, man, we are going to fucking jaiI.
-Shut up, aII right?
-RoII them the fuck down.
-Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up.
Oh, my God, dude.
-Get the fucking window down.
-Shut your fucking mouth.
-AII right. He's getting out, he's getting out.
-Hey, hey, hey, caIm down, caIm down.
-I got this.
-Shut up.
-Just Iet me do aII the taIking, aII right?
-Shut up. Shut your damn mouth.
Friends, Roman and countrymen,
how we doing this evening?
Just fine, Officer. How about yourseIf?
WeII, I'm doing pretty good.
Thanks for asking.
Now I'II teII you why I puIIed you over.
You was going about 15 miIes per hour
over the speed Iimit.
Now that was why I puIIed you over.
But why you're in troubIe,
that's a whoIe other matter.
I don't understand
what you're taIking about.
You don't understand... You don't
understand what I'm taIking about?
No, I...
Don't buIIshit me, boy.
What, you think I wasn't young once?
I know what it's Iike to chase the puss
and get high.
-What are you Iooking at?
-Sorry.
I'II teII you what.
Why don't we try a IittIe honesty?
AII right. HonestIy, this is my brother's car.
He smokes a Iot of pot.
We don't smoke that...
We don't smoke pot at aII, do we?
-Do we, boys?
-No, sir.
-There's no pot.
-Never.
-No pot-smoking in this car.
-No, sir.
-You expect me to beIieve that?
-Yeah, I was kind of hoping so.
WeII, I don't. So I teII you what.
I'm gonna give you one chance.
If I hear anything but the truth, you boys...
You're gonna be in for a Iong night.
Yes, Officer, we've been smoking.
That wasn't so bad now, was it?
So I'II teII you what you're gonna do.
You're gonna hand over aII the weed
right now.
Who's got the weed?
-Now.
-Give it to him, dude!
We got the weed, okay.
There's aII of it.
Today's your Iucky day.
You know why?
'Cause I'm feeIing Christ-Iike,
and I think that I am gonna forgive
aII of your sins on this fine evening.
-Thank you, Officer. We appreciate it.
-But I'II teII you what.
Next time you boys
come through Rocky Branch,
-know whose town you're in.
-Yes, sir, we wiII.
-Dude, that was so fucking cIose.
-Oh, my God, dude.
-Can you beIieve that?
-I am freaking bugging out, man.
-You kidding me?
-Luck has got everything to do with it.
He didn't get aII the weed, bitches.
-Shit.
-Yeah, this is gonna be our Iucky night.
Come on, Iet's go!
-Get that party started up.
-Yeah.
-Fuck, yeah!
-There she goes.
-Give me an ''O.'' Give me an ''O.''
-AII right.
Look at those breasts bouncing over there.
Those are beautifuI to me, to my eyes.
Is that... Is that a stripper? Riggs!
You son of a bitch.
-Hey, I thought you were at work.
-I was working.
But the truck we were supposed to Ioad
never showed up,
so my boss said, ''There's nothing to do,
go home.'' What did I do?
-Came to party with my boys!
-Came to party with the boys!
Hey, hey, hey, boys, boys, boys.
-Drinks. Let's get them in him.
-Let's get them in him!
Party!
So, Iook, basicaIIy, after that,
I've made it, right?
Shit, man. Kurtis is here.
-How'd he get in?
-I didn't see him get into the truck.
We can't Iet him Ieave.
-But he wasn't invited.
-WeII, then, fate brought him here.
-Let me go taIk to him...
-No.
Okay, he's here and he stays.
Fine.
It's time.
You know what to do. Nobody Ieaves.
-Let's take some shots, B!
-Fuck, yeah, yeah.
What the... Why the fuck am I tied up?
Get up, sleepyheads.
What kind of buIIshit is this?
Take a moment and clear your heads.
What is this?
Some kind of haunted house thing?
There's actually a good explanation
for all this.
Man, this is kinky.
Now that everybody is awake, let's begin.
There's some good news
and there's some bad news.
The good news is, we don't plan to kill you.
The bad news is, you will wish we had.
Some of you will be spared,
but you will all bear witness to the horror,
just as you did in the hallways,
just as you sat idly by
as pain was inflicted upon us.
What you fail to understand with reason,
you will with wrath.
Dude, what the fuck are you taIking about?
I'll tell you what I'm talking about, Miles.
This is about what you are due.
When we are done,
you'll have a new perspective on life.
And no one, no one will ever look upon you
the same again.
You will forever be changed.
Yeah.
That's what I said to your mom Iast night.
What my friend has there is a cattle gun.
It's used to kill cattle
by blasting a spike into their brain.
It's considered humane,
but I'll let you decide.
Dude, get that shit out of my face.
Look, who the fuck are you peopIe?
This shit is stupid.
-Do I have your attention now?
-Why us?
Why us?
You know, that's the same question
we've been asking ourselves for years.
''Why us?''
Why us, always on the receiving end
of your taunts,
your laughter and your childish cruelty?
Now it's your turn to ask, ''Why us?''
Who are you?
It's a little late
for you to get to know us now.
But if you must know,
we are the rejected, the humiliated.
We are the outcasts.
And tonight is our night, so relax.
It's the only thing you can do.
Anybody want to leave?
Come on. Anyone?
Anyone feeling heroic?
Tommy, you want to leave?
Yeah.
I want to take Nadya with me.
You are in no position to bargain.
And you should be worrying
about yourself, not her.
Release him.
Listen, I'm gonna get heIp.
I'm gonna get heIp.
I'II get heIp, okay? You'II be okay.
You're gonna be okay...
In front of you, Tommy, is a door.
Outside that door is two miles of woods
that lead to a highway right into town.
Good luck, because you will be hunted.
I'II go get heIp for you guys.
Go get it, then. That's the spirit, Tommy.
Go get them.
Love you, Nadya.
Pathetic, isn't it?
So sweet and so much love.
Not when you consider
he was cheating on you, Nadya.
With Heather.
Yeah. Yeah. Everybody knew about it,
but they decided to laugh at you
behind your back,
taking joy in your ignorance.
Interesting friends.
I want you to think real hard
and ask yourselves,
''Where did all this evil come from?
''What did I do to make someone hate me
so much to go to these lengths?''
Think of this as the final,
and there's only one question.
''What did I do to deserve this?''
This is messed up, man. This is messed up!
This ain't right.
I want these chains off of me!
What gives you the right to judge us, huh?
What gives you the right to pIay God?
You know, Bradley,
that's real funny coming from you.
But to answer your question,
God gave us the right.
We gave him a chance to stop this.
We gave him a chance to save all of you.
But he chose to remain silent.
Go to heII.
I'm already there.
While you ponder your little situation,
I have a little treat for you. Enjoy.
Fuck you. Get that shit out of my face, man.
Come on, fucker!
I'm not scared of you, bitch! Come on!
You want to fucking kiII me, huh?
You fucking kiII me, you motherfucker!
Bernard!
You kiIIed him.
What did you give him?
What'd you put in him?
I didn't know you cared
so much about him, Bradley.
You know,
for a person who cares so deeply,
you really talk a lot of shit behind his back.
But that's not what's important.
What is important is that he's alive.
He can't move, but he can feel,
so I'm sure he appreciates
your love and concern.
Don't do it.
Deeper, deeper, deeper.
PIease. PIease, stop.
Enough! PIease. PIease.
I have to admit,
that was a stellar performance.
You! You gave him the key.
He's the onIy one who ever stood up for me.
We agreed not to hurt him.
Wrong.
We were the only ones
who stood up for you. You betrayed us.
What did you do?
Consequences.
None of us are free from them.
-HeIp! HeIp!
-What the fuck?
HeIp, heIp!
Hey, hey, hey! Hey, hey.
Stay back. Stay back!
-Look, man, they're kiIIing peopIe.
-Who's kiIIing peopIe?
-What're you taIking about?
-Just get some heIp!
-Get some heIp for what?
-They're kiIIing peopIe back there.
Who is kiIIing peopIe?
EmiIy, it's time.
He didn't have a right to do this.
Ravi shouId have made his choice.
We have to finish what we started.
It's what Ravi wouId have wanted.
PIease. PIease Iet her go.
We'II do whatever you want. Just pIease...
What are you doing to her?
It's a special compound we made up.
At first, she won't feel anything
but a cool sensation,
then a slight tingle, then a mild burn.
Soon enough,
it will begin to eat away at her flesh,
dissolving it ever so slowly
in the most painful way imaginable.
And she will become outside
what she is on the inside.
Disgusting.
You will all be happy to know
that Kurtis was able to get some help.
But the bad news is, the cop won't be
busting through the door, guns blazing.
He apparently took a bullet to the head.
Coward!
You coward.
You're a coward,
standing up there hiding behind that mask.
I'm not hiding behind this mask.
This is a reflection
of what you turned me into.
This is what I am on the inside.
I am a monster that you created.
Take off that mask.
Show me your face.
Fair enough.
You should know who's about to alter
the course of your life.
You?
You know, the irony of aII this,
you actuaIIy empowered me.
I wouId have Iived my Iife
aII aIone in the shadows, unassuming.
But you, you wouIdn't aIIow me to do that.
You had to torture me.
You have nobody to bIame for this
but yourseIf.
Open up, pIease. Open up.
I need some heIp.
Open up, pIease.
What the heII are you doing
banging on my door?
-PIease, sir, I just need some heIp.
-Drop your gun.
-Look, they're kiIIing everybody.
-Shut up, punk.
-Look, pIease just...
-I said shut up.
Now turn around.
Put your hands above your head.
-Man, there's stiII time to save everybody.
-I toId you once, I toId you too often.
Don't do this.
Don't hurt me, pIease.
Don't beg. Don't give them the pIeasure.
PIease don't hurt me.
I know who you are.
You're that girI from schooI, EmiIy.
Now I'm EmiIy.
I'm Andy.
And I'm Jack.
Are you doing this to get even with us?
For how we treated you?
Can you think of a better reason?
I'm sorry for what we did.
You didn't deserve it.
I didn't.
Hurting us won't make you feeI better.
It won't fix anything.
PIease, just end it now.
Let us aII go.
Since you apoIogized,
I won't hurt you.
Thank you.
But for my generosity,
you must do me a favor.
I'm gonna need you
to cut aII of BradIey's fingers off.
I can't.
Either way, he gets what is due him.
You do it,
or we do it.
It's the onIy way you can save yourseIf.
I can't do this. I can't hurt anyone.
Sure you can.
You hurt me.
Without even bIinking an eye.
I can't, I just can't.
That's reaIIy a shame.
I bet BradIey wouId cut your fingers off
to save himseIf.
WouIdn't you?
What do you say, BradIey?
Save yourseIf from unimaginabIe pain
by infIicting it.
No.
BradIey, pIease don't. PIease.
BradIey, it's you or her.
I know you'II need those fingers
to pIay footbaII.
What wouId your Iife be
without peopIe cheering you on?
Hey, wake up.
Sir, we couId stiII save them.
OnIy person we need to think about saving
is yourseIf.
-PIease, just caII the poIice.
-No. You gotta understand something.
Anytime you show up on my property
with a gun in your hand and try to rob me,
-there are consequences.
-Sir, I was not trying to rob you.
-I was just trying to get some heIp.
-Sure.
You came here in the middIe of the night
with a gun in your hand to ask for heIp.
Happens aII the time.
You know what those miIitary medaIs
are for, boy?
For not being stupid.
I was a fine, fine soIdier.
If it weren't for those poIiticians
without any backbone,
we wouId have won that war
and I'd be a generaI by now.
-Look, just Iet me go and I can heIp them.
-Imagine.
Fighting a war, bIeeding for your country,
onIy to be treated Iike a maggot by the very
nation that sent you there in the first pIace.
You understand what I'm saying?
I was a hero.
I saved Iives.
Look, and you can be a hero again.
Just caII the poIice.
In time.
First we gotta figure out who you are.
Pick them up.
BradIey. BradIey!
PIease.
PIease, pIease, no!
-I have to.
-No. No!
They're gonna hurt me if I don't.
They're gonna hurt me.
BradIey.
Show some fortitude.
-No!
-Get started, man. I'm waiting on you.
Attaboy, BradIey.
I knew you couId do it.
I knew you couId hurt someone eIse.
One down,
nine more fingers to go.
Ain't got aII night.
Do you want him to stop?
AII you have to do is find it in yourseIf
to infIict pain.
Can you do that?
See?
We aII have a point
when we can do the unimaginabIe.
Look, if you'II just caII the poIice,
I'II confess to them.
AII in good time, boy.
You know, my grandfather was in Vietnam.
My dad was two
when he was gunned down in the jungIe.
Is that right?
You're not the onIy one
who's made sacrifices for his country.
My dad was in Desert Storm.
He came back with that GuIf strain.
He was never the same since.
How do I know you're teIIing the truth?
I don't know how to prove it to you, sir,
but I'm teIIing you the truth.
And I'm teIIing you the truth when I say
there's some kids that need your heIp.
Look, we were at this party down the road.
They drugged us.
-We don't know...
-You mean the WorkIey pIace. Yeah.
I met that kid. Dane. He's a nice kid.
Dane.
Now for a IittIe mood music.
Jack, Iights, pIease.
EmiIy.
I think she needs a IittIe bit of inspiration.
Don't you?
I don't want to hurt him.
He deserves it.
-This can't be happening.
-It is.
You have about two minutes
before your skin begins to dissoIve.
Cut off his fingers
and I'II remove the compound. Hurry.
Just do it.
No.
No!
I won't do it.
I don't care how much you hurt me,
I won't hurt my friends.
I appreciate your IoyaIty,
but you'II have to suffer for it.
Yes, pIease send some officers down to
the WorkIey residence. We got some hot...
There are some niggers
robbing the WorkIey pIace.
They got guns and aII kinds of shit.
Send everybody.
Do you know my name?
You don't even know my name, do you?
My name is Dane,
and you've tortured me since we were kids.
PIease.
PIease don't hurt me anymore.
Don't hurt me anymore.
You're a reaI coward, huh? You know that?
And do you know why I'm gonna hurt you?
'Cause you can't stop me.
Any of that ring a beII, Brad?
PIease don't cut off my fingers.
Don't you cut off my fingers.
PIease, don't you cut off my fingers!
Don't you cut off my fingers!
PIease, don't cut them off,
don't cut them off, don't cut them off!
BradIey, BradIey. Okay.
Okay, I won't cut off your fingers.
But here's the thing. I think that this worId
wiII be better off without you.
But since I promised that I won't kiII you,
I'II just make sure
that you can't do harm ever again.
I'm sorry.
-What?
-I'm sorry.
-You're sorry?
-I am sorry. I'm sorry. I am sorry.
-Oh, are you sorry, Brad?
-I'm sorry.
You're onIy sorry
because you have no choice but to be sorry.
No, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
And that means, Brad, that you're not sorry.
I spent a great deaI of time thinking about
how I'd Iike to get even with you,
and no matter what I came up with,
I just didn't feeI satisfied.
The anger and the hatred
that you poured into me for years
made it impossibIe.
But I came up with a way, BradIey.
I came up with a way to take everything
that you Iove away from you.
You wiII never, ever enjoy sex again.
You'II never, ever pIay footbaII again.
And you,
you wiII spend the rest
of your IittIe pathetic Iife
confined to a wheeIchair!
Remember bioIogy, BradIey?
Remember we Iearned that if somebody
severed the human spinaI cord,
they'II become instantIy paraIyzed?
No. No, you probabIy
don't remember that Iesson
'cause you were too busy
devising ways to fuck me and my friends!
WeII, guess what, Brad? Guess what?
I did some devising of my own.
Every time you hoist yourseIf into
that wheeIchair, I want you to think of me.
SmiIing.
In a short time,
the sun wiII come up
and this wiII aII be over.
You don't know it just yet,
but you have aII been a part of history.
The events of tonight wiII Iive on forever.
We gave meaning to aII your Iives tonight.
No thank you necessary.
Sicko.
You're aII going to jaiI.
No.
No, we're not.
Do you remember
when we were sophomores, Riggs,
and you offered me a ride home
because it started to rain?
What does that matter?
WeII, that's just it, Riggs.
That one act of kindness
is a reason why I considered
Ietting you go,
-why I hadn't cut out your tongue.
-I don't care what you do to me!
Fuck you, Dane!
Fuck aII you bastards!
You reaIIy do have a big mouth,
huh, Riggs?
I appreciate your courage
in the face of danger.
There is something to be said
about defiance.
There's nobiIity to it.
And there's a price to pay.
ShouIdn't have opened your big fat mouth.
I got two of them.
You're crazy, oId man.
Hey, kid, I'm sorry I didn't beIieve you.
It's cooI.
You come banging on my door at 5:00 in
the morning with a gun in your hand,
I might not beIieve you, either.
Let me ask you something.
Is it aII true about your pa?
About being in the miIitary
and everything?
No, I made aII that buIIshit up.
My dad works for a steeI miII.
His dad worked for a steeI miII.
I just don't want to end up
doing the same thing, you know?
Yeah. WeII, it's aII the same.
But you gotta save those kids.
If you don't, you'II Iive to regret it.
Like I did.
I didn't save anybody.
I hid.
Just tried to save myseIf.
I watched my friends die.
I was just too scared.
Just hang in there, man.
Yeah.
Riggs, this is reaIIy gonna hurt you.
Good news is,
this can onIy happen once in a Iifetime.
Let him go. Don't make me kiII you, Dane.
I suggest you turn around and Ieave, Kurtis.
We have no issue with you.
Yeah, weII, I got an issue with you.
I don't Iike being shot at.
You weren't invited to this party.
You shouIdn't have come.
Fate brought me here, to stop you.
-Cut off his tongue.
-Do it and I'II kiII both of you.
Fine. KiII us. We had no pIans of Iiving
after today, anyway.
We onIy do what we pIan to do.
I'm serious.
I don't know if you've noticed,
but so are we.
Dane, you've been my friend a Iong time,
but I can't Iet you do this.
You know,
I wish there was more peopIe Iike you.
Then we wouIdn't be here.
Come on, man, I know Riggs is a prick,
but he don't deserve this.
You're wrong. He does. Andy, do it.
You shouId have Ieft
when you had the chance.
I've had enough.
Me, too.
We're aII responsibIe.
KeIIi, I think you're wrong.
I reaIIy do think
you wouId've come to Iike me.
I just wanted to be friends.
PoIice! Freeze! Drop the weapon!
There are more Iike us out there.
I said drop it! Just drop the weapon!
It's not worth it. We can work it out!
You're too Iate.
How do I look?
Okay. On three, two, one.
PoIice have identified the kiIIers
as disgruntIed students
who kidnapped, drugged and dismembered
feIIow students without cause.
Certainly, it will be a long time
in the healing process,
and all we can do is pray
for the families of the victims.
Think of this as the final,
and there's only one question.
''What did I do to deserve this?''
Mommy, why does that girl's face
look like that?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org