Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
You don't speak Spanish,
right?
Are you ready?
Everything is cool?
Yes.
Good.
Use your imagination
and your skills.
Everything is subjective.
Whatever that means.
He who think he's bigger than
the rest, must go to the cemetery.
There he will see what life
really is. It's a handful of dust.
La vida no vale nada.
Diamonds are
a girl's best friend.
Go to the towers.
Go to the café.
Wait a couple of days...
...and watch for the violin.
Two espressos
in separate cups.
No. Two espressos
No.
I said two espressos.
Dos espressos, dos
espressos. In separate cups.
Señor.
Dos espressos,
in separate cups.
Two espressos,
Si.
Sus dos espressos...
No.
Very loud.
Are you interested in
music, by any chance?
What else?
Wait with the girl.
She's a criss-cross.
No.
Yeah...
...you left your bag
unprotected.
There's nothing in it.
Oh.
Ah.
Do you like my ass?
Yes.
So, what's wrong?
You don't like sex?
Never, while I'm working.
Really?
How can you stand it?
Hola.
Do you like my raincoat?
Yes.
So, you don't like
mobiles, either.
Huh.
No guns...
...no mobiles...
...no sex...
No.
Suspicion.
Hitchcock.
Are you interested in films,
by any chance?
I like really old films.
You can really see what
the world looked like...
...thirty, fifty,
a hundred years ago.
You know the clothes,
the telephones, the trains...
...the way people
smoked cigarettes...
...the little details
of life.
The best films
are like dreams
you're never sure
you've really had.
I have this image in my head
of a room full of sand.
And a bird flies towards me,
and dips its wing into the sand.
And I honestly
have no idea...
...whether this image came
from a dream, or a film.
Sometimes I like it in films
when people just sit there,
not saying anything.
Oh, yes.
Diamonds are
a girl's best friend.
Have you seen
"The Lady from Shanghai,"
Orson Welles?
That one makes no sense.
Rita Hayworth as a blonde.
I think it's the only film
she's ever a blonde in.
It's like a game.
Deception, glamour...
...a shootout with
shattered mirrors.
She dies in the end.
So, I finally have
what you need.
Do you have what I need?
Do you like Schubert,
by any chance?
I love him.
He died when he was
thirty one years old.
Something like that.
No.
Are you interested in
science by any chance?
I'm interested
in molecules.
The Sufis say each one of us
is a planet spinning in ecstasy.
But I say...
...each one of us is a
set of shifting molecules.
Spinning in ecstasy.
In the near future...
...worn out things will be made new
again by reconfiguring their molecules.
A pair of shoes.
A tire.
Molecular detection
will also allow...
...the determination of an
object's physical history.
This match box
for example.
Its collection of molecules could
indicate everywhere it's ever been.
They could do it
with your clothes.
Or even with your skin,
for that matter.
Wait three days until
you see the bread.
The guitar will find you.
Among us, there are those
who are not among us.
I'm among no one.
No.
Take a seat.
No. I don't speak
Spanish, either.
Except, maybe
when I'm in Spain.
Would one still call
those, "bohemians?"
My grandfather
was Bohemian.
You know,
in the Prague sense.
I strongly doubt that he would
have had any bloody sympathy...
...for those kinds
of bohemians.
And then of course, they are often
the true artists, are they not?
Are you interested
in art, by any chance?
Maybe painting,
perhaps?
Yes.
Well, as we were discussing, the
derivation of the usage of bohemian...
...in reference to artists or
artistic types, wasn't that it?
I don't know
the origin, exactly.
Of course there's Puccini's
opera, "La Bohème".
That's based on the French book,
"Scènes de la vie de bohème".
Probably published
mid-nineteenth century.
There was an oddly
beautiful Finnish film...
...some years ago
based on the book.
But where the use of
bohemian or bohème in French,
came from to
begin with...
I can only speculate.
Oh...
Yes, of course. I imagine
you have... things to do.
The Mexican will find you,
he has the driver.
Ah yes...
...the driver.
You do know...
...that this guitar was owned
and played by Manuel el Sevillano.
It was recorded on a wax cylinder
in the 1920's, believe it or not.
God only knows
whatever happened to that.
Been nice talking with you.
As they say,
la vida no vale nada.
Los Americanos!
I heard you have a very
beautiful black girlfriend.
She's asleep.
Nothing is true.
Every thing's imagined.
Do you
notice reflections?
For me, sometimes the
reflection is far more present...
...than the thing
being reflected.
Are you interested in
hallucinations, by any chance?
Have you ever
tried peyote?
They wear mirrors
around their necks.
And they play violins.
Handmade violins.
With only one string.
I'm going to
call the driver.
No mobiles.
Està bien.
Ya, ya, ya...
No mobiles.
These fucking
Spanish assholes.
Jesus Christ! Addington!
Fucking sound proof door.
How the fuck did
you get in here?
I used my imagination.
Is this your twisted idea
of revenge for something?
No. Revenge is useless.
Addington! Security!
God damn it!
What is your
fucking agenda here?
You people
don't understand...
...a fucking thing about
how the world really works.
I understand.
But I understand
subjectively.
That's fucking nonsense.
Your sick minds have
been polluted with crap.
Your music,
movies, science.
Fucking bohemians
on hallucinogenic drugs.
All that shit has
poisoned you.
And it has nothing to
do with the real world.
And I suppose you believe
that by eliminating me...
...you will eliminate control over
some fucking artificial reality.
Reality is arbitrary.
Fuck you.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org