I got to go. Sorry.
Are you okay?
Thank you. Lights.
Manadoro, where are you going?
Are my critiques so terrifying?
I'm sorry. It's an emergency.
Joey.
Go round to 14th.
Keep your eyes open.
Nicky?
Get over here. Don't go anywhere.
Where are you going?
Stay over here. Stay here.
What the fuck's he gonna
do to him, Lou?
Lou, you can stop this thing.
Jesus Christ!
Nick.
Nicky.
Nicky Shades was the best
sewer-to-sewer football player ...
I ever saw.
Everyone thought he was gonna be
a big star in college ...
and then go pro.
Yeah!
But after 9/11, he enlisted
and went to Afghanistan.
I didn't have the balls
to do anything like that.
The furthest I'd ever been
from the neighborhood ...
was the Jersey shore,
when my mother got sick.
But I'd always wanted
to do something brave ...
like Nicky.
In a way,
that's how this all got started.
I don't understand.
Why are you not registered yet?
You see, they only gave me
a partial scholarship,
just a partial one,
and they need me to take
a full group of courses,
which I can't afford
the full group.
Well, based on
your father's income,
you should qualify for loans.
A loan?
When my father
got out of the service,
he had a wife and two kids.
Couldn't find a job.
Didn't want to go on welfare ...
because he didn't believe
in charity.
He shined shoes.
Six days a week,
ten hours a day.
He told me,
if any of the kids asked,
that he worked on Wall Street.
Which technically he did.
Well, that's very admirable.
But things have changed.
Our government
owes trillions of dollars.
Surely you can borrow
$30,000 or $40,000.
Mike, let me tell you something.
The only school worth that ...
would teach you
how to print money.
Your father's a funny man.
He's joking
about counterfeiting.
Look, if you could just
do me a favor ...
and get me into
a photography workshop ...
with Professor Reyerson,
if you could just get me
into that one class, one class,
this guy can teach me
everything I need to know,
everything.
It's like having an appetizer
at a really nice restaurant ...
or eating a full meal
at a crappy drive-through place.
You get what I'm saying?
Besides, I always tip
really nice,
really, really nice.
Let me give you a tip.
This is a university,
not a Brooklyn trattoria.
So you're just gonna
have to coax your father ...
into the 21st century.
Sorry.
You're fuckin' sorry?
Sorry, are you kidding me?
- Hey.
You don't know my father;
you don't know me, you prick.
Yeah, reach for the phone,
you dick.
♪ Tell me where you're goin' ♪
♪ What is ♪
♪ goin' wrong ♪
♪ I felt you leavin' ♪
I had this girl at my house,
you know?
And I was like,
"Yo, you got to do your thing."
"Bitch, you got to listen up."
Hey, yo, Mikey, Mikey.
Come on, baby,
time, baby, time.
I got other jobs to do.
I lived in Bay Ridge.
Who would have thought
the ass end of Brooklyn ...
would be the next
hot neighborhood?
But some days,
it was hard to tell.
My friends sure as shit
hadn't gotten the news.
Hi, Joe.
Oh, thanks.
All right,
I'll talk to you later.
So what happened?
A three-hour trip now?
There's traffic.
What do you want me to do?
Again with this fucking camera.
Put the fucking camera down.
This is a job here.
We're working, okay?
Gina Abruzzi, my girlfriend.
She said she'll quit smoking
the day I ask her to marry me.
So on top of everything else,
I cause lung cancer.
You should try actually
sleeping in the bed.
Come on, we're late.
All right, I will be out
in five minutes.
If it ain't
Beau Brumbles himself.
What's the con?
Benefit the same
ignorant motherfuckers ...
that you took money on
last week.
♪ Won't you come around? ♪
Chuckie and my father used to
work together in sanitation.
Since his accident,
my father couldn't drive,
do any heavy lifting.
He was on
the disability pension,
which he supplemented
quite nicely ...
by taking action
in the neighborhood bars.
I drove him on his rounds
every morning,
and then he dropped off
his receipts with Tony.
When I was young, I thought
Tony was king of the world.
My father had to explain his
territory ended at 4th Avenue.
Hey.
Rumor had it the Albanian mob
was even encroaching on that.
Somebody had torched
one of Tony's social clubs,
and so he was hanging around
his brother Lou's car service.
Can I talk to you
about something?
I told you, no loans.
Come on,
give the fuckin' kid a tip.
Don't be a cheap bastard.
He drives you around
every fuckin' day.
He won't take nothin'.
Nothin'. No?
You good people
like your old man?
Come on, let's get a drink.
I got so much stuff to —
- Small drink, that big.
- All right.
- Come on.
- Go.
Every fuckin' time.
I worked in a typical
car service crew,
evenly split between
the retired ...
Danny, go, shoot.
And the retarded.
Any one,
just put one down, go.
Cocksucker.
- You said to throw.
- That's what you throw?
This is what I get for playing ...
with a goddamn
born-again Christian.
Wait, wait, so if he
don't gamble, you pay double?
Yeah, and if we win,
I win double.
But so far, that's just
a beautiful fuckin' theory.
You're not allowed
to drink neither.
It's a choice.
He's allowed
to screw his wife,
so long as he don't enjoy it.
Car service.
Come on.
It's Eileen Zaccaro.
Who's up?
- I'm up.
No, you're not up.
I'm up.
For Eileen Zaccaro,
I'm way up.
Eileen Zaccaro.
Damn.
She sucked and fucked
everything that moved,
and everybody knew that
except for her husband,
Phil Zaccaro.
It's gonna be Danny.
About five minutes, Eileen,
all right?
Hey, Danny,
have her come in here.
She could do all of us.
Yeah, invite Philly Zac.
He can come watch.
You both make me sick.
Oh, yeah, born again.
Once was bad enough
with this fuckin' guy.
You know, God danced
the day that you were born.
But when you have a heart attack
in the Battery Tunnel,
he's not gonna care that
you meant to straighten out.
When you die,
all that matters ...
is the state of grace
that you're in right then.
When you die —
- When you die.
When you die in Brooklyn,
God says, "Fuck you."
Fuckin' idiot.
Car service.
Fuckin' Nicky Shades.
And then Nicky Shades
rolled in.
First time I'd seen him
in eight years.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah, I need a job.
How's it going?
I know the neighborhood.
Yeah.
In five minutes, hon.
All right.
Hey Joey, you're up.
You see, usually, I only
take guys with their own cars.
That's my car.
It's kind of old, no offense.
Cheers.
Wait a second.
Lou.
Just give this guy a break.
If he breaks down, I look bad.
And guess what.
This is my business.
I understand that, Lou.
Look, if he breaks down,
I'll give him my car.
He fought for our country.
Hey, I fuckin' know that.
I don't hire war heroes.
I need reliable drivers.
Joey.
The fuck are you doing?
Get going.
All right, look,
if you vouch for him.
I do.
I don't want to hear any shit ...
if I call you at 2:00
in the fuckin' morning.
- You won't.
- It's gonna be your ass.
I know.
Give me your license.
Thanks.
Yeah, no problem.
Car service.
Michael, right?
Mike, yeah.
What apartment number?
What's the number?
Five minutes.
You're up.
And if I hadn't put my neck
on the line,
they wouldn't have even
given him the job.
You believe that?
Nicky Shades working for Lou.
The world's upside-down.
I work for Lou.
Pasta was better
when your mother made it.
Well, I'm going back
to work ...
for Lou.
♪ See her walking ♪
♪ With a fella ♪
♪ Two of them ♪
♪ So nice and mellow ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
Gina, hey, babe,
look over here.
Mikey, look.
It's beautiful.
Hey.
Don't you think you have
enough pictures of me?
I love you.
He's not here yet.
I'm just waiting too.
You a photographer?
Yeah, yeah.
Not like him, though.
Well, Reyerson's brilliant.
You know, he spent over a year
with the Maasai.
Yeah, I know.
Wouldn't you love
to do something like that?
And drink blood for breakfast?
That's the easy part.
In their culture,
for boys to become men,
they have to kill a lion
with nothing but a spear.
Sorry, sociology major.
Yeah, figured.
I'm Kathy.
- Hi.
Can I help you?
You were here first.
No, go ahead, please.
Mike Manadoro.
It's an honor to meet you,
Mr. Rey —
Professor Reyerson.
You're my all-time
favorite photographer.
Well, then you definitely need
photography school.
Manadoro.
Rockaway Beach.
You saw my portfolio.
Of course, I'm on
the scholarship committee.
Wow, thank you.
I mean, if you liked it.
Not that I'm assuming
you liked it.
You got your scholarship,
didn't you?
Yeah, that — that's
actually why I came.
I, um ...
I'm not gonna be able
to come here this year.
Really?
And why is that?
I'm sorry, I —
I — I can't tell you how much
I wanted to study with you.
- No, tell me, how much?
- Excuse me?
How much does photography
mean to you?
It's a family thing
and a financial thing.
I just wanted to tell you
in person.
And you need what?
They just said
that your class was full,
and — and I can't get in
unless you sign a waiver.
Apparently,
there's an opening now.
It's too bad.
You and I had important work
to do together.
Listen.
I feel really weird
about taking your spot.
What happens
if he doesn't do it?
Do what?
Kill the lion.
Whoa.
Where the fuck you been?
- Sorry, hit some traffic.
- Traffic?
Come on, you live across
the fuckin' street.
Hey, you're the one that said
you needed the money, right?
Look, you're making me
even later as it is.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't get your fuckin' Irish
up with me.
Hey, Lou, shut the fuck up,
all right?
Let the kid go.
You go do what you got to do.
Nicky's going with you.
Get going.
Let's go.
Check this out.
Ridiculous.
- Bullshit.
- Motherfucker.
Can you believe this?
$11,000 for fuckin'
bathroom fixtures?
I'm gonna stab this cocksucker
with a fuckin' pencil ...
right in his face.
All right,
there it is right there.
- Through there?
- Yep.
Oh, nice.
By the way,
nothing ever happens,
but it's kind of just in case.
Look at you.
Fuck off.
You're coming for the TV.
I know.
We should have brought
miner's hats.
Not in there.
In here.
This it?
Hey.
Hey, get up.
Get up!
Is this it?
Just take it.
Let's go.
No.
Why are you taking our TV?
My dad'll pay.
Come on!
Is it too much to turn
a goddamn light on?
This is fucked up.
That scumbag owes you?
No, Tony.
But it's still fucked up, man.
Jesus Christ.
- Well, what do you want to do?
What do you want to do?
You want to go adopt those kids?
You can't think about it.
When I cleared —
listen to me.
When I cleared a house
in Afghanistan,
they lost a lot more
than a fuckin' TV, okay?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah.
It's funny to think ...
that the people that live there
can't see it.
That's because they're in it.
Baby.
I thought we were gonna talk.
Gina.
You don't want to get married?
I want to be able
to afford it.
All right, well,
then there's no problem,
'cause Ma said that we could
move in upstairs rent-free.
I'm not taking fuckin' charity
from your mother; I'm not.
I want to be able to pay
my own fair rent.
Things aren't
fuckin' easy, Gina, you know.
Nicky Shades is working
at a fuckin' driving service.
All right, all right.
I just want to be able
to have sex in a bed,
like people.
Think I found a guy.
Yeah.
Think I found, uh,
just who I might want to use.
Yes, definitely.
Mike, I want to talk to you
about something later,
all right?
All right.
Yeah.
Hey, what's up?
You see the size
of that fuckin' guy?
He's huge.
What's he doing here?
Tony and Lou went to see
a couple of the Albanians ...
down at the gas station
on the parkway ...
to set 'em straight, right?
These guys start yelling.
Tony pulls his gun out,
tells 'em to calm the fuck down.
Next thing you know,
the Albanians
got their guns out,
but they're pointing them
at the gas pumps.
Those fuckin' maniacs,
they were gonna blow up
the whole fuckin' block.
Jesus.
Jimmy, go pick up Mrs. C.
Yeah, boss.
So who the fuck is that guy?
It's Edward;
he's from the Russians,
'cause the Russians
are the only ones ...
that won't take shit
from the fuckin' Albanians.
Hey, Mike.
You know, flies,
they shit and they vomit ...
every six seconds.
I saw it on Discovery Channel.
The fuck are you talking about?
The Discovery Channel.
Just shut the fuck up.
Where the fuck you been?
I sent you up 2 1/2 hours ago.
I needed to make
another stop.
Ooh, fellas.
Eileen had to make
another stop.
Eileen Zaccaro,
how about this?
Finally made it
with Saint Daniel.
Hey, Danny, I heard
she could suck-start a B-52.
Whoa!
You — you dip your dick
in holy water before you yeah?
Is she converted now?
Seriously, though, Danny,
you better watch out
for Phil Zaccaro.
He's a mean son of a bitch.
He'll cut your fuckin' balls off
and feed 'em to you.
He will.
Four, five, six.
He just shit in your coffee.
Fuckin' stop that with
that shit in people's coffee ...
and all that shit.
Mike, come over here.
No, it's educational.
It's stupid.
Sal, get the phone.
I hear you're looking to make
some extra cash.
I got a little side job for you.
Lou was taking care of it,
but he had differences
with our business associate.
Prick thinks he's my boss.
Anyways, I just need you to
fill in while tempers cool down.
What kind of job?
The way it works is,
you drive out to Oyster Bay.
You pick up a package
from this nigger.
African.
What?
He's Ethiopian,
you ignorant fuck.
You pick up a package
from this Ethiopian nigger,
and you bring it to a hebe
in Borough Park.
What's in the package?
That, my friend,
don't concern you.
Is it drugs?
Look, it pays
two grand a week,
which is enough for you
not to ask questions.
Just for delivering a package.
I need someone trustworthy.
All right.
But ...
I'm gonna need six weeks
up front.
What?
You believe the balls
on this kid?
Little bit every week
won't do me any good,
won't help me out.
I — I need a big chunk.
Okay.
Give the kid his money, Lou.
Big purchase, right?
♪ Meet me, oh, mama ♪
♪ In the city ♪
♪ And see everything ♪
♪ Is so fine ♪
Welcome, come on in.
Please try to sit a little
closer rather than far away.
Hey. Hey.
- What's up, man?
- What class is this?
Soc, dawg.
- What's that?
- Soc.
It's hot, bro.
It's hot.
- Yeah.
- Cool.
You're gonna see
on the syllabus —
Oh, thanks.
Four things we'll be
looking at to begin.
First it's going to be —
All right.
With an area
of women's rights.
I have women's rights down
'cause it's global.
It'll never end, women's rights.
Thanks.
Hey.
Oh, hi.
So you're coming here
after all.
Yeah, yeah, I managed
to figure it out.
Great.
You're still in
Reyerson's class, right?
Yeah, I'm all registered.
Looks like we have
two classes together.
Yeah, looks that way.
What else are you taking?
Statistics for Social Research
and Language and Liberation.
- Two classes is good.
- Yeah.
What's up, Kat?
Hey, Jared.
How was your weekend?
- I missed you.
- Oh, shut up.
Some micro societies.
Right over here.
Pull up over here.
He's an interesting fucking guy.
Thinks he's a big shot
'cause he works at an embassy.
This is Mike, the new guy.
You can call me Todd.
How you doin'?
See you Thursday.
Go ahead.
Only give the bag to this one.
Or him.
Anyone else?
Okay, then.
That's it.
Between them and the Spanish,
it's a South Brooklyn
breeding war.
Whoever wins, we lose.
Smells nice in here.
How was your day today?
I was gonna tell you.
When?
Exactly when?
After I look like an asshole
in front of Tony?
After the whole neighborhood
knows before me?
I know how you feel
about loans.
I don't give a —
I know how you feel
about loans.
I got to go to school.
I don't give a shit
whether you go to school.
Come here, come here.
Come over here.
Look, look.
See that?
See those guys?
That's what you're gonna be
in ten years.
You want that, huh?
Or you're gonna end up
in a dumpster.
What the fuck?
Why are you so mad, huh?
You work for Tony.
- I don't work —
- You fuckin' work —
- I don't work for Tony!
I give him his cut.
He ain't my boss,
and he ain't my pal.
How much is he paying you?
How much?
Two large a week.
Oh, God.
You got no brains at all?
Two grand a week
for driving a car?
He owns you now.
Did you take out the garbage
this morning?
Because I can smell it.
So why'd you go to bat for me
with Lou that day?
You know, when we were kids,
we all looked up to you,
you know, want to be you.
I know I did.
I guess you got your wish.
So what ever happened
to football?
Hey, darlin'.
Can I get one more, please?
I'm getting married.
- No shit.
To who?
Name's Luz.
- Luz?
- Luz.
She's Puerto Rican.
It means "light" in Spanish.
She from the neighborhood?
Nah, her brother
was in my unit.
Hey, want me to get that?
Uh, it's all taken care of.
What are you talking about?
Um, he said,
"Thanks for showing 'em
we ain't afraid."
Here, do me a favor.
Tell him,
"You should be afraid."
Nicky, he's just trying
to be fuckin' nice.
That guy was a fuckin' tit.
Well, listen,
I think I'm taking off.
Go out for a pass.
- What?
- Go out for a pass.
Come on, go.
Go, Mike!
Keep going.
Go, go, go!
Oh, oh, oh,
interference!
Keep going, Mikey,
point in the hook!
Yeah!
Ah!
The rookie
from Narrows Avenue.
He's at the 20, the 10.
Touchdown!
Oh, shit!
Oh, shit.
Put me down.
What's up?
You're gorgeous.
What's your name?
Listen to me.
Hey, Nicky, Nicky,
you see these guys?
Look at me, baby.
Turn around, turn around.
Nicky.
No one takes those off.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
easy, easy, easy.
Relax, I'm okay.
Get off, please, get off me.
Come on.
Dude,
put the fuckin' camera away ...
and help me up, bro.
I'm okay, bro.
It's okay.
There you go.
This is Mikey Manadoro.
I known Mike
since he was like ...
Oh, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Get off me.
Get off me, man.
What's up, Mami?
Thanks for the ride, Mike.
Mikey, you want to put
the fuckin' camera down ...
and help me up, please?
So how many of you have
ever been in a darkroom before?
Yes, I know what
you're thinking.
You're thinking why on earth
do you bother ...
when you can do in a tenth
of the time on a computer?
That's what you're thinking.
Oh.
What about you?
First time in a darkroom?
Yeah.
Welcome to antiquity.
There is something about silver
and light that is magic.
And there's another sort
of magic here too:
mistakes.
You don't get happy accidents
in Photoshop.
So let me show you
around the room,
and behind you over there
is our biggest enlarger.
So remember, everyone,
I'm looking for work
from this room,
the film work, and digital work
in your presentation.
Okay, thank you.
You know, I'm really glad
you came.
Thanks.
Well, aren't you
quite the little protégé?
You going somewhere?
Just home.
You want to go get some food?
Now?
Yeah, now.
There's a great place
around here.
I was just gonna try to make
a dent in reading tonight.
Come on, it's my day off.
I just read about this place.
Oh, yeah?
Then come on in.
I bet you're gonna like it.
Hey.
- Mikey.
- How are you?
- Little Mikey.
You look good.
How's your father?
He's okay, you know,
same as always.
- This is Kathy.
- Bella signorina.
Yeah, not bad.
Let me see what I can
fix for you.
How about over here?
Yeah.
Right near the window,
you get a little air.
Thank you.
Thanks a lot.
My pleasure.
Be right back.
- Okay.
You ever been?
- Italy?
No.
Oh, God, I wish.
I'm gonna do a summer session
there in Florence.
Wow, that's great.
Yeah, I'm excited.
It was an easier sell
to my parents ...
than a Maasai hut
made of cow dung, so ...
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Some antipasto on the house.
- Thank you.
Enjoy.
Thanks.
Well, you must be
quite the regular.
Oh, my father used to work
with the owner in sanitation.
Sanitation like the mob
or real garbage?
We don't use that word.
- What, mob?
- Garbage.
- Oh.
- I'm just kidding.
Relax, it's fine.
Anyway, he — he doesn't
work there anymore.
He — he was in an accident.
He's on working compensation.
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's fine.
He's just got a bit of a limp,
and to be honest, it's actually
probably better for him,
'cause he — he likes
to dress up all nice.
He never used to wear
his work clothes in front of us.
He'd always bring a bag
to work with him ...
and change before he got home.
Kind of like
he had to separate his job ...
from his identity.
What?
Nothing, I just feel like
I got a bone in my nose,
and I'm the chief
of the next weird tribe ...
you're gonna go investigate.
I don't —
Why don't you just
have some wine ...
and relax a little bit?
Okay.
So you think you're
the chief of the tribe?
Jesus Christ,
you don't stop?
What?
I'm sorry, I know.
It's actually —
it's really terrible.
I shouldn't do that.
I shouldn't
psychoanalyze people.
I was psychoanalyzed
my whole life.
My mother's a psychiatrist,
so ...
What does your —
what does your mom
say about you?
That I'm a classic borderline
histrionic cerebral narcissist.
Wow.
When my mother got mad at me,
she just called me
my middle name.
Well, you're lucky.
No, no, you don't know
my middle name.
What is it?
Oh, come on, you can't do that.
You can't not tell me now.
No, I'm not telling you.
It's awful.
- What is it?
Tell me your middle name,
and we'll be even.
Gandolfo.
Go ahead and laugh.
- Ciao.
- You're a beautiful lady.
- Ciao, grazie.
- Hey, go easy on the lady.
- All right, you too.
- Come on.
- Good night.
Your Italian is fantastic.
Oh, no, it's — it's really not.
I — I fake it much better
than I speak it.
No, I think you're ready
for Florence tomorrow.
I think I'm gonna have to do
a little more.
You all right?
I'm sorry.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna drive you home.
What?
You have a car?
Yeah, of course I have a car.
What, "Of course I have a car"?
Nobody in Manhattan has a car.
I'm not from Manhattan.
What?
- Sorry, I got to get —
- It's okay.
Hello?
Nicky broke down
on the Gowanus.
Fuck, not again.
He's getting a tow,
and I'm giving him your car.
What?
No, no, no, I'm in the city.
Mike, Mike, Mike!
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm okay.
Are you sure you're all right?
You made a fuckin' promise.
If you don't get your ass
in here right now,
you're gonna be back
to repo-ing —
Um ...
l — I drive car service,
and sometimes it's at night.
I — It's for protection.
No, it — it's fine.
You know, I'm almost
home anyway.
So I'll just walk.
No, no, it's all right.
I want to drive you home.
Hey, Nicky, it's Mike.
Couldn't find you
under the Gowanus,
and don't crash my car
or anything, 'cause I need it.
I'm waiting —
Mike, they're fuckin'
killing Danny!
They're killing fucking Danny!
What the fuck
you talking about?
Fuckin' around the corner.
What the fuck are they doing?
Danny, Danny!
- Mike, stop!
Stop!
Lou said he wouldn't do it
unless Zac cleared it by Tony.
Come to my fuckin' house, huh?
Sniffin' around
with my fuckin' wife, eh?
Stupid.
- Get ready to see Jesus.
- Mike, no!
Fuckin' asshole!
Who the fuck are you?
Fuckin' shit.
Shades ...
this ain't about you.
Well, let's keep it
that way then, Phil.
We're done here.
- Fuckin' payback.
- Hey, Phil.
It's over.
Okay?
All right.
You all right?
Look at me, look at me.
Danny, it's Nicky.
I'm right here.
I'm putting my hand
behind your head.
Take it easy.
No, no, don't talk.
Your jaw's broken.
Mike, pull the car around.
We got to get him
to the hospital.
I got you.
Give me a nice, deep breath.
I know.
I know, I know, I know.
It's terrible.
I got you, pal.
♪ Junkie walkin'
through the twilight ♪
♪ I'm on my way home ♪
But here's the thing.
It's the best place
I've ever been.
Snow-covered mountains,
fields of fuckin' red poppies.
Nick, what the fuck are you —
Shh.
And nobody fucks with you,
'cause you got a weapon on you
taller than they are.
It almost lets you believe
you're winning.
Nice, right?
RPG hit our convoy,
and my fuckin' knee
is shot to shit.
Bye-bye, football.
But with the morphine
they gave me back in Kandahar,
I won the fuckin' Super Bowl
every day.
Shouldn't you stop before you
have your kid, though?
All I'm saying is,
you fuckin' made it back, okay?
You made it back.
You don't want to die
in Brooklyn, do you?
Sal says you die in Brooklyn,
God says, "Fuck you."
You want that?
God already told me,
"Fuck you."
It's 4:00 in the morning.
Come on.
You're so beautiful.
Isn't she beautiful, Mike?
Look at this belly.
Get your camera.
Let's take pictures, come on.
Yeah, we'll show 'em
to the kid one day, come on.
- No.
- Take our pictures.
Take off your glasses.
Take 'em off.
Can I see?
You look tired.
Yeah.
Let's go to bed.
Good night, Mike.
Yeah, I should go too.
Well.
Oh.
Wake up, Mike.
I'm not the neighborhood hero.
Listen, our over-arching theme
should be  ...
deviance in the age
of globalization.
One country's legal punishment ...
is another's
human rights violation.
That's moral relativism.
It is all relative.
Not if you're a victim
of female circumcision.
Oh, okay, see that's nasty.
It's not a crime
in their culture.
- What?
- Check it.
Most 187s, they had head trauma.
They'd get beat the shit
out of by their dads.
Yeah, violence is directly
related to testosterone.
No, it's poverty.
Crime goes up —
And as I was saying
before I was interrupted,
most crimes are committed
by young males,
regardless of wealth,
race, or nationality.
Mike, what do you think?
I think she's lazy as shit.
This school costs
$12,800 a semester.
Divide that by four courses,
14 weeks, one class per week.
It's basically $233
we're pissing away here,
talking amongst ourselves.
It's not
sociologically irrelevant.
Didn't you read
in the course description ...
that we were
gonna be doing this?
Are you the leader
of this group?
Because I don't remember
voting for you.
Jesus Christ.
We're supposed to agree
on a topic today.
I mean, you do realize that?
Then I agree with her.
Most crimes are done by men ...
whether it be for money
or status.
Bottom line is,
it's basically who's got
the biggest swinging dick.
Am I supposed
to be intimidated ...
'cause you get into bar fights?
All right,
that's enough for today.
Remember, next week,
we will divide the research.
That was productive.
Asshole.
Easy, all.
We're supposed to study
in the library now.
I didn't think you'd want to.
How did you get that?
Polo mallet.
I broke up a fight, all right?
What do you want me to say?
That thing
in your glove box ...
have you ever had to use it?
Big Blue recovers
on the turnover.
Looks like Lamm came up with it.
And that gives Denny Lane
and the Big Blue a chance —
He's gonna score
on this next possession.
Just on the edge
of the red zone,
just outside the 20.
And now they're in the red zone.
Walker threw it.
Score, touchdown.
21-yard —
- You called it.
It's just your fan belt,
by the way.
It's not a big deal.
Thanks.
That really makes me
fuckin' sick.
It's just a collection,
you know?
Name of the fuckin' game.
- Bullshit.
Tony is just like every other
piece of shit terrorist cunt.
He's a fuckin' cancer.
He needs to be taken out.
Let's go get a beer, huh?
♪ Girl is on my mind ♪
Get off me.
My brother's gonna be mad
we're missing his barbecue.
Oh, God, look at that.
Mm, you smell that?
Freshly baked every day.
Santo's, heart
of the old country, baby.
What?
You sound like one of those
old guys down at Tony's.
Why'd you take this job?
It's not like you.
Maybe I'm tired of being me.
You don't want to end up
like my father.
Your father was
in a car accident.
That's different.
What, you think I'm an idiot?
The only person that believes
that is my mother.
My father got run over
by one of Tony's guys ...
for his gambling debt.
I'm not in college,
but I know more than you think.
Be careful, baby.
All right?
I'll see you next week.
Stop.
What's that for?
Oh, nothing.
I study photography.
Come inside.
A lot activity in there
for 10:00 in the morning.
It's an Irish bar.
They don't need a reason.
- Hey, how you doin', yeah?
- What's up?
- Same lucky three, huh?
All right.
- Hey, same time tomorrow.
- Yeah, yeah.
Take care of that leg.
Be nice, be nice.
Am I dreamin',
or did you honk at me?
I got class in, like,
half an hour.
What do you want me to do?
Tony is inviting you
to poker night.
I can't.
I got to be in the darkroom,
and I got
a sociology presentation.
Stop the car.
- I'm already —
- Stop the car!
Jesus Christ!
What, huh?
What?
- The Sociology ...
- I don't even like the guy.
You don't like the guy.
of Deviance.
You want to know
about the sociology of here?
You ever wonder why you never
got your ass kicked in school?
I have looked after you
your whole life.
I have used my relationships
with certain people ...
to your advantage.
Now, I am not telling Tony ...
that the guy he just gave
12 grand to ...
has got better things to do.
Well, you should
keep on working.
These aren't due till Monday.
No, it's all right.
I want to hand 'em in now.
You shouldn't.
They're no good.
Can we talk outside
for a second?
I'm sorry, but the last
presentation, lowly interiors,
was ten shots inside
of a janitor's closet.
The one before that
was armpits and feet.
What do you want me to do?
Worry about your own work.
Ah, Toni, yeah,
I'll see those later.
Look, if you don't
like my stuff,
why'd you give me
the scholarship?
Because I thought
I could teach you.
The scholarships aren't
a pat on the back,
if that's
what you think they are.
I didn't say that.
The work in your portfolio was
much more interesting than this.
The Verrazano Bridge at night,
a sidewalk cafe,
I can get these on postcards
at the chamber of commerce.
When did you stop
taking portraits?
Your work was so personal.
Now it's just like you're trying
to be as generic as possible,
trying to blend in.
I do have other stuff.
It's just
not for everyone, okay?
Yeah, like that pretty girl
you sit next to.
Well, she's not grading you;
I am.
I need to see something realer,
something with
a point of view, eh?
And, Mike,
you've got to work harder.
Your mates are in the darkroom
until midnight.
You barely make it to class
on time.
And don't ever ask me
to step outside again,
like we're in a bar.
Hey, you want to
skip the library ...
and maybe get a drink?
We have to work.
What about Rocco's?
You like that place, right?
Oh, sure.
So it's me, then.
Look, we're just
really different, okay?
And I'm not saying that
that's a bad thing.
It's just with two classes
and a project, it's risky.
It could get awkward.
Awkward.
Look where you're going,
asshole.
What the fuck
did you say to me?
did you say to me, huh?
I'm sorry, take it easy.
I'm sorry, I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
It's okay.
Hi.
- Oh!
- Jesus.
Sorry.
You leaving?
No, I just moved my car.
I used your keys.
Do you want me to leave?
No.
No, don't be stupid.
You must think I'm crazy.
What?
No, hey, no.
I tell you it's too risky,
and then here we are,
and I'm leaving for the summer,
and you probably
have a girlfriend anyway.
Is that — is that her
on your chest?
That's my mother.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Hey, hey.
You didn't know.
What kind of guy
leaves a girl like you ...
in the middle of the night?
You just scared me,
that's all.
♪ You got to be fortunate ♪
♪ You got to be lucky now ♪
You scare me.
♪ I was just sitting here ♪
♪ Thinkin' good and bad ♪
♪ But I'm the kind of woman ♪
♪ That was built to last ♪
♪ They tried erasing me ♪
♪ They couldn't wipe out
my past ♪
♪ To save my child ♪
♪ I'd rather go hungry ♪
♪ I got all of Ethiopia ♪
♪ Inside of me ♪
♪ And my blood flows ♪
♪ Through every man ♪
♪ In this godless land ♪
♪ That delivered me ♪
♪ I've cried so many tears ♪
♪ Even the blind can see ♪
♪ This is a woman's world ♪
♪ This is my world ♪
♪ For this man's girl ♪
Where were you last night?
I stayed at a friend's place
in the city.
Don't worry about it.
- Yeah, who?
Listen, can we just
get out of here, all right?
It's a little fuckin' awkward,
don't you think?
- Awkward?
- Yeah.
Oh, awkward.
What is that,
your new word from college?
Jesus Christ, Gina,
let's just go fuckin' talk
someplace, all right?
We need to talk.
- Oh, so now you want to talk.
Yeah.
I left you four messages.
Jesus Christ, Gina,
let's just fuckin' go and talk,
all right?
Just not right here.
- No.
- Fuck.
You know what?
You come see me when
you're ready to talk commitment.
Commitment.
Until then, just don't
talk to me at all.
Come on, baby, what,
I'll marry you.
Yeah, I bet you would.
Yeah, I will.
Come on, we'll have
beautiful children.
Fuck off!
You can — you can have those.
I printed 'em out for you.
You're late.
Oh, Mike.
I need to lock up.
- Hey.
- What?
- Look at me.
Turn it off.
I've almost finished
my presentation.
Can I see it?
- No.
- Why?
Nah.
Why?
I don't want
to show it to you.
You got to see it
with everybody else.
With everybody else?
I'm not like everybody else.
I'm sleeping with you.
No, that's not gonna work.
- Come on, show me.
- No.
Show me.
You left your flash drive
on the nightstand.
I'm gonna show myself.
Oh, no, no.
No.
Come here.
Come here, you.
Hey.
What?
What are you gonna
do to me, huh?
I'm not scared of you.
Give it to me.
I'm not anymore.
Poor old Danny.
Yeah, that dopey fuck.
He's got his jaw in a vice.
Six weeks before he can eat.
It's like I said,
that little triangle's
more powerful ...
than a freakin' load of tanks.
True.
- Am I right?
- Yeah.
Armies have gone to war.
Kings have lost their thrones.
Listen to your father, Mike.
He speaks from experience.
You know, your mother,
God rest her soul,
she was the prettiest girl
in Bay Ridge.
I mean, we were both
nuts about her.
But we make choices in life,
right, Vin?
$50.
I fold.
$100.
Oh.
I'm out.
Yeah, that's
a fuckin' surprise.
Take it down.
Lou, go get that good bottle
of scotch I got you.
Mike, get it from the back,
will you?
It's by the bar.
Yeah, sure.
All right.
Kid's a fuckin' card shark.
I don't know.
Edward, do me a favor?
Go get us a couple
of meatball subs.
It's gonna be a late night.
I'm fuckin' starving.
Counting your money?
You're gonna lose it all.
It's all gonna be gone
by the end of the night.
What do you care?
Oh, Nicky,
you're not on tonight.
Why don't you go work on
that wreck of yours?
I got other things
to worry about tonight, Lou.
Now, how do you like it with
a fuckin' gun in your face?
Isn't this what you
do to people?
Nick, calm down.
It's crazy.
You're fuckin' killing
my neighborhood.
I'm gonna fuckin' kill you.
I'm gonna fuck —
Mike?
What are you doing here?
Nick?
Nick, what are you doing?
Someone want to tell me
what the fuck this is all about?
I almost fuckin' died,
and you're killing
my fuckin' neighborhood,
and I'm gonna fuckin' kill you.
No, no, no, no!
Get a beer or something,
come on!
Sit, sit!
What the fuck?
What are you gonna do?
You come into my joint?
You point a gun at me?
You out of your fuckin' mind?
Give me your watch.
What?
Give me your fuckin' watch.
Jesus.
You got be kidding me, Nicky.
You better take
all that money,
'cause you just bought yourself
a world of hurt, son.
Shut the fuck up!
Nick.
Put it back.
Give it back.
Nick.
Nicky.
Come on.
So now you're in it.
Tough guys, huh?
Do it.
Please, Mike.
Come on.
Don't make me do this.
I want it to be you, Mike.
Do it.
Make your fuckin' balls, Mike.
That's your fuckin'
employee of the month?
Is he here yet?
Can I come in?
Do you want something
to drink?
No, thanks.
Hey, he'll be back.
They're great.
I got to go.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
What's the matter?
I'll see you tonight.
Thank you.
Lights.
Manadoro, where are you going?
Are my critiques so terrifying?
Sorry, I got to go.
Mike, this is it,
your grades for the whole class.
I'm sorry.
It's an emergency.
Professor, I'm supposed
to see Mike tonight ...
if you want me
to give that to him.
Joey.
Go round to 14th.
Keep your eyes open.
Nicky?
Hey, whoa, where the fuck
are you going?
You stay right here.
Hey, Nicky!
Just shut the fuck up
and stay right where you are.
Don't fuckin' move.
What's he gonna do to him,
Lou?
Lou, you can stop this thing.
I told you from the beginning,
I didn't want no war hero.
You know, he was
in Afghanistan too,
back when it was the Russians.
Nick!
Nicky.
What the fuck did you do?
You motherfucker!
Oh, shit.
Mike?
Nicky.
Mike.
Ow.
Nicky.
I swear to God,
I'll fucking kill you!
Mike, help me go.
Act of God, act of man.
What's the fuckin' difference?
Your mother is as dead
as Nicky Shades, you know.
I wish I had someone like Tony
to blame.
I should've brought the wig
to the hospital that day.
The look on her face.
She was so fuckin' disappointed,
you know?
Well, it had such
beautiful red hair.
It was hard for her to lose it.
But you were 16.
16, you're on a subway,
holding a red wig
on a Styrofoam head,
it's embarrassing, I know.
I get that.
Vinny, I — I got the car ready
when you —
Yeah, yeah.
H — Hey, what — what's up, Mike?
You're a stone — cold prick
to these guys now.
Remember that you've got that
going for you.
Sal, Jimmy,
go get us some coffees.
Listen, sometimes my brother
can be fuckin' careless.
I didn't intend for him
to involve you in this.
I know that you and Shades
were tight.
But you knew it had to happen.
It's nice to see a kid
from the neighborhood ...
who understands and respects
the old codes and values.
Now, today was supposed to be
your last Oyster Bay run,
but by way of thanks,
I'm giving you
the job permanent.
Holy shit!
It's not worth it.
Let it go, bro.
Let it go.
Oh, Mikey.
Thank God.
Can you help me, darling,
with this garbage?
It's so heavy.
- Sorry, I can't, Miss Gattei.
40 years I'm your neighbor,
you can't help me
with a little garbage?
There.
God bless you.
Pop.
I'm so glad you're here.
You okay, son?
They jacked —
they jacked my car.
What happened to the bag?
I think they took it.
They took it.
Oh, Jesus.
Hey, it's Mike.
Leave me a message.
Hey, it's me again.
I just haven't
heard back from you,
and I'm getting
kind of freaked out,
so give me a call.
Listen to me.
We got to talk ...
before we go downstairs.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm looking for Mike.
He's not here right now,
but he'll be back in a while.
He just hasn't
been coming to class.
I'll tell him
that you came by.
Let her in.
Yeah, let her in.
Do it.
Oh, Kathy.
Shit.
Where have you been?
Kathy, come here.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
You okay?
Come here.
Hey.
Talk to me.
Fuck, I missed you.
Mike, we got to get going.
- You okay?
- Yeah, let's get out of here.
Mike, we got to talk, huh?
Okay.
Hey, we got to get going.
I'm gonna be back
in a few hours.
The fuck you will.
You're coming with me
to see Tony.
No, the fuck you will.
Sit the fuck down.
Sit down!
Sit the fuck down!
- You let go of me!
Sit down!
You let go of me.
Let me go.
I'm taking you
to the hospital.
Fuck.
No, no, let's just
get out of here.
- Are you kidding?
- No, let's go.
Come on, you're not okay.
Oh, shit.
How's the leg?
Where you two going?
- Mike.
They're not going anywhere.
I'm calling the cops.
- No, no, no.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Easy, easy.
Who the fuck is this, Mike?
She's nobody.
You got to get her out of here.
Hey, shut the fuck up.
Nobody is fuckin' leaving.
You understand me?
Mike.
Here.
Here, check her coat.
There's nothing in it.
Check it.
Look.
Lou, let her go.
It's okay.
You know Gina Abruzzi.
Yeah, I know Gina Abruzzi.
Gina and Mike,
they're getting married.
Gina's his girl.
This girl is shit to him.
Look at her, she's a WASP.
You think I'd let my son
marry a WASP?
It's not gonna happen.
Is it true?
Just get her out of here.
Get out of here.
You're getting married.
Ow.
You know,
this Oyster Bay route's become ...
a big fuckin' pain
in the balls for me.
First you don't
get along with my brother.
Then Mike here gets jumped.
So he says.
Yeah, that's what he said.
Mike, I want you
to tell me what happened.
Don't worry about anything.
You're just here
to be debriefed,
you know,
like a fuckin' astronaut.
So I drive to Oyster Bay
like I do every week,
go pick up the bag.
And this little fuckin' guy
answers the door.
Hey, is Todd here?
Some guy I never seen before.
And he's acting
all weird like he's —
like he's fuckin' deaf
or something.
Hey.
And then Todd shows up and ...
Thank you, Don.
tells the little guy
to give me the bag,
and I leave.
- Your package.
- Awesome.
But everything's a little weird,
you know?
And I'm on my way back.
I'm at a stoplight.
And this big SUV
pulls up behind me,
And these two
black guys get out.
They come up alongside my car.
Next thing you know,
I got a fuckin' gun in my face.
And I could see it
in his eyes right away.
Let it go.
He saw I was in drive.
I knew I was dead,
because he knew if
I hit the gas,
I'd run into the getaway car.
Meanwhile, that's what I did ...
And the other guy,
he scooped up the bag.
Then you went straight home.
Yeah.
You drove all that way
with a bullet in your leg?
Yeah.
I mean, I was out of it.
I — I stumbled up the stairs,
and I — I passed out
on the kitchen floor.
That's where I found him.
Anybody see you?
No.
You sure?
'Cause Mrs. Gattei said
you took out her trash.
I did see Miss Gattei, and —
'Cause see, the thing is,
Mrs. Gattei said
she didn't see any bullet hole.
Exactly, I was hiding it.
She doesn't see shit.
Tony.
Vinny, there's nobody
here I can trust ...
except for my brother,
and Lou here thinks
you got the bag, Mike.
I mean, I don't know.
What, call it intuition, Lou?
Right.
I agree.
There's a fuckin' first.
I got to say, Mike, I mean,
I'm disappointed.
I mean, your story
is fuckin' thin.
Is that the new one?
Can I see it?
That's a nice phone.
My wife would like this.
It's got a good screen.
Who called?
I don't know.
You don't recognize
the number?
No.
Who fuckin' called you?
What the fuck's going on?
'Cause he called a lot,
ten times yesterday.
You don't know the number.
Who called you?
Huh?
Lou.
It was Lou's phone number.
What's the matter, Lou?
You looking for your phone?
It's right here.
Look, when all
this shit came down,
I called him a few times
to see what was going on.
That's all.
There's calls on there
from before Mike left Brooklyn.
I want you to know
it was not my idea.
Shut the fuck up!
Tone, you gonna believe
this piece of shit over me?
Come on, I'm your brother.
Yeah.
My own brother.
You remember what Daddy
used to say?
I'm too old a cat
to be fucked by a kitten.
Tone, come on, you can't
do this in front of everybody!
Tony, come on!
- Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Get ahold of yourself.
I'm not gonna fuckin' kill you.
Our business arrangement
is too valuable.
Mike, I'm sorry
you had to see that.
You're a stand-up guy.
Now I want you to tell me,
where's the bag?
Someplace safe.
All right, good.
I'm glad to hear that.
Wait, you lied to me?
l — I had to keep it
as an insurance policy.
Who the fuck was I gonna
give it to, Lou, huh?
Vin, your son is smart.
No.
And no offense,
but he's got ambition.
Tell your father
where he can find the bag.
It's in the boiler room,
behind the boiler,
where they used to
keep the coal,
that little black door.
This I don't forgive.
I don't.
Open it.
I don't have the key.
Your cutter has it.
Straw and rocks.
Where are the drugs?
Diamonds.
You think I'd have your son
carry fuckin' drugs?
Thank God for that, Tone.
He deserves a cut.
Pop, no.
Don't worry.
Mike will be taken care of.
No.
This kid ...
he took a bullet for these.
It's only fair he gets a cut.
I just lost my brother,
so don't you fuckin' lecture me
about fuckin' fair!
I just lost my brother!
- Tony, it ain't right.
- Vinny!
Mike, get your fuckin' father
out of here.
Get him out of here.
- That ain't —
- Vinny!
Get your fuckin' hands
off of me!
Let's go.
He'll get over it.
Oh, shit.
Hey, Pop, I'm sorry.
I know this is really fucked up.
Hey, we're —
we're both limpin', huh?
What's wrong with you?
Gina and I broke up.
Well, don't be so gloomy, huh?
You never know what'll come
with the next roll of the dice.
That got your attention.
Put 'em the fuck —
where did you get those?
What the fuck did you do?
What do you mean what'd I do?
I knew you took the bag.
Come on,
you left a trail of blood ...
right to the boiler, Einstein.
I had to clean it up
before anyone saw.
I was thinking,
"What the fuck
were you doing down there? "
Now I got a bag in my hands,
a bag that you can get
at a hardware store.
When Todd didn't have the key,
I knew that we had it made,
because that meant
that he didn't have a chance ...
to count the diamonds.
If you had to pick a time
to lie to me,
this was a good one,
'cause now I finally had ...
a decent hand
to play against Tony.
Are you fuckin' crazy?
Relax.
You know who these people are.
The guy killed his own fuckin'
brother right in front of me.
Christ.
And then you,
you have the fuckin' balls
to ask him for one.
That was so nice.
I mean, come on.
What are you laughing about?
I was so proud of myself.
I — I loved it.
Oh, my God, I was like a king.
Look, if you're gonna
ask for it,
they know
you're not gonna take it.
And remember me,
I'm the guy
that has no ambition.
Fuckin' Tony.
The more he put me down,
the more he freed me.
Look at that.
So what are you
gonna do with 'em?
Question is ...
what are you gonna do with them?
You are gonna have to leave.
You can't stay working for Tony.
If you do,
your life will be a short one.
What about you?
Hmm?
Who the fuck's gonna
take care of you if I'm gone?
Don't push me,
'cause I got to warm up.
Huh?
Chuckie would be proud,
I'm telling you.
Put it up, put it up,
put it way up.
Oh, what?
Come on, I seen guys do it
all the time at —
Look, you put a little grease ...
on the lift of the back
of the truck,
you're down, right?
Retired, you're in Miami at 50.
You're telling me for four —
for four years,
I drove you around,
and you're perfectly
fuckin' fine?
Yeah.
Why the fuck
didn't you tell me?
What am I gonna do,
tell everybody?
Come on,
there's rats everywhere.
Come on.
Told Chuckie, but —
I'm your son
for Christ's sake.
I was ashamed at first,
you know.
What your mother would think.
But after she was gone ...
look, I couldn't —
I couldn't work there
any longer.
If I would have worked there
for another hour,
I swear to God, I would have
blown my fuckin' brains out,
I'm telling you.
You know what's funny?
I've been faking it for so long,
it actually hurts
when I walk regular.
Officially, you and l,
we had a knock-down, drag-out.
You left.
Yeah, all right?
Yeah.
Gina said I'd never
leave the neighborhood.
Come here.
Look at that.
The neighborhood is leaving.
Thank you.
I'll be all right.
Kathy.
Kathy, wait a second.
Kathy, wait, wait.
I need to talk to you.
Glad to see
you're in one piece.
We talked.
I'm going to the airport.
Wait.
I want to go with you.
What?
I want to go
to Florence with you.
Why don't you go
with your fiancée?
It's a good place to honeymoon.
Kathy, I had to do that
for your own protection, okay?
I had to say that
so they'd let you go.
I apologize.
I — yes, I had a girlfriend,
okay?
That's true.
We broke up.
Good for her.
- Kathy.
- What, Mike?
I'm sorry.
You're sorry for what?
For lying to me?
For fucking me
behind your girlfriend's back?
Or are you just sorry
you weren't man enough ...
to tell me about her
in the first place?
What are you sorry for?
You know what?
Here.
Take this.
Now I don't have to ship it.
Are we done?
Can I go?
What are you gonna do now?
Right.
Well, Reyerson said
you should keep in touch, so ...
I want to take a picture
of you.
Let me.
I want you to look at me
and say, "Fuck off.
I don't love you."
Do it.
Say it.
♪ You think your days ♪
♪ Are uneventful ♪
♪ That no one ever ♪
♪ Thinks about you ♪
♪ She goes her own way ♪
♪ You think your days ♪
♪ Are ordinary ♪
♪ That no one ever ♪
♪ Thinks about you ♪
♪ But we're all the same ♪
♪ And she can hardly breathe ♪
♪ Without you ♪
♪ She says ♪
♪ She ♪
♪ Has ♪
♪ No time ♪
♪ For you now ♪
♪ She says ♪
♪ She ♪
♪ Has ♪
♪ No time ♪
♪ Found all hands against his own ♪
♪ Found all eyes looking down ♪
♪ And the sun had left and gone ♪
♪ All his friends
could not be found ♪
♪ Don't talk about ♪
♪ Don't think about love ♪
♪ She's not the one ♪
♪ You're dreamin of ♪
♪ Don't talk about it ♪
♪ Can't live without it ♪
♪ You say you're alone ♪
♪ He found all hands ♪
♪ Against his own ♪
♪ She's not the one ♪
♪ You're dreamin' of ♪
♪ Don't think about it ♪
♪ Can't live without it ♪
♪ You say you're alone ♪
♪ He found all hands
against his own ♪
♪ You say you're alone ♪
♪ He found all hands
against his own ♪
♪ You say you're alone ♪
♪ He found all hands
against his own ♪
♪ You say you're alone ♪
♪ He found all hands
against his own ♪
♪ And no light from up above ♪
♪ Just a dark and lonely road ♪
♪ He found all hands
against his own ♪