Every time I hold you
There's a feeling
You know, it's a feeling that pulls me in
Deeper and deeper into your mind
Every time
And I want more and more until they stop
Oh, there's something about you, baby
You're all I need
Slip into something
more comfortable. Hawksin Hotels.
You're everything to me
We think it really brands the chain.
Hedonistic opulence. Pampering.
The place to go
when you're with someone special.
Well. I think it's perfect.
Lf. By "perfect. " you mean low-rent porn
that's completely inappropriate
for me or my hotels.
Even the chocolate was naked.
- We could lose the chocolate.
- Why are you speaking?
- Stop speaking. Why is he speaking?
- I don't know.
You know what let's do?
When I'm speaking. You stop speaking.
- Right.
- He did it again.
Mike?
Well put.
Look. Fellows.
I don't want my customers thinking
about what their bed was doing
before they got in it.
On the good side.
The pastries were delicious.
Amici.
A vanti.
Mr. Hawksin?
The passion angle was something that
we decided on months ago.
Apparently. We define the word differently.
Have you ever even stayed
at a Hawksin hotel?
Because judging from what I saw in there.
You have no idea what we believe in.
I've never actually stayed
in a Hawksin hotel per se. But...
And what about the international angle?
We decided we would go
for global business.
Exactly. I'm with you. Sir. Great idea.
Today's business needs to attract
a wider customer base.
- Please. Sir. We can do this.
- Again with the talking.
All right. This isn't the first time
a tryst in a hotel room didn't go well.
But just give us one more shot.
If we don't make a commercial
that tells the whole world
exactly who Hawksin Hotels really is.
Well. Then I'll...
We'll both quit the business forever.
Scout's honor. You have my word.
And my passion.
- Passion.
Again with the talking.
You see Mike. Here?
He's worked for me for 37 years.
And hasn't said one word the whole time.
I'll tell you what.
We're opening a new five-star restaurant
at the Hawksin Grand
in San Francisco next week.
You're both invited.
You'll come up.
Get a feel for the place. If you can.
Call the office. They'll set it up.
"Leave the business. "
Thank you. Sir.
What did I tell you about the girl
climbing on the guy's lap like that?
What? It was tasteful.
I need to see the proofs before
you send them to LA. Before...
Call Ted Stevens' new agent.
See if Ted can shoot a spot
10 days from now.
Also. There was that video...
Messenger the Milan samples
to Granger's apartment.
...performance artist.
He was a New School graduate?
- I want to see those tonight.
- I don't remember his name.
- But find him and give me his reel.
- Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Thanks.
I've got one more shot with Hawksin.
If we don't get this account. I don't know
if Charlie and I are gonna make it.
Don't worry about it.
International angle?
What does that even mean?
You'll come up with something.
You always do.
Hello. Yeah. That's me.
I'm not interested.
CITYone Bank.
I was afraid it was another woman
who heard about your imminent success.
I didn't think Emory Banks
had a jealous bone in her body.
Over shoes and careers. Yes.
Other women. Not so much.
- You're amazing.
- I know.
Mr. Woodruff. I'm afraid
your card's been declined.
Really?
Just give me a minute. Yeah?
Mr. Woodruff, this is Jennifer David
from CITYone Bank calling again.
Please don't hang up, sir,
we seem to have a situation.
Yeah. It's more of a train wreck. Actually.
I just tried to use my card.
We've frozen it for your protection.
Our fraud division has picked up
more than $28.000 in charges
within the last 10 days to your account.
- Holy shit!
- What is going on?
- It's $28,422...
- Somebody stole my card number.
...and 48 cents. To be exact.
- So I take it these aren't yours?
- Yeah.
- I mean. No. No.
- That should work.
- Hey. Hold on.
- Thank you.
I've got this.
Just give me a minute.
- Mr. Granger?
- Yeah.
I just need to verify
some of these charges.
Jessica. This isn't really a good time.
Why don't you call me tomorrow morning?
It's Jennifer. Actually.
Jennifer David. And I can call you then.
Please don't try to use your...
Let's go.
Doesn't little Granger want
to come out and play?
No. Little Granger's tired.
Sorry. It's probably work.
- Hello?
Mr. Woodruff?
- Speaking.
- This is Jennifer David
from CITYone Bank Card. It's 8:00 AM.
Oh. Right. My wake-up call.
Good morning, sir.
- Now, we need to establish...
- This is important. Em.
- ... which of these charges are fraudulent.
- Do you want to get off the phone?
First, if you wouldn't mind
answering a few questions.
Your mother's maiden name?
I can't believe you. Just hang up.
- Klinger. No.
- Okay.
Strike that. That was
her second husband. Winslow.
- Is this a bad time, sir?
- Yes. It is.
Sorry about that. Ms. David.
That was my maid.
She was being naughty. Please continue.
Okay.
Can you list your last three purchases?
Let's see.
I bought an iPod a few days ago
for the gym,
took a potential client to Pete's.
Best ribs in town.
You'll probably see that charge
on my card a lot.
Do you remember a charge of $250
at Lotus Florists, four days ago?
- I didn't get any flowers.
- No. Not mine.
They were delivered to a Ms. Leslie Moore.
- Ms. Leslie "We're just friends" Leslie?
- Em.
...O- O-R-E. That's right.
Her mother was sick.
She just passed the bar.
- Flowers are very thoughtful.
- You're killing me here. David.
- Em. You're not leaving. Are you?
- Whatever.
- Okay, now, Mr. Woodruff...
I'm gonna have Emily come by
- and get things. All right?
- I'm going to fax you a print-out
of all these charges. Circle the ones
that are yours, and then fax it back to me.
Great.
At least tell me it's not raining again.
Is it nice out?
I don't know. Sir. I'm in San Francisco.
SF. You know. City by the Bay.
Home of the 49ers. Golden Gate Bridge.
Cable cars...
May I help you?
This is Jennifer David
from CITYone Bank Card calling.
548...
420...
Call you tonight?
But I need you to really try to...
Please don't hang up. Sir...
All right. Sir. I'd be happy to help you.
That should take care of it for now.
That's it for me.
That was my 42nd hang-up tonight.
I've had like four "Get lost. Idiots. "
And 16 "Lose my number. Morons. "
And I think this guy just called me
a douchebag. What's that?
I don't know.
I'm so happy they moved me
to Lost or Stolen.
You're so lucky.
Do you want to go for shopping
before it gets too crowded?
- Okay.
- You know. I have to go to Vikram's house
this Sunday. And Papa told me
to get a new dress.
- Wow!
- He said. "Every time the Bhatias see you
"in jeans. I'm afraid
they're beginning to think
"that their future daughter-in-law
is a boy!"
Your father has a point.
Vikram comes from a very good family.
You should impress them.
- You're killing me here.
- I'm what?
It's a slang.
You need to pay attention in class.
Teacher's pest?
The toilet is going up. You just watch it.
Good. You're here.
Priya. beta, you know
father was saying that...
Mama. Please. Let me sleep.
Good night. Please.
In that case. Good night.
Okay. I got one. "From the food
"to the toilet paper.
"Hawksin's means quality. "
Yeah. That's really bad.
"If you're tired
and you need a place to sleep... "
I've got nothing.
"People who stay with Hawksin's
are smarter than when they check out.
"Than when they check in. "
No. No. No. No.
That doesn't make any sense.
Govinda. Go get your sister.
Otherwise she'll be late for work.
- Shh. Ma. I'm watching cricket.
- Govinda!
Okay. Okay. Priya. Wake up!
- Priya. You'll be late for work.
- Look at this boy. Huh?
- Priya!
- All the time. He's watching these
- terrible programs on television.
- Yes!
These cricket hoodlums.
And he behaves like that.
- Good morning.
- Ah! It's your morning.
It's our evening. Huh?
Your dinner's almost ready.
You're not wearing those boys' pants
to the Bhatias'. Are you?
I have a dress. Don't worry.
And what is this?
Ah! That's a birthday present
for your father's cousin. Auntie Rani.
And Govinda has to take it
to the post soon.
Otherwise it won't make it on time
to Palo Alto. Right. Govinda?
- Yeah. Ma.
- Mmm-hmm. Right.
You're back? Any good news?
I went all the way to Mud Island.
They were not even at home.
I don't want to talk about it.
- What's the score?
- 121 for six.
Sounds like my day.
- Hi. Papa. How was your day?
I don't want to talk about it.
Another night without a family dinner.
If you sat down with me now.
We could eat together.
Just because you have to work
all night out
doesn't mean that I have my dinner
at 5:30 in the evening.
If you read India Today this week.
It talks about
how we are the future of India.
And. You know.
Some 10.000 people applied for the job.
And only 100 were accepted.
And I'm making good money.
Even though it's not normal
for a young woman like you
to work all night on the phone.
Talking to strangers.
- Pretending to be Americano.
- Yes. Yes!
We did it! We scored!
Like being Indian is so normal.
All right. I got some more.
- Next.
- "Our mini-bars will get you maxi-drunk. "
Oh. My gosh.
Okay. Let's start with your celebrities.
Sarah Michelle Gellar.
- Sarah Michelle Gellar.
Sarah Michelle Gellar. Good. Next.
Sarah Jessica Parker.
- Sarah Jessica Parker.
Sarah Jessica Parker. Good.
Mary-Louise Parker.
That was in your handout.
All right?
That is Dylan...
That's Dermot Mulroney.
Not to be confused with Dylan McDermott.
Formerly of The Practice.
Very good. Priya.
Okay. Tonight. I want you to study
your Jessicas and your Ryans. Okay?
- Lf somebody calls you a dawg?
That's good.
- Right. But if you dog somebody?
That's bad.
Word. Okay.
Who makes the square burger?
Is it Wendy's. Burger King or McDonald's?
Burger King.
Wendy's. Zia.
Wendy's makes the square burger.
Burger King is Home of the Whopper.
And McDonald's is famous
for its Quarter Pounder. With or...
- Without cheese.
... without cheese. Good.
- Yes. Priya.
- But many of them
are starting to add salads
and low-fat chicken dishes.
Because of the obesity
which is plaguing the country.
Good. Okay. That's it. Everybody.
Sunday. I want all those
from the Southwest here at 6:00. please.
And Californians. Monday at 5:30.
And New Jersey.
Everyone here at 8:00. please.
- Ms. Prasad?
- Yes. Zia.
May I please move out of New Jersey?
Everyone keeps swearing at me.
Zia. You know the rules.
Everyone starts in New Jersey.
And works their way out.
Flirting with disaster
You're the one I'm after
Think I've found my destiny
Luxury and danger
Rapture me, my stranger
Hold me close, don't let me be
I could fly on the wings of my heart
Deep inside, I've been falling apart
L- L-Love
There's a magic in you
And I'll be under your spell
L- L-Love
You are not sick.
You don't have time to be sick.
Therefore. You are not sick.
Hello.
Mr. Woodruff, this is Jennifer David
from CITYone Bank. How are you?
- I'm sick.
- Oh. I'm sorry.
- If this is a bad time...
- No. No. No. It's fine.
It's just. I'm...
He's sneezing.
He's allergic to you.
Just put down the phone.
Maybe I should call you later, sir...
I don't have time to be sick today. David.
I gotta nail this thing.
He's building something.
If you want to feel better right away
then try sucking on a lemon.
Then drinking a tall glass of warm water
with cardamom and fresh ginger.
I'll try that.
I'll call you back later. Sir.
Good luck with your nailing.
Bye!
There's a magic in you
and I'll be under your spell
- We going late tonight?
- Not tonight.
I've got to get home early.
Make some comfort food. Get some sleep.
Get better for tomorrow.
I got cleared for tonight.
Now I've got to check with Karen
about tomorrow?
- Spoken like a true married man.
- Hey. It could happen to you. Too.
Didn't Emory make the
"Top 20 Hottest Women in New York" list?
We're just having fun. Pal. Okay?
Don't drag me
into your own little personal hell.
The guys that say
they don't want to get married.
They're the ones who surprise you.
So. Since you've been
on the wedding bandwagon since day one.
You must secretly dread the actual event.
- You know. There's still time to back out.
- I'm not you.
What the hell are you drinking?
It smells like an Indian restaurant.
Cold remedy.
Credit-card girl told me about it.
Still can't believe
someone stole your identity.
I mean. Of all the identities out there
to steal. Who'd want to steal yours?
- Hope they're living large on your dime.
- Nice. Good friend.
There was an attempt to use your card
for $700 at the Mystery Box.
Seriously?
Unless you throw in a night
with the cashier and some dolls.
How do you spend that much
at a store like that?
I don't know what kind of store it is. Sir.
Oh. Come on.
They don't have them in San Francisco?
Yeah. Sure.
Which is why I was certain
this wasn't your charge.
Because I don't give off
a sexually adventurous vibe?
No.
Because you were sneezing profusely
into my eardrums
about the time the charge was made.
Nice work. Detective David.
Okay. The big plasma TV charge.
That's mine.
You know. Sometimes
you just have to splurge
and get yourself something
that you enjoy. Live a little.
Especially after a long day at the office.
I just have a cup of chai. I mean. Coffee.
You're not fooling anyone.
You Californians are all into your tofu
and your sandals.
You're probably a Dead Head.
Am I right. Dude?
Actually. I just prefer jazz.
All right. Here's the question.
Jalapenos in your grilled cheese.
Kicker or overkill?
- Kicker?
- Absolutely.
Hello? You still there?
And the charge to Delicious Delights?
Biggest amaretto cake known to man.
My mother was having a lousy week.
Sometimes you just want
to show someone you care. Right?
Right.
Okay. The last one. Um...
The charges from New World Video.
Those were late fees.
I rented The Notebook. Don't laugh.
Why would I laugh? I love that movie.
I don't normally watch chick flicks,
and I don't even know
if that classifies as one.
But you ever watch a movie and just think
that's the way things should be?
Like. Someone puts themselves out there
for someone or something.
And either they get it or they don't.
But love's worth it.
Hi. This is Courtney Reese from CITYone.
May I help you?
I think that will
take care of it for now.
If any more charges come in,
I'll be in touch with you.
Great.
I failed to mention that you qualify
for our platinum card.
If you agree to a four-year term.
I can get you
a very attractive interest rate.
Four years? That's quite a commitment.
Just think of all the ribs you could eat. Sir.
You don't need to call me "sir. "
I mean. Hell. You know more about me
than my own mother.
- Granger's fine.
- All right.
Granger. Be sure to contact us
if you want an upgrade.
And you should be expecting
a new card soon. Thank you.
Granger?
Jennifer David. May I help you?
I just wanted to thank you
for the cold remedy.
It really did the trick.
It's me, Granger, by the way.
I'm so glad. I was actually going to ask
how you were feeling.
Well. We do what we can do to help. Sir.
Granger, good night.
Be careful. Priya.
- No. Papa.
- I'm sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
Eh? This is the bathroom.
Do you need to use it?
- Have a look.
- No.
This is my bedroom. Our bedroom.
We're buying a brand-new double bed
with a brass headboard.
- Mother has already picked it out.
- Yes.
Oh! Uh...
Perhaps one day we'll have our own house
if we both work hard enough.
But we wouldn't have
my mother's fine cooking every day.
- She has many things to teach you.
- Yes.
So what sort of things do you like to do?
You know.
If you could live your life any way.
What would you want?
I'm pretty content with things as they are.
Once I'm married...
We're married. I'll have everything.
A wife at home.
A beautifully tended garden.
When you're not busy
with our children. Of course.
I love my job.
And as for children. I'm only 22.
There is time for us to live a little.
Don't you think so?
But we will live a lot right here.
Look at that. That's not sexy?
That's what spots are these days. Sex.
I have some vacation time.
So I was thinking.
I'm gonna go with you on your trip.
Oh. And I thought that I...
Well. I thought that I could wear these.
You don't want to go.
You know. It's gonna be cold. Foggy.
I'll be in a hotel room all day.
You're gonna need
some in-room entertainment.
I'm on business. Emory.
This account is important to us.
I can't be...
Fine.
- Fine.
- Em. I'm sorry.
No. You know what? Actually. I think
I'll take Mark Bailey up on his lunch.
I think he has a jet that he takes
to his oceanfront in Bermuda.
- You're trying to tell me something here?
- Yeah.
Nobody says no to Emory Banks.
He has an amazing voice,
he says the most interesting things,
he's funny,
and he has such kind eyes.
- ZIA: You looked up his picture?
- What if we were really soul mates?
Listen. You're just anxious about Vikram.
Trust me. When I was marrying Babu.
I thought my life was gonna end.
I mean. How can two people who
don't even know each other get married?
But then. A few months later.
We were laughing
at something really silly I'd done.
And I realized I'd fallen in love with him.
How sweet.
ZIA: And it's easier than falling in love
with some random voice on the phone.
And seriously. This guy lives in America.
- There's no point.
- I know.
I've got to meet Karen.
Oh. And she made me swear
there'd be no strippers
at the bachelor party.
Well. If Karen said no strippers.
That means no strippers.
Only. I really want strippers.
She didn't say anything
about exotic dancers. Did she?
No. She did not.
Mr. Granger. What can I do for you?
Hey. I just wanted to alert you
a future charge.
When Exotic Minx shows up. That's mine.
I think a pet should make you happy.
Do I seem sad?
Not always. But. You know.
You buy a lot of things.
And people do that
to make themselves happy.
- I eat chocolate.
- Thanks. Doc.
I'm actually hiring dancers
for a bachelor party.
You know. Before the big wedding.
Are you getting married?
Me? No. No. No. No.
It's for my buddy. Charlie.
Party's probably gonna cost
a couple grand.
Wow! So what happens
at these bachelor parties?
The usual things you hear about.
But. Really. It's just a symbolic.
Platonic representation
of the last adventure
before one commits to marriage.
I think it's actually a necessary journey.
A rite of passage. If you will.
- I think everyone should have one.
- Me, too.
Hey. Listen. I'm going
to San Francisco next week for work.
And. You know. I thought maybe we could
get together and discuss my options.
Financial things can get so complicated
over the phone.
It's not really company policy
to do these things in person.
Aren't you supposed to keep
the customer satisfied?
Yeah. We love to satisfy.
But I may not be
in San Francisco next week.
I may be in...
I may be out of town
for a relative's birthday.
I have to go back to work now.
Okay. Well. You know.
You have my number if you stay in town.
Wow!
You can really see David Bowie tonight.
- Sorry?
- In the moon. You've never heard that?
You know. When there's a full moon.
You can see David Bowie's face.
Always...
Well. I thought it was Mick Jagger.
No. No. No. It's clearly Bowie.
You know. The cheekbones. The chin.
Well. Thank you for using CITYone Bank.
Have a nice day.
Good night.
To the guy who said
he's never been anywhere.
I give you. Charlie Hendricks. The world.
Miss Russia.
- I'm from Ukraine.
- She's from Ukraine.
Miss Japan.
Miss...
From somewhere where they wear clogs.
No. No. No. No. This guy.
You deserve it. Buddy.
You deserve the world.
Charlie!
Ladies. Come on in.
Thank you.
- Oh. That's too much.
- I'll pay. Baba.
Don't be ridiculous.
Why not let her?
She makes more than you.
Aha!
You will make a beautiful bride.
Thank you. Baba.
We'll take it. Oh. My beta.
- Hello?
- Granger?
- Jennifer!
- Sounds like you're having fun.
Oh. It's a full-on rager.
It's Charlie's big night,
and the natives are a bit restless.
Next week. It turns out that I will be able
to meet you before the party.
So we can discuss the upgrade
we were talking about
when we were talking. Before.
That sounds great.
I'd like that.
- It's the credit-card girl.
- Nice.
I'll be in San Francisco on Thursday.
So maybe we can meet
at the Hawksin Grand Hotel?
- You know where that is?
- Word.
Okay. Let's say 6:00.
I'll be the dashing New Yorker
with unlimited credit.
It's a date.
I mean. Thursday is the date of the day
when we'll meet.
I'll see you then.
ZIA: You know you're crazy. Right?
Hmm.
What if this guy turns out to be
from a bad family and kidnaps you
and makes you clean their toilets
and. Like. Clean their dirty cats and all?
Then he's in real trouble.
I'm not a good cleaner.
Bhaiya, Mumbai Airport.
Thank you. bhaiya.
ZIA: Thanks. bhaiya.
You know you're playing with matches.
Fire? Why can't I have a little of that?
Why can't I have
just one amazing last adventure
before I come back to Vikram?
This is my bachelor party.
I can't believe you're going all this way
to see if this deranged guy is your Tom.
Richard. Harry. Hank soul mate guy.
- I don't know.
- I promise you. I'll be back in two pieces.
- You better.
- Wish the stars to shine bright on me.
Mummy, Papa, please don't faint,
but by the time you hear this,
I'll be on my way to America.
I know I should have told you,
but it was a last-minute decision.
I left my heart
In San Francisco
I've decided to attend
father's cousin sister's birthday party
in Palo Alto.
It's been a long time since I've seen them.
I'll send everyone your regards.
And see you in five days, maybe.
Ouch!
And please don't panic,
I'm using my own savings.
Papa, remember how you always wanted
your little daughter to travel
and learn different cultures?
This is your gift to me.
The morning fog
May chill the air
Hello. Welcome to Hawksin Hotel.
- Have you got your passport on you?
- Yeah.
Great. Thank you.
You're the behind-the-scenes creative guy.
Yes. Yes. No. And he knows why.
Mr. Hawksin.
Well. Well.
Look who decided to get off their butts
and come fight for the job.
Never turn down a second chance.
The rooms are fantastic. By the way.
Thank you. Sir.
- May I speak. Sir?
- Only to say thank you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- We're gonna knock your socks off.
- And then he ruins it by speaking again.
Didn't we talk about that?
Didn't I ask you not to speak so much?
Didn't I tell you to learn to listen?
Don't you want to be a nice boy?
Didn't I tell you to be more like him?
Here. Watch this. Your hair is on fire.
But I don't want a Honda. Learn from this.
Could you shut up? He doesn't like you.
He likes me.
I can't believe you're hooking up
with the credit-card girl.
No. Wait. I believe it. You're gutsy. Pal.
I mean. What if she turns out
to be this lonely housewife
with four kids and bad teeth and gout?
It's just drinks.
Vibe?
- I got a good vibe.
Oh!
Just your type. 1 o'clock behind you.
- This one?
- Yeah.
Seriously.
That's her.
- I'm going in.
- Good luck.
- Excuse me. Granger Woodruff.
Hi.
- You're not Jennifer David?
- No. But I wish I was.
Sorry. I thought you were somebody else.
Excuse me. Ladies...
You're not Jennifer David?
- You didn't even talk to him?
I couldn't, Zia.
I was frozen. Stuck. Like gum.
Okay. So your crazy crush is over.
Just come home. We'll watch
Fatal Attraction and you'll be fine.
Listen. This guy was no good.
I'm sure he lied about those charges
and he spends money like a maniac.
He's not a liar.
And then he just. Like. Covers it all up.
It's just much better that you run now
Than be hot-glued to the floor later.
Maybe I expected too much.
Besides, he didn't even
get a chance to meet me.
If he did...
You know. There was something
magical in our talk. Zia.
- I promise you.
- Yes.
I do think that the American slang
for that is "bullshit. "
- Just come home, okay?
- Bye.
So. Your girl stood you up.
Come out to dinner with me and Karen's
best friend. It'll be good for a laugh.
Discussing the intimate details
of bridesmaids' dresses
isn't my idea of a good time.
But you. My friend. You've got to take
this stuff seriously. It's your wedding.
Let me know how the bouquets work out.
Sorry. You okay?
- Gray...
- No. No. No. No. You... Do you see color?
Look. Red bag. Red...
Keep the legs elevated.
I think you're gonna live.
- I'm all right.
- I'm really sorry.
- I didn't see you.
- No. I... I wasn't looking. I was...
No. No. No. It's my fault. I feel awful.
I wish you wouldn't...
- Oh. I'm sorry.
- No. I mean...
I wish you wouldn't feel awful.
So. Are you here on vacation?
Yeah. From India. I'm visiting a relative
at Palo Alto. Just for a party.
Hey. I know this might sound odd.
And considering the dangers
of being with me and all.
But you hungry?
I was gonna go out to dinner.
And I thought you might want to come.
Oh! Um...
That'll be nice. But only if it's ribs.
I read about this place in my guidebook.
You do like meat. Don't you?
Yeah.
Mmm.
They're delicious. Thank you.
Granger Woodruff. By the way.
Hello. Granger. I'm Priya Sethi.
Okay. Priya. You've got to just dig in.
Okay? Don't...
Don't worry about getting messy.
Just get it all over you.
Okay.
So. What do you do in Mumbai?
- I'm a nurse. Yeah.
- Nurse.
It's quite nice.
- Good food.
- So...
- Is this your first trip to America?
- Yeah.
I always wanted to come.
And it's much more than I've expected.
- You're on vacation?
- I wish.
I'm actually here for a business campaign.
I have this huge presentation next week.
Hey. Maybe you can help me.
I mean. You're international clientele.
What attracted you to the Hawksin Hotel?
- A friend told me about it.
- So you go on personal recommendations?
I mean. Do you ever just
want to take a chance?
You know. Like... Like the feeling
of trying something different?
I take chances. But usually
I can never afford them.
Charge it. You know. Charge everything.
Just pay for it later.
Just don't let it get stolen.
Did someone steal your card?
I have my ace credit-card girl
working on it.
She was actually supposed to meet me.
But she blew me off.
Yeah. When someone opts out
of a prearranged appointment.
- For what purpose were you to meet her?
- Just casual.
She sounded nice.
But her friends probably warned her
about meeting a complete stranger.
And she probably thought I was psychotic.
Or maybe she just took
one look at me and ran.
Excuse me. I...
I need to go to the restroom.
Zia. It's me. Could you please connect me
to Granger? It's 4593330555.
Why do you want to talk to him?
I thought you blew him out.
I don't want him to think I was rude. And
actually. We're having dinner right now.
- What? You told him you're Jennifer?
- No. It... It doesn't matter.
We're meeting as our real selves,
and it's better this way.
So, could you please
connect me to Granger?
Priya. This can lead to no good.
Or it could lead to the perfect romantic
moment under the Golden Gate Bridge.
Listen. Honestly. You've lost your head.
Hello?
Hello. Granger. It's Jennifer David.
Hey! Is everything okay?
I'm afraid when you didn't show up.
I signed up with the Visa girl.
She threw in a hat.
I wanted to apologize
about not making our appointment.
It turns out I'm out of town. After all.
That's cool. Maybe next time. Then.
Very good. It...
It sounds like you're at a restaurant.
- Teddy's Barbecue. You been?
- Yeah. I was there recently.
Excellent ribs. It's very romantic. Isn't it?
Yeah. You know. Since you stood me up.
I'm actually here with a nice girl.
Of course. I did smack her in the head.
Which I wouldn't have done
if you did show up.
Well. Have fun with your friend.
I'm sure she's quite lovely.
Inside and out. Not to be conceited for her.
Enjoy your evening.
- Good night.
Oh. Wow. She's so good.
- Hello?
- Hello. Sister. How're things there?
- Ji, ask.
- Okay.
What I wanted to know. Sister...
Anji. Just switch it off. I can't hear a word.
Has finally Priya arrived there?
Priya? No. Priya isn't here.
Priya is not there?
One minute. One minute. Supposing...
Supposing she wants to give a surprise?
- Hang up. Hang up.
- Wait a minute. Sister. What?
- Hang up the phone.
- She might want to give a surprise.
- Hang up. Hang up.
- I just can't hang up just like that.
- Quiet!
- Hang up.
Haan, sister. In case Priya...
In case Priya calls up.
Just tell her that... Just inform us. Okay?
Stop it. ji, stop it.
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Hello. Phone...
He sounded very confused.
- Woodruff. Well...
- Mr. Hawksin.
I'd like you to meet my wife. Haejin.
- Hello.
- Hi. Granger.
I'd like to introduce you to a very good
friend of mine. Priya Sethi.
She's from Mumbai.
Mumbai.
That's the New York of India. Right?
I hear there's quite an explosion
of jobs there.
I like to think of New York
as the Mumbai of America.
Both with talented human resources.
- That's so sweet.
Very impressive.
Well. We opened a hotel in Mumbai in '98.
The Hawksin Standard at Nariman Point.
Do you know it?
It's beautiful.
The use of steel and glass is breathtaking.
Thank you. We think so. Too.
You're lovely. Isn't she?
- She's lovely.
- Yes. She is.
Has he invited you to our little shindig?
- I was just about to. Actually.
- Good. Good. Hold on a second.
Mary Pat. This young lady has come
a very long way to be with us.
Would you give her our nicest room.
With fruit basket. Extra chocolates.
Flowers every day? On my account.
Very good. Mr. Hawksin.
- That's very generous. Sir.
Don't be silly.
So. We'll move you to 1740. It's a nicer
floor with its own concierge service.
And I'll put you under Mr. Hawksin's name
as his guest.
Thank you. That's very kind of you.
Not at all. One of the pleasures
of owning places like this.
Doing nice things for nice people.
If you'll excuse us.
We'll say our good nights.
Good night.
- Good night.
Wow! I... You...
You know. He really...
I've never seen him act like that before.
- Yeah?
- That was amazing.
No. No.
Let me just get one thing right.
Aren't you supposed to be
Priya's best friend?
Yes. Mr. Sethi.
- Isn't she supposed to tell you everything?
- Yes.
Then why aren't you telling me
where she is?
Okay. Maybe I should ask Miss Prasad.
Miss Prasad!
No. No. No. Mr. Sethi. Please.
- I'll tell you.
- What?
- She's gone to meet a CITYone customer.
- Okay. Where?
- Mr. Granger Woodruff.
- Okay. An American?
- To America? Oh. My God!
- Oh. God. No...
- I should have never let her work here.
- No.
No. No. No! Mr. Sethi.
I promise you. She's coming back.
She had no intention to elope.
Or anything of that nature.
- Elope? Who is talking about elope?
- Oh. God.
Oh. My God. I have to go.
I have to go and get her.
- I have...
- No. No. No. Mr. Sethi! No. No!
Mr. Sethi. I promise you.
She's coming back.
Morning. Priya.
Hey! Isn't it amazing?
- I love rain.
- Yeah. Yeah. It's... It's great.
Hey. You're still going to meet me at
the restaurant tonight at 7:00. right?
Yeah.
Hey. Is this a fancy party or something?
Well. You might want to wear
something nice.
I mean. Not nice-nice. But. You know.
Yeah.
Well. I have some work to do.
But I'll see you tonight.
Great.
Welcome to San Francisco International.
Now. The moment we find our luggage.
- We'll go and find this Hawksin hotel.
- Careful. Careful.
- Rajiv Uncle!
- Who's this man talking to me like this?
- I'm Sajarit from Punjab.
- Okay. How...
I know it has been a little while
since Navinda's wedding. But...
Your family owns that store in Hoboken.
- Oh. Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
- And she's my wife. Neha.
- Hello. namaste.
And you are here
for Rani Auntie's birthday.
Of course. Of course.
And we are getting late
and we have to find a cab
and get our luggage first.
Come. Come. Come.
I'll give you a ride in my car.
No. No. No! We don't want a ride!
My parents will be furious
if I did not give a ride.
- Please. Come with me. My car is quite big.
- No. No. No... It's fine. Thank you.
My car is fast. Neha. Please hold this.
- Okay.
- Come. Come. Come. Come. Come.
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I'll help you.
- It's fine! It's fine...
It's so good to see you.
Come. Please. Excuse me.
And this is a most pleasant surprise for us.
Please accept tea.
We thought. Since you were coming
all the way from here
to Mumbai for Priya's wedding.
We thought it was important that we also
show our respects. By coming to...
Han ji. You know. But we are only sorry
that Priya and Govinda couldn't come.
- Priya is visiting friends.
- Friends.
And Govinda. You know. So
busy with exams and cricket and all that.
- His final exam's going on.
- Han ji. Han ji.
Hi. Sorry to disturb you.
Delivery for Priya Sethi.
- Really? Thank you.
- Here you go.
Anji. Where is your boom box?
- She's asleep.
- Okay.
All right. We will find this Hotel Hawkskin
as quickly as possible.
- Yeah.
- There. We will divide.
locate Priya and take her home.
Pimmi. You will stay here.
If there's a problem. We'll call you.
- No. No. No. No. I'm coming with you.
- Let her come. ji.
- Okay. Huh?
Rajiv? Where is he?
- Hello.
Oh. There you are.
Rajiv. Please come down.
Anji wants to show her dance. She's been
practicing specially for Rani Auntie.
But. Auntieji's sleeping.
I don't think it's nice to disturb her.
Let her sleep. She sleeps through
everything. You. Come down. Come.
- Now?
- Oh. Yeah. Why not?
- Right now?
- Oh. Yeah. Right now.
Come on. She's all set with her music
in her hand. Please. Rajiv.
Come on. Anji. Play some music. Come on.
Shake it. Anji!
Isn't she wonderful. Rajiv?
Come on. Do it!
Oh. I forgot. The Sawants are coming over
for dinner tonight.
Some day
When I'm awfully low
When the world is cold
I will feel a glow
Just thinking of you
And the way you look tonight
Lovely
Who's that?
Just a friend.
First impressions can be deceiving.
- The thing about this guy...
- Here we go.
...he's all casual charm
like nothing gets to him.
But really. Complete softie.
- Yeah?
- In college.
He couldn't eat or sleep
until this girl he liked finally talked to him.
- I think he actually threw up afterwards.
- What?
The man knows
how to make an impression.
Wait. Let me give you a little advice.
Don't listen to drunk Americans.
No. But I do agree with Charlie.
You know. There's something more
than what you really show.
What about you? Any secrets?
Are you an Indian movie star
hiding in America as a tourist?
Well. Glad you could make it.
Enjoying yourselves. I hope?
- Definitely. Thank you. Sir.
Thank you.
It's a wonderful party.
Same feeling as the rest of your hotels.
A magical oasis
that springs from nowhere.
It's so familiar.
We need you now.
Maybe I should hire her
for my ad campaign.
She's a smart girl.
- He's kidding. Right?
- Yeah. He's kidding.
Have fun. Buddy.
It's okay.
Look. But don't touch.
Do you know. When I was little.
I always wanted to find the golden ticket
in that chocolate.
Like Willy Wonka.
So that I could go somewhere new.
I always wanted to know
who was gonna drink that chocolate
- after the fat kid fell in it.
- Yeah.
Did you just try to push me in?
That was a tap and you're too heavy.
You see.
I knew there was another side to you.
On the outside. You're the psychic.
Sweet nurse from India.
But you've got a streak.
You're right.
There are things you should know.
- Talk. Talk.
- Are you mad?
- No.
- Talk.
I'll throw you in.
I forgot to watch out for drunk Americans.
Oh. There you are.
Listen. I know. I know.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Business first. I need you for a second.
One of us will be right back.
- Gee.
- What's up. Buddy?
- I just put something together.
- Oh. Yeah? What's that?
Well. Call me cynical.
But did you bring your Indian friend
Prius here...
- Priya.
Whatever.
To show Hawksin you're some
free-thinking. International guy?
"Look at me. I'm dating an Indian girl. "
Yeah. You...
You figured me out. Chuck.
Oh. Yeah.
All right. All right.
Priya! Priya. Wait!
- Where are you going?
- I'm going back.
I think I've served my purpose.
- What are you talking about?
- I hope I was impressive enough for him.
I heard you.
You only took me to the party
to make your boss happy.
Is that why you bought me this dress?
- So I wouldn't embarrass you?
- What?
No. No.
Okay. look. The thought did cross my mind
that bringing you to this party
would impress Kit.
- But the truth is. I think you're...
- Stupid.
Right?
Get into the car.
Both of you. Get into the car.
Rajiv! Rajiv. Where are you off to?
Priya called and asked us
to pick her up from the city.
We didn't want to inconvenience you. So...
I'll also come with you. Since you don't
know your way around here.
No. No. We've got the map.
Show her the map.
You've been already too generous. Okay?
We'll return the car soon. Bye!
- Bye!
Who is it?
I don't have time
to eat your poisoned candy.
It's just a little poison.
Come on! Just one bite.
Did you read it?
No. I threw it away.
I heard your little fingers
peel back the wrapper.
Though. As I've witnessed.
Your ears are far superior to mine.
It's American for "I'm sorry. "
Did you steal it from the hotel lobby?
That is an outrageous accusation.
Okay. Yeah. I did.
Okay. Everything except the last thing.
You're right. I'm sorry.
At least let me give you a day
you'll never forget?
All right. I promised you a day
you're never gonna forget.
- And that's what you're gonna get.
- And your presentation?
I'm procrastinating.
Actually. I was hoping
you'd be my inspiration.
Wow!
Now. Anything catches your eye.
Just take a picture.
Okay.
Pretty woman, walking down the street
Pretty woman, the kind I like to meet
Pretty woman
I don't believe you, you're not the truth
No one could look as good as you
Mercy
Pretty woman...
I don't know.
Like hold the crab.
You need to get over your crab fear.
Nibbling.
Pretty woman
That you look lovely as can be
Are you lonely just like me?
Oh, oh, pretty woman
So. In India do your parents pick out
who you're gonna marry?
Look at that.
Yeah. In a way.
Well. Probably cuts down
on a lot of bad dates.
- And a lot of good ones.
- That's true.
But. You know.
People learn that love grows.
It's not like a rose
already blooming in a flower shop.
Well. What if you get
one of those plants that.
You know. You take home.
And after like two days. It just dies?
Better luck next life.
Look at you.
Probably find Priya under Granger.
I mean. You know. The chances of you
finding your name are basically
the same as finding mine...
I'm gonna shut up now.
- So. Mr. Cook...
- Yeah.
What about dinner somewhere different?
- I'm game.
- Yeah?
Better.
This is great.
Thank you.
I should tell you that
- I've never had Indian before.
- I know.
But I'm glad
you're trying out something new.
So just dig in. Don't even think about it.
You might just love it.
- Not bad.
- See?
You know. If you ever
wanna impress an Indian family.
You should tell about the things
you really love.
You know. Family. Education.
Food. Marriage. You know. Stuff like that.
So. Your parents putting pressure on you
to get married?
I'll marry someday. You know.
Mmm.
- Let me try.
- No. Leave that!
It's really spicy.
It's very spicy.
- Some more?
- No.
Mmm-hmm. Mmm...
I'm fine.
- Has your tongue cooled down?
- What tongue?
How will you make your little jokes now?
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Are you being sassy?
You've been here. What. Three days.
And you've already picked up sass?
Couldn't you just take home a magnet
or a T-shirt?
- I always wanted to swim in the ocean.
- What? No. No. No.
You go for it. But I have to warn you. It's...
- It's kind of cold.
- It is not!
Easy.
- Okay. Come on.
- No. No. I'm not going.
- Are you scared?
- Yeah. I'm scared.
- You are?
- There's sharks in there.
Oh. Yeah? I'm a shark then.
It's all I wanna do
Give you the strength to hold on
When we are apart
I give to you my heart
I've had a really great night.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Because of who you are
You're beautiful
You're beautiful to me
Yeah
You're beautiful
You're beautiful to me
If you could live your life any way.
What would you want?
Like any way.
What would I want?
Mmm-hmm.
You mean besides a dance by the water
with a beautiful woman?
All right.
You still have to answer my question.
I was hoping I could charm my way
out of answering.
Okay. Give me a second.
I guess I don't wanna die a failure.
What do you mean?
That I didn't try hard enough
or something.
Like with my job. You know.
I want to be the best at what I do.
The scary part is putting yourself
and your ideas out there.
What if you crash and burn?
Isn't it worth it?
Deep down I guess I'm afraid
it won't work out.
What about you?
Did you always want to be a nurse?
No. I...
I guess I want to do things
that make people happy.
Well. Maybe you should do something
that makes you happy.
Turn left. Turn left.
Left. Left. Left. Left.
PIMMl: Right! Right! Right. Right.
Right. Right.
No. I don't think so.
Bye. Girls.
All you told me to get into this right
and now we're stuck in one-way street.
Ji, you were driving straight
on that crooked street.
Achha, listen. Why don't we ask
one of these nice gentlemen to help us?
- Excuse me. Excuse me.
- PIMMl: Can you help us please?
Excuse me. Could you please tell me
where is this Hawksin Hotel?
- Hi. Handsome.
- Okay. Handsome.
Can I interest you in some group sex?
- PIMMl: What?
- No. No. No. No. Don't. Don't...
Hawksin Street. Where is that?
Excuse me. We just wanted to know
where is the... No. No. No. No.
We don't like that. No. No.
Come on. Let's go party.
- Driving. Driving.
- PIMMl: Let's go!
Excuse me.
I was wondering if you've seen a girl.
Age 23. height is... How much?
- Very pretty.
Very pretty.
And she was seen here in your hotel
with a gentleman.
And I think the meeting was quite explicit.
I'm sorry. Sir. But I can't comment
on the activities of any of our guests.
Excuse me. Did you say you were looking
for a young Indian girl?
Yes! Yes. Yes. Yes.
I think I know the girl. I should.
I gave her a hotel room last night.
Pretty girl.
No. I'm saying good-looking kid.
Oh. My God!
Wait a minute.
Is this about me paying for it?
'Cause I'll be honest with you.
I do it all the time.
You are the one who has
kidnapped my daughter!
Hey. Kidnapped? Take it easy.
Buddy. She wanted it.
- She liked it.
- Yeah.
Is she with you?
No. No. No. I was with her last night.
Tonight she's probably with a guy I know.
Maybe two. He's got a partner.
- Where is my daughter?
- Hey. Hey!
Where's my daughter?
- You wanna call somebody?
- Leave me!
- No. ji!
No!
This is outrageous!
Well. Thank you for a very memorable
and very wet evening.
- I had fun today.
- Me. Too.
Good night.
Unless. You know. You want to
grab a drink.
Do you know they charge $8 for a cola?
Oh. Uh...
I need to get out of these wet clothes.
In my room.
With me.
Good night.
Night.
Zia, I called you at work today,
but you were not there.
I just want to let you know
that I think I am in love.
And I don't wanna marry Vikram.
Something could happen with Granger.
I have to go to my cousin's party today.
But then I will tell him about Vikram.
So. What's going on
with you two. Anyway?
Nothing.
She's going back to India on Monday.
- And. What. You go back to Emory?
- I don't know.
You know.
Emory. She looks good on paper.
I just never really felt it with Emory.
You know?
No.
Thanks for driving me.
Well. Palo Alto is pretty far. I don't know
how else you were gonna get there.
No. I wanted to.
So. Do you have to leave tomorrow?
I mean. I know we just met
and this probably sounds crazy.
But maybe you could stay longer.
You know. I just got my presentation
but after that...
For how long do you want me to stay?
I don't know.
I didn't really think about it.
Uh...
- This is the exit.
- Okay.
So...
Which way do you wanna go?
I don't know.
Okay. Well. You've got a 50-50 shot.
Right or left?
I'm sorry. Right. No. I mean. Go left. Left.
Left it is.
- Granger...
- Yeah?
- It's the second house on the right.
- Oh. Okay.
I would invite you inside.
But I have a rather crazy family.
Who doesn't?
So. Are you gonna need a ride back?
Um...
I'll see what's going on inside.
I need to spend some quality time
with my family.
And I'll call your cell
once the quality is over.
- Hey. Don't you want my number?
- I have it.
I don't ever remember
giving you my cell phone.
Yeah. Right. I don't have it. I guess
I was thinking about somebody else.
Uh...
I'll call you at the hotel. Yeah?
- So. I'll see you after your thing?
- Yeah.
Call me.
- Bye.
You did not just say that. "Call me?"
Auntie.
- Priya!
- Happy birthday!
- Thank you.
- Hi.
Do you remember me?
Come. Let me show you around.
You must eat something.
Pretty girl like you. Your future husband
could have something to grab on.
Yeah. Auntie.
I heard you're doing very well.
Working for a big American company.
- Your family must be very proud of you.
- I think so.
Priya!
Hello?
Hi. I'm Granger. Nice to meet you.
It's so nice. Papa.
That you've come for the party.
Not another lie.
Hi. How are you?
Hello. Hello.
Granger Woodruff.
I know why you are here
and it's certainly not for the family.
Now where is the man
you've eloped with. Huh?
- What?
- Ji, ji, I think that is him.
Priya. You left this in my car.
I don't want you
to address my daughter. Okay?
Papa.
Mr. Sethi. Granger Woodruff.
Pleasure to meet you. Sir.
What pleasure? Where is the pleasure?
Granger. Thanks for the present.
Can I talk to you later. Please?
No.
I want to know what you told my daughter
to lure her to America.
- What? What's your father talking about?
- Can we go to your car?
You thought you will bring
an innocent girl here
and I will not find you?
Sir. Sir. I just met your daughter
a few days ago.
I'm not trying to lure her anywhere.
- You are her customer.
- Papa...
I mean. For the credit card company.
Don't you lie to us. Zia told us everything.
Thank God.
Vikram's family does not know anything.
Otherwise. You know
what could have happened.
Credit card company?
Yes. That horrible job
which makes her work the whole night
pretending to be an Americano.
Are you discussing Priya's job?
She does a fantastic American accent.
Come on. Do your Streisand voice.
It's just terrific.
I'm sure your fiance must enjoy it.
You're engaged?
Oh. No. No. No. No.
He's not asking as a jealous boyfriend.
He's asking merely
as a polite conversation starter.
Priya!
Priya! Where are you going?
Look. I'm not going anywhere
until you tell me what the hell is going on.
Granger. Not here. Please. Come.
You wanna tell me
who you really are?
I'm Priya Sethi. I live in Mumbai.
Just like I told you.
And who else are you?
I'm Jennifer David
from CITYone Bank Business Processes.
Say something else. Say something else.
I'll be happy to assist you
in increasing your credit limit.
If you wouldn't mind
answering a few questions.
Okay. All right. I got it.
I'm sorry.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I was going to.
I didn't think you'd like the real me.
You're engaged. Is that how they celebrate
in your country?
I don't love him. I...
I'm sorry I didn't tell you everything.
I pretend for my job.
But the truth is everything else
I've told you.
I don't know what to believe.
You know what? Forget it.
Yeah. I've known you
for. What. A few days?
Let's not blow this thing out of proportion.
It was fun. Let's just leave it at that.
Granger. Please...
Damn it!
Stay away
from my daughter. Okay?
Who is that guy?
Oh. My God.
I always imagined Indian parties
to be peaceful affairs.
You know. Gandhi-esque. Incense
and Kama Sutra.
Never have expectations.
- You know what your deal is?
- No. What's my deal?
You never totally put yourself out there.
You round the corners and you play it safe.
You never let people
see who you really are.
But you're selling yourself short. Man.
Tired of watching you do that.
If you want big rewards.
You have to take the big risks.
But you're afraid.
So you wind up with nothing.
Wow! This girl really took you out.
So what? I'm just supposed to tell her
to leave her fiance
and move to America to be with me?
I don't even know
if I'm gonna have a job next week.
She pretended to be someone she wasn't.
Maybe that's who she needed to be
to have her big adventure.
Haven't you ever pretended to be someone
you're not. Granger?
For the last 37 years
at Hawksin Hotels. It's been our passion...
- Happy birthday.
- Emory? What are you doing here?
Well. I came to wish you a happy birthday.
Well. It's not my birthday.
And I thought we broke up.
I forgive you.
- Good luck. Priya.
- Thank you.
Emory. I...
Em... Em. Em. I can't do this. Okay?
I'm here for work.
I don't have time for this.
Okay. Whatever. You know.
It's actually probably for the best.
Since I wouldn't want
to remember us both naked when I do it.
- Do what?
- Propose. You jerk.
What?
- You're joking. Right?
- No. And that better not be your answer.
I just thought. You know.
We were seeing other people.
- You know. Mark Bailey. Private jets.
- Let's review. Sweetie. Okay?
We are both good-looking.
We both went to Ivy League schools.
The sex is amazing.
You make it sound like a merger.
You're never going to find anyone
better than me. And you know it.
Em. Em...
Priya.
Before you close your door. Please...
I know I should have had told you
I was engaged. I'm sorry.
But the truth is.
Maybe I did come all the way
wanting a romantic moment
with someone I've never met
because maybe I was running away
from my life.
And then I met you. My feet stayed still.
Maybe they floated a little.
I couldn't leave tomorrow
without you knowing how I feel.
- And I hope that maybe you've...
- Grange?
Is my fiance bugging you for towels again?
- It's not...
- Necessary.
Oh. And we're not going
to need turndown service later
because. Well.
We're just going to mess it up.
Just give me a minute. Em.
Hey!
You don't need to explain it to the maid.
It's a hotel. For gosh sake!
- Look. I'm...
- That's right.
I should have looked.
Then I'd have seen what a hypocrite...
That's the English word. Right?
Someone like you.
You're going back to India to your fiance.
What do you want me to do?
You'll like this one.
So these two lawyers go to heaven.
And they meet Saint Peter...
You guys heard of Saint Peter?
Let's just walk around
the man in the towel.
Which reminds me.
Those are the 300 count cotton towels.
Egyptian cotton. Too. I think it's the best.
At Hawksin Hotels
we help you to be who you need to be,
so you can be who you really want to be.
Hawksin Hotels.
For 80 years we've had just one passion,
doing nice things for nice people,
nice people like you.
So what do you think. Mr. Hawksin?
I loved it.
- Welcome to the Hawksin family. Boys.
- Yes!
- Thank you very much. Sir.
- "Nice people like you. "
- I like that. It's a good touch.
- Thank you. I got it...
What is the meaning of all this?
- You're home so soon?
- Wow. Full on rager.
Who told you you could have a party?
And what are you celebrating?
Ow!
That's it. My children are hooligans.
I've done nothing right.
Just go to weeds.
Oh. No. Please. Please. Please. One minute.
He is probably following
the example of his sister
to see who can humiliate the family more.
He with the party or she who ran away
to America with some stranger.
Definitely the one who ran away.
- Nothing happened.
- Nothing happened?
You spent all your money
just to go to America?
Thank God. The only blessed thing
that has happened
the Bhatias have not found out.
Oh. By the way.
Mr. Bhatia had left a message.
He found out what happened
from Uncle Sawant.
Dad. Dad.
- Ji, ji, ji, ji, you're going to have a stroke.
Tomorrow. You're going to Bhatia's place.
Kiss their feet
and apologize
for what you have done. Okay?
And beg forgiveness with the hope
that they let this marriage take place.
- What if...
- Not. What if. Anything.
The only thing you're supposed to see
is to obey your father and most probably
that future husband of yours.
Now go to your room.
- Papa.
- What?
Please try to understand.
I don't want to marry Vikram.
Papa. Vikram is a perfectly nice boy.
It's just. I know he won't make me happy.
What? What did she say? Happy?
You think I was happy
when I met your mother?
I mean...
But now. Just look at us.
We have grown to be happy.
Till our children came to make us crazy.
So don't you talk to me
about being happy.
All my life I've been thinking
about making other people happy.
Now. I need to know what makes me
happy. Not you. You or Vikram.
What is this me. Me. Me?
Crazy American talk!
Okay. Okay. Priya.
You see. You are part of a family.
And you are not entitled to hog
all the happiness just for yourself.
There are other people in this family
who also want to be happy.
But what you've done all this time?
Just break our hearts.
- Ji, ji, ji...
- No. No...
Ji, you're not feeling well.
I'll talk to her. Huh?
Priya...
Look. Priya.
This marriage is not just about you.
It is for us.
This will help our family. beta.
Look at your father.
See how hard he works.
This is important. Priya. Huh?
Family's important. beta.
It is who will always
be there for you. Huh?
This is the air I breathe
- Knock. Knock. Hi.
- Hey.
Look. I know we haven't had a
chance to talk. Really. Since San Francisco.
You know. I wanted to tell you that if
the wedding stuff is too much for you.
Let's just celebrate
your new account. Okay?
Look. It's your favorite.
- It's not working.
- What. Did you lose the account?
Right.
Okay.
Once again. And make it sound
this time like you mean it.
- I'm terribly sorry.
- Louder. louder.
I'm terribly sorry. Uncle. Auntie.
I've gotten everything out of my system.
And I assure you
I'm ready to be a devoted...
Devoted wife and mother.
I'm ready to devote myself to...
Come on.
I'm ready to devote myself to my job
and finding things that make me happy.
'Cause I lied. I haven't gotten
everything out of my system.
What system?
She's too young to have a system.
She's nervous.
She's embarrassed and she's afraid
because she thinks that
you will not accept her apology.
Isn't that right. Priya. Huh?
I'm sorry. Vikram is a lovely person.
And I know. Vikram. You'll find someone
who'll make you happy.
But I don't believe it's me.
I know I'm disappointing you.
It's just. Something happened
when I was gone.
I jumped in the ocean.
I got sick eating chocolates.
I just fell in love.
Is this man here with you?
No. Vikram. It's just...
I realize I need something else.
I told you they're all mad as hatters.
Didn't I? Didn't I?
How dare you do this to our son?
- It's not enough that you...
- Now. That is okay.
We have a whole file full of girls in there.
And I really always wanted to
meet Lavina from Gwalior.
No. It's not all right. Vikram.
It's not all right.
This little tramp runs off to America.
Then stands here and breaks your heart...
She's not a tramp! She's not a tramp.
She's a dreamer.
Her ideas are modern.
Yes. Sometimes she's stubborn and willful.
But when she walks into a room.
People smile.
When she talks. People listen.
She's wise. She's kind.
And most importantly. She's my daughter.
And I love her.
Papa.
Thank you.
This is the air I breathe
Hello, everyone. I'm Priya Sethi.
I'm also known as Jennifer David.
I've recently taken over from Miss Prasad
who was promoted to Regional Manager.
So, I welcome you all to
CITYone Business Processes.
As you all know, you'll be spending
12 hours of your day
as an American.
You'll have an American name,
an American city of residence,
but it's very important to remember
that you're not an American.
You're an Indian
and your American identity is simply there
to make it easier for you to communicate
with the person
at the other end of the line.
But you must leave it at your desk
the moment you take off the headset.
I'm desperate for you
Excuse me. Everybody. It's time
for the customary best man speech.
When Charlie and I were 14.
We went to Camp Whichiwawa
And being the mischievous
little fellows that we were.
One night we decided to
sneak across to the girls' cabins.
Now. The only way to get over to Camp
Whichiwuwu was over this little river.
Now. To the 14-year-old me. In the middle
of the night. It looked like the Mississippi.
You know. So I say to Charlie.
I say. "Dude. I'm not going in there.
"It's probably full of snakes and eels
and crocodiles. "
And by the time I'd finished
listing all my reasons.
Chucky boy here was already
on the other side.
I chickened out
and went back to the cabins.
But Charlie here.
He forged ahead to the girls' cabins
and he met a young lady that night.
Believe it or not.
A young lady named Karen Miller.
Now. When Charlie got back to the bunks.
He says to me. He says.
"Dude. Dude. I just met the girl
I'm gonna marry. "
Flash forward 10 years later. Charlie and I
are at a barbeque at Massapequa or
Quitipeak or Quahog or somewhere.
Then he sees her across the room.
Now. Charlie was on a date that night.
But he left her just like he left me
on the other side of that river
10 years earlier.
And me being the voice of reason.
I say to Charlie. I say. "You can't leave. "
And he turns to me and
he says something I'll never forget.
He says. "Nothing should ever hold a man
back from his future. "
Nothing should ever hold a man
back from his future.
So. To my best friend. Charlie.
Who wasn't afraid to cross the river.
And to Karen.
Who was waiting for him on the other...
I gotta go.
Taxi! Hey!
How're you doing?
Airport. As fast as you can.
Hear me out, don't tear away
'Cause this is what I'm trying to say
Hey. Hey. Would you mind stepping on it?
I got to get to the airport in 40 minutes.
Hey. Dude. I'm trying to go as fast as I can.
Okay. Thank you. Okay. Thanks.
Very important.
- Appreciate it.
- Sure.
Hi. Hi. Yes.
I need information for Mumbai. India.
Yeah. I can hold.
Yes. Yes. I'm here. I'm looking for the
address to CITYone Bank Headquarters.
C- I-T-I. Yes. Yes.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Slow down.
I can't understand you. I...
- Hold. Hold on. Please.
- Come on!
- Excuse me. Hey. Buddy...
- What?
Would you mind translating
for me. Please?
Okay. Just because I'm brown and driving
a taxi doesn't mean I can speak Indian.
No. No. No. No. No. No. I didn't mean that.
Dude. I'm playing. I'm playing with you.
Give me the phone.
- Thanks. Man. Thank you.
- It's all right.
CITYone Bank address. Headquarters.
Mumbai.
I can write down. I have a pen.
I can't see your face
You're calling out my name
I can hear you calling out my name
Hey. Watch it.
I can't see your face
But you're calling out my name
And all this time you let me run
Look how fast time has gone
Looking back at what we had
Hey. Buddy. Can't this thing go any faster?
Can your cab go any faster?
Stop and let me out.
CITYone Bank.
I'd be glad to help you with that.
For security purposes. Could you please
give me the last four digits of your social...
No. You listen to me.
No. Sir. You listen to me.
Just listen here. Jack.
You better pay up or else...
He hung up on me.
Balveer. You must always remember.
They are your customers.
So. Do not let things get personal.
This is a business. Right?
And your job is to be professional.
Calm and helpful.
But we must get the money.
How can we let these obnoxious
Americans talk to us like this?
What happens if the obnoxious American
is also a complete idiot?
And he's sorry it took him so long
to realize what a mistake he made.
How did you...
Well. I had to body check an old lady.
Employ a taxi cab translator. Don't ask.
Fly 18 hours.
Hijack a tuk-tuk.
And bribe a street gypsy.
And I did it all in this monkey suit.
I kind of feel like James Bond.
Only I probably don't
smell as good as he does.
- I think you smell great.
- Thanks.
I couldn't get married.
Well. It's a pretty big deal.
Sort of like a platinum card.
Once you make that commitment.
You really have to see it through.
But I think I'd like that.
Kiss him. Kiss him.
You sure
this is such a good idea?
Don't worry. It'll be good.
Best of luck.
Sir. Before you take a swing.
There's something I want to read to you.
Try English. Boy. You're hurting my ears.
I just wanted you to know that I have the
utmost respect for you and your family.
And I promise to treat your daughter with
all the love and respect she deserves.
You like alu parathas?
Let's give him alu parathas.
Sit. Sit.
Wise men say
Only fools rush in
But I can't help
Falling in love with you
Shall I stay
Would it be a sin?
If I can't help
Falling in love with you
Like a river flows
Surely to the sea
Darling, so it goes
Some things are meant to be
Take my hand
Take my whole life, too
For I can't help
Falling in love with you
Like a river flows
Surely to the sea
Darling, so it goes
Some things are meant to be
Take my hand
Take my whole life, too
For I can't help
Falling in love with you
Oh, I can't help
Falling in love
With
You