Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
EDiT BY
~ GYPTiAN ~
SEPTiCEMiA TEAM
=- www.Subs4U.gr-=
i David, is Hello you Chat give birth
Want you happy birthday.
i I Feel have not gotten
The coupons.
I will call i next week
Maybe can go out together.
Okey that you have >, i a happy one
Birthday...
i Is a big doctor.
We go, we go.
i they Think that he remains
The ache.
i Talk with my second
Wife.
i Had 19, was a model.
i Was a winner.
i Rocking in a tree.
i Had wounds in his eyes, bosoms
And belly.
I am possible i see nowadays.
i Had 30 marks.
i And fever the three last
Days.
i My second wife, was thin.
i did Not know that it was
As injured.
i If there state were to that
Cart today front.
i Instead Of that man.
i Had been I.
i By a moment I felt
His ache of mine.
i Had as 50.
You pressure  i they are strange.
Secrets, when you are guilty
The time and his rules make you innocent.
Memory what I pass.
Memory what we did.
i I Am close to the 50 now.
i I Make three big in
The street Wall.
Two i marriages
Without children.
One i joins.
i A department in the city.
i My current wife does not know it
That I pass years ago.
i Not how tell it to them.
i Why him I would do?
i Not At All in my life was
Either for the summer of 1958.
i When Ruth, Tony and Willis.
i And all the other ones
They did him love.
i To his sister.
Which searches?
Crabs.
Can I see?
I am Meg.
I am David.
They are real.
He caught them and then
The aftertastes go.
Do they bite?
Not, if you touch them well.
¿You had never seen
A crab suedes?
Them there are not in the city
Of New York.
I like them now.
They do not hurt you.
Them caress.
They do not, eat them.
Here also they eat them.
In some places
They are easy, they float.
This one does not see I eat
To eat.
We are going to look for one big one.
Can I look?
Insurance.
What is that?
My family, we had an accident.
I do not have any.
I want to say, you mark.
You have not had any.
None.
I have one.
One big.
I did it.
Boys are good.
Some times one
They kill enter if.
The shootings of new.
Insurance, I always do it.
I have to come back.
The first went
See the outskirts.
That is to say, never suedes
We saw a forest.
Gracias David
It was amusing.
He hears ¿, where you live?
I live with my cousins
The Tenders.
The Tenders
We are neighbour.
Us we see David.
LA VECINA b  i.  /  i
Based on a story b  i
True.  /  i
A day more with my sisters
And I swear you that I become crazy.
David, you give me a hand.
- Hola Woofer.
- Hola David.
What do you have the can?
One beautiful earthworms.
Is Tony round here?
If.
They eat it.
It is sickly.
The crotchets do it also.
I pick them up and I put them here.
And they do the same to that
End.
The correct answer
He is when.
When there is rain
It is well.
Us we see Woofer.
The entry is free.
Hear boys
I am I.
Boys ¿, they are there?
- Te atrapé.
- No es gracioso.
Your he catches if it was.
He hears, give me a hand.
We go, who arrives.
Bored.
Stupit.
And her?
Who?
Your cousin, I was ho
In the rocks.
He tried to catch crab.
If, she is very fantastic.
Your also ¿, it is not like that?
You are his cousin
More young man.
It is the second bonus
Of my mom.
That does not do any
Difference.
He is of that way.
He does not play anything.
He had a lesion in
A cart accident.
So he had to be one
With us.
- Si.
He looks, the two parents died also.
My mother says that
He died instantaneously.
Mom says that the
Girls did not hurt themselves.
Besides that, the ache he incremented.
Anyway
That is what they have.
Mom says Meg
I wanted it.
She says that Meg is easy.
What do they do here?
What does the cart have?
Him they were going to arrange this
Tomorrow.
I believe that he will arrange it.
He comes the summer now
And there is not anything that to do.
OH, look at the stupit one
Of David.
Keep quiet the mouth suedes
Of which you silence her.
Mom does not know where you go
He says that you must.
Put it to them by the backside.
Him he goes you really to
Put, him I go one to saying.
Tell, it and I will tell him what Cheryl
Him he did to your vagina the other night.
- Hola chicos.
- Hola Willis.
You had a good time with Denise.
Silence you, silly, silly.
Mom ordered me.
He said that he had to
Be your nursemaid.
Boys go, we look
True action.
They is vacations, because
We are not going to play a game.
Insurance that can not see anything.
He can not see a shit.
So we are going to run.
We go, do it.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7;8;9;10.
11,12,13,14,15,16,17;18;19;20.
21,22;23;24;25.
Erick, tab
One you are that.
Keep quiet the mouth.
21,22,23,24;25;16;27.
28,29,30,31,32;33;34;35.
36,37;38;39;40.
i That is.
Dog, dog.
OH shit.
He runs Kenny.
I grasped you.
- De ninguna manera.
- No.
He has to confess.
Alone one will, play, the rest will look.
I will be the first one.
I gave the truth now.
¿You have kissed sometimes
To a boy?
Not, but you if.
A pleasure will be to play with you.
What did they do?
Lie.
¿You have sometimes
Suckled new?
Big and long.
He has put it to you
In your vagina.
Do not, hold
I will tell it daddy.
What is he?
These friends are
Very rough.
Hello Meg.
Hello David.
It is high.
It is beautiful.
Do you want to set up you?
That is to say, if you want go with me.
He gives me fear also.
It does not matter me.
Insurance.
We go.
I sit down as flying
I can see all from here.
My parents.
They must be today in some
I besiege as east today.
They must be well
That I believe.
I listened to what I pass.
I establish it.
David, this is wonderful.
You are seen proud.
You say it seriously.
Insurance.
I have more coupons if
You want to return again.
I would like me.
But I have to come back
Early, home.
We can play some times.
OH if, it seemed impressive to me
I want to play again.
I say to them, something was missing for that one
Moment, I was a little movement.
That that is mom?
That movement, already you taste
That swaying.
He is when the girl dances
Around.
I eat at the shows.
When his age had
I had both.
Once I saw to one
Man with three arms.
There are not those things.
Do not contradict your mother
I saw it.
I saw a man with
Three arms.
One, I was something child
That went out of here.
¿Which más?
Which more do you dress?
Things in bottles.
Without being born.
You sew drunkards, everything
Type of things.
I tell them to him, the carnival was something
Impressive when era one girl.
- Dinos de esos movimientos.
- Si, aunque lo creo.
Am what assumes one?
I told them to him, they are dance
Of girls.
Some I was of nude.
With a small support.
Maybe I had some rubies.
With red circles
Painted here.
And here.
¿What boys think
Of that?
Good, something like that one was not
Head the community.
Not of these boys.
But they like it.
Devil, I liked me also.
The devil is wild.
Finish his beers
Boys.
It is time of going.
I do not want me to lose it
Tonight.
I am going to take these
Boys to the fair.
Remain and he take cares of to your sister.
And you do not approach to
The ice creams.
You are going to be fattening.
Especially if you go him
To dance someone.
If, I listened to this.
Maybe her see in Playboy.
If you read it in Playboy
And you you catch each page.
Very well.
I do it every month.
I listened what
They say one he feels.
If, I also.
You never join breasts before
Sight.
This is of death.
That are bigger
Jill Wickinson.
Bigger than Willis.
Where is Tony?
Mom said that it would not go out
Until I finish having dinner.
¿They have seen sometimes
A woman?
That is to say, a truth woman.
To Meg he undresses.
Do you see something?
I do not see a damn thing.
Wait, wait, there he is.
Dog.
I hate you.
Jódela.
He hears, maybe can
Make me to play.
i Complained insects.
I will kill them.
I will do east.
The boys can look
And you will do the rest, okey.
Holy Sky.
Go one bigger.
Okey, take this.
And they remember, quiet a yard.
And do not go inside of the forest.
Woofer, will take care of them.
I do not want.
Apology.
You offend me, fondness.
I by myself not do not, want
Good, you you remain.
What boys have
It is a feminism lesson.
Brandish Meg.
You understand like a girl
He grows soft ¿, it is not true?
And Meg, is a miss.
I am sure that it is.
¿You believe that I am not
A lady?
No, himself
Do not say me a word.
Because I do not need that class
Of a girl's insinuation.
That can not have
The expensive clean.
You now, go down.
And he helps your sister
With the wash.
And when you finish.
I have something more
For you.
My boys can handle it.
So we go, boys.
A hamburger and
A cold lemonade.
- David.
- Hola Meg, ¿cómo te va?
David ¿, you could buy
uno?, I have not eaten at two days.
Other Deme
Please.
Why have not you eaten?
I can not.
How is that?
I must do it.
I do not understand you.
He puts him garbage.
We go.
He jokes with you.
Not, David not you are good
She hates me.
All them.
Thanks.
¿Why you did not come
The other day?
I do not understand that why.
Maybe, I was in a bad mood.
It is not accustomed
To have girls around.
It is not alone that time.
It is all the time.
Nothing as what I act
It is well.
I think of what I had only.
When arriving here, I broke it.
I painted.
Paint the water.
That did not assume one
Not him I followed but.
My mother liked me.
I have treated but not
I can paint more.
Because one he will, say it
What he will think.
With alone look at me.
Him will tell stupit me that I am
And as I waste the time.
Your you know that it is not like that.
We go, because you do not try it.
Because not you try
Paint.
I bet that you will like it.
Not I could, not
Honestly.
¿What of it what there is
With me?
Would you really like me?
Sure, I would like me
Enough.
Okey.
I will, do it David.
And thanks.
David, by everything.
Of nothing.
I do not love you them
Outskirts, you have to come back.
It is better than you do it
Now.
If, lady.
To your room.
Saint Cielo, you can not
Do this.
Stupit, shit.
Eaten David, is
On the table.
Cielo, give me that.
That is going to put to work
Your mind.
- Hola Querida.
- Buenas tardes, Sra. Moran.
I am Meg.
It is a pleasure by
End know you.
Do you want bring in to and eat something?
Actually I can not.
I stopped to give
This to David.
Thanks, Meg.
It is something stupit one.
You can throw it
If you do not like it.
We either ¡, what we have here!
Good, he is really good.
She is slightly fantastic.
It is charming
Have her round here.
Come.
You must be David.
If, hello Susan.
Meg says that you are
Nice.
What do you have there?
What is not you
You want.
I have something for Ud.
He puts the TV out.
What is David?
It is a present.
Of Meg.
The spotted stops Ud.
David.
Meg, is beautiful.
You do not mention me.
She painted this give birth
You, David.
He did not do it.
You see this, he is a boy
In the river.
By supposition that is
For you.
Take it
I do not want it.
It was for you, Ruth really.
- Ella quería...
- David, no.
Learn the lesson
Boys.
And they listen very well.
This is important.
All what they have
That to do.
He is kind being with the woman and
She will make it by you all.
You see to David here, he is
Kind with her, thereby he painted it.
That is what you received
Is not David true?
That is to say, it is all him
That you have received.
Ruth go.
One that you are small, but in
These days you never know.
The day girls
They are very easy.
That one is the problem.
Him you promise something small one and
You will have all what you want.
Believe me.
One about what I talk.
David looks at your father.
One has caught many
Women in this village.
All the world knows that
Your mother knows it.
Not you of shame.
He is a big and decent worker
That fights for his family.
Devils, that is what
It happens to one when he gets married.
I thought that I was going to be rich.
And that one was my fault when
I was young.
And he was enough
Rich.
He looks at what I have now.
Some adorable bastards
In the nothing middle.
You believe that I am silly.
You believe that it is easy.
Guevones.
I want to go to the point.
You are going to return to him
This painting.
One him you did that to him
To David.
And do not try to say me
Slightly different.
What I want to know
Megan.
¿What you intend to receive
By this?
Everyone here know that
David is a good boy, but.
He does not go to give anything.
So I wait that this
Painting that you have given him.
Because you have not come
Here, himself to practice the art.
You give to the boys what
They want now.
And you do not receive nothing, fondness.
Do you know what he means?
You, Susan, clear that not
You are very young.
Good them I will say one.
That is someone who opens his
Legs to a man.
So he can
Arrive inside.
And everything by something.
Anyone can do it.
I am sure that any
In this village he agrees.
By myself I advise it to you
Fondness.
If I see someone by
The house outskirts.
I will get out your backside
Of that empty room.
Now ¿, who wants
A beer?
i I advised it to You yesterday.
I said  i that not the
You did and you did it.
i See you to your room, it does not matter me
What your mother told you.
i you are Not going to pass the time
With boys.
i you Lie, by yourself you lie.
Do not forget your sister.
Behave well.
That is, it happens all day
There, contained.
Good night, girls
Sweet sleeps.
Tab, tab.
Tab.
Come, he looks.
- Sus secretos.
- Déjenme en paz.
- Déjame.
- ¿Qué coño te pasa?, perra.
How do you stick him so?
You saw what he did.
He did not do anything.
He looks at what you did
You broke him your face.
I will say to mom.
I will not play with Uds.
More more.
You are a dog.
Your sister is a dog.
Someone can say me
What it happens here.
- Le pegó a Woofer.
- Si.
The face crossed him.
Good, someone had to
Provoke her.
We played, he was everything
She him gave by the face.
You also David?
What?
Him did you stick to Megan also?
I by myself did not, arrive.
Y...
I am not denouncing, fondness
I ask you a simple question.
Then ¿, where he is her now?
He is, not, he went.
Susan ¿, what dresses
It happen here?
And you tried to arrest her
So I did not hurt it.
I could not.
You must try
I want to say.
She is your sister
After all.
You know.
What he means.
Be combined with
Someone.
That does something like that one.
Good, that means that
You are guilty also.
Though there are not event
Something in particular.
But him you facilitated to
Your fellow do it.
You understand what I tell you.
Let me be clearer.
You love your sister ¿, certain?
Because you love her him
You forgive like that ¿, certain something?
She did not want to hurt it.
Of course.
- Ella no lo quiso.
- Claro que si.
You forgive her, then
Is that true?
Good, you see it now
You are wrong fondness.
That is to put in
Combination with her.
What she did
It was bad.
It is a bad behavior.
And you forgive her by yourself
Because you love her.
That neither is correct.
I want you to put to bed you
Of this bed side.
Lift the dressed one and
Get out your pantyhose.
We go, do it now.
Do not make me to be rough.
Disobedience
That one is other thing.
I will give you five by
Each one.
10 by Meg.
And other five by disobeying me.
That they are 20, hear, hear.
Boys, are here.
The girls always cry.
There is not anything that can
Do to the concerning.
And this is by his good and
Everyone has to be part thereof.
One; two; three; four.
Do not dare to touch her
Do not go one very excited
When your sister he is
...de resbalosa por los
Outskirts.
Megan is not true.
People has to show
To his way.
This is nothing, fondness.
Tab, tab
Please.
He deserves still more.
We go, give me that ring.
I did not, belong to my mother.
Your mother is dead.
And you live at my home
I do the rules.
Give me the damn ring.
- No.
- Dame el anillo.
I have to go.
David, this small disaster
It is between us.
That is to say, you saw what you saw.
But it is not problem
Of nobody.
You understand it.
Hello boys
Which do they love?
Rum it happens.
Here you have it.
Of chocolate.
Chocolate.
Okey, grace boys.
i Then ¿, until what hour it will be?
I create the eight that even.
Hello David.
Sit down
Join you.
Donny, brings a pair of
Beers.
Very, either, very.
You brought the police
To my mother.
Suit, you Willis.
I told you to sit down.
All what I want to know
What you think is Megan.
What do you have mind?
¿You think that really
You will go of here?
You and Susan.
They would go out of here.
Good, I will, say you
That it is not going to happen.
You will not go to no part.
Because neither them
He matters.
It is like that.
What most deficient?
What do you have mind?
Maybe you are scared
Of him.
The problem is.
What we will do now.
There is not anything in that man.
Or any man
That I am frightened.
If you did not know it I wait before
That he knows it now.
But I can not leave that
You go all the time to the police.
So the question is.
Now what?
I would send you to any
I besiege if him I had.
What I do not need is one
Small whore by the outskirts.
God I would not forgive it to me
If I do not correct you it.
I believe that we can
Do something.
See you to your room.
I wanted to say
All Uds.
Also you, David.
I establish it.
But I have something
Hardly that to do.
¿You want a beer
He stops the path?
- No, gracias.
- Toma.
Do not tell your father
Who gave it to you.
Thanks, Ruth.
Until the bottom.
- ¿No lo has vuelto a pensar?
- ¿Sobre qué?
Do it to them.
Not, curse.
I not do not, consider it David.
We always do it.
I not do not, want.
It is your last decision.
Correct.
I do not see the big thing
I have done it suedes.
Not the same is not, that before
You know it well perfectly.
- Es algo serio.
- No veo lo grande.
What is the big?
He wants to sleep other
Time over there.
¿Dónde?
With the neighbours?
If.
Then, let it.
You do not pass it by
The outskirts.
But there are two youngsters
That live over there.
And?
Are you not made.
To the devil with them.
That I go.
- Gracias papá.
- De nada.
Hello David.
Either, now everybody
We are here.
The game is that her
He has to count us.
Okey ¿, count what?
A secret.
He sounds well.
Something has to do.
Do not leave it go, one mom.
We are going to count, Megan.
Not it is not, ready.
Now what?
We now, will remove him
A book.
He confesses now.
Remove him other book.
So he will lengthen one more.
After a while
He is him going to hurt.
It is not, very easy.
They are him not going to give the chance
Of confessing, that one is not the idea.
It is not, very quick.
Remove him the other book
Willis.
- Que haga un stripper.
- Si, un stripper.
Silence.
He hears boys, I do not believe that
We have permission.
I tell me to be a stripper.
That one is the game
Is not it true?
Then, do it.
I will do it.
You it matters the clothes, mom
I am going to remove him the short.
It not does not, matter me.
I do not want to hurt you.
But if you do something.
I will have to do it.
Are not stupit.
Please.
Do not move you.
Maybe it is ready
To confess.
Do not, let me do
The rest.
And maybe he will confess.
You can confess now.
Remove him the rope.
Release me, really
He hurts me, please.
It is not, all what you will have.
We go, he confesses.
Talk about you.
You want him to put you
A finger ¿, not is true?
If, touch her.
If, in the class.
- David, ¿estáaquí?
- Si, estáaquí.
OH by God.
Where is Susan?
She also is here.
What one joda, to whom him
It matters Susan ¿, when you go to confess?
There is not anything that to confess.
Please.
Please, do not hurt it.
Do not touch that girl.
I do not want that none
Of Uds. Touch it.
She is not clean.
Keep his hands
Out of her ¿, he heard?
We go.
First, put him the rope
Again.
It is very dirty.
Not it is not, very dirty.
All her will be crying
Night, pónsela.
You have to think in
A thing, young man.
Really, two things.
The first one.
In which I could be your child
He joins who hangs here
...en lugar de ti.
And the second.
In the bad things that there are
Made, I want to hear them.
After all, you can
Confess them the boys.
I can hear them of you.
Or I can hear her of the other.
He thinks of that.
I wonder that
He will feel.
Stopped there hanging
One that way.
He must hurt him.
Really hurt.
Uds. Boys have seen it?
That is to say, like one he sees.
Over there down.
I never saw something like that one.
We are going to revise her.
And we can look at her
Again.
Are you crazy?
I would listen to mom.
We can go.
Boy hears.
You have read a lot of garbage.
Silence.
¿I bet that you want
Take water?
Idiot, he forgets the water and
He remembers what you come to look.
And what?
Tell me that you will not make noise.
If you make noise.
Do you hear me?
If you do it, mom will come.
And if he makes noise, you will have
Problems also.
It is not stupit.
He hurts me my shoulders.
- SuéItame.
- Sabes que no podría.
A little.
But with a condition.
Anything.
You have to promise
Not quarrel.
Not tell anyone.
Never.
What is he?
You already know.
You are not going to hurt
By myself I want to touch you.
You mom said that none
Of Uds. They will touch me.
We can do it and we want.
¿Who goes us
To stop?
I.
OH if ¿, how?
If some of Uds. Me
They touch.
I am going to shout him.
We will, either we will keep
The ropes.
And you will be hanging
Again.
It will be like that.
Very well.
Touch me.
If you do it, he killed you.
It is your will.
He opens.
We have still a relation.
You took the water.
We never were here
Do you understand it?
Good.
Boys go
Slacken the ropes.
I will do it.
Do not look at me
If they know to what I tell me.
I see you.
We go, fondness.
He eats your toast
Fondness.
We go, sweetness
He eats something.
I can not.
I do not waste the food.
I did this toast
For you.
¿What you want that haga?
Throw her.
You have insects.
I did not bring any insects.
Cockroaches, ants.
I do not have any insects in
My home.
He eats, now.
Why do you want it fresh?
You have insects.
I believe that with this
Okey is well.
Nobody said that he went
To be easy.
You are a woman, Meg.
And that is difficult.
It is not easy.
Eat it.
Curse
You broke my cup.
You believe that it is cheap.
Not it is not.
What is there with this?
¿Who is going to clean
This damn disaster?
I will, do it, establish it
Please.
Susa, they see here.
Boys, hold her, by if
He decides to do something stupit one.
Stop you here.
Then he is as we clean
The apartment.
We clean it with
Lashes.
We can do one
New rule.
If you disobey.
You do me or
You disappear slightly.
And she will pay thereby.
Put her over there.
¿You believe that that is
I joust?
Pay by what
Your sister does.
Of course that not.
But nobody says that
Life is fair.
Donny, bring down it the pantyhoses.
He hears ¿, to where you go?
I have to help
To daddy in the work.
We can play later.
Do you want to play?
- Papá.
- Si.
You have seen the boys
With the girls.
If, drunk children.
¿You have sometimes
Thought that it is well?
You want to say, that if
It is well.
If.
That one is a strong one.
Some times it is necessary
Give by the backside.
But you have to respect that
Event of which they are weak.
And be not a swashbuckling one.
Still like that.
Though some times
They deserve it.
And slave trades of not doing it.
Taking a lot goes to the abuse.
There are shouts ¿, what assumes one
That you must do?
You sit down.
It is strong.
But daddy I say
There are exceptions.
But never hurt
To a woman.
Never.
And God will grasp you
If you do it.
Some times.
Nothing there is not that
You can do.
Though they take you far.
That works give birth
Both sides.
Keep your head.
In your things.
Not in women.
Move you away from the problems.
Socket.
Hello, Susan.
Hello.
Ruth is somewhere.
He is above
Resting.
I can not arrest her.
You know it.
The one.
I would do it if I could.
¿You do not believe that he is
A madness?
Lie.
We go, shit chunk
Stop you.
Curse.
He sees and moor her.
You forgot something, David.
Mom.
I establish it.
I have something that to tell you.
Do not move you.
Good morning, David.
He drinks a beer
If you want.
I do not want.
Shit.
Curse, Donny.
He has one now
Cut.
Silence you.
Silence you or I will do it
Again.
Mom.
He answers, he sees smoothly
And fast.
Did you listen to me?
I told you to keep quiet.
Or I will make it of new.
You do not believe that someone
Are behind them.
You do not believe that you can
Handle it, Ruth.
Jennings can be the Mr
Again.
- ¿Quién?
- El policía.
I can watch her by you.
- Vigilarla.
- Para que no se escape.
If.
You watch it.
Good idea.
An alone sound and you I promise
That I kill both.
I do not punish you
I kill you.
You die
Did you understand it?
You understood that.
Good.
Very well.
i.
Here he is.
Good afternoon.
I stopped in the neighborhood
To see as they were the girls.
That is wonderful.
They are well.
Enter, please.
The girls are of
He buys at this moment.
Would he like a coffee?
No, thanks.
How are you do I join lemonade?
It has been a hard day.
No, thanks.
Do not worry
I will look for money.
And you will be well.
I will make sure that not him
Pass nothing to Susan.
I will come back to insure me
That you are well also.
I came back with the police.
They will arrange this.
Tonight
I promise it to you.
This is my child
Sheryl.
Mrs.
Everyone calls me Ruth.
I received a call of
The Mrs Marina, that of the front.
It is by his boy, Tony.
Tony, if I know it well.
He is a sweet boy.
Tony told him his mother that
The boys of here they hit to Meg.
He already knows as the children exaggerate
Maybe they went slightly rough.
He says that they give him biffs.
My boys would never do
Slightly like that.
- ¿Como sabías?
- ¿Saber qué?
What he said.
¿Say to quién?
Of which speeches?
Not me everybody, David.
Mom says that you said to him
To Jennings that came to the door.
How did you know who was?
By myself I guessed it.
Then you are very good
Guessing.
- Estoy tratando de que...
- ¿Tratando qué?
About which do not inform one by
God, of this madness here down.
It is too strange.
Me I suppose it.
What is there with Meg?
They have to put him something
In the arms.
That one joda.
I have not yet had
The chance.
In the game.
Maybe him do.
Not him one.
Yet not him one.
Woofer, puts the TV out.
i he Finishes, it is well.
i is... not, /  i
I have the door open.
You will, go out, we will see each other in an hour.
He takes this.
David, I can not.
If I do something evil.
He will not go by rub of my.
Susan is here.
I do not have chance.
Let me here.
He comes back.
This is by if
You need it.
I establish it so.
It is well.
I believe that you do well.
Okey.
He enters, he closes the door.
You do not, remain you.
That girl is for that.
You entered to the club, he does not matter.
We have this in these days.
Mom, I want to my mom.
Keep quiet the mouth.
Now of whom it is the turn.
I will do it.
Not him one, he belongs to my brother
That would be incest.
- Vamos, mamá.
- No lo creo.
Not by that damn whore.
I create.
That would be better if he were
Eddie.
Or David.
Maybe not.
You are a sentient boy
You would not touch it.
But I am not a man.
We are going to cut her.
If, I also.
Cut her?
We go
Why does one not Donny catch it?
Silence you, I talk with him.
Cut her I eat, he drinks.
With slightly long.
I seized people you will taste
That is a whore.
We go to cut her, mom.
Okey.
- Ruth.
- ¿Qué?
Really you do not go
To do that.
The boys want it.
So I believe that if.
They know what this dog
Treatment of doing last night.
He was about escaping of here.
Someone I leave the door open.
I believe that it was Donny.
Because it was the last one here.
By other he always leaves
It is sweet with her.
- Mamá.
- ¿Qué?
- ¿Por qué no?
Catch her.
Because him I say, curse
It is incest.
You are going to be where your
Brothers, it is loathsome.
You are like your damn father.
Do not talk to me.
Ruth, you can not do that.
I can not.
It is not well.
Please, you do not tell me it
That is well.
You tell it to me never again.
Here we go.
He has to hurt him really.
Of other way
He will become infected.
I go of here.
You do not go to no part.
I do not want to see this.
He turns your damn eyes.
Please.
Come.
This is now forever.
You will never marry you.
Nor remove you the clothes.
For nobody.
Better he disappears.
No man will love you.
You will never see be born any children.
You have luck.
You are out of being beautiful.
Be sexy.
The most horrible woman
Of this world.
- Si mamá, ya no lo es más.
- Te lo dije.
It is distant from being
The same woman.
It will not yet be more.
Myself shooting, take.
Uds. Better they avenge
Here of new.
Wait for a moment.
We already know that no
Man her goes to love.
The problem that I see.
Like still him.
Life is a change over there.
A woman he does not like who
A man on his body.
She by himself does not, want it
In a place in particular.
Girls, they know what I talk about.
Good fondness
If they know it.
The woman loves a man
Bring in his legs.
In his small space.
If you do not have that space.
They know what it happens.
They remove him all his wishes.
They remove him all by
He always, works.
They do it all the time
In some places.
They do it usually
When a woman.
He arrives at certain age.
Places as Africa.
Nigeria.
They consider that practice.
I wonder
Why not here?
That child remove him
That is plenty.
And we burn it.
It will be perfect what of it.
Coño.
Where do you think that you go to?
You are going to say it of that whore.
Or call the officer Jennings.
But he will not be now.
Not, until I pass it
That it has to happen.
Put you happy that you have that one
Small spar that she does not will have.
You now, have two friend of
Who worry.
Atenlo, boys.
We here go now.
David.
Do you hate me?
Clear that not.
Are you sure?
I also did it to him.
It is by my fault.
She could go and not return.
She treated, Susan.
She tried to finish it.
He remained because the
They would do with me.
He wanted to help me.
You could, not, help her a little.
One he supposed that he would turn round
Afterwards by you.
Why did not he escape?
I believe that because.
I am sure.
I was going to touch.
And they would hit me.
Ruth told him to Meg the
That would be me made.
And thereby her the
He acted as new.
They get back to hit her.
He will come by my.
Nobody could help her
That is not reason.
Quiet, you will be well.
We go, do not do that.
Hear, also you Susan.
He hurts, a lot.
Do not move you.
Okey.
Him I feel, Megan.
I establish it.
Susan is well.
We try it.
That night.
When I pass the time
My parents will worry.
- No puedes hacerlo.
- Es lo mejor.
He rests only.
I have to find
Something to hurt her.
Get out of here.
It is not well.
You know as he hurts me
When the attempt.
They are there.
Maybe.
I believe that we can do something.
Shit, mom.
He brings down that razor.
I told you to throw it.
Go out of here.
Which step?
Jennings Mr.
She was Ruth.
She made this to Meg.
Thereby I stuck him.
Remain with her.
Come, it is well.
David.
Do not talk.
Do me a favor.
Insurance.
Bring me the ring of
My mother.
Thanks.
I was all my sleep.
It is enough give birth my.
A sleep.
Our sleep.
You let hurt it to me.
I understand it.
Now.
That she can not.
That her hurts.
Not, Meg, by favor.
I always thought of you.
If.
And also in Susan.
I believe that he will achieve it.
I love you.
i The past always
It is with you.
You like  i or not.
i Can be a present.
i Or a curse
If you let it.
i I will Never forget the present
That Meg gave to me.
i I Felt the torment again that
She felt.
i The feelings of someone.
i But her he said to me.
i Is what your bundles
What remains.
EDiT BY
~ GYPTiAN ~
SEPTiCEMiA TEAM
=- www.Subs4U.gr-=
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org