Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Get out of here!
Get off!
Excuse me.
I was expecting
to be met.
Good morning,
Truscott.
I am Belansai.
Welcome
to our country.
He's a bright chap.
He'll be the head man
of his Longhouse in two years.
John Truscott.
Henry Bullard.
I'm the governor
of this district,
but you just
think of me as God.
Hop aboard.
You've got far too good
a degree for this job.
What are you running away from?
Your debts?
Your family?
Or a woman?
No, no debts.
No woman.
My mother
died two years ago.
My father was killed
at Passchendaele, so...
Well, why in God's name
are you here?
My father was
a district officer out here.
William C. Truscott?
Ahhh.
He'd drawn up a plan
to bring education to the Iban
which the governor general
had approved,
but then he had
to go back to the war...
and it never happened.
And you've brought
this plan with you, have you?
Yes, I think it's our duty
to educate primitive people.
God, you sound
a sanctimonious little prig.
Still, you're young.
Sarawak'll knock
it out of you.
Famous,
you lazy bastard!
Look at the state
of this place.
Bring Truscott tea and gadgets
double quick.
Come on.
Chibi, chibi, chibi.
It's got bugs in there.
He's the best cook
in Sarawak.
Though strictly speaking
he's still on parole.
What did he do?
Oh, he hacked some damn fool
rickshaw driver to death.
But you should
taste his meringues.
- Shouldn't he be in--
- Now, tomorrow,
you've an invitation
from your local Longhouse,
the Gawa Kenyalong.
So Belansai'll
pick you up.
The feast to honor
the war god
where they take the giant hornbill
statue down from the rafters.
Oh, God.
You read-- books.
I'm afraid they insist
upon it at university.
Do they?
Has it come
to that now?
Yes, I'll--
I'll see you
in a day or so.
Excuse me.
Excuse me...
What's my job?
This is my father,
Melaka.
He is head man
of the Longhouse.
This is rice wine.
Ah. Um...
I won't drink
on duty, thanks.
To refuse is an insult.
Left, right.
It's chibi,
chibi, chibi!
It is a... very ancient
tribal dance.
Oh, no, um... no.
Very kind
of you to offer,
but I think I'll give it
a miss this time round.
You must make us
entertainment.
A song? A dance?
A poem?
Perhaps all three.
"The sand of the desert
is sodden red,
Red with the wreck
of the ranks that broke.
The Gatling's jammed
and the Colonel dead,
And the regiment blind
with dust and smoke.
The river of death
has brimmed his banks,
And England's far
and honor's a name,
But the voice of a schoolboy
rallies the ranks,
'Play up!
Play up
and play the game!'"
" Da-dum-dum-dum "
" Da-da-da-da,
Dum-dum-dum-dum "
" Da-da-da-da "
Oh, Truscott, you are very
funny Englishman.
Excuse me.
What's going on?
The dancing is over.
We go to sleep now.
You deliberately dropped me
in it, didn't you?
You know I made a complete
fool of myself?
They like a man
who makes them laugh.
Iban society is based
on heavy drinking,
violent sport
and practical jokes.
Just think of it as
English public school
without the buggery.
I'm on a mission to civilize,
not to entertain.
The mining concessions
at Kera Pulau
have been trespassing
outside their boundaries.
Your local Longhouse
got to some Chinese miners
before I did.
You're going to have
to bring in their heads.
What?
Well...
we limit the areas where
the mining concerns can--
No, no, no.
You said...
you said "their heads."
Well, yes.
The Iban have
cut them off.
What?
Ahh.
My dear.
This is Selima.
She's going
to live with you.
As what?
Uh... she performs
wifely duties.
Oh yeah?
What... sewing?
She performs wifely duties
in the bedroom.
- For God's sakes, man.
- I sleep with you.
We expect you to know
the language within six months.
Selima's what's known around here
as a "sleeping dictionary."
Sleep...
My mother was also
sleeping dictionary.
That's why I speak
the King English.
There's nothing like bed
for learning a language.
It's the only reason
I speak Portuguese.
No, look, poor girl.
- She was just-- picked?
- I pick you.
And she's really choosy.
She turned down
my last two cadet officers.
Listen, your contract
forbids you
to marry
for three years.
Three years can be
very lonely.
And after three years?
We'll probably all be dead,
so why worry?
Oh, dear.
Listen...
you'll go home
on leave to England
and you'll come back with
a rosy-cheeked little wife.
Selima will go home
to her Longhouse
speaking
fluent English.
Oh, damn it, man,
it's worked for centuries.
There's no reason
why you should be different.
No, I'm sorry, no. No.
I know you think
I'm just some young idiot,
but if I don't follow what
I think's right, what else is there?
Then you'd better find another way
to learn the damn language.
Because if a so-called
educated man
can't speak the language
of the people he governs,
he's no right to be here!
Fine, maybe she can stay as...
just a dictionary?
- If she doesn't mind, that is.
- What?
Mind not sleeping with you?
I'm sure she'll survive.
She said yes.
What else did she say?
You'll have to learn Iban
and find out, won't you?
I'd stand back
if I were you.
Ha ha!
Ants.
Yes, ants.
Thank you very much.
Good night.
You say no,
she get very angry.
Rain always stop
in morning.
Sleep tight and don't
let the bedbugs bite.
Chinese heads
as per request.
Thank you.
As you know, the Longhouse
will be fined.
Beyond that, there will
be no further action.
Monkey heads.
We make a joke on you.
Maybe I'll make
a joke on you
and bring a detachment
of colonial police up the river.
I want those heads delivered
to my bungalow by tomorrow morning
or I will confiscate your--
your pigs.
Master?
I bring you someone.
This is Jasmine.
He is assistant chef.
What do we need
an assistant chef for?
- He assist you.
- Me?
He assist you in...
private way.
Is this one of your relatives?
No, no, no.
He very clean.
He come from
Englishman on coast
who too old
for all that now.
What?
Oh, good God.
Get him out of--
No, get him out now!
- But, master--
- Get him out of here!
And Selima,
bring me a whiskey.
What are you doing?!
I'm not servant.
Fine.
You don't have to be a servant.
You're fired!
Dismissed!
You cannot fire me because
I am not yours to fire.
I fire you.
You are dismissed.
Make no attempt
to follow me.
- What are you doing?
- I live here now.
You can't live there.
Then I will live
in the jungle.
I like the jungle.
No, listen. You must go
back to the Longhouse.
They will
laugh at her.
They will say she choose you
but you no have her.
- Is that true?
- No.
They will say you
not sleep with her
because she too
pig ugly.
Listen, I don't
think you're ugly.
I think you're
very beautiful.
I don't sleep with you
because of my beliefs.
Because... the spirits
of my country forbid it.
You want to sleep with me
but you forbid by your spirit?
Yes, you could say that.
I will go to my tree now.
Wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Perhaps we could
have another try.
If you're willing
to re-employ me, that is.
I will give you
one more chance.
Hey!
I want a word
with you.
Last night you got
completely drunk again.
My other masters,
they fine me
one week pay
if I blind drunk,
two week pay if I blind,
legless drunk.
I blind drunk two time
a month regular,
so very cheap cook.
Fair enough.
Wait.
Do you play croquet?
No.
Help me reload,
would you?
I'm clearing the jungle
for a croquet lawn
for when Cecil,
my daughter, comes out.
It's much quicker than
a working party from the jail.
Aggie Bullard,
Henry's wife.
You must be Truscott.
How are you getting on
with Henry's damn fool tests?
I think next
I have to wrestle a crocodile.
Sleeping dictionary
shaping up all right?
Truscott!
Us women don't know anything
about all of that.
- Truscott!
- And for heaven's sake,
bed her or the Iban'll think
there's something wrong
with you down below.
Excuse me.
Re-group!
Sorry?
You're not picking up
the language very fast, are you?
And where are those
Chinese heads?!
You are in the bathroom.
I am in...?
the bedroom.
What do I do?
I...
I say good night
to my father.
Where do you go?
Bedroom.
Bedroom...
bedroom.
W-what next?
I-I go to sleep.
Do English people
have dreams at night?
Sometimes, yeah.
Are we really
that strange?
Have you ever
sleep with a woman?
I won't
till I get married.
That's our way.
But when you marry
you'll be very bad at sex
and your wife
will be unhappy.
I'll take evening classes,
I promise.
I've never met anyone...
even a little like you.
Whyever did you
choose me?
Your dance is not
the dance of an Englishman.
Good night.
Yes.
I thought you didn't like
our education.
You want to educate us
like your father did?
You were educated because
you're the chief's son.
Shouldn't others have
the same opportunity?
William, William,
Henry, Henry,
Richard, John, Henry,
Edward, Edward,
Richard, Henry,
Henry, Edward,
Edward, Richard,
Henry, Henry, Edward--
Mary, Elizabeth,
James, Charles,
Charles, James, William,
George, George, George, George,
William, Victoria,
Edward, George, Edward, George.
The kings of England.
And why do I need
to know that?
The mission school
tries to turn us
into little Englishmen.
They didn't do a very good job
with you, did they?
You missed Queen Anne,
by the way.
You missed King Stephen.
I hear when you were young,
you were a champion at
the underwater battles.
When I was young?
I am still champion
of 1 0 Longhouses.
Yes, they say you can
beat any girl on the river.
Will you
challenge me then?
How you--
how you do that?
Some Englishmen
can breathe underwater
through their ears.
I wonder if I might
have a word about...
those heads.
It's lovely
workmanship.
I'll add those
to the collection.
The ants eaten
your dinner jacket yet?
I think there's
an arm or two left.
Good.
My daughter Cecilia
is arriving for Christmas.
First class honors degree
at Oxford.
You'd like her.
Come to dinner.
Oh!
How drunk is he?
Blind, legless, daft,
sick, smelly drunk.
My mother
read that to me.
My father
read it to me.
Do you remember
your father?
He go back to England
when I am four.
My dad died
when I was four.
"Deep, deep
beneath the sea
where the water is
clear as purest glass
Iies the palace
of the Sea King.
There behind its...
walls of coral
and roof of cockleshells
lives a little mermaid."
You can read English.
I remember it
by my heart.
I made him read it
many time.
Write a word from it.
"Deep."
Now you.
"Hand."
"Arm."
Neck.
Lips.
Breast.
I-I'm sorry.
That was too quick,
wasn't it?
You teach me English,
I'll teach you this.
School is not finished.
Not quite the education
my father had in mind.
Why do you always go?
For sleeping dictionary,
it is proper.
For the Iban,
if a man and a woman wake up
together five nights in a row,
they are engaged.
You don't want that,
do you?
Cecilia's got a degree
in anthropology, you know?
She did her thesis
on the Iban.
- Really?
- Mmm.
Why did you choose
the Iban to study?
I lived here until I was five.
Till Mother and Father
couldn't stand me any longer
and shipped me off to school.
But I always
remembered them.
The way you'd never see them arrive,
but then suddenly there they'd be,
standing beside you
as if they'd
been there since...
time began.
Although, for them, of course,
time only began 53 years ago.
- Really?
- Yes, the year Krakatoa exploded.
- That's their year zero.
- Is that true?
How the deuce
do you know that?
- Well, I listen.
- Do you now?
Well, I can't wait to get
stuck in and meet the Iban.
Shipperly's taken over
from Teague--
chap I told you about.
Went doolally
and ate his own toes.
I'll tell you something
I bet you don't know.
Back in Victorian times,
the young officers coming out here
were given a young woman
from the local head-hunting tribes
to share their bed...
so they could learn
the language quickly.
I hardly think so, darling.
Now you are having us on,
aren't you?
No, that's true.
I've heard tell of it
from a very old Iban.
- See?
- Well...
if it did exist,
I'm sure it was purely
a matter of convenience
and no...
higher feelings
were involved.
- Don't see why.
- Surely you can't seriously believe
that a primitive
head-huntress
and an English officer
could experience love.
Not love, maybe,
but I'm sure they could
feel a great deal.
Whatever an Englishman felt,
he would never
let that get in the way
of his duty
to the local people.
My Iban wouldn't
think less of an officer--
"My Iban"?
They're not your Iban.
They might be God's,
but they're certainly not yours.
We've got enough bloody dictators
in Europe, thank you.
- All I'm saying--
- And all I'm saying,
is that an English officer
would never let
his country down.
Nor his family.
Would he, Truscott?
No, sir.
So is she pretty?
Well, she's fairly pretty.
But does she have wings?
What happened to
the spirits of your country?
They grew old and tired and packed
their bags and left for England.
This is a land dispute
between two Longhouses.
It's fiendishly
complicated.
You must be sick of me
following you around.
No, I know how
interested you are.
At least this time we escaped
the dreaded Shipperly.
He's harmless, but...
he's like all men
who've been to an all-male
school and college.
The only women they're comfortable
with are their mothers.
He talks to me like
I'm a Labrador.
I went to an all-male school
and an all-male college.
Then something
must've changed you.
Well...
yes.
Being out here, I imagine.
So have you
sorted out this dispute?
Yes, I think so,
yes.
See, it's impossible
to sort out the argument.
So if I decide
for one side or the other,
it'll just seem
unfair to them.
Pull!
Would you mind?
That's it, perfect. Thank you.
Thank you.
Isn't she amazing?
What did she say?
There's not a precise
English translation for that one.
Cecil, these children
love having their photo--
She's wonderful.
I wish I looked like her.
Hands higher, please.
That's it.
Perfect.
Cecil, I don't think
she wants her photograph taken.
- Just a couple more.
- Truscott!
Go and see what's happening
down there, will you?
Ask her to keep up
that fierce expression, please.
- Cecil--
- Truscott!
I told you to go and see
what the devil's happening!
She won't understand.
She's Yakata.
You can tell by
the turquoise bracelet.
I studied them.
She was bleeding
through her skin.
Come away
and wash your hands.
There's a dozen more dead bodies
turned up at Laksai,
50 miles out
of their territory.
I'd better go up river
and have a look, hadn't I?
No, you hadn't!
It's dangerous enough up there
without an epidemic.
That's my job.
They'll have your head
as soon as look at you.
Besides he doesn't
speak the language.
Well,
I'll take Selima.
She speaks
half a dozen languages.
And Belansai, no one's
going to tangle with him.
Send that idiot Shipperly.
A few poisoned darts
might liven him up.
I'll set out
tomorrow morning, shall I?
Aggie,
I can't send Shipperly.
You said yourself
the man's an idiot...
If you're about to be killed,
at least stay for dinner.
Terrific girl, Cecil.
Isn't she?
Absolutely, yeah.
If you want a child
properly educated,
you've got to send them
back home.
But you can't be
in two places at once.
And I thought
it was my duty...
to stay with Henry.
Yes.
But they've done
a terrific job on her.
We're delighted.
She knows
all sorts of things.
And it means she's turned out
very self-sufficient, very capable.
Exactly the sort of girl
one wants to marry out here,
not some flimsy little miss
who's never left England.
And of course...
she's ever so fond of you.
Well, she's lovely,
like you say.
But I'm not sure
that I...
Love her?
I don't think I knew what love
was when I was your age.
I don't suppose you do.
Well, what is it like?
Well, it's, um...
it's companionship,
fellow feeling.
Now listen,
you want these schools
for the Iban.
Henry'll help you.
I'll see to that.
So...
what do you say?
I'm not really sure.
This is all rather sudden.
Don't take too long
thinking about it.
Neville's asked her
to marry him.
She'll be gone by the time
you get back from your trip
and you won't see her
for two years.
I'm sorry about
this afternoon.
I should have
stopped her sooner.
Selima?
You had other lovers
before me, didn't you?
Did you and they
have what we have?
Yes.
They were men
like you.
But...
I thought we had
something special.
No, we fuck, that's all.
You're angry?
You're not telling the truth.
I'm angry, that's why
I'm telling the truth.
Half my blood is English.
That is more than
your king and queen,
but for you,
that is not good enough.
So Iban I'll be.
Rule me if you must,
but nothing else.
Go ahead.
Do your sex.
Don't mind me.
"Hands higher.
That's it.
Perfect."
"Dear Cecil,
Everything is going
very well.
We've reached the edge
of Yakata country.
Belansai calls them
'the invisible people.'
And even the Iban admit
they can blend into the jungle
like no one else.
They're fierce warriors,
but they live
as one big family.
Sharing is so much a part
of their way of life
that they have no word
for 'thank you.'
I look forward to seeing you
when I finally come home on leave.
I'll finish
this letter later."
It's not like any disease.
It's not famine--
there's rice in the huts!
It's a white man with a rifle--
aiming at you.
Listen...
He's gone now.
Thank you.
Can you track him?
- My God.
- What?
I think this could be
a new species.
It's like the buffalo leech,
but bigger.
Would you mind just
getting it off my back?
I don't want to hurt it.
Maybe they'll name it
after you, sweetheart.
Can you remember where
you were when it bit you?
No.
No, I can't remember where I was
when it bloody well bit me,
because I was in the middle
of the bloody jungle,
which looked like every other
bit of bloody jungle,
full of bloodsucking,
bloodthirsty,
bloody little bastards!
Good afternoon,
Mrs. Bullard.
Idiot.
They come across the mountains
from Dutch Borneo.
- Very difficult journey.
- That's pure silver.
They'll be making
a fortune.
And it looks like they don't want
any other Europeans to know.
Me get sickness.
They go away.
You'll be all right.
We'll take you down the river
in the morning.
They say you brought
the illness.
The Dutchmen told them.
What did you say?
I told them
you are a god
and will cure them.
Oh. Good.
Ask them if they
will eat with us.
The Yakata don't grow rice,
do they?
So they must have
traded for it.
The bastards.
The bastards! They wanted
to clear the mining area,
so they put poison
in the rice!
- Do we die?
- No.
No, it's a slow-working poison,
so it looks like disease.
So, my English friend...
do we arrest the miners?
What will the Yakata do
if we tell them?
Kill them all.
Tell them.
Explosie.
When I found you
lying there,
suddenly everything
became clear.
I want to stay
with you forever...
if you'll have me.
Where shall we run?
Run?
We can cross
into Dutch Borneo.
There's no need for that.
I love Sarawak.
But they'll stop us.
Oh, for God's sake,
the English aren't barbarians.
I'll sort it out.
Trust me.
I'll sort everything out,
I promise.
I know
my own people.
You want to marry her.
We say we've a right to be here
because we're a civilizing force.
How can we let our officers
sleep with the local women,
and not marry them?
You're not the first,
you know.
Let me tell you something.
25 years ago,
I was a young idiot.
She was called Ipoh...
and I loved her.
But I made my decision,
and I never saw her again
until the day she died.
- You don't regret that?
- I did what was right!
I did my duty,
and so will you!
No.
No, I won't.
It's a good thing your father
didn't think that at Passchendaele!
Is it?
Maybe then he wouldn't
have drowned in a shell hole
so some senile old general
could get a knighthood!
God, you self-righteous
little prick!
- You'll do what I say!
- You let me--
Bit of
an administrative crisis.
Yes, I know
what's happened.
Everybody does!
I'd like a word
with you in private.
Selima...
The English have
sent word.
If you won't
give him up,
they'll charge him with
the murder of the white miners.
- Did you tell them?
- No!
They will charge me
as well.
That's why my father
asks you.
Look, there's a way
of doing things,
and if you change it,
our little world falls apart.
- You're the one that told me--
- For goodness sake!
Give her up and Henry'll send
you home on a year's sick leave.
You can come back
as if nothing happened.
Refuse and you'll spend
the next 1 0 years rotting in prison.
And then
we'll deport you
and you'll never see Sarawak,
or her, again.
You can't do that.
You broke the law.
You can't go around
murdering white men
just because you think
they deserve it.
He could hang you
for that.
But you'd ignore it
if I do as you want?
You've a choice.
Make your mind up.
- I want to see her.
- Send her a letter!
You've taught her
to read, haven't you?
Stop him!
Idiot.
Selima?
Selima!
Where is she?
It's all arranged,
isn't it?
- Isn't it?!
- It's not as I thought.
Th-there's difficulties.
Help me!
I'm ordering you
to help me!
You swore
it would all work out.
Truscott, I am getting extremely
fed up with you.
I'm too old to run through
the bloody jungle all night!
Just give her up now.
- This is your last chance.
- No!
Say you'll give him up.
You know what'll
happen otherwise!
Once I start this,
it can't be stopped.
John Truscott,
I charge you--
- I'll do it.
- No, no.
I'll marry
at the Longhouse.
I told you
it's not possible.
So?
Do you give her up?
I do.
I now pronounce you
man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Ready!
We'll remember this song.
Always.
There is something
I should say.
I know about your
sleeping dictionary.
At least, I presume
you had one.
Father thinks we women
don't find out about such things.
But anyway,
I don't mind.
I know how things
are done out there.
And the good thing is...
at least you'll know what to do
because I'm damned if I do.
What happened to her?
Oh, she married Belansai.
Your father
wrote me a letter.
Was that before you
proposed to me, or...
Oh...
No, I think it
must have been afterwards.
Here we go, then.
"Dear Henry,
I talked things over
with Cecilia again,
and we have decided
to return to Sarawak.
She wants to be with you,
and I would be a coward not
to finish the work I started.
I think the only way forward
is to wipe away
the last couple of years
and start life afresh.
I'm determined to make
your daughter happy.
Yours sincerely,
John Truscott."
" East of the sun "
" And west of the moon... "
I thought I'd organize
a welcoming committee.
They're wonderful.
Welcome back to hell.
Shipperly.
Weather forecast
for the next...
1 0,000 years
is too bloody hot.
Ah.
"...of the moon. "
You're looking at
the first Iban class,
the first Iban school.
Your dad would be proud.
If he saw the Iban choosing what
they were taught, he'd have a fit.
For heaven's sake, he wanted
to teach them Latin and Greek.
You know, I actually wasn't
going to mention this for a while,
but I wondered if you might
like to do some teaching?
Ow!
What in the world?
I thought
that's what you wanted.
I thought that's
what she would have done.
Neville told me
about you and her.
Have you seen her
since we got here?
No!
No, not since...
a year ago, or more.
He said she and her husband
had a little boy.
Apparently
they're very happy.
I want us to be happy.
Then why aren't we?
It's her, isn't it?
Yes.
She's very beautiful.
Isn't she?
In her own way, yes.
- What's that?
- It's Famous, blind drunk.
In fact, blind, legless,
daft, sick, smelly drunk
by the sounds of things.
You've got to fire him.
Cecil...
he's been with me
since I arrived.
He doesn't like me.
He preferred her, I can tell.
Hello?
Who's this?
This is your new cook.
Henry sent him.
Mrs. Truscott
tell Mr. Truscott...
- to give me the boot.
- Thank you, Famous.
Thank you.
Did you do that?
Famous, take her into
the kitchen and clean her up.
You do not do that.
You treat her
with respect.
We're not all in love with our
sleeping dictionaries, you know.
Tipong!
What did you say to her?
Oh, I told Tipong that
if you hit her again,
she should wait
till you're asleep,
then cut off your testicles
with a kitchen knife.
They're very good at
that kind of thing, the Iban.
Probably wouldn't
even wake you. Now--
Henry sent me.
We've got to unbugger up
your last month's work.
Cecil--
you know, I would have
made her happy.
I told him we'd
remember this song.
Don't be so pathetic.
You should forget all about
this love business.
Marriages work
far better without it.
You should concentrate
on the school.
You like that.
He just needs
a little time.
When was the last time
he slept with you?
he even touched you?
That's how you judge men.
Hello, darling.
Good evening,
Mrs. Bullard.
You will excuse us,
won't you?
You kissed me just to get one over
on my mother, didn't you?
No. No, of course not.
Take one more reading
before we go leave.
Right.
- Is the baby mine?
- Oh, yes.
And are you open
to bribery?
Oh, very much so.
So you'll arrange
for us to meet?
I am one step ahead.
I already make inquiries,
and she will not see you.
So you tell her Tipong
has been beaten again
and needs her help.
Shipperly?
Shipperly I will send
on a vital mission somewhere.
Somewhere famed for the size
and quantity of its tiger leeches.
Please.
I want to see
my son.
I don't understand "son."
My child.
Child?
You understand perfectly.
He was born nine months ago.
I don't understand
English anymore.
My son. You have my son.
His name is Mandar.
I left him on the veranda.
I was frightened of Neville.
I'll get him!
You can have one minute,
but they'll kill me
if they see us together.
Selima, stay!
For how long?
Forever?
I didn't know they were going to
treat us like that, I'm sorry.
I don't know
what to say.
He's Belansai's son now.
He marry me even though
he knew I was pregnant.
"Deep, deep beneath the sea...
where the water is clear
as the purest glass,
there lies the palace
of the Sea King.
And there, behind
the walls of coral,
and beneath its roof
of cockleshells
Iived the little mermaid."
So, Truscott.
Is there some good news
you're not telling us?
I presume you've
impregnated my daughter.
Oh... no.
Not yet.
It's just in case.
Let me tell you why
I stayed here with Henry,
and let Cecil grow up alone.
I told you it was duty.
I told myself it was duty,
but it wasn't duty.
I never dared
leave Henry alone...
for fear he'd go back
to his native girl.
So be warned.
I won't let that...
wreck another generation.
- John!
- Ah!
They've cornered him--
at the Longhouse loft
at Baritsai.
The damn fool!
I hoped he'd run over
the mountains to Dutch Borneo.
You caused all this!
Now we're going to have
to execute him.
One of the best men
I know.
Well, you can
damn well be his judge.
He had no choice.
I know that!
I know that.
But he tried to kill
a colonial official
and that has to mean death.
Even though the colonial
official in question
deserved having his throat cut
for sneaking around with his wife!
It wasn't her I was seeing,
it was my son!
My son, who you
never told me about!
Am I supposed to pretend
he doesn't exist?
Yes, you are!
For the rest of your life.
Yes.
Have you--?
Another daughter?
Yes.
The daughters
of sleeping dictionaries
become sleeping
dictionaries.
I thought
you were kind,
that you'd
treat her well.
Not quite as well as you ended up
treating her, of course.
And she doesn't know?
No.
I told her mother
to tell her
that I was
back in England.
It's normal.
This way is best.
Aggie--
it wouldn't be
fair on her.
I did my duty.
At least I didn't
kill anyone!
Belansai,
was it your intention
to kill me,
or just to wound me?
To kill you.
But did you
come to kill me?
Or did a sudden madness
seize you?
I came to kill you.
Belansai...
tell the court why
you had to try to kill me.
The court will adjourn
and pass sentence tomorrow.
- What are you doing?
- He saved my life.
Yes, and what a shame
that was.
Don't think you're going to sentence
him to anything except death.
You do that, and I'll just
step in and overrule you.
You understand me?
You'll have achieved nothing!
Leave her alone!
Go on, get back!
Move! Move!
Be upstanding.
This court is
now in session.
This court
is in session.
Belansai Ringan,
this court finds you
guilty of attempted murder.
Due to the lack of
mitigating circumstances,
I have no alternative
but to sentence you to death.
Tomorrow morning
you'll be taken from the jail,
and hung from your neck
until you are dead.
May God have mercy
on your soul.
Do they have to make
such a bloody noise
building a scaffold?
And it's all because
of that damn fool Truscott.
It'll do him good.
Now he's seen the consequences,
it'll settle him down.
But Cecilia said
she saw them talking.
- Surely we ought to--
- Do as little as possible.
He did what you asked him to,
today, didn't he?
- Hmmm.
- He's like you, Henry,
when it comes to what
really matters, he always gives in.
Now have another drink
and go to bed.
Hmmm.
You've no reason
not to take it.
Well, we're going to have
to run away together now.
Steamer leaves
tomorrow at dawn.
I'll leave at dusk, I'll be there
by 3:00 a.m. at the latest.
You won't come.
They'll find out. They'll say you
must be an Englishman.
And I'll tell them
that I'd rather have you
than a country,
or a language,
or a history.
I can't prove it,
but I know what you've done.
And I'm going to treat you
as if you had done it!
Have you
anything to say?
You're a bloody disgrace!
If it wasn't for Cecil,
I'd put you in there!
Get out to the dam
and do something useful!
Go on.
You won't get
any sense out of her.
Listen, you're not welcome
at the Longhouse,
and you're certainly
not welcome here.
So Shipperly--
Neville--
has very kindly agreed to take you
on as a sleeping dictionary.
I presume you'd prefer that
to a spell in prison.
Off we go, then.
It was wonderful
at the school today.
I tried teaching in Iban.
And I thought I said
cooking yams-- "patanta"
but actually I said "matanta--"
cooking your lover.
They laughed and laughed.
And... now I'm going
to have to tell you.
I'm pregnant.
Doctor Smith came
from Miri today and...
there's no doubt about it.
Your face.
You look so happy.
Well, of course I'm happy.
I know I shouldn't
really say this...
but I nearly
gave up on us.
But I didn't.
And I'm so glad.
Shall we open
that bottle of champagne?
"Leeches."
Hmmm?
"Jungle."
"Fucking jungle."
"Fucking jungle...
full of prick-teasing,
little brown savages."
There she is,
swearing like a trooper
blood everywhere,
the cook-turned-midwife screaming,
- "Push, lady, push!"
- Henry completely useless.
Shouting to nobody
in particular:
"Why didn't we get her
downriver before the monsoon? "
And then in walks
this clouded leopard.
It was attracted
by the blood, you see.
However,
not really dangerous.
He starts shooting
anyway.
Bullets flying everywhere,
except anywhere near the leopard.
- In the middle of all this uproar--
- Out I pop.
Yes, bright pink.
And even then, she was
the loudest thing in the room.
She was wonderful,
wasn't she?
It was wonderful for us,
the first five years
before we had to--
you know, send you home.
Yes. She was wonderful,
wasn't she?
How many glasses of champagne
have you had, Daddy?
Oh, come on,
if a man can't celebrate...
Listen, I prayed that
this would happen for both of you.
It'll make
all the difference.
Look at him.
He's still in shock.
Get baby and go!
I catch you up!
It is for me, isn't it?
Why haven't you finished it?
Because nothing
I could think of seemed...
enough.
Tonight I've been
watching you,
trying to make myself
believe you were happy.
Because I was so determined that
this would finally do the trick...
that this would
make us be in love.
I did love seeing you
so happy.
I saw that, but...
it's not enough, is it?
You know...
I think you probably know my mother
and father better than I do.
You've spent more
time with them.
Five. I was...
five when I was shipped off
back to school in England.
Some mothers came with
their children, but not mine.
She never even
came home for Christmas.
She wouldn't let Daddy
out of her sight.
So when you asked me
to marry you, I thought,
"Here's someone
who's chosen me.
Not someone who's lumbered with me
and has to pretend to love me,
but someone
who really wants me."
But all the time
you loved someone else.
If it hadn't been for her,
we could've been happy enough,
couldn't we?
No, it's all right.
You don't have to lie.
And anyway, I'm not prepared
to settle for "happy enough."
Not anymore.
I want--
I want what
you and her have.
Now go.
I want you to go.
Anyway, you've left
something of yours behind.
I won't say anything to Mother
and Father till the morning.
It's better this way.
Psst. Psst!
She think you not coming.
She not catch boat.
She making a run for Dutch Borneo.
Head for old mine.
You do realize
I can't let you go.
You might need this.
My second present.
You know?
I guess eventually.
Seems I only
ever get to say goodbye.
Come on.
I do hope you're
not incorruptible.
They're both headed
over the mountains.
I have a party
ready to follow them.
Have you?
There's no whiskey trees
in the jungle, you know.
Henry, she tried
to kill Shipperly.
- That's a hanging offense.
- I can't spare the men.
Do you care nothing
for your daughter?
I care a great deal...
for them both.
Cecil, tell him.
I don't want John hurt.
Or my sister.
He said go after them.
Come along, idiot.
What are you waiting for?
Stay here.
Selima!
Afternoon.
I thought you'd
turn up eventually.
Handcuff yourselves
to the pole.
Come on! We don't want to wake
the baby up, now do we?!
Do it properly,
Truscott.
I've thought a lot
about the order of this.
But I reckon...
rape Selima,
kill baby,
kill Selima...
kill you.
Jam, did it?
Eeny...
meeny...
minie...
mo.
"The witch said
to the little mermaid,
'Why do you want to take human form
and walk upon the land?'
'Because I love him.
He is always in my thoughts
and I would place
my happiness in his hands,'
replied the little mermaid."
They sing because
they move on tomorrow.
Make a new village
a day's journey from here.
They want us
to come with them.
Then we must go.
If we go,
you will have nothing.
I'll have this.
I'll have you.
So shall I tell them
we'll come?
Tell them.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org