Ha-ha!
♪ Yeah, my man!
♪ All right!
♪ I wanna tell you a story
♪ Every man oughta know
♪ If you want a little lovin'
♪ You gotta start real slow
♪ She's gonna love you tonight now
♪ If you just treat her right now
♪ Oh, squeeze her real gentle
♪ You gotta make her feel good
♪ Tell her that you love her
♪ Like you know you should
♪ Cos if you don't treat her right now
♪ She won't love you tonight now
♪ If you practise my method
♪ Just as hard as you can
♪ You're gonna get a reputation
♪ As a lovin' man now
♪ And you'll be glad every night
♪ That you treated her right
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey!
♪ Hey!
♪ All right!
♪ In the town of Springhill, Nova Scotia
♪ Down in the dark of a Cumberland mine
Tell us about the early days, Jimmy.
How did it all begin?
Well, Terry, I was always in the music
business, but more on the sales side.
Fuck off.
♪ Don't want your kisses
♪ That's for sure
♪ I die each time
♪ I hear this sound:
♪ Here he comes
♪ That's Cathy's clown
♪ Dearest
♪ Darlin'
♪ I have to write to say
that I won't be home
♪ Any more
♪ Cos something happened
♪ To me
♪ While I was drivin' home
♪ And I'm not the same
♪ Any more
♪ Oh, I was only
♪ Twenty-four hours from Tulsa
♪ Only
♪ One day away from your arms
♪ I saw a welcoming light
♪ And I had to stop for the night
♪ Said to the man at the railroad station
♪ I want a ticket
♪ Just for one
♪ He said: Well, if you insist
♪ Where you wanna go, miss?
♪ Oh-oh
♪ Destination anywhere
- Jimmy! Jimmy! You got the video?
- Yeah. Mississippi Burning, wasn't it?
Have you got any Hothouse Flowers?
♪ And this old world ain't got
no back door
♪ Because I saw her today
♪ I saw her face
♪ It was a face I loved
♪ And I knew
♪ I had to run away-ay
♪ And get down on my knees and pray-ay
♪ That they'd go away
♪ But still they begin
♪ Those needles and pins, yeah
♪ Because of all my pride
♪ The tears I gotta hide
♪ Right now - yeah!
♪ Needles and pins, yeah
♪ Needles and pins
♪ Needles and pins,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
♪ Yeah-yeah!
♪ Ye-e-e-eah!
We'll take a short break here,
but we'll be back,
so stay in the groove.
- Imelda, you're lookin' deadly!
- What are you doin' here?
- Friend of the band's.
- You're sure no friend o' me sister's!
The fella she's marrying
hardly knows her.
Cheeky bastard!
- You'll be next.
- Why me? I'm not bleedin' pregnant!
- Imelda.
- See yeh, Jimmy.
Fuck off!
Well, I'm three months gone.
It's a bit tight.
- Oh, I can feel it!
- You can feel it already?
That's great! Can you feel it?
- Why d'yeh want me to manage yis?
- Cos you know all about music, Jimmy.
You had Frankie Goes To Hollywood's
album before anyone else.
- You were first to realise they were shite.
- What's shite is what yous were playin'.
- We have to play that at weddings.
- What d'yeh call yourselves?
- And And And.
- And And fuckin' And?
Ray is thinkin' of an exclamation mark
after the second And.
- He says it'll look deadly on the posters.
- Yeh don't like it?
- D'yeh think it should go at the end?
- I think it should go up his arse.
We're not married to it.
Aah, no.
Dance, yeh bastard!
♪ I've looked at the ocean
♪ Tried hard to imagine
♪ The way you felt the day you sailed
♪ From Wester Ross to Nova Scotia!
♪ We should have helped you
♪ We should have told you
- Look at that eejit!
- That eejit's singin' somethin' like music.
Jimmy, we need direction.
If I'm the manager, Ray's not in the band.
- Why not?
- I don't like him. I never have.
- I hate him, to be honest with yeh.
- But he owns the synth.
No one uses synths any more.
It's back to basics.
Just as well, cos we've fuck-all else.
♪..railtrack
♪ From Miami to...
Jaysis!
- What the fuck is tha'?
- It's me hanky.
- Here yeh are, Imelda.
- Thanks.
What are yous lookin' at?
Nothin'.
- I'll have this washed for yeh, Jimmy.
- That's OK.
Wash it? I'd fuckin' frame it!
What does she see in him? He looks like
he models fuckin' knittin' patterns!
- Mothers love him.
- Why? He's a prick!
He's a prick with a job.
That band, Free Beer.
They always pull a big crowd.
- I like A Flock of Budgies.
- That's a stupid name.
It's better than bleedin' yours:
Cosmic Lino.
It has to be "The" something. All the best
Sixties bands were "The" somethings.
- We could be The Northsiders.
- Or The Liffey Lads?
How about The Fuckin' Eejits?
What kind of music are we
goin' to be playin', Jimmy?
- You're workin' class, right?
- Yeah, if there was any work.
Your music should be about
where you're from.
It should speak
the language of the streets.
It should be about struggle and sex.
And I don't mean mushy shite about
I'll love you till the end o' time.
I mean ridin', fuckin', tongues,
gooters, boxes. The works!
Jaysis! What kind of music says all that?
Soul.
Soul?
Soul! We're goin' to be
playing Dublin soul.
Dublin soul.
Fuckin' deadly!
Dublin soul, wha'?
Jimmy!
Dublin soul!
♪ In a window pane
♪ Do you remember
♪ How sweet it used to be?
♪ When we was together
♪ Everything was so... grand
♪ Now
♪ Now that we've parted
♪ You know there's one thing
♪ That I just can't stand
♪ I can't stand the rain
- Are you Mr Rabbitte?
- Yeah.
- I've come about the ad.
- What ad?
The one in the paper.
"Have you got soul? If so..."
Yeh have the wrong Rabbitte!
Can I have me paper back?
Fuck off!
Jimmy, I've more things to be doin'
than ironing shirts for you every day!
- What's this?
- What's what?
"Have you got soul? If so, the world's
hardest-working band is looking for you."
"Contact J Rabbitte. Rednecks and
southsiders need not apply."
- World's hardest-working band
- Was that someone about it?
- Where are you goin'? Finish your dinner.
- Out.
- Can I borrow your hairdryer?
- Go and shite!
- And leave my aftershave alone.
- Who was that at the door?
Some snotty-nosed fella
with a mouth organ.
- Yeh put an ad in the paper?
- I'm puttin' a band together.
D'yeh need a singer?
♪ Wise men say
♪ Only fools rush in
♪ But I can't help
♪ Falling in love
♪ With you
- ♪ Like the river flows...
- Elvis is not soul.
Elvis is God!
I never pictured God
with a fat gut in a corset
singing "My Way" at Caesar's Palace!
Don't upset your father.
- Who are your influences?
- Uh... Barry Manilow.
- Joan Baez... Joni Mitchell...
Wings...
Bachman Turner Overdrive?
Spandau Ballet. Soft Cell.
Sinéad O'Connor.
♪ It's a nice trip to a candy shop...
Hi, I've come about the audition.
Led Zeppelin.
Uh...
Billy and The Bollix.
U2?
♪ Well, the black folks are starvin'
♪ And the white trash is carpin'
♪ And the KKK's all over the TV
♪ Blood on the mirror,
and there was blood on your face!
♪ Look so good
♪ I've really done my best
♪ Powder, paint and lipstick
♪ The latest Paris dress
♪ Poppa, rumba, rumba,
hey, Poppa Joe, coconuts
♪ Poppa Joe, hey, Poppa Joe
♪ Yeah, hey... Poppa Joe
♪ Why didn't you tell me
you were bored!
♪ And still I dream he'll come to me
♪ That we will live the years together
♪ But there are dreams that cannot be
♪ In the haze of a drunken hour
- ♪ But heaven knows I'm miserable now
- Yeah, I know how yeh feel.
♪ Elvis was a Cajun
♪ He had a Cajun heart
♪ Had to move down to Memphis
- ♪ Cos that's where he got his start
- Fuckin' blasphemy! Elvis wasn't a Cajun!
♪ All that time in Graceland
and in Vegas, where he got huge
What d'yeh play?
I used to play football at school.
I mean what instrument?
I don't.
So what are yeh doin' here?
Well, I saw everybody else linin' up,
so... I thought yeh were sellin' drugs.
Hey, lads. This is Dean Fay.
Howayeh? Outspan Foster.
Derek Scully.
His influences are Clarence Clemons
and the guy from Madness.
- That's a nice sax.
- I haven't had it long.
Me uncle gave it to me
when his lung collapsed.
- This the band, is it?
- Yeah.
Bet U2 are shittin' themselves.
- Still got blue suede shoes, Mr Rabbitte?
- Fuck off, carrot-head!
♪ Who's sorry now?
Any chance for me, lads?
In your wildest dreams, Jimmy,
did yeh ever think you'd be this big?
To be honest, Terry, I did.
Even in the early days.
As big as The Rolling Stones?
Who the fuck are they, Terry?
- Who's in there with yeh?
- I'm being interviewed on television!
It's Colonel Jimmy Rabbitte now, wha'?
Interviewed on television!
He's interviewing himself!
- Yeah?
- Jimmy, there's another one.
Yeah?
- I saw the ad.
- Did yeh?
- Yeah. I'm a singer.
- Is that right? Let's hear yeh, then.
- Here?
- Yeah.
- Can I come inside?
- No.
- In the hall, even?
I can't sing. Not out here.
Fair enough. See yeh.
OK. Thanks.
♪ Only the lonely
♪ Know the way I feel tonight
♪ Know this feeling ain't right
I can't play for yis cos me drum kit's
in the pawnshop. But I'm good.
- Who are your influences?
- Animal in the Muppets.
Animal!
Jaysis!
- I used to play in a band.
- What did they do?
- Depeche Mode. Aztec Camera.
- Fuckin' art-school stuff.
- The Beatles went to art school.
- So did Roxy Music, and you liked them.
It's who it's aimed at. Wankers with funny
haircuts and rich dads with fuck-all to do.
That sounds like me arse.
But I'm sure you're right, Jimmy.
- Me boss has a truck I can get the use of.
- Could be handy, Billy.
Might help till we get a tour bus.
Hey! There's Imelda Quirke!
Fuck! Do you know her?
- Yeah.
- She was in our school.
- Oh, look at that body! She is beautiful!
- She's a little ride, isn't she?
Yeh'd think she'd be in a cocktail bar
sippin' drinks with umbrellas.
She's almost too perfect.
You mean you'd stand a chance
if she had bandy legs and a hump?
When this band's happenin',
you'll be fightin' women off.
Ohh! Rock'n'roll!
- You won't get that with And And And.
- We told Ray we left the band.
- How did he take it?
- Not too bad.
- He said he was goin' solo.
- Doesn't have much bleedin' choice!
- Howyeh, Bernie.
- Howayeh, Jimmy?
- How's things?
- Shite.
Gis a bag o' chips, will yeh?
I like the hair. Are yeh growing out
the Sinéad O'Connor?
Fuck off!
- D'yeh wanna be in a band?
- Wha'?
- Back-up singer, like.
- Me?
Why not? You used to sing
in the church choir. Lovely voice!
Fuck off! D'yeh want salt an' vinegar?
I'm serious. On the Bible.
I'm puttin' a band together. I need singers.
I'll think about it.
- How much is that?
- 50p.
Thanks.
Are you still friendly
with that, uh... Imelda?
Imelda Quirke?
Imelda Quirke. Will you ask her as well?
Yeah.
Thanks. See yeh.
Jimmy? Me friend Natalie's
got a great voice.
Good. Bring her.
But don't forget Imelda.
- OK. See yeh, Jimmy.
- See yeh.
What the fuck do they want Imelda Quirke
for? Fuckin' tits and arse -that's it.
Anyone sittin' here?
Doesn't look like it.
- How's the soup?
- Poxy.
- Anything worth eatin'?
- It's all poxy.
Me name's Jimmy Rabbitte. I'm puttin'
a band together. I need a singer.
Me?
Yeah! I heard yeh.
You've a rare pair o' lungs.
- Where'd yeh hear me singin'?
- The Quirke wedding.
I was pissed out o' me brains.
I had 14 rum an' blacks.
- You got up and sang.
- I did?
No one told me.
Hey, you!
Hey!
That's enough!
Had to see if he could play before I paid.
I'll be back at the end o' the month.
- That's what they all say.
- I will!
It's me ma's.
She thinks I'm havin' it cleaned.
Oi! Ginger!
Shut the fuck up, will yeh!
♪ I... I... I...
♪ I
♪ I can feel
♪ Love
♪ I love you so
- Can you sing that sort o' stuff?
- I can sing anythin'.
It's not the singin'. It's how he does it.
The showmanship.
Brilliant!
I'm not doin' that! I'd kneecap meself!
He's hurt, look. They're helpin' him off.
What'll they do now?
Bring on a substitute?
It's the act, lads. Watch.
- Five minutes, Jimmy.
- How are you, gorgeous?
Go an' shite!
That's what you've got to
measure up to, lads.
D'yeh not think, uh...
What?
Well, like... maybe we're
a little white for that kind o' thing.
D'yeh not get it, lads?
The Irish are the blacks of Europe.
And Dubliners are the blacks of Ireland.
And the northside Dubliners
are the blacks of Dublin.
So say it once, say it loud:
I'm black an' I'm proud!
♪ Now I know it's wrong
♪ The things I ask you to do
♪ But please believe me, darlin'
♪ I don't mean to hurt you
♪ But could you slip away
♪ Without him knowin' you're gone?
♪ Could you meet me somewhere?
♪ Take my hand
You must be gettin' desperate. Wait till
you see the little bollix askin' for yeh.
♪ Take my whole life too
♪ One, two, cha-cha-cha
Yeah?
God bless you, Brother Rabbitte.
Your band need a trumpet?
You're the same age as me da!
You may speak the truth.
But I'm 16 years younger than BB King.
- You've heard of BB King?
- I jammed with the man.
Piss off!
Leicester Mecca, 1972. Didn't give it me
best, though. Had a bit of a head cold.
What's your name, pal?
Joseph Fagan.
Joey "The Lips" Fagan.
And I'm Jimmy "The Bollix" Rabbitte!
I earned me name for me horn playin'.
What did you earn yours for?
- Don't get snotty with me, son.
- I get snotty with no man.
- You played with BB King?
- Among others, brother.
- Like?
- Have we got all day?
Screamin' Jay Hawkins. Martha Reeves.
Sam Cooke.
Poor Sam.
Otis Redding. May the Lord
have mercy on his sweet soul.
Joe Tex. The Four Tops. Stevie Wonder.
He was only 11. A pup.
- Wilson Pickett...
- Why are yeh in Dublin?
I'm tired of the road.
And me mammy isn't very well.
- Why would yeh want to join us?
- The Lord sent me
and the Lord blows my trumpet.
- What did Evel Knievel want?
- God sent him.
- What?
On a fuckin' Suzuki?
Jaysis!
He can play. That's for sure.
- The Lord doesn't like it if we whisper.
- Why? Is he deaf?
I didn't join this band to sing
Moon fuckin' River.
It's merely my favourite lip-loosener.
We'll be playin' soul.
See, the Lord told me the Irish brothers
needed some soul. Well, Ed Winchell,
a Baptist reverend on Lenox Avenue
in Harlem, told me.
But the Lord told him to tell me.
He said the Irish brothers wouldn't be
shootin' the arses off each other
if they had... soul.
I can't figure him out, Jimmy. He talks
like a priest and he's wearin' slippers!
He's played with all the greats.
Even The Beatles.
- The Beatles?
- Yeah.
♪ All you need is love!
♪ Da-da-da-da-da!
That was Joey.
- What's Steven Clifford doin' here? He's...
- What?
A medical student.
He's not like the rest of us.
Could be useful to have someone
that could bandage heads.
I'm worried about
the direction we're takin'.
Direction?! What magazines
you been readin', yeh tosser?
Look, with Joey and me,
we can touch greatness.
So if you want to be part of it, take in
the tea, and I'll bring in the Jaffa Cakes.
- It's the fuckin' Addams Family!
- The Addams Family!
Hold on, girls.
I think I've got a ladder in me tights.
Imelda! Come on!
Who the fuck will be lookin' at
your fuckin' thigh, yeh fuckin' eejit!
- Look at the size of that fuckin' doorknob!
- Fuckin' huge!
I hope some o' these fuckin' fellas
are gonna be rides.
- Are you sure this is the right place?
- I've never been here before!
- Who told yeh? It was Jimmy, was it?
- Fuck, I don't know.
Um... sorry. We were lookin' for a band.
Oh! That's my boy Joey's.
They're out the back.
Joey says no rehearsals till you get
friendly with your instruments.
- Friendly with mine already.
- Shut up, Declan.
Deco. If I'm gonna front the band,
I like the sound o' Deco.
Deco the bus conductor.
Is that top Deco or bottom Deco?
The only bollixin' thing that's important
is what this band's called.
Joey knows. Tell them.
We are...
At the end of the garden
you'll find a ladder.
- A ladder?
- Yes.
- Right. Thank you.
- You're welcome, girls.
- What are yeh gettin' us into, Bernie?
- Fuck off, Natalie! We've come this far!
Over here?
Over the top! Over the top!
I'm not goin' over the fuckin' ladder!
You're over the fuckin' ladder!
You know 'em. You go.
The Commitments?
- The Commitments?
It's a "The".
How do you spell it?
T-H-E.
It's very good. It's a statement.
- I still like A Flock of Budgies.
- Fuck me!
I just seen Imelda Quirke's arse
comin' down a ladder!
Lads, you're lookin' at
The Commitmentettes.
The Commitment-tits, yeh mean!
Brilliant management, Brother Rabbitte.
Will they be dressed in black?
What are you bleedin' lookin' at?
♪ Destination anywhere
♪ East or west, I don't care
From now on, I don't want you listenin'
to Guns N' Roses an' The Soup Dragons.
I want a strict diet of James Brown for
the growls, Otis Redding for the moans,
Smokey Robinson for the whines,
and Aretha for the whole lot put together.
- Jimmy says soul is sex.
- Dirty bastard!
I said the rhythm of soul
is the rhythm of ridin'.
You want us to sing as if
we were ridin' with someone?
You can practise with me.
I'd bite your bollix off, yeh spotty fuck!
- Might fancy that.
- Or make earrings out o' them!
Soul is the rhythm of sex.
Rhythm of the factory, too.
The working man's rhythm.
Sex and the factory.
Not in the factory I'm in.
Not much rhythm in guttin' fish!
Soul is the music that people understand.
It's basic and it's simple.
But it's somethin' else. Somethin' special.
Cos... cos it's honest.
It's honest. There's no fuckin' bullshit.
It says it straight from the heart.
There's lots of music yeh can get off on,
but... soul is more than that.
It takes yeh somewhere else. It grabs you
by the balls and lifts you above the shite.
♪ Said to the man at the railroad station
♪ I want a ticket
♪ Just for one
♪ He said: Well, if you insist
♪ But where you wanna go, miss?
♪ Oh-oh
♪ Destination anywhere
♪ East or west, I don't care
♪ You see, my baby don't
want me no more
♪ And this old world ain't got
♪ No back door
Howayeh, Duffy?
This is Jimmy.
Howayeh?
- Glad that dog's got a muzzle.
- Have to. He keeps eatin' me bunnies.
- So you've got a band?
- Yeah.
I don't know why you bother. Everything's
shite since Roy Orbison died.
- What are yeh short of?
- I need a power amp, speakers, a desk,
an' a few bits and pieces.
It's all here in the... note.
That's no problem. How are yeh payin'?
I can give you 50 now,
some when we get the gear,
an' the rest when we do our first gig.
Most bands in Dublin don't last
more than one gig, son.
- D'yeh need anythin' else? Bit o' blow?
- No.
Oh, me ma would like one o' those things
that wakes you up with a cup o' tea.
♪ Nowhere to run to, baby
♪ Nowhere to hide
♪ Got nowhere to run to, baby
♪ It's not love I'm runnin' from
♪ Just the heartbreak I know will come
♪ Cos I know you're no good for me
I'm black an' I'm proud.
♪ Everywhere I go
♪ Your face I see
♪ Every step I take
♪ You take with me, yeah
♪ Each night as I sleep
♪ Into my heart
♪ You creep
♪ I wake up feelin' sorry I met you
♪ Hopin' soon that I'll forget you
♪ When I look in the mirror
♪ To comb my hair
♪ I see your face just smilin' there, yeah
♪ Nowhere to run to, baby
♪ Nowhere to hide
♪ Got nowhere to run to, baby
♪ I know you're no good for me
♪ But you've become a part of me
- What? When can I stop?
- When your hand falls off.
♪ How can I fight a love
♪ That shouldn't be?
♪ And it's... so deep
♪ So dee-eep
♪ Deep inside of me
♪ My love's reachin' so high
- How's it goin', Cave?
- Howyeh, Jimmy.
- Long time no see.
- Long time no hear.
♪ I can't get around it, no
♪ Nowhere to run
♪ Nowhere to hide
♪ From you, baby
♪ Just can't get away from you, baby
- Jesus, it's brilliant!
- Just leave it in the state you found it.
- How long's your boss away for?
- Only two months.
Unless he gets time off
for good behaviour.
♪ Nowhere to run to, baby
♪ Nowhere to hide
♪ Got nowhere to run to, baby
- Look at this place!
- The ceiling's beautiful!
Jaysis!
- Pigeons and everything! Great
- Lovely spot!
I haven't got any bleedin' cigarettes!
- Where'd you get this piano?
- It's me granny's.
- That was nice of her.
- She doesn't know I took it.
But she doesn't use
the front room very often.
Ow!
Up! Up!
Lift it!
Two. Two.
Two! Two!
Two! Two! Two! Two!
Two!
- Where'd yeh get the gear?
- Don't ask.
Fuckin' rapid!
- Are yeh ready, Steven?
- Yeah, ready.
Two, two! One, two!
That's enough!
OK, Joey, we can't put this thing off
for ever. Let's get busy.
Mustang Sally, brothers and sisters. And
Rome wasn't built in a day.
- Dublin was.
- In an hour!
One, two, three, four!
One, two!
♪ Mustang Sally
♪ Guess you better slow
that Mustang down
♪ Mustang Sally now, baby
♪ Guess you better slow
that Mustang down
♪ Oooooh... ooh!
♪ Well, I guess you gotta put
your flat feet on the ground
♪ All you wanna do is ride around, Sally
♪ Ride, Sally, ri...
Hold it, hold it.
Hold it!
Now, sisters, that's where you
all come in. Ride around, Sally.
♪ Ride, Sally, ride
- Sorry.
- I'm scarlet!
Again.
♪ All you wanna do is ride around, Sally
♪ Ride, Sally, ride
♪ Roid, Sally, roid
Look, don't use your own accents.
It's ride, Sally, ride. Not roid, Sally, roid.
♪ Ride, Sally, ride
From the top.
♪ Mustang Sally
♪ Guess you better slow
that Mustang down
♪ Mustang Sally now, baby
- What were you playin'?
- C, F and G.
You weren't. It's not the chords, anyway.
- What are they, then?
- C, F, C, C.
- You'd look better without your glasses.
- I'm blind without my glasses.
So was Ray Charles.
Your drumming's coming along, Billy.
Have yeh been practising?
Me da's dead and
me brothers are younger.
So?
So there's no one to tell me
to shut the fuck up.
Look at him!
- He eats like a pig.
- He's such a prick!
Hasn't got the voice of a prick, though.
Joey says it belongs to God.
God should ask for it back.
- I suppose Jimmy'll groom him.
- Teach him to use a knife and fork.
- Are you all choir girls, then?
- What if we are?
Well, you've got fair voices,
but you're not putting much of that into it.
Good Jaysis!
All mouth and bollix!
- I bet he's never done the business.
- I bet he does it every night.
Get me share.
That's why you don't play guitar. You've
lost the muscles in your right hand!
Are yeh doin' what I told you? Are you
thinkin' of that reed as a woman's nipple?
- I am, yeah.
- Do you mind me askin' who she is?
She lives across the street from me. But I
feel embarrassed. She's still at school.
Maybe you should set
your sights a little higher.
My trumpet was always Gina Lollobrigida.
- I've never heard of her.
- A fine woman!
I could try, uh... Kim Basinger.
Is she...?
Ohh! Yeah!
Good.
Pick a nipple and try it again.
♪ One of these early mornings
♪ Oh, I'm gonna be wipin'
your weepin' eyes
♪ Yeah
♪ All you wanna do is ride around, Sally
♪ Ride, Sally, ride
♪ One of these early mornings
♪ I'm gonna be wipin' your weepin' eyes
♪ Yeah
♪ Oh, sweet ba-a-abe!
♪ Yeah!
OK, everyone. We're gettin' there,
no question. Let's call it a night.
That was a load o' shite.
It was woeful,
but that boy can sing.
And it was a start. I believe in starts. Once
you have the start, the rest is inevitable.
All right, folks, we've done good work
tonight. Will you form a circle, please?
You too, Jimmy.
Come on, come on. Just form a circle.
Now, everybody turn right.
Now let's pat ourselves on
the back for a job well done!
Mr Rabbitte, you've been collecting
unemployment benefit for two years.
Are you telling me you can't get a job?
We're a Third World country.
What can yeh do?
- Jimmy! Howayeh?
- Dean! Didn't know you were on the dole.
- Three months now. How about yourself?
- Lost count. Yeh know how it is.
- See you at Joey's. Tuesday, is it?
- Yeah, Tuesday.
See yeh there.
Jimmy! It feels much better
bein' an unemployed musician
than an unemployed pipe fitter!
Check that horn.
You?
Joey The Lips.
This is an all-star album. Very rare.
I'll get a pen, and then
I can autograph it for yis.
He's full of it.
Look, that's Joey there,
next to Otis Redding.
That could be anybody.
All yeh can see is the trumpet.
Look at this, then. "Trumpet, J Fagan."
- Ah, it's a very common name.
- Not in Detroit.
He's played with all the
greats, then? Your Joey?
Oh, yes, indeed.
He was in America for years!
But I'll tell you something that
nobody knows about my Joey.
Wherever he went, or wherever he played,
he always sent me a postcard.
♪ Yeah, yeah
♪ They say it's a man's world
♪ Oh, but you can't prove that by me
Excuse me. Is this Bluebell Way?
No, this is Marigold.
Bluebell's over there an' to the left.
♪ Show some respect for me
♪ If you wanna do right...
Hey!
What?
- You're not takin' that into the lift?
- I have to. The stairs would kill him.
- Hello, Mrs McGloughlin. Is Bernie in?
- She is. Come on in, will yeh?
Close that door.
- Howyeh, Bernie.
- Howayeh, Jimmy?
If Jimmy wants tea,
you've to make it yourself.
Oh, I'm not bothered, thanks.
Move that washing
if yeh want to sit down.
Bernie, you've been missin' rehearsals.
You can see why! Me ma can't work -
she's about to drop another one.
Me da's in the fuckin' hospital.
I'm the only one bringin' any money in.
- It's tough, I know, but...
- What?
It's hard when only two
backup singers show up.
You're not dumpin' me.
I brought in the other two.
Or is that why yeh fuckin' asked me?
You've got the best voice
o' the three of yis!
Bollix! You just wanted to get
your paws on Imelda Quirke.
Watch the fuckin'...! Yeh fuckin' bollix,
yeh! Go and fuckin' play!
Look at the bloody mess yeh made!
Look, Jimmy, I'll catch up.
I need this band more than any of us.
I need somethin' to look forward to.
A lot o' work.
If you didn't do it for God,
who would you do it for?
- Steven!
- Jimmy. Father Molloy will be here soon.
- Great sound, wha'?
- Yeah.
I wish my granny had
one of these we could borrow.
- Great intro, uh?
- They nicked it from Marvin Gaye.
He nicked it from Bach!
Ah, it's beautiful.
♪ We skipped the light fantastic
♪ Skipped the light fandango!
♪ Turned cartwheels 'cross the floor
♪ I was feeling kinda seasick
♪ But the crowd called out for more
Poxiest bleedin' lyrics ever written.
One of sixteen vestal virgins leaving
for the coast. What's that mean?
I never understood that, either.
It's a very peculiar lyric.
Howayeh, Father?
Did you talk to the committee?
I have, and they've agreed in principle.
It would have to be the 28th
because Danny, our bingo caller,
is going into hospital to have
a tap put in his kidneys.
28th. No problem.
I'm sure you'll blow their minds, Jimmy!
Look here, girls. Take this advice.
And remember always in life:
♪ Into each heart
♪ Some tears must fall
♪ Though you love and lose
♪ You must stand tall
♪ Cos... we've all got to cry sometimes
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
- ♪ I said sigh sometimes
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
- ♪ Pull yourself together
♪ No use crying for ever
♪ Because there's
♪ Too many fish in the sea
♪ I said there's short ones
♪ Tall ones
♪ Too many fish in the sea
You're supposed to come in.
All right, we'll take a break.
You're gettin' there, girls.
It's not just how you sing, it's how
you move. You're sex machines.
My ma would crease me
if she thought I was a sex machine!
- Greg wouldn't complain, would he!
- Piss off, you!
- Whose turn is it to get the hamburgers?
- Sweet child, it'll be my pleasure.
I'll come with yeh, Joey.
- If they're singin', what am I to do?
- Play with yourself!
Sing along.
You've bigger tits than all o' them.
Fuck you!
Oh, Jaysis!
- Here.
- What are you starin' at?
Nothin', Joey.
You fairly ruffled my savoir-faire
there, Dean, my man.
- I thought you were goin' for the burgers.
- I am gone, Dean.
♪ You're gonna want my love someday
♪ Well-a bye, bye, baby
- You've organised a gig?
- Yeah.
- Where?
- Community centre.
That's a desperate place! Full of old-age
pensioners learnin' ballroom dancin'!
- It's a room with a stage.
- How much will it cost?
Nothin'. We told Father Molloy
it's part of his anti-heroin campaign.
I can get my little brother to do a poster.
The 28th is no time away.
We've two songs.
All we need is another ten.
Ten?!
You'll never believe what I just seen!
Joey and Natalie gettin' it off on the stairs!
- I'm tellin' the truth!
- Knob off! What if she was?
- It's Natalie's business!
- Tongues, was it?
- Yeah!
- He's got terrible breath!
- Lads, it's a free country.
- But he's old and he's ugly.
You're young and you're uglier.
You'd get off with Joan Collins
quick enough, and she's 50!
And you'd do it with Tina Turner,
and she's a granny!
Joey's not married, so fair fucks to him.
Yous are all so fuckin' stupid!
Natalie got off with him!
- Then she's a slut.
- Fuck you, yeh fat fucker!
Me knee! Ohh, Jaysis!
OK. Let's have a look at it.
Hey, that's really good!
But there's only one E in heroin.
- Wha'?
- There's no E at the end of heroin.
You little bollix!
There's only one E in heroin!
- No, there isn't.
- Yes, there is!
- The syringe is good, though.
- No one round here can spell.
Today, St Bridget's Community Centre.
Tomorrow... oblivion.
Where's Oblivion?
Jimmy! Jimmy! Mickah Wallace
wants to see yeh. He's in the pub.
- Mickah Wallace?!
- I hired him to do the door. Security.
- You're mad, Jimmy! He's a savage!
- I know he is. But he's our savage.
- He'll fuck off with the money!
- Shh! Dean!
Sorry, Father.
One! Two!
One! Two! Testin'!
That's a good strong mike, that.
Quality's very rare these days.
Are yeh sure now? Two pounds to
come in. Half-price to the unwaged.
Got it.
Ben Nevis on the stand side! Come on,
Ben Nevis! Lester's out the saddle!
Shit! He's just fallen and croaked.
And now I want to sing for yis.
♪ Tell me why I don't like Mondays!
- I've a bugle here you can blow on.
- I've an arse here you can kiss!
Where's me knob? I know I tucked it
into me sock before I came out!
- I can't get this hair to stay down.
- These suits are a waste o' money.
- He's upset cos it hides his tattoos.
- All Motown brothers wore suits.
Neat. Dignified.
You'll play better in your suit.
- But I can't lift me sax in this jacket.
- Swap it with Outspan, then.
- D'yeh mind?
- No.
Fuckin' monkey suit.
I haven't worn one since that weddin'.
- I puked on mine. Remember?
- Remember? Some of it got on me.
Are yeh decent? We're comin' out!
I didn't recognise meself!
I hope I don't need a piss in this dress.
I'd never get it back on again!
There'd be plenty of volunteers to help!
Will they be eatin' chips
out of our knickers?
I wouldn't say no!
It's £2.
Howyeh doin', Mrs Foster?
Outspan's up on the stage.
Any messin' and I'll kill yeh, right?
- What's wrong?
- He's bein' sick!
Don't be nervous. Don't be nervous.
Come on. It'll be all right.
Sweet Jaysis!
She promised me she wouldn't come!
- Who?
- Me ma!
- I'm not goin' on.
- Go and find Mickah. He'll get him on.
My ma would beat the shite
out o' Mickah Wallace any day!
Shh! Shut the fuck up!
Ladies and gentlemen...
Put your working-class hands together
for the saviours of soul,
the hardest-working band
in the world! Yes! Yes, yes!
The Commitments!
Wrong rope, Brother Rabbitte.
Ladies and gentlemen,
The Commitments!
Get the fuck off!
- Hurry up!
- Who said that?
Brother Billy.
- Wha'?
- When you're ready.
Oh, shit! Yeah.
If I catch you messin', you're out!
♪ They call me Mr Pitiful
♪ Baby, that's my name
♪ That's how I got my fame
♪ But nobody seems to understand now
♪ What makes a man feel so blue
♪ Ohh, they call me Mr Pitiful
♪ Cos I lost someone just like you
♪ They call me Mr Pitiful
♪ Most everybody knows now
♪ Most every place I go now
♪ But nobody seems to understand now
♪ What makes a man
sing such a sad song
♪ Ohh, when he lost everything
♪ When he lost everything
Hello, Dublin!
I hope yous like me group!
- Fuck off!
- Yeh prick!
♪ How can I explain to you
♪ Somebody actin' so very blue?
♪ How can I tell you about my thing?
♪ Oh, nothin' to do
♪ Mr Pitiful!
- You'll apologise to the girls!
- We're not your bleedin' group!
Come on, get it back! Get it back!
Fuckin' bastard!
♪ Cos nobody seems to understand now
♪ What makes a man
sing such a sad song
♪ Oh, when he lost everythin'
♪ When he lost everythin'
♪ We-ell
♪ Your love was
♪ Sweeter than
♪ Any I know
♪ So-oh-oh
♪ Don't come back
♪ Runnin' or
♪ Knockin' on my front door
♪ Well, you said that I
♪ Was your only girl
♪ Do-do
♪ There ain't no other
♪ Do-do, do-do
♪ In the whole wide world
♪ You know you took my love
♪ Threw it away
♪ You're gonna want my love someday
♪ Well-a bye bye, baby
♪ Bye bye, bye bye
♪ Goodbye, goodbye, baby
♪ Bye bye
♪ Bye bye bye, baby
♪ Bye bye, baby
♪ Goodbye, goodbye
♪ Bye bye, bye bye
♪ Bye bye
♪ Well, goo-ood-bye now
♪ Ba-a-a-by
- Mam says to give us some money.
- For what?
- Crisps and Cokes.
- Are yeh stayin' over there?
Yeah. They're great.
- You're jokin'!
- No! They're really good!
Are yeh serious?
Ow! Jesus Christ, Tommy!
Me fuckin' head!
- Here. How much do yeh want?
- A pound.
For crisps and Coke?
Go on.
♪ Aaahh, show me a man
that's got a good woman
♪ Show me
♪ Show me a man out there
who's got a good woman
♪ Show me
♪ Show me a man that's
got a good woman
got a good woman!
♪ Show me a man that's
got a good woman
♪ I'll show you a man that
goes to work hummin'
♪ You know he's got
some sweet lovin' comin'
♪ At the end of his workin' day
♪ Yeah
♪ Show me a woman
that's got a good man
♪ Show me
♪ I wanna see a woman out there
claims she's got a good man