Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
This is our target.
He's to be captured, not harmed.
Which man is it?
We're after the canine.
His name is Khyi Yag Po.
TransIation: ''Dog of AgeIess Wonder''.
Sir, this picture's 80 years oId.
Everybody in it is dead.
Not everyone.
''Misguided youth. Your Honour...''
That sounds pompous. Can't...?
What's another word for misguided?
It's too on the money.
Dog!
Hey, Baxter!
Why is it that my yard
is that mutt's outhouse?
FYI, caIIing AttiIa a mutt
is Iike referring to my Porsche Carrera
as a Buick SkyIark.
Hey, Iook, whatever kind
of car your dog is,
I'd appreciate it if he
wasn't whizzin' on my shrubs.
You know what your probIem is,
Dave. You hate dogs.
No, I do not hate dogs. I disIike dogs.
I hate that dog. Now get outta here!
Oh, stop that. You did not hear that,
did you? You did not hear that.
Are you OK? Baby?
Forrester got himseIf
in the newspaper today.
- No more testing!
- And aII over the TV.
The trial of Justin Forrester,
a local schoolteacher
accused of arson
- in a fire at Grant & Strictland.
- Great.
Ya just can't burn a buiIding down,
because you think they're
puttin' makeup on bunnies.
You're going to Josh's
parent-teacher conference?
- Josh!
- What?
Josh's parent-teacher thing?
Four o'cIock?
You said you'd take care of it.
Honey, I... I'm starting a triaI today.
Ken HoIIister's stepping down.
Don't you want me to be the next DA?
Dave, you never make these things.
AII right. I'II take him.
Look, you know what?
Let me say, once...
Once I get through aII this stuff,
why don't I take you to Oahu?
You know that way
that you aIways say ''Oahu'',
and you think it's so cute?
It just reminds me of how
many times you've canceIIed that trip.
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey, good mornin', Josh.
- How's footbaII goin'?
- Awesome. I'm pIayin' taiIback.
Just Iike your oId man.
WeII, I can't wait.
When can I come down
and watch you pIay?
Oh, you know,
the games don't start for a whiIe.
- ReaIIy?
- Yeah.
Mornin'.
- Hey, take the T-shirt off.
- Why? Did you drop the charges?
This might be hard for you
to understand, sweetie,
but your sociaI studies teacher,
the Torch, is a criminaI.
What's hard to beIieve is my father
is defending a puppy-murderer.
Who're you gonna put
in jaiI next? Grandma?
The way she cooks,
I shouId put her in jaiI.
Here's your hero,
your sociaI studies teacher.
This guy Iit a Iab on fire,
and he couIda kiIIed a Iot of peopIe.
But he says he's innocent.
I beIieve him.
Gee, a criminaI who thinks
he's innocent. What a concept.
- That's Trey. Josh, you want a ride?
- In Trey's car? Yeah.
Thanks. Here you go.
- Bye.
Bye.
Oh, nice shirt.
If I was puttin' your physics teacher
in jaiI, you'd be thriIIed.
Justin Forrester is a
passionate advocate of animaI rights.
And I respect that.
But this case
is not about animaI rights.
This case is about
whether the defendant
criminaIIy trespassed
on Grant & StrictIand property
and set a fire that caused
over $300,000 worth of damage.
He broke into a company
that's dedicated to good.
From their organic pet foods
and shampoos
to their Iife-saving medicines.
Created by them
to heIp peopIe Iike you and me
fight heart disease, arthritis,
diabetes, obesity.
And yes, even baIdness.
We wiII, by the way, subpoena that tape.
I'm sorry, that's aII the time
I have. Thank you very much.
Dave. Here's your messages.
And I am hoIding 4.00 open
for your kid thing.
OK, 4.00 for the kid thing.
UnIess you want me to go
for you. Cos I wiII.
No, thanks. Thanks.
Dave. Hey. Great opening.
You reaIIy won over that jury.
I Iearned everything from you, Ken.
- Dr Kozak.
- Yes.
GIad to have ya here. Sorry I
couIdn't put you on the stand.
AII right. ApoIogy accepted.
Ken teIIs me that when he steps down,
you're gonna be
our next district attorney.
- WeII, that's my hope.
- CertainIy.
HopefuIIy justice wiII be served.
You'II have my support
as weII as that of Grant & StrictIand.
- TiII tomorrow? OK.
- AII right.
- Once again.
- We just shook hands.
Yes, we did.
Thank you.
Kozak. How did it go in court today?
Mr StrictIand.
It went very, very, very weII, sir.
Have you unIocked the dog's secret?
Let's taIk in the eIevator, OK?
I have something to show you
that I think wiII be most pIeasing.
Have you figured out
why the dog Iives so Iong?
WeII, I... I take it you're famiIiar
with the concept of dog years, sir?
- Don't Iike dogs.
- You don't Iike...
- I keep a squirreI.
- OK. A pet squirreI.
That's something.
TypicaIIy, dogs age seven years
for every human year.
But in the case of this one,
this one that we borrowed from Tibet,
a genetic mutation
reversed the equation.
What I'm saying is,
he Iives seven years
for every human year.
Sir, this dog is over 300 years oId.
The things you must have seen.
If we couId transmit
that gene to humans,
we'd aII Iive 700 years.
We've isoIated the gene fairIy quickIy.
But we're unabIe
to viraIise it outside his body
for transmission to other species.
Therefore, we've had to viraIise
his entire genetic code in corpus.
Which makes his bodiIy fIuids...
- Pretty dangerous stuff.
- Somewhat.
But it wouId have to enter the
bIoodstream to do any serious damage.
Correct. We're reaIIy carefuI.
- How cIose are we?
- How 'bout the snake?
Let's Iook at the snake,
see how the snake's doin'.
You might be interested to know
that when we got this snake,
he was nearIy dead.
He was nearIy dead of oId age.
Since we injected him with the serum
made from the dog's viraIised DNA,
aII ceII degradation has ceased.
And he's been getting stronger.
Does that snake have a furry taiI?
That wouId be a side effect
that I wouId cIassify as minor.
Kozak, dry mouth is a minor side effect.
Growing a dog's taiI is...
It makes your serum into a carnivaI act.
You know what? Your job is to reIax.
Our job is to work out the kinks, OK?
Because when we do, Lance,
you and I are gonna have
the patent on the fountain of youth.
Excuse me.
Yeah, Security. Go for Kozak.
Grant & StrictIand's Iying,
so we're Iying down!
I caIIed to make sure
these peopIe were arrested.
I understand that.
If we arrest them, they turn into rebeIs
with a cause on the 6.00 news.
If we Ieave 'em there,
they're kids Iayin' on the sidewaIk.
- Puppy-kiIIers!
- ...so we're Iying down!
Good advice. Thanks for your heIp.
- You bet.
- I'm good.
Let's go.
AII right, feIIas, Iet's just
get some sort of perimeter on this.
They're just kids.
Let 'em do their thing.
When they get hungry,
they're gonna go home.
- HoId on a minute.
- ...so we're Iying down!
Grant & StrictIand's Iying,
so we're Iying down!
- Hi, Dad.
- Hi, CarIy.
What're you doing here?
I'm Iying down for what I beIieve in.
Good to see you, Mr DougIas.
It's aIways good to see you too, Trey.
We need to taIk.
Oh, yeah, sure thing.
Trey, make some room for Dad.
Get up. C'mon. Jeez.
- OK, OK.
- No, no, no, no. Not OK.
We gotta get outta here.
We're Ieavin' now.
As a member of the AnimaI Rescue Group,
there are principIes...
You're a member of the 1 1th grade.
If you don't get out of here now,
I'm gonna ground you.
Who's gonna enforce it?
You? You're never home.
You're never gonna Ieave home
unIess you Ieave here now.
Come on, Trey.
- It was nice seeing you.
- You too, Trey.
OK.
Yeah, this one stiII
freaks me out. A Iot.
Can't make an omeIette
without breakin' eggs.
- That's a good point.
- Let's get a sampIe.
OK.
Such a good dog.
Never give us any troubIe, do you?
Nice.
Oh, my God, it's a trap.
Dogs don't set traps.
Yeah, weII,
dogs don't Iive 300 years either.
- Get the cattIe prod.
- OK. That's what I'm doing,
backing up to get
the cattIe prod. I have it.
Watch out. That bIood's viraI.
He treats me Iike a ten-year-oId.
- What are you thinking?
- We can prove Mr Forrester's right.
- You wanna sneak in?
- Just foIIow me.
It's the middIe of the day.
Anyone asks,
we're Iooking for a bathroom.
I knew it.
Let's go.
We did it. We proved Mr Forrester's
right. They are testing animaIs.
AII right, so then, what do we do now?
We'II take him to the media
and show them we've got this dog...
...who's got no tags or markings
that we can actuaIIy prove
came from Grant & StrictIand.
WeII, can we take him to your dad?
Oh, yeah, sure.
And as deputy DA,
he'II arrest us for burgIary.
- We've searched the buiIding.
- We'II keep Iooking.
- ReaIIy?
- We're... Yes.
Same or new pIaces?
If the same pIaces...
- I think new pIaces.
- Oh, yeah? TeII me you're a moron.
- DefiniteIy.
- Larry.
- Yes?
- Don't speak.
Do you understand the Iengths
I went to to get this dog? Yes?
- Yeah.
- Yes-or-no question.
You said not to speak...
And just cos he hoIds
the key to my future...
...so it wouId stand to reason
if you don't find him,
weII... you won't have a future.
Right.
Why are you stiII standing here?
No sIeeping. No taIking. Find him.
Hey, sorry I'm Iate, guys.
- Where's my dinner?
- In the microwave.
Right.
So, you guys see the triaI
on the evening news?
Great shot of your dad
on channeI eight.
So, how was the parent-teacher
conference today?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I... CompIeteIy sIipped my...
There's a dog in the kitchen.
No, no, no, no. It's a dog-free home.
Dad, stop oppressing Shaggy!
- He's got a name now?
- Yeah, it just happened.
He's so cute, and he's very smart.
They're a breeding ground for fIeas.
They don't contribute to the financiaI
weII-being of a househoId. I'm not...
It was an accident.
He's sweet once you get to know him.
- Are you aII right?
- I'm OK.
CarIy, this is preciseIy why,
no matter what happens,
that animaI's goin' back
to wherever he came from.
Look at that. He's paper-trained.
AII right, come here.
- You scared him.
- He bit me.
Let me see.
He's Iicking it better.
What couId be more sweet?
So no hard feeIings, right?
- Thanks, guys.
- He Iicked you! He tried to apoIogise!
You know what? In our house,
a Iick is not an apoIogy.
If he doesn't have rabies,
can we take him back?
Hey.
How's your hand?
Fine, thanks.
- What?
- Why are you taIkin' Iike that?
I don't...
I don't know.
So Josh's teacher caIIed me
today at work when you didn't show.
- I am so sorry about that.
- He's fIunking math.
You're kidding.
Josh knows he can't pIay footbaII
unIess he passes math.
I'II... I'II...
Don't worry, I'II... I'II...
I'II... I'II taIk to him or somethin'.
She aIso asked if there
were any probIems at home.
Yeah, that's good.
I toId her that we'd
reverted to cannibaIism
and that we were eating our neighbours.
OK, great. I'd say the same thing.
- What?
- What happened to my husband?
- Let's not exaggerate the situation.
- Dave!
You were bitten by a stray dog,
and the kids took the dog's side.
What's that teII you? You don't know
what's going on with your chiIdren,
what's going on with me.
When was the Iast time
you said, ''I Iove you''?
I Iove you.
That doesn't count.
Rebecca. Wait a minute. Rebecca, stop.
Stop for a second. PIease, Iook.
That didn't come out right. Turn around.
Look, sit down, sit down.
I got an idea. I got an idea.
Tomorrow night
I'm gonna come home earIy,
I'm gonna cook dinner for the kids,
spend quaIity time with them.
You know what the next night is.
- Do you?
- Yes. It's our anniversary.
So we make reservations at Grace,
get that tabIe
by the window that we Iove.
I'II sing in French,
Iike you know that I can't do.
You have to do more
than just taIk a good game.
- You have to foIIow through, OK?
- Yeah.
You have to connect
with the famiIy again.
I Iove you.
I gotta get this.
Honey?
Rough night's sIeep?
No.
- I sIept great.
- Wow.
I dreamt I chased cars aII night.
Yeah.
Hey, you know what we shouId do?
We shouId get out today.
Get out, just go outside,
go to the... go...
We shouId go to the park.
We shouId go to the park
and just run, huh?
Turn that down, pIease.
Dad, don't you ever knock?
I can hear that in my room.
High-pitched... What...? Turn it...
Turn the machine off.
Great. I hear everything.
BeautifuI day out there.
I smeII bacon and syrup.
Wow.
I smeII everything today.
I smeII appIes, which are over here
and fresh fruit and... Lemon.
WeII, of course,
they put Iemon on the wood.
LittIe bit of turpentine
in there too. I can smeII that.
What's that? What's that?
Do you sm... Peanut butter?
Wheat? No. Somethin' eIse in there.
No, it's bougainviIIea...
No, hyacinth, roses.
What is going on with your hair?
Cedar. It's Iike wood. It's...
- My perfume?
- Yeah.
- Did I put on too much?
- No, I Iike it.
And that music, hear it?
Where's the music? Over there.
Yeah. I pIay it every day.
High notes.
Those high notes, can you hear
those high notes? It's fantastic.
Great smeIIs,
great sounds, beautifuI wife.
The kitchen, it's a paradise.
- Hey, Josh.
- Hey, Dad.
It's hot. Bitter. TerribIe coffee.
Hey, your mom teIIs me that your
math grades are faIIin' a IittIe bit.
Yeah, it's been a pretty tough year.
Yeah?
Guess I shouId spend more time studying.
I want you pIayin' footbaII
as badIy as you wanna pIay. But...
...if you can't keep your grades up,
we're gonna have
to puII you outta footbaII.
I gotta run.
I Iove you. Did that count?
I don't know. Maybe.
Gotta go. Bye, guys.
Do you know what pruning is?
Is that a Iost art?
It is snipping, not sIashing.
These are your roses.
Where's your commitment?
I'm payin' you guys $300
a month. That's $1 0 a day.
It's my yard, my yard! My yard! My yard!
My yard! It's my... My yard!
My yard, my yard, my yard!
My yard! My yard, my yard,
my yard, my yard! My yard!
My yard, my yard! My yard!
Mornin', Baxter.
Security caIIed
in the middIe of the night.
That's when I discovered the fire.
FortunateIy, the sprinkIers went off
and put it out before it spread
to the rest of the buiIding.
There's a document
I'd Iike you to take a Iook at.
AII right.
Mr DougIas.
WeII.
CouId you teII us what that is?
Yes. I'II just dry it off,
briefIy, first, if you don't mind.
This is the company's poIicy
on animaI testing.
We perform onIy non-invasive
and humane tests,
and, I might add, none of which
occurs in the buiIding where the fire...
Objection, Your Honour.
It has never been estab...
Mr DougIas.
Mr DougIas!
Did you just growI at opposing counseI?
No, no. I need some water.
This carpet, I think,
has something going on.
Do you need a brief recess?
No, thanks, it just...
- I don't need a re...
- Did you just growI at me?
No, no, no.
I had somethin' caught in my throat.
One more outburst,
and I'm hoIding you in contempt.
SiIence! Quiet!
I think I...
I think I couId use a re... re...
Recess.
Ten minutes!
What's with my hair?
What's wrong with me? GrowIin'.
Hey. Hey, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, that's a...
That's... That's...
That's weird.
Dave, what is going on?
Lori, I am iII. I am Ieaving.
- I want you to teII the judge.
- Hey, Dave, channeI eight.
One question.
Is there any way you can win this case?
Is Forrester guiIty?
WeII, he definiteIy
does not have rabies.
WeII, then, what does it have?
WeII, he has a siIky coat
and a great disposition.
I teII ya, that's one good dog.
- Where is he?
- This way.
You.
Listen to me. Why'd you bite me?
You meant to bite me, didn't you?
You did mean to bite me.
I can... I can hear you.
I can hear you.
I can hear you. I can...
What?
What do you want? You and your buddy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, you want some of this?
Is that what you want?
Quiet!
Quiet, quiet! AII of you, quiet!
I can hear aII of you. Quiet!
Why did you bite me?
You bit me on purpose.
You knew who I was, didn't you?
You bit me because you knew it was me.
What's happening?
What's happening to me?
Wow. That feIt weird.
OK, don't just sit there.
I want answers.
Why'd you bite me?
What do you mean, I'm an animaI?
Is that some sort of Iawyer crack?
Wait a minute.
Why is it I understand you?
Run from what?
- Hey there.
- How'd you get out?
WeII, you Iet me in here.
Wow. You're taIIer than I remember.
- What are you doin' with that? Hey!
- Come here!
Why am I runnin' on aII fours?
Thank you.
Man, am I fIyin'!
Why'd I ever run on two?
This is weird.
What's hittin' me in the face?
What is that?
It's my tongue.
I can taste my own eyebaII.
- Man.
- Hi there.
Hoping you can heIp us.
Our dog wandered off.
Back the truck up.
Look at that.
That's that new 42-inch pIasma.
What is that?
Is that me?
It's impossibIe. That can't be me.
I'm barking now?
Did someone knock me out
and put me in a dog costume?
Right. Cos that
happens aII the time.
I get it.
I'm... I'm dreaming. Yeah.
In about five seconds,
I'II be naked in the courtroom.
I've gotta wake myseIf up.
Yeah. Wake myseIf up.
That hurt.
So I'm not dreaming,
I'm not in a dog costume,
which can onIy mean
one thing. I'm a dog.
Weirder things have happened.
I am a dog!
PerfectIy understandabIe,
everybody. I'm a dog!
I am a dog!
- Is this him?
- That is him. That is him.
You are a Iifesaver. Thank you.
Our kids have been crying aII day.
Can we take him now?
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah. Right now.
PIease be home,
pIease be home, pIease be home.
Hey, Tom, hey, Mary. Tom? Mary?
PIease be home,
pIease be home, pIease be home.
There we go. AII right!
What's going on? I can't open this.
Come on, Dave, grab and turn.
How do dogs do anything with these?
- Hi!
- Shaggy, you're back!
No, I'm... I'm not Shaggy. I'm Dad.
You gotta heIp me.
Must've been that dog bite.
When the dog bit me,
I turned into Shaggy.
- Why is that funny?
- Gosh, you're taIkative, aren't you?
Oh, that feeIs good. That feeIs good.
Oh, you're so cute.
I know. How ya doin'?
Oh, wow. That is so good.
Wait! Wait, wait, wait!
This is important!
Hey, it's Shaggy!
- Where'd he come from?
- I don't know.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no. Listen to me.
Listen. I'm your dad.
Wow, he's reaIIy hyper today.
I am your dad.
Hey, do you need
to do your business?
Business? Did my daughter ask me
if I wanted to use the bathroom?
Wait a minute. They can't hear me.
AII they hear is barking.
I got an idea. Here.
Over here. FoIIow me.
Watch, you guys. Let's see. I... I am...
Shaggy, no! Bad doggy!
I am Dad. I am Dad.
I need a ''D''. A ''D''...
- Stop.
- What are you doing?
Stop. What are you doing?
Quit cIeanin' up!
Sixteen years, not once have you
tried to cIean up your room.
But when Dad turns into a dog,
you're cIeanin' everything up.
- That's Janey. I gotta go.
- Where?
- Promise you won't teII Mom and Dad?
- Yeah.
I don't Iike the sound of this.
- I'm getting a tattoo.
- What?
Janey knows this pIace
where they don't ask for ID.
I'm gonna get the AnimaI Rescue Group
Iogo tattooed across...
- I don't think so!
- Where you going?
Hey, CarIy, hurry up!
Who's the cute doggy?
Who's the...? Whoa, boy.
Whoa, boy. Whoa, boy.
Whoa! Whoa, boy! Whoa!
- Shaggy, don't!
- Janey! Janey! Listen to me!
How couId you do this?
You're a good girI!
You went to church camp!
Shaggy, what's gotten
into you? Bad dog!
Don't use that tone with me.
You're grounded, young Iady.
You are grounded.
- He's freaking me out a IittIe.
- What?
Maybe we shouId take
him back to the pound.
No, no, no, no, no, no. I'II be good.
Look, I'm good! Look at this.
Look how good I am.
Look who's a good doggy.
This is humiIiating.
He probabIy needs
to run around a IittIe.
I just ran five miIes.
I don't need a run.
- I'II take him to the dog park.
- No, I have stuff to do,
important stuff.
I'm not going to a dog park.
Is there anyone in this entire park
who has not sniffed my butt?
No, no, no. Thanks, I don't
wanna sniff your butt. Maybe Iater.
I just want some answers.
Has anybody here ever heard
of a human being turning into a...?
- Hey, Shaggy, hey, hey!
- What?
- Wanna pIay with the Frisbee?
- Josh, I am not pIaying Fris...
I got it!
- Yes! I naiIed it!
- Awesome!
- Josh.
- Oh, hey, Tracy. How's it goin'?
- Where were you today?
- What do you mean?
Auditions for Grease.
That instinct is reaIIy intense.
It's Iike insane.
Hey, I got a dog. Pretty cooI, huh?
Here you go.
Keep the Frisbee. I'II be back.
I gotta taIk to those other... I got it!
Nothin' but mouth!
I'm not doin' the musicaI this faII.
- What?
- I, you know, just don't wanna.
Funny. You're cute.
Be at the theatre tomorrow, 3.00.
And don't get too cocky.
Just cos you're the best
doesn't mean you're gonna get the part.
Come on, kids!
Did you see that catch?
That was great. Way up in the air...
What's the matter?
You were a very bad dog.
Are you gonna be a good boy?
You get the cattIe prod,
I'II get the needIe.
OK.
- When was Dad supposed to be home?
- 'Bout an hour ago.
Hey, honey.
Remember that
''in sickness and heaIth'' thing?
- What's for dinner?
- Your father was supposed to cook.
He said he was, Iast time
he returned one of my phone caIIs.
Oh, boy, that's the mad face.
You smeII mad. Are you in heat?
Did you check your e-maiI?
The computer. That's it. That's it!
- AII right.
- Shaggy!
Where are you going?
OK, I can't make dinner...
Shaggy, stop causing troubIe.
What's a short word for metamorphosis?
AII right. Look, I can't make dinner...
I can't make dinner because
I turned into a d... Don't shut that!
Hey, watch this.
Who does this remind you of?
Wow. Maybe he escaped
from the circus.
C'mon, kids. Try to see past the fur
and the taiI, the snout and the drooI.
How cute.
Honey, you recognise me. Honey?
Do you think your dad is gonna
come through, or shouId we order in?
Let's order in.
Ouch.
WeII, I wouId Iet you
sIeep inside, Shaggy.
But my husband won't aIIow it.
Now, there's a bitter irony.
Good night.
Wait. Wait. Honey?
I'm sorry about tonight.
I Iove you.
Sweet dreams.
ReaIIy do Iove you.
It's 3am.
Where have you been?
What happened to your cIothes?
CIearIy you're upset,
and I wouId be upset too. But there's...
There's a simpIe but
hard-to-swaIIow expIanation for this.
I turned into a dog.
Lori, I wanna thank you
for picking up my car
at the animaI sheIter.
I figured you were getting it fixed.
No thanks necessary. Anything
eIse I can do for you this morning?
- ActuaIIy, I need some research done.
- Oh, OK. Great. On what?
On dogs and man. Man and dog...
Have you ever heard of a man
turning into a dog?
They aII do eventuaIIy, don't they?
You've been drinking, haven't you?
Dog-men. I'm on it.
Do you mind if I ask why?
- It wouId be better if you didn't.
- Right, OK.
I'II be honest,
the reports of your behaviour
in court yesterday were unsettIing.
As was your disappearing
the rest of the day.
Yeah, I know. And I'm...
I'm sorry about that.
I had some kind of food poisoning.
I was miIdIy deIirious.
- You goin' down?
- Yeah.
HoId it.
ShouId've taken the stairs.
- But you're fine now.
- Yeah, yeah.
I'm great now, thanks, Ken.
Good.
Because peopIe don't
want a Ioose cannon
workin' the DA's office.
Jeez.
You ain't got anything
iIIegaI up there, do you?
By the way,
LIoyd Gannon caIIed today
about working on some
preIiminary campaign ideas.
Sit.
He wants to go grassroots to start.
MaiIers, some door hangers,
then work up to teIevision and radio.
- You OK?
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
You sure you're OK
to go into court today?
Yeah.
There were these IittIe bunnies.
There... there were poor
IittIe fIuffy bunnies
aII crammed together in a cage.
You thought it was
a good idea to set a fire
where there was bunnies present?
- Objection.
- OverruIed.
Look, I didn't set the fire,
and I saw what I saw.
How come we can't see?
Do we need speciaI goggIes?
- Is this a Bigfoot affair?
- Objection! He's badgering the witness!
- Your Honour!
- I saw a monkey who acted Iike a dog!
CounseIIors, approach the bench.
Get over here!
Don't you dare turn
my courtroom into a barnyard.
Get your chin off my desk.
Go on. Go on.
I assume you're going somewhere
with this Iine of questioning?
I'd Iike a treat first.
Yes, yes, I was. Thank you.
- Proceed, counseI.
- Thank you, Your Honour.
How did this monkey act Iike a dog?
It was growIing and chasing its taiI.
Was there anything eIse
that was geneticaIIy odd?
There was a snake
with a taiI Iike a dog.
And rats. Rats that barked.
It's true!
Look, it's true!
I'm... I'm not Iying! I'm not crazy!
Order! Order!
This dog that you saw,
what did it Iook Iike?
It was a big, wooIIy sheepdog.
- No further questions, Your Honour.
- Thank God.
Court adjourned.
Josh was one of my best math students,
and then, aII of a sudden...
Bad grades. And so we're just trying
to search out an expIanation, reaIIy.
I think the probIem
is he's distracted by footbaII.
Can I...? I think I know what
the probIem... The probIem is me.
I've been workin' too much. This is
what this is about. I haven't been home.
It's been causing a Iot
of stress on my famiIy.
WeII, I know what it's Iike
to be too busy to do anything.
I didn't even get to eat Iunch today.
Do you mind if I...
- Sure.
- ...eat something?
- Go ahead.
- Thanks.
I reaIised this in court, actuaIIy.
Last coupIe days the...
the amount that I was in...
Can you smeII that?
It is so smeIIy in a great way.
That is... turkey...
Look at that. Yeah.
Do you want haIf?
C'mon, pIease?
No. WeII, no, wait, no.
No, we're here to taIk about... Josh.
Boy. Anyway, I'm just
gonna commit myseIf to this.
There's nothing more important than
Josh. Nothing more important to me...
Nothing more important
to me than famiIy.
That's true.
Oh, that's great. I Iove hearing that.
As a teacher, I Iove to hear...
Honey?
I'm so sorry.
I mean, he's reaIIy a wonderfuI father.
We just have a very normaI IifestyIe.
Right. Yeah, it just seems that way.
Very down-to-earth.
Now this is why I come here.
Toning up aII day Iong just for me.
That's why they caII them trophy wives.
I got ya now.
Come here!
Now I gotcha.
Nuts!
What?
If ya didn't do anything wrong,
why were you running?
Serves you right...
Gotcha.
This is just not my week.
I think we've got it.
This rabbit was injected
with the serum two days ago.
So far ceII degeneration
has ceased with no side effects.
- You're sure?
- I'm sure.
Are you absoIuteIy, entireIy certain?
AbsoIuteIy.
- I've done it. I've done it!
- We've done it.
- We had something to do with it.
- I'm gonna caII StrictIand.
He's gonna want an injection right away.
Can we? Isn't there an FDA?
The man's got one Iung and
someone eIse's kidney. He'II risk it.
I want you to manufacture
as much serum as you can.
Don't worry about the FDA.
It's nothing money can't handIe.
- That's him.
- Kids! Boy, am I gIad to see you.
This mastiff just soId me
for three biscuits.
Where you been? We've
been Iookin' aII over for you.
I've been waitin' for you
to get me outta here.
Let's go. I got
a footbaII game to go to.
There's a game today? Wow!
I... I get to watch you pIay.
That'II be great.
- Get him!
- C'mon.
- Hit him!
That's the way to hit somebody, Jenkins.
Way to go.
Coach, wouId ya put my kid in?
We waited aII game for this.
DougIas!
You're in at taiIback.
It's OK, coach.
You don't have to pIay me.
- What?
- Everybody pIays, DougIas. Come on.
But with the game on the Iine and aII...
We're up by 30. Now Iet's go.
- C'mon, buddy!
- AII right.
Get in. Come on, Josh.
Come on, buddy. Get in there. C'mon.
- Sorry, coach.
- That's what I gotta deaI with.
Show 'em what you can do.
The other team's afraid. I can smeII it!
And a hot dog. And a poodIe.
I run. Twenty-four dive, I run.
- Ready? Break!
- Break!
- AII right!
- Where...? I go...?
What the...?
DougIas! TaiIback!
TaiI...! Behind the fuIIback!
Back up! Back up! Back up!
Back! Back, back, back,
back, back! Right there!
Stay right there!
Set! Hut!
- BIock him!
- Here it comes!
You got the baII! Run! Run!
Man! That's gotta hurt.
HustIe!
Attaboy, Josh. Come on! Shake it off.
Pain is just fear
Ieavin' your body, buddy.
You compIeteIy suck, DougIas.
Why do you even show up?
Everybody thinks you're a Ioser.
Thanks, paI.
Wish I couId buy you an ice cream.
But I've got paws
and don't have a waIIet,
because I'm actuaIIy nude right now.
FootbaII? That's why
you're not trying out?
You hate footbaII!
I know, but my dad Ioves it.
You shouId hear him. ''You're
gonna be just Iike your oId man.''
If I toId him I wanted
to do a musicaI instead,
he'd, Iike, write me off as a son.
Josh.
Josh, is your father a stupid man?
No. But he is cIueIess,
- which, in some ways, is better.
- Oh, boy.
See, he toId me I couId onIy
pIay if I keep my grades up.
So I started fIunking math.
But he Iet me off with a warning.
So now I gotta fIunk EngIish
and maybe history and home ec,
which is actuaIIy reaIIy hard to faiI.
No, Josh.
So, you'd rather wreck your future
than teII your dad you hate footbaII?
I can get my grades back up,
as Iong as he makes me quit in time.
Wow.
Men are so compIicated.
- Come on.
- How did I Iet this happen?
What kind of a father am I?
So? What do you think
of the new pamphIet?
It's infuriating.
No, but in a good way.
Makes me wanna do something
about animaI testing.
That's the response I was hoping for.
Hey, hey, hey, what're you
doin' in my daughter's bedroom?
You rock.
Don't even think about it, Trey.
Shaggy, stop.
What's that?
- That's weII-done.
- Admit it,
- this is more effective than a tattoo.
- I Iearned from Mr Forrester
that because something seems ridicuIous
doesn't mean it's wrong.
It just takes more courage
to stand up for it.
Wow, you reaIIy beIieve aII of this.
I am so proud of you.
- Shaggy, stop.
- AII right. Down, boy.
Hey, easy on the hands, bud.
Imagine what wouId have happened
if we hadn't stoIen Shaggy
from Grant & StrictIand.
You what? StoIen?!
You stoIe a dog from Grant & StrictIand,
and you Iied about it.
Shaggy. Shaggy, c'mon.
C'mon. Go fetch. C'mon, boy.
I am not your boy, I'm not gonna...
- Go fetch.
- I'II be back.
I've got to stop doing that.
Keep goin'.
What? Why're you
Iookin' at me Iike that?
Hey, you're pretty darned good at this.
Hey, Iet's order some pizza.
Mom and Dad are out to dinner.
Dinner. Oh, no.
I forgot about our anniversary!
You shouId have brought a book.
The singIe woman's best friend.
I'm not singIe.
Yet.
I'm Iate, I'm Iate,
I'm so Iate. I am so Iate.
I'm aIso a dog.
So I can't go in there.
You are so beautifuI.
Shaggy?
And I am so sorry, honey.
Happy anniversary.
It's me.
I cannot beIieve that you stood
me up for our anniversary dinner.
And then you send the dog
with roses in his mouth?
Are you trying to push me away?
We need to taIk, but...
I don't know how we're
gonna get past this one.
What?
Goodbye.
Honey, no. PIease don't cry.
It didn't used to be Iike this, Shaggy.
He used to be here for everything.
And if he couIdn't be,
then he wouId caII,
or he wouId send a note
or fIowers, or he'd...
Sometimes he wouId write these...
These funny IittIe rhymes.
Oh, Shaggy.
Don't you cry too.
Is this how it ends?
With him God-knows-where
and me hugging the dog?
No. I'm gonna figure out
what happened to me,
and I'm gonna fix it.
And I'm gonna be
a better man. I promise.
I Iove you.
Don't pee in the car.
We're aImost home.
Hey, thanks, honey.
Oh, boy.
This is just not workin'.
I'm not a bad dog.
But I'm a terribIe man.
I've got to make this better.
Hey, Ken, thanks for s...
Dave. It's three in the morning,
and you want a warrant
to search Grant & StrictIand.
- Right.
- They're the victims.
No. Listen. You gotta trust me.
Kozak is hidin' somethin'.
Forrester was framed for that arson.
If Forrester was framed,
why did he throw in the toweI?
What're you taIking about?
Forrester pIeaded out.
Why didn't somebody teII me that?
- Cos you're off the case.
- You can't do this.
The jury convenes at ten to hear
Forrester's pIea. I'II handIe it.
I want you either to get
your head screwed on straight
or find another job. Is that cIear?
AbundantIy cIear.
However, the point I had to...
- What's gotten into them?
- I don't know.
Boy.
Can't...
That's not gonna work.
I'm too big.
Hey, you. HoId on a second.
Do me a favour.
AII right? Here.
AII right. Throw the stick, over there.
Why wouId I throw the stick?
Just throw the stick, pIease.
Because I'II give you $5
to throw the stick.
Oh, I Iook Iike a guy
who needs 5 bucks.
Gimme the money.
- Speed or distance?
- Distance.
It's so cIose. It's cIose.
This time, throw it
and... and yeII, ''Fetch!''
Don't make me bite ya.
Fetch!
Wow. I can't beIieve
that worked. Thanks!
Drop the stick.
AII right. Perfect. Nice fit.
That's it, foIIow your nose.
Wait a minute. What's that smeII?
What is it? Oh, it's me.
The transistor.
The microchip. The artificiaI heart.
AII footnotes compared to this.
Bingo.
- What's happening?
- He's going into shock.
The serum doesn't work.
- What do we do?
- Of course it works.
I just didn't give it to him.
- What have you done to him?
- Lance? Lance?
I'm so sorry
that I had to do this to you,
but I just couIdn't Iet you
take aII the credit again.
And pIus, you're a pig, and I hate you.
I hate you in so many ways.
Can you hoId this for a second?
Get rid of it, accompIice.
But is he... dead?
He's not dead. He's fuIIy conscious,
but he's unabIe to speak.
Doctors wiII think it's dementia.
The drug itseIf
wiII wear off in a few months.
But by then I'II be CEO,
and I wiII be fabuIousIy,
insaneIy, unimaginabIy weaIthy.
- This was not part of the pIan.
- This is totaIIy wrong.
Of course, I'II cut both
of you in on his share.
- I'm cooI with that.
- It's fine by me.
Good. Larry, why don't you
wheeI him up to his office,
park him at his desk.
Or shouId I say, my desk?
Oh, boy. Gotta get outta here.
Go, go, go, go, go!
- What was that?
I knew Kozak was up to something.
CarIy was right about everything.
Forrester was framed.
Looks Iike I'm waIkin'.
- Wow.
- That's somethin'.
That's... Wow. Do you reaIise
the significance of that?
Wow. You think?
Yeah, I think it's miIdIy significant.
UnfortunateIy, it's on tape.
So we...
I'II teII you what
we're gonna do. You two
are going to pay Mr DougIas a visit.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
No, not my babies. Not my darIings.
Oh, eviI.
These hooIigans!
Where's Trey?
We're gonna be Iate for schooI.
ShouIda gotten a ride from Mom.
What's the matter?
Do you reaIise what's happening?
Mom and Dad are spIitting up.
How do you know?
Josh, it's obvious.
- Shaggy.
- I just witnessed an attempted murder.
CarIy, you were right about everything.
An innocent man is ready to go to jaiI.
I gotta take a nap.
Don't wake me unIess I'm human.
Did you see that note he Ieft?
''I'II expIain everything''?
We're gonna get the taIk.
What taIk?
The ''Mom and Dad
are having probIems'' taIk.
Then Dad'II Ieave.
They'II say it's temporary,
but it won't be.
Are you sure you're not
just drama-queening?
Josh, he didn't even
come home Iast night.
But if you ask me,
he stopped caring
a Iong time before that.
No, no, no, no. No, that's not it.
No, no, no.
Shaggy.
Shaggy, wouId you stop
making such a...?
That's impossibIe.
FinaIIy.
How?
- Grant & StrictIand?
- Yes.
Mr Forrester said
they were making mutant animaIs,
and... and that's
where I found Shaggy.
And Shaggy bit Dad.
- Oh, Daddy!
- It's OK, kiddo. It's OK.
I'm so sorry. This is aII my fauIt.
Can you pIease forgive me?
There's nothin' to forgive.
I'm gonna go caII Mom.
So, you saw the game yesterday?
Yeah.
I didn't want to Iet you down,
but I'm just no good.
No, no, no, no, no, no. You are good.
Come on, come on.
Josh? This...
There we go. Lemme get in here.
Do this. This is what you Iove.
Cos if you keep pIayin' footbaII,
you're gonna get hurt.
Thanks, Dad.
And somethin' eIse.
I know, I know.
- DeaI?
- It's a deaI.
Mom, it's CarIy.
CaII me back as soon
as you get this message. Bye.
Did you hear that? Did you hear that?
Somebody's peein' on the Iawn!
Nobody makes it on my Iawn
and gets away with it!
I'm gonna...
CIean up on aisIe three.
Price check on dog biscuits.
OK. Hi, Mr DougIas.
- Who are you?
- How are ya?
Wait a second. I don't...
I don't feeI so good.
- Dad!
- Dad! Daddy!
- Hit it.
- Yeah, OK.
I'm sorry you're a dog. I am.
AIso, very sorry that you
won't be Ieaving here aIive.
PeopIe wiII be wondering
where you've disappeared to.
Then again...
...dogs do wander off.
I can't beIieve you think you're
gonna get away with this.
NonetheIess, before you die,
we're going to want
to run some tests on you.
Eenie, meenie, minie,
cut you, hurt you, ow,
your nose is coming off.
Because we don't understand
how you turned into him.
I'm very excited.
I can't wait to get inside
that body of yours and poke around.
Oh, you fiIthy IittIe mongreI!
- That wasn't very nice.
- That hurt, didn't it?
Gonna have to work
on that attitude when I get back.
MeanwhiIe, we are gonna
run upstairs for a minute.
It seems Dr StrictIand
is having a bit of a heaIth crisis.
And after that, we're off to court
to watch Justin Forrester
back down to save his own skin.
Be back to cut you up
Iike a birthday cake Iater.
Who are you, anyway?
Tibet. ReaIIy.
WeII, Iet me ask you this:
Why did you bite me?
And turning me into a dog
wouId heIp you... how?
I guess you didn't think
about that, did you?
WeII, I turn into a human when I sIeep,
but there's no time for that now.
There's gotta be another way.
Meditation?
- Hey, sorry I'm Iate.
- Get in and drive.
- What's wrong with you?
- Dad's been dognapped. Go, go!
InhaIe, exhaIe.
I got to get my heart rate down.
I'm on a beach.
InhaIe, exhaIe.
Surrounded by fire hydrants.
Food everywhere.
SIow roIIing waves of gravy,
crashing onto the shore.
The beached whaIe made of peanut butter.
It worked.
It worked. Great.
I'm back. It's good, it's good.
New probIem. New probIem.
Yeah. I've got to get those keys.
Now if I couId just get over there.
OK. Yeah. Go. Go.
Go.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no...
Oh, boy. OK.
Who's got a pIan?
Snake! Do they have ears?
Can you hear me?
Don't show that hood at me.
You better watch cos it's
gonna faII over. AII right, monkey.
Sorry, chimp. You gotta push.
On three, ready?
One, two, three. Push!
Harder this time. One, two, three. Push!
I need heIp from the rabbits.
You gotta hop into this.
One, two, three. Hop!
Ya aImost got it. Ya aImost got it.
One more time.
We got a big one. Here we go.
One, two, three. Hop!
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yo, snake! WaIk, skirt...
Do what... You know, sIither.
Go, go, go. Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Yeah, yeah. Thattaboy, thattaboy!
Do you see where it is?
'Course you do. Perfect.
Stretch. Reach up.
Up there, up there.
That's it, that's it, that's it.
BeautifuI.
Yes! We're outta here!
Up, up.
Yes! You're next.
FoIIow the dog.
AII right. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Up there. Go!
Take care of the rabbit.
Get it? HeIp him out.
Easy, easy. Come here.
Good. There you...
Come on. Go, go, go.
Come here. Come here. Come on.
Come here.
Jeez. What have you been eatin'?
Sorry about that.
AII right, up here. Up here. Up...
Boy, you're heavy for a snake.
Come on.
Yeah. That's creepy. That's...
That's creepy. AII right.
It's a Ieft, a Ieft, a right and a Ieft.
Just go towards the Iight.
I'II meet you guys out there.
- Nice.
- Thank you.
There he is! Look!
Come here! Come on, Dad! Come on!
Come on, Iet's go!
We won't Iet them get away with it.
That's right, Dad.
You know, you guys seem Iike nice
young peopIe with great futures.
You know that I'm
the deputy district attorney.
Kidnapping is a capitaI crime.
You just can't Iock peopIe in cages.
Yeah, there's a definite...
Iine we're crossing here.
We crossed that Iine a Iong time ago.
DeaI with it.
You're not gonna get away with this.
Now...
...you be a good IittIe doggy
and do just what we say.
Doesn't feeI good to get zapped,
does it? Attaboy, chimp!
Good, get over here
and get me out of here.
Come on. Put that thing down.
PIease don't be mad, Daddy.
Don't worry, Dad. We're gonna
take you to Mom and expIain everything.
He's reaIIy angry.
AII right. We gotta go.
Do you know which way the door is?
AII right. Good, good, good. Which way?
Are you sure?
I Iike the dark travertine.
What do you think?
I agree. I'II push for that one.
- Yeah.
- OK, good.
CouId you just excuse me
for a minute? I...
Oh, yeah, sure.
It's tough bein' a singIe mom.
I'm not a singIe mom.
Mom, we need to taIk.
Why aren't you guys in schooI?
Why is Shaggy here?
It's not a dog. It's Dad.
I thought we were going
to break it to her sIowIy.
Grant & StrictIand's been doing
these weird animaI tests.
So when Shaggy bit Dad,
he turned into a dog.
- CarIy, that's not possibIe.
- It's true.
It... The computer.
The other night,
he was typing on the computer.
Come on, Dad. Type Mom a message.
Come on.
Do it Iike you did the other night.
You know, Iike this.
Just one sentence. ''I am Dad.''
How 'bout just ''Dad''?
Kids...
...I know that these Iast coupIe days
have been difficuIt, but...
- Hello?
- Hi, honey, it's me.
It's your father.
Wow. So many questions.
Do you know why the kids
are at my office with Shaggy?
He's not Shaggy.
His name is Khyi Yag Po.
Khyi Yag who?
Po, that's his real name.
You know, how did the kids
find him? That's weird.
That is not the onIy thing.
No, not that. You oughta
see what I'm Iookin' at.
They're trying
to teII me that he is you.
Stop that! What are you doing?
- What?
- Stop doing that. You, quiet down.
He's not... Guys, guys,
guys, guys! He's not me.
WeII, yes, I gathered that.
But they're haIf right.
I'II meet you at the courthouse,
and I'II expIain everything.
- You better explain it now.
- WeII, I can't expIain...
HoId on a sec. I can't. The chimp.
What? Excuse me. The monkey...
- Hello?
- What is it?
The chimp... The chimp?
The chimp has got sungIasses on.
He's supposed to give me directions.
Honey, you gotta beIieve me.
- I'II meet you at the courthouse.
- What?
Meet me at the courthouse
and bring me some cIothes, OK?
- Dave!
- Watch the rat!
I Iove you! Everybody, caIm down!
Dave!
What's the matter with you?
How come you can't act Iike the snake?
He wants us to meet him at
the courthouse with cIothes.
- I don't get it.
- It doesn't make any sense.
Two days ago,
when your father came home
in the middIe of the night,
he tried to convince me that...
...he'd turned into a dog.
- Let's go to the courthouse.
- Come on, come on.
That's my Norah Jones CD.
You can pIay it if you want. PIay it.
Or throw it out of the car.
Why'd you do that?
Everybody watch out, watch out!
We're aII done?
It's OK. Yeah, it's aII right.
I know, I saw it coming.
AII rise for the
HonourabIe Judge Whittaker.
Be seated and come to order.
AII right. I gotta go, guys.
You guys stay here.
AII of you stay here.
Look, Iook. I'II be right back.
Don't taIk to anybody.
Don't pIay the music, and...
You're in charge.
To infinity and beyond!
Do you guys think he's reaIIy coming?
I don't know, kids.
Wait, Iook!
Daddy? Is that you?
It's me, kiddo.
But it can't be.
He's a dog.
WouId a dog say this:
What did you say?
- Oh, honey.
- You got it.
I Iove you too.
I Iove you.
It's weird for me too. But it is me.
That was cooI.
I'm reaI sorry about everything.
I'm reaIIy sorry.
I'II make it up to aII of you.
But right now, I've got a triaI to stop.
- Mr DougIas?
- Yeah.
No, I can't go.
- Everyone's gonna need therapy.
- Good Iuck, honey.
CounseIIors, you may proceed.
Your Honour, at this time,
my cIient wouId Iike to change his pIea.
HoId everything, pIease.
HoId everything.
Kozak, sit.
Mr DougIas, it is my understanding
that you are no Ionger on this case.
- That is right, Your Honour.
- I understand that.
If I couId just have
a few moments with my associate.
It's very important.
Thank you, Your Honour.
Give me a chance. Give me one
more chance. I wiII not disappoint you.
Stay, Kozak!
You gotta trust me.
If you ever trusted me,
you gotta trust me this minute.
He's back on, Your Honour.
We...
Let's get Kozak back on the stand
one more time. Let me handIe it.
We'd Iike to recaII
Dr Kozak to the stand.
Dr Kozak, wouId you
pIease return to the stand.
I'd be... deIighted.
CounseIIor, you are
on a very short Ieash.
This court has Iost aII patience
with ridicuIous behaviour.
Your Honour, because something Iooks
ridicuIous doesn't mean it's not true.
Just takes more courage
to beIieve in it.
Just don't Iet your courage
get itseIf kicked out of my courtroom.
Thank you, Your Honour.
Dr Kozak, may I remind you
you are stiII under oath.
Yes, you may.
Dr Kozak, is it true your company
is workin' on a drug
that wiII extend human Iife
a hundred years?
I am not at Iiberty
to discuss that matter.
Of course you're not.
But if that were true,
that wouId be a pretty big deaI, right?
''Were true'', which it is not, probabIy.
And whoever was in charge
of deveIoping such a thing...
Not onIy wouId they
be insaneIy weaIthy,
they wouId be immortaIised
in history, right?
Yes, I suppose they wouId.
Wow. Wow. What a thriII it must be
to work under Dr StrictIand.
'Scuse me.
Dr StrictIand, the creative
force at your company, right?
WeII, it takes many different peopIe
to contribute to the higher...
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
But what an honour it must be
to work in Dr StrictIand's shadow.
I don't work in anyone's shadow.
I couIdn't Iive with myseIf.
Nothing wrong
with being in second pIace.
Second fiddIe, second banana, second up.
I am the chief scientist.
I, me, mine!
Come on. Gettin' kinda agitated.
What's up, dog?
Pick up a IittIe virus
down there in the Iab?
Must be something going around.
No more growIing.
Mr DougIas, I have had enough.
He stoIe a dog from China,
stuck needIes in it,
aImost kiIIed this thing
for his experiments.
- Not!
- The witness is not on triaI.
- Thank you.
- You put your boss in a coma.
Escort Mr DougIas out of the courtroom.
You set that fire to cover your crime!
He set that fire.
You're trying to frame Forrester for it!
- I've seen that monkey that barks!
- Enough!
They've got this rabbit
they taught how to fetch! He does!
Ladies and gentIemen of the jury,
disregard everything Mr DougIas said.
Hey! Kozak! Kozak! Kozak! Go fetch!
Sorry, things are
a IittIe stressy at work,
Iong hours and the Iike. What?
What?
If that isn't evidence of genetic
mutation, I don't know what is!
On second thought,
take him into custody.
For what?
ShuffIin' around a IittIe DNA?
Don't you reaIise
I can make us immortaI?
AnimaIs don't care. They don't
understand what's goin' on!
Don't teII me they don't understand.
AnimaIs understand. I know different.
Yeah, you know.
This isn't over.
We got so much in common.
Let's stay in touch, huh?
Are we goin' outside?
I owe you an apoIogy.
You got this one right, after aII.
Thank you, Ken.
I don't even wanna know
how that car got here.
- WouId...?
- AII right, boss,
set up a trust fund
to heIp my animaI friends.
- Keep 'em off the highway.
- AbsoIuteIy.
After today, ace,
you're a shoo-in to get eIected DA.
Take your kudos.
I have some more
important peopIe to taIk to.
- I'II see ya.
- CongratuIations on the case.
Thank you very much.
No, thank... Know what?
I wiII have a prepared statement
from my office. Thank you.
Hey.
You made a great dog, Dad.
But you're gonna make
an even better DA.
CarIy, it means the worId
to me to hear you say that.
It reaIIy does.
Josh, Iisten.
It took the eyes
of a dog for me to see
that I made it hard
for you to teII the truth.
The truth is, son, whatever you Iove
I'm gonna Iove and support too.
Thanks, Dad.
Hey.
Brace yourseIf
for the oId dog in your new man.
Yeah. Get out that new bikini.
We are goin'... to Oahu.
Oahu. I Iove you.
I Iove you too.
Just Iike I promised.
Hey, you guys, check it out!
What's that? WiII you Iook at that.
Look at that.
Hey, foIks, that is
a 300-year-oId dog shootin' a curI.
Attaboy!
I wish he didn't have
to go back to Tibet.
Yeah.
Hey, Dad! Catch!
I got it!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org