Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Hi, how you doing?
- Hi.
You looking for a date?
- No, thanks.
- Okay.
- Do you want a date?
- No, sorry.
- You sure?
- I'm sure. Sorry.
Would you like to go out?
- No, I'm just driving around.
- Okay.
You change your mind?
- You look pretty.
- Thank you.
- I like your necklace.
- Thanks.
That's your name? Rose?
- That's a nice name.
- Thank you.
I wasn't really driving...
I wasn't driving around
looking for anything like that.
No? Well, you found me.
You want to just have lunch with me?
That'd be nice,
but I need to make my money.
What?
Come on, it's time to go.
Here.
Stefano!
Okay.
That's fine.
Let's go.
Open the computer.
- Where did you say you're from?
- Laroux.
Stefano?
Yes, sir?
- Can I get some earplugs, man?
- Yeah.
Come on. Roll it out.
Are you going to be
driving up to the track tonight?
I think I'm going to stay in LA tonight.
I'll go in the morning.
Daisy!
No one's there!
Hello. I'm in Room 325.
I might be getting a call soon.
I just wanted you to know
that if somebody calls...
to put the call through.
And she might just come by...
so if somebody named Daisy
comes to the front desk looking for me...
I'm Bud Clay.
You can let her come right up to the room.
Daisy.
Okay.
Bye. Thanks.
Hi, Bud.
I got your note.
I have to use the bathroom.
Can I hug you, Bud?
Can I sit on your lap?
Can I touch you?
You don't want to touch me anymore?
Don't you like me anymore, Bud?
I like you.
Can I hug you?
Remember how, after dinner,
when you were done eating...
you'd always turn sideways in your chair
and pat your thighs...
and I would come and sit on your lap?
You would let me sit there for a long time
and we would kiss.
Remember, Bud?
Please, can I hug you?
Okay.
Missed you. Missed you so much.
I'm thirsty. I'm gonna get a glass of water.
You want some?
No.
I'm sorry. Don't look at me like that.
I know I look ugly.
I'm sorry.
I know I look terrible.
I didn't have time to fix myself
before I came over.
I know we haven't seen each other
in such a long time.
I'm sorry I look so bad.
I have to use the bathroom again.
I drank a lot of water before I came here.
I have to take my antibiotics,
but it's for my allergies.
I'm sorry, but I guess
I'm just a little nervous.
Should I go to the store
and get us something to drink?
- Do you remember the last time I saw you?
- Yes.
I don't drink anymore.
I don't drink at all anymore.
That's great, Bud.
I keep a photo of us in my purse.
I look at it every single day.
Do you want to see it?
Remember, my cousin took it...
in front of our house on Bay Street,
the day we moved in?
We're kissing in it. You want to see it?
Isn't it nice, Bud?
It was a long time ago.
I used to love kissing you...
all over your mouth.
I love the way you taste.
You're my favorite person
in the whole world, Bud.
I never want to kiss anybody else.
- Really, Bud.
- It's not true.
I did. I loved kissing you.
I loved your mouth. I loved the way it tasted.
It's not true.
- I never want to kiss anybody else.
- That's not true.
It is.
You kissed other boys.
Do you remember the time you bought me
the really big chocolate bunny?
It was so big. I ate it in like an hour
and got really sick and threw up.
You kissed me anyway.
I remember.
You used to really like me.
I still like you.
I wish you liked me again...
like before.
When you liked me the most.
I liked you the most my whole life.
You're the only person I liked.
- Tell me you love me.
- No.
I missed you so much.
It hurts me when I don't see you
for such a long time.
I just want to hug you. Come here.
No.
I love you so much.
I always loved holding you.
- That's not true.
- Yes, it is.
Kiss me, Bud.
Don't leave.
I missed you so much.
I love you.
Come on, won't you kiss me? Please?
I missed you.
I missed you a lot.
Take off your shirt.
But it's so bright in here.
I want to see your body.
Can we turn off the light? Please?
Can we go under the covers?
You only do this to me?
You only suck my cock, baby?
You don't do it with anybody else?
You don't think about doing it
with anybody else?
You like doing it?
You won't suck anybody else?
Never?
Never again?
You promise?
You won't fuck anybody else?
Never?
You won't suck anybody else's cock?
You promise me?
Why did you suck that guy's cock?
Why did you fuck those guys?
Why did you do that?
Tell me, why did you do that?
Tell me. I saw you.
I saw you fuck them.
Did you know I saw you?
Never?
- Why did you let me see that?
- No.
You're a fucking whore. You're a whore.
You fucked them. You fucking asshole.
I hate you so much.
I don't love you anymore.
- It hurts me so much when you say that.
- It doesn't hurt you.
Please don't say that.
I should've never let you come over here.
I'm so stupid.
Why?
I'm so stupid for telling you to come here.
- Bud, I love you.
- You don't love anybody.
- I love you. I want to be with you again.
- I don't want to be with you.
- Can't we be a couple again?
- I'll never be with you again.
- Don't say that, Bud.
- I don't trust you anymore.
I don't love you anymore.
I'm sorry, Bud. I'm sorry that that happened.
- You're not sorry.
- I never meant to hurt you, Bud.
I don't understand why you did that.
Why you went with those guys,
I don't understand that.
It was just a party. I was just being friendly.
Why were you talking to those guys?
I saw them talk to you.
Why were you talking to them?
I thought they were nice guys, Bud.
- Nice guys?
- I talk to lots of guys at parties.
I didn't want anything from them.
I didn't care about them.
Why did you get high with them?
They just came into the bathroom
and they...
started smoking, and I thought it was pot.
Why did you smoke pot with them?
I was just going to have a little.
I just wanted to get high, Bud.
You were pregnant.
You shouldn't even have been drinking.
I know.
Why do you take drugs? I don't understand.
Because I'm an addict, Bud.
- Why can't you stop taking it?
- I don't want to take them anymore.
Why can't you stop taking drugs?
Why do you have to drink and take drugs?
I don't understand.
You made our baby die. Our baby died.
I'm so sorry. I didn't want it to die.
I didn't want any of it to happen, Bud,
but it did.
- Tell me what happened.
- They just barged in, Bud.
- There was no lock on the door and...
- Why didn't you tell them to leave?
They were standing in front of the door
and started smoking...
and I thought I'd just have a little bit
and then leave.
- And then what happened?
- Then I passed out, Bud.
Oh, my God!
They raped me.
You saw them and you left me there.
No, I saw them with you. I didn't see...
I was unconscious, Bud, and you saw me,
and you didn't help me.
You just left me there.
But I didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what to do.
- Why didn't you help me?
- I didn't know what to do.
You didn't know what to do?
No.
Why didn't you help me?
You left me lying there like that?
I don't know.
- I would've helped you, Bud.
- I know.
- I would've helped you.
- I know you would have.
I walked away. I saw you in there.
I saw you in the bedroom.
I saw them touching you.
I saw them put their hands on you
and touch you.
And you had your clothes on.
They pulled your bra down.
They had your pants down.
Then I left. I just kept walking.
And I was walking away to go home.
When I came back,
there was an ambulance there.
Why was there an ambulance there?
I was dead.
What do you mean?
I don't understand. Why was there...
I died, Bud.
I got sick. I choked.
And I died.
- I'm sorry.
- You didn't die.
Don't say you're sorry. You didn't die.
I know you didn't die.
You'll be okay, you're just sick.
- I'm not going to be okay, Bud.
- Yes, you are.
Nobody was there and I got sick,
and I threw up, and I choked, Bud.
The ambulance came...
and I was dead, Bud.
I died.
No.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org