If they have Strabo, who has girl?
Answer. Answer, Mother.
You okay, darling?
- What's up, Jill?
- Nothing.
Open the trunk.
Don't even think about it.
Thank you.
- I think you nicked his head there.
- I'm sorry. I didn't see you.
- What is your problem, Jill?
- Nothing.
- I don't have a problem.
- Good.
Why don't you go and check us in.
Okay.
I wouldn't mind you wearing it,
it's just so ugly.
- Just throw it away.
- I can't.
- You still have feelings for her?
- It's sacrilegious.
- Why not give it back to her?
- I haven't seen her since my nickel in Joliet!
Where does he get sayings like that?
We aren't gonna talk much, are we?
There is something
really wrong with you, Jill.
- You're still in love with her.
- That's insane. Isn't it?
- Why don't you let me take it...
- Tell you what:
- Jimmy, Jimmy.
- I love you, Jill.
But if you touch this crucifix,
I'll kill you. That's a promise.
This is my good luck charm.
I take it off, I'm jinxed.
Wanna see me dead, Jill?
Do you?
Sometimes, yeah.
- I'm going to check in.
- Can you believe this?
- Well, 47 percent of couples at some point...
- You know, you've got a very long face.
Like a goldfish...
...or a Shetland pony or something.
- Bring Strabo, Oz.
I gotta have you...
Where is she?
Look, how nice. Everybody is still here...
...having a little repast. Isn't that lovely?
Where else would I be?
I don't know.
One would venture a guess.
A question could be asked:
Where have you been?
Big loft, very drafty. I understand.
Get me Figueroa on the phone!
Mr. G., Frankie Figs is dead.
How sad for him.
Try calling the one who's still alive!
Jill. Come on, open the door.
Jill!
Jill, will you come on? Be sensible.
Apologize.
Jill, honey, I'm sorry
I pointed a gun at your face...
...and said I was gonna
blow your brains out.
Okay? I didn't mean that.
- Come on, knock it off.
- I will when you get rid of that crucifix.
This cross represents my Lord and Savior.
The baby in the manger.
I throw it away...
...I go to hell!
- Coming from a man who's killed 21 people.
- Twenty-one? That's impressive.
- It is, isn't it?
Two years, I've been begging you to go
back to work. Cynthia gets kidnapped...
...you're off to the races!
Off to the races?
"Apologize, then she'll come right out."
Squeal bag! Squealster!
Remington Squeal!
See what you got me into? Get over here
and you help me out of this jam.
You better make it good.
Snoodster? Hon?
You're gonna be hearing
from somebody else now.
Jill? Scooster?
Snoodster.
I think you're being a little unreasonable.
When he pulled a gun on you...
...that was pretty funny.
Oz, nobody's talking to you.
Hey, you take it easy on Oz, okay?
He's a doctor.
- People see him when they have problems.
- People see him when they have plaque.
- He's a wonderful dentist.
- Pipe it, toughie.
I promise I'll shoot you. Frankly, I don't care
whether we get Cynthia back or not.
Well, that's a bad...
- Oh, trouble in the bedroom?
- What'd you just say?
- Nothing.
- Excuse me, please.
Did you tell him that?!
Did you tell him that, Jill?!
A few moments of erectile dysfunction...
Just a few, really.
- And I'm not a man now? Is that it?
- Stop kicking.
If you didn't love her, you'd take it off.
- Is that it?!
- Excuse me.
Can we please call Lazlo
and make the switch for Cynthia?
No. I'll tell you why we can't do that!
Because that would involve me talking to
my wife, which I am never gonna do again!
I'm going to get drunk.
- You believe this?
- Well, erectile dysfunc...
Shut up. I'm gonna
go get Jimmy. Will you...
...watch Strabo for a while?
- Eat shit.
How can he get drunk at a time like this?
Maybe this whole "erectile misfiring"
is God's way of punishing me.
He sees all things great and small.
You know, I've done
some very bad things. I lie to Jill.
I don't take the trash out.
- I killed 21 people.
- Actually, 22.
- Who'd I forget?
- Frankie Figs.
This is it. This is the reason that God
does not want me to father a child.
He does not want me to spread my seed.
God is counting my seed, Oz.
He's probably up in heaven right now...
...counting my little seeds. 138, 139...
...140...
- Stop, stop! Stop counting your seed.
I don't think God is keeping an eye
on your sperm.
What kind of a job is that for God?
It'd take him all day. I'm gonna throw up.
Fine. Throw up.
Go ahead, you have your fun.
- What about me?
- Why don't you just consider adopting?
Come on, Oz.
How many adoption agencies
are gonna give a kid to a professional killer?
- You may have a point there.
- Maybe I could just steal a kid.
They're small. How hard can that be?
That's the thinking
you gotta get away from.
But I'd be a great father, Oz.
I would. I'd be a great dad.
I'd teach the kid how to play baseball.
- I've always been good with a bat.
- True.
And, I mean, when I was kid,
I had this cool little slingshot, right?
And I could make a slingshot
for my little boy.
And I could teach him how to use it.
And if he couldn't get it right away...
...I'd be patient. I wouldn't yell at him.
I wouldn't make him cry.
Jimmy, there's a lot of people looking.
Things with the husband
not so well going?
I was thinking...
...if you were to have sex
with another man...
...it would make Jimmy jealous.
Oh, yeah?
- Like with who?
- Well, let's say...
...with me, for example.
You look good with a gun.
Did you have a good relationship
with your father, Oz?
- We were like pals.
- Like to kill my father.
Like to take an ice pick
and stick it right in his eyeball.
Still wanna throw up.
Can you help me?
Can you tell me? I mean, what the...?
What the hell is going on here?!
Why are we all on this big,
spinning ball that we call Earth?!
Why? Why?
You ever hear of avoidance behavior?
I don't wanna talk about that...
Let's talk about avoidance behavior.
Like sitting here in a bar...
...drinking shots instead of saving Cynthia?
- She'll be fine, Oz.
- What do you mean?
- I'll tell you one thing:
I am not gonna go out there
and risk my ass for my wife...
- My wife!
- Whatever!
I'm not risking my ass before I get
a few things off my chest.
Fine. Say them. What do you wanna say?
- You know I was a bed wetter?
- You don't do it anymore, do you?
At 12, I saw my dad
naked in the shower.
Well, that's probably why you wet the bed.
Very Freudian. Jungian.
- We had some great times.
- You and your father?
No! Me and Cynthia!
- That's almost vomit.
- What was it like when Cynthia told you...
...she was pregnant?
- Oh, well, that was a beautiful moment.
- She's got a great rack, doesn't she?
- I'm sorry?
I mean, she was so wild.
So wild. I mean...
...one time we wrecked
an entire suite at the Hotel Drake.
- Seven thousand dollars' worth of damage.
- Let's stop talking about you and my wife.
I mean, we didn't
come out of the room for four days.
But I don't gotta tell you, do I?
You're married to her,
you lucky son of a bitch.
- What is this thing?
- What we've been building.
- Get it out of here!
- Why?
Because I hate it!
It makes me sad.
What's happening?
What's happening now?
Where are you going now?
Check.
Good morning...
What the hell is this?
Just give me five more minutes, baby.
You are really noisy in the morning.
Jimmy, what the hell happened
last night?
And why does my ass hurt?
- You fell down the stairs.
- Oh, good. So nothing happened.
Of course not. Not really.
- What does that mean?
- We were just a couple of guys...
...helping each other out. That's all.
- I'm sorry, but what does that mean?
It was a really magical night, Oz.
Don't ruin it.
- What is it now?
- That thing.
- Oh, this?
- I knew it.
- Oh, my God.
- You guys enjoy your slumber party?
This is not what it looks like. Right?
- Where's Strabo?
- He got away.
- I'm kidding. He's right here.
- Okay, well, I'm gonna put some clothes on.
- You want some help?
- I think I'm fine. Thank...
- A little male bonding?
- Just like C block, huh, Strabo?
I fell down the stairs, Strabo.
Going out to get some coffee.
I should probably
put some clothes on first.
Yeah.
- Hey, Oz, can you come in here for a sec?
- Yes.
Listen, that was not what you...
Let me close that.
Why are you bottomless?
I hated that skirt.
- You don't like that shirt too?
- Came with the skirt.
I see. I mean, I really see.
What are you doing?
Oz.
You like my perfume? Smell it.
- I've been a little stuffed up, feeling nasally.
- Smell it.
Yes. Yes, I do.
It's...
You like my bra?
This... Here it is. It's a purple shirt.
- Give me your hand.
- What are you gonna do...
Give it!
Feel my heart.
I don't think that's your heart.
Isn't your heart in between all that?
My heart is broken.
Can you feel that?
Yes. Yes, I do. Yes, I...
It's so broken, Oz!
- Jill!
- Oz!
- I'm so sad. Oz!
- Don't be sad.
What's all this?
First my ex-wife and now my wife-wife.
No, no, no. She just hated her outfit.
- He wants to talk to you for a second.
- No, you.
I've been waiting a long time for this, Oz.
Oz? I think Oz is gonna be out
for a good half-hour, 45 minutes, Jill.
I didn't... I just...
Jimmy, I...
You do love me, don't you?
Up on your toes. Stand up.
Come on, tippy-time, tippy-time.
- Why can't I stay in here?
- There you go. Sit down.
Read a nice book.
Oh, God!
- Yeah, baby!
- That feels so good!
She just hated her outfit.
Yippee ki-yay!
Yeah!
You believe I fell down the stairs, right?
What stairs?
- Hello?
- Bring me the phone.
- Put Liberace on.
- Is this who I think is this?
- Back from the dead?
- Yeah, Lazlo, skip the formalities.
Call you at 2:00 and tell you
where we'll make the exchange.
Well, it better be 2 on the dot
or I start cutting off the batch's fingers...
...one at a time! Wouldn't that be nice...
...to get little pieces of the girl?
One, two, three...
...little tiny pieces.
- Drop dead.
- What'd he say?
- He said hi.
- We'll need more firepower.
- I got guns. All you need.
Oz, you stud.
- Here they are. What do you think?
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God, you have an H and K MP5K.
- Can we hurry? It's almost 2.
We're gonna be fine.
Oh, wait, can I see this?
- Allow me. I got it.
- Okay.
Gotta be careful with these things.
I got it.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, topnotch.
It's almost 2. We've gotta
load them up and move them out.
- Don't screw around.
- Careful.
- All right.
- There.
I got it. I got it.
Hold on, Oz.
Would you be careful of the fixtures?
I hurt the side part of my head.
Nice guns. Put them in the back seat.
You made her carry all the guns, Oz?
Okay, can we call Lazlo? It's after 2.
Jimmy, you're late.
Bring Cynthia to the Beverly Center.
- Meet at the food court in an hour.
- I wanna talk to my son.
You're gonna have to
hold on a minute.
- Go get Strabo.
- I'll get Strabo.
- I just said that.
- Right.
Go.
Strabo.
Damn it!
I can't find Strabo.
I think he's gone.
- What?
- He's not where we left him.
Hold on.
What do you mean?
I'm holding, I'm holding.
There's just pieces of wood...
- Where the hell is Strabo, people?
- In the trunk.
Okay. How did Strabo
get in the trunk, Oz?
- I don't know.
- Well, get him out.
- Where are the keys?
- In here, with me.
- It keeps getting better.
- Why's he in the trunk?
I don't know! You were
supposed to be watching him!
Tulip!
- Hold on, Lazlo.
- All right, you know what?
No more holding.
Put my son on the phone now!
- Your son's...
- Strabonitz?
- Your son's in the trunk right now.
- The trunk? I wanna talk to my son!
Strabo, your father
wants to talk to you.
What?
- Did you get the gist of that?
- Yes.
You locked my son in the trunk?
No, no, sir. No, sir.
He locked himself in there.
This I believe. Fine.
You have a spare key?
- A spare key?
- No. Car Ranch Rentals only gave us one.
- Negative on the spare key.
- What about a locksmith?
- Do you know of one in the area?
- It's your town, dentist.
You should know where a...
Fine, you know what, Mr. Brain?
The trunk release button,
how about that?
Every car since 1985 has
a trunk release button.
Find it, open the trunk
and let my boy out.
There's a button on the driver's side.
Every car since 1985...
We kill them the moment we
see them. In the head.
- I can't find it.
- What kind of piece of shit car is this?
- Well, Car Ranch Rentals.
- It's a hitter!
- A hitter. Lazlo's got a hitter on us.
- Did you hire a hitter?
Did I? I don't remember, really.
- Is someone shooting at you?
- Your hitter is hitting at us!
That's bad. My son is there!
- Tell the hitter to stop.
- Your boss says to stop.
- His son's with us. Stop!
- This is Lazlo.
- Stop shooting!
- That's a direct Hungarian order!
Let me find speakerphone.
- Cease fire!
- What's going on? Talk to me.
He's not listening to you.
Well, you should fire him.
- Are you kidding?
- That was me.
- Try not to shoot Oz, honey.
- Yeah.
Let's go, kids!
Get up!
You are in no danger.
If she moves,
put your cane through her eye.
Unbelievable.
- How did you do that?
- Every car since 1985...
...had a little button right here.
All right, come on out of there...
- What is this?
- That's a dead hostage, Oz.
- That is what that is.
- That can't be good.
No, you're right. That's not good.
It looks like he got shot in the foot.
Who dies from a shot in the foot?
He probably got shot when
the hitter was shooting.
That's really great. Well done, Jill.
Hey, look, shit happens.
That's right.
Shit happens, to you.
All the time!
You know why? Because you don't
follow the ABC's of killing.
- There's an ABC's of killing?
- Shut up!
How was I supposed to know
he'd climb in the trunk?
- That's a good question.
- I mean...
I know! How about you
just watch him...
...and you don't let him
climb in!
I am a professional marksman.
It's not my job to babysit...
You know what? I think
you have to hit something...
...to count as a marksman.
- Ozzie. Harriet.
Can we stop fighting and go get my wife?
Well, you can just forget about
that, Oz. Cynthia is as good as dead.
- What? Don't say that.
- I am saying it.
She's as good as dead.
We have nothing...
...thanks to Jill. Look at this guy.
- Don't pin this on me!
If I'm a screwup,
what are you doing with me?
You know what?
That's a really good question.
I'm out of here.
Well, you're not going, are you?
Hold on a minute.
You're gonna need the keys.
- Bye-bye.
- I'm serious.
If I get in that car, you're
never gonna see me again.
Careful backing out, hon.
Let's go.
Bag.
Why don't you take your pal Strabo
with you. Remember him?
The Hungarian mobster
that you let die?
He's sorry. He's very sorry!
She's coming back. I mean,
she's gonna come back, right?
- I don't think so.
- Oh, well, this is just great.
What are we gonna do now?
You know what? I'm gonna leave.
You're on your own, Oz.
I thought we were friends.
Well, that's what you get
for trusting a contract killer, Oz.
You son of a bitch.
You can't do this to Cynthia. Okay?
Not okay. Your darling Cynthia's
not completely innocent in all this, Oz.
- What? What does that mean?
- Shit, shit, shit! Jill took my bag!
So?
- So there was something really important...
...in the other bag, okay, Oz?
Great.
- Hello.
- Dentist, you hung up on me.
- Are you insane?
- Lazlo.
- Hey, there was a button in the trunk.
- That's great news.
- Put my son on the phone, damn it!
- He's...
We're gonna have to
push back that meeting, Lazlo.
No, no. No pushing.
Put him on the phone.
I'm sorry, what? I can't hear you.
There seems to be a little static.
- Are you going through a canyon?
- Am I going through a canyon? No.
Hello?
- Hello?
- Lazlo? Lazlo?
Dentist! Can you hear me?
You're seconds from dead.
Strabonitz.
Hey, Jill.
- It's me. How you doing?
- Let me ask you something.
If you hadn't taken the wrong bag,
would we be talking?
- Are you mad or something?
- Get real.
- I mean, seriously.
- No.
All right? You happy now?
I chased you away
so I could protect you, Jill.
- I don't know why you don't believe that.
- I don't believe you.
- Jill.
- I don't trust you.
How am I supposed to have a kid
with somebody I don't trust?
Forget it. I don't even know if
I wanna have a kid with you anymore.
Hold on a minute.
I think that if I were pregnant
right now, I wouldn't even tell you.
If you had a son and l...
And you were his mom and I was his dad...
...you wouldn't let me see him?
- Not once.
- Don't say that.
- Take it back right now.
- I'm not.
You better tell me everything now
or I'm not gonna help you.
How far back does this thing go?
Like a couple days or something.
You're so full of it.
You're gonna lie to me more?
All right, months.
You happy now?
And why was Cynthia in on it?
I wanted to keep you
out of harm's way.
- You trusted her not to get hurt.
- Jill.
I gotta go help Oz. For me to do that,
I've gotta go up there.
- Just do everything I told you, all right?
- Don't worry.
I'll remember everything you told me.
Call Mrs. Himelfarb,
remind her to floss...
...cancel my appointments
for the rest of my life...
...send in as much nitrous as you can,
call the FBI.
- What?
- Call the FBI!
- What's wrong?
- What's wrong? What's wrong?
I'll tell you.
Everything's wrong.
Take a look around you.
Nothing's right.
Cynthia got kidnapped by Hungarian killers.
And instead of calling the FBI...
...or the police,
like every other rational man, I thought:
"Hey, let's try to get in contact with
somebody else that kills a lot of people."
So I went down to Mexico,
which is heavily underdeveloped...
...and I asked him to help me.
Did he?
No, he didn't help me out.
He didn't help me out!
Know what he did?
He put on bunny slippers...
...he shot at me and then
he cooked me some chicken!
I'm gonna be okay.
I'm gonna calm down...
...I'm gonna go downstairs and I'm gonna
take a nice, leisurely drive in my Porsche.
Wait a minute. I can't drive my Porsche,
because I don't have one anymore.
That's gone, that's history,
that's archives!
We left the Porsche so we could get
on a bus and rent some other car.
And you know why?
Because I don't. Do you?
Some kind of GPS,
I don't know, system.
- What's that smell?
- I'll tell you what that smell is. It's me.
I smell. And you know why?
I've been wearing this suit
for three days. I smell like ass.
Or foot. Or some kind of foot...
...that's been lodged up deep, deep, deep
inside an ass. I'll tell you the worst thing:
I woke up naked next to another
naked man who admittedly wets the bed.
So if you talk to anybody
or anybody calls here...
...you tell them I fell down
a flight of stairs.
- Yes, sir.
- Don't "Yes, sir" me!
- Call the FBI.
- Calling. I'm calling.
Dial F-B-I.
Call the FBI and tell them
I fell down a flight of stairs!
Going to the feds is the thing
that's gonna get Cynthia killed.
What are you doing here?
I don't need you anymore.
I can handle this on my own.
I'm an adult.
You okay?
Thanks.
Let's face it, Oz. Kicking ass is not
your expertise. That's my job.
Hanging on to the woman you love
is where I fall a little short.
- How do you do that?
- What?
That. That.
One minute I wanna kill you,
the next minute you got me...
...feeling sorry for you.
- Oz, you really are a good guy.
And I don't want you, Cynthia or anyone
else paying for my past sins.
I thought you said friendship
was overrated.
I'm a liar.
- So, what do we do?
- Go get Cynthia.
- How?
- You just leave that to Jimmy Tudeski.
- God, Julie. Julie, Julie...
...don't call the FBI!
- Julie who?
My receptionist.
Your wife's replacement.
- Julie, what did you do?
- I chloroformed his ass.
Why?
You don't have to tell me why.
Now, you can go quietly or your ass
can get the chloroform too.
- What kind of receptionist are you?
- The kind that doesn't forget...
...who murdered her brother.
- What?
Look, I'm gonna get
the temp agency on the phone.
Don't you dare make a move,
Dr. Oseransky. Keep your ass right there.
Julie. Julie, if that is your real name...
My name is Jules. Jules Figueroa.
- Frankie Figs?
- Frankie Figs.
You remember that? He was my brother.
And I do believe you knew him.
- I'll take that chloroform now.
- Yeah, I know you will.
- You smell great, baby.
- Oz.
You know, I don't have to be
at work today. We can:
Oz.
Jimmy.
Jimmy. Jimmy!
It's been a long time since
I've been chloroformed.
Still got that little zing to it,
though.
Tastes like they put a bunch of pennies
in your mouth, doesn't it?
Jimmy, I'm sorry.
- I didn't find it.
- What?
You've been here three days.
- I got into the safe. It's not there.
- Safe?
- It's here somewhere.
- This isn't exactly...
...what we talked about, either.
- Calm down.
- What do mean, "Calm down"?
- All right? I'm on it.
What safe? Why are you guys
talking together so much?
Have you been involved in this
from the beginning?
- Oz...
- Correct me if I'm wrong...
...but we took vows.
One was you're not
supposed to pretend you're kidnapped...
...and get your husband shot at
while he's trying to save you.
- That was uncalled for.
- I'm not a lawyer...
...but I believe this is grounds for divorce.
And what is that sound?
- That's chain saws.
- Chain saw. Check.
Hack tub.
What is that for?
- What is it?
- They hack us up into pieces in that...
...so blood doesn't get everywhere.
- I see.
They put the hacked-up
pieces in those bags.
- Are you done?
- Yes, he's done.
Jimmy Tulip.
The rat-shit scum of Chicago.
Mr. Tough Guy...
...served up to me on a platter
by the pretty black girl.
That stings.
I made you who you are
and you stab me in the heart...
...with something sharp.
He made you who you are?
Oh, yes. Could not fire a slingshot
until I taught him how.
"Pay attention, little boy. Hold it firm.
Stop crying and watch.
Like this."
- Where's Strabo?
- I'm pretty sure he's with Janni right now.
Where is my son?
- Where's my boy?!
- All right, that's it. I've had enough.
- Oz.
- No. If you ever wanna see your son...
...alive again, you'll let
us go right now.
Is that right?
Yeah, that's right.
And if we're not out of here by 11:00...
...Jill's gonna put one in Strabo's forehead,
just like Jimmy put one in Janni's forehead.
- It wasn't pretty.
- Give me a gun.
- Not bad, Oz.
- Thanks.
- I think it's Jimmy's wife.
- What?
No. That was going so well.
- What is this?
- I wanna come in...
...and talk business with you.
- Or else.
- Or else what?
Or else I'm afraid I'm gonna
have to blow Strabo's head off.
Oh, no, no, no.
Strabo, you all right?
He's fine.
He can't talk, he's duct-taped.
I got this car wired with explosives.
- You let me in, he'll be fine.
- Fine.
Come in, do whatever you want, apparently.
Get the broad! Get the car! Get the Strabo!
Wait a minute.
What is in the big purse?
- Nothing, it's... I'm good.
- It's what?
- Take a right.
- This way.
What the fook are you
assholes up to now?
Look who's here.
Can I ask you a questionnaire
how you found this place?
Nice Porsche you got.
You still have the Porsche?
Let me explain when we all get
a moment together...
...the concept of the secret hideout.
- All right!
Drop your weapons now
and slide them to me...
...or I press the button and Strabo gets
blown to little Hungarian meatballs.
- Don't push nothing.
- I'm gonna push it. Drop them! Now!
- Drop them!
- Drop it.
- Go ahead. Come on.
- On the floor.
Kick them over. Step away.
- Untie Oz and Cynthia.
- No untying...
- Do it! Untie them.
- Let's see where it's going.
All right. Come on, come on.
Aren't you forgetting something?
Am I forgetting something?
I don't think so.
- They had a terrible fight.
- Did they?
- What if I had something you want?
- I would be baffled, to begin with.
Or, more precisely...
...half of something you want.
Don't.
You have Jimmy's half.
- Would you cut me in for a slice?
- You want a slice of the pee?
Maybe...
- Keep talking.
- I wanna work for you.
- Of course you do.
- I don't have any allegiances.
I'm all yours. And I could be your
most valuable hitter.
You shut up or I'll
blow your brains out!
First thing I'm going to need
is my son Strabo in my company.
Secondly, maybe a little test.
I'm thinking, kill Jimmy.
In the melon. One shot.
- What do you say?
- Name the time and place.
Is now good for you?
- Right here, right now?
- Right now.
- You gotta be kidding me, right?
- What the hell are you doing?
Take your little cross back.
What'll you do without
your good luck charm?
- Stop screwing around.
- Shut up, Oz!
That's right, Jill, stop screwing around.
You're not gonna shoot anybody.
Just tell me you're not
still in love with Cynthia.
- I'm not gonna do that.
- Why?
She's my ex-wife. I still have feelings
for her and I always will.
- That's a really bad answer.
- Shut up, Oz.
You can't even just say it, can you?
Just say it.
This is reminding me now
of my favorite soup opera:
The Hourglass of My Sand Children.
Listen, you're either a shooter
or you're not.
I am. I am.
I am.
Here's an idea for you:
- Got an elevator shaft around here, Lazlo?
- I'm sorry?
Because I could fall down that,
you know. Die that way.
- Stop.
- That would be the only way to get killed.
- Shut up!
- You couldn't even hit that lamp over there.
I'll give you a tip. You wanna hit that
lamp, you should aim at me.
She aimed and hit the lamp.
- Lucky shot.
- I'm gonna give you one last chance, baby.
You don't have the balls.
- This from a guy who rarely gets it up.
- We never had that problem.
Not helping.
Why isn't anybody helping?
I think you have to be in love
with someone to get it up, Jill.
Shoot him.
You're never gonna be a hit girl...
...just a stupid, stumbling, bumbling,
can't-kill-anything ex-dental assistant.
- Jimmy, Jimmy.
- He's dead?
- Yes?
- He's dead. He's dead!
He's dead! I didn't think you
had it in you, quite frankly.
Don't cry. Everything's going
to be fine. Go get Strabo, now.
Give me this. For the record,
this is, what, a garage door opener?
Very clever.
So clever, I want you to keep
that aimed at her, please.
- Wait. I thought we had a deal.
- "I thought we had a deal." No.
Locked.
Lazlo, the car is loaded with Primacord.
I'm sure it is.
The first dollar
I ever stole is back together.
- You okay? You okay?
- Yeah.
You killed Strabonitz.
Oh, look what I did.
Good work, Jimmy.
"Jammy, Jammy."
Nice work with that chair, Oz.
Way to go, Cyn.
- Come here, baby.
- You're alive?
I mean, good, but you...
Don't even think about it. You were
in on this whole thing from the beginning!
Of course. It's an old routine.
It's the Skokie Switcheroo.
"The Skokie Switch..."? Where do
you guys come up with these names?
I just watched my friend
get shot through the heart.
- Larry's House of Halloween.
- And what is the deal with that lamp?
I saw her shoot the lamp.
The first round was live, the rest
were blanks. Try and keep up.
- We are gonna have such a talk later.
- Sons of batches!
So how far back does this go?
Hell, you were shooting at me in Mexico.
Was that all part of the plan?
As a matter of fact, it was, yeah.
- You killed my Strabo!
- Actually, Strabonitz was already dead.
Your hitter got him
when she was shooting at us.
- This true?
- Lazlo, shit happens.
Shit...
Yeah, watch this shit happen.
- All right. Take it easy.
- Was that real? Is she really dead?
I mean, was that a fake bullet?
Jimmy, let me propose something
before you start the killing.
Regroup the Gogolak gang.
Fifty-fifty, you and me.
Like the old days.
Murder, mayhem, a couple of laughs.
I don't think so, Lazlo.
Jill, tie him up.
- Wait.
- What am I gonna tie him up for?
- I'm gonna kill him.
- No, he said...
I said that, but we can't.
Of course you can't.
You can't kill anybody for real.
I can. It's point-blank range.
I didn't mean you can't shoot him...
...I mean you just can't shoot him.
- Come on.
- You said I'll make my bones.
- On somebody else.
- You can't kill him.
- How do you "make bones"?
She wants to make a name for herself.
You said I could!
- Will you just listen?
- Tell me why.
- You heard what he said!
- Tell me why not!
Because he's my father!
- Even I didn't know about this.
- See? See?
It doesn't feel good to not be involved
in the plan, to not know what...
- He's your father?
- I raised you as one of my own.
- That's far enough.
- I made him a man!
A man who can't kill his papa.
Step aside, Jill. It could go right through.
Jimmy.
- Jill, shoot Papa in the foot.
- Straight through or leave a souvenir?
- Souvenir.
- Wait.
That's gotta hurt.
- Who is that? The fake police?
- Okay, we gotta go.
I'm not going anywhere until somebody
tells me what this is all about.
Cynthia, help me get Oz out of here.
Thanks for the inheritance, Pops.
- Way to go, Cyn.
- You'll never live to spend a dime, Jimmy!
We're rich! We're rich!
- Baby, you were so good.
- I had a good teacher.
I'm so glad we're so overjoyed.
I've never been this confused in my life.
I think you dropped this a while back.
No, just borrowing it
from an old friend, that's all.
- Don't need it anymore, Cyn.
- Okay.
Would somebody tell me
what's going on?
This is what's going on.
See that number right there?
That is Lazlo Gogolak's main account
in the Grand Caymans.
Somewhere around 280 million dollars,
half of which is yours.
Your tooth-pulling days are over, Oz.
- That was the plan?
- Yes!
- Were you in on it?
- I didn't know until this afternoon.
Why couldn't I have been involved?
I could have played a part.
I minored in theater.
Two hundred and eighty million dollars?
That's it. This is too much.
It's great, but it's too much.
- Any more surprises?
- Just one.
- What?
- I guess the doctors were wrong.
- What do you mean?
- I'm pregnant.
Oh, my God, congratulations!
Oh, my God, are you serious?
I'm gonna be a dad?
We're not gonna start
with that again, are we?
Put the top up, okay?
It's just... It's embarrassing.
- Come on, come and get me.
- Freeze, right there!
- Cross, cross.
- Watch it, buster.
Anybody for cookie, coffee, tea?
Mother, please.
One of you, could
you just shoot me? Please.