Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Colonel George
Herbert Merryweather...
ashes to ashes...
dust to dust.
Aah, Miss Merryweather.
This being the last
will and testament of
Colonel George Herbert
Merryweather of London.
He... he...
lost it all?
Including the house?
No!
No, Papa can't have been in London.
Why, he wrote to me and
said that he was coming home,
he wouldn't arrive and not...
Aah, well...
Your father did leave you this book...
as your inheritance.
"The Ancient Chronicles
of Moonacre Valley"
I know it's hard...
but you know I...
I'm sure that your father did...
did love you.
He just... um,
and... and you know,
everybody does have to go out on
their own at some point in their...
lives.
Miss Heliotrop, I'm fine!
Really!
Yes...
"Once upon a perfect time...
many hundreds of years ago...
when the old magic called
Moonacre Valley...
there was a young woman whose
skin glint as pale as the star...
and whose heart was
as pure as a meteorite's...
such was her bravery and goodness...
she was beloved by nature...
as if she was their daughter.
One fateful night...
the moon blessed her
with an extraordinary gift...
with a tinge of the
magic of the valley...
forever!
The moon power!
From that day forward...
she was known...
as the Moon Princess!
Two ancient families lived in harmony
at the edge of the valley...
sharing nature's bounty.
Daughter to the De Noir clan...
the Moon Princess
was deeply in love
and was to be married
to Sir Wolf Merryweather.
Her father,
Sir William De Noir,
blessed the union by presenting
the couple with a rare black lion.
For my daughter's bridegroom!
Thank you, father!
In turn,
Sir Wolf gave his bride a unicorn.
Littered from the
wild white horses of the sea.
Only an animal of such beauty and purity
could be the companion of the Moon Princess.
Her heart overflowed with happiness!
The Moon Princess revealed
the magical powers to both families.
This was found deep
in the heart of the ocean.
This pearl was given to us
by mother nature herself!
Promising untold riches to us all.
Look!
They have a unique power!
They can reveal the truth
in man's heart!
Legend told of their unique powers,
so strong the pearls
will grant every wish.
Both good and evil!
Good bye...
You be Miss Maria Merryweather?
My man!
Quick!
Madame...
Get on with you!
Good bye...
yes, yes, yes...
Miss Heliotrop?
Maria...
When your dear mother died,
I promised her faithfully
that I'll take care of you.
So I'm not going to abandon you now!
If you're going to live with your uncle,
or in the middle of the country-side,
then I shall be there with you.
Where are my charcoal tablets?
These are doing nothing
for my indigestion.
How can I possibly go
live in the country?
It's like a camp-site!
Maria, there's only one thing
that can save us now.
Clever girl,
French,
needle point.
What's happening?
Have we arrived?
Is he deaf or something?
The man is obviously a half wit.
Who are they?
What do they want?
Don't worry my dear,
Sir Benjamin will protect us, I'm sure!
Miss...
Welcome to Moonacre!
Unfortunate circumstances.
There we are, nothing to be done.
I'm pleased to meet you, Uncle.
Miss Heliotrop.
Oh, Sir Benjamin.
Oh, what a journey we had!!!
Not one hour from this
very door we were accosted by
a bunch of ruffians.
Madame, please!
- It...
Tell me your fascinating story
some other time if I may.
His name is Wolf.
There are those
who find him alarming.
He can kill in an instant.
But you're a Merryweather.
He very probably won't harm you.
Miss Heliotrop,
your room is over there to the right.
Oh, thank you, Sir Benjamin.
Well, come along Maria.
I'm sure that your room...
will be next to mine.
No, Maria's room is up in the tower.
But, I'm kind...
You have to inspect the room first
before you turn your
nose up at whatever it is.
Good night, Uncle!
Charmed, I'm sure.
What on earth is this?
Oh, no!
No, I think not.
Young lady.
We're taking breakfast in here.
Where did you get this from?
Oh um, papa left it to me.
Well, he had no right...
This belong here.
But, that's mine!!
Miss Heliotrop!
Help!
Help, tell him he can't
take my father's book from me!
Maria!
Good question!
Why don't you just speak...
That he can't just go and...
Maria!
Don't worry.
I'm sure that he's just keeping
it safe somewhere for you.
Sit down.
Have your porridge.
Miss.
There be your breakfast, Miss.
Maria, you really must
try this delicious omelet.
Hum,um, a dish best
enjoyed in silence, I'm told.
Uncle, when can you return
my father's book to me?
Now,
you certainly have a very,
very good cook, Sir Benjamin.
Have you... have you had her long?
Madame, no woman has stepped
in this house for years!
And believe me,
the silence has been blissful.
Now, I must say, this country food is
doing wonders for my trapped wind!
Madame, please! Can't a man enjoy
a meal in his own home in silence?
Well, do tell us Uncle...
Why did you invite such
irritating and noisy females
into your nice quiet house?
I'd love to know.
My useless brother died in debt
and it fell on me to take you in.
The man was a... cowardly
good for nothing.
Sir Benjamin!!
How dare you say that?!
My father was a Colonel!
Yes.
And he died in debt owing money
to half the regiment.
He fought for his country!
And got himself killed
in a backstreet gambling den.
Borrowed money once too many times
from the wrong sort of money lenders.
He wouldn't take money from me,
would he?
Oh no.
Damn, all his pride.
You're a Merryweather, Maria...
And this is where you belong.
Here, at Moonacre.
There we are.
Nothing else to be done.
Library is private
and my study prohibited.
And in here...
The East wing, closed...
the West wing, out of bounds.
There we are.
- And here...
- Uncle, about that attack yesterday.
Can't something be done?
Yes... keep your little nose out.
I beg your pardon?
Just keep out of the forest.
But why?
Who are they?
There's a band of ruffians in the woods.
The De Noir clan.
You mean like the "De Noir"
from the story book?
No, no, no... these are real enough.
Poachers, bandits, plunderers, robbers.
Ladies.
This should suit your needs.
And this will be your classroom.
(Speaking French)
Digweed...
Bring me my whip.
You weren't expecting me to...
She can ride, can she?
Oh, Sir Benjamin,
it's a matter of fact
that a lady should never be
allowed to sit on a horse!
They're unstable and
they're vicious creatures.
I think, Sir Benjamin, it might be an
appropriate moment for me to retire.
Take care!
Come, Maria.
Every Merryweather rides.
It's in the blood.
This is Peririco... she's a little
feisty but she's a loyal stead.
Just hold out your hand.
I give you my word,
it'll stay attached to you, Miss.
You see, Miss?
She knows.
- You're getting on well with Peririco...
- Yes, Uncle.
We should be heading back.
It's getting late.
Uncle, I'm really enjoying this.
Could I stay out a little longer?
As long as you promise to stay
within the Moonacre boundary.
Remember...
I can only vouch for your safety
if you stay out of the forest.
I will be home before long,
and Peririco will take good care of me.
Very well.
Goodbye Uncle!
What's so special
about the forest anyway?
You stay here.
Oh, little baby.
Who did this to you?
One catch two captives.
What do you want?
Let's go. Catch an animal that
comes to get you coming to help!
I know who you are!
You're bandits and plunderers!
You!
You're coming with us now!
My father's just dying
to make your acquaintance.
It's the demon dog!
Thank you,
you obedient doggy!
Come on, little one...
Let me take you home.
Robin, it's your father!
What did I do to deserve
such a prize filth for a son?
I hope Peririco gave you an
educational tour of the estate.
I have a wounded hare.
That, young lady,
is a rare Moonacre rabbit.
By far the most beautiful,
brave and serene creature.
And as you've brought
her in from the wild,
she's now your responsibility.
And with your knowledge of animals,
I very much doubt it will
live to see the morning.
Keep out of the forest child!
Maria?
Goodness gracious!
Look at your...
dress!
Maria, there's something
alive on your body!
Miss Heliotrop, please calm down!
This is a Moonacre rabbit...
A beautiful, brave and serene creature.
I intend to look after it.
And I'm going to call her Serena.
Uncle?
I really think you and I
have some matters to discuss.
There are some very strange things
going on in this house.
First off, who always keeps my dress
and leaves the biscuits in my room?
The stars on my ceiling move.
There's a mysterious
white horse outside.
This place is falling apart,
things appear to move,
and the piano plays
music on its own!
I mean, I have never even
seen the kitchen.
So where on earth
does all this food come from?
Do you ever stop asking questions?
Uncle, I...
Sit down, my dear.
Wolf?
Where are we going?
Wolf?!
Marmaduke Scarlet.
Chef of all chefs,
at your service, Little Princess.
How do you do that?
Get me some sherbet, will you?
Chop, chop...
I'm not actually really sure
where your sherbet is...
Never you mind...I'll get it...
Are you the one who leaves
the milk and biscuits for me?
These past few days,
it all comes back to me.
Scarlet please, will you stop
yourself for just one moment?
Surely somebody in this household
must be able to answer my questions.
Dear Princess, a little bit of magic...
has come back to the valley.
You obviously haven't
finished reading the book.
The book?
But my uncle took it
away from me.
In the library,
you'll find a slim volume,
Secret Doors and Private Lockers...
Perhaps a piece of...
stargazer pie for your study.
The Moon Princess truly believed
in the goodness of all.
But the men soon fell to the greed
that was in their heart.
Each desperate to claim
the power of the pearls for himself.
We are the chosen ones!
These pearls stay with
the De Noir clan forever!
Father?
Come! Be with me.
Let Moonacre be your home
and be your family.
Speak true!
With the power of these pearls,
I can claim the valley for myself.
No.
Together, I mean together
we could rule the valley.
These pearls belongs to no man,
they belong to nature!
Give it to me!!
No! Give them to me!!!
No no no!!!
I beg of you... please!!!
You cannot let your heart
be ruled by greed!
Betrayed by those she loved the most,
the Moon Princess unleashed
the power bestowed upon her,
and cast a terrifying
curse over them all.
Hear me!!!!
You've gone against the nature,
and you shall suffer for it!
Nature will wreak her revenge
and put a curse upon this valley.
One day,
a pure heart will walk among you.
If she can't lift the curse,
when the 5000th moon
rises from the sea,
this valley shall be plunged
into eternal darkness!!!!
The moon pearls vanished that day,
and where to find them
remained a secret.
Marmaduke!
The house... the valley... it's all...
- Cursed!
Oh yes!
Take a look around you.
Everything's falling apart.
Ever since that terrible day,
the two families have
been totally consumed
with pride...
and blind hatred.
And the only person
who can break this curse
is a true Moon Princess!
The Moon Princess?
But...
she lived hundreds of years ago.
The legend tells...
of a little white horse,
a mystical companion
to protect her.
A magical creature...
invisible so they say...
to anyone...
except a true Moon Princess.
You mean...
I'm suppose to be this...
I'm supposed to undo this curse?
Everyone knows the legend.
Peace will never be restored...
until the pearls are return to the sea
and the families reunited!
This is all madness!
Time is slipping away.
the 5,000th moon...
to set it right.
Stop! Stop...
I don't want to hear another word!
You are all insane!!
Three hundred and eighty-four years...
times thirteen for the moon's per annum.
Plus...
seven moons for this year.
That's...
That makes...
four thousand nine hundred
and ninety-nine.
Oh Serena, the very next moon's
arrival will be the 5,000th moon.
Everyone knows the legend...
These pearls belongs to no man...
They belong to nature!
5,000 moons to set it right!!
You're a Merryweather...
You're the chosen one!
Keep out of the forest child!
I've to get out of this
remote place, Serena!
I don't want anything more
to do with this!
Miss Heliotrope
will take good care of you.
Maria....
Maria...
Who are you?
You look...
just like the lady in the painting.
Come along.
Oh, do come in!!
You naughty hedgehog!
In my favorite chair again!
You cheeky monkey!
Be nice and still,
don't make any sudden movement.
Then she won't be so scared!
I will try!
Oh! I was talking to the snake.
I rescued as many
injured creatures as I can.
And did you do the embroidery
and brought all those
strange dresses in my room?
Yes.
My name is Loveday.
Our time is nearly spent right here...
the moon shall not be our forever.
You saw something,
didn't you?
Didn't you?
Tell me what you saw.
I have to leave!
No no no no...
Stay with me!
I've frightened you, haven't I?
You see,
I'm not used to visitors.
And I do so much just
want to be your friend.
It's no use you know...
your father...
he tried to run away too.
But there is nowhere to hide.
He sent you here
because he loved you.
Because Moonacre
is where you belong.
You and I are the same.
Except...
Except?
Where I failed,
you might succeed.
What about my uncle?
Sir Benjamin... can't he help?
Never, ever mention that man to me again,
do you understand?
Your past is behind you.
Your future awaits you
if you want it.
You decide.
I want to help.
I just don't know what
I'm supposed to do to begin.
Find the pearls!
Nobody knows where they are.
Each family blames the other
for taking them.
They are both to blame.
The De Noir took the casket
then we must have the key.
The key!
Now for the casket.
You have to take me there.
- Where?
- To De Noir.
You've to take me
to where they live.
There it is!
Loveday...
are you alright?
I'm sorry!
I can never go back there!
Loveday!
Father, I could pad and place a scythe
and nail it under their roof.
Don't go near Moonacre...
that house is damned!
No...
the word is...
she is about to meet her downfall.
How kind of you to join us,
Moon Princess.
Oh...
Oh, and what is this?
She has brought us
the lost key, gentlemen!
Wasn't it terrible of the De Noir
to have the moon pearls
hidden up here all the time...
haven't we?
Well, it's true isn't it?
Your ancestors stole them!
My ancestors?!
Well, perhaps Princess...
I should introduce you...
Maria Merryweather...
the last Moon Princess.
Sir William.
The very first De Noir.
The pearls casket!
And you so very kindly
brought us the key.
You've hidden them!!
They were never there, girl!
Your filthy Merryweather family
took them!
Before he...
picked up the box!
They stole the pearls.
But soon...
the final moon will rise...
and the thieving Merryweathers
will be punished!
I'm glad that we have you here.
There's nothing anyone can do to stop it!
At last the entire valley will be ours!
And the De Noir will finally
feast upon revenge!!
Leave me alone, you ogre!
You know,
for someone in your predicament,
I have to admire your spirit!
Witch!
Hey!
Lock her in!
Welcome to your new house!!
Hope you make friends
with the roaches!
Guard, watch her...
she's slippery.
Where is that girl?
Unbelievable!
Absolutely irresponsible!
Oh, this dress!
Come back here, you witch!!!
The girl has escaped!
Princess!
What're you going to do now?
She won't find her way
out of the forest.
- She can't have come this far...
- Let's try north!
Go Robin, find her!
I want her killed!
I want her to stop the curse.
Their death is our victory!
Stupid girl...
should have stayed where you were.
Robin!
This way!
Oh... Wolf!!
Quickly!
Can you find the way home?
That demon dog
can't protect you forever!
Now that be Miss Maria home, sir.
Uncle Benjamin...
Miss Heliotrop!
I'm really sorry!
Where are your...
where are...
Miss Heliotrop!
I'm perfectly alright...
yes.
But what happened
to your clothes, my dear one?
How dare you come home
in this manner and at this hour?
I'm sorry but you don't
know what happened, I was...
I was...
in the forest and...
In the forest?
Didn't I expressively forbid
you to go to the forest?
Yes.
But... listen,
I've so much to tell you!
Go upstairs this instance
and tidy yourself up!
But...
Just do as you're told!
You're not my father!
Maria!
Maria, open this door!
Listen...
It maybe possible...
that I was... a little rough earlier.
The point is you were gone
for such a long time.
I mean you didn't even tell us!
I...
We!
Miss Heliotrop was
beside herself with worry.
Maria...
I know that...
given that women and I
normally don't see eye to eye...
It wouldn't be untrue to say...
I'm glad that you're back.
Who put this back on the wall?!
Digweed? Digweed!!
Come and take this away!
Seems that there won't be
any stars left tonight, Serena.
The Moon is getting closer and closer.
What're we going to do?
How could you
leave me like that?!
In the forest.
This belongs to the
first ever Moon Princess.
Forgive me?
Fits you like a glove!
Oh Loveday, this is all hopeless.
What?
I'm as far away from actually
finding the pearls as ever.
Perhaps it's here somewhere...
hidden.
Come on, come with me.
Where?
Downstairs?
Oh no no, I'm not going downstairs.
Isn't it bad luck for the groom
to see the dress?
I wanted you to see me
just as I am before the wedding.
And what does that mean?
Benjamin.
I have to tell you something.
Something I should've told you
a long, long time ago.
My darling...
what ever is it?... Hmm?
I am not who you think I am.
I'm a De Noir.
A De Noir?
I was brought up to
despise the Merryweathers,
but later then I met you and
that changed everything.
You tricked me!
No!
You pretended to love me!
And all these times you
were plotting behind my back,
trying to find those
ridiculous pearls.
It was your father that sent you,
wasn't it?
No.
By marrying you,
I lost his love forever.
But Benjamin,
don't you see?
Our love could bring
our families back together!
Can put an end to
this dreadful curse!
Curse.
No, don't give me that nonsense!!
And you filled this house
with your De Noir flowers!!
No no please...
you don't understand.
Doesn't love change everything?
No... my dear...
but hate does.
So...
you missed your chance
to bring the families together.
He broke my heart.
I think he broke his heart too.
But he let me be lost forever.
It must have been
quite a shock for him.
I mean,
maybe if you've waited
for him to calm down.
Perhaps apologize?
Oh, me apologize?!
You don't understand, do you?
I'm starting
to understand one thing.
The real curse of this valley...
is pride!
Digweed, stop!
But that'll be the master wishes!
I'll be back.
Exactly!
Miss Maria,
tell me more about this curse!
There she is.
Each time when
a new Moon Princess arrives,
so does this picture.
But look at it...
look at it!
Digweed...
you can move now...
Oh...
thank goodness!
Can't you see?!
There, look!
She's showing us!
She took the pearls!
Maria...
are you telling us...
that the Moon Princess herself
took the Moon pearls?!
Yes!
Yes, and she's showing me
where she hid them!
But where?
Where did she put them?
They're in the trees somewhere...
out in the forest.
Well, that's a help.
No, I saw that it was nearby.
I think I'll know it
again if I saw it.
Hmm, what?
What?
There's only one person
who has walked the woods his whole life.
Someone who has it in his blood.
Robin?!
Impossible!
He's an arrogant so and so!
I never ever want
to see him again!
It's a point of honor.
It's a matter of...
Pride?!
Good luck, little Princess!!!
Bye!
Wait... wait...
No, Miss Heliotrop.
No, you won't stop me!
This is my home and
I'm going to fight for it!
No, no no...
I know you've got to do this.
I'm beginning to understand a little.
I believe in you!
- Bye...
- Bye, Miss.
But be careful!
I will!
That will be the post, sir...
Loveday?
Princess!
Giving yourself up?!
How good of you?
The grand trapper...
trapped!
Let me down,
you little witch!!
Certainly...
No no no, no don't you dare!!
Oh... my foot.
Thank you darling Serena.
Off you go.
Please!
Wait!
I'm really swelling,
I can feel my head hurting!
Oh no...
it was like that before...
- I would let you down if you do one thing for me.
- What?
Just promise you'll listen!
Say "I promise"!
Just say it!
I promise!
Alright, you beat me,
let me down!
Very well...
What about him?
You're a De Noir...
he very probably will hurt you.
I'm listening.
Miss De Noir.
Sir Benjamin.
- Well...
Benjamin?
I'm here.
- I believe apologies are in order.
- Yes, they are.
After all, one's behaviour have not been...
as it might.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Yes, you should be.
Beg your pardon?
It shall be easy to forgive you,
but...
Forgive me?!
What on earth
are you talking about?
Don't play games with me,
Benjamin Merryweather!
You asked me here!
- It was you who asked to see me!
- What!
Maria.
Where the devil is that girl?
- Goodbye!
- Robin, please!
I promised I'll listen to you,
and I have!
Robin, you've to help me,
you have to!!
You are a Merryweather!
- Right now I want to kill you.
- Kill me and the whole valley dies with me.
You and I can solve it
and we only have until moon rise.
Tonight!
I'm still listening.
She's back in the forest,
and this time...
she won't be leaving.
They are armed men out there
whose express aim it is to do her harm!
I would have never agreed.
I didn't know, you see.
I must go to her.
Oh, don't be a fool. I'll go.
I know the forest.
Wait!
If you'll forgive me...
I believe I know exactly
where Maria will be.
- You do?
- How do you?
I'm a superb chef, madame,
it follows that I should possess
a truly superb nose.
In my youth, when I
would roam those woods,
I could track anything that moved.
Plus she told me where
she was going.
What was that?
False trails...
What were you doing with
one of my ribbons in your pocket?
There are in the trees,
that is very distinctive...
It has massive roots
twisting around a big dark color.
I know where that is.
Suppose for a moment,
I do this to help you out.
And suppose we actually manage
to find the pearls... what then?
Well... we...
return the pearls to the sea
and then we go.
You know my father
is coming after you?
It's just a matter of finding
them before he finds me.
Miss De Noir, it's highly
dangerous out there,
this is no mission for a woman!
Perhaps you should have
told that to Maria.
As a matter of fact I did.
Frequently...
Wait!!
That will be another
female for the party.
Madame... you're not required
on this expedition.
Oh... that's better!
- That'll be your wind...
- Enough... Digweed...
I've been taking care of Maria
since she was a baby.
And I intend to protect her now!
I know which way to go!
Come on!
Marmaduke?
Marmaduke, you blithering ex-hunter,
what are you doing?
Sorry, sir...
It appears... my power's out here...
are not what they are in the kitchen.
Just show us where to go,
would you?!
I notice the house is falling down.
Sad to see the place
is in such a state of disrepair.
If you're so fond of it,
why did you run away from it?
You took everything I held dearly
and ripped it away from me.
How could I stay?
Run far, did you?
No, not very far...
But then you never came
to look for me, did you?
He spent months on horseback,
scouted the entire county, searching for you.
Marmaduke?
- Are you leading this expedition or not?
- Yes, sir. Yes.
Hum... strawberry.
This way!
I think we might have a
greater chance of finding her
if we divide and spread
the arc a little wider.
It should be clear over the
next hill... we're not far now.
Wolf!
Wolf!!!
Wolf?
Robin?
Robin?!
Wolf?
Wolf...
Wolf!!
Let's go boy!
Oh, this is pretty.
Isn't it enough for one
member of my family to betray me.
Now I find the half-brother
is a traitor too?
I will take care of this Princess...
myself... once and for all!
Wolf?
This is the place!
Where are the pearls?!
Listen!
The moon will kill us all!
Wolf, we have to find Maria!
Wolf!!
You!
How could you betray me like that?!
I will not let you take her, father.
Put the knife down, boy.
Father, please, you have to listen
to what Maria has to say!
Traitor!
You're nothing to me now.
Go!
I know where to find you again!
Back to where it all began.
In here.
Where did they go?
Robin, look at this!
Where are they?
It's her. It must be.
Where... where did you put them?
The pearls!
Open the door!
Robin, let's go!
It's so dark here.
Moon pearls... we need your power now...
show us the way!
Suddenly seems...
very quiet...
That will be the absence
of the ladies then, sir.
Sir Benjamin!!
We're lost!
Maria!
Robin, come on!
Don't you see?
She's showing us the way!
De Noir!
Merryweather!
Good evening!
Your niece has failed!
If you harm, hurt her...
in any way...
Stop!
- Uncle, No! No!
- Father, we got them!!
Look!
Give me the pearls!
Those damn pearls!
They brought nothing but harm and grief!
No, Uncle... it's not the pearls but the greed
in our heart which brings us such misery.
Father!
Why do you have so much
hatred in your heart?
My daughter!
Don't you want to be free
of this darkness imprisoning you?
It is he! It is he!
Father!
Benjamin!
Look!
The 5,000th moon.
The curse is coming true!
If you can sacrifice your pride,
we can save our families.
We can save the valley!
You first.
No, no... after you.
I must do this myself!
At the 5,000th moon,
I,
Maria Merryweather,
Moon Princess of Moonacre...
do remove the curse
that has darkened this valley.
Take back what is yours!
No!
Maria!
Oh, my sweet child...
you're alive!
Uncle!
Were you worried, Robin?
No... I could've done that.
You're the true Moon Princess!
Oh... nasty!
That will be a black lion male, sir...
It's alright, Uncle.
It's just a Wolf.
Please forgive my stubborn pride!
Loveday.
- Stop right there! I'll finish her right now!
- No, stop... you idiot!
Maria! I'm here!
I've come to save you!
Is there...
going to be a wedding?
Oh, my...
Mr. Digweed?!
Well, there we are then...
nothing to be done!
Subtitles edited by LeapinLar
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org