IRAN, DESERT ONE, 200 MILES EAST OF
TEHERAN, APRIL 25TH, 1980 - 4:00AM
(shouting)
Let's go! Get on there!
Move it! Move it! Move it!
Move it! Sergeant, get your men on there!
Is that Peterson's helicopter?
He was in that damn chopper
that blew up!
McCoy!
McCoy, get back here!
Where the hell are you goin'?!
We're pullin? out!
Captain McCoy!
- Bobby, where's Pete?
- Still in the chopper.
The flames are too high.
He can't be reached.
Captain, don't go in there!
The fuel bladders are about to blow!
Pete!
(moans)
Pete! Where are you?!
(Pete) Get the hell outta here!
The thing's gonna blow!
Scott?
Goddammit, get out!
This goddamn thing's gonna blow!
- Hang on!
- (Pete) Get out!
Hang on, Pete!
(Pete) Get outta here!
Ow! My God!
Oh, my God! My leg's gone!
Come on!
Get outta here, Captain!
Listen, Pete! When I raise up the jeep...
...move your leg!
Ready?
Move it!
Move your leg! Pete, move it!
(Pete groans)
Hang on. Hang on.
Move! Get 'em up here! Come on, move!
All right, take it up! Let's go!
- Scott and Pete are still back there!
- I got a squadron to think about!
Come on, get it up!
Hey, there they are!
(Bobby) Come on, Scott!
Take it down! Take it down!
(Bobby) Come on, man!
(soldier) Get that air load secured!
Come on! Come on, man!
All right, we've got him.
(Pete cries out in pain)
Come on, make a move! Go!
- Come on, close the door.
- Give him some room!
Why wouldn't they listen, Nick?
We told 'em it's too dangerous
to launch this operation at night.
They thought their plan was better.
I spent five years in Vietnam watching
them do the planning... and us the dying.
Well... I'm resigning when I get back.
(TV) We interrupt this programme to bring
you the following special news bulletin.
An hour ago an attempt to rescue the
American hostages held in Teheran...
... ended in disaster for the Army'
top- secret antiterrorist special forces.
Eight members of the special unit
have been killed and 13 wounded.
No further information as to the cause
of this disaster is available at this time.
ATHENS,
FRIDAY, JULY 19TH, 1985 - 7:45AM
(Tannoy) American Travelways
Flight 282 from Cairo has just landed.
Passengers taking this flight to New York
via Rome should proceed to Gate 11.
I have a bad leg.
I thought you would like to know,
it's our silver wedding anniversary.
- Mazel tov!
- Congratulations.
We'd have divorced years ago but
neither of us wanted custody of our kids.
Please don't listen to him. If it was
up to him, he would spoil 'em rotten.
- I'm going shopping.
- Good idea. I can check on my daughter.
- You wanna go to the duty-free?
- OK.
Watch the things, honey.
- Harry Goldman. Philadelphia.
- Ben Kaplan. New York.
Deborah, let her have
the doll she wants. She's a baby!
Momma, she's not a baby.
And you're spoiling her.
I'm not. I didn't do
such a bad job with you.
Harry wanted to buy me a new ring
for our anniversary. I said no.
He got me this ring in Jerusalem
on our honeymoon.
Really? Oh, it's lovely. What does it say?
One minute. I'll show you.
Here, take it.
It says: Anti
... vie dodo li.
Ash, that's... that's Hebrew. I know that.
It's from the Song of Songs.
"Me to my lover...
...my lover to me."
- You're Jewish, huh?
- No, I'm Chinese.
Of course!
- What's the problem?
- There's no problem.
- We thought you had a water leak.
- Can we start boarding now?
Sure. Better check that
with your flight engineer.
Have a nice flight.
(announcement in Greek)
I'm sorry, sir. This flight is full.
Check the ticket counter for the next one.
- No, no. I must go on this flight.
- I'm sorry, sir. You have a stand-by ticket.
(man) We're full, sir. Please move aside.
- You see in your book if there is space.
- Sir, you can't go on board this flight.
You see if there is a place for me.
They told me there is a place!
- Move aside, please.
- No! You move aside!
They told me I got a ticket!
Send security - immediately!
Calm down. Show me your ticket.
Here. Here. Go see.
What shall we do?
We do what we have to.
(shouts in Arabic)
- Where's my back brace?
- Robert has your back brace, Ma.
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
This is your captain speaking.
My name is Roger Campbell.
On behalf of American Travelways,
welcome to a continuation of Flight 282...
... to Rome, then onward to New York.
Our flight time to Rome
will be 55 minutes.
- Don't be scared to take off.
- Honey, could you pull this for me?
- Yes.
- Don't kill me, just pull.
Take a deep breath, I won't kill you.
- Stop it.
- I'm kidding.
Are you all right, sister?
- Could I have a glass of water, please?
- Sure.
She's afraid of flying.
Sister wants to get to Heaven.
She just doesn't want to fly to get there.
I'll get you some.
Excuse me.
You're from Chicago, no?
Yes! Yes, we are. How did you know?
I am from Chicago myself. I must have
seen you somewhere in Chicago.
- You don't sound like Chicago.
- I've only been in Chicago four years.
- You're Polish?
- Russian.
Do you know the Orthodox Church
by Lincoln Park? Father Duchinsky.
I go to hear his sermon every Sunday.
- Are you going back home?
- My first vacation since Russia.
- Enjoyed yourself?
- I feel like I am reborn.
America has been good to us.
God be praised.
(whispers) Oh, shit!
- (whispers) Dad, look!
- Let me sleep.
This is a hijack! Heads down!
- Heads down!
- (gasps and screams)
Everybody down! This is a hand grenade!
We will blow the plane!
What are you doing?!
- Get your heads down!
- What are you doing?!
(screams)
- (accomplice) Get down, everybody!
- Put your heads down!
This is a hijack! This is a hand grenade!
We will blow the plane
if you do not do exactly as we say!
Put your hands on your head!
Oh, my God!
No!
Robert, are you all right?!
We are prepared to die!
Do not provoke me!
Hitler! You want to die,
die someplace else!
Shush, shush.
Mister... Mister... Don't. Don't.
Don't. Don't.
- Cockpit. Come!
- We will cooperate.
- Open...
- Calm down. We'll cooperate, man.
We'll do anything you want.
Open the cockpit. Open the cockpit!
Open this door!
Jim! It's me.
Open!
- Open, Jim!
- (Jim) Is everything OK?
Everything is all right! Open, please!
Open this door or I will blow the plane!
JIM, YOU HAVE TO OPEN!
Pick it up.
Move.
Sit down. Sit down!
I am taking over this airplane.
You will cooperate.
We'll take you anywhere
you wanna go, buddy.
Now why don't you put that pin
back into that hand grenade?
Put it.
Easy, Jim.
(hijacker) I am prepared to die.
I am Abdul Rafai. I am a commander
in the New World Revolution.
You will take orders from me,
and from no one but me...
...or I will blow this airplane.
- Do you hear me?
- Loud and clear.
Now, you fly to Beirut.
- Where?
- Beirut! Fly to Beirut!
Beirut.
Roger.
- Take your hand away.
- That's normal procedure.
Damn it, it's a hijack!
Call the American Embassy.
- Dave, contact Athens departure control.
- No!
You will fly by map.
I know flying. You will fly by map.
I don't think
we have enough fuel, Captain.
Then you will fly
until your fuel runs out, Captain.
That is all.
American Embassy? This is
Athens airport tower. It' urgent.
This is the American Embassy in Athens.
Get me the State Department
operations centre. This is an emergency.
I'm reporting a hijack.
It occurred five minutes ago...
... aboard American Travelways
Flight 282...
WASHINGTON D.C.,
FRIDAY, JULY 19TH - 2:10AM
We have no more information
at present as to the status...
THE PENTAGON,
FRIDAY, JULY 19TH - 2:15AM
Yes, sir. I'll put the President on the line.
Good evening. Or, rather, good morning.
As you know, we have
a major crisis in the Middle East.
The President is sending the Delta Force
into the area immediately.
Now, what we have to do is work out
an emergency rescue operation.
Get me Nick Alexander at Bragg.
FORT BRAGG, NORTH CAROLINA,
FRIDAY, JULY 19TH - 2:20AM
Well, I got a good imagination. I, uh...
I was just tryin? to be nice.
Anyone ever accuse you
of being a gentleman, Nick?
- Not lately.
- (beeper)
Grab me the phone,
would you, sweetheart?
Alexander here.
Put Delta Force on a Phase Three alert.
ATW Flight 282 was just hijacked.
- Get Sabre Squadron to the Middle East.
- Lebanon?
We don't know for sure.
- Check in while you're in the air.
- Will do, General.
Here you go, sweetheart.
Ladies and gentlemen...
...this is your new captain speaking.
My name is Abdul Rafai.
(PA) I am a member of the New World
Revolutionary Organisation.
We have declared war on American
imperialists, Zionists, terrorists...
...and all other antisocialist atrocities.
Your plane is now headed
for a new destination.
For your safety, I suggest
you listen carefully...
...and follow all instructions.
- Harry.
- What?
My ring, it's Hebrew.
Take it off. Put it in your purse.
(Harry) Take it off.
Harry, there's a white mark on my hand.
Think they'll notice?
Will you marry me?
Oh, Harry! What's gonna happen to us?
One thing is certain.
We'll always remember
our silver wedding anniversary.
(man whispers) Let's do something.
- It's only two of 'em. We can take 'em.
- Shh!
It's not a good idea.
These guys are dangerous.
If they're gonna blow this plane up, that's
a lot of people. We gotta play their game.
All right!
You can all sit up now!
But nobody talks!
Nobody move!
Excuse me, sir.
- This young lady is preg...
- Shut up!
Please, I'm not feeling well.
FAYETTEVILLE, NORTH CAROLINA
McCOY'S RANCH,
FRIDAY, JULY 19TH, 2:42AM
... has just been hijacked.
Over 100 Americans are believed
to be on board the ATWairliner.
We'll bring you further developments
as they occur.
None of the known terrorist groups
in that region...
... are willing to take responsibility
for this current action.
Now!
All men sit by the windows!
All women sit near the aisles!
Do it now - and quickly!
Just do it!
Fast! Fast! And quiet!
- (whispers)
- (Abdul) You shut up! Nobody talk.
(TV) The hijacked plane is still in the air
heading for an unknown destination...
... presumably somewhere
in the Middle East.
There is still no word on the condition
of the Americans and the other hostages.
We'll keep you updated
as further information becomes available.
(horse whinnies)
(Abdul) Everyone get up
and go into the back!
Hurry up!
We're coming, we're coming. It's OK.
Move! Move!
- Excuse me. I left my purse.
- Leave it! Go!
(man) Come on back. Keep movin'
Move! Come on, move, move, move!
- Come on, move. Keep movin'
- Sit down! Sit down!
- I can't sit on the floor!
- Sit!
- My back! My back.
- Sit! Sit up there! Sit there!
Sit!
- I'll sit on his lap.
- Thank you very much. Thank you.
- Sit down!
- Watch that gun, sir.
- (screams)
- What'd you hit him for, man?!
Keep quiet.
Silence!
- There's no space to breathe here!
- (Abdul) Shut up! Everyone, shut up!
(Abdul) Sit down!
(Deborah) Ellen! Come back here!
- What are you doing here? Go back.
- My doll!
It's a nice doll. What is your name?
Ellen.
Ellen. It's a very nice name.
- How old are you, Ellen?
- Six.
You know, Ellen...
...I had a daughter exactly your age.
Her name was Salima.
You understand, Ellen?
Good. Good. Take it.
Thank you.
Go, go, go, go. Go!
(Deborah) Come on.
POPE AIRFORCE BASE, NORTH
CAROLINA, FRIDAY, JULY 19th - 3:00 AM
Hey, Ace. You think
the Captain's gonna show up?
- I'll be damned if he doesn't.
- Wasn't he called?
Who'd call him? He's retired
to that old horse farm of his.
Though I must admit I wouldn't mind
havin? Captain McCoy along.
- I took the liberty of giving him a call, sir.
- You what?!
He wasn't at home.
He just might be on his way here, Colonel.
Nah... None of that.
That looks good.
Oh, yeah. (chuckles)
Pull down the shades!
Pull down the shades.
Pull the shades down! All of you!
Shades down!
Pull them down!
All right! Pull them down,
all these window shades!
Pull the shades down. Pull the shades.
Pull these down!
Abdul, come here.
What is it?
Come quick.
What?
Look.
This is Hebrew.
There are Israelis here.
(Abdul) Come here!
Come here!
There are Israelis aboard this airplane.
I want you to identify them for me.
We don't know who the Israelis are.
How could we?
They came off the El Al flight!
And I will find them.
Collect all passports.
- Why?
- Do it!
OK.
Ladies and gentlemen, attention. They
want all of you to turn in your passports.
So, please, get out your passports...
...and hold them over your head.
- Why?
- I don't know why.
(stewardess) Thank you.
Come on!
Mustafa, watch her.
Just be quiet and
do what they tell you to do.
No! Just women! You go back! Go back!
(nun) Miss, did they tell you
why they want our passports?
Will we get 'em back?
Put them here!
All of them! I want all of them!
No cheating. I know
there are 144 passengers.
Ingrid is getting the rest.
Excuse me, miss. We don't have
passports. We're in the Navy.
- We have these Navy IDs.
- Hide them away.
(whispers) Hide it, man. Put it away.
Hey, you. Why didn't you
collect these men's passports?
- They don't have passports.
- You are lying.
No, wait a second. We have these.
We have these.
It's a Navy ID.
- Marines.
- No. We're divers for the American Navy.
- You?
- All three of us. We're all Navy.
Marines. American Marines killed many
of my friends when they bombed Beirut!
America never bombed Beirut.
Planes from your ship New Jersey
bombed our camps!
- Relax.
- Son, you're making a mistake.
America never bombed Beirut.
- Your American ship!
- (woman) No!
No!
(all protest)
Stop! He's a priest!
Enough, enough!
These three are
American Marines. Look.
Oh, yes?
Three American heroes.
From now on, you travel
only first class, gentlemen.
- What's goin? on here?
- Shut up.
- Why do you want us...
- Just shut up!
Come here.
Hold this.
Please, please, just be quiet.
OK?
Everything will be all right.
Listen. You don't have to do that.
- We'll cooperate.
- Shut up. Sit down.
Sit... down!
Now you listen to me.
Look at these passports one by one.
Pick out the passport with Jewish names.
American passports do not state religion.
Give me the Israelis.
There are no Israelis on board.
Then pick out the Jewish names.
I told you, there is no way
I can know who is a Jew. How can I?
Do it!
I can't! I won't do it!
Yes, you will do it!
No, not me!
Don't you see? I'm German!
- What does that mean?
- The selections.
The Nazis!
The death camps!
Don't you see I can't do
what you want me to do?
Very sorry, dear lady.
But... you must do this for us.
You claim you belong to
a revolutionary organisation.
That is correct. We are freedom fighters.
We are fighting for our brothers.
But then you don't want
to be associated with Nazis...
...who killed six million Jews.
Not enough, lady! Not enough.
The Jews stole Palestine.
They took our lands.
Leave her! With no gun,
you wouldn't be shit!
- Shut up, you American imperialist pig!
- Stop it, please!
You are all pigs and killers!
Don't kill him, please!
Stop him! Don't let him kill him!
(sound of punches)
You will do what Abdul said!
He is your new captain,
and you obey or you die.
Do you hear me? You die!
We will kill everyone on this bloody plane.
No! I won't do it!
Yes!
What's going on, Colonel? Men and
equipment are aboard. What's the delay?
- I'll give him five more minutes.
- Who?
Oh, uh, nothing, sir.
Just... Just a few more minutes.
(vehicle approaches in distance)
Colonel?
(tyres screech)
Well, it's about time you showed up.
I was afraid I was gonna have to use this.
What is it?
A presidential decree
ordering you back to duty.
And you can leave the keys
in the van, too.
I've got your gear on the plane.
General, we're all set.
- How was your engagement party?
- A little cut short.
- Bobby, good to see you.
- Welcome back, boss.
- Do you know who that guy is?
- No!
- Well, let's go do it.
- Let's do it!
- Great to see you.
- Good to see you, Captain Jack.
- Don't make me carry your ass this time.
- No way, Captain.
Uh... Major.
Yes, sir, Major!
- What the hell, huh?
- Congratulations.
Ladies and gentlemen...
(PA)... this is your new captain speaking.
Miss Ingrid will read some names...
- What are they doing?
...immediately to first-class cabin.
I repeat: immediately.
Kaplan, Benjamin.
(Ingrid) Mr Benjamin Kaplan.
This... can't be happening.
Not... not again.
Not again.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
- Don't go.
- We... We survived once.
We can do it again.
I'm coming.
(soft crying)
Where are you going?
Go back to your seat.
He is my husband!
- Sit down!
- No.
No. I won't listen. No, I won't!
Go on! Why don't you all do something?!
There's only two of them!
There's so many of you! Why don't you...
- (shushing)
- (Mrs Kaplan) I don't care!
(woman) She's just upset.
No! It's the war! It's the war all over again!
The concentration camps!
Why don't you do something? Something!
- There's only two of them!
- Sit down!
And there's so many of us!
- Well, do something!
- Please...
(Mustafa) You! Sit down!
Sit!
I'm Benjamin Kaplan.
What can I do for you?
Sit down.
Next one!
Harry Goldman.
Mr Harry Goldman,
come to first class, please.
Please... don't take him!
He's a sick man! He has a heart condition!
Sylvia! Sylvia, be strong.
Listen to me. Be strong. I'm OK.
- Please don't go! Please!
- I can go. I can go. It's OK. It's OK.
- It's OK.
- (Mustafa) Move, move.
Oh, please don't...
(mouths)
(Mustafa) Go!
- Harry Goldman.
- Sit.
- Next!
- Robert Levine.
Mr Robert Levine, please come
to first class, please.
OK, OK. Move, move. Move, move.
(EIlen) Please don't take my daddy!
Daddy, take me with you!
I have to go, sweetheart.
But I'm not leaving the plane.
He can't, sweetie. Daddy can't...
I'll be back.
Daddy, here! Take!
OK, move, move, move!
Move! Move! Move!
Go, go, go! Move! Move! Move!
You just keep your hands
off my daughter.
Go!
On the floor.
David Rosovsky.
Mr Rosovsky, come to first class, please.
They're making a mistake.
They're making a mistake. I... um... I'm...
Mr Rosovsky, you move
or I shoot you right here.
But I am not Jewish! I'm American!
I came from Russia
but now I live in America!
I am Christian Orthodox! Ask them!
Sister, tell him I am not a Jew!
Father, don't you know me from Chicago?
- Move!
- Wait!
- This is man is telling the truth!
- Sit down! We know what we are doing!
Sir, you are making a big mistake...
(Abdul) Sit down.
On the floor!
- (nun) He is telling the truth!
- We know what we are doing!
- Father! Where are you going?
- You! Come back!
(screams)
- I said come back!
- No!
Sit... down!
- What are you doing here?
- You called me.
- What is your name?
- William O'Malley.
- I did not call you.
- You called for all the Jews.
I'm Jewish, just like Jesus Christ.
If you take one of us,
you gotta take us all.
Sit down, then.
- You!
- Me?
Yeah. The pregnant lady. Come on!
Excuse me.
Go, go, go. Move. Move.
Come, come, come.
I need some pillows.
Give me some pillows.
(Mustafa whispers) Come, come.
Yeah... Sit down. Sit.
OK, that's enough. Sit, sit.
That's enough. Sit down.
- You feel good?
- Fine. Thank you for remembering.
- OK everything?
- Thank you.
Good, good.
(speaking in a low voice)
- Sleep well.
- Thanks.
(Campbell) Beirut approach control,
American Travelways Flight 282...
...under command of Captain...
...Abdul Rafai...
...of the New...
(Abdul) World Revolution.
...World Revolution...
... requesting landing instructions.
American Travel Way, I am unable
to give you landing instruction.
This airport is closed today
to all international flights...
...by order of the Lebanese government.
You heard the man.
Now what do you want to do?
Land.
Damn!
(sirens)
Beirut, you must clear that runway
at once or we'll all die!
You are facing disaster if you try to land!
- Where is the plane?
- There.
Do you have the captain? Give it to me.
Captain? Captain...
... this is the Minister of Defence speaking.
You cannot land in our country.
We have enough trouble.
We have 144 men, women and children
aboard this aircraft!
The hijacker has threatened to blow us
up. If he does, it'll be your responsibility.
Do you understand that, Mr Minister?
Do we now have your permission to land?
My answer is definitely not!
- Yeeeagh!
- (punch)
(sound of punching)
Mr Minister... Mr Minister...
...listen.
What is it?
(punching and groaning)
(Mustafa shouts)
Captain! What's this shouting?
What' going on there?!
They're torturing a young boy.
A Navy hostage.
They're killing him.
Mr Minister, we're coming in for a landing
whether we have your permission or not.
Reducing power.
Let them land.
Captain! Captain, it's OK.
You have permission to land.
But just give me a minute.
I want to clear the runway.
OVER THE ATLANTIC OCEAN
FRIDAY, JULY 19TH - 5:45AM
(Nick) Gentlemen,
we'll go in in three sections.
McCoy, you'll lead the first section.
I want you to hit the emergency exits
on the port wing... here and here...
...clearing the first-class cabin...
...and the cockpit.
Pete, you'll have the second section.
Hit the emergency exits on the starboard
wing, here, clearing the main cabin.
Bobby, you'll have section three
for backup and emergencies.
It should be a piece of cake.
- There are only two terrorists on board.
- How do we know that?
A calculated guess.
All right, gentlemen. Any questions?
LEBANON, BEIRUT AIRPORT
FRIDAY, JULY 19TH - NOON
Please help yourself.
Tell America in five minutes...
...we will kill one after the other.
They'll kill one every five minutes.
This will be a disaster.
Jamil. Thank God you came.
They're going to kill one
every five minutes.
- Let me try.
- Try.
- Hi, brother.
- Jamil.
- Congratulations.
Now we need the sympathy of the world.
Now we need
the American public opinion.
Now is the time to be united.
Release women and children...
...then the Americans will talk.
No.
Listen to me, brother.
I am your commander.
Not any more.
Abdul, we're all fighting
for the same cause.
No. Give us fuel.
No way?
Their way is suicide.
Get them fuel and get rid of them.
All right, Abdul...
finish your mission your way.
God be with you.
Momma, it's so hot!
I know, sweetie. Everybody's hot.
What are they doing there with Daddy?
Asking him some questions.
What kind of questions?
(sighs) Maybe...
...about being Jewish.
They don't like Jews, huh, Momma?
No, sweetie, they don't like Jews.
Open the door. Open the door! Open!
- Hassan.
- Mustafa, welcome.
You - move! Move! Sit down!
Come on!
Congratulations, my brother.
Happy to see you.
Take them off.
(men shouting in Arabic)
- Father, God be with you.
- Take care of yourself, sister. And them.
You stay.
(Mrs Kaplan) Ben!
- Don't take him, please!
- Daddy!
Mommy! They're taking Daddy!
No! No!
Move, move!
All right. Time to leave.
We take off.
- Where to?
- I'll let you know when we reach the sky.
BEIRUT, CENTRE OF TOWN -
TERRORIST HEADQUARTERS
FRIDAY, JULY 19TH - 2:00PM
(shouting in Arabic)
Put them in the cells.
Move! Quickly!
(chants in Greek)
(speaks in Greek)
Israeli Intelligence says they've left Beirut.
We believe they're on their way to Algiers.
If so, they'll land
at Boumédienne Airport in four hours.
Nick, I've just had confirmation
from the President.
The Algerian government is ready
to cooperate. You can go to Algiers.
All right, guys! Listen up!
We're landing in Algiers!
Prepare your gear!
Algiers, this is Delta One
requesting permission to land.
This is Boumédienne International
Airport. Permission granted.
American Travelways Flight 282,
this is Boumédienne Airport.
You are cleared to land.
So you men stay with the equipment.
We are gonna go for it this time,
right, Colonel?
Damn right.
(beeping)
This is Delta One. I receive you.
Delta One. I receive you.
Yes, sir. Just a minute, sir.
Colonel! General Woodbridge, sir.
General, we've got
damn near perfect conditions.
It's just the situation
we've been waiting for.
If we wait any longer,
we can end up with another fiasco.
I'm sorry, Nick. The President
doesn't want to risk any lives.
If he can release our people
by negotiations, that' what he wants.
So until the negotiations break down...
...your people are on hold.
How long do we have to wait?
Woodbridge is waiting for
the go-ahead from the President.
I'm waiting for the go-ahead from him and
you're waiting for the go-ahead from me.
Meantime I'm going over to the terminal.
I wanna debrief any hostages that are
released - if and when any are released.
So you get out there, and get set.
- But wait for my signal.
- Got it.
OK, get rid of the box.
Move out!
Captain Rafai,
the flight from Athens has just landed.
Your comrade will be with you
any moment.
We expect you to release the women
and children without any more delays.
(Abdul) We shall keep our word
as promised, Mr Ambassador.
- Colonel, I'm gonna go to the plane.
- I'll wait here, Mr Ambassador.
You send back any hostage
from that plane that speaks English.
McCoy! Nobody moves until
all the women and children are safe!
All sections, acknowledge!
One, two and three!
Jaffer!
I'm happy to see you again, brothers.
You wait. You get women and children.
How are you, Jaffer?
So... so. How is the mission?
Everything is great.
Mustafa.
Shall we release
the women and children?
Yes, go ahead.
Please...
...let him go.
He's almost dead.
No.
But you may go.
I release you with the women.
Go!
Ingrid...
You're a brave woman.
Section one in position.
Section two in position.
Section three in position.
We don't move until
the women and children are safe.
- Acknowledge, section two.
- Section two acknowledge.
- Section three?
- Section three acknowledge.
Ladies and children, Allah be praised.
It is time to leave the airplane.
Men will stay in their seats.
We will ask you to have...
...your valuables, your money,
your jewellery...
...out in your hands for us to collect as
you come through the first-class cabin.
Go on, sweetie.
We'll see you later.
(shouts in Arabic)
Jay, you take care of your mom.
You understand me?
You ladies, go forward. Everyone forward!
- Keep it with you.
- (Abdul) Move forward, Christian ladies!
Why are you behaving like bandits?
Aren't you freedom fighters?
Go.
I take this... and this...
I have some money.
- This is yours?
- Yes.
Thank you.
You have some money? OK, go, go.
Here.
Go, go.
Thank God the women are safe.
(beeping)
Yeah.
The bus has left.
We're ready to make our move.
Sorry, McCoy. We're still on hold.
Damn it, Nick. Let's not screw this one up.
Everyone to the back!
To the back! Everybody to the back!
- Colonel Alexander?
- Yeah.
They want you on the phone.
- Alexander here.
- Nick...
...it's a go.
Gotcha.
McCoy... it's a go!
Take 'em down!
OK, section two and three, let's do it.
Close communications.
We go in... 60 seconds.
Ready? Mark.
Mark.
We go in 60 seconds.
60 seconds. Mark.
Radios off the air.
Colonel, this is Ingrid Harding,
the plane's purser.
Mr Ambassador,
I'd like to talk to her alone.
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
Miss Harding,
this will only take a few minutes.
- What's happening?
- Commandos are gonna storm the plane.
Oh, no. Don't.
All the hostages in Beirut,
they'll kill them all.
- What hostages?
- Navy guys and Jews who left the plane...
...when the other hijackers came on.
- What other hijackers?!
All those men who came on board.
10 or 12 of them.
Oh, God!
All sections! All sections!
OK, 30 seconds. All right?
All sections! Come on,
somebody respond!
Let's go! Turn the light on! Hit the siren!
(siren)
- (siren still blaring)
- What the hell is that?
Come on, get out of there, McCoy!
McCoy!
Turn the lights out! Turn the lights out!
Get down! Get down!
What the hell?
Don't shoot back! We're clearing out!
- Get out!
- Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Get out! Get out of the tanker!
(siren)
Oh, shit.
Take off - immediately! Take off!
- All right, all right!
- Take off! Take off!
Come! Come!
(speaks Arabic)
Americans!
Look what you have done!
Look here, Americans!
- Look!
- He's gonna kill him.
Now your president
will know we are serious!
- Here is a token...
- Don't shoot.
...for the American people!
One Marine killer!
- Oh, Jesus!
- Son of a bitch. Let's go!
Come on, move!
Sorry I had to do it that way, boys. It was
the only way I could stop you in time.
- What happened, Colonel?
- 12 terrorists got on board.
They were in every part of that plane with
machine guns. It woulda been a disaster.
He's an American. He was in the Navy.
- Where do we go from here?
- After them, I hope.
They're going back to Beirut.
- You mean it' all over for us?
- On the contrary, Colonel.
The President wants you to fly to Israel.
Israel?
Israel is our best friend in the Middle
East, and it' only 20 minutes from Beirut.
You're gonna get everything you want
to do it right.
The President wants those people home.
So do we, General. So do we.
We are Americans! Stay down!
- Clear!
Not bad, McCoy. Not bad.
20 seconds. Just like clockwork.
- We can do it in 10.
- All right, one more time.
ISRAEL, AIRFORCE BASE
SATURDAY, JULY 20TH - 5:50AM
Hold it, McCoy. We've got visitors.
- Colonel Alexander?
- Yeah.
Good morning. I'm Colonel Amir
from Israeli Intelligence.
Oh, yes. This is Major McCoy.
- Good morning, Major.
- Colonel.
Can I talk to you?
Certainly.
Bobby, take over.
I want it done in 10 seconds.
We'll be right down.
- (Nick) So what's happening?
- They took the hostages off the plane.
- Where to?
- I don't know.
They could be spread
all over Beirut by now.
Colonel, I assume your Mossad still has
people planted in Lebanon, right?
Your assumption is correct.
- I need to get in contact with one of them.
- Do some reckoning before the rescue?
- It'd be a great help to us, Colonel.
- If I may suggest...
- They've announced a press conference.
- Ah, of course.
Now that they got the world's attention,
they wanna manipulate the press. Perfect.
BEIRUT, MEDITERRANEAN BEACH
SATURDAY, JULY 20TH - 8:00AM
(priest chants in Greek)
(chants in Greek)
(shouting in Arabic)
? Oooh... ooh, ooh, ooh
Move them in... quickly!
Bring in the mattresses fast.
Give them to the dogs.
Mahmud! Go and double
the guards. Quickly!
Another funeral.
Another Christian.
I was in Beirut 20 years ago.
You should have been here then.
It was something. They had everything.
Nightclubs, dancing, concerts...
...laughter.
It was the Las Vegas of the Middle East.
Beirut was beautiful then.
Beautiful.
I don't like it.
What don't you like?
This Christian place.