False alarm. It's just a old bicycle.
None of y'all brought a thermos
of coffee out here?
That day at school -
you looked kinda strange
at me and Jessica.
Did you think something bad then?
Shit! Come on.
- Donnie, he called, I told him...
- Pearl!
Shut your mouth!
- What are you doin' on my property?
- I'm on Sheriff's business.
- Got permission from your wife.
- Think that ninny talks for me?
How did your arm get all scratched up?
Stray cat. She didn't like it
when I killed her.
- What brought you here?
- Routine investigation.
We're checking
all the ponds in the county.
- I knew it was you!
- No! You...
Hey! I'm on county business, Donnie!
Don't fool with me.
- Hey, Pearl!
- What?
- You need to take a look at this.
- Watch him.
It's her!
Donnie?
Get those hooks outta my baby!
Get her off them hooks!
- No!
- Cuff him!
- No, no!
- Mr King!
Get an ambulance!
I think he's having a heart attack!
- I didn't do this!
- Get him outta here!
This ain't right, Pearl! Bitch!
Bitch! Bitch! Pearl!
Come in.
- Somebody might come in here!
- Guess you'd better fuck me fast!
You want some coffee? Mrs Wilson?
Do you want some coffee?
No, thank you.
Have a seat.
Why have you called me here?
Tomorrow Donnie Barksdale
goes on trial for murder.
I feel that we have a powerful case.
Today the coroner verified Donnie's
tissue under the victim's nails.
I only have one weak link
I gotta worry about.
- What?
- You.
You see, you're how we found out
where the victim's body was,
and how you found out, well...
...that might open up
a real can of worms for us.
Psychic phenomenon,
ESP, dreams, visions.
The defence could go to town on you
and, if that's not bad enough,
I understand there was bad blood
between you and Donnie Barksdale?
Yeah, he threatened my kids!
That's what I heard. I also heard
you threatened him right back.
Told his wife to leave him.
Donnie's quite a ladies' man.
Were you involved with him?
- What?
- I can deal with any revelation now.
But at the trial,
there can't be any surprises.
Is there anything I need to know
about you or Donnie
or Donnie's wife or the victim?
No.
Will that be all?
Yes, ma'am.
You know, Mr Duncan...
...the victim had a name.
It was Jessica King.
Mr Hawkins, how long
have you worked out at Ay Jay's?
About ten years.
Were you working
on Saturday night, April 8th?
Yes, sir.
Did you see Donnie Barksdale
that night?
Yes, sir.
Could you describe the circumstances?
The circumstances were I come outside
to throw out some trash.
- Do you recall what time it was?
- About midnight, I reckon.
Anyhow, I seen Donnie Barksdale
out there by his truck
having an argument
with this white lady.
She scratched his arm
and he slapped the tar outta her.
About that time, I go back inside.
- Is this the woman you saw with him?
- Yes, sir.
Your Honour, let the record show
that I've just shown Mr Hawkins
a photograph of Jessica King.
You just said
that your attention was drawn
to the defendant's pond.
Drawn in... Drawn in what way?
Me, Wayne Collins and Kenneth King
went to see a woman
name of Annie Wilson.
What made you think
she'd be able to help you?
Well, word around town was
that she was a...
...uh... well, I don't know
what the right word is.
- Isn't it "fortune teller"?
- I guess so.
What did this fortune teller see
when she looked into her crystal ball?
Well, she didn't have no ball.
She had these special cards.
What did she see
when she looked into her cards?
She didn't see nothin' then,
but next day, she come to see me
and told me she'd had this dream.
- She had a dream?
- Yes, sir.
She'd seen this pond that looked
a lot like Donnie Barksdale's...
...then she woke up from her dream
and she went outside
and looked up in this tree...
I'm all ears!
She seen Jessica King...
...floatin' in the tree...
...half-naked, with a chain
wrapped around her.
Floating around in a tree?
Yes, sir.
Floating in a tree...
...half-naked...
...chain wrapped around her.
Thank you, Sheriff.
Gerald Weems is just mean and skinny!
Never known a Weems worth a damn!
- He was just doin' his job.
- Mrs Wilson.
Can... Can I talk to you
for a minute?
Just call me later on, OK?
- OK.
- OK. Bye.
Look, Buddy, I got a lot on my mind,
hon. It... It's not a good time, OK?
Mrs Wilson... you did tell me
to do some thinkin' and talkin'
and I been thinkin'.
What?
Can you tell me
why I do things to myself
when I think about my daddy?
Oh, I... well...
Bud, you call me later, hon,
and we'll talk, all right?
- I need to talk to you!
- Buddy!
I been thinking about my daddy
and touching myself!
- How?
- Why do I do that?
- Oh, Buddy...
- Something's bad wrong with me!
And... And I keep thinkin'
about that blue diamond...
If you look into one,
you won't think a negative thought!
I promise! Hon, I'm going
through a hard time myself!
I just...
I can't talk to you now, OK?
Y'all burn in hell,
Annie Wilson!
Mike, I know you skipped school
and went to that trial.
- How do you know?
- A little bird told me.
It's time you started
making things easier on me.
Phone's ringing.
Second of all, I'm gonna have
to testify at that trial tomorrow.
- The phone's ringing, Momma!
- I'm not deaf!
Let the machine get it.
Donnie Barksdale's side
are gonna give me a hard time.
They're gonna call me names and I...
I just want you all to be prepared...
If you hear any bad stuff
about me, all right?
We're gonna have
to stick together on this.
Annie Wilson,
it's Buddy's mother!
Buddy's threatening
to kill his daddy!
He's got Odell tied up
in the back yard!
- Accusing him of horrible things!
- Have you called the police?
He said if I did,
he'd kill Odell! He wants you!
Hey, Bud...
Buddy, put the strap down, hon!
Tell me what he's done to you!
I'm here, Buddy.
You can talk to me, hon.
IT'S TOO LATE FOR THAT!
IT'S TOO GODDAMN LATE!
This here... is a criminal!
And he's gonna be punished!
- Buddy... Buddy, it's Annie...
- You shut up!
- YOU SHUT UP!
- It's all right...
- GET AWAY! Where were you?!
- I'm sorry!
You knew everything...
and you did nothing!
You ruined me! YOU RUINED ME!
I was just a little boy, Daddy!
It got so I was embarrassed
to go to school, Daddy!
How could you do that
to your little boy?!
No, Bud, you put that down!
No, you put that down, Bud!
- You put that down! Listen to me!
- Get away!
- You, get away!
- All right, all right.
It's all right. Come on.
Why didn't you help me, Annie?
- What?
- Why didn't you help me?!
- I had you for a friend and then...
- I am your friend.
Now I have nobody! I have NOBODY!
I'm gonna kill this thing.
NO!
Help me! Help me!
Look into that thing and tell me
what kind of thoughts you have!
You... look!
You lookin' at that thing?!
Mrs Wilson... Mrs Wilson.
Your husband, Ben Wilson Senior,
was one of the men killed last year
in the explosion at the cable plant.
Yes, that's right.
You were left
with three children to raise alone.
Yes, sir.
How do you provide
for you and your sons?
I get a little bit of money
from Social Security
as a result of my husband's death.
And I... I also give readings.
- Psychic readings?
- Yes, sir.
What does being psychic
enable you to do?
I see things...
...and I, you know, I sense... things
that hadn't happened yet or...
...they happened someplace else.
My granny told me that I... I had
a gift, that it runs in my family.
She told me
I shouldn't be afraid of it,
I should just always use my instinct
and I'd be all right.
So you're swearing before this court
that you didn't get your information
from any other means
than your special ability, your gift?
Yes, sir,
I'm swearing that, yes.
Thank you, Mrs Wilson.
I have no further questions.
Mr Weems.
Mrs Wilson...
...how many fingers
am I holding up behind my back?
Objection!
My client is on trial partly because
of powers this woman claims to have.
In all fairness, I should be given
the opportunity to test the powers
instead of having
to take her word for it!
You have a good point.
Objection overruled.
Can everyone in the jury box see
how many fingers I'm showin'?
How many fingers, Mrs Wilson?
I don't know.
You don't know?
- Seven. Seven fingers.
- That doesn't prove anything.
Your Honour, I can't do this -
you know, at the drop of a hat.
Well, ma'am, how about doing it
at the drop of a dollar bill?
What are you trying to say?
Maybe this gift doesn't work
unless you're being paid.
Like they say in the army -
no money, no honey.
That's not true.
In Hatcher County, it's illegal
for a psychic to charge people money.
- I-I don't charge money...
- You testified that you do!
No, I accept donations.
People give me gifts.
Oh... a distinction
worthy of a lawyer.
Mrs Wilson, are you a rich woman?
- No.
- Why not?
If I had powers like yours and could
read the future, I'd be filthy rich!
I'd be playing the stockmarket,
I'd be at Mobile betting on the dogs.
I'd warn my husband not to go to work
on the day the plant's gonna blow up,
leaving three children to be raised
in a carnival sideshow!
It doesn't work that way.
I can't use my gift for personal gain.
Except for those -
what you call 'em? - Donations.
You have had some personal troubles
with Donnie Barksdale, haven't you?
Yes, I have.
A few weeks ago, you said you were
gonna have his ass thrown in jail!
He was threatening my kids!
Isn't it true,
in one of those readings of yours
when you were doing your ESP,
you told Valerie Barksdale
that Donnie was an insecure redneck
and he wasn't really crazy enough
to kill anybody?
- Yes, I did say that.
- Then why are you saying he did?
- I have never said that!
- You might as well have!
You wanted his ass in jail and...
I just told the Sheriff what I saw.
And how could any of us
ever forget that?
Jessica King floatin' up in that tree...
...naked...
...with a chain... wrapped...
...around her.
It must be so much fun for you.
You must be having the time of your
life entertaining yourself with...
Think it's fun seeing decomposed
bodies in my tree, do you, sir?
You think it's fun that I've people
trying to strangle me in my sleep?!
I'm blaming myself 'cause some crazy man
tried to burn his daddy half to death
and you think I'm having fun?!
I'm sorry, sir,
you're crazy if you think that!
No more questions, Your Honour.
You're dismissed.
Let's cut to the chase. Did you
or did you not kill Jessica King?
I did not.
Did you or did you not see Jessica
King on the night she was killed?
Yeah, I seen her.
Describe the circumstances.
I'd been seeing her
for quite a while.
Would you clarify
what you mean by "seeing"?
I mean her and me
had been... having sex.
OK... go ahead.
Well, she called me about 11 o'clock
so I told her
I'd meet her out at Ay Jay's
and I told my wife
I was going out for a beer.
- What happened?
- We got into an argument.
- She didn't wanna see me no more.
- She tell you why?
She said she was getting married.
She wanted to stop playin' around.
Least till after the wedding.
During the course of this argument,
did you at any moment strike her?
Yes, sir.
What happened after you struck her?
She banged her head pretty hard
when she went down,
so I decided
to take her to the hospital.
- Did you reach the hospital?
- No, sir.
Are you feelin' OK?
I'm fine.
I wanna go back. I don't wanna go
to the hospital. Someone might see me.
She said
she was feelin' better anyhow,
so I took her back to Ay Jay's.
I dropped her off,
then I... I went on back home.
And that was the last time
you saw Jessica King alive?
- Yes, sir, the very last.
- Donnie...
...are you guilty
of the charge against you?
I'm guilty of cheatin' on my wife...
...of being a bad husband...
...a bad Christian...
...but I ain't guilty
of killing Jessie, I swear to God.
No more questions, Your Honour.
Mr Duncan.
Mr Barksdale,
you're a wife-beater, aren't you?
I've swore
to tell the truth here today.
Yeah, I've hit Valerie before.
Guess it ain't no secret.
You admit to having a history
of violence against women
and to beating up the victim
the night she was murdered.
- I wouldn't say I beat her up.
- You're the expert.
How badly do you have to beat a woman
before it fits your definition
of beating up?
Now, your story is that you've been
having an affair with the victim.
Tell us why a beautiful young woman
like Jessica King,
from one of the finest families,
about to be married
to a decent professional man
and with a bright, shining future,
would get involved
with something like you.
I asked her that myself one time.
She said I was the only man in town
who knew how to fuck.
You're really disgusting,
you know that?
- Objection, Your Honour!
- Sustained.
Mr Duncan, refrain from making
personal comments.
I apologise, Your Honour.
It won't happen again.
So let's get this straight.
Let's clarify this.
You're saying
it just was a coincidence
that on the same night
that you assaulted Jessica King,
someone else
put her body in your pond?
- I'm not saying that!
- What are you saying?
- I got framed!
- Oh, what an original defence!
Did you think of Jessica as a stray cat?
- No.
- Did you say a cat clawed your arm?
Didn't you just tell us
that Jessica scratched your arm?
Didn't you tell the Sheriff the cat
didn't like it when you killed her?
I was lying!
My wife was standing right there!
- How do we know you're not now?!
- I'm not!
- It's her, goddamnit!
- Be seated, Mr Barksdale!
She's a goddamn witch! She's putting
spells on every-damn-body in town!
In Brixton today,
Donald J Barksdale was found guilty
in the sex and strangulation
killing of Jessica King,
daughter of the prominent
businessman Kenneth King.
Is everything gonna be
all right now, Momma?
Yeah, hon.
We can get on with our lives now.
I-I guess I'm the last person
you wanna see.
How you been?
Terrible.
Annie, if you tell me
to get goin', I will.
I wouldn't blame you,
but... I need you to read for me.
Give me a hand.
I feel like I can't hold on
any longer.
I mean, I know Donnie's mean
and everythin',
but I feel real lost without him.
You know, I ain't ever been
on my own before.
I-I'm scared, Annie.
You don't need to be scared, hon.
You'll be fine.
You see that in the cards?
Mm-hm. Right through here.
Can you see what I'm thinkin'?
Can you see that in the cards?
What do you mean?
Well...
I've been thinkin'
some real bad, bad thoughts.
Un-Christian thoughts.
Like what?
Like...
...I'm glad that girl's dead - Jessica.
Messin' around with my husband,
she deserved what she got.
No one deserves that.
Like I said,
I know it's un-Christian...
What?
Are you seeing something bad?
I don't know.
It's not clear.
FUCK YOU!
Wayne?
It's not normally like this.
You need to lie down.
I'm really... not sleepy.
I think, if you sleep,
you'll feel better.
Thank you, Annie.
Wayne...
...I don't think this is a good idea.
No...
...it's not.
I just thought we could
forget all this for a while.
You want to, don't you?
I know there's something between us.
I can't.
I guess I still feel married.
You're not, though.
He's gone.
I know.
You gotta learn to deal with that.
The same way I gotta learn to deal
with the fact that Jessica's gone.
She's dead.
Oh, Wayne, I'm so sorry.
It's OK.
No, it's not OK.
I don't think
Donnie Barksdale killed her.
- No, no, Annie...
- I'm really sorry.
I... I can't do this. It's finished.
I know I want to let
that bastard rot in jail.
- He's guilty!
- No, Wayne.
I see it.
I see he didn't do it.
- Do you see who did?
- I-I'm trying.
But... I don't know yet.
What are we gonna do?
Well... if you ever had
a piece of clothing...
...or maybe
I could go out to the pond...
...or... see if I...
It's not over.
Jesus!
Come on in.
Well?
What brings you out here?
I'll just come straight out
and say it.
I don't think Donnie
killed Jessica King.
- It was open-and-shut.
- I'm telling you he didn't.
The killer is still out there.
- The Barksdales threatening you?
- No.
- I'll talk to Pearl...
- This has nothing to do with them.
I know Donnie didn't kill Jessica
the same way I knew
her body was in his pond.
And do you know who did kill her?
No.
So what do you care? He's in jail.
I got a warning today.
I think somebody's gonna try
and kill me.
- So what do you want me to do?
- Re-open the case.
- I can't. He's been convicted.
- Talk to somebody!
- I'd look like a fool!
- I don't give a damn how you'd look!
Now, you listen to me.
I know you had an affair
with Jessica.
So how will you look if people find
out you had sex with the "victim"
the night before she was killed?
You want money?
No, I want you to re-open the case.
There's a saying
about letting sleeping dogs lie.
You think you're in danger now?
Look at it logically.
The danger begins if it's re-opened
and someone starts worrying
that you're gonna have
another one of your damn dreams.
The wrong man's in jail -
I don't care how awful he is -
and I helped put him there.
I can't live with something like that.
So you find a way to re-open
this case, sir...
...or I will.
Buddy?
Buddy, I'm here...
- Hello?
- Hi, Mrs Francis, I'm back.
- How are the boys?
- Just fine.
- Want me to bring them over?
- No!
No, listen... could we stay
over at your house tonight?
- Sure you can. You all right?
- Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
- Well, come on over.
- All right.
- I'm just gonna lock up.
- OK.
- Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
Buddy?
Have you seen Buddy Cole?
No, I thought he was
at the hospital in Benton.
- Oh, he is.
- You OK?
- Maybe I imagined it.
- I don't know what I'm gonna do.
Since you told me what you told me
today, I feel like I'm going crazy.
I can't stand another night of this.
I need you to read for me.
It's no good.
- Try again.
- I can't make it happen.
How about what you said today?
What?
The... The pond.
What... What if we did
go back out there?
Do you think that might help you?
I don't know. Yeah... maybe.
Yeah, OK,
then it's worth a try, right?
You mean tonight? No, Wayne, I can't
do that. I got my kids. It's dark.
You know, it's...
It's a police matter now.
How long do you think that'll take?
It'll sit on someone's desk
for months.
It's over for them.
They've got their man. It's up to us.
I know, but I'm telling you,
I don't see anything!
You can't keeping running
from things.
Maybe if you just sort of walk around.
All right.
Oh, shoot!
Jeez! You all right? You OK?
Yeah.
What are you doin' here?
You seeing something?
I've been thinkin'
some real bad, bad thoughts.
I'm glad that girl's dead -
Jessica.
Messin' around with my husband,
she deserved what she got.
I couldn't sleep.
I met the girls for a drink.
Take off your clothes.
Aren't you taking yours off, too?
There's a saying
about letting sleeping dogs lie.
You just fucked him, didn't you?
Donnie Barksdale?
- So?
- Why would you do this to me?!
- I love you!
- Maybe I wanted to be with a man!
- Watch your mouth!
- You watch your mouth! Fuck you!
We're through!
I don't like being spied on!
The only reason I'm with you
is 'cause my daddy likes you!
- You're a joke!
- You little bitch!
I'll show you a bitch
if you don't let go of me!
- I think we'd better go back.
- Nothing's coming to you?
No...
...nothing.
You know.
I knew if I got you
close enough to it, you'd see it.
- Wayne, I-I told you...
- No, no, it's OK.
I swear to God, Annie,
it's OK, it's OK.
I wanted you to. I swear to God,
I wanted you to see it so bad.
That's why we're here.
I'm not some killer, Annie. I'm not.
You don't... Do you know
what it was like with her?
She... She was
so fucking hurtful and spiteful!
- Wayne...
- I know!
It all happened
in this flash of a moment.
- Wayne, I...
- Listen to me! I'm a good man!
If it had been you with me instead of
her, none of this would've happened!
It's all right, you know.
I won't... I won't tell.
I-I won't... I won't tell anybody.
Oh, Annie...
Are you all right, Mrs Wilson?
I thought you were supposed
to be in the hospital.
I escaped, Mrs Wilson.
I'm free.
Buddy, I'm so sorry
I wasn't there for you.
- I should've been...
- Don't you say another word.
You was the only one
that was a friend to me...
...and I love you.
You're the soul of this town,
Mrs Wilson...
...and you just need
to keep doin' what you're doin'.
I washed it.
Will you come back into town with me?
Yeah.
You know you're gonna have to go back.
Yes, ma'am, I know.
Can I have your keys, ma'am?
I just talked to Wayne.
He pretty much admitted to everything.
I've known that boy...
about half my life.
Just goes to show -
you can know somebody...
...and not know 'em.
How's his...
- How's his head?
- You put a pretty good dent in it.
Oh, no, Sheriff. I told the...
I told the deputy.
It wasn't me who did that. It was Buddy.
- He saved me.
- No, it weren't Buddy.
Well, yes, it was.
Why don't you just ask Wayne?
I did.
He don't remember what happened.
- Head injuries is funny.
- I'm telling you, it was Buddy...
What I'm trying to say is...
it couldn't have been Buddy.
I called at the State Hospital.
- He told me he escaped.
- Ma'am...
Buddy Cole is dead.
He hanged hisself
in the shower room...
...at six o'clock this evening.
But he...