Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Five minutes.
Where is Frank?
Lenny Drake
8 YEARS
VIV Batista
12 YEARS
Brodie
LIFELONG
James Lacey
7 YEARS
You've just got a friend there.
Your bets.
He is handycaped
This misses a leg.
I put two in red.
- Too late, Frank, the riders walk out
Give it back.
- Sorry, Frank, you are owed the bank
Transfer?
- I go out, Frank.
Just so?
Well.
Where is Hedges?
Have you seen him?
He said it.
Is that so?
- You're the next Lenny.
If they let him go
then you also have a good chance.
They will not as a dream couple
apart?
Drake!
Get your paws off me!
Hedges!
Catwalk!
Hello, brother.
Come on, let's get them.
- You smoked.
Give me one. Come on.
You have them all.
Someone takes care of you.
- Of course not.
Are you sure?
- Yes, I want one of the sissies.
Come on, come on.
Give me one.
Pansy!
Hey, you!
Look good to me!
The next time I see you
stand with your face against the wall!
Against the wall, yeah!
- You bet.
Pansy! Pansy! Pansy!
This is your cell. This is your bed.
This is your celgenoot.
James Lacey.
Perry. Post.
RETURN TO SENDER
Frank Perry
Prisoner Number 23401
Look somewhere else.
Think of me Muschi
I know you do to me.
Prisoner 24484 Brodie, to your Cell
Prisoner 27103 Lacey, to your Cell
Prisoner 23410 Perry, to your cell!
- Prisoner 26432 Drake to your Cell
Prisoner 135 Batista, to your Cell
You come at the wrong time,
the chapel is closed.
Perry!
Well...
It is a while ago.
I wait outside.
This is very difficult.
But...
I have her own show.
It is dinner time, Batista.
Book!
Book.
Magazine.
Give me a ticket.
Come on, a ticket, Batista.
Give me one.
Give it to me!
Ask your brother.
Do you just wait.
It is cheeky, Rizza!
You know that, damn!
Go away.
You hear me, Tony. Go away.
Batista!
Come with me.
Your choice.
Tony said...
Tony...
Checkmate.
The first time in 11 years.
Another game?
Lacey, a round to go.
I do not want.
- Go to a button.
Come on.
Five minutes.
What?
The ventilation pipes in the laundry.
Are they connected to the sewer?
What do you mean?
- The back of the dryer.
Is this connected to the sewerage system?
Frank, what is going on?
My first letter in 14 years.
Since that my little girl
is a junkie.
Her heart is twice ever since.
She is not...
- No.
Before it happens again...
I must see her.
I have things straight.
- Frank!
I want out, Brodie.
Not in a month,
not six.
Now.
Are the ventilation pipes in the laundry connected?
- Frank, I do not think...
Are they connected?
I do not ask again.
Yes.
But the vent is closed.
You will not go through a hardened steel.
Lenny Drake can do it.
- Lenny Drake? That is rapidly released.
His release was rejected.
Hedges was against the early release.
Suppose you come across,
then somewhere on the shaft.
They await you on top.
So I go deeper.
No, I do not back down.
- Should you not.
Jesus, Frank. You know why I'm here.
- Will you listen?
I want you to tell me not come.
- I can not tell you.
Damn.
I can not even draw a map for you.
Are you sure of your case?
Frank!
Without me, you save it.
Look at someone else.
I am not in the mood for a chat.
- I can understand that.
That bastard has betrayed me.
I can tell you that nobody
more surprised than me.
He hit out
and I pay for Gomez?
I have a security guard slain,
but Hedges had him detained.
When I roll-out door...
Suppose I'll get there,
with me?
Take me in the piss, Perry!
I am not to vote.
Would you prefer to save that sandbag
or number two?
Save?
I had some brutal in mind.
You walk through walls, Lenny.
This is very useful.
Is that so?
Suppose that we talk
and you're not interested,
there is still that we
never have spoken.
Yes, without saying anything.
Domino.
Three players.
Well. Closures.
One.
Two.
Three.
Locks?
- Grendel and keys.
Chance.
I am a thief, not a magician.
There is another way.
- How?
The shower drain.
Right there.
The same problem there.
And more walls.
But one. The chapel wall.
That lasts all night.
- Once considered to confess?
Behind the confessional...
separate panels.
And the chapel door?
What about the tools?
The Lord...
for us.
Domino.
The first battle
they come after us.
Alarm could be louder.
- Who sets that? - We.
If they see that we are missing.
- It is an obstacle course.
If they chase us...
We are past the drainage as the alarm
sounds. By the time they leave...
We are in the laundry.
- How long before you're in the laundry?
Five minutes.
That is enough.
Well.
Next piece.
The dryer.
Locks?
- Older than me.
What about the vent cover?
Since you do not worry about it.
I normally do.
- Yes, I am sure.
Do you have something that cuts through steel?
I have everything needed.
Have you five minutes, Two Ton?
I think I have a challenger
for you have found.
Domino.
Once we have been received,
you breathe, and you do not talk.
That underground is an echo.
Ignore you think
that just makes you crazy.
The things below are different.
The venting channel of the laundry
brings us to here, to a shaft.
Then we go deeper.
The drain.
We must pass through.
And then...
To the river.
What river?
- We are in the South, remember?
I can not swim.
No? We go underneath.
There is a reservoir below the dam.
This is the network connected.
As soon as we get to the rails,
All roads lead to Rome.
For 'Charing Cross' come out.
Why there? There are stations closer?
- Many outputs.
Easy in the rush hour to disappear.
- No, for the rush hour.
From five o'clock, the track under power.
630 Volts.
If we are not on the platform,
then we tap-dance.
How do you know all this?
How did he know all this?
Because I have 12 years.
For you a routine job.
Ok. How much time?
The night bell is about nine hours.
That gives us eight hours.
Where do we start?
- How long do you need?
Three days.
That is good for me.
On Friday...
we go away.
Another thing:
Make sure you tonight
not killed.
Please proof that
David against Goliath, is bullshit.
I would not be sure.
Did you drop something?
That I had not seen.
No, you do not.
Thought you were smart, Frank?
Was?
Do you consent?
That you do not.
Shit.
Rizza will not like.
The problem is,
that if my foot opendoe,
that those of you pissing.
You might want to regulate.
Problems.
What?
Wait a minute, Frank.
Ren is not gone.
I'm faster.
To find out Rizza,
nowhere to go.
Unless you do me a favor.
Yes, that's correct.
Do they still all in a row?
Tomorrow, when the first call, Frank.
In your cell, Frank, yes?
First bell.
Drop it!
Do not.
I do not want you ruining!
'Fish and Chips "with much vinegar?
Who want that?
You look there is to it?
Right?
A bench in the park,
the first summer...
A beautiful large portion
fresh fried cod,
wrapped in a newspaper.
Beautiful girls who look past jogging...
Understand what I mean?
No.
Are you okay?
What?
Tony.
Fuck.
- What?
How has he come back?
What does he want?
- Half a kilo.
Half a kilo? This is very much worth it.
- We have alternatives.
Yes, I think the option;
for him to murder.
Rizza and get behind us.
No way. Tony has been untouchable.
Not Tony. Batista. We murder him
and plunder his hideout.
What do we do? Looking under
his mattress? Checking his pockets?
The guy is a professional,
underestimated him.
He is not Superman!
Nobody's hands
to Tony dirt. Nobody!
Blow your case?
- No.
So?
What if...
freedom,
for Batista would be worth something?
Half a kilo?
Should I just give you that?
- No.
It is an exchange.
Who goes there any more?
Brodie.
And Lenny Drake.
Lenny Drake?
Half a kilo CAT
My monthly production.
Tony knows that.
So...
Tony about anything.
He will think that you me
have me killed or stolen.
And that stops me in a coffin,
I Rizza no liver.
It...
as Tony knows, Tony will know it.
He will not let you.
But if you want to act
then I trade with you.
CAT is a dangerous drug
but it is fatally poisoned.
Do you understand?
If it looks like,
smells and tastes like CAT...
Who will know?
- No person shall matures to Tony.
Rizza...
- Rizza?
Who says it Rizza?
Junkies die every day.
Well.
We do business.
Shit.
Brodie, wait!
Brodie...
Lights out.
You smoke?
That was the last time that I've seen.
Tomorrow she is 21.
He took a knife and cut her loose.
And on her breast, he found these lines:
Oh, what a stupid girl
I was still, hanging myself
a butcher boy.
Go dig my grave
well wide and deep.
Put a marble stone
to my head and feet
And on my grave...
...I love died.
This is cozy.
Wrap him in a blanket,
he's cold.
Give us a moment.
- No.
No, he continues.
I love his company.
You have something for me or not, Frank.
What does Sykes here?
Call it peace of mind.
How do I know if you shut up?
Be glad you still stands.
- I want a guarantee.
What do you want?
- It is trade.
I want a guarantee that you keep your mouth,
otherwise there is no deal.
You make the rules.
Yes.
Try it.
Rizza!
It is good.
It's good, kid.
Make the door
Do it, Perry! Now
Frank...
Frank.
I see something.
- What?
He came from nothing.
Could you do nothing?
He is now a walking body.
- That we all.
Why?
Little has solved for us.
As soon as he finds Sykes,
Rizza is from his roof.
Rizza know nothing.
The only thing he knows,
is that Tony cases.
And Lacey?
What happens to him?
He will not stay down long.
That makes for Rizza.
Let him Rizza about?
What weighs more, Frank:
a tonne of bricks...
or a ton of feathers?
He is a dead man,
with or without us.
We are going tomorrow,
as planned.
Where are you going?
- It is long since I've gebiecht.
Let me.
Four hours!
Let's go, we have an hour
before the trains run.
Listen!
They have found us!
- Let's go!
Keep running!
Hi, Frank.
Hi, Rizza.
Sorry about your brother.
- Why? Did you kill him?
I had no reason.
- There is always a reason.
He was a junkie,
a dick, nobody liked him.
I do not smoke, Frank. I do not
that in my neighborhood is smoked.
Did your family, Frank?
Yes.
Children?
Clever girl.
Do you love her?
Family is important.
The only significant.
So I ask you only once.
I do not ask again.
He was the guy to tackle.
He had a weakness for him.
Tony stood at the door...
and what he tried.
Sykes...
attracted him to the door way.
I heard them fight.
Fight.
After a minute.
There was very quiet.
You have not done much...
and now you take it some way.
- Rizza...
If you lie to me once...
Your little there tonight again.
I want him to sleep in my cell.
You bring him.
You have an advantage, Frank.
You're too old, too young to die.
Everything good?
- No.
It goes well with him.
Stay with us, Frank!
Are you ready?
Perry?
Batista, Mitra,
Parkhurst.
Visitors Area.
Wait, Frank.
Let's go
The track is so energized.
Frank!
Frank, now hurry!
Help me.
Go, go, go!
Go!
Hurry!
Sit down.
Where are you from, boy?
London.
Old Street.
- Old Street?
I can imagine my street
not remember.
Rizza in his cell waiting for you.
He wants me to bring you there.
Go to the chapel, boy,
for the night bell.
And do you confess.
Give it to Brodie.
I do not understand.
- Yes, do you.
Why me, Frank.
You remind me of someone.
Five minutes.
Where is he?
You know...
I got this book has certainly
read a thousand times.
If I once again could start
and could read this book again,
I would go talk with someone.
I would teach him some sense.
I would tell him
how things really are.
But I can not.
That man is a long road,
and only I am left.
Where is he?
- But you know what?
I am now Friday
Like my little girl.
- Free?
You have imagination.
- Fantasy protect us.
That keeps us alive.
You still alive,
but always less.
Inside is all yours.
You are the boss of everything
you are the king,
but look around you, what you see?
Everything is prepared.
All out.
You have nothing.
Nothing except cells, bars,
and a rusty metal staircase.
You'll never live
because your outside does not exist.
Nobody will remember you.
- Behave yourself.
Me act
kept alive as long as me.
Tell me where he is.
- Lacey?
It is well with him.
He is gone, Rizza.
- What did you say?
Way.
Where is Frank?
The kid is Friday
Do not walk away from me!
It is just what you said:
I'm too old...
Alarm!
Frank...
Frank!
I get no air.
Brodie...
Frank.
- Frank!
There is no air.
I can not breathe.
...can not breathe.
Stay with us, Frank
Stay with us!
- Come on, Frank!
Come on, Frank.
Come on.
We are Free
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org