Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Watch down the road!
- Kermit!
Look out for the billboard!
- Take off. Fozzie!
- Yes. sir!
Come back. you!
No frog's gonna make
a monkey outta me!
- I'm back.
- I don't understand any of this.
I just gotta
catch up with those guys!
Kermit. You were so courageous.
so magnificent.
Gee. I don't know what to say.
Say the bear was magnificent.
After all. I did the driving.
And I took a 1 00-foot belly flop
onto a moving car.
Yes. but. Kermit assumed
the awesome responsibility...
of command.
- Gee.
- Oh. brother.
Why don't we stop
somewhere for the night...
and have a quiet.
little dinner for two?
Terrific!
I'll eat with you. Miss Piggy.
Not you. buzzard beak!
Just mon capitaine...
and moi.
Well.
that might be nice.
Wow.
Good evening. Miss Piggy.
You look lovely tonight.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry
if I kept you waiting.
It was worth it.
How charming of vous.
I took the liberty
of ordering us some wine.
Oh. waiter.
Yes?
May I help you?
The wine. please.
You mad. impetuous fink.
It's champagne.
Not exactly.
Sparkling muscatel.
One of the finest wines of Idaho.
- You may serve us now. please.
- May I?
- Look how he does that.
- Yeah. Pretty suave.
Don't you want to smell
the bottle cap?
- Smells good.
- Yeah.
Would you like
to taste it first?
Well--
- I think he's supposed to.
- Would you taste it for us. please?
Excellent choice.
Should be for 95 cents.
- And may we have straws. please?
- Yes.
I expected that.
Thank you.
That'll be all for now.
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
Here's to you. Miss Piggy.
Drink up.
Makes me giggly.
The wine?
Everything.
It's a beautiful evening.
isn't it?
Uh-huh.
And the moon
is just lovely.
but you know. Miss Piggy...
the moon doesn't look like you.
Miss Piggy! Miss Piggy!
- Are you Miss Piggy?
- Yes?
Telephone.
I did place one phone call
to my agent.
It'll only be
an eensy-teensy moment.
What the hey.
Evenin'.
Rowlf. Rowlf the Dog.
Sit yourself down.
- Kermit. Kermit the Frog.
- Pleased to meet ya.
I'm no Heifetz.
but I get by.
That was--
That was very nice.
Whoa. hey.
broken heart. right?
Does it show?
Listen. when you've been ticklin'
the ivories as long as I have...
you've seen a broken heart
for every drop of rain.
A shattered dream
for every fallen star.
Exactly.
She just walked out on me.
- Typical. That's why I live alone.
- You do. huh?
You bet.
I finish work.
I go home. read a book...
have a couple of beers.
take myself for a walk and go to bed.
Nice and simple.
- Stay away from women. That's my motto.
- but I can't.
Neither can I.
That's my trouble.
You can't live with 'em
You can't live without 'em
There's something
irresistible-ish about 'em
we grin and bear it
'cause the nights are long
I hope that somethin'better
comes along
I see what you mean.
It's no good complainin'
and pointless to holler
If she's a beauty
she'll get under your collar
She made a monkey
out of old King Kong
I hope that somethin'better
comes along
Still. it's fun
when you're fetchin'
And agree to see an etching
That you keep at your lily pad
There is no solution
It's part of evolution
The pitter patter of soles
The little feet of tadpoles
Rowlf. tadpoles don't have feet.
Sorry about that.
Two. three. four.
There's no limitation
to mixin'and matchin'
Some get an itchin'for a critter
they've been scratchin'
A skunk was badgered
The results were strong
I hope that something better
comes along
Phone call for Kermit the Frog!
- You Kermit the Frog?
- Yeah.
Phone.
It's not that often you see a guy
that green have the blues that bad.
Kermie. please!
- Piggy. is that you?
- Yes. that's her.
And this is Doc Hopper.
Now you listen. frog. and listen good.
Step outside the motel right now.
My guys'll meet you there.
Well.
what if I don't?
Then your girlfriend
will be ham hocks by breakfast.
Kermie. don't. don't!
Are you the guys
I'm supposed to meet?
Good. Glen. That's good.
Nice and tight.
- The professor's here. Doc.
- Show him in. Show him in.
Kermie. I'm not a bit worried.
I know you're planning
something bold and clever.
Well. I got us
this far. didn't I?
- How are you?
- Professor Krassman.
It's good to see you. Doc.
you little rustic devil. you.
Where's my victim?
I mean. patient.
- Step this way. Professor.
- Of course.
Let me introduce you
to your patient.
Prof. Krassman is
the world's leading authority...
on mind control in frogs.
It's a very rapidly growing field.
You like garlic. don't you?
Tell us what you're gonna do
to our little Kermit.
Well. we're going to perform
an electronic ''cerebrectomy.''
- A what?
- An electronic cerebrectomy!
What's that?
It's something so sensational
that you'll have to hold on to your hat.
- Yes?
- When a German scientist says...
'' Hold on to your hat.''
it's not casual conversation.
Hold on to your hat!
Hat. hold! Good!
Now. what we're going to do is bring out
a machine that's going to wow you.
bertram. bertram.
bring out the machine!
Wait till you see this. You think
we're sleeping in Dusseldorf?
You think we're taking a nap
in Cologne? No. we're working at night.
Each night. a new dial.
a new knob. a diode.
- Electronic ce--
- Cerebrectomy.
- Electronic cerebrectomy.
- What does it do?
What does it do?
It turns the brains into guacamole.
First of all.
I'll pull out of this. okay?
Wonderful.
Second?
Halt!
I detest the surfeit
of provincial laughter.
Now. we take your friend.
the little '' F-O-R-G''...
put him in the chair.
clamp on the terminals...
drop the electronic yarmulke...
and throw. what we call
in German. the switch.
Yes. you little green devil...
soon it'll be a hot time
at the old skull tonight.
Thank you. Herr Machine.
Now. the frog will do your bidding.
He will do your every whim. He will do
your television commercial. yes.
He will sell your frogs' legs.
- Zaparooni.
- Head full of jelly.
- A noggin full of library paste!
- Let's fry them brains!
- You've got a fun job.
- I love it. I love it.
If I could inflict a little pain during
the afternoon. I sleep good at night.
- We'll let you get on with it. then.
- My pleasure.
Max.
I'll be back later
to pick up what's left of the frog.
''What's left of the frog.'' You can have
everything. excuse the brain.
All right.
bring over the frog.
Kermie. whatever happens next...
I wouldn't give up
this evening together for anything.
- Would you?
- Make me an offer.
Okay. I got him.
I got him.
Good. good.
And why don't we take
a little seat. Kermit?
Hold his hands down.
Get your feeties in place.
Will you
stop whimpering?
Go out like a frog.
not a little toad.
Okay. Herr Machine. this is
big time here. Ready to go to work?
Hand clamps!
Foot clamps!
You can struggle
all you want now. frog.
It'll do you
very little good.
All right. And now
it's time to drop...
the electronic beanie.
Soon there'll be enough voltage coursing
through your little frog brain...
to light up Cincinnati.
- Here we go.
- Oh. please! Not my frog. please!
- Say good-bye to the frog. pig.
- Why should I?
because in ten seconds.
he won't know you from kosher bacon.
That does it!
What the heck's goin' on here?
A pig that goes bananas?
What is this. a luau?
Where'd she go?
Oh. boys.
There she is! Get her!
I must reach the switch.
I must!
- Switch-- I must reach--
- Oh. no.
- Now. Kermie.
- Thank you.
Well...
shall we go now. Kermie?
Well--
Just a second.
What?
Piggy. it's your agent.
Thank you.
Yeah. Morty.
What have you got?
Commercial?
How much? When?
Take it.
Good-bye!
What happened?
Flip. flip. flip. flip.
Don't worry. Animal.
Your big scene is coming up.
Yeah. yeah.just be cool and
eat another seat cushion.
Seat cushion!
Well. how do you
like the film?
I've seen detergents that
leave a better film than this.
I don't care what anybody else says.
I'm having a great time.
Oh. good.
- The ''flim'' is okey-dokey.
- Good. Roll film.
'' Flim'' is ''rooling.''
Quiet. quiet.
This is the patriotic part.
- Should we stand up?
- No.
Oh. beautiful
for spacious skies
For amber waves of grain
For purple mountains'majesties
Above the fruited plain
America. America
God shed His grace on thee
And crown thy good
with brotherhood
From sea to
Shining sea
Patriotism swells in the heart
of the American bear.
Hold it. boys. Hold it!
Hold your fire!
Now. boys. no reflection
on the job you been doin'...
but I decided
to bring in a specialist.
Now. boys.
this is Snake Walker.
Tell 'em what you do. Snake.
Kill frogs.
- How long is it to Hollywood?
- We gotta be there by tomorrow.
Hey. Kermit! Are you going to
get an agent like that pig had?
Gonzo. you know
he's touchy about that.
- Hey. who's that? I don't believe that.
- Oh. no.
- That's Piggy.
- Yeah. I know.
Do you think we should
help her with her bag?
Oh. Kermie!
What an unbelievable coincidence!
Hello again.
It's me!
Would you hold
my laundry case?
- Well.
- Well what?
So much has happened to me
since I saw you last.
Frankly. Miss Piggy.
I don't give a hoot.
My name is Rowlf the Dog. and I was
playin' the piano in a-- Oh. never mind.
I missed you.
Don't I get
one kissy-kissy?
I don't think so. Miss Piggy.
Just one little hug?
You've been listening
to music to hug frogs by...
and this is Doc Hopper sayin'
that if Kermit the Frog...
don't stop right now and call me...
and agree to be my national spokesman.
he will soon be a frogburger.
- We'll be okay.
- Oh. mon capitaine.
Oh. boy. Yeah.
What? No problem!
It's okay. it's okay.
No problem. Hey. all right!
We're in trouble.
I wish I still had
my Studebaker.
There's probably somethin'
broken about the engine.
Hey. don't worry.
Someone's bound to come along.
Yeah?
Well. I guess we blew it.
huh. Gonzo?
Yeah.
but the sky sure is
beautiful out here.
Look at that.
We're gonna miss
the auditions tomorrow. right?
boy. you could get lost
in a sky like that.
I wish I had
those balloons again.
So much for Hollywood.
Listen. gang.
I never promised we'd make it.
I never promised anything.
This looks familiar
Vaguely familiar
Almost unreal.yet
It's too soon to feel yet
Close to my soul
And yet so far away
I'm going to go
back there someday
Sun rises. night falls
Sometimes the sky calls
Is that a song there
And do I belong there
I've never been there
But I know the way
I'm going to go back there
Someday
Come and go with me
It's more fun to share
we'll both be completely
At home in midair
we're flyin: not walking
On featherless wings
we can hold on to young
Like invisible string
There's not a word yet
For old friends who've just met
Part heaven. part space
Or have I found my place
You can just visit
But I plan to stay
I'm going to go back there
Someday
I didn't promise anybody anything.
What do I know
about Hollywood anyway?
Just the dreams I got from sitting
through too many double features.
So why did you leave the swamp
in the first place?
'Cause some agent fella
said I had talent.
He probably says that
to everybody.
On the other hand.
if you hadn't left the swamp...
you'd be feeling
pretty miserable anyhow.
Yeah. but then it would
just be me feelin' miserable.
Now I got a lady pig
and a bear and a chicken...
a dog. a thing--
whatever Gonzo is.
- He's a little like a turkey.
- Yeah. A little like a turkey.
- but not much.
- No. I guess not.
Anyhow. I brought 'em all out here
into the middle of nowhere.
It's all my fault.
Still...
whether you promised them
something or not...
you gotta remember
they wanted to come.
but that's because
they believed in me.
No. they believed
in the dream.
- Well. so do I. but--
- You do?
- Yeah. Of course I do.
- Well. then?
Well. then...
I guess I was wrong
when I said I never promised anyone.
I promised me.
Hey. now. wait a minute.
Hey. what's happening?
At the moment.
we're what's happening.
Oh. great!
Wonderful! Yeah!
Zoot! Hey. Zoot!
Hold it. hold it.
Animal. cool it back there.
Yeah.
All right. yeah.
Hey. it's wonderful to see you.
but how did you ever find us?
Oh. easy. We just read
the screenplay you left us.
'' Exterior desert. night.''
We knew right where you were.
Like. can you get behind it?
Hey. when you dudes
have to be at that audition?
- 2:00 tomorrow afternoon.
- Well. climb aboard the bus.
We'll have breakfast
at Hollywood and Vine.
Movin'right along
Oh.yeah
Here we go.
Movin'right along
Kermie. whisper sweet nothings
into my ear.
Motorcycle cop.
'' Motorcycle cop''
is a sweet nothing?
A motorcycle cop is chasing us.
Hey. Dr. Teeth.
you better pull over.
Hey. easier done than said.
- Drag city.
- What do we do now?
Oh. dear.
Hey. hey. The man with the badge.
The police.
The cops. the fuzz. the P-I--
- Don't you dare.
- I wouldn't think of it.
Did we do something
wrong. Officer?
- Kermie. it's him!
- Okay. gang. Let him explain.
This whole disguise is
only so I could warn you.
Yeah. Sure. sure.
I never thought Doc would hurt Kermit.
I thought he was gonna lean on him.
but now he's got this
frog killer in from the coast...
and the man is deadly!
Oh. no. Kermit.
what are we gonna do?
It's time to beat feet.
green stuff.
I love it. Chase music is
one of our best riffs.
Hold it. Dr. Teeth.
What's up ahead?
- Only an old ghost town.
- Fine.
Listen. you go tell Doc Hopper
I'll be waiting for him there.
- What?
- Kermit. you'll get killed!
Listen. guys. Listen.
I can't spend my whole life
running away from a bully.
It's time for a showdown.
Chugga. chugga.
Hey. listen.
I'm gonna check things out.
Everybody stay
on the bus. okay?
- Hey. Kermit?
- Yeah?
Can I take Animal for a walk?
He needs some exercise.
Yeah. sure.
What is that?
That's one of my latest inventions--
a musical rotating rain barrel.
- Oh. yeah.
- You see...
I'm Dr. bunsen Honeydew.
and this is my assistant. beaker.
We live here.
perfecting useful inventions.
Come in. come in.
Welcome to our laboratory.
Please don't touch anything.
Is this the only street into town?
Yes. yes.
Hey. what are you dudes
doin' in here?
I'm so glad you asked!
We're perfecting
our latest invention...
insta-grow pills.
Well. what in the name
of Fats Waller is that?
A four-foot prune!
A four-foot prune.
Yeah. man. Well. what else
do these pills make big?
They work on anything.
but the effect is.
sadly. temporary.
Sadly temporary.
Hey. Kermit!
Here comes Doc Hopper!
I know.
I'll be ready for him.
Okay. frog. Where are ya?
I'm here. I'll meet you
in the middle of the street.
- Oh. yeah?
- Man to frog.
- All right. Hopper.
- All right. frog.
One last chance.
You can do my TV commercials
live or stuffed.
What's the matter with you?
You gotta be crazy chasin' me
halfway across the country.
Why are you doin' this to me?
'Cause all my life I wanted to own
a thousand frog-leg restaurants...
and you're the key. greenie.
Yeah. well.
I've got a dream too.
but it's about singing and
dancing and making people happy.
The kind of dream that gets better
the more people you share it with.
And. well. I've found a whole bunch
of friends who have the same dream.
And it kind of
makes us like a family.
You have anybody
like that. Hopper?
Once you get all those restaurants.
who're you gonna share it with?
Who are your friends. Doc?
Those guys?
I got lots of friends.
Max. for instance.
- Max.
- I don't think you're a bad man. Doc.
I think if you look
in your heart...
you'll find you really want
to let me and my friends go...
to follow our dream.
but if that's not
the kind of man you are...
and if what I'm saying
doesn't make any sense to you...
well. then.
go ahead and kill me.
All right. boys.
Kill him.
No. wait. please!
- Everybody goin' to Hollywood?
- Yeah!
Next stop is
Hollywood and Vine.
Look at the ocean!
The ocean!
Yes. Mr. Lord. I'll have those
deal memos for you in a jiffy.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Lord can't be disturbed by anyone.
He's packaging a blockbuster.
Look! It's wonderful!
Like a dream come true.
Don't count your tadpoles until they're
hatched. I still have to audition.
Hey. ain't nothin' to it
but to do it.
And where do you think
you're going?
Hi. there!
I'm going to audition for Lew Lord.
You can't just walk in here
off the street. you know.
Especially not with
all these animals.
Animals?
What's wrong with animals?
This is a movie studio.
not a zoo!
besides--
I'm allergic to animal hair.
Now. get along. all of you.
Now. wait a second.
See here. miss.
I may not be one of your fancy
Hollywood frogs. but I deserve a chance.
We're going to stay here until you let
us in to see Lew Lord. aren't we. gang?
Yes! Yes!
- Yeah. come on!
- We're gonna sit right down and wait.
Yes. Security? Miss Tracy.
I want to report a--
Shake! Shake. everyone!
- That's it!
- Look what it's doing!
- Go get 'em. man!
- Way to go!
Allergies are nothing
to sneeze at.
I'm allergic to cats. myself.
Okay. way to go. guys!
Thanks. miss.
Well. friends...
this is it.
Mr. Lord? Forgive the interruption.
but I'm here to audition.
Yes. yes.
We've come over 2.000 miles just--
Oh. boy.
We're all with you.
Please. sir. my name is Kermit the Frog.
and we read your ad...
and. well. we've come
to be rich and famous.
Miss Tracy...
prepare the standard
'' Rich and Famous'' contract...
for Kermit the Frog and company.
Just look at all this.
How did a frog
make the big time?
It starts when we're kids.
A show-off at school
Makin'faces at friends
You're a clown and a fool
Doin'pratfalls and birdcalls
and bad imitations
Ignoring your homework
There's that dedication
working the mirror
You're getting standing ovations
You're burning with hope
You're building up steam
what was once ''juvenile-ish''
is grown up and stylish
You're close to your dream
If somebody out there loves you
- Stands up and hollers for more
- More!
You've found a home
at the magic store
All right. everybody.
production number. okay?
Off the trucks
and on the job!
- On the job!
- Hey. whoa! Aw. geez--
Wow. let's do it!
- Do what?
- The movie!
- Yes. sir! A footstomper!
- Makeup!
-Yes! Let's do it!
-Fozzie. take those wagons out of there.
Yes. sir. I'm off.
Scenery over there. Great.
Moving right along. Hey!
Hey. those are
the trees for the swamp.
Mellow and profitable.
- Let's make the scene!
- Okay. hon.
- Watch the tree. Rowlf.
- Careful. Scooter.
Watch it!
Miss Piggy.
you look beautiful.
- Thank you!
- Hollywood talk.
Good.
The lights-- Yeah.
Good. Save those arcs.
Crazy Harry plays
with electricity!
Sound is ready.
Give me a level.
Testing!
Rolling.
Okay. everybody.
Stay in focus. huh?
Okay. Muppet Movie.
scene 1 -A. take 1 .
- Makeup ready!
- Scenery ready!
- Yeah. good.
- Film is running!
- Camera rollin'!
- All ready. Kermie!
Okay. stand by.
Here we go!
why are there so many
Songs about rainbows
That's part of what rainbows do
Rainbows are memories
Sweet dream reminders
Of what is it
you'd like to do
All of us watching and wishing
we'd find it
I've noticed
you're watching too
Someday you'll find it
The rainbow connection
The lovers. the dreamers and
Life's like a movie
write your own ending
Keep believing
Keep pretending
we've done just what
we set out to do
Thanks to the lovers
The dreamers
And you
I just knew I'd catch up
with you guys!
Go home! Go home!
bye-bye.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org