Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
It's 4:15
on a Saturday morning...
My mother told me never to do this.
Bless you.
- My name's Jim Halsey.
- John Ryder.
- Can I drop you off somewhere?
- I'm getting your car wet.
This isn't my car. It's a drive-away.
The owner lives in San Diego.
So where are you headed?
- Have you got a smoke?
- Yeah, sure.
- So tell me where you're going.
What are you looking at me
like that for?
I'm just looking.
What are you doing?
What did you do that for?
I asked you a question.
Did I scare you?
I think you'd better get out now.
The ride's over.
Goodbye.
I'm going to sit here,
and you're going to drive.
DOOR AJAR
Excuse me.
What was the matter back there?
- Why?
- I thought I saw something.
- I ran out of gas.
- So you need a gas station.
- It would help.
- Okay.
Gas stations have cigarettes.
- What about gas?
- I don't need gas.
What do you want?
- What's so funny?
- That's what the other guy said.
Who is the other guy?
The guy driving the car back there.
He picked me up before you did.
- Was that him in the car?
- Sure. He couldn't have walked far.
Why's that?
Because I cut off his legs...
And his arms...
And his head...
And I'm going to do the same to you.
Don't.
What part of Illinois are you from?
- What?
- Your license plate.
Tell the man.
- Chicago.
- My wife's from Rockford.
- Have you got a cigarette?
- No.
All right, the road's clear now.
Get going, sweethearts.
Drive.
Do you want to know what happens
to an eyeball when it gets punctured?
Do you know how much blood
jets out of a guy's neck -
- when his throat's been slit?
What do you want?
I want you to stop me.
You've got the knife. You'll stick me
with it before I can do anything.
That's right, so what
have you got to lose? Stop me.
Crying isn't going to help.
Keep driving.
Please, I'll do anything.
Say four words.
Say: "I want to die."
Say what?
"I want to die." Say it.
- I don't know if I can say that.
- Sure you can. Repeat after me...
I...
Want...
To...
Die.
I don't want to die!
Fuck you, buddy.
Hey, pull over.
Pull over.
The guy in your car is a nut.
- Shoot him.
- That guy's a fucking nut.
- Kill him.
- That guy will kill you.
Get that guy out of your car.
Where do you think you're going?
See you later.
We're closed.
We don't open for another 45 minutes.
- I need to use the phone.
- Sorry, we're closed.
- No, I have to call the cops.
- What happened?
I can't explain right now.
I need to use the phone.
If Jack saw me doing this,
he'd kick my butt.
The phone is around the corner.
You stink of gasoline.
Were you in an accident?
Hello. Police? My name's Jim Halsey.
I know who killed those people...
I picked up a hitchhiker...
He blew up the gas station.
Jim Halsey. H-A-L-S-E-Y.
I'm at the Longhorn restaurant.
You do? Yes, sir.
I won't go anywhere.
Jesus...
The cops won't get here so quick.
A guy got shot here
a couple of months ago.
It took 45 minutes for them to get
here. By that time the guy was dead.
Specialty of the house. It's the
only thing I know how to make.
Thanks, that's real nice of you.
- Is everything going to be okay?
- I hope so.
You sure look a lot better.
I guess it's safe for me to smoke now.
I'm sorry I gave you a hard time.
A lot of trash passes through here.
- How is it?
- Real good. Thanks.
- My name's Nash.
- Jim Halsey.
I really appreciate this.
- Where are you from?
- Chicago.
Where are you headed?
California?
- How did you know that?
- Everyone's going. Hollywood?
- No, San Diego.
- I thought about moving.
Jeremy, who owns this place,
he's my cousin.
Uncle Jack does the cooking.
It's like that, see.
We're all kind of interrelated.
It's hard to just pick up and leave,
but you never know.
My brother Bill is from Mars.
Actually, we're all from Mars.
We keep our spaceship out the back.
What planet are you from?
- What?
- You haven't heard a word I said.
- Yes, I have.
- It's okay. Eat your burger.
I ought to get some stuff
out of the freezer.
Stand where you are!
Put your hands in the air!
- He's in there.
- Get your ass on the cement.
I'm not going to tell you again.
Put your hands behind your back.
- My wallet is in my pocket.
- Shut up! We know how to do it.
He put that there.
Shut up! Don't move.
What's going on?
What did you do to him?
- You keep to yourself.
- Why are you arresting him?
Do you know this guy?
- Not really. No.
- Then what's he doing inside?
Half the cops in the state are looking
for this creep. Get him out of here.
Where's your driver's license?
Your ID?
Where are your credit cards?
The guy I have been telling you about
took my wallet and planted the knife.
My license was in my wallet.
I don't have any credit cards.
I suppose he took
your vehicle registration, too.
That's a fancy car for such
a young kid. Did you steal it?
The car doesn't belong to me.
It's a drive-away.
I'm delivering it to California.
The guy is in San Diego.
What's his name?
I don't remember.
I know the number of the drive-away
company. Call them.
We'd better call somebody,
because you're in deep shit.
It's 312-399-2090.
I know their number. I was
on their waiting list for a month.
I wanted a car going to California.
That's why it took so long.
Midwest Drive-away.
Our office hours are 9 to 5.
Closed Saturday and Sunday.
Now what are we going to do?
You've got one more call.
Call my brother. He'll be home.
It's 312-905-9044.
You didn't let it ring long enough.
Do I look like a killer to you?
Some folks from Austin
will be here to talk to you tomorrow.
You'd better get some rest.
Get him locked up.
Let's go.
Jack, that kid isn't a killer,
any fool could see that.
Okay, face front. Hold real still.
Turn to your right. Steady.
Make a left.
Those are real good.
Your mom is going to like those.
You behave yourself now.
Hello?
Hello!
Come on.
- Stop!
- Take it easy.
Get over by the car.
Those cuffs on your belt,
put them on your partner.
- You mean me?
- No, you!
Okay, we're going for a little ride.
Get in the front. I'll be in the back.
One of you open the door.
Get in the car.
Okay, you and me
are going to get in together.
Go.
- May I close the door?
- Yes.
Start the car.
Head for the highway.
Can you get me in touch
with someone who's in charge?
I'll try to get through
to Capt. Esteridge.
Okay, do it...
But don't tell them where we are.
- Central...
- Don't tell them anything.
Central, we have been hijacked
by the suspect.
He wishes to speak
to Capt. Esteridge directly.
We'll try to locate Esteridge.
Stand by.
This is Capt. Esteridge.
Do you read? Over.
This is Jim Halsey. Listen,
I swear I didn't kill those people.
I got set up
by this guy I picked up hitchhiking.
- What do you suggest we do?
- Come on, man, you tell me.
Stop this right now. Let my men go,
and give yourself up.
I don't have any identification.
How are you going to check me out?
Are you willing to surrender?
I'll do everything in my power
to see that you're treated fairly.
I'm putting my trust in you, Captain.
Take us in.
I know you caught something.
You're the best fisherman around.
But if that's the best you can eat,
I don't know what you're going to do.
- That'll tide us over.
- Then you'd better go.
- We'd better get on the road.
- Yeah, I'll see you.
- What happened to you?
- Nothing.
Nothing happened.
- I need some coffee.
- It's brewing.
- I'll sit in one of the booths.
- Are you okay, kid?
No.
How do you like shitsville?
Don't you move.
You stay seated right where you are.
Or I'll blow your brains
through your ass.
The gun is empty.
- You never checked it.
- I'll blow you in half.
- All right, squeeze the trigger.
- I will.
You can sure as shit bet
I'm going to squeeze mine.
Why are you doing this to me?
You're a smart kid.
You figure it out.
I didn't do it.
I didn't do any of it.
I'm not going to shoot anybody.
I'm not a killer.
This morning a guy tried to kill me.
He's been following me ever since.
I don't know why.
Do you believe me?
Sure. Yeah.
No, you don't. I wouldn't either.
Let's go and sit down.
What are you going to do?
Give up. I have no choice.
Step down.
All right, step down.
I'm turning myself in.
Step out from behind the door.
Step away from the bus. Move.
- Move your ass, now.
- I'm giving up. I'm not guilty.
You just wasted two of my friends.
You spit on my wrist.
You spit on my wrist. Wipe it off.
- You can see I'm not armed.
- Lyle, go easy.
- Wipe it off.
- Put the gun down.
Goddamn you.
Drop your guns. Don't turn around.
I can't believe you were going to do
what you were going to do.
- Don't you know who he is?
- You've got the wrong man, Lyle.
Like hell we do.
Just settle down.
- Don't come any closer.
- Hand me that gun.
- Empty them. We're in enough trouble.
- Your life's going down the toilet.
When the truth comes down,
I'll be just fine.
I'm taking him
to the sheriff's office in Riley.
Let's go!
- Now what?
- We're going to Riley.
- Can you use the radio?
- I'd better let you out.
They won't hurt you if I'm here.
Talk to them on the radio.
- What are we going to say?
- That we're turning ourselves in.
Buckle your seatbelt.
Do mine.
Can you hear me?
We're turning ourselves in.
We are turning ourselves in.
Do you read me?
We just want to turn ourselves in!
Take the gun. Use it.
- Shoot somebody?
- Aim for the tires.
They're going to kill us.
Use it. Shoot them.
Use the gun.
Shoot back!
- I dropped the gun.
- You what?
Take the shot gun.
Hold on.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Go, you son-of-a-bitch.
Let's get out of here.
- Why didn't he kill us?
- Let's go.
Why didn't he kill us?
Let's go.
Are you okay?
Why did you pick him up?
I wanted to help him.
I was tired.
I thought he'd help me stay awake.
Can I sit by you?
- What are you doing? No calls.
- It's only my father.
No calls, not until I figure out
what we're going to do.
- I can explain it.
- It's not that simple.
I've already tried.
I'm scared.
Me, too.
Nash...
Are you awake?
No, I'm okay.
I just want you to know
where I am.
Everybody has got
this whole thing wrong.
I sound funny,
but I'm okay.
Nash?
Nash!
Take it easy now.
Are you Jim Halsey?
- Who are you?
- Esteridge. We spoke on the radio.
- Where is she?
- We need your help.
Hold your fire.
- No, don't.
- Why don't you do something?
We can't.
If we shoot him, his foot slips,
that truck is going to roll.
You get in there
and see what you can do.
Please, help.
She's sweet.
The gun is loaded.
Go for it.
Go ahead. Pick it up.
I'll let you hold the gun on me
before I do anything.
They'll catch you.
Yeah, sure. So what?
Pick up the gun.
Put it in my face.
Right there.
That's good.
You know what to do, now do it.
Squeeze the trigger.
She'll die.
You useless... waste.
I can't tell you
how sorry I am for you, son.
Anything I can do for you?
You should probably go
and see a doctor for a full check-up.
We all know
there was nothing you could do.
- Who is he?
- We don't know.
No prison record. No driver's
license. No birth certificate.
We ran his prints,
but we came up with nothing.
Right now, I don't even know his name.
How do you feel?
Tired.
He can't see us or hear us.
I want to talk to him.
What's your name?
Come on. What's your name?
- Do you have a name?
- John Ryder.
- What did he say?
- His name is John Ryder.
Do you have a police record?
Where are you from?
Disneyland.
- How long do we keep playing games?
- Can you give me a minute?
All right, that's enough.
This was a bad idea.
All right, get in the car.
Are you okay?
You'll never hold him.
You listen up now, son.
I know there's something going on
between the two of you.
But he's in our hands now. We'll
decide what happens to him, not you.
It doesn't have anything to do
with you anymore. Okay?
- Can I have a cigarette?
- Sure.
Stop the car.
You're not going to use that thing.
Stop the car
and don't do anything stupid.
All right, what's on your mind?
Get out.
You're going to get yourself killed
or end up in a whole lot of trouble.
I'm sorry, sir.
It's something I've got to do.
- You don't know what you're doing.
- Yeah, I do.
Hi, kid.
Come on.
Come on!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org