Malone!
Williams, what is it?
What did we hit?
I don't know.
There's something in the water.
Clear us now, Williams.
- Hold steady, Wayne.
- There's something down there.
Clear it away.
I can't see anything.
Williams.
Hey, out there.
You've got the one and only
Stevie Wayne...
... broadcasting from my own
little corner of the world...
... high in the KAB lighthouse
on Antonio Island.
It is perfect weather for this week's
dedication of the new statue...
... honoring the memory
of Antonio Bay's founding fathers.
So get on down to the town hall
and check out the monument...
...to those four brave men.
One of whom was
my great-great-grandfather...
... Richard Wayne.
Did I already mention that?
David Williams.
Patrick Malone.
Norman Castle. Richard Wayne.
- It's all wrong.
- Oh, come on, Kathy.
Who cares which one
holds the telescope.
It's a spyglass, Tom.
David Williams is supposed to be
holding it. He was the visionary.
We've gotta get this right.
The four of them rode out
against impossible odds...
...to defend this island
with their lives.
I know, I know. Through the fog.
The Malone family name is on
that statue, Tom.
- It has to be accurate.
- We've got tourists arriving on Friday.
What do you wanna do,
send it back?
Fine. We'll have
the unveiling tomorrow...
...and I'll send it back
at the end of the season.
Look around you, boys.
This is God's country.
Anywhere you go on Earth...
Sea of Cortez, Nantucket Sound...
...Gulf of Mexico.... You'll never find
better fishing than what we had here.
- Sushi?
- No. I'm good, thanks.
Nice speech.
And you've been to how many
of those places?
Not a one.
My dad used to tell me stories.
He was the traveler.
Sure is a long way out
to find the sandbar.
Well, this is where
the ocean floor is.
Which is where the kelp
and the little fish are...
...which is why you got
some big fish here today.
- Mr. Spooner?
- Sir?
- Let's weigh the anchor, call it a day.
- Yes, sir.
Damn. Hey, yo, Nick.
We're snagged on something.
Spooner? You all right?
The winch is jammed.
I can't shut it off.
- Shut it down.
- I'm trying to.
Spooner. Spooner.
- Nick, get up here.
- Give it some slack.
I'm trying to, all right?
The winch is stuck.
Hey, I lost all my fish.
- We're going down.
- We're not going down.
- Spooner.
- Can't get it. It's not coming loose.
You guys okay?
Yeah. See?
You got a little something there.
Sorry about the mishap.
Come back and see us again.
Yeah, we'll be back.
What? They said they'd be back.
They... They... I believe them.
I was convinced, when they said...
..."We'll be back,"
they had the "I'll be back" face.
- Hey, yo, Nick.
- Yeah, in here.
I don't suppose they left
a brother a tip.
Yeah, right.
Hey, you know
that wasn't my fault, right?
Don't... Do that again.
Damn, you sexy as hell
when you're mad. It's incredible.
Where you going?
We got decks to swab.
I'm going to Little Ray's to get
a clutch for the one you broke.
I broke it?
Make sure you end up at Little Ray's.
Don't end up at little Stevie's.
- That was a one-time thing.
- All three times?
Because I remember the lighthouse,
then the time in the field.
Oh, let's not forget about
the little church parking lot, choir boy.
- Twice. It was twice.
- Twice all three times?
- Your point is?
- Really don't have one.
But she does know Elizabeth.
What if she blabs?
Elizabeth...
...is 3000 miles away.
She's been gone for six months.
Distance is not a factor.
Women have testicle telepathy, man.
Hose down the boat, lock it up...
...so we don't go out of business.
- "We"?
We need to book
another charter to make money.
I got a idea.
Why don't you do some work here...
...and I'll get the clutch.
I'm The Skipper,
and you're Gilligan.
Like that? After all that "we,"
now I'm just Gilligan?
And I'm by myself, huh?
So that's it, huh?
How much that cost?
A heartfelt tribute to the founding
fathers of Antonio Bay.
Could've used that money
down at the marina.
New sea-wall, shore up that pier.
These four men built this town
out of nothing.
Without their sacrifice,
there wouldn't be a marina or a pier.
In honoring the past,
we celebrate the present.
I never understood that line myself.
- And I'm sure you never will, Nicholas.
- Mrs. Williams.
Gonna come to the unveiling?
Your family's name is on that statue.
I can't help that, can I?
Oh, no.
- Adrift. North-by-northwest swells
past the break.
Otherwise, you've got fair winds
and flat waters.
Oh, and me, your lighthouse keeper,
Stevie Wayne.
Voice that launched
a thousand ships.
So if you're not in the mood...
...turn it down,
because I'm gonna turn it up...
...on 94.5, KAB...
...your island alternative to
the modern music establishment.
Playing the music I wanna hear.
- Want a ride?
- Wrong direction.
Not anymore.
You're not a freak, are you?
Yeah, actually, I am.
- Good.
- Shit.
I leave town, you start picking up
strange girls on the road.
- Elizabeth? No, no. I recognized you.
- I haven't been gone that long, Nick.
I knew it was you.
- So you're back.
- No place like home.
Only took you six months
to figure that out.
I just need to come back for a while.
And, Nick...
...next time
open the door for a lady.
Ahoy, mateys.
Another perfect moonlit eve
here on the isle...
... and you're listening
to Stevie Wayne...
... your very own
beacon in the night.
Oh, shit.
Can't say that on regular radio
but what the hell.
I can say whatever I want.
It's my very own station.
Listen up. Got a low-tide warning
in the a.m. For you.
And as I check
my lighthouse gauges...
...looks like the old barometer
is on the rise.
So it could be, Dan the Weatherman
might just be right for a change.
Hey, yo, Sean.
Get your ass up here
and take the helm.
One second, ladies.
Yeah. My turn to play.
- This is my cousin's boat, man.
- Well, Nick's not here, is he?
Huh? You see your cousin?
That sucks.
Why do I have to drive?
Because I'm The Skipper,
and you're Gilligan.
Oh, right.
Ladies, the Spooner wait is over.
Yeah. Booty on the Boat,
the new reality show.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'd like to
introduce you to our guests of honor:
Mandi and Brandi, the twins.
We're not twins.
- My name's Jennifer.
- Sean, they're not twins.
- Neither are we.
- So we can do this now.
You swear y'all ain't twins?
You know you girls could model?
I could hook you up.
Right after this little audition tape.
I just gotta pick up
a part for the Seagrass.
It'll just take a second.
And, you, don't go anywhere,
all right?
You know the difference
between flotsam and jetsam?
- Machen.
- People get washed up on shore.
Some bob around at sea forever.
You used to be Elizabeth.
- I still am.
- I have something to show you.
If you touch it, things will change.
It's still ticking.
It wasn't ticking before.
Where'd you get it?
From the sea. Came back.
Sooner or later, everything does.
Do you have a lighter?
Yeah.
It's a hallmark. Tells where a piece
was made and roughly when.
Looks familiar.
Elizabeth.
Farewell, Elizabeth.
What was that about?
He found a watch on the beach.
That guy gives me the creeps.
I know it sounds crazy, but I felt like
I'd seen it somewhere before.
Where?
I don't know. Let's go.
- Hey, Andy.
- Hey, darling.
Hey, Dan.
You lonely over there without me?
Remind me why I gave you
my cell phone number again?
Because I'm 6 feet of burning love.
Actually you're 5'9", Dan.
Now tell me why you called,
or I'm gonna hang up.
Okay, okay. I just thought you might
like something to talk about.
Okay. I'm listening.
I got something
on my Doppler a minute ago.
Sounds kinky.
Looks like a fog bank
about 10 miles out...
...and it's moving
straight towards us.
Well, my gauges must be wrong then.
I'm showing a wind blowing due west.
Now, what kind of fog
moves against the wind?
You got me.
But my radar doesn't lie.
- Gotta go. I'm on.
- Okay.
It is just before 10 on Spivey Point.
This is Stevie Wayne,
beaming my signal across the sea.
Dan the Weatherman says
a fog bank is rolling in offshore.
So if I were you,
I would lock the doors...
...throw away the keys
and whip up a pitcher of martinis...
... while you listen to another hour
of music on KAB.
Serving up the platters that matter.
There's no fog out there.
Hey, Spooner.
You see any fog out there?
There's no fog out here.
Ladies, you see any fog?
I don't see any fog out there.
Did they talk about beautiful women?
Because that's definitely out here.
Look at this. Blurring my vision.
Spooner, the engine's dead.
Nobody care about that.
You know why? Because we got beer.
And for two, we got beer.
And after that, beer.
And we got music too.
That's all that matter, all right?
Dance over here
and have some fun.
Look at that. My Lord.
Yeah.
Yeah. You all wanna see
Spooner get low? Let me get low.
Harbor patrol, this is Seagrass.
Do you copy?
Coast Guard, this is Seagrass.
Do you copy? Over.
Damn. Wait a second.
This new radio is...
I don't know why it does this.
It's that new song
that starts with the static.
It starts with static then it goes to
the beat and music. Wait a second.
What are you doing?
No coats.
Coats, bad. Naked, good.
It's freezing out there.
What's going on?
Hell of a fog bank.
Where'd that come from?
Hey, Spooner.
What's going on out there, man?
Spooner.
Dude, do you see this?
So I guess New York is just, like,
the best thing ever, huh?
I wouldn't say that.
Well, you happy there?
Sometimes.
I don't know, Nick.
What do you want me to say?
I don't know. I wake up
one morning and you're gone.
No note, nothing.
I don't belong on this island, Nick.
The thing I always loved most
about you...
...is you were the one person
who understood that.
The day you left,
I bought you something.
- What?
- A ring.
You bought me a ring?
No. But I thought about it.
You're such a liar.
- Are you okay?
- I think so.
- What the hell was that?
- Murderers.
Nothing but murderers.
Blood for blood.
Father Malone.
Nicholas.
Elizabeth.
Did you see what happened
back there?
- I...
- Did something hit us?
I didn't see anything.
Looking for my car.
It's around here somewhere.
I can't...
Sure you're all right?
Yeah.
Man, I can't see nothing.
- What's going on?
- These...
- The hell did you do?
- Nothing. I just called for help.
Oh, my God. There's something
right in front of us. Look at that.
Stop. Screaming will get
nothing done.
You all right? Calm down.
Just get us out of here, please.
You're all right.
You'll be okay, all right?
- Are there any lights anywhere?
- Wait. One second.
You okay?
Hello?
Is somebody out here?
Sean.
- Sean.
- Does this radio work?
- It's gone. It's gone.
- What?
- What is?
- There was a big sailing ship.
- Y'all didn't see that ship?
- No.
I'm trying to tell you...
It was right here.
Let's just see what the hell
happened to the engine.
Jennifer, what are you doing?
- What the hell was that?
- I don't know. I don't know.
Dude, let's fix it
and get out of here.
- What the hell is that?
- Don't know.
Somebody in there?
- You sure you wanna go in there?
- My mom will kill me if I don't.
Call you tomorrow?
Good luck.
Hello?
Who's there?
It's me.
Well...
- This is a surprise.
- A good one?
Don't see any suitcases. I guess
that means you're not moving back.
I thought you'd be happy
I came back at all.
I wish you'd called me. I...
I mean, it's not like
I'm running a hotel here.
Good to see you too, Mom.
You waited.
You lasted 30 seconds longer
than I thought you would.
You're learning.
Did you say hello for me?
So where to now?
- Let's go to your place.
- For some wild and crazy sex?
With a strange hitchhiker?
You wish.
Elizabeth? Hey.
Hey, it's... What is it?
What's wrong?
I...
I keep seeing people...
...burning.
And they're screaming.
And I'm watching and... And...
And then I'm drowning.
It's just a dream.
I've been having them a lot.
It's why I came home.
Come here.
Come on.
Elizabeth.
You okay?
What are you doing down here?
It's freezing. Come on.
Let's go back to bed.
Mom.
Mom, wake up. Look what I found.
Andy, what is that?
I found it on the beach
between some rocks. It's heavy.
Feel.
Looks like it must've been somebody's
hairbrush once upon a time.
Want me to make you
some breakfast?
No, I wanna go back
down to the beach.
Fine, just a half an hour, okay?
I have to go into work early.
I have a very busy day.
Can I come to the station with you?
No. Not today, hon.
I have too much work to do.
But maybe later in the week, okay?
How's that?
Maybe Aunt Connie'll go to the beach
with you and help you find more stuff.
No.
All she does is eat Ding Dongs
and watch Jeopardy!
I love you.
"Love you too, Mom."
It's usually after a storm when
anything's washed up on the beach.
Yeah, but we haven't had
a storm in months.
- It's an interesting piece, isn't it?
- Yeah, it is.
- I'll let you know.
- Thanks.
Oh, this is a beautiful piece.
If it washes up on the beach,
it's ours now, right?
Well, technically speaking.
So, what's it worth?
Hey, Nick.
Stevie, how you doing?
Great. I hear your girl's
back in town.
- Yeah, she is. She's back.
- Good. She's gonna be here a while?
Who knows.
Yeah, who knows.
Saved by the bell.
Hello? Hey, Uncle Hank.
- Elizabeth?
- Mr. Latham.
It is you. How are you, dear?
- Good.
- God, we missed you around here.
What are you up to?
This stamp. I feel like I've
seen it somewhere before.
You recognize it at all?
No. Can't say I do.
But I know Prince William Island.
It was a big trading post up north.
Gold, seal furs, fox pelts.
They traded with Shanghai
for spices and jade.
A lot of people got rich in a hurry.
So then why did they stop
production suddenly in 1871?
Nobody lived there
after the outbreak.
What outbreak?
Leprosy.
The Chinese brought it over.
Wiped out half the island.
The other half left by ship.
That's as much as I know.
They never came back.
- Elizabeth.
- Nick, what's wrong?
Hank just called.
Spooner took the Seagrass out
and never came back.
We gotta go.
Like I said on the phone...
...I saw them head out
last night at 8:30.
Haven't been heard from since.
- And no one's seen her?
- Not that I've heard.
- I gotta call the Coast Guard, Nick.
- Don't do that just yet.
They... They're probably just...
...anchored up the channel
somewhere. We'll go find them.
- Can we use your boat?
- Sure.
Thanks.
Spooner!
Spooner?
Maybe somebody picked him up.
Let's hope.
Look at this.
The gauges are all smashed.
Got a half a tank of gas.
The engine still works.
Spooner?
Sean?
Nick?
- Nick, what's wrong?
- Sean. He's dead.
- What?
- His eyes...
- He's dead.
No!
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Go inside. Call for help.
Mayday. Mayday.
Hello?
No!
Let me go. Jennifer.
Did he say anything to you two?
Not a word.
Mayor, you still want me
to lock him up?
Lock him up for what?
You saw the bodies.
You think they got that way
by accident?
Tom, Coast Guard wants you
on the radio.
You tell your pal, when he thaws out
he better have a damn good story.
I hid from it.
You hid from what?
It killed them.
The fog killed them.
I hid in the freezer.
It couldn't get in the freezer.
All right, Spooner, just relax.
You're not making any sense.
You'll be all right.
Okay, guys, we'll take care of him.
Okay, come on.
It's gonna be all right.
It's okay now. It's okay.
The fog killed them?
Look. I found this on the boat.
Take it. Keep it safe.
It's a piece of evidence.
It might prove
that Spooner's innocent.
Just keep it safe.
Okay.
Let's see.
So you like your gift?
I think it's more for you
than it is for me, Dan.
It's pretty cool, though, huh?
If I wanted people to see me,
I wouldn't have gone into radio.
- Over and out.
- You hear about the Seagrass?
Yeah. Yeah, I did.
Well, I gotta go.
- Call me later, okay?
- I will.
Somebody please
beam me out of here.
Look at that.
Beautiful women
cavorting around half-naked.
This new radio is...
I don't know why it does this.
- We're going inside.
- No, no.
- Oh, God. It's freezing.
- Wait.