[¶ ¶]
- Need a hand?
- Um...
yeah. Sure.
Thanks.
It's just through here.
Hey. Hi, buddy.
Hey, Dex.
Boy, it's a hot one, huh?
Yeah.
Do you have fish?
No. Take a closer look.
Hey. Good boy.
Stick insect.
- Stick insect?
- They're actually very friendly.
George.
Mary.
Want something to drink?
I think I got juice, maybe beer.
Oh, no, I'm okay.
I'll just let you carry on.
It's fine.
- Thanks again.
- Okay.
Hey, um, that stick insect?
How do you know
it's being friendly?
I have no idea.
[WOMAN 1 ON TV]:
She loved you too.
[MAN]: You let me go on
loving you, waiting.
Also, why did you try
to kill something that can't ever die?
I needed you then.
I need you now.
I'll always need you.
[PHONE RINGING]
[WOMAN 1]:
I knew it all the time.
Hello?
[WOMAN 2 OVER PHONE]:
Is that 722-5795?
- Yeah.
- Is Bobby there?
No. I just moved in.
Maybe he had the apartment before?
[LINE CLICKS]
[WOMAN]: Mr. Davies,
anything you wish to add?
Like I said, Your Honor, um...
my client feels a restraining order...
to be an unjustified stain
on his character...
and would like to have it lifted
at first opportunity.
Noted.
There's also the matter
of the family pet.
I've made my position clear on that.
But my client would like to know,
if there's any...
Counselor, Miss Kee keeps the dog.
Mr. Kirby.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Your Honor, the divorce papers.
Your Honor, there's been
an unforeseen delay.
I will send them right over.
[¶ ¶]
[DOORBELL BUZZES]
You can't be here.
Just wanted to drop them off myself.
Figured it was the least I could do.
[DOG BARKING]
Oh, there's the bad boy.
Yes, it is.
Daddy's home.
Yes, he is. Yes, he is.
You signed them?
[¶ ¶]
We had some good times,
didn't we?
[¶ ¶]
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[WOMAN]:
How about work?
[MARY]:
They're being understanding.
You are going back, right?
Not yet.
Has he called again?
How about going out,
meeting people?
[¶ ¶]
He said if he couldn't have you,
no one else would.
You live like this,
in fear,
he's won.
Come here, come on.
[AIR CONDITIONER RATTLING]
Come on, come on.
[AIR CONDITIONER STOPS]
Come on.
[MAN 1 ON TV]:
Question nine:
Edinburgh is the capital
of which country?
Ireland.
- [MAN 2]: Scotland?
- That's what I meant.
[MAN 1]:
Is the correct answer.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
[WOMAN]:
May I speak with Bobby, please?
There's no Bobby here.
May I ask who you are?
Who I am?
Is this a joke?
Did Steven put you up to this?
Would you do me a favor, please?
Tell him Rose called.
I'll be in Frank's at 8
if he wants to see me.
Rose, this friend of yours?
He really isn't here.
And, you know, like I said,
I moved in a couple of days ago.
I walked past the house last night.
I saw him right there
in the window.
- You have the right address?
- El Falansterio, L-2.
Just tell him Frank's at 8, okay?
Frank's at 8. Sure.
If a guy called Bobby passes by,
I'll tell him whatever you want.
Hello.
Hi.
[CLEARS THROAT]
There are strict rules
in this college...
about perpetuating age-
or gender-based stereotypes.
Excuse me?
It would be a breach of guidelines
for me to suggest...
that you may have
mistakenly wandered...
into Math for Stage Two Mechanical
Engineering here in 14-A...
as opposed to, for example...
Conversational French?
In 14-B.
Well, as it happens, I was wanting
to pursue a course on Math for...
Stage Two Engineering.
But having heard there's a course
on Conversational French...
I hope you won't be too offended.
A little disappointed, maybe.
Excuse me.
What?
[¶ ¶]
You look tired.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
[ROSE]:
Bobby says he doesn't know you.
Bobby's right.
You should listen to him.
And while you're at it,
check his goddamn number.
You think I'm mad at you,
don't you?
But I'm not.
He's using you. It's what he does.
Normally I like talking to crazy people,
but I'm kinda tired today.
Wait, don't hang up, please.
Please.
[ROSE SOBBING]
Look, there's been a mistake,
a crossed line or something.
He said he loved me.
[ROSE CONTINUES SOBBING]
[¶ ¶]
Rose?
I'm sorry for what's happened.
But your friend isn't here
and I don't know you.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
No harm done.
What's your name?
Mary.
Mary what?
Mary Kee.
He asked me to marry him.
Lucky you.
The day he got back from Vietnam.
Came by in his uniform,
got down on one knee.
Vietnam? You mean the war?
Oh, he didn't wanna go.
He was drafted.
How old are you?
Forty-one.
Rose, the Vietnam War was,
what, 35, 40 years ago?
You would have been a child.
Why are you doing this?
Doing what?
What did I ever do to you?!
[LINE CLICKS]
[¶ ¶]
[RECORDED VOICE]: We're sorry.
That number is unobtainable.
[SIREN WAILING]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[¶ ¶]
[SCREAMS]
Oh, sorry. I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I wasn't thinking. I shouldn't have just...
Wait let me help you with that.
- How was... how was French?
- I have to go.
- I really didn't mean to scare you.
[CHILDREN CHATTERING]
You trying to steal my job,
young lady?
Do you do the weeding
around here?
I sure do.
What do you call this?
Oversight.
Pack up your desk, mister.
You're fired.
Wow, you're a hard one.
Knew that the first time
I laid my eyes on you.
"Pack up your desk".
[PHONE RINGING]
Excuse me.
- Hello?
- [ROSE]: What's the date?
This is harassment.
September 4th, 1979.
I can prove it.
You know that big kitchen pantry?
I'll draw something.
Um...
On the wall, just inside the door
on the right-hand side.
And then if it's still there,
you'll know I'm right.
Will you do that?
Will you look?
Sure, Rose.
I'll look.
[LINE CLICKS]
[¶ ¶]
[CLOCK TICKING]
[PHONE RINGING]
- Hello?
- [ROSE]: Was it there?
It was, wasn't it?
A picture. A rose.
I knew it.
- I wanna know what's going on.
- What do you mean?
You knew the picture was there.
Maybe someone told you about it.
- I don't know. I want the truth.
- I drew it.
I did it last night like I said I would,
and it's still there.
I don't believe you.
But I'm supposed to believe you?
You tell me you're from the future
and I believe you. I don't call you crazy.
I give you proof
and you call me a liar.
I'm not calling you a liar.
This is happening for a reason.
I gotta go.
Not yet, please.
There's things I need to ask you.
Carter loses.
Reagan becomes president.
[¶ ¶]
Morning.
They're beautiful.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, man.
Did you know the people before me
in the apartment?
A Spanish couple.
Mr. and Mrs. Alvarez.
Nice people.
You know Mrs. Alvarez, she would cook
this caldo gallego from time to time.
To die for. Yeah.
Why did they leave?
I don't know.
I got up one day, they were gone.
Guess some family stuff
or something. Not sure.
I don't know.
And the people before them?
Before?
I could hardly remember what
I had for breakfast.
I don't know.
[¶ ¶]
[PHONE RINGING]
[ROSE]:
Don't hang up, please.
Please?
Mary? Are you there?
I just need someone to talk to.
I get so lonely. Please.
You're so busy,
you can't spare five minutes?
I'm here.
Thank you for not hanging up.
[MARY]:
This is a little weird.
[ROSE]: Well, people come together
for a reason, Mary.
It doesn't matter how.
Do you believe that?
[MARY]:
I don't know. I suppose.
- [ROSE]: Why are you sad?
- [MARY]: I have to go now.
[ROSE]:
Is it a man?
- Did he cheat on you?
- No.
[ROSE]: Oh, don't be sad, Mary.
You sound like a smart lady.
You'll find someone better,
someone who deserves you.
Bobby cheats on me all the time.
[MARY]:
Why don't you leave him?
[ROSE]:
I love him.
[MARY]:
So find a good substitute.
Chocolate's good.
[ROSE LAUGHS]
[ROSE]:
He keeps promising he'll change.
[MARY]: You've heard of feminism, yeah?
Women's lib?
[ROSE]:
Yeah, of course.
[MARY]:
Jump on the bandwagon. It's a goer.
[ROSE]:
Bobby doesn't like women's lib.
He says they need a good smack.
MARY: He ever do that to you?
[ROSE]:
Not really.
[MARY]:
Not really?
[ROSE]:
He says he loves me.
[MARY]:
They don't change, Rose.
Ever.
Sometimes I think
I should have just got rid of him.
Sometimes I think walking out
was the worst mistake I ever made.
[PLASTIC BAG CRINKLING]
[¶ ¶]
[PHONE RINGING]
[ROSE]:
I took your advice.
What?
He... he laughed at me.
I told him about you and me
and how he had to change
and he just kept on laughing.
I got rid of him, Mary,
just like you told me to.
I worked all night.
Real quiet
so the neighbors wouldn't hear.
They'll never find him.
They'll think he ran away
with one of his tramps.
You killed him.
I can move into
the apartment now.
They don't care who pays the rent.
I always hoped I'd live there
with Bobby someday, but...
Mary, are you there?
Don't ever call me, understand?
I just did what you told me to do.
Don't ever call me again.
[PHONE RINGING]
[RINGING STOPS]
[¶ ¶]
[SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
Marie?
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
Oh, God.
[SCREAMS]
How big is he?
Bigger than you.
Yeah, but I'm wiry.
Be careful.
Come here.
Why?
That's not what I saw.
[JOHN]:
How did you end up down here?
[MARY]: Navy brat. My dad
was stationed at Roosey Roads.
- It's just closed, right?
- Mm-hm.
You?
My grandparents came over
from Turin.
I was born here, but I went to school
in Florida. Gainesville.
Taught there for a while.
And then I saw the opening
at the college.
Don't get many Italians
in San Juan.
By the time my grandfather
realized this wasn't New York,
the boat had already sailed.
That's not true.
Ma, that true about Pappy?
Idiot got on the wrong boat.
Thank you very much, Mrs. Guidi.
I like this one.
Does he, uh,
bring girls around often?
One time before.
Ma.
She asked, I'm gonna tell.
A girl called Trulli.
Trudy, Trudy.
That girl could eat like a horse.
Ma.
Giovanni, that girl Johnny
brought home, what did she eat?
Let's see.
Caesar salad, roast beef,
french fries, carrots,
minced peas, three pieces of
bread and butter and a tiramisu.
What happened to Trudy?
She exploded.
Would you like something else?
No, thank you.
We should be...
We should be going.
Mm-mm.
Hey, see you, Pop.
Nice meeting you, Mary.
Good night.
Bye-bye.
It's not where
I pictured you.
I needed a place in a hurry.
It's not so bad.
The apartments are really big.
Thanks for tonight.
You're welcome.
Good night.
[¶ ¶]
[STEVEN]: Whose jacket?
How did you get in here?
How many times I told you?
Can't go leaving the back door open.
Lucky it was me.
Could've been anyone.
I'm calling the police.
Go ahead.
If you wanna make me angry.
Neither one of us wants that.
All these lawyers.
We haven't had a chance to talk.
You can't be here.
Not within 500 feet of me.
Five hundred feet.
[GASPS]
[CHUCKLES]
Come on.
It's kinda ridiculous, isn't it?
What do you want?
I miss you, Mary.
I mean, the way we were,
the fun we used to have.
Remember? So I just said,
"Screw the judges. Screw the lawyers.
They don't know us".
I just came to talk.
The way we used to.
Remember?
[DOORBELL BUZZING]
Don't answer it.
[JOHN]:
Mary.
I forgot my jacket.
I didn't mean to intrude.
Excuse my manners.
- John Guidi.
- Hey, Steven. Nice to meet you.
Um, excuse me.
You wanna tell your friend
you're busy?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you busy?
Not really.
I'll be in touch.
You need to get
the air conditioning fixed.
Tell that to my building manager.
I could take a look at it
some time if you want.
Thanks.
You should call the police. I mean you do
have a restraining order on the guy.
It wouldn't make a difference.
Only makes him mad.
Mary, listen, I can...
I can handle it.
Thanks.
I'll check that lock.
That should do it.
Gonna be okay?
I'll be fine.
All right.
In case you need anything.
Thanks. Again.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[CELL PHONE BUTTONS
BEEPING]
Hello?
- Hi. Is that Luillo?
- [MAN]: Yes.
It's Mary Kee.
I'm calling from apart...
- Hello?
- I'm here.
I'm calling about
the air conditioning.
I can't hear you. Hel...?
Hello?
[LINE RINGING]
- [MAN]: Hello.
- Luillo?
- Yes?
- Hi, it's Mary.
You're calling about...
The air conditioning.
- What's wrong?
- It's been broken since I moved in.
It's something I can fix in...
That long?
- Yeah.
- Okay, I'll be calling.
I'll wait for your call. Thank you.
Bye.
[PHONE RINGING]
I told you to stop calling me.
[WOMAN]:
What happened?
Are you okay?
Hi, Mom.
No, it's not Steven. It's just a crank.
[¶ ¶]
No trouble?
No, she's sweet, a really nice girl.
She's a little bit down today.
Hey.
Your buddy John?
Great job fixing my lawn mower.
[JOHN]:
It's just a couple wires.
I'll tell you, he handled that
engine like a nervous lover.
It was really just...
A feather touch.
Hey, can I offer
you guys a soda?
Um, I gotta go.
So soon?
It was...
I really just came by to make sure
that you were okay.
- Everything's fine.
- Bye.
- Bye, George.
- [GEORGE]: Okay.
I will call you.
We should do something.
Okay.
Feather touch.
You're a wicked man, George.
That I am.
[CHUCKLES]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
[ROSE]:
I know you've been avoiding me.
But that's going to stop now.
I told you...
I saw you and your mommy today
posing for photos
outside the cathedral.
When I call,
you're going to answer.
I wanna keep you safe, Mary,
you and your beautiful mother.
[LINE CLICKS]
[¶ ¶]
Shit.
[YELLS]
[¶ ¶]
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Who won the World Series in '79?
Pirates beat the Baltimore Orioles.
Pirates were down
a three-game-to-one deficit.
They won it in seven games, yeah.
- Is that right?
- Yeah, look it up.
Clemente would've been
proud of that.
And that same year,
the year the Pirates beat the Orioles,
who lived in my apartment?
What is this about?
You said you can't remember
what you had for breakfast.
I think you remember just fine.
Rose. Rose Lazar.
You knew her.
She said, "Good morning".
You know, things like that, yeah.
And?
You know, she was the sad type.
She had a boyfriend
who worked over at the Army base.
They were together for a while.
From time to time,
they'd be fighting.
Come home around midnight,
they'd be hollering
and banging doors.
One day, the guy just disappeared.
That's when she moved in.
What happened to her?
Killed herself.
Here?
She wrapped the phone cord around her neck,
hung herself from the ceiling.
[MARY]:
Do you know why she did it?
[GEORGE]:
Like I said, she...
she was the sad type.
[¶ ¶]
[WOMAN]:
Are you sure she's dead?
That's what I was told,
but there's no death certificate.
Sorry, I can't help you.
[JOHN]:
It's Steven. It has to be.
[MARY]: How? How would he build a wall
without my noticing? A wall.
And how would he know
about Rose?
He set it up.
He must have done it.
I can't believe
I'm telling you this.
You're talking to a Trekkie.
I can handle it.
All right.
Let's say that you're right.
You talked to this woman
a few weeks ago
and then she put something
in your pantry.
- A body.
But according to
your time-jump theory,
she doesn't do it a few weeks ago,
she does it in 1979.
When you moved in, the pantry
would already be bricked up.
- But it wasn't.
- Exactly, so it doesn't work.
Unless you're remembering
the past as it was
before it changed.
This is time
like a river.
And this is something
that happens.
An event.
Which affects the way the river flows.
Right.
So if you follow this path,
he ends up leaving
and she hangs herself.
What if something
interferes with that?
She makes a new friend, say.
[PHONE RINGS]
- Hello.
- [ROSE]: Is Bobby there?
We get a whole different path.
The boyfriend ends up dead
and you lose your pantry.
Right, but why...?
- why did you remember the pantry?
- Right.
You remember it
because you caused it to change.
And somehow it leaves a trace,
like a pencil drawing a line, so...
You erase it...
and you draw another line.
But you can still see
where the first one was.
But only you.
Only the person that erased it.
- You really think that's it?
- Honestly, no.
I think we pull down that wall,
there's some sick surprise from Steven
and he's fucking with you.
I'm not touching that wall.
What? You're just gonna
leave it there?
Really? Come on, really?
You're gonna go to bed wondering
if there is a corpse in your kitchen?
I'm not touching it.
[HORN PLAYING
AND DRUMS BEATING]
[PEOPLE CHANTING]
[¶ ¶]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
Can we get the bear?
No, I don't want the hat.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
[MARY]:
I still can't believe you lost my hat.
I loved that hat.
[DOORBELL BUZZING]
Stay there.
[¶ ¶]
John, is that you?
Hey, buddy.
[METAL CLATTERING]
[¶ ¶]
Hello?
Who's there?
[MAN ON TV]: Which fictional family
lives at 742 Evergreen Terrace?
[WOMAN]:
Repeat the question, please.
[MAN]:
742 Evergreen Terrace.
Which fictional family lives
at that address?
[STEVEN]:
Simpsons.
[WOMAN]:
I'm gonna pass.
[MAN]: You were right to pass.
The correct answer is the Simpsons.
Question six.
Worcestershire sauce contains two
of the following ingredients.
Which ingredient
does it not contain?
Molasses, anchovies, mustard.
- Mustard.
- [WOMAN]: Mustard?
[MAN]:
Is the correct answer.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING ON TV]
[PHONE RINGING]
ROSE:
Did I wake you?
You're not gonna hang up
on me now, are you?
Oh, come on.
You're not gonna talk to me?
We're friends, aren't we?
Don't want anything to happen
to that charming mother of yours.
You out late last night?
What's his name?
John.
John what?
John Guidi.
Guidi.
Sure, his parents run the little diner
on San Francisco.
I saw you yesterday.
What?
In a nursing home.
I don't understand.
I found you through
social services.
Is something wrong with me?
Am I sick?
Not physically.
A little thin, maybe.
You don't eat.
Mentally, though...
Tell me.
What do you think?
All that anger, all that rage.
You didn't think it would
affect you?
You're lying.
Think about it, Rose.
Ever wonder why
you don't have any friends?
Why you're stalking someone
you never even met?
You think that's normal?
Shut up.
What about Bobby, all the times
he screwed around on you?
All the times
he walked out on you?
He never walked out on me.
Who told you that?
It doesn't matter.
Who have you been talking to?
Who's been telling tales?
It's not important.
What's important
is that you can change this.
You don't have to end up
in a nuthouse.
You can stop this happening.
You spoke to me?
You don't talk much.
I stayed a little while,
watched some TV, played cards.
Said I'd come visit again today.
I don't play cards, never have.
Well, I guess you learned.
Not well, either.
I beat you every time.
You think this is funny.
You think this is fucking funny?
A sad, pathetic woman in diapers
who can't feed herself?
No, Rose, I don't think it's funny.
But it doesn't have to be this way.
It's your choice.
All right.
That should do it.
[WHIRRING]
That is so good.
Do you know why
they call them daisies?
No.
It's from "day's eye".
Because they open their petals
in the sun.
You know what I call them?
Weeds.
No, you don't.
Sure, I do.
No, you like them.
You think they're pretty.
Is that so?
There you go.
[PHONE RINGING]
[ROSE]: Did you visit me again today?
You said you would.
Just got back.
We play cards?
A little.
How did I look?
A little better.
More color, maybe.
That all? Nothing else about me?
Nothing unusual?
I'm really not sure.
Think real hard.
Okay, Mary.
I'm going to bury something
next to the palm tree
a couple of feet out
towards the apartment.
You go dig it up. You understand?
Dig it up.
[LINE CLICKS]
[¶ ¶]
ROSE:
You lied.
You didn't find me in
a nursing home, did you, Mary?
You didn't find me at all.
Because if you had,
you'd have known what to say:
"Yes, Rose, you did look different.
You looked a whole lot different".
[SCREAMS]
It's not real. It can't be real.
That is fucked.
[AIR CONDITIONER RATTLES
THEN STOPS]
Great.
[PHONE RINGING]
Let me.
No.
Trust me.
Hello?
ROSE:
Who's this?
Name's John. Who's this?
John Guidi, Mary's little friend.
I know your parents, John Guidi.
That's nice.
Put her on.
I think me and you
should talk first.
I said, put her on.
She doesn't wanna speak
to you right now.
Did she find my gift?
Yeah.
I gotta say, I think that's pretty
screwed-up, don't you?
I've got another little surprise.
Tell her I guessed
who the tattletale was.
What?
Tattletale tit
Your tongue shall be split
And every little puppy dog
Shall eat a little bit
You know, Rose, I don't think
you should call here anymore.
This whole thing has gone too far.
Just tell hen
[LINE CLICKS]
Well, that's one seriously nutty lady.
What did she say?
Something about
a tattletale.
Said she guessed who it was.
What?
[¶ ¶]
George. George.
Where's George?
Excuse me?
This is his apartment.
No.
I just saw him this evening.
I made him a daisy chain.
I hope you don't mind me asking,
how long have you been here?
A few months,
since the baby.
And before that?
Do you know who was here before?
Older couple,
Dominican, I think.
Sorry to have disturbed you.
Thank you.
You remember George.
George. You met him.
You made jokes.
You fixed his lawn mower,
for chrissakes.
I never met him, Mary.
[¶ ¶]
You think I'm crazy.
I think we should go inside.
Maybe it would be a good idea
for you not to be here tonight.
I'm not crazy.
You've been under a lot of pressure
with Steven and the phone.
Maybe you could go to your mom's.
You could stay at mine.
This isn't...
It wouldn't...
I'd stay on the couch
and you could get some sleep.
And see how you feel
in the morning.
- Through here.
- Thanks.
Hey, it's okay, Dex.
Keep going.
Maybe you should move out.
- I've only just moved in.
- This woman is crazy.
Whoever she is,
wherever she's calling from,
if you move out, maybe it'll stop.
Maybe that's what she wants.
So now you don't think
it's Steven?
I don't know who it is,
but if it were me,
I would be out of there.
I should go to bed.
Leave this.
There are fresh towels on the bed.
Thanks.
[UNKLE FEATURING GAVIN CLARK'S
"EVERY SINGLE PRAYER" PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[¶ ¶]
[GIRL SCREAMS]
[ROSE]:
Mary!
What's wrong?
What?
Nothing.
Nothing, I'm fine. Go back to sleep.
Morning.
Hey. Hey, Dex.
Coffee?
Yeah,
that sounds great.
Have you decided
what you're gonna do?
Um...
I think I'm gonna
take Dexter for a walk.
And then?
And then I'm gonna go back
to the apartment,
pick up my things
and make the dreaded call
to Mom.
I think that's right.
[¶ ¶]
Hey, Dex. Hey.
You wanna go for a run? Yeah?
Go on.
[¶ ¶]
Let him go, Steven.
Come on, Dex.
Come on, Dexter.
Come on, Dex. Come on.
So are you
sleeping with him now?
That new friend of yours?
Dexter. Come to Mommy, Dexter.
That's a good boy. Come on.
I don't think it's really fair.
He gets to share my dog.
Come on, Dex.
We're leaving.
[STEVEN GRUNTS]
[¶ ¶]
He doesn't get
to share my dog.
You understand?
Hm?
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
- Hello?
- [JOHN]: Hey, I'm finishing at 3.
And you wanna meet up after class?
Yeah.
Meet you out front.
Sounds great.
All right. Okay, bye.
Bye.
[¶ ¶]
[RECORDED VOICE]: The number you have dialed
is not in service.
- I'm looking for John.
- Ah, I'll call him.
[SPEAKING IN ITALIAN]
I'm sorry, Mr. Guidi.
I'm actually looking for John Jr.
I tried his cell-phone,
it doesn't seem to be working.
- John Jr.?
- I was supposed to meet him.
I only wanna talk to him.
You wanna talk to my son?
- I don't understand.
- [MRS. GUIDI]: I'll tell you.
Santa Margarita, south entrance.
That's where I go
when I want to talk to him.
[¶ ¶]
[SOBBING]
WOMAN:
You knew him?
I see his mother
from time to time.
She comes here a lot.
My husband, Charlie,
prick that he was.
You know anything about the boy?
How he died?
They don't know he died.
They were never sure.
They never found him.
[GRUNTING]
[¶ ¶]
[SCREAMS]
[SOBBING AND GRUNTING]
[SOBBING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[ROSE SINGING]: Bobby Shafto went to sea
Silver buckles...
You were supposed to kill yourself.
George found you here
in the kitchen.
You'd started to smell.
This was your fault, Mary. All of it.
He was gonna take you away
from me.
You were gonna let him.
I'm willing to forgive, start over.
You'll never be happy, Rose.
We both know that.
So why put up with it?
A few pills, that's all it would take.
But I am happy.
I have a friend here with me.
GIRL:
Hello?
Who's this?
GIRL:
Mary. Mary Kee.
You're lying.
GIRL: No, I'm not.
Where do you live?
GIRL:
Roosey Roads.
Rose says
you're one of her best friends.
Says I'm one
of her best friends too.
Mary, listen.
You need to go home now.
Understand?
ROSE:
Hello, Mary. Recognize the voice?
You should. It's yours.
What are you doing with her,
you crazy bitch?
We're making dinner, Mary.
Surely you remember.
We're frying chicken.
But we have to be careful, don't we,
because oil is hot.
Oil gets very hot.
We have to be very, very careful,
don't we, Mary?
Yes, please be careful.
What was that?
Please be careful.
You were mean to me, Mary.
You were gonna let that man
take you away from me.
I'm sorry, Rose.
You don't sound sorry.
I really am.
You sound scared,
but you don't sound sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
One more time.
One more time and we'll see
if you sound like you mean it.
I'm really sorry, Rose.
I don't think so.
Please. Please, Rose. Please.
[LIQUID SPLASHES
OVER PHONE]
[YOUNG MARY SCREAMS
No! Stop it, please!
Please, stop, Rose, please!
Stop! Stop!
[GASPING AND YELLING]
No!
[WHIMPERING]
[KETTLE WHISTLING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[¶ ¶]
- Rose?
- [ROSE]: Yes, Mary.
- Are you still mad at me?
- No.
You?
I was.
You see why I did it now,
don't you?
All I ever wanted
was to be your friend.
Don't ever leave me, Mary.
- It's my birthday tomorrow.
- Congratulations.
- What have you got planned?
- Nothing.
I remember it back then.
It was horrible.
[ROSE]:
Yeah?
[MARY]: I had a party
at the bowling alley on the base.
Nobody came.
They were scared of how I looked.
I was so sad and lonely.
Maybe you could come, Rose.
[MARY CHUCKLES]
I'd like that.
It would be just like we were friends.
I'd look after you.
I know that now.
We got there around 3:00.
Maybe a bit after.
I'll be there at 3.
I'll hold a lane for you.
Thank you, Rose.
What are friends for?
[LINE CLICKS]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[¶ ¶]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
WOMAN: Oh, hi, honey.
Hi, Mom.
Yeah, I'll be there soon.
How's Dexter?
Good, okay.
Love you.
Yeah, love you. Bye.
[PHONE RINGING]
Mom, I told you...
ROSE: Hello, Mary.
[¶ ¶]
I missed the bus.
I didn't make it to the bowling alley.
Lucky in a way, though, wasn't it?
- Rose, I didn't...
- [YOUNG MARY]: Hello?
Hello?
Mary, I need you to go home, okay?
Can you do that? As quick as you can.
Just put the phone down,
run as fast as you can.
ROSE:
Not such a bad kid, is she?
What happened, Mary? What made her
turn into such a bitch?
Don't hurt her, Rose.
- Please, don't hurt her.
Like you tried to hurt me?
- Like you tried to kill me?
- Rose, I...
Only she wouldn't understand, would she?
She wouldn't think it was fair.
You'd understand, though,
wouldn't you, Mary?
Please.
Rose?
I best let you go now.
You have things to do.
No, I... I have time.
Not today, Mary.
You have a visitor.
[DOOR CREAKS]
[VOICES WHISPERING
INDISTINCTLY]
[WHISPERING STOPS]
Leave me alone!
[SCREAMS]
[¶ ¶]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
[BANGING]
[BANGING STOPS]
YOUNG MARY:
Hello? Hello?
Mary?
Mary, you have to run, understand?
I don't know what I did
to make her mad.
Is she beside you?
She went to get her pills.
Listen to me. This woman, she's crazy.
It's not your fault. It's nothing you did.
But she's gonna try
to hurt you again.
- I'm scared.
- I know, baby.
But you gotta get outta there, okay?
So you have to run. Go, go now!
- But she locked the door.
- Pull! Pull it harder!
She locked them!
She locked them both!
Mary, you have to run!
[SCREAMING]
[DOORKNOB RATTLING]
[MARY GRUNTING]
[ROSE]:
I waited, Mary.
I waited all this time.
I wanted you to know why
you're going to die.
You shouldn't have tried to kill me.
Mary, are you there?
[YOUNG MARY]:
Hello?
Okay, I want you to grab a knife,
Mary, from the kitchen.
Okay? Grab a really big knife.
Tell me when you have it.
Do you have it?
I can't, she's coming.
[ROSE]: You never
should have lied to me, Mary.
Mary, the wardrobe.
Do you see the wardrobe?
- See the wardrobe in the bedroom?
- I see it.
I want you to smash the mirror,
okay?
I want you to kick it
as hard as you can.
She's coming!
Just do it!
[YOUNG MARY CRYING
OVER PHONE]
[GLASS SHATTERS
Mary? Grab one of the pieces, Mary.
- Grab one of the pieces.
- She's in the room!
- You know what you have to do.
- I can't!
Stick it in her, Mary,
as hard as you can!
- Please, don't make me.
- Do it, Mary!
- Do it now!
- Go away! Leave me alone!
[YOUNG MARY SOBBING
OVER PHONE]
[YOUNG MARY]:
Her eyes are open.
And she's lying on the floor.
Go home, Mary.
Go home.
[¶ ¶]
[DOORBELL BUZZING]
- Hey, sweetheart.
- What do you want?
"Hi, honey.
Tough day at work?"
No, sweetheart, it's fine.
It's all fine.
Oh, hello there. Hello.
- Get outta my house.
- Is there any beer?
I said, get out.
All right,
if you put it that way.
[MARY GROANS]
See what you made me do?
How about that beer?
[YOUNG MARY]:
Please, don't make me.
Last chance, Steven.
Yeah?
Or what?
[¶ ¶]
[MARY SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
[SINGING]
Bobby, Bobby Shafto
He'll come back and marry me
Pretty Bobby Shafto
Bobby Shafto's tall and fair
[¶ ¶]