Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Congressman.
- General.
Herzlich Willkommen in Berlin.
Who is that guy?
It's Breimer. He's a congressman.
- You're here for the peace conference?
- To write about it.
- You ever hear of The New Republic?
- No.
The uniform
is the Army's idea of a joke.
You see any action?
I was in London when Franz Bettmann
aimed his Roman candles...
...about a hundred feet away from me.
Broke all my martini glasses.
Who is Franz Bettmann?
Bettmann, Von Braun.
The Kraut brain trust,
the guys who built the V-2s.
I actually wrote a column about it.
I wish I could write.
I have some great stories I could tell.
No sense beating up on the Germans.
The Russians are the enemy now.
They're godless people. Go down
to the railyard and see for yourself.
Anything's not nailed down, they're
taking it, sending it to Moscow.
Well, why not?
They took most of the bullets.
We've been teaching the Ivans to play
ball. Some of those fellas can really hit.
I bet you can't wait
to go home, huh, soldier?
Yes, sir. You know the Germans.
They make excellent Danish...
...but they can't bake apple pie
like my mom.
Nothing wrong with the Germans.
Plenty of good German folk
back in Schenectady.
Oh, excuse me.
Let me help you with that, sir.
I got it, Tully.
- Being helpful is all.
- You know who's driving me tomorrow?
Got my trip ticket. I'm your driver
for the duration of your stay in Berlin.
And I got you...
...a little housewarming present.
Thanks, Tully.
- See you in the morning. Say, 0800?
-0800.
I wouldn't myself have sized him up that
way, you know? Just meeting the guy...
...you wouldn't think of him as a patsy.
That's what I loved about Berlin:
Even a guy who wasn't a patsy back
home turned into one. It was inevitable.
The city spread its legs.
All that "eat, drink and be merry"
bullshit, "seize the day. "
It sure didn't make anyone smarter.
And the best part of it
was no one got hurt.
There was too much money around
for anybody to fall...
...without a nice soft cushion.
Occupation marks printed just for us.
Funny money.
It didn't feel like losing it
when they lost it.
The Russians, they had to spend it
before they went home.
Which was all anyone talked about:
Going home.
Everyone, even the Russians.
God, who would ever want to?
Say what you want about the war.
I would never wish
for all those millions of people to die...
...but the war was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
When you have money, then,
for the first time in your life...
...you understand it,
what money does for you.
Where before all you understood
was not having it.
Money allows you
to be who you truly are.
So you like your job?
What?
Your job.
Sure.
Yeah?
What are you doing
with that cigarette?
Waste not, want not.
It is a job, right?
How do you like your job?
How do you like working
in the motor pool?
What the hell does that mean?
- Nothing.
- That doesn't even follow.
Perhaps my English.
Like you should be fucking Dwight
Eisenhower, Countess Roundheels?
- I was making conversation.
- No, you weren't.
That's what I was doing.
Don't tell me my business.
Two thousand yards of silk
in the Russian zone.
I get in and out anywhere.
The British zone, the French.
I got the vehicle. The motor pool's
the best job in the fucking Army!
I'm sorry.
I thought you were going to help me
get out of Germany.
It's gonna get harder,
not easier. Watch.
They put your name on a list,
and then that's it.
I forget sometimes
what a boy you are.
Such a boy.
- A sweet little boy.
- No, cut it out.
Does that bother you?
Why should it?
My husband was a boy too.
A little boy
who saw numbers in his head.
I'm your fellow, okay?
I'll get you out of here.
You watch.
My gill,
she's not just a pretty face, no, sir.
She won first prize last year with her
rhubarb pie, and second with her gourds.
- That's terrific, Tully.
- Oh, she's pretty terrific, sir.
Any luck, I'll be home
for the harvest dance.
Well, at this rate
we'll still be driving to Potsdam.
Somebody got up
on the wrong side of the bed.
- Some son of a bitch stole my wallet.
- No kidding.
It must have been
in that crowd at the airport.
I can loan you money if you need it.
Thanks, Tully.
Don't want you to miss
all the great things Berlin has to offer.
I used to live here before the war.
- Really?
- Ran the AP bureau.
They're not really gonna put
the country on trial, are they?
Do you think they shouldn't?
Doesn't seem American
to lock a person up...
...for something they didn't
have anything to do with.
Somebody you know, Tully?
I'm just saying.
Well, there's a piece that would sell:
"Fallen Women of the Third Reich. "
That's pretty raw, sir.
Millions of people didn't disappear
because the elves came out at night.
Your Fräulein knew exactly
what Hitler was doing. They all knew.
- Did she lift a finger?
- You don't know a thing about her.
And you do?
Just because you're a German
doesn't make you a Nazi.
You heard Breimer.
It's on to the Russians.
The next war.
They'll leave your girlfriend alone unless
there's some special reason not to.
It's gonna cost me
to get her out of Germany...
...I can tell you that right now.
I wish I could help you out, kid.
You want an hour with her?
Beautiful day, huh?
Are you looking for an argument?
I'm sorry I broke your tooth.
It was an honest disagreement.
What do you need?
Papers.
To get someone out of Germany.
- A Nazi?
- Not a Nazi. A friend of mine.
With what I've been through, you'd
ask me to help a Nazi escape Germany?
Hey, cry me a river.
Fuck, everyone in this town's
got a hard-luck story.
You gonna help me or not?
I'll see what I can do.
Great. Just don't Jew me on the price.
Lena?
- Where's Emil Brandt?
- Who?
- Emil Brandt.
- Who the fuck is Emil Brandt?
- Where's Emil Brandt?
- Fuck you!
Fuck!
Who's Emil Brandt?
- Emil?
- Who is he?
They were looking for him
in your place, Lena. Where is he?
- He's dead.
- Don't lie to me!
He died.
He died in the war.
Like you fucking know! Who is he?
He was my husband.
Lena?
- Emil Brandt. That's your husband?
- Yes.
I'm Lena Brandt.
- A last name. What a cozy feeling.
- Tully...
He must have done something
if they're hopped up to find him.
I'm gonna find out sooner or later!
He was a mathematician.
He saw numbers in his head?
It's bullshit! They broke my fucking arm!
He was a nobody.
- Somebody's secretary.
- Whose secretary?
What does it matter who?
My husband brought him his coffee
and took steno.
When's the last time you saw him?
Three... Three years ago.
I'm with you now, Tully.
How am I supposed to help you, Lena,
if you won't help me?
I would never hurt you, Tully.
Never.
You can get anything
on the black market.
I talked to someone.
A little lop-cock, no legs...
...but he can run down anything.
He can get you on a train out.
That's what you want, right?
They told me he was dead.
One more dead, or not dead.
Who would know?
Poor, fucking stupid Lena.
You don't know fucking nothing,
do you?
Hey, Sikorsky.
What happened to your arm?
Scotch from Scotland. Forty cases.
Good?
They flew it in for Churchill.
Can't afford it.
Hey, who's your comrade?
Don't worry, I'll give you a price.
I got something else for you.
Really? What's that?
Emil Brandt.
Remind me who that is.
You should know.
You've been looking for him.
Have I?
Names, names, so many names.
Maybe I should just turn him over
to the Americans.
Why don't you?
Because when everyone else
pulls up their tents...
...you Ivans will be the only game
in Berlin, and the fact is...
- ... I like it here.
- That's it?
A favor?
Two hundred thousand marks.
It's not like I'm asking for real money.
Have the printing press work overtime.
Plus papers, so I can get my girlfriend
on a train out of here.
The trouble is, Tully...
...I have seen Emil Brandt's
death certificate with my own eyes.
I thought you weren't looking for him.
Now, let me do you a favor.
You remind me of my son, a little bit
of a buffoon, but good-natured.
Get out. Now. Before you get hurt.
Suit yourself.
I just gotta figure out
how to get my girlfriend on that train.
What's your girlfriend's name?
Mrs. Emil Brandt.
Imagine her surprise
when he turned up like that.
And mine too.
Hey, Tully.
I'll take your offer.
Two hundred thousand marks.
A lot to arrange, getting him out
of the American zone. You follow?
Come back in two hours.
I'll advance you half.
And bring Mrs. Brandt.
I'm not going with you
to the Russian zone.
Lena, half up front,
100,000 marks.
Have you checked
the exchange rate lately?
What happens when they find out
you don't have Emil?
What happens is, we're in London
with 10,000 fucking dollars.
You're out, I'm out.
It's a perfect plan.
I won't go to the Russian zone.
I won't.
He just wants to see you. What's the
big deal? He wants to know I have him.
- But you don't have him.
- You're out selling love you don't have.
Hey, fish.
I had to hitch a ride
from the conference. What happened?
Blow.
I hate to pull rank on you,
but you are my fucking driver.
I'm off the clock, sir.
Lena?
I'm off the clock too.
I'll pick you up in the morning.
I'm in the middle of something.
- We know each other.
- I'm in the middle of something.
- What happened to you?
- I need a minute to think, Tully.
You can think on the way.
- Hey, don't push her around like that.
- Fuck you!
Move!
Get in.
Hey!
- Tully, stop.
- Shut up!
Stupid fuck!
They gave me a choice:
London or Berlin.
For me there was no choice.
The minute it came over the wire
that the war in Europe was finally over...
...all I thought of was Lena.
I didn't expect to run into her.
Not that way.
Not my first week in town.
But that was just like Lena.
She always kept me off balance.
Tully wouldn't be a problem,
or not anything I couldn't figure out.
I just had to find her again.
I knew the bartender would help.
Tell a bartender you're looking for
a friend, and you have two friends:
Him, and the girl he steers you to.
- What the hell is she doing with him?
- Who?
- Lena.
- Tully?
He's not a bad sort.
Just a bit of a cunt.
Yesterday he tried
to pimp her to me.
Well, she and her friend Hannelore
come around and cheer up the Gls.
We're all trying to get by.
This whole goddamn country,
she winds up fucking my fucking driver.
Oh, you knew her?
I hired her as a stringer.
Her husband was never home.
There were no kids.
She got tired of rattling around
the house all day.
She was good at it too.
She could get people to do things,
and they didn't know how she did it.
- You were screwing your secretary.
- Stringer.
Sorry.
What the hell does it mean
she's with him, anyway?
She seems to have made
quite an impression on you.
I just didn't expect
I'd find her like this.
I didn't expect I'd find her.
When you say to yourself, "That's
the worst thing I've ever heard"...
...stick around.
That's Berlin. Now it is.
There's always something worse.
- Geismer. G-E-I-S-M-E-R. Geismer.
- Yes, yes, I understand.
I'm sorry, The New Republic
is not credentialed for today's schedule.
- We can't have you without a press card.
- I told you my wallet was stolen.
I have a line of people behind you.
You should speak to General Sikorsky.
He's in charge of security.
Where's Charlie Ross?
I played poker with him in St. Louis.
If I could just talk to Charlie Ross.
Oh, fuck a duck.
General, over here, please.
Welcome.
Wonderful, wonderful.
Congratulations.
General.
General, I'm with the office
of the military governor.
I'll be escorting the captain
back to the American zone.
Were you with Corporal Tully
last night?
I was in a club up till dawn
drinking with the bartender...
...if your girl Friday
had bothered to check.
Checkpoint recorded Jacob Geismer
crossing into the Russian zone...
...just after midnight.
- Fucking Tully.
- What's that?
My wallet was stolen at the airport.
- Did you report it?
- It's not exactly a war crime.
Where did you get those bruises?
I got in a fight with Tully.
- Over...?
- He rode the brake.
Wasn't over a girl, was it?
He was supposed to pick me up.
He didn't show. I got pissy about it.
The Russians want this to go away.
An American serviceman turns up dead
in Potsdam...
...on the eve of the peace conference?
It's pretty damn embarrassing.
Good news for you, frankly.
We want it to go away too.
Well, maybe I should talk directly
to the MG.
He won't wanna bother with this.
He doesn't wanna know
what Tully was doing in Potsdam?
We're doing a hell of a job in Berlin.
Is there a black market? Sure there is.
Are some of our boys involved in it?
Yes, they are.
- If the Russians killed Tully...
- Then he deserved whatever he got.
And his poor family
doesn't need to know anything more...
...than that he crashed his jeep
trying to avoid a bunny rabbit.
We're not gonna start World War lll
over some dumb Gl...
...who got his dick stuck
in a pitchpot.
You stay out of the Russian sector
for the rest of your time here.
Now, we can't protect you over there.
Thanks.
And if you find that girl...
...we'd like to talk to her.
Kids. Two months ago,
they were shooting at us.
If it isn't Jake Geismer.
Who did you insult this time?
- You got a second? I'll tell you.
- Yeah, why don't we catch up?
- How's 1946?
- You mean you're not interested?
I know you, Jake. We're a long way
from South Street.
That's funny. I haven't met a DA yet
that could resist a murder.
Nothing better for a prosecutor
than a criminal with a sense of history.
Everything got written down.
Who they killed and what it cost.
Meticulous record keepers.
...forces from the west are poised
to strike the final blows upon Japan.
This military power is sustained
and inspired by the determination...
...of all the Allied nations
to prosecute the war against Japan...
- ... until she ceases to exist.
- It looks like you're putting...
- ... the whole country on trial.
- These are just the active cases.
The rest are kept under
lock and key at Kransberg.
They want me to decide
who the ardent Nazis were.
Truth is, it was the whole country.
Nobody's hands are clean.
Twenty-hour days
just to get my arms around it.
So, what's the murder
you wanted to tell me about?
What, Gunther?
He used to be a cop here in Berlin.
Don't worry, he doesn't
speak a word of English.
My driver, a kid named Tully,
turned up dead in Potsdam.
Potsdam? Potsdam's closed
for the conference.
Whoever wanted him dead
had access to the delegations.
- That's somebody high up.
- Why haven't I heard about it?
Muller didn't want you to.
He ordered me to leave it alone.
Nobody around here's
acting like the war is over.
Not the Russians. Not the MG.
- What's your angle?
- Why should I have an angle?
It just doesn't sound like you.
You came home, all you talked about
was what a great lay your secretary was.
- Stringer.
- Stringer. Sorry.
A bullet through the chest, in the river.
It's like it never happened.
Isn't that what we fought a war about?
Even a louse like Tully?
Okay.
What?
The Russians will have to do
a police report. Can you get me a copy?
This guy drove one of the gas vans.
They would load the Jews in back,
run the exhaust inside.
By the time they got where they were
going, they were dead. Very efficient.
Driving to work he killed more people
than Al Capone in all his years.
But if you asked him,
he isn't a murderer, he's a truck driver.
And he still thinks that.
Thanks, Bernie. I owe you one.
Thank you, Danny.
I can't be out after curfew.
Would you walk with me?
You live here with someone?
Big man.
You want two girls?
You know a girl named Lena?
Who told you about Lena?
I'm not trying to get something
for nothing.
Aren't you going to offer me
a cigarette?
I didn't see her at the club.
Skinny Lena.
A big Yank in the saddle,
you'd break her in two.
Can I look in your bedroom?
Come. Fuck me, Dutch.
The princess,
who knows where she is?
Lena was raped by the Russians.
You'll get yourself a good dose.
I apologize if I hurt your feelings.
She's not so special.
They raped everyone:
cripples, children.
How did you find this place?
Five hundred just to talk.
That's what I call a real pervert.
Take a couple hours off, would you?
I have nothing to be ashamed of.
- I didn't say you did.
- The war, it's convenient.
We can all blame everything
on the war.
Isn't that why you left?
The war?
I found that blue dress I bought you.
All the old things. All the old times.
This is my life now.
Tully at least understood that.
What was Tully doing
in Potsdam last night?
- I don't know.
- You weren't with him?
Potsdam is in the Russian zone.
I don't go to the Russian zone.
Lena, if I can find you, so can they.
As if I'm the only one
who needed help.
- Look at you.
- What is it you're not telling me?
It couldn't be that I loved him?
You don't need
to be afraid of him anymore.
to protect him anymore.
I think if you hadn't left, Jacob...
...nothing would be any different.
Nothing.
If.
If you want to stay, it's 500 marks.
Make up your mind.
I'm going to sleep.
Did you get the report?
I had to get it from a friend of mine.
Even Muller hasn't seen that yet.
- Interesting reading?
- They found 50,000 marks on him.
So figuring they stole half, 100?
They found a slug lodged
in his backpack,.32 caliber.
Our guns are. 45.
Thanks.
Now, listen,
I'm the first to recognize...
...there were excesses
in the Nazi leadership.
But if we besmirch an entire people
because of a few bad apples...
...we're no better than Hitler.
Then it's not about war crimes at all.
It's about revenge.
Revenge. Right. Got it.
Exactly. Revenge.
I found that in the dirt
where Tully's body washed up.
The little dash that you'll sometimes find
near the serial number? It's not there.
- That's meaningful?
- It means Tully had something to sell.
Something that our side
badly wanted...
...and you very badly
didn't want us to have.
You solved it
the way Russians know how to:
You put a bullet in him. In Potsdam.
Where he thought he'd be safe.
All that from a mark of punctuation.
No dash means that it's American.
You could check it against the money
you stole from him...
...if you felt like it.
I was expecting Tully that night.
Here. Not in Potsdam.
He never showed up.
Instead of the usual Scotch
and cameras, he was selling...
...for the price of 200,000 marks,
a man:::
...named Emil Brandt.
What's so interesting
about Emil Brandt?
The Americans were looking for him.
That made me curious.
We pack up entire factories
and ship them back to Moscow.
Now the peace conference...
...Poland, Romania,
half of Europe, a windfall.
Something for the sacrifice
and suffering.
Now ask yourself:
What do the Americans get?
Sounds to me
like we're getting a good fleecing.
You may not be as safe
on the American side as you think.
Hannelore, Lena.
Even radar couldn't find you here.
Of course, you won't be earning...
...but Jacob here volunteered
to carry you girls on the cuff...
...till things have settled down.
I'll check in on you when I can.
As long as it's on the cuff
and not on my back.
He gives me the creeps.
Fixing your mouth,
with where it's going, sweetheart?
Let's give them a minute.
I don't want you to go out anymore.
It's a good thing I wasn't there,
don't you think?
- I went for a loaf of bread.
- I can bring you anything you need.
Stare at the same four walls.
I'd go mad.
You wanna tell me why Emil would be
worth 100,000 marks to someone?
There'd be no reason.
That's how much money
they found on Tully's body.
That doesn't make any sense.
Might have been nice to know,
Mrs. Brandt...
...that Tully was auctioning off
your husband.
We never talked
about Emil, remember?
One of our rules.
An affair has more rules
than marriage.
The Americans are looking for him,
and the Russians. Why?
- I don't know.
- Where is he, Lena? Where's Emil?
Emil's dead. He died six months ago
in the bombing.
Tully found out the Americans
were looking for Emil...
...so he offered him to the Russians.
One of his schemes. Stupid.
A way to get money to get me
out of Germany. Sell them a dead man.
Now he's dead too. Maybe you next,
if you don't watch yourself.
This isn't gonna go away
because Tully's dead.
- That's all I know.
- Emil was with the SS?
Two years ago they all got uniforms.
- Who knows why?
- Stop lying to me.
I'm a Nazi myself, did you know that?
It's true.
- You're not a Nazi.
- No, not a Nazi. None of us.
Just something to join,
like a sport club.
How could you fuck someone
for all those years and not know them?
- Stop it.
- Did you ever fuck a Nazi?
- Cut it out.
- How about a Jew?
- Why won't you let me help you?
- A Nazi and a Jew both, better yet.
- You did nothing wrong!
- I survived.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org