Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
This spot is beautiful.
Yeah, it really is.
You guys are lucky. I didn't have
a place like this where I grew up.
What are you talking about?
You grew up like half an hourfrom here.
Whatever. My parents
didn't let me out much.
Yeah, well, it was
really amazing for us.
In high school we used to sneak out
and come here all the time.
That's right.
Late-night rendezvous. In fact,
we shared ourfirst bottle
of tequila right here at this very spot.
Wow. I am impressed
that you even rememberthat.
"I am impressed that
you even rememberthat."
So do you guys feel like
you were the same as you were back then?
Well, I know I'm
exactly the same.
I still have absolutely no idea what
I want to do when I grow up.
Well, hey, you used to
work at Foot Locker, and I'm sure
if you went back and asked,
they'd give you the job.
- Very funny.
- What about you, Nick?
- Have you changed much?
- Mmm-mm.
Although I must say,
Trevor has gotten way hotter.
You know that that is a fact,
my friend, okay?
My jaw is way wider now.
It's striking.
All right, loverboy.
How about you and me
go get some wood
forthis fire, huh?
All right,
take care.
I got a really good feeling about
the next couple of months.
Yeah? Why is that?
If we just close a couple
of our own accounts,
you know how huge
that could be for us?
Yeah, I mean, retiring early
would be very nice.
By 30?
Oh, shit.
Look, look.
Gross, dude.
Come here. What, you
afraid of a little crab?
Gross, dude!
Those things are just sick! Don't!
- Come on. Come on.
- No, don't! Dude, don't! Don't!
Fucking pussy.
This is so exciting!
Yeah. Maybe I should
wait till tomorrow.
No, you have to
tell him tonight.
Hey. Took you guys
long enough.
What are you
talking about?
There it goes.
There it goes. Okay, ready?
Nice. Yeah, I'm ready.
- Happy birthday!
- Oh!
- Oh, they went out. Relight.
- Wait wait.
- All right.
- Okay, now make a wish.
I can't.
Everything's perfect.
- That's lame.
- Oh. Oh, sweetie.
Whatever, dude.
If you need something,
I've got a whole list of things.
- How about a million dollars?
- Blow 'em out, already.
- Let's do this.
- All right, all right!
- Yay!
- No!
- Come on. No. I bought 'em.
- It's my birthday cake.
- I want it in the shot.
- In what shot?
- Good idea, okay.
- Behave.
- Okay, everybody.
- Come on, hurry up, I want a cupcake.
I know, just hold your horses
for a minute, all right?
- Art. It's perfection.
- It's kinda ghetto frosting.
- That's good though.
- That's my favorite.
Yup. Are you ready?
Yes.
- Everybody say "chingas."
- Chingas.
- Good, guys.
Check it out,
ladies and gentlemen.
I brought my own
special kind of birthday candle.
- All right.
- Drugs!
- You kids have fun.
- That is awesome.
- Light it up.
- Come here.
- Hey, where are you going?
- Somewhere.
- Really?
- With you.
- Okay.
- Camera, please.
- Yes, sir.
- Put this on.
- All right.
- This is kind of exciting.
- Oh, I will now be blindfolding you.
- Really?
- Are you going to take advantage of me?
- Mm, I might.
- All right, hold this.
- Okay.
- And...
- Oh!
- We shall return.
- See you later.
Don't worry
about me.
- Open.
- Oh.
Rememberthe first time
we came here?
Yeah. What was that,
like three years ago?
Yeah.
Nick, um,
there's something
that I want to
tell you.
Me first.
Happy birthday.
Nick! Oh!
- It's beautiful.
- Wish it was a diamond, but...
Well, I love it.
I love you.
Here, put it on.
So, tell me again I'm not crazy and I
shouldn't go get my master's.
Oh, no, you should.
You should go pay some
art-school lifer
to grade your pictures.
I don't have to pay them.
I can use my grant money.
You get the point.
And more importantly, it's in New York,
which is 3,000 miles away from me.
I know.
My job is about to blow up.
I promise you.
I'm gonna have the money so we can
open your own gallery.
You can shoot
your own pictures,
just like we
talked about.
- Isn't that what you want?
- Of course.
This is perfect.
- Hey, don't get that, okay?
- Hey. Oh, where is it?
Remember, I wanted to
tell you something.
I know.
Just give me one second.
It's work.
Hold on.
Hello?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Right. No no no, it's not...
it's not a problem.
All right.
Bye-bye.
It was Bristol.
I have to go to work.
Yeah, and it's my birthday,
so call him back,
tell him you're sick.
You just can't go.
Listen.
If you do this for me,
we will come back
here next year,
and we will stay
the whole weekend,
and we'll get
a hotel room, and...
Baby?
Help me out here. I really need to go
to this meeting.
No, forget it.
I want a week.
- Aweek?
- That's right.
You and me
and no cell phones.
You can personally
smash this thing
before we leave.
How's that?
Okay.
Actually, you know what?
Why wait? I say...
we just drown this thing now
to make sure.
Oh! Oh! Oh, that's...
I don't think so.
Give us something
to talk about
Take yourtime...
Aw, shit. Baby, did you remember
my sunglasses?
Mm? What would you
do without me?
Yo, this is stupid!
Bristol's a dick.
Yeah, a dick who's gonna
get promoted instead of me
if I flake on this meeting.
- So he gets to ruin our Sundays then?
- And Julie's birthday.
If I want to beat 'em,
I have to join 'em.
- Right now!
- Don't.
Whatever, man. I'm telling you you
just should blow the whole thing off.
Yeah, you know, you're right.
I don't need this job anyway.
Great idea. And when you get fired
I'm sure Trevor will last
about two weeks
at work without you.
Why do you
have to say that?
Wait, guys.
Hold up, hold up.
Okay.
Nice.
You know what, baby?
You can move to New York with me,
and we could be
starving artists together.
Wouldn't that be perfect, hon?
Sounds like you
have it all worked out.
Shit!
Hold on!
Oh God!
- Is everyone all right?
- You okay? You okay?
- I think so.
- Are you sure?
- Oh! Oh God!
- Oh, shit!
Nick, move! Ah!
Nick.
Oh, Nick.
Shh.
Shh. Shh.
Nick, it's okay.
Room 9, we've got a code blue.
He's gone into attack.
190 and rising.
Shh, Nick.
Shh.
Nick...
It's okay.
He gets nightmares
sometimes.
He always has.
Nick.
Oh, Nick!
Where's Julie?
Honey, she's...
- Where are they?
- They didn't...
- No. No.
- Nick...
Okay, everybody.
- Just hold your horses for a minute.
- Hurry up, hurry up.
- Yay! Come on!
- No!
You know what? I cannot imagine
my life without you now.
You know, I was thinking...
if you, um...
if you really need a change
of scenery or whatever,
I've got some extra
room at my place.
For what?
You.
I want you
to live with me.
Nick, it's Mom.
How you feeling?
I spoke to the doctor.
He said you canceled
your appointment again.
Nick, you've got to
take care of yourself.
You don't want the headaches
to get any worse.
Please, call me.
- Hey, man.
- What's up?
- Thought you were out sick.
- No.
Bristol's looking foryou.
Just a heads up.
Thanks, man.
- You don't pick up your phone?
- Oh, I was in the copy room.
I need those spreadsheets.
Yeah, I put 'em on your desk
last night.
I was here until 7:00.
Afterthat.
Did you check your inbox?
Look, I'm telling you
I can't find 'em, so just...
print me up a new report,
spare me the boring fairy tale.
We've got the Rosemont
Equities meeting, one hour.
Wait. What are you
talking about?
11:00,
sales presentation...
- I thought that was at 4:00.
- I had to move it, okay?
And you're just
telling me this now?
Look, Nick,
80% of all start-ups fail in the first
two years. It is an uphill battle.
Everyone's got to pull
their own weight. No exceptions.
Okay. No problem.
I'll have the spreadsheets.
I can give the pitch myself if you think
you can't handle it.
I said no problem.
Okay.
You keep
your shit together.
Okay? I can't have you pop another
brain fart and fuck this thing up.
Clean up your desk.
It's a mess.
What we're talking about is software
that will enable your handheld
to communicate with
any wireless technology.
Imagine being able to access
all of yourtechnology from here.
Picture it. Say you're in a cab
on your way to a meeting.
You're checking your e-mails,
you're surfing the web, a call comes in.
Well, your new client decides
that they need additional product images
to be included in the presentation
that you're giving in an hour.
You rush over
to the job site
snap a couple of jpegs,
get to your meeting.
And gentlemen,
what you've got
is a slideshow
in your pocket.
Okay, so...
everyone's developing
next-gen software for handhelds,
including the big guys.
Why put money into yours?
Because ours
is ready now.
We, with our partners
at Strike Line, believe
we can have this on the market
within the quarter.
- Nick.
- Is he having a seizure or what?
No, he gets headaches.
Nick! Nick!
I'm so sorry.
I swear, if I get
one more S.E.C. Notice,
I'm gonna burn the whole stack and move
this thing to the Caymans.
Yeah, the weather's
nice there.
I'm... sorry about
the meeting, sir.
Nick, I shouldn't
have to tell you...
80% of all start-ups fail
within the first two years.
We make one mistake,
it affects everything.
We can't go back
and do this over again.
You're absolutely
right.
I assure you this will
not happen again.
Dave tells me you've been
having some problems lately
with concentrating
and remembering stuff.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Really, it's...
it's not a big deal.
I want you to just go home,
take the rest of the week off
and recharge the batteries.
- Mr. Callahan, really, I can work.
- Nick...
I need to work.
It's done.
Just go home.
We'll see you in a week.
Always searching
Looking forthe one
to wrap your soul
Around
Sing the one name
as you let go
The fear of flying
You're on your way
Endless love
And you say
You're gonna turn
time around...
Oh, man.
Oh, shit. Baby, did you
grab my sunglasses?
Mm? What would you
do without me?
Hmm?
Yo, this is stupid!
Bristol's a dick.
Yeah, a dick
who'll get promoted
instead of me if I flake
on this meeting.
- So he gets to ruin our Sundays?
- And Julie's birthday.
Whatever, man. I'm telling you you
should just blow the whole thing off.
You're right.
I don't really need this job anyway.
Yeah.
Great idea.
I'm sure when you get fired,
Trevor will last
- two weeks at work without you, maybe.
- "Two weeks at work without you."
- Why you got to say that?
- What?
Ooh, guys, wait.
I want to get a picture of this.
Nice. And you
know what, honey?
You can move to New York with me
and we can be starving artists together.
- Isn't that a perfect idea?
- Put your seat belt on.
- What?
- Put it on!
Okay. Shit.
I think so.
Hey, pumpkin. Hey, do you know
what you're gonna wear?
What's happening?
Are you okay?
Nick?
Oh, Nick,
are you okay?
What's wrong, huh?
Huh?
What's the matter?
I think I was
having a nightmare.
Oh, baby!
It's okay.
All right?
It's all over now. It's all over.
Oh, shh.
Oh, God!
Okay?
Now let's get going.
We'll celebrate my birthday.
It'll be fun.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna go get ready. All right.
Okay.
I know how weird it sounds.
It's just...
I can't explain it.
I...
there's this entire
other version
of my life
without you.
I went through
a whole year
believing you were dead.
And then ljust...
ljust wake up, and there you are.
Okay, it was just
a bad dream, all right?
It wasn't real.
I'm here.
Come on.
I hearyou, I do,
but it's just I'm having
a really difficult time believing it.
It's been
a traumatic year
for both of us, okay?
- But we made it.
- It's not that.
Hey.
I am here.
And that's all
that matters.
All right.
- You're right.
- I know.
Oh, fuck.
You're right.
Hi.
Sorry we're late.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- Happy 25th, old lady.
- Oh!
How's it going, man?
Good.
It is really
frickin' good!
Oh, it's good to
see you, man!
Yeah, it's good.
Good.
You two,
you look amazing!
Oh, how much has
he had to drink?
Well, it's been
a long night.
Speaking of which,
why don't, uh...
- Yes, let's.
...you and I do the...
- Right.
- Okay.
...and you two...
good. All right.
Hey, how's it goin', man?
Two MGDs,
Jack on the rocks
and a house red, please.
Please tell me that you
locked down the strippers.
The strippers?
For my bachelor party.
Your bachelor party?
Because... you two
are getting married,
and I'm...
the best man.
Which means I would have
locked down the strippers.
Of course I did,
dumb-ass!
- You're scaring me, man.
- Dude, I got the...
10 hottest
strippers ever.
10?
Awesome! Thanks.
Thank you.
I am...
I am so psyched
foryou guys!
Oh. Okay.
Do you still think
you're dreaming?
Baby, what's wrong?
Nothing.
- I love you.
- Oh god.
- All right, baby.
"Migraines have been linked
to seizures in recent studies.
Patients with a high frequency
of migraine attacks
are at greater risk
for cerebral strokes.
This progressive brain disease
can lead to
acute and selected
memory loss.
Behavior changes might
include the following...
delusions, hallucinations, hearing
things that are not actually present..."
"Schizophrenia refers to
a split between emotion and thought."
"Studies have shown the disease
to be genetically linked,
which in its end stages
can result in suicide."
Hey!
How ya feelin'?
Oh, busted.
Looking at porn. Again.
- Yeah.
- By the way,
you were really
fucked up last night, man.
Yeah, I had
a couple of drinks.
- Yeah, a couple.
- Um...
What?
Hey, guys. Bristol just called
a staff meeting.
Conference room, five minutes.
Oh, God. What does
that prick want now?
I don't know, but he wants to see you
in his office beforehand.
What?
Oh. Oh, guys?
I think I can already
feel his foot up my ass.
All right, people,
let's get right to it.
You've all heard me warn you
about the problems
of the average start-up company.
Well, it seems that we've been on
the losing end this week.
I had five deals
fall through,
including R.S.B.
Financial.
That's...
That's Trevor's account.
He said it was a sure thing.
Well,
he was wrong.
And unfortunately,
Mr. Callahan felt
like he had to send
a message on this one.
We've had to let
Trevor go.
So I suggest that we all
get back to work, hmm?
Doesn't that seem
a little harsh?
Yes.
- So what actually happened?
- Excuse me?
Well, if Trevorthought
it was a sure thing,
why'd the deal fall apart?
Come on, Bristol.
You had Trevor's job once,
and you know
how hard it is.
Yeah, and I worked my ass off,
I didn't make mistakes
and I got rewarded.
Why? 'Cause
the Strike Line deal
fell on your lap?
You were supposed to close
the R.S.B. Deal, not Trevor.
And you think you know
something we don't?
What I know
is Mr. Callahan pays me
to be the judge of you people,
and right now my judgment is telling me
that you'd much rather be
at home watching "Oprah"
with yourfriend
than working
on this team any longer.
Congratulations, Nick.
You're fired too.
Anyone else?
I love you, man,
but this was not your problem.
Fuck that.
If it wasn't for us, Bristol wouldn't
have been promoted in the first place.
I'm not taking
orders from him.
Nick, you worked your ass
off at this place.
You put your blood
into this place, man.
Yeah, I put my blood into this place,
and Bristol's the one who gets promoted.
Nick, that's business.
You taught me that.
Now, look.
Go tell Bristol you're sorry.
Tell him you're still having
side effects from the accident.
Only side effect I'm having is knowing
life is way too short forthis.
What is this,
a guy thing?
Trevor gets canned, so you just jump off
the bridge with him?
Look, I was never gonna move up with
Bristol as my supervisor anyway.
Ever since the guy got promoted,
he's just been looking
for an excuse to fire me.
- Well, you didn't have to give him one.
- You know what? The truth is,
he's the weak link.
He's ruined the whole company,
and everybody knows it.
And you know what?
I am better off
just getting out from under him.
No, Nick.
You're better off with a job.
I told you,
I'll find another one.
A better one.
We'll all be okay.
You also told me to stay here and not go
to New York, because that would be okay.
I'm sorry,
and ljust can't
forget what we lost in that accident.
Hon?
Hey.
Hey, it will be.
It just takes time.
Nick, it's been a year.
I spend my days cataloguing other
people's photo shoots for minimum wage.
I have half a portfolio
and no time to finish it, and now...
Well, now I have to get
another job so that we can pay our rent.
Excuse me.
Hey. Hey.
Hey.
It's about the big picture.
I finally see it now.
All that other stuff
is just... just stuff.
Look, the only thing
that is important
is that we have
each other.
That's all that counts.
Always the salesman,
aren't you?
Mm. Maybe I'll be
a technical copyeditor.
Is that Bristol?
Jerk.
Come on.
Nick?
Nick.
- Perfect shot.
- Ah! Great.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Isn't that great?
- You look so good.
Nice.
So, what do you think?
- Hmm?
- The ring, honey. Isn't it beautiful?
Can you believe
I picked that thing out myself?
- It's fantastic.
- Ooh.
Yeah.
Sure, it's beautiful.
We're thinking
next October.
Oh, how many people
are you gonna invite?
You know, maybe 50.
Just the important ones.
- Mmm.
- Ah. Right.
- Dave Bristol.
- What?
From your office?
Yeah, right. Like I'd
invite that tool.
Looks like I'm out.
Anyone else need more?
Oh, no, honey.
Bristol,
merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
Oh, come on, Nick!
- What are you doing?
- Bristol, I'm sorry, man.
What a klutz.
Can l...
Nice.
That's really nice.
Oh, man.
Oh, that's embarrassing,
so embarrassing.
No way.
Hey, Nick.
I know you need
those spreadsheets.
I'm just waiting on some numbers
from the clients.
Holy shit.
I'm the vice president.
Uh, yeah, of course.
I'm not trying to make excuses.
I pulled the Strike Line
deal, not you.
I'm sorry.
I'm just not following this.
Where's Trevor?
At some off-site client meeting.
He said you knew about it.
Oh, yeah, right.
Thanks.
Oh, and Bristol, clean up that desk.
It's a mess.
I swear, if I get
one more S.E.C. Notice,
I am gonna burn the whole stack and move
this thing to the Caymans.
Well, I hear
the weather's nice there.
Yeah, I guess.
So how you feelin'?
Oh, betterthan ever.
Listen, I'm having dinner
with a potential investor.
He's a big one.
We need him.
You know what they say
about start-ups.
I want you riding shotgun.
I wouldn't miss it
forthe world, Mr. Callahan.
"Mr. Callahan."
That's cute.
The weather burns in you
I can't predict the rain
The silence falls...
"Pacific Avenue."
You've reached Julie Miller
Photography.
I can't take your call,
so please leave a message,
including your phone number
and the date you'd like to book.
Thank you.
Well, hello there,
Julie Miller Photography.
It's Nick Larson calling,
and the date I would like to book is for
tonight after my client meeting,
which hopefully won't
last too long.
So why don't you
give me a call back
and let me know if that works
foryour schedule?
Unless of course I see you at home
first. All right. I love you, babe.
Honey, I'm home!
No.
What?
Hey, Nick, it's Mom.
I hope you're okay.
I'd say so.
Call me. I haven't seen you for weeks.
I know you're busy,
but let me know
how you are.
Atoast... to
successful partnerships.
- Salud.
Your daughter is
charming and beautiful.
Thank you.
Mm. And what
about you, Nick?
Do you have
family here?
Uh, just my mom.
Yeah.
My, uh... my father moved away
when I was a kid.
Ah. I am very sorry
to hearthat.
Well, it seems that
you turned out all right.
You have certainly made
an impression on your boss.
Oh, well...
Nick's had a bit of
a magic touch lately.
Well, ljust try to keep
things simple, you know?
Know what you want
and try to make that happen.
And if that doesn't work out,
you steal the file
from the guy sitting next to you
and hope that one's a winner.
All right, Nick.
Well, let's get serious for a minute
and tell Mr. Fuentes
about the new numbers.
Now? Oh, we're having
such a good time.
The new numbers,
Nick.
We're about to ask
Mr. Fuentes for a large amount of money.
You have to dazzle
the wallet out of his pocket
and make it dance
on the table.
No, really, Ron, you take the glory.
This is your baby.
The numbers, Nick.
Well, what we're, uh...
we're really talking about
is, uh...
the next generation of
hand-held operating systems.
Our software capitalizes
on optical internet protocol,
using light-wave
architectures for processing
so that it will send and receive data
over multiple wavelengths.
Our system can be commercialized
within six months,
and with a working beta product
and your company's backing,
we can expect to sign one,
maybe two of the incumbents.
Then we'll minimize
ourfront-end expenditures
by outsourcing to
a flex manufacturer in China.
If we're right,
our product margins will add
500 basis points to your company's
gross margins within 12 months.
Bottom line, if we achieve one-third
of the unit sales forecasted,
we'll double your
company's cash flow.
All right.
Hey.
How's it going?
I'm about to pull out
my hair, I'm so bored.
Yeah, it's, uh...
sorry for all
the technobabble.
Actually, you know,
that's the part that got me hot.
Grace?
Oh Jesus.
What are you doing?
Baby, it's been
a week.
What, you want me
to beg for it?
Whoa. Hey. Hey hey hey.
We're in a restaurant.
When has that ever
stopped you before?
Oh fuck.
Hold up.
Your dad's right outside.
I don't care about that,
and neither does he.
Besides, I'll just tell him
to give you another raise.
Oh, Nick!
- I want you, Nick.
- I hearyou.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Oh my God.
What are you doing?
Let's have some fun here.
Smile, baby.
Uh-uh. Hey...
- I'll be in touch.
- You're most welcome.
You did great, Nick.
Thanks for coming.
Yeah, Nick.
Here I am
to let you know
Take it back
and let it slow
Lust away from
all that ends
Try to keep
all amends
Try to keep all amends
Your home
You hardly know it...
- Oh! Jesus!
- Where were you?
I was waiting fortwo hours.
Trevor, settle down, man.
I was at dinner with Callahan.
What? I told you,
we need to talk.
All right.
What's going on?
I've got a problem with
one of my investors.
- Who?
- Malcolm.
- "Malcolm"?
- Are you playing with me?
Malcolm, from the club.
We took his money. You closed the deal.
- Is your head fucked? Come on!
- Malcolm, of course.
Yes. What's up?
What's going on?
The money...
h-he-he... he wants it back.
- All right. How much?
- All of it.
- 250 grand.
- "250 grand"?
- Did he do that to you?
- It was one of his guys, as a reminder.
Just listen.
Listen to me, Nick.
You've got to make
this happen, man, okay?
'Cause I can't mess
around with this guy.
I-I-I can't make him
wait anymore.
Hey, Trevor...
I'll talk to Ron.
I'll take care of it.
It's no big deal.
All right?
- Yeah. Yeah, all right.
- All right, okay.
- I owe you my life, man.
- No no. Dude.
- It's all right.
- All right.
Hey.
You, uh... you talk
to Julie lately?
No. Not in a while.
Why?
I'm having a hard time
tracking her down.
Dude.
You told me last time,
you're done with her, right?
See you later.
Ron.
How's it going, man?
For shit.
Fuentes bailed.
What? You got to
be kidding me.
After last night
I thought we had him.
Yeah, well, fuck him.
His mistake.
Oh, Jesus!
Listen, I hate to
pile on, man, but, um,
it seems we have a problem
with one of our investors.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Guy Trevor brought in back
in July, gave us 250 grand?
Anyway, he says, uh...
he says he wants it back.
- That's it?
- Yeah.
That's pocket change.
Why don't you just go get the checkbook
off my desk and write it yourself?
Ron, thank you so much, man.
I knew you'd understand.
Why don't you write
a few more while you're at it?
I mean, just go down to the corner
and pass 'em out with milk and cookies.
I mean, if you really
want to give some money away.
It's not like that, man.
Nick,
we have contracts
that specify how and when
people get paid back.
I know. I understand.
Look, it is a one-time thing.
I'll make it up to you
on the next deal.
I don't get it. Were you asleep for our
entire conversation yesterday?
Which... which one?
The one where
I told you we're broke.
- What?
- Nick, the money is gone.
No matter how many times
we go over it, it is gone.
We've spent it...
everything we had and more.
- Ron, that's not possible.
- You wouldn't think so,
but somehow we managed
to pull it off.
What about
the Strike Line deal?
Nick, you're
a good salesman.
You've done a lot of
great things for my company.
I'm glad I made you v.P.,
but let's face it...
you blew it on that one.
What are you
talking about?
You approached them
during Christmas.
We weren't ready.
No matter how you look at it, Nick, you
scared them off. That's the truth.
I didn't make
the Strike Line deal.
Hell, you know,
if... if we had just nailed that deal,
we'd actually probably have some
working software right now
instead of this
pile of garbage.
Hey.
- So what's the story?
- Still working on it.
Nick, come on, man.
I'm meeting Malcolm tonight.
Hey. I'm gonna
take care of it.
Okay.
Julie.
Hey, it's, uh...
it's me, Nick, again.
Um...
listen, I know that
there's some stuff between us,
and you're obviously
not calling me back, but...
I'd really like
to talk to you.
Happy belated birthday,
and, uh...
I miss you.
- Hello?
- Nick. Finally.
- Oh, hey, Mom.
- How are you?
Fine, uh, what's up?
I've spoken to yourfather's doctor.
He'd like to see you.
Will you talk to him?
Why? What...
what do you mean?
I'm concerned about you.
I really want to come and see you.
- No no, I'm good, Mom. I'm fine.
- No, I really...
Hey, listen, I got to go, okay?
I'll call you later.
- Nick...
- I love you.
Bye.
Let me see.
Oh, looks good, huh?
Julie.
Hey.
Wow, I...
hardly recognized you,
you look so different.
Uh, thanks,
I think.
No, I mean,
you look beautiful.
Um, I left you a bunch of messages.
Did you get 'em?
Yeah, I got 'em.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I know I...
I got a little carried away.
Ljust really wanted to talk to you.
Well, I'm standing here,
so go ahead.
Um...
What are you doing?
- I'm working.
- At a club?
Yeah, at a club.
I'm shooting a fashion show.
Well, that's cool.
Who hooked that up?
Christopher. He introduced
me to a few people and it just took off.
Wow.
Who's Christopher?
- Hey, baby.
- Hey.
- You call me?
- I did.
- And who's this?
- Oh, uh, Nick.
Old friend.
We're just catching up.
Nick, she's the greatest, isn't she?
She's gonna be a star, aren't you, baby?
Listen, I'm gonna
get another drink.
- Can I get you something?
- Sure.
- Nick?
- No, I'm good.
All right
Julie.
Listen,
I know some stuff
went wrong with us,
but you have to believe me, I never
meant for it to end up like this.
Oh, cut the shit, Nick.
You know what?
You got everything exactly
the way you wanted it,
so don't start caring
about me now.
I am telling you,
whatever I said,
whatever I did, whatever...
happened between us,
just... just wipe it
out of your head.
Don't you get it?
I already have.
You know, and all yourtalk
about your job
and my career,
the future,
that's all it was,
Nick... talk.
And now
I'm my own boss,
and forthe first time
I'm doing exactly what I want to do.
No, you're not.
I know what you want,
and it's not this.
- Things change.
- Not us.
Julie, we can
start over.
Just give me a chance.
- That's her, isn't it?
- Who?
Grace.
Julie, no.
You are the only thing
in this world that matters to me.
I don't know how
I lost sight of that.
I can fix this.
I promise you I will.
Always the salesman,
aren't you?
Hey...
Nick.
Oh, thank God.
See, I told you
he'd show.
I'm really glad
you could make it, Nick.
- Malcolm, I assume.
- Yeah,
- good to meet you face to face finally.
- And you.
This is Wayne.
He owns half the club with me.
Wayne?
Nick.
Good luck.
Have a seat.
All right.
Malcolm, this space
is fantastic.
Thank you very much.
Here we go.
A little black tea
with ginseng
and mango.
We call it
Chinese rocket fuel.
Keeps you sharp,
mind and body.
It seems to be
working foryou.
I know why
you're here.
You want to renegotiate
your contract.
Yes.
Yourfriend made
a lot of promises.
Said he could get me in on the ground
floor, triple my money with some sort of
turbocharged
super-phone software,
and I'm no expert,
but it sounded pretty good.
And it is, Malcolm.
That's all true.
It is an excellent product. I'm sure
your investment will see a great return.
Malcolm, I'm not sure what
it is you're looking for,
but if you look at your contract, you'll
see we're well within ourtimeline.
Okay,
but at some time,
I need to feel like there's some sort
of progress going on.
Okay. Well, how can I
help you feel like that?
See, we're part
of an organization.
There's a chain of command.
It's the way things are done.
Which is why we sign
contracts that specify
how and when people
are paid back.
You're a businessman.
You know how the whole thing works.
Have you ever wished you could look
into the future?
The Chinese believe it's possible just
by looking at a pattern of tea leaves.
So... the question is,
do I see a waterfall
dripping with all the money
you guys are gonna make me?
Or, uh,
do I see a little bonfire
cooking as everything
- I gave you goes up in smoke?
- That's not it, Malcolm.
Well, I'm dying foryou
to prove me otherwise.
I think I can help.
Because of your
relationship with Trevor
and my confidence
in this product,
I've written you
a personal check for 10%.
25 thousand
out of 250?
It's a Band-Aid
until your...
your investment
sees its return.
Band-Aids.
I love Band-Aids.
Now, you see?
I told you,
Nick's on this now,
and he's gonna take care of everything.
Well, it's better
than nothing,
which is all I've gotten
from you so far.
So, maybe it's time we cut out
the middlemen, right?
No!
Get him out.
Nick?
- No!
- What?
Stay in here, okay?
Come on, move, move!
Get out!
Shit!
Get out! Now!
Fuck! Fuck!
Julie?
- Nick?
- No!
No, Julie!
Fuck!
- Oh, Julie! Oh, my God!
- What's happening?
Shh. Shh.
I love you, baby.
I love you.
You're okay, okay?
Here. Don't look.
Here here. Hey, look at me.
Look at me, look at me.
Everything's fine. Okay?
You're okay. Shh.
Breathe.
Come on!
Just breathe.
All right.
Oh, Grace!
Oh, God.
Found something that
would wake you up.
What the fuck?
Relax.
You're enjoying it.
Your shit's on the floor.
You want something
to drink?
Who are you?
Huh?
How did I get here?
You are
so bloody cute.
- Answerthe question.
- Get your hands off of me.
You don't remember me?
We met at the club.
Malcolm and I
are partners.
On everything.
Which means I own half your ass.
I understand you
owe us $250,000.
If you hadda behaved yourself,
I could've persuaded Malcolm
into reducing your bill,
but now you're not going anywhere
until he gets here.
Don't you get it?
I'm sure your girlfriend
and Trevor would agree.
Fuck you.
I really screwed things up, Mom.
I tried so hard
to fix everything, to just...
make things right, and every time I do
I make it so much worse.
I don't even know
who I am anymore.
Don't. You remind me
of yourfather when you talk like that.
- Why?
- You try to control everything.
Mom, I want
to talk to Dad.
No, you can...
you can't, okay?
You don't understand.
It's really important.
- No, you don't understand.
- Mom, you've gotta help me find him.
Nick, he's dead.
He committed suicide.
Why would you
keep that from me?
I don't know.
I didn't want you
to remember him like that.
The point is, Nick, it's you
I'm worried about.
You can't do this alone.
You need to see a doctor.
You don't have to
have the same fate as yourfather.
Nick, you can't
control everything.
You have to let it go.
Another drink, please.
Thanks.
Nick.
What's going on?
Oh my God.
What happened to you?
Did you bring it?
Where is Trevor?
I can't believe that
was only a year ago.
I know
something's wrong.
First, Trevor comes home
with a black eye.
Then he says you have
some meeting together,
but he doesn't
come home at all.
And now you want me
to bring you some old picture?
Nick, I'm really scared.
I know.
You know that
I'd do anything for Trevor, don't you?
I'd do anything
for all you guys.
Yeah.
Come here.
I know you're scared.
I can't explain it...
but I promise you
that Trevor's okay.
Oh, great, guys.
Check it out...
I brought my own special
birthday candle.
- Yes!
- It's drugs!
Oh! My favorite.
Light it!
- Light it.
- Yes yes.
Where are you going?
- Somewhere.
- Oh, really?
With you.
Okay.
I need to talk
to you alone.
Oh.
Put this on,
it might get cold.
Hmm.
Ah. This looks exactly
the same as it did
when you first
brought me here.
I can't believe...
when was that?
- Three years ago.
Wow.
I can't imagine my life
without you now.
Nick, I want
to tell you something.
Me first.
Okay.
You need
to go to New York.
- What?
- I know that it sounds strange,
but trust me,
it's forthe best.
Where is this coming from?
This is your chance
to pursue your art,
to... find out
about yourself,
to not have to worry
about me or us or my job
or all that
other bullshit, just...
- I don't want to be free.
- Listen to me.
This is
your last chance to...
pursue your own path
in life,
one that
I can't fuck up.
Well, I don't want to pursue
my own path. That wasn't the deal.
- Listen.
- We were going to do this together
and we were gonna work it out,
and you promised you would be there.
Just trust me, I know, baby.
I don't think you're getting it.
Julie...
ljust need a little
space myself right now.
I'm sorry.
You're breaking up with me?
- That's it?
- Yeah.
I don't think
there's anything left to be said.
Nick, I'm pregnant.
Trevor.
Where's Julie?
- What happened?
- Yeah, dude, she ran down here,
grabbed your keys
and took off to your car.
No! Oh God!
- All right, here we go.
- Keep going to the point and back.
Hey, man, what are you doing?
That's my car!
Slow down.
Please, slow down.
Oh God.
- Oh, you've got to be kidding.
- Julie!
- God!
- Pull over, Julie, please!
Please, pull over.
I'm sorry!
I love you!
I didn't know!
I'm sorry!
Julie, you have to
pull over!
Pull over!
You don't understand!
Please!
Oh my God.
I love you.
I would do anything
for all you guys.
You know that,
don't you?
Hey, Nick.
You're awake.
Come on, baby,
we've got a big day.
I've got class
in a half-hour.
Ah...
That's right,
Nicky, yeah!
Aw...
Mommy has to go to class
in a half an hour.
That's right. Okay?
I'm gonna drop you off
at Grandma's. Yeah!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org