Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
[Birds Twittering In Distance]
[Harp Plays Slow, Bright Intro]
#I don't want to play in your yard #
#I don't like you anymore #
# You'll be sorry #
# When you see me #
#Sliding down #
#Our cellar door #
# You can't holler #
#Down our rain barrel #
# You can't climb our apple tree #
#I don't want to play #
#In your yard #
#If you can't be good to me ##
[Bicycle Bell Chimes]
[Thuds]
[Man] Somebody forgot
something in the bathroom.
Lenny, you forgot to flush.
I'm eating my cereal.
Don't you see?
I need to use the restroom.
- So flush it.
- I'm not a housekeeper, remember?
I'm a home health-care professional.
Not mine. You're hers.
Go bother her. I'm eating.
Go take care of your business
in the bathroom, Mr. Savage.
You do it.
As you already pointed out,
you are not under my jurisdiction.
I am not paid to take care of your shit.
What the hell are you doing?
Take care of your business in the bathroom,
and I'll give you back your Wheat Chex.
[Birds Twittering]
[Muttering]
Son of a bitch.
[Radio Plays In Other Room]
Are you cleaning up after yourself,
Mr. Savage?
[Radio Continues Playing]
[Door Slams]
[Swing Music Plays]
# Way out on the briny #
- # With the moon big and shiny #
- [Sighs]
- Lenny?
- #Melting your heart #
#Of stone #
#I'd love to get you #
#On a slow boat to China #
I don't hear a flush, Lenny.
#All by myself, alone ##
Leonard?
[Groaning]
[Phone Ringing]
- [Ringing]
- [Bette Davis, Recorded] Fasten your seat belts.
It's going to be a bumpy night.
[Wendy Savage] That was
Bette Davis as Margo Channing...
and this is Wendy Savage as herself.
- Leave me a message after the-
- [Beeps]
[Woman]
Aloha, Wendy.
This is Nancy Lachman, Doris Metzger's
daughter, calling from Honolulu.
I'm calling because- Well, I just got
a very disturbing call from Arizona.
There's been some trouble with your dad.
[Vacuum Cleaner Whirring]
[Wendy]
Dear Selection Committee...
If awarded your prestigious fellowship...
[Vacuum Cleaner Whirring]
... for artistic creation...
I would use the money...
to complete the writing and research...
of my new semi-autobiographical play-
No, wait.
My new...
subversive,
semi-autobiographical play...
about my childhood, entitled...
Wake Me When It's Over.
- Hey, Wen.
- Hi, Matt.
- How's it going? Getting anywhere?
- Just trying to power through.
Oh, yeah. Just do what you can.
Don't kill yourself.
[Wendy]
Inspired by the work ofJean Genet...
the cartoons of Lynda Barry...
and the family dramas
of Eugene O'Neill...
[Whirring]
Wake Me When It's Over
tells the story...
of a brother and sister who...
after being abandoned
by their abusive father...
are forced to fend for themselves...
when their depressive mother
goes out on a date...
from which she never returns.
Thank you for considering my proposal.
Sincerely yours, Wendy Savage.
[Creaking]
[Cooing]
Hello. Hello.
[Cat Mewing]
You have two new messages.
First message:
Ms. Savage, this is Donna
from Dr. Reichman's office.
I'm just calling to let you know...
that your Pap smear results
came back today and it's normal.
Everything's fine,
so there's nothing to worry about.
- If you have any questions
regarding the test, give me-
- [Doorbell Buzzes]
[Hits Switch]
- Hi.
- Is this a bad time? I saw your lights come on.
- No. I'm just-
- You know-
- Oh, okay, then.
- No. I don't want to disturb you if you're-
- No, do, if you can.
Can you?
I got Marley.
[Heavy Breathing]
- Let's move to the bed.
- No, I like it here. Let's do it on the floor.
- No, come on, Larry.
- I need you to feel how hard my cock is.
I don't want to! The floor is gross.
You used to like it on the floor.
When you first moved in, remember?
Yeah, well, not anymore.
It's middle-aged and depressing.
It makes me want to cry.
- Come here, sweetie.
- What's the matter?
- Come here, good girl. There we go.
- [Whimpers]
- What?
- I've got things going on.
- What things?
- Just... things.
Larry, things. It's personal.
I thought this was personal.
Oh, personal... medical.
Okay?
It's cervical.
I had a Pap smear.
Something was irregular.
Then I had to have another Pap smear.
They just called with the results.
And?
And it's-you know,
it's not for sure yet, you know...
but they might have to go in
and take something out...
and test it and make sure it's not,
you know.
God forbid.
- I'm sorry, Wen.
- Mmm.
Annie had that.
What?
A cervical thing-
some kind of procedure.
I went with her to the appointment.
She said it was pretty painless.
A little sore afterwards-
I feel- I don't need to be hearing
about your wife's cervix right now.
- I'm just trying to be comforting.
- Oh, well, it's not.
- Oh.
- It's upsetting.
Okay.
- Sorry.
- God!
[Breathing Heavily]
[Bed Creaking]
[Grunting Softly]
[Softly]
Come here.
Come on!
See you.
[Slurping]
[Phone Ringing]
[Ringing]
[Moans Softly]
Hello.
[Wendy]
Jon, it's me.
Dad is writing on the walls
with his shit.
- He's what?
- He's writing with his shit, Jon-words!
On the bathroom wall, and he's
leaving them there, for this guy...
Eduardo, to find, like messages.
Wendy, what-what the fuck
are you talking about?
- I am talking about Dad.
- Okay.
He is losing his mind, or something.
I got a phone call-
there's something wrong with him.
He's acting out with his shit.
It's all he has left.
And now he's using it
to piss this guy off.
- Uh, what guy?
- Doris's caregiver guy.
- Here, here. Listen.
- [Beeps]
[Nancy]
Aloha, Wendy.
This is Nancy Lachman,
Doris Metzger's daug-
[Fast-forwards Tape]
There's been some trouble
with your dad.
I know you haven't communicated
with your father for quite some time.
He's not the same anymore.
He forgets things, and-
I'm sorry to leave this
on the machine-
but Eduardo found Lenny
this morning...
- handling his, uh, fecal matter.
- Uh, Wendy-
We hired Eduardo to care for
our mother, not your father.
- [Jon] Wendy!
- What?
Turn it off!
- What is your problem?
- It's the middle of the night.
I've got to teach in the morning,
and I'm on a deadline.
He is writing with his shit, Jon!
Our father!
Do not leave me alone with this!
I'm not leaving you alone.
I'm just hanging up.
- We'll talk tomorrow. Okay?
- We don't even know
where the man lives anymore.
You want to know where he lives?
Sun City.
Have you ever heard of that?
In the middle of the desert somewhere.
We're gonna have to
go out there and find him.
We are not gonna have to
Wendy, we are not
in a Sam Shepard play.
We're gonna have to do something.
This is a crisis.
Look, I don't think
this actually qualifies as a crisis.
It's an alarm, okay?
But it's not a crisis, not yet.
- You mean, it's like we're in Orange.
- What?
Yeah. Right, exactly.
But we're in Yellow, okay?
So we should just... be aware...
and be cautious.
And when it hits Red,
then we're in trouble.
Okay?
Your color, right?
Ms. Metzger? Ravishing Red?
Uh, right?
[Speaking Cantonese]
[Cantonese]
See? Good color, right?
Sexy. Okay.
[Cantonese]
- [Clattering]
- Oh, my goodness.
Ms. Metzger?
[Yelling In Cantonese]
[Engines Roaring]
[Jon]
Andy, it's me, Jon.
Good, good.
I'm, uh, still plugging away
on that Brecht book.
Yeah, well, he's a complex man.
And you?
[Wry Laugh] Oh, yeah, I heard
Stanford's playing footsie with you.
That's great. Oh, great.
- Look, I need a favor.
- [Kisses]
Well, it's kind of last minute.
I'm out of town, actually.
Arizona.
Yeah, it's a family thing.
No, nothing serious. It's my father.
No, he's just, uh-
his girlfriend died.
Yeah. And, uh, he's getting pretty old
himself, I guess, like everybody.
Yeah. Well, that's what
I was gonna ask you.
It's my 9:00 a.m. On Monday.
"Oedipal Rage and Beckett,"
of all things.
- I have to stop at baggage claim.
- Hold on. Hold on a second.
- You checked luggage?
We're only here for a day.
- Two days and one night.
Excuse me
if I plan on changing my clothes.
Sorry. Uh, it's my sister.
- I gained some weight.
- I didn't say anything.
Kasia didn't have you pack
a button-down?
- What is this, a goddamn fashion show?
- No.
It's just, when someone dies,
people dress up.
She's moving back to Poland.
- What, you and Kasia broke up?
- Her visa expired.
S-So that's it?
Her visa expires, so- so it's over?
Well, it's either that
or we get married...
and no one's ready for that, okay?
You've been together for over three years.
You're 42 years old-
Wendy, I really don't need romantic advice
from my little sister at the moment.
Let's just take care of the situation
and stay out of each other's shit, okay?
I'm just trying to talk about it.
Well, we're not in therapy right now.
We're in real life.
Oh, here. I almost forgot.
Shoot. We have to sign this.
They didn't have a very big selection.
Is this okay?
"These words, we hope,
may ease your loss.
"Our prayers are with you,
our love, our thoughts.
So this is sent with some-"
[Quietly]
Here.
Don't forget the balloon.
[Doorbell Rings]
You must be Leonard's kids.
Uh-huh.
The hospital's just five minutes away.
And don't worry. It's nothing serious.
He's been feeling kind of faint...
and what with
the toileting incident and all...
the doctor thought a few tests
were in order.
Well, l-I guess-
I guess we should be going then.
- We're really sorry about your mom.
- Oh, thank you.
Uh, Jon, Wendy-
One more thing before you go.
Please sit.
I just want to say...
you know, we love Lenny.
He's been like family to us, but...
he's not really our family-
he's yours.
So...
I hope you'll be able to find
someplace nice for him.
- What do you mean?
- She means a place where he can live.
- Right. He lives here.
- That's correct.
Your father's been living off the charity
of our family for quite some time.
- Bill-
- Why would you say charity, Bill?
Doris asked my father to come live
with her as a boyfriend, not a boarder.
They were a couple.
They were together for over 20 years.
You can't just throw the man
out on the street.
He has a right to live here. Legally speaking,
it's a common law marriage at this point.
Not exactly.
Not in front of the kids, Bill.
[Sighs]
Let's step outside.
[Jon, Muffled] So, was Lenny there
when this was signed?
[Muffled]
Notarized, all legal.
It's called a non-marital agreement.
It's like a prenup without the nup.
It says that even though
they lived together...
they have no legal obligation to each other,
that everything's separate.
And, basically, Dad has no legal right
to any of her property.
Bet you they've already
got the place listed.
Did you notice that there wasn't
one picture of us anywhere?
Are you surprised?
It's like we don't even exist.
[Indistinct Page Over P.A.]
[Man On TV]
... on your toughest stains.
[Woman]
How about this coffee stain on my blouse?
I'll add some things
and make it really messy.
Oxy Clean seeks out stains
and works right before your eyes.
Grass and dirt don't stand a chance
against new Oxy Clean.
It tackles grass, dirt and grease better
than ever. It gets the stains out.
It's safe on all your laundry,
because it's chlorine-free.
Wow!
Add a scoop to every load
and see for yourself.
It's tough on stains, safe on colors.
And Oxy Clean still works great
on carpet and upholstery.
Call now, and you'll receive
a whopping six pound-
- Where the hell have you been?
- Hi, Dad.
- Hi, Dad. How are you?
- How are you?
They had me hog-tied for two days.
We got here as soon as we could.
We came straight from the airport.
It-It's Jon and Wendy.
I know who you are.
The late ones. You're late.
You weren't here,
and this is what they do, see?
- Dad-
- You weren't here, I said! Nobody!
- Jon, go get somebody.
- We weren't here 'cause we live
on the East Coast.
- Remember?
- Yeah?
We haven't seen you in a long time.
We're here to help you.
So do something!
You're the doctor!
I'm gonna go get somebody.
He's not that kind of doctor, Dad.
He-He's a professor.
I thought my boy was a doctor.
Doctor of Philosophy.
PhD. Teaches college.
- [TVPlays Quietly In Background]
- Medicine?
No.
Drama.
- He teaches theater.
- Like Broadway?
No, like... theater of social unrest.
Stuff like that.
He's doing a book on-on Bertolt Brecht.
I'll release him
only if he promises to be good.
We can't have him get out of bed by himself.
Are you going to be good, Mr. Savage?
Are you going to be good, Dad?
You're not good, they won't let you go.
You can't keep pulling on everything.
This is for your own good.
This is your food.
We don't want him
climbing out on his own.
- He's unsteady. He can fall.
- We'll keep an eye on him.
Thank you.
[Doctor]
Vascular dementia or multi-infarct...
usually follow one or more strokes...
but I am not seeing
any sign of a stroke here.
But the disinhibition,
the aggression, masked facies...
with a blank stare that we had talked about
earlier, are all fairly good indicators.
- Is it like Alzheimer's?
- There are a lot of illnesses
that can cause dementia.
I'm not prepared to make
a diagnosis yet, but I think...
his symptoms are much more
characteristic of Parkinson's disease.
So, w-what do we have
to look forward to?
Well, he's not a young man, so cardiac
or respiratory failure may spare him...
from the worst of it, but, uh,
tremors when the limb is at rest...
a shuffling walk, freezing up,
unable to initiate movement...
more and more loss
of motor coordination in general.
[Piano Plays Upbeat Tune]
[Man, Woman]
# You make me feel so young #
# You make me feel
like spring has sprung #
#And every time I see you grin #
#I'm such a happy individual #
# The moment that you speak #
#I want to go play hide and seek #
#I want to go and bounce the moon #
#Just like a toy balloon #
#You and I #
#Are just like a couple of tots #
#Running across the meadow #
#Picking up- ##
Maybe Dad didn't abandon us.
Maybe he just forgot who we were.
- I'm gonna give Brian Deener a call.
- Who's that?
He's a friend of mine,
teaches in the English department.
He just put his mother
in a nursing home near campus.
Could we have some more nuts?
- Nursing home?
- Yeah. What?
- I wasn't thinking about
putting him in a nursing home.
- What were you thinking?
- I don't know, but I wasn't thinking that.
- Where else is he gonna live?
I mean, really, what's the alternative?
You want to-
- You want to change Dad's diapers, wipe his ass?
- He doesn't need diapers.
- What do you think that catheter was?
- He's in the hospital.
# You make me feel-#
But look, even if they did
let Dad stay here...
he'd still have to have somebody take care
of him. We can't afford that.
You heard the nurse.
Dad falls. He's disoriented.
He hasn't fallen once
since we've been here.
Don't make me out to be the evil brother
who's putting away our father against your will.
All right,
we're doing this together, right?
#Two of a kind
for your information #
#We're two of a kind #
[Wendy]
Well, there's places.
- What places?
- Like Aunt Gertie.
That's assisted living. I'm not sure
Dad would get into one of those.
Gertie's pretty independent, remember?
She's also rich.
Okay, so I'm gonna call United...
and try to get the first flight out
first thing tomorrow...
get back and see if I can find
a place that'll take him.
What am I gonna do?
You're gonna stay here and hold down
the fort until I find something.
By myself?
Wendy, this is not the time to regress.
[Playing "Mairzy Doats"]
[Playing Off-key]
[Playing In Tune]
[Jon Talking Quietly In Distance]
I just don't know
if it's something that I can do...
and so I just don't talk.
I don't know how long he'll be gone,
you don't know how long you'll be gone.
And that's just not something
I think I can deal with...
by talking on the phone
every couple weeks.
We can talk more about this
when I get home.
Tomorrow morning.
I'll make sure to call when I get in.
- Okay. Bye.
- [Hangs Up]
[Sniffling]
[Crying Quietly]
[Jon Whispers]
Hey, Wendy? Wen?
I'm going.
That should take care of the hotel.
Thanks.
- Jon?
- Yeah?
You okay?
Yeah, I'm all right.
I'll talk to you later.
Okay.
[Door Squeaks Open And Closed]
- [Upbeat Music Playing]
- Walk up, walk back.
Two step touch.
Tap that left for four.
Grapevine left.
Step touch four times!
[Woman Over Radio]
Now to the Sunday Puzzle from NPRNews.
[Phone Ringing]
And the chance to match wits with fellow
listeners and puzzle master Will Shortz.
[Phone Line Ringing]
- Here it is.
- Oh.
Hello. Hello?
Hello. Who is it?
- Hung up.
- [Man On Radio] Book Expo was the big-
[Woman] So, not only do you have a formal
dining room, if you like to entertain...
but you also have an updated kitchen
with granite countertops...
oak cabinets,
brand-new appliances...
and they all convey to the new owner.
And look at this dramatic view...
of the eighth tee
on the Lake West golf course.
How perfect is this?
You're also only
a five-minute stroll from-
When you purchase a home
in Sun City, you're eligible-
... recreation centers.
We have eight golf courses-
[Pills Rattling]
[Rattling]
Sure. We could try maybe 30 days.
No, they're already pre-approved...
so it's not gonna take any time at all.
- [Door Squeaking Shut]
- Okay, I'll see you about 3:00.
[Birdsong Echoing]
[Phone Rings]
- Hello.
- Hi.
Oh, my God, Jon. You are not-
You are not gonna believe this.
L- I just- I found this stash...
of photographs and stuff
that Dad's kept all these years.
I can't believe it. I am looking at
the funniest picture of you right now.
- Oh, yeah?
- You have braces.
How come you got braces?
I never got braces.
Ever looked at my teeth?
They're still crooked.
Oh, yeah. How come?
'Cause Dad never paid the bills,
and the orthodontist was so pissed off...
he pulled them out of my mouth
before my teeth were fixed.
[Laughs]
So I think I found something.
What?
It's a place with an opening
that can take him right away.
What kind of place?
A-A facility for older people.
In this country,
they call 'em nursing homes.
I thought we were gonna try
assisted living.
They're not gonna take him at
assisted living, Wendy. Let's just be real.
- He's got dementia.
- Well, don't lead with that.
Look, if it's any consolation,
uh, this place...
they don't call it a- a nursing home.
- Well, what do they call it?
- Uh, rehabilitation center.
It's called the Valley View.
That sounds nice.
- Is it?
- It's a nursing home, Wendy.
- Does it smell?
- Yeah, it smells. They all smell.
Look, this place has an empty bed,
they take Medicaid and it's close to my house.
Believe me, once you get inside,
these places are all the same.
- Hello?
- Make sure you have a coat for him
when we get there.
He doesn't have any warm clothes.
- Hi, Dad.
- Hiya.
How ya feelin'?
Not bad.
You don't need these, right?
Not your style.
Look like Grandpa Walton.
Okay, just sign and initial at the X's.
And here are your valuables.
New prescription. Medication.
Thank you.
And let me give you these.
They don't really like us to give these away,
but you might need 'em.
Thanks.
[Latches Clicking]
Excuse me. Sorry.
I'm sorry.
- Hi.
Okay, Dad.
Thank you.
Excuse me. Sorry.
[Flight Attendant Over P.A.]
Can we have your attention?
We'd like to point out our safety features:
To properly fasten your seat belts-
- What are you doing?
- Bathroom.
- What?
- Bathroom!
- O-Okay, we need to, um-
- Now!
No, we need to wait for
the nice attendant to come-
Okay. Sure. All right, all right.
I got- I got it.
All right, all right.
There, there, there. All right?
All right, wait. Wait for me,
wait for me, wait for me. All right.
I'm right here.
Okay?
[Quietly]
Okay.
All right.
What-What is it, Dad?
- What are these?
- They're Dad's. I couldn't
get 'em back on his feet.
They swelled up. I need ten bucks.
- Where is he?
- Inside.
Thank you. Pop the trunk.
- Did you remember the coat?
- Yeah. I can't, uh, leave the car unattended.
I'm sorry.
[Woman On Radio]... the diplomats
were referring to intelligence reports...
that North Korea had loaded booster
rockets onto a launchpad...
and moved fuel tanks to the test site...
in preparation for a possible launch
as early as tomorrow.
[Jet Engines Whooshing]
[Wind Whistling]
[Woman] We don't usually admit
new residents after 5:00...
but I understand
you came a long way.
Isn't that right, Mr. Savage?
- What'd you say?
- You came a long way.
Not too bad.
How about Bingo?
You like Bingo, Mr. Savage?
Every Tuesday and Thursday night.
[Mr. Savage]
Don't like it.
[Meows]
[Chuckles]
That's Winston.
We call him The Mayor.
All right. Here we are.
Have the bathroom and closet there.
You will share that with Mr. Sperry.
These are just the bare essentials,
of course.
But once you move in,
you can fix it up any way you like.
Mr. Sperry, you want to meet
your new neighbor, Mr. Savage?
[Sperry Mumbles]
Hi.
- Hi.
- [Chuckles]
All right. Well, I'll leave you alone to, uh,
look around and get yourselves together.
[Chuckles]
Gonna need you to sign some papers.
- I'll send somebody in to get him ready for bed.
- Okay.
[Male Attendant]
Good evening, sir. I'm Jimmy.
You ready for a good night's sleep? Hmm?
Give me arms up in the air. Up.
Come on.
Like you're under arrest.
Good man.
You ever done time, Mr. Savage?
[Laughs]
It's a good idea not to make too big of a thing
when you leave for the first time.
Just go real casual.
No big good-byes.
We don't wanna get him agitated before
he's had time to settle in to his new home.
- All right.
- Thank you.
Don't worry.
We'll take good care of him.
- Is everything okay, Dad?
- Not bad.
All right then. See ya tomorrow.
Good night, Dad.
Hey.
Don't forget to tip the girl
on the way out.
All right.
- [Sobs Quietly]
- What's the matter?
[Sniffling] He didn't- He didn't
even know where we were taking him.
[Sobbing]
He still doesn't know.
He doesn't know where he is, Wendy.
We are horrible,
horrible, horrible people.
We are horrible!
Horrible!
Just horrible.
Horrible.
Looks like the Unabomber lives here.
Yeah, well, I've been doing
a lot of research for the book.
The couch is actually pretty comfortable.
Great. Where is it?
Those go over here... actually.
It doesn't look like it, I know...
but there's actually
a system to all this.
Okay.
[Stack Thuds]
Jon? What's Zocor?
Is it for depression?
- It's for cholesterol.
- You have high cholesterol?
Yes!
Is this all your nursing home research?
Most of these aren't even open.
Hill Haven. This looks nice.
It's in Vermont. I really wish
you hadn't brought that down.
- Jon.
- What?
- What is it?
- Theatre of the Absurd.
[Chuckles]
[Grunts]
You gonna stop?
Yeah.
[Sighing]
Sorry.
We're doing the right thing, Wen.
We're taking better care of the old man
than he ever did of us.
I know.
Good night.
[Female Announcer] We know this is one
of the toughest decisions of your life.
What to do when the parent
who took care of you...
can no longer take care of themselves?
That's why here, at Greenhill Manor...
we are committed to providing
the highest quality of care...
for your loved ones.
Our board-certified physicians
are dedicated...
to maximizing both the physical...
and emotional well-being
of your elder.
Come celebrate 100 years
of award-winning care.
["Cheek to Cheek"Intro]
#Heaven #
#I'm in heaven #
#And my heart beats so
that I can hardly speak #
[Woman]
And exhale.
#And I seem to find
the happiness I seek #
And breathe it up.
And breathe up wonderful, good energy.
Fill yourself with it.
And let go of everything you don't need.
Ahh.
Good. Reaching for the person
in front of you, stretch... forward.
#I'm in heaven #
Well, his Medicaid
seems to be squared away.
And as far...
as the advance directive-
Hey, I take that.
On your pen, for anxiety.
Not all the time.
Just when I need it.
[Wry Laugh]
Here's the, uh, health care proxy
we talked about...
and the living will material.
We'll need these signed
by both you and your father.
The only thing missing here
is the paperwork regarding...
the funeral arrangements.
We'll need to know your father's
burial or cremation plans.
[Jon] See, if you switch
this little thing here...
you can change the volume...
and turn it off.
- Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
There you go.
H-He's got it. He's got it.
How's that?
- Good level?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Dad, we need to talk
about a couple things.
- But we-we don't want you
to take it in the wrong way.
- Okay.
Yeah, it's just, uh-
it's a couple questions...
that'll make everything easier
in the long run.
- Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
In the event-
In the event
that something should happen-
[Wendy]
Um-
Mm-hmm?
How-
- Dad-
- How do you want us to, um-
Dad, what if you were in a coma?
[Groans]
Jon.
Would you-Would you-Would you want
a breathing machine to keep you alive?
[Scoffs]
What kind of question's that?
It's a question we should know, in case.
In case what?
In case something happens.
Nothing's gonna happen.
Right now. Nothing new.
Right, it's- it's just procedure.
It's something they want
for their records.
- Who?
- [Wendy] The people who run the place.
The Valley View.
What the hell kind of hotel is it?
Dad, it's not a hotel,
it's a nursing home.
Unplug me.
[Exhales]
What?
Pull the plug!
Okay, Dad. So now,
um, once we unplug you-
- I'm dead.
- Right.
- And then, we-
- What?
What do we do with you?
Bury me!
What are you, a bunch of idiots?
You bury me!
[Mutters]
Christ.
- Oh, Jesus!
- Sorry to scare you.
You just gave your sister heart attack.
She didn't expect to find Polish woman
in her brother's home.
- I told you.
- No, you didn't.
- Yes, I did.
L-I'm taking Kas to the airport in the morning.
Early flight, right?
We have to leave at 6:30 at latest.
Okay.
It's back to Krakw for Kasia.
Yeah, Jon told me. I'm sorry.
Your brother won't marry me...
but when I cook him eggs, he cries.
[Laughs]
I should take cab to airport
like self-respecting feminist woman...
but here I am.
See you in morning.
[Sniffles]
[Sniffling]
- How'd it go at the airport?
- It was fine.
Good.
- Was it emotional?
- No, not really.
She loves you.
Yeah, well, there are
practical considerations...
that love has nothing to do with.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Like what?
Do you have any idea how many
Comp Lit critical theory PhDs there are...
running around this country
looking for work?
Even if Kasia and I did get married
and she stayed...
she could end up teaching
at some university...
that's farther away from here
than Poland.
And then we wouldn't be together either.
See what I'm saying?
You're an idiot.
Can we just play the game?
- I got us an interview.
- For what?
For a really nice alternative
to the Valley View.
- But we just got him in there.
- Just hold your judgments until you see it.
It's very beautiful.
It's called Green Hill Manor.
Sounds like an insane asylum.
Aah! Oh!
- [Yelling, Groaning]
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not okay.
- Are you having a heart attack?
No, I'm not having a heart attack!
Wendy, fuck!
- How much do I fill it up?
- [Jon] 18 pounds.
[Chuckles]
What do I do with it?
Just hook it to this.
[Moans]
Okay, further down.
- What, am I gonna pull it?
- No, that's it, that's it, that's it- good.
- [Both Laughing]
- Ow, ow.
- [Laughing]
- What, it's not funny.
[Laughing]
It's not.
- Really, it's not.
- What-
It's not funny.
[Laughing]
- What's it supposed to do?
- It relieves the pressure.
I'm supposed to stay like this
for 30 minutes.
- Oh.
- And-
All right, Wendy. Go get my mail.
Just go get my mail.
[Sighs Loudly]
[Chuckling]
- Stop staring.
- [Laughing]
This is for you.
Larry Mendlessohn.
Who's Larry Mendlessohn?
A friend of mine,
forwarding me my mail.
Is it the married guy?
I'm starving.
Want something to eat?
I thought you were going to stop
seeing that creep.
- How about tuna melts?
- Whatever.
[Timer Bell Clanks]
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Look, I need you to spend
Thanksgiving with Dad.
We're not doing it together?
It's the only time I can get away
for research.
- Well, I have things to do, too.
- Like what?
Like my life, for instance,
in New York City.
Maybe it's time to stop
being so self-involved...
and think about someone else's life
for a change.
Yeah, like you, who can't put his book aside
for a minute while Dad dies.
I've got to get this thing finished, Wendy.
My editor thinks it's a good time for it.
Everyone's really itching for a book
about Bertolt Brecht this holiday season.
Wendy, I'm working.
I'm working.
[Sighs]
I know you are.
L- I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's just-
It's just I got a lot riding on this book.
And-And your life's
much more portable than mine.
What is that supposed to mean?
What, like-like a toilet?
What, like a porta-potty?
No, it's just, you know,
you don't have a job job, I do.
I have obligations.
You're- You're freelance.
Couldn't you just hook up
with a temp agency around here?
Actually, Jon...
I'm being funded right now,
to work on my plays.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org