Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shirley Liner. I am a pupil in
the high school.
This is my babysitter service.
The answer is' No '.
My mother does not drink.
My father has never beaten me.
My uncle steve has never been me
precious parts show.
I have not even an uncle Steve.
The money is nice, and ...
Paid oral sex is no longer
humiliating than flip burgers.
But that's not why I do.
Maybe we should even decline.
S. A. T.
If you go to a university
outside this state wants,
then the S.A.T. 's where you are
to be sure.
The time to complete the test
condition at 3 hours and 45 minutes.
Hey, Brenda
Brenda
I just ignore you ...
You step remains to
look here.
Size, I think they will reach you look.
Do you think he ever Nadine
has tried to suck?
It is not incest as the hair
Stiefbroer.
What? Brenda knows that her sister
a whore.
How many hearts she has broken?
This is your future
If you want to succeed, then studying hard.
Everything you're doing, determines whether
you can go on to university.
For how late Mr.. Beltran?
Have you seen my wiskundeboek?
Maybe in the basement?
Is the case nearly completed?
No, that score was his cousin ...
He is here!
How is it?
What is with you?
Shirley, where do you live again?
-- Southfield.
Oh, that's far, right?
Oh Damn.
If they would write an autobiography,
you know how that would be called?
'Hurry you and wait for me! "
Want you to overcome?
Shirley is here.
Oh, great!
He is angry because he did not
should only continue.
Mom!
Mikey, what you do when there ga
Adam is an emergency?
How do you to the hospital?
Ga yourself with the car driving?
That would not be the first time
OK, but stop wijsneus.
-- Braaf, hear.
I see you tomorrow morning.
Rugged guy? Correct?
Paardenneukers.
The emergency hang on
refrigerate
And the restaurant?
Ok.
Have fun.
-- You, too.
Nice.
-- Okay, here we go.
Ok, good evening
-- Please
I will tell you one thing.
If it continues to go as it goes
Ga I have two restaurants
open next year.
An in the east and
one along the river.
Ensure that the kamelenrijders
not to come here.
Jerry, komaan.
And if we start the company ...
Are we to you for the
Instead of Deputy Director.
That I do not know.
I do not think that I have them
can simply leave.
Jesus, he's just a
broken plate.
We have two children, Jerry
And then? We also have a child.
We have a child. I
you get benefits and such.
Yes, you have a child, we
Two courses to pay
Ok, And then, they can grow up,
to Michigan and death are like Mike.
Shirley.
Ok, I took the idea of the restaurant
rather well, we have to consider.
Deputy Director under Jerry?
-- Yes
Anyway, the day that a Jerry
startup company, ga me to the circus.
You could not ask he,
You could not really leave.
You have the right where you are,
correct?
Correct?
Hey, you see those old locomotives
over there?
Come along to watch the old trains.
Wherever you go ga?
They are just as
broken toys.
The boys are waiting.
-- No, the boys sleep, komaan.
Do you think Mike goes to sleep at 9 o'clock?
You have a computer in his room put.
You know what he's doing?
He is online to buy heroin
It is a joke, it's a joke
-- It is not funny.
I know it's not funny, but
everyone in the program ...
Ok Michael, I do not want to fight.
Why do you not? If you
evil are simply say it.
It is late, let's go
Come on.
Just call me a bastard. It will give you better
do feel it is step 9 ...
Okay, forget it.
Step in, step.
I am a bastard,
Now I feel good.
I tried just spots of
the floor.
It is good, do not worry.
Ga then you have answers?
-- I'm sorry
Have you eaten anything?
-- I have a cut.
I can hear stop.
-- No, it is good
I'm okay
-- You know, I need coffee
Well, I wanted her with hunger
sent home
Why can not the range,
then the smoke it away.
I am within an hour at home?
Ok, day.
Are not you tired?
-- No, I am a nocturnal.
I thought that I would ever outgrow.
-- That to me I thought too.
I think I should get additional pay
because you've polished my kitchen.
What? What is happening?
-- Sometimes I do stupid things.
I do not know why.
-- That I'm too.
It is ... It is stupid.
Well, if it works.
That is good. Do you see that?
You see where I want to go?
No, not really.
And that is bad
-- This is bad, yes?
If there is one thing wrong, then
is there anything wrong around
That is a domino effect,
a kettingractie.
Everything and everyone has his place.
-- Right.
You find me a freak.
-- Oh yes.
No, I make a joke
-- A portion of fries
How did you meet your wife?
-- What?
What?
-- I mean 'Why'?
Ok, I met her just outside
Ann Harbour, there is this bridge ...
... with a river below and
a treinspoor that it runs.
And it's pitch dark.
Oddly, I do not know why I tell you this.
And that's what the young people go
to be high.
And on an evening takes me Jerry.
-- The man was where you out tonight?
And we went just to see how
it was.
Really do.
Anyway, we are there and a small
feestmeid comes at me.
And that appears to Gail.
And she had a massive dose ...
Anyway, while viewing it with headless
to toe.
And then she turns to Jerry and says:
What do you do for me included?
I do not know, you had to be there
-- I wish I was there.
And when?
We will go to her friends and I say to
Jerry: That girl looks like problems.
Crazy how people change.
Do you have a boyfriend?
What? Come on. You're smart, mature,
you are undoubtedly clever.
Want to see something cool?
Ok.
Walk!
I'm sorry.
You know, we can not do this.
We can not do this.
You know what I mean, I have children.
-- Yes
Thanks to the children.
HPV, Herpes, Syphilis, Gonorroe
Gonorroe Closeup
Ladies and Gentlemen, The numbers show
Seeing
The study returns it
Americans want a car.
A beautiful car, which we their
can sell.
A car with clutch, horsepower
By how much horsepower?
An Entire hope, George
Phil Yes, yes Phil, a whole lot of horsepower
Are you Mike?
... female version ...
It is my car
-- I bring him back
You do not even have a driving licence
-- To you that I will destroy him?
Yes.
-- I'm a better driver than you
No, you're not, you have the car
Ally of destroyed.
And you have those of your mother
without gasoline dropped
You are three times failed the
roadworthiness testing.
That is because the instructor
hated me.
No, because you have a bad
drivers are
I can be arrested.
Val death, dikzak
... round and in the vagina.
He tells me that they are just friends
but why he takes her only agree to
the ball and not in a group?
Jesus, Brenda, ask him anyway.
But girls told not to ask
Well, then alone, stay home and pitch
you full of dieetpillen, I've had enough of
Why you trap me?
-- Friends remain okay?
It does not matter how many defensive
or aanvalspunten he has.
No you simply submit it on the table
-- That's it?
Baseballkaarten are a lot easier.
Do you have a brownie?
Er. An ice cream
Ok, what you want, you've
good points, right?
Shirley, hello, you come here?
that is so cute
Sometimes
I was still calling you, I do not like the vague
but can you Thursday babysitting?
I know it's a schoolavond.
Maybe you can use the bathroom polishing?
Grapje,
Thursday is good do you think?
Is it?
Come you vanboven
No, wait, wait
You have a mess of it.
-- 'We'
Ruik you know?
It is challenging the lentelucht
That is my favorite scent.
Excuse me, I must go
It is in order, right?
Yes, yes, thanks
Do you have extra vigilant to the duodenum
not to punch?
If you do not know where the doudenum,
Consult your book.
a perforated duodenum is not
picnic
What? What is happening?
-- Nothing
Yes.
-- No, it was late yesterday
Do you like the small etter
books?
Yes.
-- Have you earned money?
-- How much?
200 Dollar
Jesus, Shirley,
Have you Mr.. Beltran gepijpt?
I can not believe that you do not
've called
I have called you when I get my
menstruation got.
And when I change my virginity
lost to camp I go to your room demolition
Shit, I even when I called my first
lost a tooth.
And this is not a tooth Shirley.
There is something happened between you.
Listen to me, nothing has happened
he has a family, children, a job
I have me worried
to the university
You have a way needed
to the university to pay
You do not know where you are talking about it.
There is one thing which I regret to have
Is not it crazy sorry to have something
that is not gebeud ... according to you anyway
Non-stop, non stop.
For you I've paid ...
it was ...
I mean, it had ... euhm ...
I do not know ... a game could be ...
I do not know what I thought
I thought that you seemed unhappy after
I suppose you had paid.
Well said, idiot.
I do not know
I mean, you've said nothing
Mostly not
That's just how it works
Size, you may say against anyone
That may not
Tell against anyone
No, I'm seriously
Tell even to Tina
-- Tina? Shit? Why do you think?
I do not know, it's your wife
Believe me, there is much I do not what to tell Tina
and that is just as conversely
God knows where she has been
I do not want it ...
Ignorance is beatitude
Why do you think our marriage is running so well?
I do not know. Maybe you by Ga
your mid-life crisis
But you're always been so stupid
You fucks the babysitter and I ga
by my mid-life ...
You have to stand in my shoes to know
what I encounter
My friend asks if you know someone who wants
babysitting ... on him ...
He says he gladly pays
Yes
Yes I know someone
Bring her home
I Ga you eat
I ga her to bring home
What is your favorite subject?
Hey
-- Are we going to hell?
Yep
I knew the
I must go
Doug, every day at home
And, I mean, I know he has friends
with my Stiefbroer
but komaan, Scott is not that cool
and he is always there when I'm watching TV
So I think he sees me.
I'm back
What's that? Is that new?
He is a freak
He wore a cowboy outfit and he
had a moustache
Was he friendly?
I need coffee
-- Melissa?
I was thinking ...
Since I've scheduled
I was thinking that I might
a portion of the money could get
Thus a 40 dollar
That seems to me fair
Yes that's right
20%
Thanks Shirley
Oh my god, this is not great?
Yeah, a lot of fun with all the kots to
to overcome your parents come home
What?
-- It is totally amazing
Shirley, we need to talk with Doug
Ok
Hey
-- Hey
I have a friend for what weed
Interested?
it is amazing
I do not really ...
-- Natural
Erm Shirley, if you later a lift
to house searches, can I bring you
If you have a need
I'm with Melissa came just ...
maybe yes ...
I must kotsen.
What about it?
I've had phone calls from two
of Jerry's friends.
That's great!
-- Great? That is not great!
Jerry could not keep his mouth, we
go to prison
We are minor, a few hours compulsory
guidance and we are there from
Wives, parents, children.
-- Ensure all for themselves
They always believe that their men from them,
their daughters are virgin
and their sons no pijpbommen in the basement
because they go there to death if they believe something else
They are the ones who make it so easy
to get away to come here
They want both Thursday
-- I have Jerry Thursday
That I know
Can you take one of them?
Then there is still without a date
Find someone else to baby-sitting
Jesus, Melissa
-- You know what the pimps say:
I have no whore of it
She was already a whore.
That's great, where did you hear that?
Wait, I get more beer
And then ... Who's the whore?
Oh yes, that's clever
No, no, they would never ...
-- They do not.
But let her take that decision
For once in her life. Let her
a decision on something
Do you want me to row?
Hey
Ga you go?
-- Yes I am waiting for Melissa
Are you cold? Do you want my ...
-- No.
Certainly?
-- Thanks
Excuse me ...
-- No Problem
It seems always kissing or better in the cold
Oops
Ok er ... Nice hotels
Nice hotels
I crept out
-- Rebel
I am a rebel
Treasure?
Your mother says you've Peroxide?
How was it ...
-- Good
Was there a lot of people?
-- Yes
Er ... The step of your girlfriend ...
-- Scott
Yes, he has to call you ... So ...
you go along?
Where?
Er no, are you two ...
-- No.
Indeed, he seems a nice boy
I mean, cool, he looks cool
Big.
-- Pap I'm tired
Thus ... I see you tomorrow
-- Slaapwel
Are the children calm?
Where are we?
A friend of mine has lived here
If we stay in the car or do we
in the grass?
What?
Come on, no games
Stop astublieft
You ... Wait, Shirley said that one of you
they were ...
one of their what?
Oh Shit
Er ... I knew that everything would go wrong
I knew the
This did not happen
Jesus
Brenda, if you go home, I want you
take a picture of yourself
Because now you perfection ...
And I want you to that picture every day
look, and never change
Erm ... Ok
We have nothing to do
You can talk, I can listen
Hello?
-- How is it?
I'm on the babysitting
-- For whom?
Listen, I'm doing now ...
Shirley, since when babysitting your ...
-- Excuse
I must go.
-- Shirley, Shirley ... Auw!
Is it?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm gestruikeld, I'm so awkward
Can we get started? It is late
How long already?
-- Nearly a month now.
You do differently lately.
You do not need to do what you do not want
-- That does not make good what you've done
Who?
Who has a babysitter?
Shirley Hey, I want a kitten Order
If you do not say on the phone?
Melissa?
I want a babysitter in order to
my offspring to watch.
That is better
Make sure she has big tits.
No, they have a new way to share
We no longer have the brackets.
They do no more long divisions
and Bailey is the only one in which these kindergarten
"After the division."
So we had to a conference with
other parents with gifted children
It was interesting how they taught us to
their small brains to stimulate
Using them now not all
calculators?
Bailey's teacher says that he
no need
The other day we were watching TV
and he turned around and says:
Mama, I should study.
Can you imagine the proposals?
He is still a child
I saw what you did on the Mustang
bill.
And what do you think?
Not determined your best work.
If you have suggestions ...
-- It seemed more like a crude version
Especially because it's yours.
Is there anything on?
There is nothing in your hand. Nothing.
I do not know. I thought it was good
And if you think that there is work to
is that so, what can I do about it?
Have you heard? We have
same babysitter
Really?
-- Yes Shirley
But sometimes Shirley, sometimes the other
girls
She has a whole bunch of girls
who works for her.
Really?
-- Let him the ticket.
My god, look!
She is very enterprising
I've seen the ticket
Yes.
Sooner or later there will be someone behind.
You're right.
-- About what?
There you call so many men that women
suspicious.
Keep it there and then just ...
-- Dollar 200?
Look at the risk, look at
the reward.
Look at me.
Ga back in your car!
Let me reassure!
You have those tickets.
Is that what you want to do? Do you want this?
I thought that it went to us
Would you not? Pay
there was no longer!
I stood here! You got that money from you
bag and you gave it to me!
So I do not try to blame
do feel.
You have not by how far you
it is, do you?
You risk everything! Teenagers!
-- I wish they did not
Pap Hello!
-- Hello
The price goes up.
300 Dollar from now.
Are you here for one reason or
just boring to do?
Do you look nice?
Where have you met?
-- Summerset
Do you ever borrow?
-- It is probably too big for me.
They have also in black.
Dad says that I do not get more money
until I get better points at school.
I can help you with money.
Hello
-- Brenda
I have the pressure tonight so it is
Nadine well as babysitting?
Can I get you alletwee?
It is not good, but ga.
Great ... 7 hours ...
Brenda!
Ok, I have to go, day boys
Hey.
-- What is happening?
Where were you during lunch?
I was in the chill with
those handsome guests.
Got my 20%?
I'm not gone?
-- What?
Jesus
-- He gave no!
That is ...
-- It is OK
Got my 20%?
We can help you with the mathematics.
-- Keep your mouth
Why should I pay you anything?
I have this guy fucked.
Nadine's how it works.
I make appointments, I care
there that everything is in order.
I get a percentage of what
you deserve
It is 60.
Should I encourage you to schedule the Video
or was it for once?
I'm still sometimes
Do not you bus
Hello?
George, it's Nadine
You know me still.
Some friends also want babysitting
I've actually been something
Shirley governed
George, Shirley's friends
not at all like these girls.
And George, let this
between our two keep
Oh, watch out for your head
Sorry, oh God.
Slowly, slowly, ok?
I've only had 2 phone calls
Last week
I tell you: it is Nadine.
Brenda!
-- Hello
Come here.
What is happening?
Does Nadine other things?
-- No.
I do not think so ... No
-- Are you sure?
I do not think
Can you find out?
-- How?
Look at home was around.
Can you do that?
-- Yes, yes, no problem
Thank you!
She is lying
No additional money or phone numbers?
-- No, nothing of that
And its box?
-- Her box?
Erm ... I do not think so, no.
Have you looked?
I've had a couple days ago
still looking.
Ok, Thank you Brenda
Everything OK?
-- Yes
Are you sure, because ...
What do you do?
-- Allow simply lookout!
On the lookout for what?
-- We are losing time
Shirley, komaan, Shirley
-- I have said that we had to call Jerry
Shirley!
I said it ...
-- This is burglary, komaan, we go ...
We are now al
There is nothing broken
-- It's not true, it is simply not true.
Michael has a moral crisis.
I thought you were the combination
had, what are you doing?
Caution
Fuck, Fuck, Brenda klote
-- Come on that's enough, we go ...
We can not let it so, as she
ask who has done this, we insist
We can not rectify
it is clearly mad, they will ...
Zeik not pervert
-- You need help
Be adult
-- You can imagine what
Everyone, stay calm
Shirley!
Hey, I'm sorry, I had to work
-- I called every hospital, police station
Gail, I'm sorry, I was in
A meeting
I could not hear the phone and I
would not call the children and arouse
Michael, I ask you this only once
Was your ...
No
Next time ... Call me your
Ok, ok, I'm sorry
Excuse me really
Attention all students, there will be a
veplichte are gathering at 11.15
Attendance be recorded.
You do not steal customers
You can not take any money from my pocket.
And you do not run around in an outfit
Dollar, 1200
We assume that nobody is going
it will brands
And everyone gives me their percentage
You fucks nobody, not even you
date for the ball ...
... without my consent
I hope that after today, nobody more
doubts about how serious I am
You miss the meeting.
Shirley Liner, you're in
holiday
Yes?
Well, actually, I thought more
a werkvakantie
Jerry has a house in the north
What are they?
-- Approvals for absences
Hey size, forget the fish
not to enter, ok?
Nice, that's nice
Those annoying company,
I'm sorry
Are you trying to amuse, it would
sometimes fine may be
Ok, I see you Sunday ok?
Will I do not kiss?
-- Oh, honey, I'm sorry
I love you
-- Ok
Hey, do you want to eat? how
time is it?
Oh, it's dinnertime.
Jerry Hey, look at all these beasts
Hello, are you nervous?
You need not be nervous
Hey, stand up
Hey
Take it as a
It is my ... Medication
What is happening?
Oh, that stain, it seems as if
you have in your pants geplast
Have you ever ... something done with
that other girls?
You know who's really ...
really special?
Brenda
Every time I get her, give
I need a little extra tip
because ...
It is not as if they were something ...
exceptionally ... game does
Nothing so what I can tell ...
It is more ...
You know, it's just so
Young and stupid
She has no idea what
they get from us, no idea
Monday she looks back and thinks they:
wow, that was really something special
It is something special, man
I do not know
We are the best thing these girls
will ever overcome.
Jesus, Erm ... Nadine ... You are ...
Stupid old people, thinking that X
makes you horny
It is ... it is exonerating
it is so beautiful.
No, that's not good
-- Try it
Got water?
Hey, come here, come here
-- No, Ga road
I am here inside.
Brenda, is everything okay?
-- Yes
Can I come inside?
Ogenblikje.
There you are.
-- Sorry
What is happening?
-- I want the stops.
Have you taken too much?
-- I do not know, but not much
Come here, I try to calm down
since I was always very good at
Yes?
-- Yes, what you want to do ...
You're really ... sweaty.
Just ... Look at ... not look at me
Look at yourself, look in your eyes
Concentrate on your eyes
What is happening?
-- I do not like to see myself
What are you talking about?
look at that face
My god, look at those eyes
Beautiful, beautiful eyes, they are green
with small blue dots
Stop
I can do anything about it
-- I do not know, I feel sick
I have taken too much
I make it better
No, no, I ga vomiting
Not do not do that, not surrender
Come on, my boy
That's my boy
Come on, stay there
Help me, komaan
Help me, help me
Stay just ...
I must surrender, Jerry
do not, no, no
That's my boy
No
-- Do not do not do
No. No, shhhhh
komaan, shhh, do not say that
Oh, komaan
Come on
mama ...
Okay ...
Fuck!
That is not worth the damned
Boys, it's time to go to
go to bed
Come on boys, touch me not to, ok!
Touch me not to
Come on boys, we go to bed, ok?
My turn, my turn, my turn
-- Shut up!
shut up, shut up
-- My turn, my turn, my turn
Ga simply sleep
I have no way, I have to go
Scott?
Brenda, what's going on?
-- Driving!
Brenda, what ...
-- Driving! Ride!
Brenda
-- Who stores with doors?
She was in the babysitting and they
called me hysterical on
Should I call you Mom?
-- No.
I'm sorry
-- What happened?
I can not ...
-- It is okay
This is me not ...
-- I can not ... Brenda
I can not do more
I ga for you and I do these things
with strangers
And then I come home and I have that
stuff from my hair washing
I can not do more
Listen to me Brenda, if you look
want, you may look
But be silent!
-- What happens?
Familieproblemen
Yes, really ...
I must go
I'm allowed
I graduated a year earlier,
I am ready in June
Leave me?
-- Brenda You can not let go
They will tell everyone
Are you afraid that the university
no permits whores?
She herself does not indicate
if they are in the club's
Verknoei not, Shirley
We have worked too hard
Ga go home, you have a test tomorrow.
On the side, on the side ...
-- Do not hurt him
Tell your sister that she should remain silent
whether we address it to
Leave her alone damned
Oh my god, what happened?
I've fought
-- With whom?
There is nothing happened
-- Scott, who has done this?
Have you seen my thing?
What have you done?
-- What is your problem?
Talk not to me as if I
am an idiot
You're crazy to be
-- I said that you had to leave in peace Brenda
I am not Brenda been
I've done for you
I did it, so you this
can keep rotating
In a few months, I'm away
Who is your help?
You control
-- Not about you
This has always been your game
I just played it
Hey what are you doing home so early?
Mikey's director called
Mikey told his teacher for his kl ...
a pillow.
What did he ...?
-- That is not funny
Your son laughs, and he is
not even twelve?
I can not believe it
-- Why are you home?
I am of the mustang-taking
met
Are you fired?
No, I'm not relieved, but
taking a minor move
In other words, a demotie?
No it's not demotie. George thinks
just that I'm better somewhere else
Have you told what happened?
-- Hold on, hold on
You work so hard you can
-- I am a mature man ...
... and I can fight my own
and that I have done?
And so it is ..
-- It is everything we worked for!
What do you want? How much do you want?
What makes you happy?
We have the
How much security do you have?
-- Oh my God
What?
-- I can not have this conversation now
I'm sorry
That is good, walk away,
every time, every time
Each time
If you have a problem with me?
Tell me
If I do something wrong ...
I would not have to tell you that.
I am not your conscience
Why do not you ga to top
talk with your son?
I Ga to the vrijdagsvergadering
What do you mean?
we had plans
Yes, plans change
Hey champion.
Okay, what is the name of that teacher?
Mr. Lebette
Size, you can not just
people press
I have already heard mama
I know how you feel,
I know how you feel
I am also angry, I become angry at
my boss, because he never listens
and he has these rules he imposes
because he says what people want to do
Why?
I would have him say that he
kloten can kiss my
I must tell him that he
his kloten can cushion
That's what I'm supposed to do
Are you hungry?
-- Yes
What do you think of a large pizza?
-- Okay
You know where the issue lies?
-- In the big slide
That's right, order two large pizzas,
no olives, and also question Adam
And do not forget him tip to give
Ga Where you going?
Do you not to be Adam?
Not at all
-- Thanks, and he no olives
And this, this is for you
What? You have this arrangement already weeks!
Shirley Sorry, but if I fail to
This test could I not to Cancun
Can you find anyone else?
-- Do you love me for a ride?
Listen, I'm sorry, I can
Just do not.
What was that?
-- My life
I can still speak
She deserves the Brenda
Is it normal not later?
Gail has my event cancelled
I just wanted to say that I am
sorry ... on the pills.
And how about that whole thing ...
But, you know, Gail and I ...
we are simply not
Gail and I ...
-- Keep non astublieft
We are terrible people
Probably we deserve each other
But it is something for later
nostalgic about to be
No, I've told nonsense for a
Much of my life
But some things out of what
your mouth ...
What do you think will happen?
-- I do not know
Are we running away together?
Get the clothes on anyone of us
hold, which depends on us
What do you think will happen?
Listen to me!
You'm the first thing I would like
fifteen years.
I can simply no secret life
more suffering, do you?
I need you
I need you in every part of my life
I need you ...
Why should you do?
Why can not you just
alone?
Should I pay you? is that what you want?
Should I pay you?
Is this what all this means for you?
I'll pay you to listen to me
I'll pay you to be with me
I'll pay you to turn me into
I'll pay you ...
I want this no longer among us
Do you understand? I have no longer needed
Tell me how I can back
gain
Say me that I have any part of your back
It is too late
Who is here within?
You know that this is private property?
-- No. sorry that I did not know
What are you doing here?
-- I just love of trains.
I just look around
Is there someone with you?
No.
-- Are you sure?
Yes, I ... there is none, I just love
trains, so I came.
In order to look around, that's all
It is time to go
-- Yes, sir, thank you
Buk you
Hello
-- It's Shirley, Brenda is there?
They can not come to the phone
Well, can I speak Nadine?
She is busy
Scott, give her the phone
She is in the babysitting
I try to not to hate
Call astublieft no return
What? What?
What are you doing?
Hello?
-- Nadine did it again
She takes back to work behind my back
She is now someone to fuck.
I know where they go.
Where are you?
There, running
You're guilty me something for this
Shirley, a lot of guilt.
Hey, what are you doing ...
Hey! Wait!
Keep your damn mouth!
Come here!
Wait, wait! Stop!
Astublieft, Shirley!
What have I told you?
What have I done you?
I can not check
Pap?
You had earned the
You had earned it ...
We all lead secret lives
Even if only in our heads
I think the question is: Why?
Are there not simpler ways
to wake up pinching myself?
I ask no forgiveness for what
I've done.
I have to live with my own sins
I think it's just one of
those moments was
A unique detail ... In another
simple life
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org