Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Scared?
- Cranky?
- Jewish.
- Same thing.
But the Heritage Hill series
is very inclusive.
ln fact, there is a whole chapter
about Hanukkah.
l just love the chapter on pinecones.
They're not just for wreaths
and centerpieces.
You can use pinecones to create
a very special Yuletide menorah.
Your pinecone snowman
could be Jewish.
Just add one of those little beanies.
Or maybe l could just use
hundreds of pinecones
to spell out the words ''Big Jew''
in letters 1 5 feet tall
in the snow in my front yard.
That's a wonderful idea.
- Oh, yes, yes.
- That's very wonderful.
- Yes.
- She's so smart.
l love the idea of creating
a life-sized Santa Claus,
- all out of pinecones.
- OK, l love that.
l'm going to use a pinecone in
my nativity as the baby Jesus.
And l'm going to attach
a pinecone to my vibrator
and have a really merry
Christmas.
Here comes Santa CIaus
Right down Santa CIaus Lane
He's got a bag that's fiIIed with toys
For the boys and girIs again
Hear those sIeigh beIIs jingIe jangIe
What a beautifuI sight
So jump in bed, cover up your head
Because Santa CIaus comes tonight
- Who?
- Santa CIaus comes tonight
Joanna, how is she fitting in?
Well...
OK...
l'm among friends, right?
- Of course.
- Yeah.
So...
Joanna and l had this big talk,
and we were really open
with each other.
l mean, we really got it all out.
And l think from now on...
...she's gonna be very, very different.
You think Joanna's
really going to change?
Yes, l do. Absolutely.
And how long
have you been married?
- Ted!
- Yes.
Don't you owe Walter $20?
That's absolutely right, l do.
Babe!
Yes, darling?
Walt, sit down.
l need 20.
- You know my PlN.
- Of course.
She gives singles.
Are these all for day camp
tomorrow?
l just want you to be proud of me,
honey.
Dad, watch this.
Ball.
- Aren't robots cool?
- Oh, yeah.
May l speak to the man
of the house?
- Snot-butt.
- Funkmaster Markowitz.
- Stone-cold Thriller Killer Kresbo.
- Cupcakes, anyone?
- Cupcakes!
- Cupcakes.
Hey, right on time.
Jo, these are smoking.
- Why don't you make stuff like this?
- Why don't you?
Because l have a penis.
- We should get moving.
- Yeah, we got a meeting.
- At the Men's Association.
- When will you be home, honey?
When l'm home.
Call a sitter.
Bobbie, are you sure about this?
We're not spying. We're just visiting.
Fellas, l can't tell you
how happy we are
to welcome all of this new blood.
- You said it, Mike.
- That's right.
l love, love this space.
lt's very Ralph Lauren meets
Sherlock Holmes.
lt says, ''l have taste and a scrotum.''
- Roger, you promised.
- What?
- Whore.
- Bore.
- Sorry.
- No, no, no.
Jerry, you're gonna find that
Stepford is very open-minded.
- Oh, yeah.
- We welcome you and your partner,
just like any other couple.
Absolutely. Any other.
- That's right.
- Girlfriend.
Miss... Miss Thing.
- To Stepford!
- Stepford!
You bet.
Yeah.
Damn. Come on, let's go.
You think this is all right,
sneaking around?
Add it up.
All the women around here
are perfect sex-kitten bimbos.
All the men are drooling nerds.
- Doesn't that seem strange?
- Not to me.
- Why not?
- l work in television.
Oh, come on.
You know, Walter,
l think Joanna is right.
- l think Stepford is the answer.
- She's a great gal.
Or she will be.
- Come on, help me up.
- We shouldn't be here.
Oh, come on.
Don't be such a chicken.
- l should be home with my cupcakes.
- Why?
Because you only made
5,000 of them?
- We're trespassing.
- Only if we get caught.
Damn, l can't see a thing.
Oh, there's the light.
There it is.
No, Bobbie.
This is like some alien freak show.
Why? They're just family portraits.
Yeah, that's what l said.
The lights.
We should get out of here.
Should we run?
Oh, my God.
Clarice?
- Hi, girls!
- Roger!
You scared us.
- What are you doing in here?
- What's going on?
Do they have hookers or old PIayboys
or cable porn?
Oh, please.
They barely have throw pillows.
- They're coming.
- The menfolk.
- Call us.
- OK.
Rog?
What was it?
Did you see anyone?
Not a soul.
But what's back here anyway,
in all of these rooms?
Storage? Sweaters?
Bodies?
- Jerry.
- Do you see that door on your left?
Check it out.
Oh, boy.
Why, l can't see anything.
lt's dark.
Use your flashlight.
l feel like Nancy Drew in
The Mystery of the Mid-Iife Crisis.
What am l looking for?
Look down.
Jerry?
Roger!
- Bobbie.
- Roger!
- Bobbie?
Roger said there was nothing going on
at the Men's Association.
Well, then why doesn't he
answer the phone?
- lt's been two days.
- Bobbie.
Roger!
lsn't that his favorite shirt,
the Dolce & Gabbana?
The Guccis.
- And the Versace.
- Maybe he's donating them.
To what? The gay homeless?
He loved this.
His program from Hairspray.
- Oh, my God.
- What is it?
Viggo.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
l'm Jerry Harmon, and l...
l know l'm pretty new here,
but already l feel so at home.
Why did Jerry ask us
to meet him here?
Proud that l can introduce Stepford's
brand-new candidate for state senate.
Ladies and gentlemen,
l give you Mr. Roger Bannister.
What?
He's wonderful.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
You may very well ask, what are
my qualifications for higher office?
Well, l believe in Stepford, America
and the power of prayer.
Values l've discovered thanks
to my partner,
in life and in the Lord,
Jerry Harmon.
Roger. Roger.
Yes. ls there a question?
Mrs. Markowitz?
So you two are happy now?
More than ever. Because now
l know that being gay doesn't mean
a guy has to be effeminate
or flamboyant or sensitive.
- l'm no sissy.
- No.
- Way to go, Roger!
- That's a man!
- Roger?
- Yes. Mrs. Walter Kresby.
Roger, l don't understand.
You were out there, you were Roger.
And now...
Now you're different.
Your hair, your clothes.
- You're like someone else.
- People change.
You can't stop Stepford.
So that's why we have
to leave Stepford?
- l'm not following.
- OK.
Before, Roger was witty
and stylish and ironic.
- And l'm sure he still is.
- No.
Now he's making speeches
in a Brooks Brothers suit.
Hey, there's lots of ways to be gay.
Don't try to make him
into a stereotype.
Bobbie is right,
and she's leaving too.
This place does something to people.
All of the women are always busy
and perfect and smiling,
and all of the men are always happy.
- And that's a problem because...?
- Because it's not normal, Walter.
lt's... lt's not the world. lt's not us.
And l'm picking up our kids
from camp right now,
and we're getting out of here.
With or without you.
Secure.
You'll never change, will you?
Not really.
Open the door.
UnIock front.
And you're right.
About what?
lf you're that unhappy,
then we should move.
Maybe head back to the city.
We could leave tomorrow.
Thank you.
What do you got there? Huh?
Sweetcakes?
lt's 4 a.m. What are you up to?
Just recipes for tomorrow.
l like to get a head start.
- On what?
- Apple pie. Bobbie recommended it.
l'll be right up.
Walter?
Babe?
Bobbie? Bobbie!
Oh, my God.
Bobbie?
Good morning, Joanna.
lsn't it a lovely morning?
That's a pretty color.
- Mom!
Good morning, my precious ones.
And thank you for leaving
your requests on my e-mail.
Adam, you wanted
peanut butter and jelly, no crusts,
a Snickers bar and a Rolex.
Ben, here's a whole-wheat burrito,
a soy protein shake and three pieces
of German chocolate layer cake.
- From scratch?
- Of course.
And, Max, you get bacon,
lettuce and tomato
on a lightly-toasted
sesame seed bagel.
But what about my action figures?
There's Mace Windu and Amidala.
- Where's Boba Fett?
- They were out.
- Mom!
- Here's $500.
All right.
Bye, Mom. Bye, Joanna.
Oh, they grow up so fast.
l think l'll have three more.
Bobbie, listen to me.
What have they done to you, huh?
What have they done to you?
ls it drugs?
ls it brainwashing?
Come on, hey, talk to me.
Of course, but only for a minute.
Then l have to get to work
on this pigsty. Coffee?
No, no coffee. Bobbie, Bobbie.
Last night l went online, all right?
And l found out,
all of the women here,
they used to be big deals,
l mean, big deals.
CEOs, executives, judges.
Sarah Sunderson,
she used to run an airline.
With that perfect skin.
No. No, no, no.
She didn't used to look like that.
- None of the women did. They...
- Coffee?
Coffee? No. No coffee.
Bobbie. Bobbie. This isn't you.
That's right, Joanna. This isn't me.
lt's a whole new me.
l'm happy and l'm healthy
because l understand
- what's important in life.
- Yes.
- Your new book.
- That's right.
That's what's important,
my new cookbook.
And my husband and my family
and making a perfect home.
lt's a lesson every gal needs to learn.
Especially you.
l'm your friend, Joanna.
l'm going to help you.
- You need me.
- You stay away from me.
You're driven.
- Well, sometimes.
- And you're selfish.
- You wanna rule the world.
- No.
l can fix you. l can change you.
What...have...they...done to you?
Let's get busy.
Answer the phone.
Hello, is...? ls this the day camp?
Oh.
Yes, this is... This is Joanna Eberhart.
l would like to speak to my children.
l'm coming to pick them up
right now.
What?
Walter!
Walter, where are you?
l know you've got the kids.
Pete, Kimberly!
Oh, boys.
Welcome.
Where are my children?
- They're perfectly safe.
- Where are my children?
- You'll see them soon.
- Where's Walter?
How could you do this?
Ever since we met,
you've beaten me at everything.
You're better educated.
You're stronger, you're faster.
You're a better dancer,
a better tennis player.
You've always earned
at least six figures more
than l could ever dream of.
You're a better speaker,
a better executive.
You're even better at sex.
Don't deny it.
l wasn't going to.
Well, don't l get anything?
You got me.
No, l got to hold your purse.
l got to tell the kids
that you'd be late again.
l got to tell the press
that you had no comment.
l got to work for you.
With me.
Under you.
All of us.
We married wonder women.
Supergirls.
Amazon queens.
Well, you know what that makes us?
Smart, worthy, lucky.
We're the wuss.
The wind beneath your wings.
Your support system.
- We're the girl.
- And we don't like it.
- No, we don't.
- Yeah, that's right.
- You're damn right.
- Yeah. That's right.
And is this your answer,
to kill us?
Oh, no. Nothing like that.
We help you. We perfect you.
By turning us into robots?
Does any fraction of these women
still exist?
Of course. Almost everything.
- Shall we show her?
- Show me what?
lt's a promotional thing l've been
working on for when we go global.
Walter, l don't think you've seen this.
Some guys ask, how do we do it?
In Iayman's terms,
it's reaIIy pretty simpIe.
Come on aIong.
First, we take a gIoomy,
dissatisfied woman.
Then, in a very private experience
between husband and wife,
he gentIy pIaces her in our
femaIe improvement system.
It's fuIIy automated.
And then, abracadabra.
Her transformation begins.
First, we Iocate her brain.
We insert a few nanochips.
Then we program them.
AIso, we add
some secret, speciaI ingredients.
To avoid any accidents,
her husband is kept
at a comfortabIe distance.
Safety first.
FinaIIy, we enhance her,
to fit the ideaI Stepford Wife
specifications.
And...
...voiIa!
Everything is copasetic.
WeIcome to the future.
lt's a painting again.
l should explain. You see,
my real name isn't Mike.
lt's just a nickname
from where l used to work.
- Where?
- Microsoft.
- NASA.
- Disney.
AOL.
ls that why the women
are so slow?
Joanna.
ls this what you really want?
Women who behave like slaves,
women who are obsessed
with cleaning their kitchens
and doing their hair,
women who never challenge you
in any way,
women who exist
only to wait on you hand and foot?
- Yeah.
- That sounds good to me.
Joanna, you're a brilliant woman.
Surely you can appreciate,
at the very least,
the genius of the concept.
Picture, if you could streamline
your spouse,
if you could overhaul
every annoying habit,
every physical flaw,
every moment of whining
and nagging and farting in bed.
lmagine...
...if you could enjoy
the person you loved,
but only at their very best.
And the only reason for your anger,
your resentment, your rage
is really very simple.
You're furious
because we thought of it first.
While you were trying
to become men,
we decided to become gods.
Let me ask you something,
these machines,
these Stepford Wives,
can they say, ''l love you''?
Mike.
Of course.
Fifty-eight languages.
But do they mean it?
Enjoy.
Walter.
Walt.
Joanna. Right here.
- Sarah.
- Claire.
- Marianne.
- Charmaine.
- Roger.
- Roberta.
Oh, Mike!
Mike, Mike, Mike!
Good evening, everyone.
What a delight to see
all of our wonderful wives
and their happy, happy husbands.
Tonight is truly the highlight
of our year because tonight
we honor our very newest citizens
of Stepford.
ln my opinion, they are
the cream of the crop in couple
that proudly proclaims Stepford
the American way of love.
Now...
...l'd like to ask my wonderful woman,
my lovely wife,
my bride, my best friend,
to join me in a glorious
midsummer night's waltz.
Yeah.
ls everything perfect?
Everything.
- Mike.
- Yeah.
Darling.
- My pleasure.
- lt's an honor.
- Champagne?
- Allow me.
Doors activate.
WeIcome member 1 956.
Kresby, WaIter.
Entering secure area.
Warning.
Initiating.
So, Joanna,
are you enjoying Stepford?
Oh, yes. The town is so splendid.
Everyone is so kind.
And then, of course, there's you.
Me?
And it's simple really.
Honey, grab me another Scotch.
Right away, dear.
Begin nanoreversaI.
NanoreversaI compIeted.
DeIeting Stepford program.
FiIe corrupted.
DeIeting vacuuming function.
Honey.
Oh, Herbert.
Restoring originaI personaIity.
DeIeting Stepford program.
What is this?
What am l wearing?
Mike!
Mike, there's something...
...unspeakable going on
in the ballroom.
You have to come right now.
lt's an apocalypse!
What did you do to us?
- Mike!
Men, control your wives.
Control your wives.
lt's not working!
This is not Stepford.
Mike, what's happening?
l was in the garden,
and l was dreaming of your...
Your smile and your after-shave.
And l realized...
...l can do better.
- Walt.
- She's not a robot.
- What?
What, she's not a robot?
She never was.
Wait a second.
- l couldn't do it.
- What?
Why not?
Because she's not a science project.
Because l didn't marry something
from RadioShack.
That's a shame.
No.
That's a man.
l thought you were ready.
l thought... l thought you were ready.
l thought l knew you.
You're a disgrace.
To everything this town stands for.
To the future.
That's right, that's right. Tell him.
You're gonna have to pay for that.
Don't you touch him.
No!
He's a Stepford Husband?
An angel.
Now he's just...
...spare parts, thanks to you.
But what are you?
Are you a person or a machine?
l'm a lady.
A real lady?
- Every inch.
- Wait.
Wait, a real, real lady?
Are you a human being?
Yes, and l may very well be
the only decent human being left.
- ln Stepford?
- ln the world!
She's fabulous.
All of this, Mike, the wives, Stepford,
this was all your idea?
Yes.
All l wanted was a better world.
A world where men were men
and women were cherished and lovely.
Does anyone have a screwdriver?
She's nuts.
A world of romance and beauty,
of tuxedos and chiffon,
a perfect world.
But you were married to a robot.
The perfect man.
And all l wanted was to make you,
all of you...
...into perfect women.
We don't need to be perfect.
How could you do this to us?
Because l was just like you.
Overstressed, overbooked,
under-loved.
l was the world's foremost
brain surgeon and genetic engineer.
l had top-secret contracts
with the Pentagon, Apple and Mattel.
l was driven.
Exhausted.
Until late one night,
l came home to find...
...Mike.
With Patricia.
My brilliant...
...blond...
...2 1 -year-old research assistant.
lt was all so...
...ugly.
Then early the next morning,
as l gazed across the breakfast table
at their lifeless bodies, l thought...
...''What have l done?''
But more importantly...
...what l could do to make the world
more beautiful?
l had the skills.
But l needed help
to realize my larger vision.
And so l made...
...Mike.
Because he was someone
other men would listen to.
And then l asked myself,
''Where would people never notice
a town full of robots?
''Connecticut.''
So l decided
to turn back the clock,
to a time before overtime,
before quality time,
before women
were turning themselves into robots.
- Back off!
- Sorry.
Why didn't you change the men too?
That's next.
You're insane.
l'm in love with a waltz
and a town...
...and a man.
So, Joanna, you produced
the hard-hitting documentary,
Stepford: The Secret
of the Suburbs.
And won... Five Emmys, was it?
Oh, six.
- She's shy.
- And so humble.
And, Bobbie, your ordeal
has lead to a bestseller.
You know, l just can't hold a grudge.
So l've written my very first
book of poetry.
And it's all about hope
and communication
and the healing power of love.
What is it called?
Wait UntiI He's AsIeep,
Then Cut It Off.
- lt's a page-turner.
- l cried.
Now, Roger, good news.
You ran and won.
You're in the state senate.
- lndependent.
- Next stop, the White House.
- Yes, this country needs highlights.
- That's our hero.
And, Jo, Walter really came through
for you,
so how's your marriage now?
ls everything just perfect?
No way.
But we're doing just great.
Because, um...
Because now, now we know for
sure that it's not about perfection.
Perfect. Perfect doesn't work.
What about
all those other husbands?
Are they still angry? Do they still want
all these women to be robots?
Of course. Men are pigs.
They're disgusting, they're frightened,
repulsive little rodents.
But we're trying to help them,
right, Bobbie?
- Right.
- Yes, we're trying to reeducate them.
And where are they?
Oh. Oh, they're still in Stepford.
Under house arrest.
Hey, you guys.
Which aisle is quilted paper towels?
lf l don't get the right kind,
my wife's gonna kill me.
Oh, aisle three. And l need...
No talking, keep shopping.
subrip by goldy
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org