Chief Metacomet.
Without
your father's friendship,
none of us could have survived.
My father should have let you
die!
You are
the only one
who comes to us
with an open heart.
But your people have murdered
my father
with their lies!
My name is Pearl.
This is the story of
my mother, Hester Prynne.
It was the year of our Lord 1666,
when she arrived in the
Massachusetts Bay Colony
filled with the hope that at last,
in this new world
would come the freedom to worship
without fear of persecution.
My esteemed colleague!
Thy years of toil become thee!
Thy fame preceeds thee, sir.
Governor Bellingham,
may I present
the Reverend Thomas Cheever.
Welcome, sir.
It's a long voyage.
3 months at sea,
will either take away your faith,
or harden it to iron.
Allow me to introduce a woman
who's been travelling with us,
- Mistress...
- Hester Prynne.
I apologize for the coarseness
of my hands, Mistress.
But here in the colonies,
everyone must work.
I look forward to the hard work.
It says id Psalm 92: "I will
triumph in the work of thy hands".
Thou canst quote the Scriptures.
Aye, Reverendo, both Testaments.
My husband taught me.
You must rest.
Then I'll show you
what's been accomplished.
I thank thee.
- Then it's Goodwife Prynne.
- Yes, yes.
But I prefer to be called Hester.
Welcome, Hester.
I wish I could've seen it before,
when it was wild and untouched.
Madam,
you should use less lace
in your dressmaking.
Indeed, Reverend.
Master of us all,
we give thanks for
another bountiful meal,
and for newly arrived disciples,
that share it with us this night.
- Amen.
So, Governor.
I am impatient to know
how you fared with Metacomet.
Well, Metacomet
isn't Massassoit, Major Dunsmuir.
But if we respect the agreements
we made with his father,
we've nothing to fear.
So we don't
grow complacent,
our wise God sends us a sign.
When we sailed,
your letters said we were
at peace with the savage.
Well,
I fear the days of "peace"
with the Wampanoag is at an end.
Major,
we are frightening
our new arrival.
We hear much
of your success
with the praying Indians.
I'm very eager to meet
Reverend Dimmesdale
and his converts.
The runts of the litter.
Dimmesdale's little treasures!
Some of us
have other opinions.
Mistress Prynne,
I hope you'll stay with us
until your husband's arrival.
You're most kind,
but I intend to find
a house of my own
as soon as possible.
On thine own?
Why, yes.
It's not considered fitting
for a young woman to live alone.
I've come first to prepare
a place for his arrival,
so that is what I intend to do.
Mistress Prynne.
The rules we live by may seem
arbitrary to a newcomer,
but we have learnt
the hard way
that without absolute order,
we cannot hope to survive here.
Rules, Mistress Prynne.
Order.
Survival.
Would you have me
disobey my husband?
- I...
- Reverend, you might enjoy
the company of my son, Brewster.
He studied Divinity.
Harvard wasn't good enough
for him,
so he came home to
make his fortune as a...
Minister's sons all moaning
the Lord's Prayer
in their sleep.
Everyone must find his place.
- Morning, Mistress Prynne.
- Good morrow.
So you intend on scandalising
the town!
Get up!
Good!
I confess,
I feel alone in a
sea of conformists.
Where should we begin our search?
On the cliffs by the sea.
No, it's out of the question.
Why?
No one's lived
by the sea
since the Indians
wiped out Ballinger's Point.
I say we start there.
Well, if you've decided.
Is that it, Brewster?
It's beautiful.
I tried to imagine
what herlife was like
before she came
to the new world.
Why did herhusband
send heron ahead,
alone?
Was it a test ofherloyalty,
orherspirit?
Or was it in his nature
to set traps
forpeople in the hope
they would fall into them?
It's perfect!
With a cart and a musket,
I could have a home here!
A cart, a horse,
a pitchfork, a plow.
I can think of better things
to do with these pretty hands
than grow calluses on them.
I'll need indentured labor,
at least two men.
- The land needs draining.
- You are headstrong.
Perhaps it runs in the blood.
I'm told your father was too.
Is it true
he was in debt to your husband
and you were the payment?
I've said something
to disturb you.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
God, thou art wondrous fair!
That hurt!
Good. It'll remind you
not to do it again.
Faith?
Prudence?
Did you hear Mistress Prynne
has a bathing tub?
What is she, French?
2 Shillings.
Will you bid 2 shillings?
2 and a half?
Come on, gentlemen,
do I have a bid for 3 shillings?
3 shillings?
Anyone else?
Going for 3 shillings.
Any other bids?
Sold to the gentleman
for 3 shillings.
- Next we have this other one,
- Those two.
How much time left
on their indenture?
About 3 years, but,
shouldn't your husband or father
be doing business with me?
Is my money
no good to you, sir?
Your money's as fine as wine
in the sunshine, Mistress.
If you buy them at a just price,
I'll throw in the girl in red.
She's a slave!
But she don't speak, if that
be a problem. Born that way.
Name your just price.
We'd best accompany you
if your going to the forest.
Don't worry Mr Bobbin.
I shan't go far.
Mistress Prynne?
Where are you?
Mistress Prynne, where are you?
I found her.
- You did not.
- I did to.
Mistress Prynne,
Have you forgotten
it is the Sabbath?
Of course not.
Forgive me.
We've come by especially
to bring you to church.
Thank you, so much.
Please, go on without me.
I will follow at once.
Make haste.
Yes, sir.
All right, girl,
Come on.
Oh goodnes!
Back up. Back up.
Come on now, back up.
Come on. Come on. Back up.
Good morrow.
May I be of assistance?
Not from up there.
Come on.
Steady. Steady.
I can't make this horse
understand me.
Let me try.
Come on, girl.
Come on, back up!
Come on. Come on.
I'm afraid you're in too deep.
She'll not make it.
Let me try this.
I do hope you can get it free.
I'm already late for the service,
and everyone's talking about me.
I've been away and I'm quite
behind on local gossip.
I bought the old Newbury place
out on Ballinger's Point.
Then,
I owe you an apology.
I've been trespassing.
There's a place at the point
where I like to bath.
Really? Well, I shan't charge
too steep a tariff.
Come on, girl, back up!
- Back up.
- One,
Two,
Two. Three.
I'm afraid this cart will be
stuck here until Sabbath next
unless I gather hands to help.
Would you care to ride with me?
On your horse, with you?
Aye, unless you can ride.
I can ride.
You take my horse
and I'll take yours.
There's a shortcut
to the meeting house,
but it's a difficult road.
I shall manage, sir.
- Are you certain?
- Just you lead the way.
Come on! Come on!
May God be with you.
I'm sure he already is.
But aren't you coming to...
Good Sabbath to ye all.
Friends,
and fellow voyagers,
in the greatest of all dreams.
We've been singled out,
like Israel of old,
to serve as a model.
But if we are to succeed
in building our new Jerusalem,
our "City on a Hill",
then the power of love,
yea, His Divine Love,
we must bind our hearts as one!
English and Indian,
gentry and indentured,
free man and slaves,
and make of us
an example for all the world,
to marvel at and proclaim:
"Here...
is the measure of perfection!
Here,
lives God's own!"
But we are not succeeding
in that test.
We are failing!
And why?
Because we covet,
nay,
we lust after
what is not ours.
Be it for the rich land
of our Indian brothers,
be it for glory,
for profits or for revenge.
Need I read the secret
of every heart?
I will if you want.
Yea, I will if you want.
I will lay open the secrets
before the eyes of God!
What thou lusteth after is my enemy,
sayeth the Lord God.
For only I shall consume thee,
only I shall fill thee up.
If thou failest to heed
my commandments,
then my fist
shall descend on thee
like a stone!
And thy sword shall cut thee
into bloody parts,
and even thy memories
shall be sacrificed
to the winds
for all time!
May God bless you,
each and every one of you.
Amén.
Allow me to present a newcomer
to our congregation,
Mistress Roger Prynne.
Mistress Roger?
Aye, her husband, a renowned
physician will join her before...
Reverednd Dimmesdale and I
have already...
I helped when her cart
got stuck in the woods.
I greatly enjoyed your sermon.
It's rare for a man so young
to speak with such passion.
For some reason,
I felt most inspired today.
We welcome you and your husband
to our congregation.
Mother! Mother!
There you are, Hester.
Meet my friend, Running Moose.
He's our schoolmaster.
And I'm sure you'd like
some refreshment.
Do you teach the English children
as well Mr Running Moose?
They call me John or Johnny here.
We try our best, but the English
are a bit slow-witted.
Slow-witted?
Johnny's a bit of a jester,
but he was our first praying Indian.
My best friend in the colony.
Arthur,
- this is Mistress...
- We've already met.
Excuse me.
So like home.
Yet beyond those trees
I suspect a savagery,
of savage passions,
dark and untamed.
Reverend Dimmesdale,
have you met our young friend?
Yes, we've met.
Mistress Prynne and I
traveled out on the same ship.
I'm going to marry him one day.
No you're not, I'm going to
aren't I Mistress Prynne?
- Marry whom?
- Reverend Dimmesdale, of course!
"A Short Description of the
Great and Last Judgement".
Well, "Platform for
Church Discipline".
They're all tracts!
"The Goodwife's Manual... "
for Animal Husbandry"
I believe we've already met.
Oh, yes, I...
I'm sorry, I didn't realize.
I should have
announced my presence.
What are you reading?
- "Comus", it's by John
- John Milton.
I know it. I've read it.
Have you?
I'm not all counterpanes
and coverlets.
Every spare moment, I read.
I'm the same.
I've read every book in this room.
Some of them several times.
Even "Manual for Animal Husbandry?"
A most exhiliarating read.
So, did you truly
enjoy my sermon?
Yes, it was most skilful.
Clearly your congregation
reverences you.
You liked it not. We don't
come up to London standards.
To the contrary.
I was moved by your passion.
And?
Well,
when your fist struck your hand,
and sliced through the air
like a sword,
I found myself wondering
what manner of pain lay
beneath such forceful oratory.
Your tongue knows no rules,
Mistress Prynne.
And if it did, Reverend,
what purpose would it serve?
And here I thought
comprehending God
was to be my greatest challenge.
Yes, Reverend?
This morning in the forest,
why did you not say
you were married?
Why did you not say
you were a minister?
Good day, Mistress Prynne.
Good morrow, Mistress Prynne.
Good morrow.
You care for a cup of cider?
We are your neighbours, it seems.
Did you like the sermon
this morning?
From where I sat it
seemed it did please thee.
I liked it very much.
I thought the
young minister very...
Handsome?
Harriet Hibbons.
Ruth?
How do you do?
Come and meet some of
the others who were not invited
to the Governer's shindig.
Sally Short, Mistress Prynne.
How do you do?
I was on the dock
when you arrived.
Mary Rollins.
Mary don't like to speak much.
She's only been free from
the savages this half year.
And Matona don't trust
the English, do you dear?
Mistress Prynne?
Thank you, no.
I never imbibe.
You've gathered some fine
Balm of Gilead,
Shepherd's Purse, yarrow.
You know your plants?
I do. I recite "Culpepper"
by heart.
Really?
Then what would you use to
heal a bad burn?
I've seen sweet fern work miracles,
but Culpepper suggests blackberry
and red cedar.
Well, you hear that.
My husband has
a very large library
and I was able to school myself.
How do you like our new
Jerusalem?
Sober enough for you?
Aye,
sober enough.
What I miss is the dancing.
Dancing?
When first we came,
they'd be dancing round
the maypole.
Feast days we'd sing
bawdy songs.
People weren't afraid
to play the fool.
We'd teach
the bears to dance.
Now days, everybody getting more
and more sourfaced and ponderous.
And a whipping post stands
where the mayppole used to be.
But there's a few of us who
haven't forgotten to laugh.
It's been a pleasure
meeting you all.
I'm sorry I must take my leave,
but I don't want to be stuck
in the wilds at night.
There are things that sound to me,
the wilds at night are
my natural territory.
Particulary when there's
a full moon.
Do you try to frighten me
with this witch talk?
Not so, Mistress Prynne.
But I can see
what others cannot.
Be a curse, to be sure,
but I know the hearts of men.
And what does my heart tell you?
You're a most comely woman.
Let a man tremble
who wins the hand of a maid,
but possesses not the
full passion of her heart.
My husband has nothing to fear.
Good day Mistress Hibbons.
Good day, Mistress Prynne.
Good day, Goody Gotwick.
I brought these for
Reverend Dimmesdale.
The Reverend be occupied
with his work, Missus.
Leave them books on the table
and I'll be sure he gets them.
Good morrow, Reverend.
Good morrow, Mistress Prynne.
Knowing you hunger for new reading,
I brought you some books.
How courteous of you.
Please.
I must apologize for my
forthrightness on Sabbath last.
I've earned a few reprimands
for speaking too bluntly.
I owe an apology, too.
I can't understand why
I took such offence
to such a simple comment.
But I have wondered
how you were able
to see so deeply
into my nature.
Perhaps I'm a witch.
I must be keeping you
from your chores.
Thank you for the books.
Good day.
I'm sorry. My hands
are covered in ink.
I've been
hovered over
my translations all day.
Translations?
Aye. I'm attempting to
translate the Bible into
the local Indian language,
Algonquin.
What an ambitious undertaking.
But I'm told the Indians don't want
to be guided by our Bible.
That war with them is inevitable.
Some think that way,
but they're wrong.
The Indians, born from a
certain liberty,
take not easily
to bridle and bit.
No man should.
Well...
What?
You keep putting ink
on your face.
Oh, I do.
There you are.
I do hope you enjoy
the books.
Thank you.
Good day.
Mituba?
'Tis only a bathing tub,
not a toy of Satan.
Mistress Prynne?
Reverend Dimmesdale!
- You frightened me.
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
It's a wonderful surprise.
- It's beautiful.
- Yes, and frightening.
Just as Eden must have been.
So untouched.
Does it not cry out
with it's promise,
that everything
can begin anew?
I brought back your books.
You couldn't have read them all
in four days.
Oh no, I did.
I read most of them twice.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Farewell.
Hester...
I'm not the man I seem.
I've lived here all my life,
my purpose clear.
But now I'd risk everything,
my life, my ministry, my soul
just to spend a few
moments alone with you.
God help me, Hester.
I love thee.
God help me.
I love thee too.
Oh God. Have we lost our way?
No!
I dreamed of thee speaking
thy heart.
I have prayed for it even as
I have dreaded it.
Was I alive before
I laid eyes on thee?
What shall we do?
I know not.
Say something to end it,
for I have not the power.
Nor I.
Nay!
We could be hanged for this.
I've put you in too much danger,
and I must end it by walking away
and never speaking with you again.
Go then.
Do as you promised.