Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
That's my train.
Wait! Wait!
Shit.
Ow.
Wake up, Jack.
Have you seen Francis?
Hello, Peter.
Good afternoon. Whitman?
Yes. -Yeah.
-Yeah.
May I see your tickets, please?
Thanks.
There's no smoking, please.
Welcome aboard.
Sweet lime?
Yes, please. -Sure, I'll
have one. -Sounds good.
Let's go get a drink
and smoke a cigarette.
I want to start by thanking you both
for being here. Thank you.
You're welcome.
-Thank you.
You're the two most important
people in the world to me.
I've never said that before, but it's true,
and I want you both to know it.
I love you, Peter.
Thank you.
I love you, Jack.
I love you, too.
How did it get to this?
Why haven't we spoken in a year?
Let's make an agreement.
To do what?
-Okay.
a.) I want us
to become brothers again
like we used to be,
and for us to find ourselves
and bond with each other.
Can we agree to that?
Okay. -Yeah.
-b.) I want us
to make this trip
a spiritual journey,
where each of us seek the
unknown, and we learn about it.
Can we agree to that?
Sure.
-I guess so.
c.) I want us
to be completely open
and say yes to everything,
even if it's shocking and painful.
Can we agree to that?
Now, I had
Brendan make us an itinerary.
Who's Brendan?
My new assistant.
He's gonna place an updated
schedule under our doors
every morning of all
the spiritual places
and temples
that we need to see
and expedite hotels
and transportation and everything.
How's he gonna do that?
I had him bring a printer
and a laminating machine.
Where is he?
In a way, it actually
doesn't matter.
He's in a different compartment
on another part of the train,
but we never see him-ever.
That's more or less it.
Three, please.
Does that sound okay to you?
It sounds good, sure.
Yeah, it sounds good.
Do you have any questions?
I do.
-Okay, go ahead.
What happened to your face?
I only remember
certain details,
but from what I've been able
to reconstruct,
it was raining, I was going
about 50 miles an hour
as I went into a corner,
did some wrong steering,
wheels went out from me,
and I suddenly, whoo,
skidded off the road,
slammed into a ditch
and got catapulted
50 feet through the air.
Little particles
of glass and debris
were stinging my face as I flew.
And for a second,
there was just total silence.
Just...
Then bam! The bike crashed
to the ground,
exploded and caught on fire,
and I smashed into the side
of a hill with my face.
I was driving home.
I live alone right now.
Anyway, two joggers ran up
and started digging out
all the dirt that was
jammed inside my mouth
and my nose and my ears.
My brain had stopped,
my heart had stopped,
so technically I was dead
at this point.
They did all the procedures
exactly right,
as a result of which
I'm still alive.
Boy.
-Wow.
The first thing I thought
of when I woke up was,
I wish Peter and Jack were here.
Have you heard anything from Mom?
No.
Have you?
Me neither.
Fuck.
What's that?
Some kind of Indian muscle relaxer.
I got it at the pharmacy
next to the train station.
What's that?
You don't need a prescription here.
A type of Indian flu medicine.
It's got a tranquilizer in it.
What's that?
Strongest Indian
painkiller you can get.
It's for my face.
Be careful with that.
You only want to take one drop.
Shh.
I also lost a tooth.
You want to read a short
story I wrote in France?
How long is it?
What?
-How long is it?
Never mind. Forget it.
You can save it till after dinner.
You know,
maybe right before
whenever you're about
to take out your tooth,
you should say something
like, "Please forgive this. "
Because it's, actually,
it's kind of...
Can... you... back away a little?
You just spit in my eye.
When was the last time you
were in America, by the way?
I don't know.
The funeral.
In other words, a year?
I have to tell you,
I support this relationship
not working out.
May I take your order, please?
Let's see.
Do we want meat or fish?
I'm gonna have the chicken.
Jack, you want to try the fish?
I bet that's delicious.
And, Peter, the lamb?
A chicken, a fish and a lamb?
How does that sound?
Who wants a soup?
Raise your hand.
Are those Dad's glasses?
Yeah.
You still have
his prescription in here.
How can you see in these?
Three soups.
Soup.
Could you not order for me, please?
What?
Order for yourself.
What part are you on?
Nothing.
It reminded me of something
not related to it.
How's Alice?
She's fine.
She actually started
this company
where she makes these
little clay pots.
They're quite popular.
We sent you one.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Oh, thank you.
I want that stewardess.
These Germans are bothering me.
Ladies! Please keep it down.
Lower your voices. Thank you.
Did I... raise us?
Kind of?
Hang on-I'm gonna ask this guy
if he can get me a power adapter.
She's pregnant.
Alice.
Really?
You're kidding.
-No.
Uh, how long?
Seven and a half months.
So it's gonna be
born in, like,
six weeks or something.
I think so, yeah.
I'm trying not
to get too caught up
in it right now.
Don't tell Francis.
Brendan got the wrong voltage.
Your soup, sir.
Please forgive this.
Hmm.
Is it supposed to be sad?
I think so.
Well, I'm not too crazy
about the part
where I start screaming
at the mechanic.
That never happened.
The characters are all fictional.
May I take your dessert order, sir?
Let's see.
Do we want sweets or fruit?
I'm gonna have the pudding.
Jack, you want to try the cake?
And, Peter, what looks good to you?
The cookies?
He's gonna order for himself.
The cookies.
Excuse me, I'm...
Has he been rooting around
and taking things?
Maybe.
I think he's still in mourning.
Well, I probably
am, too, but there's
something kind of unethical
about it, isn't there?
Legally those glasses
belong to all three of us.
I'm gonna take this bed,
because I'm the oldest
and my ankle's fractured.
Peter, you don't mind climbing
a ladder as I recall,
so why don't you set up shop
topside?
And, Jack, you're a little bit
of a lone wolf.
Why don't you bunk out next door?
How does that sound?
Oh, sorry.
I was...
Stand up.
Brendan, this is Jack.
Good evening.
-And this is Peter.
Hello, Brendan.
Nice to meet you.
Let's update me.
How's everything going back there?
Pretty good.
-What does that mean?
I never heard back.
So try again.
What are you waiting for?
Well, I left a message.
Why are you smiling?
What do you think
he looks like
under all that tape and everything?
FRANCIS
Brendan, what did I tell you?!
Well, I don't know
about his face,
but I think his brain
might be pretty traumatized.
Damn it!
Come down to this spot over here.
Call her again
right now
and keep calling
every ten minutes
until you get through.
-Okay.
This is urgent.
We're almost there.
Okay.
-And once again,
so we're explicitly clear,
I don't want you
to mention this
or discuss it with anyone.
In other words, it's a surprise.
Okay.
Did you find me a power adapter?
Not yet.
How long are you gonna stay here?
What do you mean?
He said till the end of the month.
Uh-huh.
Why do you ask that?
I'm just trying to know so
I can figure out my plans.
What plans?
I don't know yet.
Anyways, I've got my own
ticket, just in case.
Don't tell Francis.
Well, I'm not gonna stay here
with just me and him.
Is that one of Alice's pots?
Oh.
We should order some more of these.
I'll tell Brendan.
Okay.
He has this disease where
his head is shaved,
except he doesn't
have to shave it
because he can't grow any
hair in the first place.
Don't... talk about it
around him, though.
It might offend him.
Are these Dad's keys?
Yeah.
You've got his car keys, too?
Where's those nuts at?
I got it, I got it, I got
it, I got it, I got it.
Good evening, Mr. Whitman.
How can I help you?
Is it possible for us
to get some more
of those Savoury Snacks, please?
Of course.
Can I offer you anything else?
Um... I don't think so.
I'll be right back.
I forgot something.
You want to smoke a cigarette
with me in the bathroom?
You're crazy.
What's your name?
Jack. What's yours?
Rita.
You're beautiful.
Don't come into me.
Jack's got his own return ticket.
He says he might leave early.
What are you talking about?
Don't tell him I told you.
Brendan's got all the tickets.
There's a whole itinerary.
Where is he going?
Air Italiano?
What the fuck is this?
I'm keeping his passport.
In fact, give me yours, too.
I want to keep
all the passports
so nothing happens to them.
I'm keeping mine.
No. I want to keep
them all together.
Why are you standing there?
I'm waiting for you.
Mr. Whitman,
the whole point
of us coming
out separately
is so no one sees us together.
Jack.
Right. I get it. Okay.
Good night, then.
Go back to your compartment.
Move over, please.
Where are the Savoury Snacks?
Huh?
Did you just fuck that Indian girl?
What?
Sweet Lime.
Of course not.
I went for a walk.
Something just happened.
Shh!
-Who's he talking to?
No one.
He's got the code
to his ex-girlfriend's
answering machine,
and he's checking her messages.
What? When... When did
he confide that to you?
Just now.
Why am I not a part of this?
I've never liked that girl.
Me neither.
Anyway, I never trusted her.
I don't feel good about myself.
Okay. Let's make another agreement.
On the spiritual journey,
it's crucial
that we don't splinter
into factions
or not include somebody
who has advice and may know better.
Can we agree to that?
-Okay.
What did you find out?
-Nothing.
Good.
She put this in my suitcase.
Is that her?
Mm. That's her.
How did she gain access
to your personal belongings?
She came to see me in
France for 24 hours.
Could she be gaslighting you?
What's gaslighting?
Okay, hang on a second.
Let's make another agreement.
From now on,
if you want to talk to her
or check her messages,
you speak to us first.
Day or night. Anytime.
Can you agree to that?
I think we should destroy that.
Jesus!
Okay. All right.
Let's check the itinerary.
Give me a little light.
Okay, here we go.
Train stops first thing
tomorrow morning
for an hour and 45 minutes,
which is just enough time
for a quick visit
to Temple of a Thousand Bulls,
probably one of
the most spiritual places
in the entire world.
Wow.
Power adapters!
Can I get a power adapter?
Yes, yes, yes.
Do you have a power adapter?
No, no.
No power adapter.
Use battery.
Do you have these in, say,
a ten-and-a-half medium?
These all size.
Take off shoes and try.
Yeah, like that. That's good.
Pepper spray. What ingredients
does this have in it?
I don't want to kill
anybody or anything.
No, no.
Not for killing.
Spray in face.
Okay. Spray in face.
Most rare, from desert.
Very poisonous.
How much you want for him?
This is incredible.
Ring it.
Take some of these
rupees and put them
on this thing in front
of the deity here.
Is that my belt?
Can I borrow it?
Well, no, not right now.
I was looking for that earlier.
Ask first... next time.
-Right.
Where's my passport?
I got pickpocketed.
My passport got stolen.
Calm down.
It's not stolen.
-No, yes, it is.
It's gone.
-No, it's not.
I have it.
I'll be right back.
You stole my passport?
Peter, where are you going?
I'm going to go pray
at a different thing.
I hear you're leaving early.
What are you talking about?
I thought we made an agreement.
That's why you stole my passport?
Well, no, but I think
we have a chance
to make this kind of a
life-changing experience,
and I think we need it.
In other words,
I don't want you to leave.
He's going to have a
kid in six weeks.
Who?
-Him, Rubby.
He doesn't want you to know.
-"Rubby"?
Yeah, you know, Rubby.
Yeah.
Why doesn't he want me to know?
Because we don't trust each other.
Wow, right?
Yeah, amazing.
-Great, thanks.
Let's get a shoeshine.
Oh, hit it.
Hey. Hey, come back here!
What?
-The kid just left...
Who?
-He just...
Get him!
He left his shoeshine kit.
-He...
Well, now he can pay
for this building.
Those are $3,000 loafers!
Yeah, but he only got one of them.
Yeah, but that's...
We're in an emergency here.
I got my face smashed in,
Jack's heart's been
ripped to shreds,
and Rubby's having a child.
Let's get into it.
You told him?
It's okay.
Okay, that's what
we're here for,
to start trusting each other.
I don't get it, by the way.
Why aren't we celebrating?
'Cause I don't want
to talk about it.
Well, why not?
I guess because
I always expected
eventually I'll get divorced,
so having children...
really wasn't part of my plan.
Okay, but you're never
gonna do better than Alice,
and what's the point
in getting married...
Why'd you expect to get divorced?
I don't know.
I love Alice.
Maybe it relates
to how we were raised.
I was gonna save this
for later in the itinerary,
but I think it's time.
There's a ceremony I want
us to do where we each
take one of these peacock feathers.
We're gonna go off
into the wilderness
and meditate for...
Damn it, I gave them to Brendan.
That's all right, we'll
do it after the next stop.
Those guys are laughing at us.
Where?
I love it here.
These people are beautiful.
They're playing cricket
with a tennis ball.
Hello.
How do you do?
-Hello.
It's great.
Yeah?
-Yeah.
It's so well-written.
You remember everything so clearly.
Peter getting all frantic
getting the car started,
you with the suitcase.
The characters are all fictional.
Well, anyway,
I think it's the best thing
you've ever written.
Thank you.
Here are the peacock feathers,
plus some instructions
from the guru.
What's in that box?
He bought a snake.
It's got a skull and crossbones...
Let's update me.
Anything?
She got the message, yeah.
And?
What? That's it.
That's it.
She got the message.
You're satisfied with that?
Well, she knows you're coming.
Does she want to see us?
But she's your mother.
Happy birthday...
from last year.
I can't accept this.
It's too valuable.
It's got one
wrong initial,
but you can paint over it.
It's from me and Jack.
Yes?
Would you like tea?
Okay.
Thank you.
I got to get off this train.
What's her name again?
Rita.
What'd you say?
There's a hole in it.
He escaped.
No, he didn't.
How?
Now-Now you believe me, assholes?
We think a snake might
have gotten on board.
Don't go in there, Rita.
You got him!
I'm kicking you off
at the next station.
Please don't do that.
We're very sorry.
It won't happen again.
I know it won't.
What's that smell?
Voltaire Number Six.
Do you have
a prescription for these?
A prescription?
I almost died.
Give me a second.
That animal's deadly poisonous
and you brought him onto my train.
We didn't know.
It was an accident.
We're just trying
to experience something.
It's very important to us.
You're confined
to your compartment
until further notice.
Is our snake getting confiscated?
Do you think it's working?
Do we feel something?
I hope so.
-It's got to.
Do you trust me?
Where are we?
Brendan, what's going on?
I don't know. I guess
the train's lost.
What'd he say?
He says the train's lost.
How can a train be
lost? It's on rails.
Apparently we took a wrong
turn at some point last night.
That's crazy.
How far off course are we?
Nobody knows-we haven't
located us yet.
What'd you just say?
What?
What you just said.
Say it again.
We haven't located us yet.
Aah!
Is that symbolic?
"We... haven't
located... us... yet. "
Where's those feathers at?
In the envelope
I gave you this morning.
Meet me on top of
that thing out there.
The guru told me
when the moon turns...
Do you trust me?
I hired a private detective
to track down Mom.
She's living in a convent in
the foothills of the Himalayas.
We'll be there in six days.
How is that possible?
I guess she became a nun,
apparently.
You know what she's like.
A nun?
Apparently.
Did you talk to her?
No, I didn't.
Does she know we're coming?
I think so.
How do you know she wants to see us?
She probably doesn't.
But maybe she does.
Why didn't you tell us sooner?
Because I'm trying
to protect you
from all the painful emotions
this is probably gonna stir up.
Well, aren't you kind of
doing that right now?
Yeah.
I'm scared, too.
She's obviously suffered
some kind of mental collapse
and we've got to go get her
and bring her back home.
Actually, it's in the itinerary,
but I put it under "T.B.D."
Why are you laughing?
You didn't tell us
'cause we never
would've come here
if we knew about it.
I'm gonna hold this in
for a little while.
You gonna drink that whole
bottle of cough medicine?
That's a dumb way to get loaded.
Let's look at the itinerary.
Fuck the itinerary.
You know, I think I'm gonna have
to get that belt back after all.
Because it cost me $6,000
and it was made special for me.
We'll get you a different present.
I don't think so.
What is that supposed to mean?
It means there's been too much
Indian giving over the years.
These guys are driving me crazy.
Is there an empty compartment
I can move into?
No, there isn't.
We're fully booked.
I really want to kiss you
right now. Can I?
No.
No?
But we already... did it.
I have a boyfriend.
You do?
Actually, I just broke up with him.
Or I'm about to.
I really need someone
to talk to right now.
And I feel like you might be
very important to me in my life.
All right.
What did I tell you?
Get back in your room.
What's happening?
-What do you mean?
I rang the bell.
-I'll be right there.
Is that Dad's razor?
Yeah.
Can I say something?
What?
You don't have permission
to take his property
that belongs to all of us
and use it for yourself
as if it's yours.
Jack agrees with that.
Right, Jack?
Plus, Dad would've hated it.
Why?
That's my opinion.
I knew him well.
That's a terrible thing to say.
Well, I don't mean it to be.
I just don't want you
to get the feeling
that you're better friends
with him than we are
or something weird like that.
And, also, you can't
leave your wife
just because she's pregnant.
Jack agrees with that, too.
Right, Jack?
Stop including me.
I was his favorite.
He told me that with blood all
over him laying in the street
right before he died.
How is that supposed
to make us feel?
I want my passport back.
Francis?
Yeah?
Here's your belt.
Fuck. Stop!
You don't love me!
-Yes, I do!
I love you, too, but I'm gonna
mace you in the face!
Stop!
I had to do it!
Jack!
You maced us!
Stop including me!
I'll find us a hotel.
Next train's in 24 hours.
This just came in.
Why are your eyes all red?
Why is your head so bald?
Because I have alopecia.
Oh, yeah.
That's like albino, right?
Not really.
Jack maced us.
Was I just mean to Brendan?
He's not coming back.
He just quit.
He did, didn't he?
Can we at least get our snake back?
It's dead.
You killed him?
Your fake tooth's gone.
Fuck.
What did you say?
Shame on you.
Did you get maced, too?
No, I'm crying.
What's wrong with you?
Let me think about that.
I'll tell you
the next time I see you.
Sure, tell me then.
Thanks for using me.
You're welcome.
Good-bye, Rita.
So long, Sweet Lime.
"Dear boys... "
Bad timing.
This morning I received the
details of your travel plans
in a document sent to me
from a man named Brendan.
Unfortunately,
I cannot receive you now.
A neighboring village requires
our urgent assistance
due to an emergency,
not to mention the recent
arrival of a man-eating tiger
in the region.
I suggest you come
in the spring
when you'll be safe with me.
You must know how sad I am
to experience this long separation.
I hope you'll eventually
understand and forgive me.
God bless you and keep you with
Mary's benevolent guidance
in the light of Christ's
enduring grace.
All my love, your mother,
Sister Patricia Whitman.
That sounds like bullshit to me.
Me, too.
Obviously.
She's trying to sell us
a vacuum cleaner.
Let's get high.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
I wasn't trying to aim
for your face.
Doesn't matter,
it's already demolished.
Let's just go home.
She doesn't want to see us anyway.
You don't think so?
Not even on some primordial level?
No.
She's been disappearing all our lives.
We weren't raised
to be treated like that.
It's just not done.
Maybe this is how
it's supposed to happen.
It could all be part of it.
Maybe this is where the
spiritual journey ends.
You read the instructions,
right?
Okay, let's do it.
I'm gonna go over here.
Yeah, g... that's good,
get on the rock. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
-Peter, you get... Yeah.
Everybody ready?
-Yeah. -Yeah.
Ah! Oh!
-Shalom.
Okay, that's it.
That's it.
Okay.
Well, all right.
Which direction did yours go?
What do you mean?
Your feathers.
Mine blew towards the mountains.
That's not right-it's
not supposed to get blown away.
You're supposed
to blow on it...
And then bury it.
I didn't get that.
I still have mine.
You guys didn't do it right.
I asked you
if you read the instructions.
You did it wrong.
I tried my hardest.
I don't know what else to do.
I don't think Dad
would have hated it.
Did he really say
you were his favorite?
I don't know.
I could barely understand him.
He wasn't really breathing.
I wonder if the three of us
could have been friends
in real life.
Not as brothers but as people.
Well, we probably would've had
a better chance, I guess.
Let's make another agreement:
We'll all come back here
in the spring when...
We're never coming back here.
Let's just find an airport
and go our separate ways.
Wouldn't it sound great
if you could hear a train
going by off in the
distance right now?
Not really.
-Probably be annoying.
Look at these assholes.
That's gonna tip over.
Go!
Get the little one.
Francis!
Grab him!
Don't let go of me.
He's all tangled up.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org