THE INGLORIOUS BASTARDS
FRANCE 1944
-Are you alone here?
-Yes, I was a prisoner.
-But I fled.
-And?
I am unarmed.
-What's your name?
-Private Adolf Sachs.
ID number 1 040.
Come here.
Nice and easy.
-Which is the safest way to Switzerland?
-The germans sieged the villages.
The safest yet longest way
is through the woods
First group, forward!
Hurry up!
Watch out for dud granades!
Take cover, fast!
Take cover! Hurry up!
To the right!
Prepare for battle!
Stop!
Come here!
-Who are the americans?
-Four soldiers and an officer.
-Where did you come from?
-Saint Michel.
-We attacked and captured them.
-Where are you taking them?
-To the headquarters for
further interrogation.
-The new order is: no prisoners!
-The army didn't receive that order.
And they call themself soldiers.
They're a bunch of cowards!
What have you got there?
Trouble...
-Lieutenant!
-Yes, captain!
-Shoot those men!
But those men are prisoners
of the army, not Waffen-SS!
Ah, to hell with Waffen-SS!
You have an american machine gun.
Shoot this traitor too!
Vehicles, drive on.
Carry out the order and follow us.
Take cover!
Papers please.
Americans!
Ten beautiful women.
Americans.
Nicole, here's an american.
Take great care of him.
Marcel and Robert, take care of
the americans lodgings!
Are you american?
Sit down.
Want to buy?
The watch?
Nicole, bring the aid box!
There's almost nothing left,
just some bandages.
-What is it?
-Nicole, we're waiting for you.
-I'm coming!
Au revoir.
Turn on the searchlight!
Come on now, hurry!
Get ready
Quick, hide the parachute
and put out the fire.
-Come on, hurry up down there!
-Have you seen, Pierre?
What are they doing?
See you soon.
Hurry up and load the stuff.
-I have two american prisoners here.
-What shall we do with them?
-I need a car.
-Can you affirm that?
What do you mean "affirm"?
What the fuck do you mean by that?
We were to transport the prisoners,
but our truck was blown up.
We've been walking for two days
and are exhausted.
-We don't...
-Come here!
Heil Hitler!
-What's going on here?
-Nothing, sir.
I have two american prisoners
and I need a vehicle.
You can have a new car,
but the prisoners stays.
Quiet! - Bring the prisoners
to my office.
Let's go.
Here's the car.
-Don't shoot!
Throw your weapons under the table.
What are you doing?
Look out, it's a trap!
Move it, come on.
Papers, please.
Everything's under control.
Let them pass.
A mere mistake can be fatal,
so everything must be perfect.
Your papers, please.
Everything is in order.
You may step aboard.
Thank you.
General Tieck, officer
Ritter and Schaefer!
Good to meet you. The train will
depart in a few minutes. Sit, please.
We would prefer to start our
work immediately, general.
Sorry, but no one is allowed in the
laboratory before departion.
-Oh, of course not.
-Of course not.
Hello? Hello?
The train just took off.
What? Yes.
We've departed. May
we start working now?
Yes, but first you'll have to
turn over your weapons first.
-It's a mere formality.
-Yes, of course.
Major Schaefer, major Ritter?
I'm cardinal Hauser. Cardinal
Brenner is in the darkroom.
He'll be assisting you shortly.
Have a seat, please.
Brenner told me you've been
working together.
Charming...
Stop!
Damnit!
Here is a detailed description.
Everything you need is in there.
Have fun, you'll have to
excuse me now.
Stop!
I'm going to pay cardinal
Brenner a visit.
Certainly.
Cardinal Brenner, major Schaefer
comes to pay you a visit.
-Schaefer?
-Yes, sir.
Nice to see you again.
One moment please.
-What happened?
-He felt nauseous.
Prepare for battle!
-The bridge is destroyed.
-Why do we stop?
Make contact with the headquarters.
We need to protect the rocket.
There is another way, but
it goes to near the american line.
Tell the engineer to back all
the way to the trackswitches.
-Where's cardinal Brenner?
In the darkroom. I'll
go see how he's doing.
Contact Pont Mosson immediately.
As you can see on the map...
Hello? The bridge is destroyed
We're coming back.
How's the situation at your place?
Notify the general that the situation
is calm and the track is safe.
Yes, the situation is calm
and the track is safe.
Do you have some chocolate?
Follow me!
Gather the wounded ones
and get your guns.
Where did they come from?
-A train full of germans! Hide!
Hurry up!
-What's going on?
-Stand still!
I just saw someone who
fell off the train.
Quick, open the door!
He's hiding in there.
Help! Help us!
THE INGLORIOUS BASTARDS