Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Why do police believe the man you saw
is the killer when you said he wasn't?
Would you comment on rumors linking you
with the suspect romantically?
Miss Fang? May l have a word with you?
No. Don't you have a certain fugitive
to apprehend?
No. l just want to talk to you
for a second.
This is harassment.
I’m just trying to protect you, ma'am.
From who?
Our fugitive friend is mixed up
with the Triads.
You know what that means.
My best friend is dying up there.
lf you want to help, find the person
who tried to choke the life out of her.
Okay.
lf you want to call me, there's my card.
Fuck!
Help! Somebody help me!
Go, girl. Go.
Go. Come on.
In the car.
Move over.
Not a word.
Move on.
Who do you work for?
Are we just going to sit here!
Please, stop that.
No.
No?
I’ve got you figured out.
You do?
You think l don't see
you're as scared as l am?
The reason you won't say what's going on
is you don't know either.
All right. That's enough.
Okay?
All right?
What are you?
Some kind of government agent?
Translate this for me and you go free.
Free?
Free to go where?
All right. Play it again.
This is Ambassador Wu.
Yes.
He's saying that the dead refugees...
...were a deliberate action...
...to derail the trade agreement.
And he knows who is responsible.
Who's he talking to?
He got here too late.
She was already dead.
So he took it out on a Triad stiff.
Jana Novak.
Her passport is Czech.
Her file came up blank.
Same as our guy. Same dead end.
Weird same.
Weird.
Phone records you asked for.
There's definitely a pattern
showing up here.
You mean other than
half a dozen dead bodies?
Yeah, look. Phone numbers in sequence:
555-3901 .
-555-3902, 555--
-Okay, let's see.
What you've got to do is,
you've got to go all the way up to 99.
isolate the possibles...
...stake out all the locations,
wait for our guy to show up.
Bob's your uncle.
That's a good plan, but who's Bob?
He's your uncle.
This better be a fucking emergency.
Hello? Who is this?
We are unable to complete your call
as dialed.
Please check the number and dial again.
Protests like this one at the U.S. Embassy
in Beijing are causing many to believe...
...that the UN Trade Agreement
will dissolve before it ever starts.
All eyes are on
Secretary-General Douglas Thomas...
...to find a peaceful solution to the strained
relations between the countries.
You have a monumental crisis emerging,
Mr. Secretary-General.
I’m convinced there's only one man
in the whole world...
...who can compel those fellows in Beijing
to stick with their agreement.
And that man is you, David.
l don't know if you're trying to flatter me
or frighten me, sir.
l think what the Secretary-General
is suggesting...
...is that you can remind all parties
involved that, as history has shown...
...economic prosperity does wonders
at keeping the peace.
Excuse me, Madam Hooks,
l missed CNN today.
Is there a war going on
that I’m unaware of?.
There's always a war going on.
There's your side, there's theirs...
...and me in the middle
trying to make it look like peace.
The Secretary-General spoke
to the President this morning.
lf the situation does not improve...
...he's prepared to fly in
from Washington tomorrow...
...and attend the ceremony himself,
as a show of support for the agreement.
It’s a last resort.
l don't want it to happen. l want this to be
a United Nations' initiative.
But, more than anything else,
l want it to work...
...and I’m afraid that, as things stand now...
...without the President's presence,
it can't work.
Don't bring in the President.
it’ll only complicate things.
In the meantime, we were hoping...
...that you wouldn't mind acting
as interim diplomat.
An ambassador of good will, if you will.
I’d be honored to help...
...and allow you to take the headlines:
''Secretary-General saves
China Trade Agreement.''
Excuse me.
Eleanor Hooks.
You posted a missing cat?
Yes.
Yes, l did.
You found him healthy?
Yes.
You'll need to keep him for a few days.
Is that a problem?
No problem.
l know where to reach you.
-Asshole!
-Get a house, you jerk!
internet chat rooms,
though they're a free-for-all...
...you just have to know where to go.
''Triads killed Wu.''
''Framed me.''
''Possible mole in department.
''Hold communications and expect cover...
''...to be compromised...
''...within 24 hours.
''Stay under radar.
''Good luck.''
Yeah, good luck.
You work for the UN, don't you?
Jesus, you do.
Go in there and buy some bottled water
and some food that we'll keep.
When you come out,
there's one more thing you must do.
One more thing?
Must be nice for you to assume
l will bend over whenever you please.
-It’s--
-It’s bend over backwards.
It’s what l meant.
Thank you.
I’m trusting you.
l really don't care nothing about it
that you're drunk!
But you better cook that food
like it's supposed to though.
Excuse me.
-Hello?
-Is Marie there?
-No Marie here.
-Sorry, wrong number.
Pay phone?
Over....
l am not through with you!
l keep telling you, don't nobody want--
Get over there!
Hi, Lo Kee Bakery.
Bingo.
Great.
Down!
Everybody down!
-Get undressed.
-Excuse me?
Strip. All your clothes off, now.
-You think I’m--
-Now! Take your clothes off, now!
You think I’ll get undressed for you?
You're bugged. There's a transmitter
in your clothing somewhere.
-A transmitter? How?
-l don't know how.
How do you think they tracked us
to the diner? Think about it.
They went after you in there. Not me.
Take 'em off.
What was that?
You said l was free to go.
You want to go?
Okay.
Here.
Go.
See ya.
Thought so.
Glasses.
Watch.
Best l could do.
You're not used to this, are you?
Not having control of the situation,
being manipulated.
You're normally on the other side
of the equation.
Are you stating the obvious
for your own personal enjoyment...
...or are you moonlighting
as a psychic friend?
lf l help you,
it would follow that l help myself.
Okay. Then, help yourself
by telling me about Ambassador Wu.
You said you worked for him
for a long time.
Ambassador Wu was an outsider.
He knew China's future lay
in economic growth.
But the party line was to keep
a separation with the West.
He believed that the gulf could be crossed.
What gulf?.
I’m talking about appearances
and meaning.
Frankly, l thought you'd be more sensitive
to this concept.
Who are you calling?
You tell me.
Lo Kee Bakery.
Okay, it's a front.
For what?
This is an athletic club.
A private gentleman's club
for gambling and....
And?
And sex.
You're late!
Where's one of the moron brothers?
Where are you guys?
Frank, my clients are waiting.
You'll be able to hear me with this.
And you'll be able to talk to me...
...with this.
l need your help.
Help me find what I’m looking for, okay?
-What are you doing?
-l don't have time to worry about you.
-Where would l go?
-l don't know. A place l haven't thought of.
Tell me why my helping you
is conditional on being a prisoner.
You're not a prisoner.
I’m protecting you. From yourself.
One of these days, you'll have to tell me
how you know about this place.
Julia?
You awake?
I’m awake.
l was just in a different place.
Can we stick to the present?
You know, l read a book once
about these prisoners of war...
...who construct the house of their dreams
in their head...
...to keep their sanity.
Sanity?
l thought you lost that a long time ago.
Right now I’m sitting at a cafe,
in a small village...
...in the south of France.
There's a familiar face.
There's cops pulling up everywhere.
Did you hear what l said?
Yeah.
Party's over.
Did you need any help with those?
We have a full license.
You got a fucking license?
We'll just be on our way then.
You're in way over your head, boy.
We have an understanding with the police.
Well, now you have an understanding
with the FBl.
l said assume the fucking position.
-Assume position.
-I’m not going anywhere.
You kung fu motherfucker!
Didn't you hear that officer talk to you?
What's wrong with you? Get over here.
Give me those.
Get up the stairs with your bitch ass.
Let's get their names.
Get them out of here. Come on.
Sometimes it's hard to tell the difference
between the good guys and the bad guys.
It’s not always obvious--
Excuse me, miss.
Is this man bothering you?
Steel. Left hand.
Nice and slow.
All right.
Step back.
Not exactly FBl waist regulation, is it?
I’m on probation.
Okay, Cappella, why don't you ask her.
Ask her who the bad guys are,
and if she wants to walk away with you.
We're both after the same thing.
Why can't we work together on this?
Because your idea of cooperation
is me in a cell.
l don't particularly like that.
I’m just after the truth.
Why don't you check out the Vietnamese
refugees underneath the bakery?
My guess is they're linked to the dead ones
you found in the container.
You can be a hero.
l doubt there's a weight requirement
for Attorney General.
Probably not.
Probably not?
Cappella?
Yeah?
Thank you.
That club stinks of David Chan.
He's in bed with the Triads
and definitely linked to the refugees.
But l need proof that he took out Wu
to kill the trade agreement.
I’m not so sure about your theory.
David Chan was supporting
the trade initiative.
Appeared to be.
But ask yourself this:
Who benefits the most from Wu's death?
Besides Mrs. Wu?
lf the trade agreement is signed,
Chan's business monopoly would be over.
He'd have to compete
with the Western companies.
Kill Wu and the UN Trade Agreement
with him...
...Chan keeps China to himself.
You make a lot of sense...
...for a car thief.
Okay, just relax.
Okay, ready.
Log on to the main Web site,
then follow the instructions l gave you.
Wait, the access is denied.
Okay, simultaneously press
Control, Alternate, F8, twice.
Backslash.
Enter.
Password and log in lD.
Don't worry. You don't need it.
Just follow the last lines of codes
on the page.
Department of Defense?
-Julia, look--
-Don't tell me. l don't want to know.
It’s just a trick l picked up
from some friends l trained with.
Did they train you to be this vague?
Or is it a gift?
What's that supposed to mean?
You know what l mean.
l mean your evasiveness.
Comes with the territory.
The strong, silent-type cliché thing
is becoming tiresome.
Okay, we're in.
Okay.
-Wait a minute. Wait, stop.
-What?
Rewind.
Play it again.
All right, let's go frame by frame.
And look very carefully.
Chan's looking before the shot was fired.
l don't believe it. He knew.
He knew that it was coming?
More like, he made it happen.
All right, make a copy
and get back to the car.
Twenty-four hours are nearly up.
I’m putting the trade deal
in the President's hands.
I’m gonna let him run with it.
Bringing the President in, sir,
seriously undermines your authority.
Your strength is what will keep
the UN strong.
I’m using all my sources.
lf anything should leak out, l can kill it.
l feel certain you can keep
this deal together and avoid a scandal.
Thank you, Eleanor.
Thank you, but no.
Reports state
that Secretary-General Douglas Thomas...
...has asked the United States President
to intervene...
...and solidify the Chinese Trade Agreement
before it collapses.
The President and the Secretary-General
will address the General Assembly...
...and attend the signing ceremony
at the UN tomorrow.
lf Chan's serious about killing this deal,
that's where he'll make his next move.
All right.
l want you to take the videotape
and Wu's recording to Eleanor Hooks.
She can get it to the right people
without bringing me into it.
Meanwhile,
I’ll get the final piece of this puzzle.
Finish this once and for all.
-Where are you going?
-The last place l should.
Yes, l will.
I’m sorry. Miss Hooks is quite busy.
l hope you don't mind waiting.
Happy New Year.
Yeah.
She's ready to see you now.
Do you always exhibit such flair
at entrances and exits...
...or is it just when visiting my hotels,
Mr. Shaw?
Actually, l find them rather inviting.
Kind of like a second home, you know?
As my most effective asset in the field...
...I’m almost embarrassed
that you're not on my payroll.
Then maybe you'd like to make me
an offer l can't refuse.
l would.
But I’m afraid you would never get
to enjoy the rewards.
l guess this is my reward.
Excellent, actually.
Assassinate the man
who's been tracking you.
At the same time,
blow apart the trade agreement...
...that could cost you billions.
l know that nothing is what it seems.
But I’m dying for you to explain this.
lf this information were to get out...
...the scandal could seriously damage
China's credibility on the world stage.
Do more harm than good.
l never thought of that.
Appearances are everything, Miss Fang.
Politics and deception are built on it.
Head for the street!
l got him!
Mid-block. Construction site.
Location?
Bly!
Freeze! Drop your weapon!
l said, drop your weapon! Drop it!
That should do it.
Come on!
You're gonna need some silk.
Are you all right?
How does it feel to be a puppet
without the strings?
The Art of War teaches:
Win by destroying your enemy from within.
Ironic, isn't it...
...that a 2000-year-old strategy would be
turned against the people who created it?
Better us doing it to them,
than them doing it to us.
What are you talking about?
I’m talking about 20 years of China fucking
America from within and nobody noticing.
Now they're going to notice.
You.
You're behind all this.
With just enough help from David Chan
to keep everyone guessing.
David Chan, most of all.
l don't understand.
Of course you don't, my dear...
...because you, like most people,
never stop to look at the big picture.
I’ve been looking at the big picture
everyday for 20 years...
...and I’ve tried to look forward.
And you know what l see?
l see China maintaining
a stranglehold on freedom...
...influencing our political process
with illegal campaign contributions...
...stealing our most secret military
technology and selling it to our enemies...
...weakening us from the inside,
like a virus.
This trade deal is an invitation
to finish the job.
We intend to cancel that invitation.
We intend to return America to Americans.
We? Who do you think
you are representing?
The people who have steered this nation
for decades behind the scenes.
The people who protect
democracy from itself.
For a woman obsessed
with Chinese conspiracies...
...you sound frighteningly similar
to the government you are trying to stop.
Thanks for stopping by.
Thanks for this useful bit of evidence.
I’m sure you'll find your own way out.
Shit, shit. Just think, girl.
Julia?
Shaw?
Julia. Hello?
You're breaking up. Shaw?
Move where you can get better reception.
-lf you can hear me--
-Shaw?
Move where you can get better reception.
I’m locked in the UN building.
Hooks is behind everything.
Julia? Julia?
Shit!
Hey, guys!
You call this a perimeter?
Come on, wake up! Jesus Christ!
Cappella.
America's most wanted.
The man of the hour. Why are you calling?
To explain Chan's murder
or apologize for this afternoon?
Both. You want to meet? Let's meet.
Okay. Are you in the area?
With a rookie boy's head in my sights.
Really? l could live with that.
Get in your car. Pick me up
on the other side of the car park.
No, l got a better idea--
Okay, l get the message. I’ve got to go.
What are we gonna do?
l don't know. Figure out something.
Do not underestimate your friend.
There's a reason l chose him
as team leader...
...and there's a reason
l asked you to deal with him.
You obviously do not appreciate
the schedule I’m working with.
l agreed to play Neil because l wanted to...
...not because of the money.
And certainly not because
of your right-wing ideology.
You let me handle Neil. My way.
This is not about male testosterone
between you and your idol.
You were just a cog in the wheel
of a larger machine.
It could've just as easily been you
out there chasing your own tail.
l understand.
What do you want to do about the girl?
It’s almost midnight.
Security will be doing a check
of the upper floors.
You have a 30-minute window.
What about the guards in the lobby?
I’ll take care of them.
Yes, ma'am.
What?
-Drive.
-Okay.
Where's your first aid kit?
Security.
Yes, ma'am.
Attention. Stand by
for a motion sensor test...
...protocol T-7.
All lobby personnel report to Sublevel 1.
Repeat. Lobby personnel stand down
for a motion sensor diagnostic.
The trail ends with Eleanor Hooks.
My guess is that she was using Chan,
and then she double-crossed him.
It’s a long story.
Just drive.
Jesus Christ.
This information has to come out
to clear your name.
l can't do that.
Any connection between Wu's murder,
Chan, the Triads and Hooks...
...would kill the trade agreement.
Holy shit.
And completely destabilize the UN.
Damn it, that's it. That's it!
All she has to do is come clean.
Tell the truth.
Truth?
The truth about me, about the UN
covert operations unit, everything.
She pins the assassination on you
to discredit the UN?
Taking out the one organization
that could hold it all together.
Back to a cold war.
Give me your business card.
Hello.
Roll your window down so l can see.
Jesus!
Security's not where they're
supposed to be.
Neither am l.
Cappella.
It’s for you.
Yes.
l have a proposition for you.
Come on, sweetheart.
All right, you want to play.
Let's have some fun.
The Art of War.
Sun Tzu.
Chapter 13:
''The Doomed Spy. ''
Does any of this ring a bell?
''Sacrificing an agent
without his knowledge...
''...can turn the battle in your favor.
''Befriending you, gaining your trust...
''...all the while setting you up
to take the fall. ''
You disappointed me, Shaw.
You were always one step behind.
I’ve got to tell you, my friend.
By the time we're done with you...
...you're gonna make Lee Harvey Oswald
look like a fucking boy scout.
But first, we're gonna have a short class
on Pacific Rim social economics.
Specifically: The effect of
negative Chinese population density...
...and how it relates to
the African-American world view.
In other words, you're gonna watch me
put a bullet in little Miss Shanghai here.
Shit.
l was thinking, neighborhood rules.
Sounds good to me.
It’s nice when an opponent
raises the level of play.
You're too kind.
No, I’m not.
There's still one left in the chamber, amigo.
Tell me, master.
What are you gonna do now?
Move.
You all right?
Hello?
Get me out of here!
Hello!
Here's your paper.
Have a nice day, Miss Hooks.
Dramatic.
I’m just reading about your handiwork.
l was thinking of yours.
You betrayed me, Eleanor.
Shaw.
l thought our Eastern associates would've
made arrangements for you by now.
Staying alive is what you pay me for.
I’m curious.
What makes you think what you did
to Chan won't happen to you?
l don't like to speak ill of the dead...
...but between you and me,
and whoever's listening...
...David Chan was a self-inflated,
pig-headed asshole...
...who no doubt deserved
whatever came his way.
As for you, Shaw...
...you're still alive.
You just remember, Eleanor...
...what goes around comes around.
Sore loser.
Max, you missed the entrance.
Eleanor Hooks was my right-hand man.
She was my mentor.
She taught me
that a successful road to peace...
...is founded on a principle of action,
not reaction.
She said that if what l believed
to be the destiny...
...of the United Nations is to be fulfilled,
then we could not afford to wait around...
...and then react to
a member nation's call for help.
We have to anticipate
to diffuse volatile national...
...and international conditions
before they became explosive.
Before they led us to catastrophe.
It is in the memory of Eleanor Hooks...
Freeze!
...that l pledge the commitment
of this organization...
...to a policy of intervention,
a policy of leadership...
...a policy of aggressive peacekeeping.
Down on your knees!
Call the coroner.
-Ca va bien, Madame?
-Oui, oui.
Merci.
C'est la vie.
Excuse me, do I know you?
No, l don't think so.
Do l know you?
Maybe it was in another lifetime
or something.
-Have you eaten?
-l have not.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org