Fuck this.
- Let me inside!
- There's no way they're getting in.
Yes, there is.
- How much longer?
- 30 seconds.
- That's it!
- Let's go!
Son of a bitch.
Nobody's supposed to die.
You said nobody's supposed to die!
I lied.
TRANSIT
...Tuesday, so drink lots of water.
Temperatures are skyrocketing...
...and we're expecting...
...all major arteries coming to...
...route 962 is...
...take every precaution...
...four suspects fleeing the scene
no vehicle description...
...proceed with caution,
suspects are armed and...
Four armed suspects.
Repeat. Four armed suspects.
- Slow down.
- Yeah, right.
- Why are we heading west?
- They're talking about the 10.
Shit. I told you!
There's a roadblock ahead.
- What are we going to do now?
- Everyone calm down.
I told you to ditch that.
It's a murder weapon.
- Shit!
- Just cross the median.
Hey, Evers. Right. Turn right there.
LUCKY LOUIE'S
TRUCK STOP
So, now what?
- Dad, turn the shit off, please?
- Hey!
How long has he been
cursing like that?
I don't know. It stopped
being shocking six months ago.
Shane? When we get off the
interstate, you can play your music.
- Big mistake.
- You want to play your music?
You don't want his music.
It's all bitches and hoes.
Well, it is. Mom, yell at him!
There's a rest stop. Maybe we should
get something to drink?
- What are we going to do?
- Ditch the car. Go on foot.
120 miles to the boat?
We've got to cross tonight!
- Or chance it with the roadblock.
- No. We fit the description.
Okay, so... we split up.
We meet up on the other side.
One of us takes the bag,
hitches a ride to the port.
Fine, I'll do it.
- And go to Mexico without us?
- Exactly. We don't split up!
Evers. Go up and park.
Do it.
I can't even feel my left butt cheek.
Dad? Are we going
to be back by Thursday?
- Saturday.
- Shocker.
- Dave's having a pool party.
- We'll see. I said we'll see.
- Think fast!
- Kenny. What are you doing?
- You getting too old?
- Like hell I am.
- This won't work.
- It will, play it cool.
- I'm not feeling it.
- What do you think, baby?
Easy.
- Do it.
- This is bullshit!
You're starting to become a problem.
Leave the gun.
- I'm not going to shoot them.
- Leave the gun.
Go. Come on!
Dad? What's a "half-and-half"?
- Kenny, stop reading the walls.
- Is it something sexual?
It's something you put in your
coffee. Stop reading the walls.
Sweetheart, you almost ready?
Okay. Think fast, Kenny.
Fuck! Whose retarded
fucking idea was this?
- Lay off it.
- That bag is one-quarter mine.
It's one-quarter mine, too.
- Oh, my God. It's a parking lot.
- What's your hurry?
- Knock, knock.
- Who's there?
- Butch, Jimmy and Joe.
- Who?
Butch your arms around me,
Jimmy a kiss before you Joe.
- Knock, knock.
- Who's there?
- I got one. Knock, knock.
- Who gives a shit?
- Shane, watch your mouth.
Afternoon.
What's the problem, Officer?
Sir, I'm going to ask you
to pull over to the right, there.
Sure.
- How're you doing?
- Fine. What can I do for you?
Step out of the vehicle
for me, please.
- Mind if I search it?
- Sure, be my guest.
Step out of the car, please.
- You going camping?
- Yes, Sir.
- Who belongs to this?
- That's mine, it's a scanner.
I know what it is.
Why do you have it?
Is it against the law?
Would you mind telling us
what it is we've done wrong?
Thought you folks might have robbed
an armored truck near Baton Rouge.
I think I might remember that.
Clean.
You folks have a good day.
- Give us some props. It worked.
- I'll celebrate when I get the money.
- Run them off the road.
- That's not the plan.
There's no rush.
They're going our way.
- For how long?
- Losada, think about it.
They have Texas plates,
probably from Dallas or Houston.
A city family with a load of gear.
They're headed for the coast.
- I don't get it.
- Of course you don't.
Does she shut up when your dick
is in her mouth?
They're going camping
in the middle of nowhere. Alone.
Why'd you tell Shane we'd come back
earlier? We need this time together.
He's a teenager,
what do you expect?
What's your excuse?
Nobody wants to do this.
Nobody wants to reconnect,
we're just wasting time.
We decided we're doing this.
We're all here.
What more do you want?
I just...
I just want everything to be
like it was before.
- Still part of your plan?
- Fuck you.
- Just keep looking.
- Anybody see them?
- There they are!
- How are we going to get up there?
- Turn around!
- Everybody hang on.
- We got them.
- Good.
Hey. Jeff Gordon, watch your speed.
Dad? What's going on?
What are you doing? Slow down.
- Are you racing this guy?
- Everybody hold on.
- Make him pass.
- I don't think he wants to pass.
Don't let them get away.
One, two...
- Cop!
- I don't see him.
- Slow down.
- Get it over with.
Fuck!
Damn it, Nate.
- You're getting pulled over.
- Thanks for pointing that out.
- Get back in your vehicle.
- They were chasing us.
- You've got to go after them.
- No, they were piggybacking.
Speeding in your radar shadow,
letting you take the fall.
Worked, didn't it?
License and registration, please.
- If they find the money...
- They won't.
They don't know to look for it,
they're getting a speeding ticket.
It's just a setback.
Pull over at the next town,
wait for them.
Now we've got to wait
for our own money. That's right.
Please understand. I wouldn't make
up a story to avoid a lousy ticket.
Lousy ticket?
This is Louisiana, not Texas.
88 in a 50 here gets you reckless
driving, a class 2 misdemeanor.
Oh, no, no.
Officer, you can't do this.
- I can't? We've got laws here, Sir.
- I understand that.
A misdemeanor's going to get me
in a hell of a lot of trouble.
It'll put me
in violation of my parole.
- You're an ex-con?
- I just served 18 months in Elgin.
I'm not a violent offender,
it was just real estate fraud.
"Just". If you didn't
want back to Club Fed-
- you shouldn't have tried to break
the sound barrier on my road.
Get back in your vehicle.
We have a fair magistrate.
He'll be fascinated by
your story of being chased.
- Get back in your vehicle.
- Officer, please.
Whoa! Get on the ground!
Down on the ground, now!
On the ground, now.
All the way! All the way!
Put your hands behind your back.
I told you clearly to get back in
your vehicle. Did you listen? No.
- No, you did not.
- Shit.
- What are they doing?
- Looks like Daddy has a temper.
I'm going to have two kids
in college before long.
It was easy money. Secure loans
for some over-valued properties.
- Which is a gray area.
- But you got caught.
Buyer was a drug dealer and this
was part of a laundering scheme.
I had no idea.
That's why the IRS got involved.
It was a big mistake. Cost me 18
months, my broker's license...
...and the trust of my family.
- Is that your wife?
- 40 years and counting.
How do you do it?
I don't know. I guess, if you say
you're going to fix the screen door-
you'd better fix the screen door.
The first time you let her down,
she'll be waiting for the next time.
Dad got pulled over plenty of times,
and he never ended up like that.
When you break the law,
they don't trust you.
- It's not fair.
- Get used to it, Dad's a convict.
Shane, he's not a convict. He served
his time, he made a mistake.
He's in jail right now, isn't he?
They won't send him
back to Florida, right?
Guys, it was a misunderstanding.
- I like having Dad home again.
- I know you do.
Mom? Why don't you go inside?
We've got this.
Don't stay up too late.
We're going to be on the road early.
- It's heavy.
- Want me to help you?
I got it.
Yeah. I understand. Okay. Alright.
Judge is in Baton Rouge. He won't
be back until late tonight.
Why don't we let Mr. Sidwell
spend the night at the motel?
This man failed to cooperate with a
police officer. He is an ex-convict.
Okay, fine. You've made your point,
Lieutenant. Okay?
Tell your family you're
going to be here overnight.
What?
I'm sorry.
- Can we go back now?
- No. Not yet.
What is that?
- Holy shit!
- Shut up.
...investigation into the robbery in
Baton Rouge...
...suspects were armed
and shots were fired...
You know they're
getting divorced, right?
Dad said they weren't. Why would
they get divorced? He's back home.
Yeah, right.
Except now he's a lying fuck.
Nate?
- Damn it!
- Shit.
The largest robbery...
- Headquarters to Greenwell Springs.
- Greenwell Springs.
We received a call from the Springs
motel, possible 10-14 in progress.
- Copy.
- What's that mean? What's 10-14?
- Possible 10-14 at the Springs Motel.
- That's where my family is, right?
Get to the motel,
I'll see if I can raise Mike.
Where is it?
Call from the Springs Motel,
possible 10-14 in progress.
- We've got to go.
- Come on!
Help!
What happened? What happened?
Listen to me. Calm down.
- Paolo.
- Go for Paolo.
There's been an incident. Get down
here, and bring Mr. Sidwell with you.
On our way.
No me importa. Digale que Losada
lo llama. Esperare.
You gave it away. Four million
dollars, you gave it away.
What, you want to take a shot,
Losada? Let's see you try.
Don't fucking tempt me, you bitch.
Your boyfriend's the only thing
keeping you alive right now.
Oye, Oscar, soy yo...
Are you just going
to stand there and watch?
- Don't worry about it.
- I'm being serious.
It's all just a hiccup.
In 48 hours, we'll be on a beach,
drinking cervesas.
And making babies.
Yeah. That sounds nice.
Hey, Dad.
What did they want with us?
We're nice-looking
out-of-town people.
They think we've got nice things
they could sell for drug money.
- Hey, what's the story?
- They had another room.
Money must have been in there.
Cops advised them to go home.
- What about the boat?
- I've got that covered.
We can make it tomorrow. Right now,
we need the fucking money.
We just need to know
which way it's headed.
It's headed south.
They're going to keep going.
I want to go home. What part of that
do you not understand?
Sweetheart, please. Whoever it was
took off. Cops are outside.
They're reducing the ticket
so it's not a misdemeanor-
- and giving us a police escort
in the morning.
We've driven 200 miles, we can be
at the campground tomorrow.
Dad, I want to go home.
Well, that's two votes for home.
What about you, Kenny?
Hey, guys. Today was a lousy day.
No argument. This was the shittiest
day... oh, excuse my language.
This family is in trouble.
That's my fault, I know.
It was hard to be in your lives
from 2,000 miles away.
That's why we're doing this.
Hey. You guys know I used to come
down here to camp with my dad?
You know that?
Some of my greatest childhood
memories. You know that?
Kenny, Shane...
...we need to have
memories like that.
We need to get to know
each other again.
Robyn, if we turn back now,
what's going to become of us?
Shane?
Kenny?
- I want to go camping.
- That's good! - Come on, baby.
Let's see what they've got.
So, I'll see you guys
out to the town limits.
I'm sorry about everything.
All of it.
- Y'all have a safe trip.
- Yup.
Come on. That's the best you can do?
We can't take the cop. We've got to
get them in the next town.
We wait until the Bayou.
Take this path and intercept them.
- That's right.
- Are you sure about that?
Trust me.
You folks drive safe, now.
POSTED
PRIVATE PROPERTY
Dad? Dad? The bungee's loose,
can we fix it, please?
- Holy shit!
- Shane, watch your mouth!
- But it's a gator. Look at it!
- That's just a baby.
They're out there and will eat you.
Don't wander into muddy water, cher.
- Tie this one up, the top's undone.
- Cher, that be short for ma cheri.
"Kitty, what are you doing?
You've never been to the Thibodaux."
- "I know the Cajun way, you know!"
- Boys, get in the car.
Get in the car now!
- You lousy son of a bitch!
- What?
That's why we had to go camping
near the border.
- What are you talking about?
- Who are they, Nate? Who are they?
I almost got killed last night!
I can't believe you would do that
to your own family!
Your own kids.
What is wrong with you?
I'm leaving you here with the
only thing you give a shit about.
Robyn!
Roll the window down now.
Get over here!
Robyn!
Mom?
Shit!
- Mom, what happened?
- What's going on?
I don't know.
Your dad's in trouble again.
He took something that didn't belong
to him and someone wants it back.
Was that who broke into your room?
- Is Dad going back to prison?
- Who cares!
Who cares?
You are so stupid! Stupid!
Pull over, Mom. Come on.
Mom, pull over, get Dad. We'll
go home, everything will be fine.
- Mom!
- Run, boys, run!
Go! Get out of the car!
Get them!
Get the bag!
- It's not here!
- Where's the bag?
We don't have it!
Wait a minute. Where's Daddy?
Huh? Where's Daddy?
Why did you leave him
in the middle of nowhere?
No! No!
- Shane!
- Give me your phone!
- Shane, no!
- Don't do that again.
No! Shane! Get up. My god, Shane!
- Are you alright, baby?
- Don't hurt us, please.
We don't have the money.
I'm telling you the truth.
I left my husband on the road
back there. He has your money.
Then let's go get it.
Hey! Hey!
- No!
- You catch up. Come on.
Hey! Hey, hey!
Hey!
- You see what's happening?
- Marek's taking care of it.
Him and that bitch. I'm sure
they can divide four million by two.
Are you going to hurt him?
I don't know what scheme he's into.
Please don't hurt him.
What are you talking about?
Where is he?
Did my Dad steal
the money from you?
Your soccer coach dad steal money
from us? That's adorable.
- Money. Where's the money?
- Take it easy.
- I want the money.
- I want my family.
Where is it? - Go look around!
- Where is it?
- You let my family go.
What the fuck?
Get up.
Let them go.
Hey. Hey! Come on.
Let's get in the car.
Get in the car.
- You get up. Get up! Come on.
Get in.
- Yeah?
- How the hell did you miss him?
We got the Dad. He stashed the
money, wants to trade for the family.
Be right there.
- Turn around. Turn around!
Turn around! Let's go! Fuck!
You put a lot of trust in those two.
And you saw how easy it was
for them to leave us.
- He wouldn't. He needs you.
- That's right.
That's why I should
be calling the shots.
I'm the linchpin. His part is over.
Did you stash your guns
in somebody else's car?
Or did you rob
an armored truck with that one?
I'm going to cut your fucking yuppie
head off, if you don't shut up.
- I'm sorry.
- Please... let them go.
Where's the money?
Listen... we can
work this out. No!
Do you think you're
in a position to deal?
- I'll take you to it.
- Yes, you will.
Go get it.
Where is he?
You stay calm. Think about your kids.
Come on.
Where's the bag?
- Where's the bag?
- I thought we had a deal.
- What deal?
- The money for my family.
Yeah, so where's the money?
Let my family go
and I'll give you the money.
- Hey, asshole. Deal with me, not him.
- Who's in charge here?
- I am!
- Fuck you, man!
Shut your mouth,
I'm dealing with this!
Want to get on a boat to Mexico?
Push me again.
- Where's the bag? Where is it?
- Please get him off me.
- Let go. Let him go.
- What's wrong with you?
- I said lay off.
- You fucking asshole!
Don't even try it, shithead!
Go, Mom. Go!
Mom!
Holy shit!
Dad!
Slow down, slow down.
Mom, slow down.
- Close it!
- Call 911!
- They took the phones.
- What happened to your hand?
- Are you crazy?
- They don't have guns!
- We're fine.
- You guys okay?
- Nate, look.
- What?
- Okay, okay.
- Dad, what do we do?
Okay. It's 40 miles to the next town.
We've got to turn this around. We've
got to get back to Greenwell Springs.
You can do this, okay?
Sweetheart. Okay?
- Come here. Come here.
- I'm sorry.
Hey, they're coming back!
Come on!
- You didn't do anything, did you?
- No. These guys pulled a heist.
Remember that roadblock?
They used us to get through.
- Just give them the money.
- These guys are killers.
We have to try,
they're not going to give up.
Dad? Where's the money?
- Dad, where's the money?
- I lost it!
Kill the wife, kill the teenager.
Slit their throats.
Watch them bleed out.
Then put the knife to the kid. He'll
tell us where the money is then.
- What happened to the money?
- There was a guy in a boat.
He must have found it. That's
the only thing that makes sense.
About the only thing that makes
sense. Why did you hide the money?
I hid the money to have leverage
to get you back.
- I don't think like a criminal.
- Nate! Stop it!
Dad, a cop car!
Police! Police!
Hey, hey!
- Lieutenant!
- What happened?
Those guys are still after us.
- What guys?
The guys you arrested me for.
The guys you took me to jail for,
who attacked my wife!
- Slow down, Mr. Sidwell.
- They think we have their money!
What money?
From the robbery yesterday
in Baton Rouge.
Get them!
Dad, there's no way.
Dad!
Hang on!
Get down, everybody!
Hold on, everybody! Hold on!
Fuck!
Nate!
- Nate, where are you going?
- I don't know. Anywhere.
Here!
You alright?
Get the fuck off me, man!
Evers! Come with me. Grab that.
- Baby?
- Just leave me. Go with them.
Look at me. Look at me.
- It's all gone to shit, baby.
- But we're not done yet.
Fuck it. Let's go.
Hey. I'm not going to lose.
Not to this guy.
- See anything?
- No. Nothing yet.
Alright.
Watch your backs.
- Get your ass down!
- Dad, look! There!
Is that the boat
you were talking about?
Yeah. I think so.
- Are you okay?
- Is that the guy?
Shane. Damn it! Shane!
Hey. Where's the money?
The bag of money, you took it!
What are you talking about?
- Pardon me. We need your help.
- You didn't find a bag of money?
Forget about the money!
Are you accusing me of something?
Sir... I'm sorry.
We need your help. Please.
Some guys are trying to kill us.
Could you just take us out of here?
Please? For my family.
I did see a black car over there
driving up and down the highway.
Let me call the Sheriff.
Let's go, stay down!
Fucking great.
Now they've got a radio!
You'd get further in life if you
thought before opening your mouth.
Really? A lot further?
You're so smart, get out of this one.
We've followed your fucking lead.
And this is where you lead us!
This is not you, Evers.
I just want my cut, Marek.
I don't care how I get it.
You fucked this up!
You and that fucking bitch!
We had to pass the roadblock.
She got out of their car!
She let them get away!
She fucks it up every time.
You stand there like a fool.
You've seen her knee. That's broken.
You still need us. We don't need you.
We don't need you at all.
Wait! Wait, wait.
Do me a favor,
when you get the money?
- What's that?
- Choke on it!
Baby, look away.
Alright? Did you get
what you fucking wanted?
If we're done fucking around,
I suggest we go get our money.
Keep an eye out.
Shane! Damn it! Stay in the boat!
- Let me help, Dad.
- I've got it. You listen to me!
- You piece of shit!
- No, stop it!
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
Dad. You still don't get it.
Don't you see what you've done?
This is your fault.
- They're coming. I've got to go.
- Nate? Where are you going?
You watch your mouth, okay?
Here they come. Go! Go!
It's empty!
Okay, take the boat.
Keep Daddy alive.
And one more for leverage.
Is this like a shrimps place?
Kenny, come on.
Shit.
Hello? Hello, is anybody there?
Anybody? Fuck.
- Maintenance dispatch, who is this?
- I'm Shane Sidwell.
My family's in trouble,
we need the police.
He's okay.
Kenny, maybe he went to
give them the money back, or...
What are you doing?
- Oh, shit!
- Don't touch that. Don't touch that!
Mom, what is it?
- We didn't believe him.
- Oh my God.
Where is it?
- Where is it?
- I don't know.
- I lost it.
- Where's your family?
Where's yours?
If you don't give me my money,
I am going to kill you.
- I know.
- So what are you doing?
Fixing the screen door.
- Shane? Come in, Shane.
- I'm here. I'm right here.
Police are on their way,
will be there in half an hour.
- No, no. Mom. Mom!
- We're going to give them the money.
Dad was right. They won't let us go.
We saw them kill a fucking cop.
That money is keeping us alive.
We have to make a stand.
Kenny, get in there.
Sounds like
we just found your family.
- We have to keep one of them alive.
- They shot me!
Oh fuck!
- They've got the money inside!
- That's right, we've got it!
We'll burn every last dollar
unless you back off.
- We can't let them go.
- Fuck!
They're inside.
They've got the money.
Motherfucker.
We've got Daddy!
He's alive.
- Get out of this fucking car.
- Get out.
Throw out the money,
or I'll blow his fucking head off!
- You have three seconds.
- No, Shane! No!
- One!
- No, no! Shane!
- Two!
- You have to give it to them!
- We don't have a choice.
- Three!
Wait, wait. Wait.
Let him go.
Like hell.
Get down.
Watch your back.
Come on. Come on. Go!
- Go!
- Here they come!
Don't fucking move!
Don't fucking move.
Easy.
You've got nowhere left to run.
No!
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck!
Dad. Dad!
Kenny.