Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I mean, it's pretty dumb, but whatever.
Look at this.
Oh, my God, that's so pretty.
I love it. Thank you so much, Aunt Nicole.
Isn't it pretty, Brit?
Dad? More decaf?
So, you two. High school. That's pretty great.
I guess. It's gonna be sorta weird though.
Really?
Our school is kind of a feeder for New Trier's
so we're gonna know like a ton of people already.
Here, Annie.
Happy Birthday!
It's like the one you saw on The Hills, right?
I don't think The Hills are the
role models we were looking for.
It's a bit revealing, don't you think?
She's fourteen, you guys.
Yeah, no need to remind me.
- So. You did great.
- Mmm hmm!
Come on.
Come on what?
Give it to me.
What's she talking about?
It's a heavy box.
It's the new MacBook Pro.
It's got a four gigabyte hard drive
2.53 gigahertz proc--
What? I know what that means.
I think you're actually passing wind at this point.
Daddy.
It's getting late, Banannie.
Five more minutes, Dad, please? It's still my birthday.
15.
Promise.
Who are you talking to?
I'm chatting, Dad.
My friend Charlie from California.
He's a junior and plays volleyball for his high school.
Ooh, a junior. Well, he's obviously a very smart kid.
LOL. Laugh out loud. Right?
Nice one, Dad.
PWOMS?
"Parent watching over my shoulder."
And what is that?
"Laughing my ass off. Me too."
No, wait.
Dad, can you go talk to Mom about
mortgage payments or something.
All right. Good night, birthday girl.
Good night. Love you.
Love you.
All right. Let's see what you got.
There you go, ladies. Touch the line.
Make sure you're touching the line.
Last one. You're almost there.
Hey, Annie, come here!
This is Serena.
So, you're Peter Cameron's little sister.
Your brother's hot as shit.
Uh, thanks, I guess.
So, I'm having a little party
at my house Saturday night
and you, little Cameron, are invited.
Okay. Uh, thanks, Serena.
Tell your brother.
Is it deliberate?
No, not at all.
Hey, honey?
No phones at the table, please.
Sorry.
Katie, will you take a picture of me and Peter?
Hey, what did Mom just say?
I was just gonna send a photo to Charlie, but okay.
So, seriously, what's this guy's deal?
Well, he's smart. And funny.
His brother's being recruited
by UC Berkeley for football
and that's where he wants to go, but for volleyball.
Oh, right. The girl's sport.
What do his parents do?
His mom teaches kids with autism
and his dad works for ESPN.
I don't know, sweetheart.
Sounds like he's got too much
going for him for my likin'.
Hey.
Yeah, I know
what you're talking about.
I'm looking at them right now.
These are definitely for a clothing company, right?
So why isn't anybody wearing a shirt?
No, I'm kidding. Yeah. They're
good. Go with it. Okay. Bye.
Hi, Mom!
Hey, honey, how'd it go?
I made the team!
You did? That's great!
What happened?
Annie?
Come on. Where are you?
About time.
Hi, Charlie.
Where's mine, bozo?
What?
"I'm really 20. Sophomore at UC Berkeley."
Twenty?
Bye.
Hello.
Wow.
Hi, girls. So did your brother come with?
No, he's packing for college.
Great. Looks like I wore these for nothing.
Come join us.
We're teaching Alexa how to give a blow job.
She sucks. She keeps gagging.
Serena, where's your bathroom?
We have like six of them. Go
down the hall. You'll find one.
Hi, Dad.
Hey, sweetheart. You have a good time?
M m-hm.
Those girls kinda freaked me out though.
Yeah?
I-I really want them to like me, you know?
It means a lot.
Just be yourself.
If the Serenas of the world don't like it, it's their loss.
No, it's high school, Dad.
If the Serenas of the world don't like me
I'm screwed. You get it?
Not really, no. Sorry, I've, I've really gotta--
Yeah, okay.
'Night.
Is that Charlie?
Yeah, he has a big paper due tomorrow.
That picture he sent you is so hot. He's totally ripped.
Sh. Shut up. My mom.
I got donut holes.
They're very good. Here.
Who was that?
- It was Serena and Tanya.
- Oh.
Get anything good?
M m.
What?
She told me to buy a bra.
Oh, really? Let me see.
Classy.
- You saved the receipt though, right?
- Mom.
If you think you're ready for a bra like that
then we'll talk about it, okay?
Serena kinda made fun of her sports bra.
- Why?
- 'Cause it totally, like, flattens out my boobs.
She said that guys would think that I was hotter
if I, like, had a better bra.
Does, like, Serena say like all the time too?
Because, like, you never used to.
Sorry.
You don't have to dumb yourself
down for guys, like Serena.
You know that.
Maybe she thinks that's all she's got to offer.
Her parents own half of downtown
Chicago.
You get my point though, right?
Yes, Lynn.
It's a parking lot, moron. Go around!
Did you get my point?
Yeah, Mom. I get it.
Oh, for the love of--
- Bite me!
- Mom!
Yeah, I'm gonna get the steak sandwich
, medium, with grilled onions.
And can I get a side of chips, please?
Oh, I'm sorry, we don't--
He means French fries.
Twenty years here, he still can't say French fries.
I'm gonna have the same thing, actually,
except rare on the steak.
And to drink, we'll have a bottle of--
Really?
'92 Rothschild.
Fantastic selection.
So what are we celebrating?
So A & A wants to use us. For everything.
- They liked the campaign?
- Liked?
How 'bout I just got a phone call from the CEO
that was basically ten minutes of phone sex.
Hey, let me ask you something.
How old are you?
- Old enough.
- Oh.
I'm Claire, by the way.
Hi, Claire. I'm Al.
- That's Will.
- Hi.
Please let me know if there's anything else you need.
Anything?
Can you stop? She's nineteen.
One hour. That's all I ask.
Just one hour with that ass.
How's Barbara?
Oh, fuck off.
That is so weird.
Peter and I were just doing exactly
the same thing in his room.
Ah, Dad.
Okay. What now?
What? How old are you?
Why do you keep lying?
What?
Why do you keep lying to me?
Man, you won't believe
the stuff I'm finding in here.
I'll say. You wanna keep these Playboys?
What?
Just kidding.
Oh. Yeah, me too.
What, you packed 'em already?
Yeah, kinda.
You all right with this?
With what?
The whole college thing.
Yeah, I guess.
Don't feel pressured
into doing things you don't want to do.
Wait. This isn't another father-son talk, is it?
Oh, Dad, we had the sex talk, like, three years ago
and I still can't order a salad with cucumbers in it.
I just don't want you to lose sight
of what's important, like--
Taking responsibility for my actions
living up to my potential and personal expectations
staying true to my beliefs. Basically, being a man?
Something like that.
Relax, Pop. I got this. Trust me.
God. Come on. Let's hug it out.
I feel the same way.
You coming in, sweetheart? It's getting cold.
Hold on a sec.
Um, I'm talking to Brittany, Dad.
Two minutes.
Okay. Now go away.
Hi.
How do I know that?
Okay.
Well, are you still a virgin?
Good, 'cause that would have been creepy.
So, um, how old were you when you--?
Did you set the alarm?
Force field activated.
Is Annie upstairs?
She's in her room. Peter's still out.
Amen to that.
You heartless witch.
What?
You're happy he's going, aren't you?
Two words for you. Home gym.
His room's gonna look great with a treadmill in it.
Our poor kid is barely packed and
you're already redecorating.
What can I say? Except--good riddance!
Fuck.
Oh, for God's--
They're in their room.
Right now? Just a T-shirt and some underwear.
No. With just the T-shirt.
Okay.
Okay, it's dark now.
Oh, I guess. What is it?
No.
Okay.
Is that everything?
Yeah.
Katie, come give me a hug.
No. I don't want you to go.
So, I guess I'm gonna go to college now.
I love you. Email me, okay?
Okay. Hey, and check my tweets.
Okay, we gotta go, guys.
We'll see you later.
Bye. Bye, angel. Bye.
Hi. Uh, it's me again.
Where are you? I'm sitting on the bench just outside.
Annie?
Yes?
It's me. Charlie.
Hey, you.
God, I can't believe it's really you.
Look at you. You're gorgeous.
Is this a joke?
What?
No, it's me, Charlie.
What's wrong?
You're not 25.
Oh. Well, hey.
Don't get upset.
Annie, please.
Just give me a chance to explain.
It's me, Charlie.
I'm sorry, I, but--
Okay, all right. You're right.
I just couldn't think of a way to tell you.
You have to believe me.
Annie, please. Please?
Don't get upset. You're killing me here.
Annie? It's still me. Okay?
Forget the age thing. All that
stuff that we talked about?
All the things that we shared? It's me. Charlie.
I'm sitting right here next to you.
Why do you keep lying to me?
Because of this.
I was, I was afraid
that you wouldn't be mature enough to understand.
Annie, when you connect with someone
the way that we connected
when you find a soul mate the
way that we found each other
then nothing else matters.
I thought you were old enough to understand that.
I mean, you made me think
you could handle this, Annie.
I mean, this is ridiculous.
I mean, it's me, Charlie.
The same guy that you've been talking
to every day and every night
for the last two months.
I love you.
Annie.
And I don't get why age has to change that.
Can we just walk a bit? Huh?
Talk a little bit more.
Just for a couple of minutes
before I have my long drive back to the airport?
Come on. Just--
I was just looking forward to seeing you so much.
I thought we were friends at least, Annie.
This remind you of anything?
I was just thinking that. Your year abroad in London.
All these American students come in. I saw this girl.
Love at first sight.
Didn't work out. I ended up with you.
There.
Sorry.
Go ahead, spin it.
The candy's weird. It's better without it.
Can I have some of yours?
Oh.
Yeah. You win. Pistachio rocks.
So Peter took off, huh?
You must be so excited.
Yeah, I'm happy for him.
I'm just gonna miss him, that's all.
I just hope he doesn't get caught up
into that whole fraternity rush thing.
Sounds so stupid.
Yeah, there's definitely some
stupid stuff involved, but
I have to say I was a Delt
and there were some great things about it, too.
I met some, some quality guys that
I hope will be friends for life.
Yeah, I just, when he drinks he kind of loses control.
This one time he tried to text me
the sound of him vomiting.
It's kind of tough to spell.
It's kind of-- I, I don't know.
It's like, "UG," I don't know. But...
I just hope he doesn't just do it to party and get laid.
But, yeah, I guess that's what college is for, right?
Finding out for yourself, finding out who you are.
What?
Nothing.
It's just
you amaze me. Seriously.
You're so intelligent and sensitive, like
wise beyond your years.
It's just amazing, that's all.
Hey.
Want me to teach you the secret Delt handshake?
Okay.
You can't tell anyone.
I won't.
Okay.
Stick out your hand
like you're gonna shake mine.
So--
So.
You still mad at me?
No, not really.
Wanna check out your present?
Oh, yeah.
You said you'd want one in red, so--
It's sexy, right?
I can't tell you how many times
I've thought about you in it.
It's crazy, I'm so nervous and excited
to be sitting here with you finally after all this time.
There.
Happy?
You look ridiculously sexy.
No, don't go.
I'm serious.
Come here.
Come sit down.
Have you thought about us like this?
I know you have because you
told me about it, didn't you?
You don't think my body's weird?
Are you kidding?
You're, you're gorgeous.
So you're not-- disappointed or anything?
Annie. Annie.
You're perfect.
You take my breath away.
Can I just--?
No, wait, Charlie, wait. Hold on.
It's okay.
Charlie--
Charlie, wait.
Charlie.
It's okay, Annie. Don't worry.
I'm just taking these off.
Oh. Hold still, Annie. I've gotta take these off, too.
That's my girl.
Oh, God. Look at you.
This is perfect.
How about the boys in class?
They're okay.
Are they?
Um, we're making bowls in pottery class, but
mine looks like an ashtray
which is kind of funny because I don't smoke.
Nice.
How 'bout you, Annie? How's school?
Annie.
Hm?
School. How is it?
Annie?
He's so cute.
I know.
You should go out with him.
Did you get my text?
M m-hm.
Why didn't you call me back?
Check it out, Annie. Your boyfriend.
Ow!
I told you before. He's not my boyfriend.
You keep saying that.
Makes me think you like him.
If you're so obsessed with him, why you fuck him?
- What's your problem?
- Yeah? He's cute!
Pick up, please pick up.
Is this about Charlie?
No. No.
Annie, what happened?
That was him at the mall, wasn't it?
How old is he?
It doesn't matter.
Annie, wait.
Oh, my God.
It's not that big a deal.
We met up on Saturday. We had sex.
We're in love.
Oh, my God.
Now just drop it. I'm serious.
The word ciao
comes from schiavo, or servant, and was used as--
Sorry to interrupt, uh
mind if I borrow Annie Cameron for a second?
Ms. Worley, why are we going this way?
Oh, it's all right, Annie. Come on in.
Why don't you have a seat?
I know, yeah.
Holy shit! Dude, dude.
No, it's Antigua. Anguilla
is a totally different island.
Honestly, I was hoping to get the crew
and the equipment in the same place.
Yeah. Hang on. Hang on just a second.
Hello. Speaking.
Sorry, I, I don't understand.
Will. Will!
What happened?
They won't tell me anything.
I just, I just got here, and I--
Excuse me. Annie Cameron. We're the parents.
Let me find the nurse.
M r. and M rs. Cameron?
I'm Officer Gomez.
Your daughter wants you to know that she's okay, but
maybe you should have a seat.
- What's going on?
- What?
We don't know exactly what's happened.
What we do know so far
is that we think she was assaulted
by her alleged boyfriend three days ago.
She hasn't got a boyfriend.
Well, apparently on Saturday
she met up with a man she calls Charlie
at a motel, where she was sexually assaulted.
The man is at least 35 years old.
Jesus Christ. Where is she?
She's in an exam room with the nurse
collecting evidence for the rape kit. She's okay.
One of the counselors from the hospital is with her.
I have to see her.
Look, there is a private waiting
room just down the hall--
We have to see her right now!
We want to see her right now.
She's having an exam. You'll see her in a minute.
I'm almost done.
I just need to get one more picture of that abrasion.
This is fucking insane.
Oh, baby.
It's okay. We're here. We're here now.
M r. and M rs. Cameron, I'm Gail Friedman.
I'm a counselor with the hospital.
I'm glad you're here.
- Annie here is an amazing young woman.
- Gail.
- Ah. This is Special Agent Doug Tate with the FB I.
- Hi.
FB I?
Well, any time a crime is committed
against a child using the I nternet
and the suspect is a traveler
someone from out of state, they call us in.
Look, Annie, I know you've had a rough day.
But I need to ask you a couple of
questions. You feel up for it?
Do we have to do this now?
Trust me, the sooner we start
this investigation, the better.
Gail, do we still have the clothes
she was wearing that night?
- Yes.
- Are they here?
No, they're at her house.
Okay, I need to get those from
you as soon as possible.
Is that okay?
Yeah, I guess.
M r. Cameron, M rs. Cameron
I would like to talk to Annie alone.
Could you please just--
Look, I've had enough of this.
This is our daughter. We wanna be with her.
You've got to understand that right now
Annie's a victim of a crime and you
and your wife are just witnesses.
That's why we interview everybody separately
so as not to contaminate anyone's testimony.
Now if you can just give Annie and I a second alone
and then I 'Il come back to your house
and we can all sit down and talk.
Fair enough?
So how long will this take?
Well, it depends if we get enough
genetic material to run a profile.
And if there is, how long?
Right now, there's a nationwide backlog.
I n I Ilinois alone, we've got 2 ,000 unopened kits
sitting in freezers waiting to be processed.
Some people have been waiting a year.
- What?
- How is that possible?
We'll run this through the FB I facilities.
So, two weeks, a month on the outside.
A month?
Now can I see the family computer?
Doug.
Yeah.
- Did you copy the hard drive?
- Yup.
- We'll take that with the evidence down to the lab.
- Okay.
Apart from Teen Chat
were there any other networking sites
you used to communicate?
No, not really.
Did you guys ever speak on the phone?
You spoke to him.
Now, you said his mother was sick.
Yeah. Cancer.
Yeah, okay.
Tell him you feel awful about his mother
that you really wanna talk to him
that you lost an uncle to cancer.
I-I don't know.
You don't know what?
I just don't wanna lie to him.
What are you talking about,
sweetheart? He lied to you.
What do you think of writing to him
and just telling him how you feel?
Yeah, Annie. Would that be good?
Yeah, I guess.
Okay, good.
Okay, just keep it simple. Be yourself.
Maybe he didn't even like me.
He didn't.
Will!
It wasn't like that, sweetheart.
The man tricked you.
What?
- Is that him?
- Charlie.
Okay, now, remember, he's gonna test you
to see if you told anybody. You haven't, okay?
Tell him that you're concerned
and a little worried that he hasn't called. Okay?
Should I?
Yeah, answer him. Yeah.
A-are, are you guys tracing this?
Yes.
It says private. What do I do to answer it?
Frank, are we good?
We're good.
Annie? Look at me? Just, just talk to him.
All right?
Okay.
Hello?
Annie?
Charlie?
Hi.
It's kinda late. Where are your parents?
They took Katie to the movies.
Charlie?
Shit.
Shame on you, Annie.
Charlie?
Charlie, are you there?
Damn it!
Frank, did we get it?
Well, that's it. He's gone.
Why did you make me do that?
Annie!
He probably got your
cell number off your website.
Look, I 'Il give you a call
when I get back from the motel.
Tell me something. Did she yell for help?
I mean, did she scream, tell him to stop?
Just because she didn't scream for help
does not mean this wasn't rape.
Now that guy is 20 years older than she is.
He groomed her for weeks just
to get her into the motel room
and she's armed with what? The eighth-grade biology
and the expectation that the world is a decent place.
I'm gonna fucking kill this guy.
No, you won't. That's why I'm
here. Now, we will find him.
And what am I supposed to do?
You go back inside, you support your daughter
and you let us do our job.
What, with just five of you guys
working the whole state?
There's gotta be something I can do. I'm
not just gonna stand around and wait--
M r. Cameron, I promise you.
I put everything I got into these cases.
You just gotta give us a chance.
Now, my cell is on the back.
You call me if you need anything.
I 'Il drop you a line tomorrow when
I get back from the motel.
You want me to sleep with you tonight?
No, I just want my blanket.
No, please, stop.
Stop, please!
Dad, please help me to stop him.
Please, Dad, help!
Don't. Please, Dad, help me, please.
Stop! No!
Will.
You all right, buddy?
Yeah, of course.
If M rs. Van Dersey wants the meeting, fine.
But I think that we should dictate the parameters.
No more of this bullshit.
Good.
Is there any more coffee?
Grab another coffee.
Hey. I got you a new cell.
Now, you have to promise me
that you're not gonna try and call him
or text him with this new number.
Remember what Tate said about the old one
that if he tries to call you on that,
you tell us immediately.
I'm gonna have to check the bills.
And if I find out that you've tried to contact him
I'm gonna have to take it back.
Okay?
So what? Do I just start talking like Tony Soprano?
Boy, I hope not.
I'm glad you came.
Yeah, well, my parents said I had to.
Well, even so, I'm still glad.
I want this to be a place
for you to feel safe and comfortable
talking about anything.
I just wanna be helpful to you.
You think I need help?
I think that what you've been through
must be very difficult.
You know, what's the big deal?
There are girls at my school
who've had sex with half the football team.
I lose my virginity and my parents
make a federal case out of it.
Literally.
I think they're more concerned
that you may have been in danger
more than anything else.
Danger?
That's 'cause they don't know him.
You know, the thing is
I bet my dad would really like him
if they'd met, you know, before.
What is it about him you think your father would like?
He's sweet, and smart, and really funny.
And gives great advice and which
, by the way, worked.
I-I made the team because of him.
You think that's the only reason you made the team?
Because of his advice, and not your own ability?
Well, he's older. He's been playing longer.
What'd you think about him being older?
At first I thought he was 16, okay?
And then, all of a sudden he's 20 and I'm like, what?
And then we kept talking
and I was, like, what's the big deal?
He gets me, you know?
He's not judgmental.
He's encouraging.
And despite my age difference he still loves me.
And he thinks I'm beautiful.
What'd you think about him
not being honest about his age?
You know, Charlie said that
when you connect like we did
when you find that soul mate
that's the only thing to think about.
Don't you believe that when two people are in love
nothing else matters?
I can understand how strong those feelings are, Annie.
But, there are reasons why girls your age and men his
aren't supposed to be together.
Whatever.
He loves me. I know he does.
And he's dying to call me or email me
but he knows it's not safe
thanks to my parents and the FB I.
I just--
What?
I just hope he's okay.
What, he go to lunch early?
He went home. Said he wasn't feeling well.
Hello?
Will, it's Agent Tate.
I wanted to give you an update.
Now, look, the motel didn't give us much.
He paid cash for the room.
He told the manager he lost his wallet.
He even ordered a credit card right in front of him.
The, uh, the cell phone was prepaid
. It was purchased in St. Louis.
He paid cash for that, too, whoever he is.
So his name's not Charles Hightower.
Yeah, not that we can tell.
I found seven of them living in the U.S. so far
but none of 'em fit the description.
There's nothing that even confirms he's from California
we, uh, we actually traced his IP
address to the Czech Republic.
What?
It seems he's running some sort of ghost program.
It's a software that basically bounces
his IP address from one server to another
all over the world.
Sir?
Sorry, I don't understand.
What does that mean?
It means he's good at what he's doing.
But don't worry, don't worry.
This is exactly how it starts.
You need to go on through, go get your stuff.
Yeah, one minute, please.
What about the car? Anything?
Hang up the phone, sir.
It was an airport rental. He must've
swapped the plates.
Gary!
Look, I'm, I 'Il have to call you back. Okay?
Seriously, is my conversation
that much of a threat to security?
Thank you, sir.
Is it over?
Yeah, you missed a pretty good fight.
When they do Real Housewives of Chicago
I am so auditioning.
Yeah, right.
I talked to Jennie.
Brittany's really upset you won't call her back.
Good.
She was only trying to help, honey.
Yeah, well, she's a bitch.
No, she's your best friend.
Best friends don't narc on each other.
Not like she'll ever get a boyfriend
but if she does, I hope someone ruins it for her, too.
Lynn?
Did you get my message?
Yeah, I called you back
but it went to voice mail. Did you eat?
Have a look at this a second.
You won't believe this.
What is this?
This is the National Sex Offenders Registry.
There's perverts all over Wilmette, not just Chicago.
See this? All these red dots.
They're everywhere.
Oh, my God.
This guy here is literally three blocks away on Linden.
What's going on?
Hi, sweetheart. Um, come here a second.
I, I need you to do something for me.
These men are all registered sex
offenders in the neighborhood
that fit the description.
I need you to look through them.
Why?
I n case one of them's Charlie.
What?
No. N-- No.
Honey, you should. One of them could be him.
None of them's him.
Forget the hair and the mustaches.
Just look at the face.
Could any of them be him?
I said, no.
God, what's your problem?
My problem is you were attacked.
It wasn't like that.
Besides, none of them are Charlie, okay?
Are we done?
PervertTracker. What is this?
It's a group I met with today.
Supposed to be the best in the
country. They hunt predators.
Today? It says they're in New Jersey.
You were in New Jersey today?
You got on a plane today without telling me?
Are you fucking kidding me?
I swear to God, Will
if you ever get on a plane again without telling me
I swear to God, I don't know what I'd do.
I'm sorry.
Honey, you're right. I'm sorry.
I'm gonna go check on her.
I've gotta get out of my house.
How come? What's happening at home?
You know, they think I'm stupid
for meeting up with him.
Going back to his hotel.
They said that?
My dad looks at me like I'm an idiot.
He wants to kill Charlie. That's all he talks about.
Getting his hands on him.
Well, what would you do if he got in touch with you
have you thought about what you would say to him?
I just wanna talk to him. Hear his voice.
See how his mom's doing, and his little dog.
See how we're gonna make this work.
I just wanna talk to him about what happened.
We haven't really talked about that
about what happened in the motel.
Are we supposed to?
I n my experience, it helps. It really does.
But only if you're ready.
It's kind of weird, you know.
Like it wasn't really happening to me.
Like I was watching it from above.
Sometimes when you can't physically
escape from a situation
where you feel frightened or threatened
you find a way to remove or distance
yourself psychologically.
It's a way of protecting yourself.
Does that make sense?
Still have ten minutes.
Yeah, well. I 'Il see you later.
Chicago has a very strong sense of history.
Kinda like when they bought Marshall
Fields, turned it into a Macy's.
They lost half their client base.
It's a fine line. You want a fresh look
but you don't want to alienate your loyal customers.
We loved what you did with A & A
particularly in the tween market.
Well, that was mostly Will's work here.
Well, I don't know if that's true
but I'm very happy to take the credit.
Rebecca?
Becky.
Jerry?
Yeah.
Hi, Jerry.
Look at you. You're gorgeous.
You really think so?
Yeah. Can't believe it's you.
Did you bring your stuff?
Uh--
Fuck!
Hey! Hey! Stop! FBI!
Hey, get that guy!
Go, guys, get him, get him! Come on!
Hey!
Actually, there's a lot of similarities
between your company and Academic Appeal.
It's just you have a much more
sophisticated client base.
Everybody wants to broaden their consumer appeal
especially in the tween market.
I mean, it's like the Holy Grail of--
Sorry, would you just excuse me a minute?
Look, I'm really sorry, Will.
So what made you think he was our guy?
The program he was running to scatter his I P address
the chat rooms he used.
Mostly, Will, it was his conversation.
It was the way he spoke.
It was very similar to the way Charlie chatted.
How do you know that?
I was able to get transcripts of
two months worth of I M chats
between him and your daughter from Teen Chat.
You're kidding.
No. I'm not.
So when can I see them?
You can't, Will.
It's an ongoing investigation.
I'd completely lose Annie's trust.
Now, I do have some good news.
The lab was able to extract enough DNA for a profile.
We're gonna run it through CODIS
, the national database
and if there's a hit we should know
within a week or two at the most.
Hey, I 'Il be right back. I gotta call in.
Lynn.
Will, what are you doing here?
I just came from seeing Tate.
What's wrong?
You're not gonna believe this.
What? What is this?
Read it.
What is it?
Just read it.
"I can't stop thinking about it."
"You inside me. I get wet when I picture it."
Okay, stop.
Our daughter wrote this.
Annie.
"How big are you? I bet you taste good."
Will, stop it.
"I wanna see it right now."
Stop it, Jesus God!
I mean, she's 14. Where the hell did she learn this?
She's 14, she didn't make this happen!
Yeah, but we're gonna have to talk to her about this.
- You are not gonna talk to her.
- But look at it!
Our daughter sounds like a fucking porn star!
You cannot confront her about this.
- I'm gonna kill him.
- No.
I swear to God, I'm gonna find
this animal and I'm gonna fucking kill him!
Stop it!
Oh, my God. You're acting crazy, Will.
No, you're not gonna-- You're not gonna read this.
Just leave it alone. Give it to me.
I 'Il see you tonight.
Now I need you to bring
that back to me right now, Will.
I 'Il get it back to you tomorrow.
You do know it's a federal crime, right?
I just think I have a right to know
who my daughter's talking to.
No, no, no. You are interfering with the investigation.
You've betrayed your daughter's trust to me.
She doesn't need to know.
You're not letting me do my job, M r. Cameron.
I need you to bring them back to me right now, Will.
Yeah, I will. I 'Il get it back to you.
Right--
Oh, you son of a bitch.
Hey, stranger.
This is something, huh?
Oh, yeah, it's great. I feel 80.
Mojito?
I'm fine, thanks.
Hey, great party, man.
Will, come here!
Will. Are you all right?
No, I'm, I'm, I'm just feeling, I'm--
S-- Sorry.
Will? Will!
I heard the door.
That was me.
I, I couldn't sleep. I took a drive.
Well, you scared me.
Will, you scared me.
Sorry.
All right, so, are you coming up?
In a bit.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Is this you?
Are you, are you Sad Little Girl?
What are you doing?
You're posing as a teenage girl
to chat with men on line, seriously?
That's what they do. They showed me.
Oh, my God.
It's a way of drawing them out.
Good night.
I spoke to Pete today.
He's coming home for Halloween.
Well, he said he would
try. He's got a lot of work.
But, and he sounds good. Happy.
You didn't tell him, did you?
No. But I--
Don't, okay?
Oh, about what? What?
Remember what we talked about upstairs, sweetie
about Annie being hurt?
I'm serious, okay?
Okay.
How 'bout we go to the movies this weekend?
Is there anything you wanna see?
Nothing you'd be interested in.
Well, try me. I may surprise you.
Yeah, right.
What does that mean?
Why are you being so mean to me? What did I do?
I'm not being mean.
Katie, am I being mean?
No.
How 'bout we go on a bike ride this weekend?
Well, yeah. Uh, can we also go along the lake?
Yeah. And we can go to that
favorite rock that you like.
Cool.
Great.
You know, you don't have to do this, honey.
Yeah, I know.
Well, call me if you need anything, okay?
Honey? Give me a kiss.
I love you.
See you later.
Okay.
You're gonna have to talk to me sometime.
I'm really sorry, Annie, okay?
I didn't know what else to do.
Annie?
You're sorry?
Yeah.
Do you realize what you did?
You fucked up everything.
Charlie, my parents, everything.
I was scared, okay?
No. It's not okay.
I kept every secret of yours.
Annie, you're my best friend and
I was worried about you.
"Was." I was your best friend.
Do me a favor and never talk to me again.
Annie.
Annie!
That was fucking embarrassing
at the big launch party.
Oh, yeah, I know, I'm sorry.
It was just some personal stuff. It was nothing.
You're sure?
Because you've been kind of M IA around here lately.
There just could not be a worse time to be distracted
while I really need your head in the game.
What, you don't think I'm giving a 100 %, Coach?
Well, you tell me. I put this on your desk a week ago.
Mel's been waiting since Monday
for you to sign off on this.
Well, tell him, then, fine. Run with it.
You haven't even looked at it, have you?
What the hell's going on?
It's Annie.
She was sexually assaulted.
What?
Oh, my God.
I had no idea, Will.
She's fine. I mean, she wasn't, but she's okay.
They catch the guy?
They're looking for him.
They started with the crime scene in the motel.
Jesus. She was kidnapped?
No, she-- She sort of knew the guy.
I-- I don't understand.
It was someone she met online
someone she'd been talking to for a while.
Oh, I thought you meant she was
like attacked, you know. I--
You scared the shit out of me.
She was raped.
She's 14. The guy's in his 30s.
I know, I know. It's just that I was picturing--
Well, you don't wanna know what I was picturing.
Could have been much worse.
Hey, can I come in?
I guess. What's up?
How was school?
Okay.
Was it weird seeing your friends again?
It was fine, Dad.
Did you see Gail today?
No, tomorrow.
How, how's that going?
Great. I'm cured.
Still no contact from "Charlie"?
I hate when you do that.
Say his name like that.
It's not his real name, is it?
What do you want, Dad?
Has there been any contact?
No.
None at all?
What, you don't believe me?
You wanna check my phone?
Would you have a problem with that?
Yeah, I would.
Why, if there's nothing to hide
why would that be a problem?
You're unbelievable.
What?
Take it. What's your problem?
What is my problem? My problem
is you lied to me, sweetheart.
From the second that you knew he wasn't
15, you should have told me
and you didn't. You lied.
Why didn't you come and talk to me or your mother
and say what was going on?
When you found out for the first time, what--
What were you thinking?
You didn't know then that something was wrong?
When you, you met him in the mall
and saw him for the first time
what do you do, you don't call
me? You don't run away?
You get in a car with him? It's like rule number one.
You know, I'm trying to understa--
Please just leave me alone.
But talk to me. I--
You're just pissed you didn't know.
No, that's not--
No, everything would've been fine
if everyone would've just chilled out.
- What are you talking about?
- Charlie and me.
Are you out of your mind?
You're the crazy one!
Checking my phone,
bringing out sickos on the web.
I'm trying to find the scumbag!
He's not like that!
You don't even know him!
My God, you're protecting him. The guy raped you.
And you're protecting him.
He didn't rape me!
Get out, get out of my fucking room right now!
I hate you. Get out!
Get out!
Get out of my room!
I just wanted to know how Annie's doing.
You know I can't discuss her treatment
with you, M r. Cameron.
I'm sorry, but this still doesn't make sense to me.
She's my daughter. A minor.
If she needed an appendectomy
you'd need my signature for surgery, right?
Therapy is different.
Yeah, but this whole--
None of this makes sense to me.
And I'm really starting to--
What's going on?
I cannot stop thinking about it.
I'm driving my car
whatever, in the office, in a meeting
and I think about him on top of her.
The other night I had this dream. I'd got him.
I was beating the life out of him.
I was on top of him and I was punching him
and punching him and his face was caving in
there was blood going everywhere
and I could actually taste it.
I woke up, I found I'd actually chewed
the inside of my mouth.
It's my own blood I was tasting.
What if they did catch him and they put him
in jail him. How would that make you feel?
Good. Relieved.
Angry.
Why angry?
Because I'd still want to rip
his fucking head off and now I couldn't.
What else are you angry about?
I'm angry I didn't know what was going on.
I'm angry that Annie lied to me.
That I didn't know the extent of her intimacy with him.
That I couldn't--
What?
Stop it?
We can't control what happens to us or our loved ones.
What happens when Annie goes to college?
What are you saying?
People get hurt.
There's only so much we can do
to protect ourselves, our children.
The only thing we can do
is we can be there for each other
when we do fall down, to pick each other up.
Ugh!
Can I help you with anything today, sir?
Hey, Pop!
Hey.
You look older.
It's only been six weeks, smart ass.
Yeah, still, maybe it's, uh
like Einstein's special relativity.
You know, six weeks to me, five years to you.
I think I preferred you with
a high school education.
Dude. No way. I don't
want you to hurt yourself.
So how was the ride in?
Okay.
Okay. I'm still a little, ech.
Oh. Big night, eh?
I was off my face, wasn't I?
Come here.
Jesus, Pop. What is it?
Where are the kids?
Come on, kids. Hurry
up, the food's gonna be cold.
All right, ready?
Hey!
It's fantastic.
Look at the toilet seat cover.
It was her idea.
Let me help you off with your flippers so you can eat.
No, Mom, that's cheating.
That's not a very scary mask, Pete.
It is to Grandpa.
Don't get me started.
He's a socialist.
Oh, Cal, now come on.
No costume, Annie?
This is my costume.
You're not supposed to wear a penguin
you're supposed to be a penguin.
Do you want me to come or not?
Okay. I guess you can come.
I'm sorry I didn't get to email much.
You know, things have been really crazy.
It's no big deal.
No. No, I should have called more. Checked in a bit.
You know I love you, right? Right?
Did you kids ever hear the story
about when Grandpa and I met on Halloween?
He asked me to take a picture of him
next to this statue of a werewolf.
They've all heard the story, Susan.
No, no, we haven't.
Okay, good.
So, he goes up
and he stands right under it
trying to impress me, of course.
But it turns out it's just a guy in a costume, right, hon?
And he grabs Grandpa.
And Grandpa starts screamin' like a girl.
- I did not.
-  You did.
Annie, honey. Is that corn cold?
Because I could heat it up for you, sweetie.
M m. It's fine.
Annie, you have to try the sweet
potatoes. They are amazing.
Oh, they are, sweetheart, they are. Just,
just have a little. You'll love 'em.
You guys wanna cut my steak, too?
So, I hear you got a girl, Pete.
What? No. No, God, no.
No, it's just this girl I met at a mixer.
Yeah, she's a DG.
But we're not-- you know, we're just friends.
She's super athletic though. She
plays tennis and lacrosse.
You'd really like her.
Cool.
But, you know, she's, she's not
my girlfriend or anything.
We just started hanging out.
Yeah.
Peter, it's okay for you to have a girlfriend.
It's pretty normal. Right, Dad?
I'm not sure I understand.
You don't understand?
Have you guys had sex yet?
Annie.
Was she good?
That's enough.
What?
You can tell everybody about my life
about me having sex and who
with, but I can't ask him?
I asked you not to tell him.
That's the only thing I asked.
Thank you, Dad.
I hope you guys have an awesome time.
Honey, please, please stay.
No. No. Let me go.
Okay. Good news.
We ran the DNA from his shirt
through the national database.
And we actually found a match.
That's, that's incredible.
So what happens now? You arrest him?
It's not that easy.
While the DNA is on the database
it's still a John Doe. We don't know who it belongs to.
I don't understand.
Well, there were other cases, Will
three of them, where rapes were reported.
We were able to recover genetic material
from the victim and the crime scene.
The DNA profile is the same.
It's just that we don't know who it belongs to.
So he's done this before.
- Yes, he has.
-  Oh, my God.
Well, he's had other girlfriends before. I told you that.
These weren't girlfriends, Annie.
These were minors who reported a rape.
Well, DNA can be wrong.
The odds of these four samples not
coming from the same person
are in the hundreds of millions. It's the same guy.
Now, look. We, uh, we don't normally do this.
We're very careful with victim information.
But I'm hoping there might be some kind
of connection between all four of you girls.
Maybe you went to the same camp together
you shopped at the same mall.
I can't give you their names but I was hoping that
you might take a look at their pictures.
Wait a minute. I don't
know if this is a good idea.
No, no. I want, I want to. Yeah.
All right, Annie, do you know this girl?
She's from Cleveland.
She's fifteen years old.
No.
No? Okay.
This is the M ilwaukee case.
This photo was taken about a year ago.
She's fourteen.
Now, this girl was assaulted in
St. Louis seven months ago.
She's twelve.
Oh, my God.
I don't, I don't know them.
Okay. It's okay. You did a good job.
Thank you, Annie.
Honey.
No. I'm fine. I just need a second.
So you're telling me the FB I's been
chasing this guy for years?
It looks that way, yeah.
Look, on the upside, Will there's
more information for us.
There's more evidence for us.
The investigation is seeing a real breakthrough.
I bet the agent in St. Louis said the same thing
to some family about seven months ago.
I understand your frustration, Will, I do
but I'm working as hard as I can for Annie.
Yeah, but it's not enough, is it?
I mean, that sick fuck is still out
there grooming other girls, right?
Will, I'm doing all I can. I'm sorry
you don't see it that way.
Annie? Annie!
Did she come down here?
You okay?
You want something to drink? Water?
There were other girls.
What other girls? Tell me what you mean.
Charlie. He had other girls.
Three of them. Like me.
There were other victims, you mean?
He said that I was special.
That I was the only one for him.
But if there are other girls--
They weren't even-- They weren't even that pretty!
Tell me why it matters.
No. No. No.
Why does that matter?
Because they were just like me.
He told me, he said I was pretty.
What's wrong with me?
Why does it mean that something's wrong with you?
If he lied to me the way he lied to those
other girls, he never loved me.
He lied so he could have sex with me.
What, Annie?
Oh, my God.
He raped me.
He, he raped me.
How could I have been so stupid?
All he wanted-- My God.
All he wanted was--
God, I'm so sorry.
Oh, God. She's finally asleep.
This guy is one sick fuck.
Will, I'm so worried about her. I've
never seen her like this. I'm just--
He's just destroyed her.
He sent her a picture of his dick.
Please stop looking at this shit!
What are you doing?
What the f-- What are you doing?
Why are you down here when you
should be up there with her?
You think finding this guy is more important
that it's gonna make her better? Do you think that--
Well, it might. Or it might save
some other poor fucking girl.
I want this guy out of my house.
I want him out of my house!
You want me to go up there
and talk to her? I've tried.
She won't fucking talk to me!
Shut up!
She finally fell asleep.
You'd fucking know that if you were up there with her.
It's Annie. It's Annie.
She is in pain. She needs you and you're just--
You're sitting there doing nothing!
All right.
Here, here you go.
Cameron!
Look, Vicki's sick. She can't play today.
You're gonna start in her place.
I don't know, Coach. I--
We need you, Annie.
Can I count on you?
Yeah.
That's the spirit.
At the net.
Annie! Harder!
Hey, guys. Hi, Lynn.
Hey.
You having fun? Yeah?
Dig in!
Nice set!
Block it!
You having a good time?
Huh?
You enjoying this, looking at all the young girls?
What's that?
You sick fuck!
I'll kill ya! You fucking shit.
You sick fucking cunt! I'll kill ya!
Oh, my God!
Dad, are you okay?
What happened?
What are you doing?
I'm calling the police.
Hey, hey, no, no, there's no need
it's, it's just a misunderstanding.
Dad, you're hurt.
No, no. Pumpkin, I'm fine, I'm fine.
I'm sorry if I scared you, I'm okay.
- Are you sure?
-  Absolutely.
It's just a misunderstanding, that's all.
Okay, can we get the game going
again, please?
How could you do that to me?
I'm really sorry.
You're sorry? Gee, Dad, thanks.
That makes everything so much better.
I lost my temper. I don't know
what else to say. I'm sorry.
Don't you get it? There's nothing anybody can say.
My life is ruined.
No, it's not ruined.
We're going through a tough time
but your life's not ruined.
We're going through a tough time?
We didn't get raped.
We're not the laughingstock of New Trier. I am!
I got raped. Not you!
I know that.
Nothing's ever gonna be the same. I know that.
But, please, can you please stop reminding
me of it every second?
Annie, wait! I'm so sorry.
For what? It's not your
fault my dad's a psycho.
What? No. I swear to God, I had nothing to do with it.
Wait, what are you talking about?
The I nternet thing.
What?
Oh, uh--
Annie!
Cameron.
Oh, my God.
My God.
Hello?
Lynn?
Will, where have
you been? I've been calling you.
What, what do you mean? I'm
, I'm here. Where are you?
On my way. Is, is Annie there?
No, I don't, why?
Just-- Brittany called me. Something's happened.
Is she there?
What? Annie? What, what happened?
I-- don't-- just go check, please! Call me back.
Annie!
Annie.
Annie, are you in there?
Annie, open this door!
Annie!
Shit.
Will?
Call an ambulance!
How many pills have you taken?
I'm not really--
Call an ambulance!
Hello?
Open your mouth.
Open your mouth, sweetheart.
We need, please--
She's taken too many pills?
Yeah. Come on.
It's all right.
She asleep?
I'm through talking.
Brittany's spending the night.
Good night.
Dad?
Dad.
Are you okay?
You remember the first time you went in the pool?
What?
You probably don't. You were two.
Peter was scared to death the first time he went in.
He screamed and cried so much, he didn't stop.
He was fine in the bath, but pool...
Not you.
You were fearless.
I remember.
You were amazing.
Came in with me and almost immediately
started laughing
and playing and splashing around.
You just had this confidence.
It wasn't just swimming.
You just had this--
trust--in things, people, the world.
It was who you were.
No fear.
God, I loved that.
I was so proud of it.
I envied it.
And I was so afraid that you'd lose it as you grew up.
That confidence. That faith.
But you didn't.
And then I failed you.
It was my job to make sure you didn't lose it.
To keep you safe.
What am I if I can't protect you?
And to see you lose that confidence
to see you question yourself.
That the idea would even occur to you
to want to hurt yourself.
Or for you to think for one minute
that you weren't as beautiful--
I don't know if you can ever forgive me, Annie.
I really don't know if you should.
But I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Dad. Daddy.
I love you so much.
Dad.
Dad. Come on. How much longer?
We just got here, buddy.
Let's at least pick up some stuff for the park. Okay?
What a day.
Susanna. Grab some apples, will ya?
Hey, Dad. Can I do it for awhile?
Okay. Be careful, all right, buddy?
Well, hello. How do I look?
Goofy.
Yeah. Probably so.
Mr. Weston!
Hey, Tyler, how's it going?
I'm good. How about yourself?
I'm good.
Uh, Mom, Dad, this is M r. Weston.
Hey, very nice to meet you.
He's my physics teacher.
Pleasure, pleasure. Hey, Susanna.
One of my students, Tyler.
Oh. Hi, Tyler. I'm Susanna. Nice to meet you.
My wife, Susanna.
And I'm Jennifer.
Hi, Jennifer.
And this is our boy, Mark.
Hey, man. How's it goin'?
So, great day, huh?
It is gorgeous.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player