There was once upon a time a town,
not far from a big city.
Road went through, but there were
only a few business
a coffee shop, a hardware store,
a sheriff office.
and all kinds of people..
vagrants, runaway teens...
religious fanatic, retired seniors who ...
well, it was the town of those who
want to be left alone. .
and so they were...
the sheriff, Bobby LaGrange, went
there for years...
also made wood novelty.
but the most astonishing about
the town was ...
an old bell free with the clock
tower with seven faces.
You could see the time from anywhere
in the town of Swan Valley.
the faces consistently show different times.
No question, something evil
is biding there.
perhaps it was because the terrible
murder happen years before.
too terrible to talk about. But
would haunted the town.
or perhaps it was those teenagers who
gather across the lake.
some people thought they did bad things.
They worship Satan.
the way their dress, the
music they played...
and their mysterious leader known
only as Flamingo.
a seducer of innocent youth...
some said...far worse.
in this set of certain time...
the stream writers...
of popular fiction, Hall Baltimore ...
drove in Swann Valley. On his book
signing tour...
another series of his novel ...
about witchcraft.
Excuse me, do you know where
the bookstore is?
There is no bookstore around here.
- Great.
Have you ever read a of Hall Baltimore
thriller?
No, thanks.
did you ever read a of Hall Baltimore
thriller?
No...Who is Hall Baltimore?
I am him.
- Oh. Nice to meet you.
and you are ...
- Stacey.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
- Hi Stacey. bye Stacey.
You're sale weapons?
No weapons, only ammunition.
- Pistols?
Ammunition?
- Yes.
Knives? Have you ...
- In row 2.
The Hall Baltimore. I take one.
Could you autograph it?
- sure.
to Bobby LaGrange.
To Bobby LaGrange. Best witches. Hall Baltimore.
How does it feel to be the bargain
statement of Stephen King?
not to wonderful.
you know, I write horror stories
myself.
You don said it? And you are the
sheriff here in the town?
40 years.
Would you mind to read some of my stuff?
I have been multiplied.
You know We have had a mass murder
while back.
Many folks thinks that the town is haunted
Well, I am just wrapping here in
the town...
and then I'll goanna be on my way.
You mystery write and you're not
interested in a mass murder?.
No.
you come with me right now...
and take a look at the deuce I got a morgue
you got a deuce at a morgue?
- Yes sir.
now?
- Yes, sir.
There is a story in.
I know how this look likes ...
- It is like a ...
Jesus. Let me ask you a question?
How long have you work here?
You don't run a gurney with the dead
person on over my foot.
Sorry, sheriff.
this is from the current case in Swann Valley?
- it's happen before.
serial killer used to be
leave the calling card in wooden stake
I don't wanna see her face.
- I don't blame you.
I mean, it's real a tragic.
She is just one poor girl.
Arbus?
- Yes?
alright.
- You around the clock.
do you know who she is?
- this girl?
We get all kind in here
vagrants, runaways..
worse. Those kid at the lake.
All kind.
How about you like to calobrate on a book
about this? You and me?
and you goanna got me stricken likes that?
How day. Like to full my thermos with a coffee, please.
okay
Has Edgar Poe lived in this town?
At the old Chickering Hotel
way back went.
Chickering Hotel...Thanks.
- Have a good day.
With my respect sir.
My dearest daughters, these is my first novel.
I am proud of it, just as same of you.
to daddy with Love.
to daddy with Love, Vicky.
I want a write something I do.
I want write something for me.
something personal.
because it makes any sense? I had to
break this spell of this downward spiral
There's the one way to do and I'm trying
to do it. I'm not goanna write another witch book
and That's it. than. I am going to
do something for me.
you have done it before
When you were not drinking. before Vicky's accident.
it can't rashes this thing.
You can do these. I... I knew what you mean about...
you just had to do it one more time. Just
write the damn thing, then you can take time
and write what you really want to write. I understand, I get it. you know I did.
did you call Sam? did you tell him
you need  an advice?
well I did and it was very extremely humiliating
and I not goanna write witch story anymore.
you are on holiday and I'm stuck here
and try to put piss off ...
come on magic numbers...
to make all work out.
to pretending nothing wrong and put
food on the table.
so you cannot speak to me... just grow up
...grow up
people often asks me, how do you
know so much about witches know?' ...
and I tell them, because I am married
with her.
Hey.
- Hello. Where do you come from?
just down the road. You past me.
you looking at my teeth?
No, I just don't know where you came from.
I am very concise about my teeth.
tell me.
your teeth are fine. It is braces.
anyway I hate them.
- No, they are fine. Your outgrows into.
they call me Vampire because of
these teeth.
but you may call me V..
- V. that's nice.
What's your real name?
- Virginia.
Virginia.
You're about 13?
Yeah, I'm 12. But I look older
because I tall.
I know who you are. You wrote those
witch stories.
and you're here to sign a book in hardware
store.
I love your books
specially the part where Elizabeth says,
'forsake me never, because I will untied
you from my grave'.
That is my favorite part.
Thanks, I like your look.
oh ...yeah.
just the way I dress.
you're scared of me yet?
- What?
Yes.
a little.
that clock chime midnight three
times already.
keeping track time right here is pointless.
That's why Mr. book signing.
that old hotel is open. Come on
I buy you soda...sweetie
I have a daughter at your age.
No, I don't think that a pretty good idea.
- Why not?
better we go to hardware and talk about
My story.
tell me now.
- No, I can't.
come on.
We are open. Come in.
I go for walk, I guess I got lost.
What happen to that little girl?
- What little girl?
is the restaurant open?
- restaurant is always open.
With that old clock tower and all of those
faces, you can get breakfast any time.
Yes.
Well, Mr...
- Baltimore.
Damned clock.
that clock has never told the correct time.
just you wait but. You will goanna
be very surprise.
There's all is the important thing
and that's working beautifully.
better than before.
- I just have a beer.
Melvin is the bell custodian, he
assign the big clock at church
It is a hopeless job. And a real burden.
that old mechanism does not keep
it for a long time more .
I go up there every day.
the seven faces look at me like I was the
one who invented the day and light savings time.
you know who thought up, hey?
Hitler. And, you know who support him now?
doctors. And you know why? golf
they want more time golf. That is
what all about.
You cannot change the time. The time
will changes you.
don't you' agree? What do you think
about the daylight savings time?
I never really thought that.
- When do you think about it?
That is the grave.
- Grave?
you can walk on it. don't worry.
The whole floor is a grave.
Really?
- There are twelve children buried right down here.
13 children murdered in cold blood.
Well, actually he is right.
it has been dozen but one get away and
she was damn.
When was that?
- Long Time ago.
The clock is fixed.
got you, devil.
she has bite.
- suck it out...suck it out
Damn ...it hurt.
what is the time she bite you. 4 o'clock.
- It isn't 4 o’clock.
the clock said four o'clock.
- are you kidding me?
It is the devil.
is the dead little kid.
you?
why are you here?
what she have told you?
- nothing. What should she tell me?
go away, old man...you know
Children...hurry.
the moon is going down...
time for nap.
come on.
my God, I am lost.
maybe this is story what I need?
...this story.
help me.
you? my god...Edgar Poe.
show me the way.
Hall, wake up.
I know you're there. are you awake?
- What? It wasn't me.
It's me. It is your wife. Hello?
Hall, wake up. I know you're there.
What is the matter?
- If you're awake? It's me.
What is the matter? Everything okay?
This is your wife. Yes, I know who you are.
I do not have ...
I need a second. oh my god..
What have you done?
Yeah?
That?
do you know how much it's worth?
- Yeah, I do.
160,000 dollars.
No, it's worth a lot more than that.
It's priceless.
you shouldn't be touching it. How did you get
into my safe? just calm down.
please stop, whatever you're doing, just stop and put it down. That's really not a joke..
you think. I don't think it's funny. It is a nice book, by the way
Yes, Whitman only had...
there's only four on private hand okay.
Understand what that's mean?
do you.. He set the title himself.
- Do you think I'm joking?
please.
- you know what... I think I know
more this old book than you do to your own family.
you need the gloves.
- You Know what?
kiss for good bye.
please.
- don't have me to do this.
I don't want to...I have to.
Hello. I am looking for ...
- Mrs. LaGrange is sleeping. quite.
Sorry.
I like to know if you have information on the old Chickering hotel?
I check the file.
Thank you
EDGAR POE PENS A TALE ABOUT
SWANN VALLEY'S BELFRY!
MURDER OF THE INNOCENTS! SWAN VALLEY
DEVASTATED RESIDENTS SHOCKED
MINISTER SAID DEVIL LIVED IN
BELL TOWER
26 September 1955
HE TOLD US THAT THE DEVIL HAD COME TO THE TOWN
OF SWANN VALLY, LIVED IN THE CHURCH BELL TOWER.
Swann Valley, sheriff office please.
one moment.
The number is 393 229 39 23 .
do you wish to be connected?
Yes.
Sheriff office, we are closed.
Yes, hi, it's me, You remember me,
the writer.
I at the window.
I'm go to the front door.
Alright.
We are closed.
- Can I talk to you?
look sheriff says nothing  happen as long as that thing is in here.
Where is the sheriff?
- It is Sunday.
he is in the church. he is the ministry not very religious
listen...what time did you said the country coroner come to take this trakeout?
I didn't said nothing ..about nothing
Somebody said this week...somebody said
-  but it's wasn't me.
Can I coming?
okay but look you can't touch anything. It's all evidence.
don't touch anything, you got it?
It is my responsibility, and I don't want that guy yell at me, I am sick of it.
Hello.
- Yes, can I talk to the sheriff?
just a minute.
Bobby.
Telephone.
Yeah.
- Hi Sheriff, I got a writer fella from out of town  here at the office.
he does not know that's Sunday?
let me talk to him.
Bobby, it's Hall Baltimore.
I could get your story and the image of that poor dead girl out of my mind.
Really?
- Yes, I dreamed the whole night.
.. that I would like to write the book with you.
so, you're the sheriff and you make bat house
Yes, and that is a bird house.
totally different. .
The bats and birds know which is which.
normally I write about witchcraft ...
but vampires are actually witches that suck blood.
they are entirely different.
we really have one here.
There are no witches he, as long as I can remember.
I could ask to my sister. she is older than eighty.
welcome in my office. Come on have a sit..
imagine this. Written by...
Hall Baltimore and Bobby LaGrange. It's sweet.
Or, Hall Baltimore with an idea by Bobby LaGrange.
What do you mean with an idea by? I got a lot more
then the idea by.
I got a great character.
- Yes, who?
Bobby LaGrange.
- come down. Tell me what you got.
I got the vampires executions. .
and that will sell.
Not bad. go on.
The girl, who is she? is she just runaway?
or just a 12 or 13 years old girl ...
which looks much older than she really is.
A Vagrant? A homeless?
Why the wooden stack?
- Yes, why?
Or, what that's kill her?
Or was it something that was add a later?
as a calling card of the real killer?
you see, one end the one smooth.
No fingerprints.
and then it was press injurer...Slowly.
Not jab, not stab.
almost it was done by
some kind of a machine.
a machine?
- Yes.
that why I called it a vampires execution.
I think she was killed by ...an electric chair ...
or vampires.
an executions device, designed especially by and for vampires ...
that's different...I wonder what it will look alike.
While I thought of that. I have a model.
Ready?
- ready
how about that
watch this.
you' love it
How can I help you, Hall.
- hay Sam ...
remember you said if I come with a bullet proof
idea, you would give me an advance?
another advance.
- Yes, another more
a bullet proof idea come with meat on the bone.
not like fog on the lake.
you know
well no one can better metaphors quite like you Sam.
here the title, right...just listen The vampires execution.
vampires?
and the main character get this...
she is a little girl, a murdered girl.
beautiful.
- Beautiful, yes, but she just a kid.
No, I meant that's beautiful...that's she get murdered.
but it must be a good of story.
Not a lot of hassle with the style bullshit.
Tell me, how does that execution being playing up?
I will find out. I mean it's a great...great twixt ending.
With heart.
with tons of heart, I'll give complete
outline in the morning
but you'll got me a check
to Denise right the way.
I'm not kidding around, in facts the bank wire transfer will be better. It’s an emergency
I am thinking about it. It is not bullet proof.
but Hall Baltimore, master in the witchcraft doing a vampire story
It is not a bad.
- Not at all bad.
if it got and ending.
- It's got an ending.
a bullet proof ending.
- a bullet proof
but Sam, you got tight my wife over
right? okay
this is why I'm doing it right?
25 grand’s.
okay, you know what I am going to do?
I goanna wire Denise 10,000 dollar
25.000.
That is great. I really appreciate it.
I said that I wire Denise 10,000 dollars...
but I need the outline in the morning or I will goanna stop the payment.
Sam?
- And no fog on the lake...
The night was ... humid.
The night was ... cloudy.
fog. A Mist ... mist descends ...
on the lake Mini ...
More WANIPALUKi.
The fog ... floated out like
Virginia's silent ...
dream.
No, that something else.
The fog on the lake ...
The fog on the lake ... just to torture Sam.
the scent floats out like ...
tears.
on a whale? No.
The fog on the lake...
looks like a razor blade.
The fog on the lake remind me my
first wife.
it disappear with the time.
I lost my mind.
And now I have a lisp.
And now I suddenly turning into a
black basketball player.
she ... was ...
I typing such as a basket ... a gay
basketball player from the sixties.
I like short short.
there are reveal but they are confortable.
They help me to jump.
there was no fog on the lake.
Swann Valley, sheriff department.
Deputy Arbus speaking.
Arbus, the writer fella told me to go to ...
well, he is still not back here in his motel.
If you see him, tell him I wait
another thirty minutes...
and that's it... I got to go.
- Alright, sheriff.
Why the door is not lock, Arbus?
I have left them open for you, PJ.
what happened to your diet?
- I was wondering when you get here
with my hamburgers.
feeling like to play cards?
sure, but when you goanna pay up?
PJ, get the cord here will you.
- Okay. .
don't ever walk into the morgue
without unannounced
My heart can't handle it.
- Sorry, I have knock..
well, the sheriff is over at your motel ...
and he said
I only be here for thirty minutes
okay, thanks.
you owe me eighteen buck, Arbus.
Snooze, Ropopose, Sleep all ...
Night all ... and you didn't put this
in your list. But I like it. I thought it was good.
Sleeping All.
- Just what I needed.
Are we not working together? That is,
after all, what you said.
and you're just goanna put a sleeps.
then I have a chance to dream.
but you didn't read the label’s.
- yes it is.
this is how you write? I thought that
all city writers...
just get itself was drunk and wrote
some kind of trance
- we do...we do but...
there is bullet proof of ending out there
and I know just a guy to get me there ...
do you know a doctor that's can give
me prescription for a real..real one?
I cannot do that. I'm a public officer.
what a lies..lies. By Bobby LaGrange.
her's skin was so fresh as cream, comes
out from the butter ...
under the lace by teenage witch
What keep bringing you back?
I'm trying to solve a mystery.
I have waiting for you, my friend.
here, in her tomb.
after you.
here you are... Edgar Allan Poe,
so..if  you...
How can I help?
well... I got have no ending.
did you know the deacons once corresponding
with me ...
concerning on the technique ...
write the ending first. And work it backwards.
What did you need? Length?
40 to 50 lines ... per page.
200 pages minimum.
providence?
- Beauty.
The tone?
- they will tell you.
these point has being settle...
shall we consider the reframe?
- right
I think the bell tower coming to me.
the reframe must be brief.
It my own work, almost famous...
it just only a single word is the best..
I'm afraid.
never more.
The difficulty arose from the
presumption that the word ...
could only monopoly be spoken by
a human being.
then immediately a rose an idea of non
reason creature capable to speak ...
and, very naturally of parrot suggest of
itself.
but this idea was replaced immediately
by raven equally ...
capable of speech of the bird
announcing ...
infinity more keeping within terms
this all is in the price of that
very bottle of Irish whisky?
Yes, of course, please continue..
So, I asked myself ...
of all melancholic topics ...
what according the universal understanding
of mankind is the most tragic?
death.
and when it is most tragic
melancholic topic ...
most poetical?
when there is most loosely allude
itself ... to beauty.
the death of a beautiful girl ..
is unquestionly the most poetical
topic in the world.
equally it is beyond the lips of
best beauty of the topic
of those a man ...
who loved her.
so ... I had to combine these two ideas ...
of the lover who lamented about
his dead mistress ...
and the raven' continuously using the
word "Nevermore"
in a poem of 100 lines.
and "nevermore" was the conclusion
of each dancer ...
in a poem with a melancholic tone.
How do you find the ending?
Your story is a tragedy.
it happened here at the old
Chikering hotel where I once slept.
There were many children in the town.
orphans some ware, the lost children
and before long they were taking in
protection by pastor Alan Floyd.
he was a kindly man, adopt this kid
everyone was agrees that he is
good character...
as his capitalism, another god
and goodness
And one night it happened.
one of his children was missing.
and then what it came out.
whom I miss here?
who is it?
Peter?
Where ...
he is did surely not cross the lake.
never ever go with the people
across of the lake.
This is very important. They are like
like... fur man.
uncleaned. Those teens across the lake
they are ... the undead..
They are vampires.
He took care of them and care and
gave them to eat.
Hearing Impaired by: "Zacxbauer"
And anointed them with the juices of the unpretentious,
With sinking foil and a wolfbaine.
anointed them against the evil.
Turn your head.
- Thank you..
That's right. There we go.
We make sure that you are nice and safe.
someday you will wearing ... nylon.
Where is he?
- What are you doing with my mom Ouija board?
Have you ever seen one of these?
- What would you do with that?
Innovation has made the detective
story and Charlie Chan entertaining.
Bobby LaGrange ...
is an innovative detective.
after you, sir.
That. Ouija board.
we are very close proximity.
to the disease.
and the killer probably still
in this area.
maybe we shouldn't doing this
in the morgue.
dim the old lights..
Hello.
do we know you?
- Yes, it is.
you doing that, I can feel it.
No I'm not
- shut up!
H.. I.. M.
Him.
it wants you
Okay, do we know you?
I...
am ... her.
I am.
Arbus, what was that?
Pastor, let go watch.
who kill you?
B...
Sheriff, you doing that. I can feel it.
- do not.
who kill you?
B...
young people ...
They are evil.
and that flamingo kid, he is the one
that has infected them.
he is a vampire. Is he?
'Yes'.
Come on, Arbus. Keep your gun hidden.
you must be thirsty?
- exactly
I'm looking for Flamingo.
- He is right back here.
when the sky low and heavy,
weighing as a lid ...
on the groaning spirit, falling
prey to long boredom...
Educated.. you know BAUDELAIRE.
I know life man. And I know the
dreams of BAUDELAIRE.
and he from the horizon, the entire
circle embracing...
a dark day for our pour, even sadder
than the nights.
I hoped you will help me to find
the missing girl ...
She is 12 or 13 years.
There are a lot of girls there.
you know. People say what going on here
...evil
are you worried about that?
Look around you. This is what evil to you?
look at that moon.
It is beautiful.
I have been worried ...
it has been 3 days since we have seen it..
This is a little kid which i take care but
I am worried that something happened to her.
Arbus. Damn it.
You?
You out off uniform?
You are here for unofficial business.
What the hell you doing here?
he said you okay with it.
He gave me 20 bucks.
Mr. collaborator.
I thought that we were a team,
all the way through these investigation.
Bobby LaGrange does not like
to be tricked.
nor that he's like made to be pull off
the famous Flamingo
..my..my..my
the lady killer
Arbus, arrest this murderer.
he's like that...He can coming or go.
or he would be gone.
those are the real keys ...
- Yes they are ....
this is the official keys.
- That's amazing.
of the clock tower?
- Yes, really?
give me that. Where are you going?
Come on, I just want to see.
- You don't want to go up there.
That's odd, I was up here yesterday ...
and I had no problem with the lock.
- Yesterday?
perhaps it was last week.
It worked?
- Last it worked.
Let me try.
here.
- Thank you.
What the hell with that?
you tell me you got the butt, have you
ever seen this like that when you're here?
I'm not go up there. This place is haunted.
Did you know that?
What is that smell?
- The devil.
The devil is up there.
You will get all over yourself.
I going out.
goodbye.
come with us daddy...
come with us daddy
Help me, daddy...
Come with us daddy.
Help me...
Help me...daddy
listen,
- What is that?
are they evil?
No.
tell me who killed her?
...tell me.
You say that you want to know..
but do you?
I want to know the truth.
- There are consequences.
What choice do I have?
tell me all of the story.
- As you wish, my friend.
that happen events just make
you shame to remember.
please.
- Thank you, it a sharp of knife.
I would like to add a secret ingredient.
we goanna have special lemonade
for everybody.
that's right...good job.
This sap stinks.
- Careful.
you cut your finger.
Please, Alice.
-thank you.
you're welcome
here you go
- Do not drink the lemonade,
he put something on it.
No, stop.
- No I would like to lemonade, Virginia
Virginia, fine. Enough,
..stand still.
Virginia, is being very...
very stupid to do it.
we are all going to have some lemonade
it's delicious and sweet...taste it
stay...stay...stay here.
- What are you doing?
and, then he make a freak full decision.
rather than have the children
souls be damn as vampire
he drug the lemonade, and cut
their throats.
Can you make him stop?
Do something..
dead of beauty.
one child try to save her soul.
Virginia?
you play our favorite game?
I will find you.
got you.
Virginia.
one path to God.
one, one way to God.
I got you.
once he caught her and put chain
had its fascination.
No.
you must stop screaming.
I told you...God want you to meet mom.
that's right. scream all what you want,
Even God can't hear you now.
One road, one way to God..
One road, one way to God...
Only through this way ...
during the bright days of its eye-catching
beauty...I took a great deal from her..
not as the living and breathing Virginia ...
but it's the Virginia of the dream.
you see ...
dear friend ...
she was my young cousin ...
my beloved wife.
her name was Virginia.
but I gave her many names.
Lenor
Bernice.
The lady Gaia.
Madenasha.
Annabelle Lee.
Alianora.
you know certainly that I am your
partner?...Open the door, wake up.
wake up.
open the door, Hall.
- alright..I  hear.
Wait until you get to see this.
- What?
I have subscribe the 'Writers Weekly'.
and this just in
That he said that you took  10,000 dollars
as an advance was for a project call 'Vampire Executions'
No, no no.. that was money for some old write.
and that money already went to my wife.
that is a mistake.
but I was thinking, I do like
'Vampire Executions'...
by Hall Baltimore and Bobby LaGrange.
give me my $5,000 dollar now.
there's no goanna be money exchange until
we get the story right.
we got to right to the end.
- The end?
The end is who gun it. Like every other
murder mysteries.
Let me wake up.
- It's come to who did it
Okay.
- What's the matter with you?
You forget your greatest asset.
- yeah..what's  that?
Bobby LaGrange is the detective..
You got to take Bobby LaGrange use much more
throughout in the entire story ...
because he can solve the crimes himself..
clearly he's work of a serial killer.
someone want to silence the girls,
on the other side of the lake.
because, they fried a sick mind.
And then they sizzling because some psyco
hocus pocus condition...
the condemn them the evil slaughter they are
And that is what in their sick mind.
you think so, Bobby?
you think they're evil slut?
whom?
- The young girl.
yes, they are all in the dark thing ...
every one of them should dead...
and sexs.
what do you think?
oh no you don't...
No, not Bobby LaGrange...
them.
Those devil worshiping whore be heard
on the other side of the world.
Shit Yes, they are all in dark thing
every one of them. They worship dead and sex.
they were just too brutal for
their own good.
you know, they have a white flash
with the devil inside them.
little spicy cannot stop,
thinking about.
that not me.
- It's not me.
It's them.
- They are the.
flash of the devil.
I saved their souls
You...
you don't touch me.
do not touch me. tearing out the from me.
Priest.
- If you will excuse me ...
forgive me for seeking
pleasure outside the company ...
cast me another way for the
lighting of my spirit.
perhaps, it is the dirt of the boy,
only here alone?
with all of these things together,
thrown ...
will burn it ...
- Flame-proof, bullet-proof.
I can't ever look at the Clift,
I am trembling.
This little cliff?
Wait.
do you dare to go further?
- Where you're talking about, tell me the ending
If you don't stop now, every word ..
what you write with you pen will be your
your own tale.
You.
You're the ending you seek.
How can you stop now when it's
close to the end?
then it's a time to face the truth.
to end this story, there is no other way.
I am so ashamed, I should cry
That is my little girl.
That is my daughter. She wanted me
to go with her friends.
I thought that there were
little boat....
I thought there were children boat
I did not know there were speedboats.
I could guide them. I was
too drunk to wake up.
I was with a woman.
I am so ashamed.
I could go there,
set the clock
but the wrong time So the alarm
went off.
I could been there ...but
maybe they are still...
so ashamed.
than perhaps they would have
survived.
I should been there,
that little girl.
We share this little ghost,
my friend.
our work must be the grave that we
prepare as a lovely talent.
'Guilty'.
Oh God ...
help me...help me, daddy..
'Bullet Proof'.
You delivery a good here.
I telling you, meat on
the bone.
you think so, Sam?
- I do.
Hall Baltimore,
master of witchcraft, no more.
Never more.
Hall Baltimore the 'Vampire Executions'.
has sold 30,000 copies, which is okay business.
the suicide of Bobby LaGrange was
eventually linked to...
three other murders of 'Wooden Stake', killings in addition to the murder of his deputy, Arbus.
Denise Baltimore never sold
Hall's rare copy of  ...
Walt Whitman 'Leaves of Grass'.
They are still married.