Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Edited by : Mohamed Elqusbi , LIBYA
http://subscene.com
(CHATTERING IN RUSSIAN)
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(SCREAM)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HORN HONKS)
(HORN HONKING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(SCREAMING)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(MACHINE GUN FIRES)
(SCREAMING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(SCREAMING)
(IN RUSSIAN)
Prime Minister Musayev,
if you don't recognize me,
look hard at my face
and you'll understand.
General Vasilly Topov
was not only my father,
he was my comrade,
my leader in battle.
And now his fight
for the liberation of Pasalan
is my own.
His army is under my command,
and I will stop at nothing
to make his dreams
become reality.
Prime Minister Musayev,
we have occupied
the Chernobyl nuclear power plant.
(ALARM RINGING)
The abandoned city surrounding the complex
is under our control.
No longer can we be ignored.
Now, we are the occupiers.
Any attempt to
penetrate its borders
will be met with
fierce resistance.
The reactor has been
rigged with explosives.
Detonators have been set
to 72 hours.
Should our demands go
unanswered, they will go off.
Such an explosion would
produce a radiation cloud
100 times stronger than
the bombs dropped on Japan.
We call for the
imminent release of all
227 political prisoners
you've held captive.
We call for the complete and total
independence of Pasalan.
Nothing less will be
deemed acceptable.
Prime Minister Musayev, this fight is not
only about country and politics,
it is about blood.
Mine...
...and now yours.
We have your children.
Should you ignore my demands
they will be the first to go.
I urge you to act responsibly.
We ask only to be free,
as you would want
your children to be free.
(BEEPING)
Come on, come on, come on.
That's it.
Hey, take it easy.
This way.
Okay, come on, come on.
Over there, right over there.
All right, now take it easy. Take it easy.
Hey, easy! For Christ's sake,
there's spare parts in there!
Morons.
Sit.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Any problems?
No.
Do you know
where you are?
Yes.
Do you know
why you're here?
Yes.
Is it necessary for you to question
the things you don't know?
- No.
- Excuse me, Doctor.
Thank you.
Okay, can you please
move your right fingers,
one by one, beginning with
the forefinger?
- Limited range.
- All right.
Okay.
Do you feel warm?
Yes.
I'm gonna cool you off.
Very good.
You were very good today.
So you've seen the security tape
from the museum?
I have.
You want to describe
what you saw, or shall I?
I saw an armed assailant
take direct hits to vital areas
and still manage
to overpower a security detail.
This remind you
of something?
White Tower was shut
down over a year ago.
- Maybe it was something else.
- Maybe.
But we should still
prepare for the worst,
however remote
the possibility.
So, if we assume the worst,
the problem becomes ours to share.
Hypothetically.
So then, hypothetically,
What is our
shared solution?
(DOOR OPENS)
Let's load them up.
COBY.' On April 26th, 1986,
Chernobyl Reactor Number 4 exploded.
Worst nuclear power
plant accident in history.
The ensuing fire
released a plume
of highly radioactive fallout
into the atmosphere.
The city of Chernobyl
was evacuated
and has remained abandoned
for over 20 years.
We believe the rebels
have set up their bunker
in one of the buildings adjacent
to the reactor complex,
about two miles due east
from our current position in Chernobyl city.
While the site itself no longer has enough
fuel to make a bomb,
it has 100 times
the radiation.
An explosion in Reactor Number 3
Would release that radiation.
And now for the bad news.
It appears the general's son has gotten
his hands on some of our Weaponry.
Here to explain,
Dr. Richard Porter.
In the 1960s,
with war in Asia looming,
the U.S. Began research
into Operation Black Tower,
what we've now come to call
the Universal Soldier program.
A high-response,
self-sustaining,
quick-healing, stronger,
faster soldier,
fueled by high-concentrate
nutritional supplements.
A soldier that operates Without
conscience or hesitation.
By freezing a human body
With nitrogen-based gas,
repairing it and reheating it
through thyroid and pituitary augmentation,
We were able to revive
a recently-deceased soldier,
and, in the process,
improve them.
Programmable and erasable.
One that you can
turn on and turn off.
Deceased, as in dead?
That's right. Five years ago,
the program was suspended,
or, rather, replaced by a program
known as White Tower.
Led by Dr. Robert Colin,
under my supervision,
White Tower sought
to improve and perfect
What Black Tower
had introduced.
Using gene therapy techniques
developed during Dr. Colin's cloning research,
We were able to give our
UniSols a DNA tune-up from the inside out.
The new model was superior
in every physical capacity,
a virtual killing machine.
The next generation UniSols,
or NGUs,
as We like to call them.
There was, however,
an incident in a government building.
(SCREAMING)
Twelve dead.
Nobody injured.
It was considered
to be a malfunction,
though I believe their
temperature had not been properly moderated.
We were instructed to shut down
all the existing NGUs, Which we did.
But there was a break-in.
Some things were taken,
including a Series 7 model.
We have reason to believe
it was my former colleague, Dr. Colin.
We suspect he's been
continuing his studies.
Colin's been operating
out of Eastern Europe as a gun-for-hire.
Gentlemen, we'll be fighting
against the perfect soldier.
One who is impervious
to injury and pain, quicker than hell,
and with a nervous system
unaffected by radiation.
We have four
first-generation UniSols
that are more than capable
in this type of endgame.
Dismissed.
You say four, Colonel.
That's correct.
I thought there was five.
There were.
Now there's four.
What happened to the fifth?
He's the subject of a privately-funded
program run by Dr. Sandra Fleming.
Project Phoenix.
Doing what?
DR. PORTER: Behavioral
modification therapy
or psychological rehabilitation
as Dr. Fleming calls it.
She's trying to reintroduce
him into society.
He was one of the very first,
but by far the best of the group.
Dr. Fleming has been conducting her
research in Switzerland.
LUC: I think of escape.
Peaceful feeling.
Shame.
Why do you say that?
I don't know.
Yes, you do.
Just say the first thing
that comes into your mind.
I don't remember.
Maybe for things
I have done.
What have you done, Luc?
I don't know.
I think he's hungry.
Why don't you feed him?
How do you feel?
Helpless.
Maybe you're feeling
the weight of responsibility.
It's what it feels like
to grow older, Luc.
Do you realize
how far you've come?
Two years ago when we started
this, when you first woke up,
you couldn't remember
the day before.
My head feels full.
It's just another stage
in your development.
We're getting there.
You may have forgotten our
agreement, Doctor, but I haven't.
Consider this
my last reminder.
I haven't forgotten,
I've been in surgery,
which appears to
be quite a success.
So, when will we do it?
I told you, I'm gonna
run a diagnostic...
I have to guarantee the safety
of my men, as well as my own.
It'll be taken care of.
So you want to wait? Then I guess
the wire transfers can wait as well.
What's the hurry, right?
Miles.
Yes, Doctor?
The general's son
is growing anxious.
He'd like to be micro-chipped this instant.
It can't possibly wait.
I'm nobody's son anymore,
Doctor. It is Commander Topov.
Oh.
Right.
I've done it to myself.
It does hurt a little bit now.
Maybe for you.
Failsafe is active, sir.
Satisfied?
No. My men.
Fine. Round them up.
(BONES CRACKING)
Gentlemen,
two-pronged objective.
Securing of the reactor site and
the dismantling of the detonators,
and the extraction
of the two known hostages.
Now, we have
reason to believe
that the children
are being held here.
However, their positions
could be fluid,
so we're moving in on
a staggered six-front maneuver.
Disable all communication
and transportation vehicles
that you encounter,
and remember the objective.
If it comes
down to either-or,
we go big picture and
we take the reactor.
Are there any questions?
What if we encounter
the freak?
Avoidance, if you can.
Keep it occupied.
Is that the best
you can do, Doctor?
It's probably programmed
to defend the reactor site,
so it'll stick close
to it like a nest,
making it impossible
to use high-powered
weaponry in the presence
of the explosives.
Captain, your men should
not engage with the NGU.
That's what my men are for.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(SIGHS)
It's hot in here.
Take your coat off.
We've been here before?
Every week.
That's what I thought.
Can I get you
guys some coffee?
Yeah, sure, I'll have
some coffee, thanks.
What would you like,
Luc, to drink?
Uh... Orange juice.
Great , I'll be right back
to take your orders.
How are your
knees feeling?
A little better.
I think the anti-inflammatories are working.
We need to get you
some more of those.
The weather report said there may
be another snow front on the way.
Could get a couple of inches
over the weekend.
I think the cold weather's
been affecting your joints.
The next shipment should
be in by next week, so...
Luc!
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
SANDRA: Luc, stop! Luc! No!
Luc, stop! Luc!
Luc, stop! Stop!
No! Luc, no!
No! Luc, stop, stop!
Luc, stop!
MAN: Somebody help him.
Go! Go! Go!
(EXHALES)
(CHATTERING ON RADIO)
(SCREAMING)
SOLDIER.' Man down! We got a man
down. Move, move, move!
(SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN)
Let's go!
Move, move, move! Go!
Come on, come on!
TECHNICIAN.' Hold fire,holding fire.
All units proceed to reactor complex.
Repeat, hold fire,
holding fire.
All units proceeding
to reactor complex.
SOLDIER.' Copy that. Unit One holding fire.
All units holding fire.
All systems green, sir.
Good.
SOLDIER.' The complex
in sight. All units falling into position, over.
TECHNICIAN.' Unit One,
Unit Two, two units, report to the south perimeter...
TECHNICIAN.' Cover your...
SOLDIER.' Unit One holding.
Contact back.
I'll take the north side.
Unit Two is on the move.
Proceeding to north perimeter.
Unit Two to
north perimeter.
TECHNICIAN.' Unit Two,
hold position in north perimeter.
We're on the south perimeter,
Structure 3. We're going in. Over.
Burke, the show's on. Send them
in and provide cover.
Sir, we have successfully
taken out all lines of defense.
We need to send in
two units.
Negative. Send in the freaks.
That's an order, Burke. Pull back.
Roger that.
It's all yours, boys.
Don't fuck it up.
COBY: How long before they
reach the Meeting Point A?
Stand by, sir.
(GRUNTS)
There he is.
Shut him down.
I'm on it.
(GRUNTS)
TECHNICIAN: Holy shit,
did you see that? Did you see that?
COBY: One is out.
Tell Two and Three One is down.
We need Two, Three and Four to
triangulate on the new position. Do it!
We're gonna triangulate...
Come on!
We're gonna triangulate
on what's... Hang on!
Triangulate...
Listen to me.
Let him go! Let him go!
Move Four to the reactor.
Have Three engage.
(GRUNTS)
COBY: What the hell
is going on?
He's too fast.
They can't track him.
COBY: All right, let's get
Four to the reactor. Get Four.
Four moving to
the reactor, sir. Four moving.
(TIMER BEEPING)
Sir, approaching
the reactor right now.
COBY: Okay, there they are.
There they are.
Shut them down, Doctor.
Deactivate.
Repeat, deactivate.
(YELLS)
(YELLING)
(CHOKING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Complete evac.
Send the order.
Burke, complete evac.
Pull them out!
Evac. Evac.
Pull back now!
Get everybody out of there!
Complete evac now. Complete evac.
Colonel.
Tell them to retreat.
Get them out. Get the men out of there.
Retreat. I repeat, retreat...
Get them all out. Tell him that is an order...
(STATIC ON RADIO)
You're not coming in clear.
Sir.
(MACHINE GUN FIRING)
(CHATTERING ON RADIO)
SOLDIER.' We're under fire.
Unit One under fire. Falling back.
Shit.
Colonel Petrov's down.
Request transportation.
No, no.
Request transport.
Go. Go.
Listen to me, God damn it.
You're coming with me.
(GROANS)
Go now.
Take him with you. Go.
(GUNSHOTS)
Take him with you! Go!
Look. Is he coming?
How's my boy? Mmm?
I feel good.
Good. That's very good.
That's my good boy.
Yes.
Magnificent.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
That's because we're gonna
give you a chance
to explain the situation
when they get here.
I told you from the start...
We were sitting ducks out there.
You don't need to tell me.
I saw it with my own eyes.
If you let us in,
we would've taken him out ourselves.
You didn't stand a chance.
You never did.
Hey, hey, come on.
Knock it off. Get back.
You don't have to like it,
but it's the truth.
It took on your entire outfit
and forced you to retreat.
One man. We're talking about
a perfect specimen.
One who knows
nothing other than to obey an order.
Something you seem
to know nothing about.
Fucking knock
your teeth out!
Hey, hey, hey!
Get back!
What the hell was that?
(TOPO V SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
TRANSLATOR: "This imprudent
act of aggression
"has resulted in
a swift response.
"We have detonated one of
the explosives around the reactor.
"Consider it a warning shot.
"The world doesn't appear to apply
pressure to the Bosorow bullies.
"They're allowing them
to stall.
"You are not doing anything.
Think about your children."
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(LUC SCREAMING)
(IN RUSSIAN)
I empathize with your father.
I know how he feels.
You only hope for
your family to be safe.
And when they are not
you carry it with you
like a cancer.
Unlike me,
he can change this.
(IN RUSSIAN)
I would rather die than
see my father give in to you.
And so it may be,
for all of us.
Hey. Stockholm syndrome, huh?
Bonding with the captives.
You know, I'm touched.
(IN ENGLISH) What's the matter
with you, Doctor?
Did the kids pick
on you in school?
Yes, yes, they did.
I was asthmatic, bad athlete, terrible skin.
Don't be so hard
on yourself.
No, no, it's true.
Perhaps I overcompensated.
Yes, we all congratulate you
on your science project.
Now, why don't you go back to
your room? You're boring us.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, you know, kids,
this is an important lesson.
You always have
to ask yourself who's in control.
It's not always
the one doing the talking.
Sometimes it's the guy
in the background.
I mean, okay, let's be honest
with ourselves here.
You call that an army?
Come on, it's a bunch of peasants
with slingshots.
But just one of
my men, just one...
That's all it took.
Now I want you
to imagine an army of men like that.
That, children,
that is real power.
(LAUGHS)
Bravo.
Very captivating.
Thank you.
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Or maybe
your poodle would like to get a word in.
My poodle.
Well, he's kind of shy.
No, please...He's not blessed
with the gift of the gab.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Then maybe you
can shut the fuck up
and do what I'm
paying you for.
Hey, you're the boss.
We think that the main
detonators are over here.
Pull back and encompass
the whole compound.
Copy that, sir.
That's the cooling tower.
If we can get in those pipes,
we can access the reactor there.
It's probably been capped off
after the accident, but it can be reopened, sir.
He's here.
Hello, Luc.
I expect you're feeling
somewhat fatigued.That's normal.
The sedation should
wear off soon enough.
Sandra?
Dr. Fleming is here
and has authorized this examination,
so there should be
no cause for alarm.
We're your friends.
You're home, Luc.
I have a few questions for you.
Please answer yes or no.
I want to talk to Dr Sandra.
Just answer the questions.
Do you see yourself
as a person who is a reliable worker?
Yes.
Do you see yourself as a person
who is original, comes up with new ideas?
No.
Is relaxed?
Handles stress well?
Yes.
Starts quarrels
with others?
Sometimes.
Yes or no.
I'm gonna give you something
that will help with your recovery.
I'm gonna make you
feel better, Luc.
Gonna make you
whole again.
Where am I?
LUC.' Where am I?
We started him on a mixture
of both psychotropic drugs and ergogenics.
His system isn't
ready for that. Methylphenidate
and mentenolone...
Please, listen to me.
His nervous system
will break down.
You can't reverse
years of hormonal therapy in a day.
It's like rehabilitating
a fight dog, then putting it back to fight.
This could backfire
in a myriad of ways.
Rehabilitation was
never part of his design.
And as you can see,
he's at odds with his nature.
He was created to serve a need,
and he's not doing that.
But now you're just
compounding the situation.
Dr. Fleming,
you have to ask yourself
whether a dog, once it has tasted blood,
can ever forget that taste.
There is substantial
power inside of him
that I have spent
two years regulating.
If you unleash
it this quickly,
you may not be
able to control it.
Just get him up
to speed, Doc.
You let me worry
about controlling it.
Listen. You said something
about some pipes earlier.
Yes, sir.
You still think you can
get in through there?
I know I can, sir.
Okay, we're gonna try this your way.
Listen to me.
This is strictly recon.
Do not engage this thing.
It's not combat.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's go.
(MEN CHATTERING IN RUSSIAN)
(SHOUTS)
(GROANS)
Why is she in there?
Unfortunately, at the moment,
she's the only one he trusts.
You know,in business,
as in life, people are so distrustful.
- They always want insurance.
- Yes, sir.
I mean, whatever happened
to the handshake deal? Am I right?
You're right, sir.
Fail-safe.
Everybody wants a fail-safe.
But where is my fail-safe?
Mmm? You understand?
Yes, Doctor.
No, no, I'm asking you.
Where's my fail-safe?
This is your failsafe.
And why is that? Mmm?
Because the NGU cannot
hurt the commander and his men.
Right.
But... But he can.
Indeed he can.
Very smart, Doctor.
Of course it is.
You see, Miles, there's always
a way around things.
Now, I want you to
count his fingers and toes.
No, I'm just kidding.
We've come a long way from
replicating sheep, wouldn't you say, Miles?
Yes, sir.
Happy birthday, my boy.
(PIPE'S COVER MAKING NOISE)
Colonel, I can
disconnect this thing.
That'll tip
them off too soon.
Find the kids. Do not engage
the freak. We need you alive.
Roger that.
(IN RUSSIAN)
He's going to do as
he threatens, you know.
Are you listening to me?
I have to address
the country in an hour.
I can't discuss this
with you right now.
You are not alone in this.
You think
I don't know this?
Sending in troops was
the act of a desperate man.
That frightens me.
They've left me
with no choice.
Yes they have.
Is it right to sacrifice
others' children but not our own?
And what then?
What is proved?
I am obliged to
think beyond myself.
Beyond our son
and daughter.
Obliged to what?
Your image in history?
If you allow something
to happen to them,
I will never forgive you.
(MEN CHATTERING IN RUSSIAN)
(PEOPLE WHISPERING
IN RUSSIAN)
I hear two voices.
You guys picking this up? Over.
There's a female voice.
That must be where he's got the kids.
We don't have
all day, Miles.
Yeah, right.
Okay, Doctor, all right.
Miles is gonna run the diagnostic today,
Andrew. Are you okay with that?
Yes.
Okay, first question.
You are a punctual
and reliable person.
Yes.
You know how to
make efficient use of your time.
Yes.
Okay. Friends find you impulsive
and unpredictable.
No.
You like to spend
leisure time relaxing
in a tranquil
family atmosphere.
Yes.
You often contemplate
the complexity of life.
Yes.
Andrew, did you
hear the question?
Hook him up.
Yes, sir.
Okay, just a sec.
Andrew, listen carefully.
You often contemplate
the complexity of life.
No.
That's right.
You have to listen, Andrew.
It's important.
(MUSAYEV SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
As the leader of
a nation in crisis,
my decisions have been dictated
by a single principle:
To serve the common
good of the people,
no matter what might be sacrificed
in the process.
While pride demands aggression
be met with aggression,
humanity depends on diplomatic and peaceful
conflict resolution.
It is therefore the responsibility of those
in positions of power
to question any
hard line policy
that threatens
survival as we know it.
Therefore,
I have authorized
the release of 110 prisoners
in exchange for immediate deactivation
of the detonator
at Chernobyl reactor three.
Over the next 48 hours
all troops will stand down
in ceasefire mode,
as the terms of exchange
are implemented.
The remaining prisoners
will then be released
in exchange for the hostages.
(ALL CHEERING)
It's over, Luc.
We might have had our
share of differences,
but it is the result
that is important, yes?
Yes.
For a world leader to
give in to the demands
of a small outfit
such as our own,
one should savor the rarity
of the experience.
The thing is,
to stop at this moment would be a shameful waste
of both leverage and position.
Yeah, you're young, you'll learn, but now
we have to move...
It is over,
and that is that.
That's not really
for you to say,
because there have been expenses.
Unanticipated expenses.
It's hard to budget these things in advance.
Now, I have an army to build.
And, like you said,
moments like these
don't often
present themselves.
I don't think
you're hearing me.
You want to fuck around?
Is that what you're trying to do?
You have been paid.
You and me, our business
together, it is all over.
You want to try
to test me? Huh?
Easy. Easy.
Who is this?
Vasilly!
Okay. Very good.
That's a good boy.
We have to go now.
You have to finish your job.
Then we'll go.
Hmm? The children.
Can I ask you a question?
(LAUGHING)
No, you cannot.
You often contemplate
the complexity of life?
Hey, it's not for you to ask questions,
understand?
Andrew.
Yes or no?
Andrew, you're tired.
You've been through a lot today.
Are you a punctual
and reliable person?
I don't like
your tone. Sit.
You answer my question.
I'm not gonna...
How do you feel?
Do you feel warm?
Do you need me
to cool you off? Mmm?
Answer me.
Answer my question.
You answer my question.
I'm not gonna an...
Andrew, I want you to sit down.
I need to help... To cool you off now, please.
Sit down. I order you to sit!
Stop it.
You have to...
You know how to put
every minute of your time to good purpose?
No! This is a mistake...
Are you rested?
(CHOKING)
Are you happy?
Stop. Stop. No.
Yes or no?
You often think about
humankind and its destiny?
Yes or no?
(GRUNTING)
Who am I?
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(SHUSHING)
(WHISPERING) Be quiet.
I'm on your side. It's okay. It's okay.
Are you one of them?
Who? One of the ones
who can't be killed?
Let's hope so. Now come with me and
be very quiet. Come on.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, let's go!
(BEEPING)
Colonel, they've reactivated
the detonators.
What the hell are
you talking about? Look.
What's the communication status
on Captain Burke?
None.
TECHNICIAN: Game's back on.
Communications are down.
We've got no way of knowing if anyone's
alive over there.
What about Burke?
Nothing.
Is it possible your creation might have had
an episode, Dr. Porter?
It's possible.
Thirty minutes.
We're officially at Defcon One.
Where are we with Deveraux?
As he is right now, he wouldn't stand
a chance against the NGU.
Dr. Fleming?
If we proceed with
the double dosage
and leave him
something in reserve,
it's possible we
can get him there.
Then let's do it.
But understand this
is your last bullet.
Assuming he survives,
there'll be no controlling him,
no communication hookup.
He'll know only what
he's been programmed for.
To find those kids
and stop the detonation.
Beyond that...
Who's gonna dose him?
It's not gonna be safe
in there. I'll do it.
No, I will.
I owe it to him.
I know what's happening.
What is happening, Luc?
I'm going back.
I'm going to fight.
Yeah.
I remember.
Give it to me.
I'll do it.
I want to be
here with you.
It's not safe for you.
It's okay.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Go now.
(GROANS)
(CHOKING)
(GRUNTS)
Go.
(EXHALES)
(ALL CLAMORING)
(SCREAMING)
(GUNFIRE)
Run! Run! Get out of here! Run!
Go, go, go! Run!
(GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
Fucking prick.
Fucking prick...
(GROANS)
Keep asking them
questions, just...
Trying to get some...
An answer.
Nothing.
Just a simple yes or no.
It's ridiculous.
I knew I had
something to tell you.
It was right there on
the tip of my tongue.
Shit.
I'm sure I'll remember
it in a minute, just... Just wait right there.
Something so familiar.
Can't explain it.
You know exactly what
I'm talking about, right?
You understand.
You don't have to answer.
We're good
like that, right?
We've been over
this all before.
I'm just gonna
do something here.
(GROANING)
(YELLS)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
I just remembered what
I wanted to tell you.
Wait a second.
(PANTING)
(BEEPING)
That's Luc.
DR. PORTER: He's just
used the booster shot.
Something must
have slowed him down.
We'll get another
20 good minutes out of him.
DR. PORTER: I hope.
Come with me.
(GIRL SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
(BEEPING)
(SCREAMS)
(TIMER CONTINUES BEEPING)
(EXHALES)
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org