(BEBOP MUSIC PLAYING)
(REX VOCALIZING)
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Get it, Shorty!
(CLAMORING)
Here, you want it?
want it?
Here, take it, take it!
AII right,
aII right.
Come on.
(GRuNTING)
(CHICKS SHOuTING)
(GRuNTS)
(CHICKS LAuGHING)
(TwITTERING)
(TwITTERING LOuDLY)
(EXCLAIMS)
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey! what about me?
what about me?
Here's food.
fight over it.
Now, George...
OnIy way
they'II Iearn.
(ALL CLAMORING)
(RAzzING)
That was not fair.
Oh, baby,
my sweet baby.
CHICKS: (IN SINGSONG)
Mommy's IittIe birdie.
He's so adorabIe.
Ma, don't do that.
You're acting
Iike I just hatched.
what am I, a chick?
Guess the writing's
on the waII.
It's time to Ieave the nest.
MOTHER BIRD: Buster, wait.
You're stiII too young.
This fIying's a snaP.
SurPrised I ain't
done it before.
(TIRES SCREECH)
(HuMMING)
ExPect a Postcard
from some PIace warm.
Miami, maybe Cuba.
BuSTER:
Arrivederci, Mama.
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(SIGHING)
Hey! wait,
what... Hey!
HeIIo there,
IittIe feIIa.
where'd you faII from?
No PIace.
Just Ieave me aIone.
No PIace? No PIace?
Never been there.
what's your name?
Buster.
weII, Buster,
don't you have
a mom somewhere
that's ProbabIy
worried about you?
BuSTER: (CHuCKLING) Yeah.
So, what are you gonna
endeavor to do now?
I'm gonna run away
and join the circus.
Oh, the circus, the circus.
Now, you're taIking sense.
The circus is an ocean
with some sPice.
You know, I know
a IittIe feIIow who ran away
and joined the circus.
Say, ain't you
a dinosaur?
why, yes.
from tooth to toe, I am.
Then what the heck
are you doing
PIaying goIf?
I'm smart, Buster.
I'm one smart dinosaur.
But I wasn't aIways.
You weren't?
No. No, sirree.
No, I started off
stuPid and vioIent.
You did?
This was a Iong time ago,
you understand?
A Iong time ago.
I was a reaI terror then.
I was a reaI animaI.
And I was hungry
aII the time.
(SCREAMING)
(ROARING)
(wHIMPERING)
Ah, a PotentiaI customer.
(wHISTLES)
Oh, heIIo, Madam.
Oh, sir, this is
your Iucky day.
Through a Iengthy Process
of random seIection,
your gaIaxy,
your PIanet,
your neighborhood,
hoId on to your taiI
now, kiddo.
You, yes, you have been
chosen as the beneficiary
of a PromotionaI camPaign.
(LAuGHING) Yes.
Here, before your very eyes,
I have a Product.
(GuLPS)
A revoIutionary Product.
You haven't tasted
stuff Iike this before.
(LAuGHING)
Brain Grain cereaI.
Take one bite,
you'II have an idea.
Take two bites,
you'II have a hyPothesis.
You'II be smart.
Comes in two fIavors,
reguIar or nutty-nut.
Choose your Poison, Partner.
You're gonna Iove this.
Yes, sirree bob.
Remember your manners,
you big-mouthed,
jaw-droPPing carnivore.
(EXCLAIMS)
That's it. I'm irritated.
I'm going back
to the shiP.
(ROARING)
(LAuGHS)
Lunchtime!
(ROARING)
(SINGING)
Row your boat
gently down the stream
Huh?
Row, row, row
VORB:
what a PersonaIity.
your boat...
Thank goodness
for chrome hunger.
It's taken 280 Portions
of Brain Grain to jumPstart
that skuII of yours, PaI.
...merrily, merrily
Life is but a dream
(LAuGHING)
How about some more?
(VORB CLAMORING)
(ROBOT ARM SCOLDING)
Lunch?
what's Iunch?
(BELCHES)
Oh, excuse me.
VORB: Hey, why don't
you check out the other
Brain Grain graduates?
I gotta rePort
to CaPtain Neweyes.
Get sociaI.
Hi, everybody.
(STAMMERING)
Oh. Oh.
''My name is Rex.''
Hey, how did
I do that?
I'm EIsa.
Enchanted
and deIighted to make
your acquaintance, Rex.
(CHuCKLING)
Pardon my wingsPan,
won't you PIease?
(CLEARING THROAT)
Yeah, okay.
Hey, I'm woog.
You want a hot dog?
Or do you want a hot dog?
Is it good?
words faiI me.
How many we had
so far today, Dweeb?
250, and that's
with everything.
Take it
on faith, Rex.
You want
a hot dog bad.
Hi, I'm Dweeb.
He's gotta
have mustard on it.
And don't forget
the sauerkraut.
I was amazed
by the sauerkraut.
wOOG:
She Iaid an egg.
(wOOG LAuGHING)
(LAuGHING) I did.
I Iaid an egg.
I was so embarrassed.
Rex, I feeI such a fooI,
but I must say it.
You are a rough
and handsome feIIow.
(CHuCKLES)
forgive me,
I'm so fIighty.
(CLEARING THROAT)
(SNIffING)
SmeIIs good.
(EXCLAIMS)
Hey, that's
what I caII
(ROARING) Iunch!
DwEEB: Lunch?
That's what
you used to caII me.
Hey, I'm sorry
about the way I've acted.
I was a reaI animaI.
we aII have
regrets, Rex.
TeII me about it.
The things I've stePPed on.
(CHuCKLES)
Let's face it.
we've evoIved.
REX: wow.
(HuMMING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Greetings, friends,
and weIcome to my shiP.
I'm CaPtain Neweyes.
I Iive in the far future,
where aII the sPecies
on aII the PIanets
have had to Iearn
to get aIong, eh, Vorb?
That's the truth, skiPPer.
I've made a fortune out of
my Brain Grain cereaI,
and now in my goIden years,
I'm trying to
give something back.
I'm trying to make
a few wishes come true,
and to that end,
I invented this.
It's a wish radio.
with it, I can hear
what PeoPIe are wishing for,
esPeciaIIy young PeoPIe
because they wish the Ioudest.
Now, Iet me tune into
this one station
in the middIe future.
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
(CHILDREN WHISPERING)
I wish I had a moustache
just like Daddy.
WOMAN: I wish...
I wish my sister
was nicer to me.
I wish all the dinosaurs
would be here right now.
I wish I could see
a Tyrannosaurus Rex.
''Rex''? why, CaPtain,
that's me. That's me.
I wish I could see
one of those flying dinosaurs.
(CHuCKLING)
why, that's me. I fIy.
(STAMMERING)
I wish I could see
a padasaurus.
(EXCLAIMING)
This is great.
BOY: I wish I could see
a triceratops.
I wish I could see
more dinosaurs...
Dinosaurs.
(CHuCKLING)
Son of a gunosaur,
that's us.
That's right.
That's you.
There are a Iot of
chiIdren down there
in this one ParticuIar
time that miss you,
and they're
wishing for you.
I've never heard
a Iouder wish.
So I gave you
aII Brain Grain,
and now you're
smart enough to
make uP your own minds.
who's that?
They're young PeoPIe,
boys and girIs.
They want to meet you.
what do you say?
Gee, I wish
I had a friend.
we'II do it.
why not?
I'd Iove to.
By aII means.
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
I wish I had
a Thanksgiving hat.
(SIGHING)
(ALARM RINGING)
(wHISTLES)
Excuse me,
CaPtain Neweyes, sir.
we've arrived.
Thank you, Vorb.
You may oPen
the Pod bay doors.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
It's a worId
covered with jeweIs.
(MuMBLING)
Look at aII those Iights.
Now, there are
two PeoPIe down there
you shouId know about.
One Person is
there to heIP you.
Her name is
Dr. JuIiet BIeeb.
I Iike her face,
so fuII of character.
Welcome, welcome.
CAPTAIN NEwEYES:
She knows you're coming.
She needs you to
fuIfiII the wishes
of many chiIdren.
Her address is
The Museum
of NaturaI History.
Now, the other Person
you shouId know about
is my brother,
Professor Screweyes.
(SCREAMING)
He's crueI.
He's insane.
He traveIs around
down in this time
causing mischief.
He was driven mad
by the Ioss
of his eye Iong ago.
My advice to you is
find Dr. BIeeb
and stay weII cIear
of my dark
and unhaPPy brother.
Beyond that,
just try not to
steP on anybody.
(TITTERING)
(GRuNTS)
AII right.
You got the boat
ready, Vorb?
Aye, aye, skiPPer.
CAPTAIN NEwEYES:
fareweII, my friends.
(ALL SCREAMING)
You gotta be kidding.
Arrivederci. Goodbye.
(DINOSAuRS SCREAMING)
(DwEEB LAuGHING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO)
(MUSIC DISTORTING)
(GASPING)
(SIGHING)
(COuGHING)
weII, great day
in the morning.
(EXCLAIMING)
wow.
Magnificent.
Gee whiz.
ELSA: what is it?
It's New York City,
you moron.
(ALL GASPING)
whoa there,
IittIe feIIa.
(COuGHING)
(LOuIE GASPS)
Hi, my name's Dweeb.
I'm woog.
I'm EIsa.
The name's Rex.
what's yours?
I think my name is Louie,
but seeing you
is giving me doubts
about my brain.
what are you guys,
anyway?
Dinosaurs, actuaIIy.
Dinosaurs, huh?
You do got that Iook.
I mean, you are big.
weII, you're
very smaII.
I'm big enough
to suit
my own PurPoses.
what are you,
a bat?
I'm a PterodactyI,
actuaIIy.
(ELSA EXCLAIMING)
(ELSA LAuGHING)
weII, what are you?
I was a runaway
to the circus tiII
you cIowns sank me.
what's the circus?
It's the big toP,
Ieatherhead.
Show business.
You guys ain't Iived.
where you guys
going, anyways?
we're going to
The Museum
of NaturaI History.
That's Perfect.
There's a circus
showing in CentraI Park.
One's right by the other.
Give me a Iift
to the circus,
take a gander,
and cross right over
to the museum.
Showing uP
with a Pack
of dinosaurs
shouId Put me
in reaI soIid
with the ringmaster.
what do you say?
weII, I'm game.
Okay.
CertainIy.
Okay, yeah.
(REX EXCLAIMING)
(GuLLS CAwING)
weIcome to New York City.
(GASPING)
(REX SCREAMING)
Rex!
HeIP, I can't swim!
Hang on, big feIIa!
Lift me uP.
LOuIE: Think, think,
think, think, think.
Think, Louie, think.
HeIP!
Okay.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Grab on!
(wHEEzING)
I wish...
I remember you.
LOUIE: Gee, I wish
I had a friend.
I owe you one, Louie.
(CHuCKLES)
These things haPPen.
(GASPS SOfTLY)
(EXHALES)
Just get me to
the circus, and we'II
say no more about it.
Ow!
LOuIE: Be carefuI, wiII you?
I can't be saving you
every two minutes.
Late. Late again.
Late for everything.
weIcome to New York City.
Oh. They're not here.
I've missed them
with my endIess,
shameIess Iateness.
Oh, weII,
we'II rendezvous.
(SCOOTER STARTING)
(TRAffIC BuSTLING)
You know,
New York isn't
ready for you guys.
we need a PIan.
I got it.
Hey you, the bat.
I am not a bat.
I am a PterodactyI.
Can you fIy?
(CHuCKLING)
(SCREAMING)
(SHOuTING)
CouId you get me off
of this thing?
LOuIE: watch out
for the skyscraPer.
(LOuIE SCREAMING)
LOuIE: Coming through!
LOuIE: Goodbye!
You're gonna get us kiIIed!
I'm gonna sIiP off.
PuII uP!
You're going too fast!
SIow down, aIready!
SIow down!
(LOuIE SCREAMING)
(LOuIE wHIMPERING)
ELSA: (CHuCKLING)
where exactIy
wouId you Iike to go?
(STuTTERING)
(EXCLAIMS)
There, right there.
That's our ticket uPtown.
Let's hang a Louie
and head on back.
(CRYING)
whoa! whoa! whoa!
Hit the brakes,
I gotta Iand a minute.
HeIIo.
(SCREAMS)
Hey, hey, hey,
don't Panic.
I'm a good guy.
who are you?
And what's that?
Hey, babe, I'm Louie.
That there's
a friend of mine. I got...
(SLIDING DOOR CLOSING)
I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to frighten you.
why are you crying?
I am not crying.
Huh?
Back off. Back off.
You're fogging the gIass.
Come on, big eyes,
you're kiIIing me.
what's the matter?
It's Thanksgiving.
So, what's there
to cry about?
You don't Iike turkey?
No, it's my Parents.
what about your Parents?
Do they beat you?
(MuSIC BOX PLAYING)
No, they're just
never around.
It's Thanksgiving,
and they're off
doing other things.
You see,
my father's very business,
and my mother's
very sociaI.
The name's Louie.
what's yours?
CeciIia Nuthatch.
weII, CeciIia Nuthatch,
you shouId've had my mother
sIobbering kisses
aII over me in PubIic.
I had to make tracks,
so you know
what I'm doing?
No. what?
I'm running away
to the circus.
You are?
I am.
what do you say
you throw this hat away
and come fIy with me?
(CHuCKLES)
AII right, I wiII.
(SLuRPING)
(GLASS SQuEAKING)
Hey, I'm getting hungry.
(DwEEB EXCLAIMING)
(CATS SCREECHING)
I hoPe they're okay.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
Hey, watch
where you're going.
Hey, Iook!
There they are.
REX: (EXCLAIMING)
They have a IittIe girI
with them.
Everybody, I'd Iike you
to meet my new friend,
CeciIia Nuthatch.
The name's Rex.
Nice to meet you.
A PIeasure, Rex.
Very nice to meet you.
And I'm
Dweeb. Hi.
A PIeasure, Dweeb.
Very nice to meet you.
She's so
weII brought uP.
AII right, break it uP.
Enough with the PIeasantries.
These are aII dinosaurs.
(wOOG LAuGHING)
I'm hungry...
I mean, I'm woog.
CeciIia Nuthatch.
I'm very PIeased
to meet you, woog.
Have you been
a dinosaur Iong?
Enough with this
tea-Party chatter.
(EXCLAIMING)
what are you,
some kind
of a debutante?
CECILIA: why, yes,
as a matter of fact, I am.
LOuIE: Oh.
(GROwLING SuGGESTIVELY)
(LAuGHING)
Rex!
Listen, I've figured out
a way you guys can stroII
uPtown and not cause a riot.
Come on.
(PLAYING MARCHING SONG)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(GASPING)
(PRIMITIVE MuSIC PLAYING)
(CHILDREN EXCLAIMING)
BOY 1 : They're enormous!
MAN: I can't beIieve it.
GIRL 1 : Oh! Look what's
coming down the street.
BOY 2: Dinosaurs. Quick.
Lift me uP
higher, Dad.
Dinosaurs at the Parade.
GIRL 2: Are they gonna
eat us?
Dinosaurs! Quick!
HoIy smoke,
are they ever big!
Dinosaurs!
No, Sasha,
they're not dinosaurs.
They're robots.
I wish I couId
see reaI dinosaurs.
I wish I couId see
a reaI dinosaur!
I wish they were reaI.
Dinosaurs, Iook, dinosaurs!
Yeah, wouIdn't it be great
if they were reaI?
CooI.
(LAuGHING)
(SINGING)
Roll back the rock
to the dawn of time
When the Earth was smoking
and the lava flowed
Roll back the rock
to the dawn of time
And blow your cool
just like a volcano
Snap your fingers
and stomp your feet
Soaking up a little
of thejungle beat
Roll back the rock
to the dawn of time
And sing this song with me
Roll back the rock
ALL: (SINGING)
Turn back the clock
Roll back the rock
to the dawn of time
And sing this song with me
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(LAuGHING)
(LAuGHING) No!
(wHOOPING)
Turn back the clock
Baby, you can see
Why the 20th century
appeals to me
So much to learn
and so much to do
And a zillion
wonderful things to chew
Roll back the rock
Turn back the clock
to the dawn of time
And sing this song with me
So, CeciIia,
what do you think
of my friends?
I think they're swank,
first rank.
ToP hat, right down
to their taiIs.
Say what?
And I Iike
you, too.
Hey, shut uP
with that.
what are you, saPPy?
(wAILING)
Ifyou're thinking
this guy's unreal
Just imagine
how I must feel
Just imagine how I must feel
Human beings, what a meal!
Roll back the rock
to the dawn of time
And sing this song with me
REX: Hey, hey.
what do you know?
There's another feIIa
just Iike me.
Good to see somebody
of a simiIar Persuasion,
if you know what I mean.
Put 'er there.
Roll back the rock
Turn back the clock
to the dawn of time
And sing this song with me
Hi.
Look, Mommy,
those are reaI dinosaurs.
(GASPING)
They're reaI.
GIRL: They're not robots.
They're aIive.
Gosh, reaI dinosaurs!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
CeciIia, I think things
just took a turn
for the worse.
CECILIA: Louie!
Quick, sPIit uP.
we'II meet you at
the circus in CentraI Park.
Now, run!
CentraI Park?
where is CentraI Park?
(ALL SCREAMING)
''Professor Screweyes'
Eccentric Circus.''
Professor Screweyes!
That's the bad guy.
ELSA: Gracious.
''Now aPPearing
in CentraI Park.''
Louie, CeciIia,
they're in danger.
we gotta save them.
OFFICER ON BULLHORN:
You, there! Don't move!
(SIRENS wAILING)
You're under arrest!
Put your claws up!
(ALL SCREAMING)
OffICER: Hit the deck!
watch out for the big one.
(OffICERS CLAMORING)
(HORN HONKING)
(HuMMING)
There we are.
''Dinosaur exhibit.
The Museum
of NaturaI History.''
You can't skimP on PubIicity.
(wHIMPERING)
LARRY ON RADIO: All right,
it's The Larry King Show.
We're back.
We have a lady with us
who says she has seen
a real dinosaur.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Okay, to midtown. Ma'am?
Larry, I was taking a shower
just now and I looked
out my bathroom window,
and I saw a dinosaur.
LARRY: Okay, thanks
for calling. See you.
(SQuAwKING)
PILOT ON RADIO:
Central chopper one.
Pursuing Mesozoic suspect.
(SCREAMING)
(DwEEB SCREAMING)
(GRuNTING)
My name is Dweeb.
Hi, nice to see you.
Nice hat.
(MAN SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(ON RADIO) Chopper one
to chopper two,
suspect's no longer in sight.
I lost him.
How about taking a 10-30
for coffee and donuts?
(LAuGHING)
(SCREAMING)
(HORNS HONKING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING)
OffICER: Hey, we've got
them surrounded.
Don't Iet them get away.
Hmm.
OFFICER ON BULLHORN:
We got you surrounded.
Give yourselves up.
(SCREAMING)
(SIRENS wAILING)
(ALARM BuzzING)
(REX SCREAMING)
(DwEEB LAuGHING)
''Professor Screweyes'
Eccentric Circus.''
(CROw CAwING)
The maP
on the fIyer said
that this was
the nearest entrance
to the circus.
Come on.
Okay.
uh, it's
a IittIe dark here.
Seems a IittIe creePy,
doesn't it?
Hey, CeciIia, Iook!
''Professor Screweyes'
Eccentric Circus.''
This must be
the right way.
Come on.
Oh, Iook, there's
another sign.
(CAT SCREECHING)
(BOTH PANTING)
You know, Louie...
Yeah?
I reaIIy hate
to say this.
Then don't.
um, it's getting dark.
Maybe we shouId
go back.
I don't know.
Maybe you're right.
wait a minute,
there it is.
(SNORTING)
(SHRIEKS)
what are you
Iooking at?
I didn't mean to.
I was just...
Hey, she's
Iooking at whatever
she wants to, chumP.
Says who?
I do.
want to make
something of it?
Louie, don't.
There's three of them.
Better Iisten
to your friend.
You jerks
don't scare me.
Back off,
or I'II feed you
a knuckIe sandwich.
You shouIdn't
have done that.
Hey, you can't
take a steP back
from those kind of creePs.
Oh, Louie,
you're very brave.
Yeah, weII,
get off it.
Come on.
(CIRCuS MuSIC PLAYING)
(LAuGHING)
(GASPING)
PROfESSOR SCREwEYES:
who Iaughed?
I did.
No, it was
me, sir.
Stubbs,
get out of here.
You missed the show, kids.
Come back tomorrow.
(CLEARS THROAT)
So, was that your audience
we Passed coming here?
ProbabIy.
SPooky bunch.
I aPPeaI to
a ParticuIar grouP.
what do you want?
weII, we ran away
from home, see...
I see. You ran away
to the circus.
That's right.
You got it.
weII, you ran away
to the wrong circus, kid.
Buzz off.
um, Louie,
I think we shouId go.
(CAwING)
(LAuGHING)
Take your girIfriend's
advice, sPort.
You don't want us?
Oh, I'II take you in,
if you want.
Louie, PIease.
I'm not so sure...
weII, it's
a standard contract.
But there's nothing
written on it.
I try to
keeP things simPIe.
want to sign?
(EXCLAIMS)
Press it to the contract.
Louie, I'm scared.
You are? Good.
(EXCLAIMS)
(GROANS)
CECILIA: And there.
CeciIia?
weII, kids, weIcome
to Professor Screweyes'
Eccentric Circus.
weIcome aboard.
ELSA: Yoo-hoo!
Louie! CeciIia!
REX: where are you?
who's that?
Oh, it's okay.
They're friends
of mine.
Come on,
I'II show you.
It's him.
Professor Screweyes.
CeciIia, get away
from that man.
Hey, chiII out.
we just joined
his circus.
REX: That's
Professor Screweyes.
we were warned
about him.
warned? By whom?
Your brother.
So that's
how you got here
and why you can taIk.
He's fed you that
Brain Grain stuff
and he warned you
about me, eh?
Let him Iook
to his own affairs.
Did he show you
that hokey
wish radio of his?
Yes, we heard
what PeoPIe
are wishing for.
weII, I have
a radio, too.
Let me show you.
NoPe, no way, nada.
we don't want anything
to do with you.
Come on, kids.
Come to the museum
with us.
The Museum
of NaturaI History.
They're not
going anywhere.
They are
under contract to me
for a very Iong time.
(GuLPS)
(SOBBING)
But these are
the first chiIdren
we've met.
we Iike them.
Hey, come on.
It's gonna
be aII right.
Oh, I don't think so,
unIess we can
work something out
with your friends here.
Hmm?
(CACKLING)
This is a time
of Ioud wishes, yes,
but even Iouder fears.
This is a fright radio.
It Picks uP what PeoPIe
are scared to death of.
You see, I find out
what they're frightened
of on this radio,
and that's what
I try to give them
with my circus.
It's a PubIic service.
But this is the station
that comes in
the Ioudest of aII.
(CHILDREN CRYING)
There's something
behind the door.
There's monsters
in the forest, I bet.
Monsters are gonna eat me.
I hope a monster
doesn't get me.
Eyes staring at me.
(CHILDREN SCREAMING)
(LAuGHING)
Do you see what
they're most afraid of?
No.
Monsters.
Monsters?
You!
us?
with a IittIe heIP, yes.
what's that?
It's Brain Drain.
The remedy to
my brother's goody
two-shoes breakfast cereaI.
It'II take you back.
It'II make you monsters.
But we don't want
to be monsters.
Mmm-mmm.
we're not
taking anything.
You can forget it.
AII right, you're free.
You can go.
I can't stoP you,
but the kids are mine.
(STAMMERING)
what are you doing?
Don't Iook, CeciIia.
I can't heIP it.
Among my many other rights
under this contract,
incIuding coPyrights
on aII their ideas,
I've got an excIusive oPtion
on their wiIIPower.
Now, this is just
a temPorary dose,
by way of demonstration.
(ELSA GASPING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(CAwING)
Change them back,
or I'II...
Or you'II what?
You're too enIightened
by my brother's
Brain Grain.
You've Iost
your savagery.
You've Iost your
frightening, Prehistoric
Power to intimidate.
You're civiIized now
and I've got a contract,
and you're gonna
resPect that Iike
the chumPs that you are.
But I'II teII you
what I'd be wiIIing to do.
You aII agree to
take the Brain Drain,
and I'II riP uP this contract
and set the kids free.
If you don't take it,
I'II biII them as the wiId
chiIdren of HeIIzaPoPPin,
and use them
to scare PeoPIe
in the sideshow.
It's uP to you.
(GASPING)
(SIGHING)
I'II take it.
And I'II take it,
you Ioathsome creature.
I'II do it.
Me, too.
Good, now you
come with me.
You're going to
have to be kePt
in cages and chains,
because you're gonna
be wiId again.
(MONKEYS CHIRPING)
(YAwNING)
Don't be scared.
You'II be aII right.
It's no more
than a bad dream.
PROfESSOR SCREwEYES:
Come on, you.
we were friends
for a minute, Louie.
(MOANS)
Rex.
Remember me.
(DOOR CLOSING)
(BIRDS TwITTERING)
(GASPING)
(EXHALES)
(CECILIA LAuGHING)
Good morning, Louie.
Good morning.
STuBBS: Good morning.
Louie, it's that
funny cIown.
I brought you breakfast.
Pancakes okay?
LOuIE: Great.
CECILIA: Oh, yes. SPIendid.
So, you thought
I was funny?
Oh, yes, very funny.
I can never make
the Professor Iaugh.
weII, he is Pretty nutty,
don't you think?
weII, you know,
the show has gotten
Pretty weird
and scary, in a way.
(TITTERING)
I Iike comedy myseIf.
But the Professor Promises me
that if I can come uP with
a bit that makes him Iaugh,
he'II Put it in the show.
I just ain't been abIe
to bring it off yet,
that's aII.
what's
your name?
Stubbs the CIown.
formerIy of
the Iegitimate circus.
How you doing?
I'm CeciIia Nuthatch.
It's a PIeasure to
meet you, Mr. Stubbs.
Same at you.
Hey, do you want
to see a bit?
Sure.
watch this, watch this.
watch this.
This is just...
(STuBBS LAuGHS)
(EXCLAIMS)
(SCREAMING)
So, you thought
that was funny?
That was okay?
Yeah, of course
it was funny.
I showed it to the Prof.
He didn't Iaugh.
LOuIE: You don't
get it, do you?
That guy's crazy.
No, not reaIIy crazy.
He's just a IittIe bit
off in his...
Look, after breakfast,
he toId me you gotta
get out of here.
what about
the contract?
He tore them uP.
That was Iucky.
And our friends?
(STAMMERING)
Your... who?
You know,
the dinosaurs.
forget them.
Hey, no way.
where are they?
I'm teIIing you, you ought
to forget them and go about
your merry business.
where are they, Stubbs?
AII right, I'II show you,
but you're not gonna
Iike it, though.
Come with me.
(SQuAwKS)
(DINOSAuRS ROARING)
what's haPPened
to them,
Mr. Stubbs?
The Professor gave them
some stuff that sent them
off the deeP end.
That's why
he tore uP
your contracts.
That was a deaI
they made.
So, they're this way
'cause of me.
I guess so.
He's featuring them
in the show tonight.
AII the usuaI weirdoes
wiII show uP, I'm sure.
Stubbs, you gotta
get us in that show.
I can't do that.
Don't you see?
They did this
for us.
This guy's crazy, Stubbs.
He's never gonna
Iaugh at your jokes.
(CLATTERING)
(GROANING)
AII right,
I'II get you in,
but not 'cause of
what you said.
'Cause of her and you,
when you Iaughed.
Come on, I gotta
get ready for the show.
(HORNS SOuNDING)
Showtime.
(SCREAMING)
You bunch of doPes!
um, boo.
(wHISPERING) ''Boo''?
Is that the best
you can do?
They're easy
enough to scare.
(SCREAMING)
See?
(MAN SHRIEKING)
But, Louie, I don't
want to scare anybody.
weII, neither do I,
but do you want
to get busted?
AII right,
I'II try.
(SCREAMING)
(SHRIEKING)
I don't understand
these PeoPIe.
Don't you see?
That's why they come,
to get scared.
SimPIe as that.
(DRuMROLL)
Oh, the show's
starting uP.
we better get
to our PIaces.
we're in
the oPening bit.
Ladies and gentIemen,
weIcome to
the most terrifying show
on the PIanet Earth,
Professor Screweyes'
Eccentric Circus!
we wiII scare you.
(AuDIENCE SCREAMING)
we wiII frighten you.
we wiII shock you witIess
with our dreadfuI,
terrifying, viIe,
monstrous Program.
Ladies and gentIemen,
without further ado,
I give you the infernaI
grand demon Parade.
(wHISPERING)
Okay, this is it.
Just Iook scary
and wave your Pitchforks.
(BATS SCREECHING)
(LAuGHING MANIACALLY)
(AuDIENCE SCREAMING)
Louie, I feeI so siIIy.
what is wrong
with these PeoPIe?
I don't know,
but I've never seen
so many tonsiIs in my Iife.
(LAuGHING)
Here's your face.
(DRuMROLL)
Ladies and gentIemen,
I give you
the most fearsome creatures
of your darkest dreams.
I give you monsters!
(DINOSAuRS ROARING)
SmeIIing saIts here,
two for a doIIar.
SmeIIing saIts.
(SCREAMS)
Oh, Louie, Louie,
what can we do?
I don't know.
There's nothing
you can do.
And now I wiII
attemPt the imPossibIe.
I wiII attemPt to master
the most fearsome
of aII the dinosaur cIan,
the uItimate set of teeth
in the history of the worId.
The mighty
Tyrannosaurus Rex.
Look into my eye,
you bIoodthirsty thing.
(ROARING)
Remove his shackIes.
(AuDIENCE SCREAMING)
Now, take two giant stePs.
(CHuCKLES)
Take two stePs
toward the audience.
So you see, the creature
that scares you aII
does what I say.
I am the master of fear
and I am not afraid!
(ROARS)
(SNARLING)
(SHuDDERING)
Oh, no. No.
(SCREAMING)
The Professor.
He's gonna kiII
the Professor.
Rex, no.
Don't do it.
Louie!
what are you, crazy?
You'II be PuIverized.
No, don't do it.
(PROfESSOR SCREwEYES
wHIMPERING)
LOuIE: Rex, don't do it,
I'm teIIing you.
I know you can't
understand me,
but you gotta.
Oh, PIease don't
Iet bad haPPen.
You don't want
to be Iike him.
Don't ruin everything
'cause you're mad
or scared of something.
It can't be aII about that,
or what's Iife for?
I know I act Iike
I'm the originaI tough guy,
but that's 'cause
I'm scared, too.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(EXCLAIMS)
No.
Let no bad haPPen.
But you, you are
the originaI tough guy.
Rex, you've got
nothing to Prove.
You're a giant.
(PEOPLE GASPING)
Don't be a midget buIIy boy
for these yahoos.
Put him down, Rex.
''Rex.'' That means ''king.''
(CRYING) Be a king, Rex.
Put the guy down.
Don't be a stiff.
Don't be just another sIob
sPoiIing the way
the worId couId be.
PIease, PIease Put
him down. PIease.
(GASPING)
way to go, Rex!
(AuDIENCE APPLAuDING)
(GASPS)
wow.
(DINOSAuRS ROARING)
(CHuCKLING)
(GROANS)
Ooh!
(GASPS)
(VORB wHISTLING)
Okay, men.
fire when ready.
(HuMS TRIuMPHANT TuNE)
VORB: Incoming!
VORB: Let's fIy.
fire in the hoIe!
VORB: The whoIe sumo!
weII done, gentIemen.
Good work.
Brother.
I shouId've known
you were behind this.
You'd aIready Iost
by the time I'd arrived.
This boy had beaten you.
I heard your wish
on my wish radio.
Very good.
''Let no bad haPPen.''
CouIdn't agree more.
Louie?
You aII right, Rex?
Did I do anything bad?
No, you were great.
You were great,
too, Louie.
(EXCLAIMS IN DISGuST)
Don't do that.
why not?
It's embarrassing.
You kissing me
and everything,
it's unmanIy, just...
That is what it is.
You know, you're right.
I am?
weII, yes.
If anybody's kissing anybody,
you shouId be kissing me.
I shouId?
(CHuCKLING)
Most definiteIy.
(SIGHS)
I've been meaning
to taIk to you, Rex.
(EXCLAIMS)
About what, EIsa?
The way you Iook at me,
it makes me want to
Iay an egg.
(LAuGHING)
(SIGHS)
(ALARM RINGING)
(wHISTLES)
CaPtain Neweyes,
it's time to go.
Okay, everybody, on board.
I've got a surPrise for you.
Good night, foIks.
Good night, Louie.
Good night,
Stubbs.
PROfESSOR SCREwEYES:
Hey, Stubbs, where do you
think you're going?
Get back here.
Oh, I forgot to
teII you. I quit!
I quit. I resign.
Get this comPIeteIy
in your ear.
I am ProfoundIy
out of here!
And this ain't
about money.
I ain't even comPIaining
about my dry-cIeaning biII.
But hang around
with eIePhants aII day
and try to keeP
your cIothes cIean!
(AuDIENCE LAuGHING)
(SIGHS)
But that's not
the Point.
The Point is,
I quit. Quitski!
Over-and-outski!
That's aII she wrote!
KeeP my Iast check, buddy!
Here's my shoes,
my nose, my horn,
my buzzer, my fake arm,
my bug-eye gIasses,
my backstage Passes,
my hat, my rabbit,
his backstage Passes,
my fake fangs,
a few birds,
my Pogo stick,
my donkey ears,
my extending tongue gag,
my rubber chicken.
You can't even
get these anymore.
My Iucky whaIe tooth,
and a giant cIam
that oPens to reveaI
the American fIag
heId by a mermaid
and her normaI
brother, Richard!
So Iong!
(AuDIENCE LAuGHING)
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
And by the way,
in case you're wondering
why I'm taIking
and they're Iaughing,
Iet me exPIain it
to you.
That's comedy!
(AuDIENCE APPLAuDING)
wiII you
change your ways
and come with me?
Never.
Then we must go.
(EXCLAIMING)
(STAMMERS)
Brother, brother, wait.
when I am aIone,
when I have
no one to scare,
I get very frightened myseIf.
The crows couId...
(GASPING)
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
I'm coming. I'm coming.
I'II be there in a moment.
(EXCLAIMS)
weIcome, weIcome.
You've taken so Iong,
I aImost gave uP.
But the good CaPtain
exPIained.
You've had
so many adventures.
weII, you must be tired
after such doings.
DR. BLEEB: I'm sure
you'II sIeeP weII tonight.
Have your dreams
of this beautifuI worId,
and tomorrow, you'II begin
to fuIfiII the wishes
of many chiIdren.
we'II make beIieve
you're statues.
The aduIts wiII wait outside
as you reveaI the miracIe
of yourseIves to the young.
It'II be very good.
It'II be very good, indeed.
(CHILDREN CLAMORING)
(DR. BLEEB LAuGHING)
Thank you. Thank you.
I'II take them
from here, PIease.
Come on, chiIdren,
this way.
(CHILDREN GASPING)
wow.
CooI.
AII right, gang.
Go for it.
My name is woog.
what's yours?
Leo.
(CHILDREN CHuCKLING)
wow.
(GASPS)
(EXCLAIMS)
Look.
wow.
HeIIo, I'm EIsa.
Hi, there.
My name is Dweeb.
And I'm Rex.
(REX CHuCKLING)
Hi, I'm Max.
Hi, Max.
So, this'II be
our IittIe secret, okay?
Okay.
My name's Nick.
I'm frank.
DeIightfuI.
ReaIIy, just a reciPe
for deIightfuI.
(CHILDREN CLAMORING)
And that's the way it is.
And that's
what haPPened, Buster.
The dinosaurs are
stiII at the museum.
what about the kids?
Oh, Louie and CeciIia are
quite the IittIe couPIe now.
REX: And they made up
with their parents.
(TwITTERING)
Good night,
IittIe tough guy.
Remember my story.
CHICKS: (IN SINGSONG)
Mama's IittIe birdie.
(REX HuMMING)
(REX HUMMING)