Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Mike, can you please
let these single people
- have a private moment?
- I agree.
Maybe after dinner you two
could go for a ride or something?
Oh, that sounds great.
So nice.
That sounds nice.
Fun.
Trina ain't going
nowhere with him.
- Why not?
- Yeah, Mike.
Why can't this single woman go out
with this single man?
Can we just drop this, please?
I'm so agreeing with
Dianne right now.
- Let him answer.
- Marcus, get your wife.
Come on, baby.
Give me that drink.
No. As matter of fact,
let me get another drink.
So Mike can tell us why
Trina can't go with Troy.
Angela...
really. It's no big deal.
OK. Let's do it.
- Come on.
- Mike.
- No, no. Come on. Talk to me.
- Calm down.
- Eat your food, OK?
- No, no.
No. Let him talk.
Let him talk, Shelia.
She's just a little drunk.
Yeah. You know what, Marcus?
I may be a little drunk
but somebody
at this table got
some damn secrets.
- Really?
- That's enough.
No, no, no. Dianne...
somebody got some secrets.
What are they?
You know, I'm so sick
of this. I'm sick of it.
The reason she can't go
with this man or any other man
is because she's sleeping
with yours, Shelia.
What?
No.
Yeah, Shelia.
Oh, hell.
Well, y'all,
thanks for dinner.
But I should be going.
I think you need to stay, man. We're gonna
need some law enforcement around here.
I'm sorry.
Is it true?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's true.
That's my secret. I'm the bad guy.
I'm not the only married person
with a secret at this table.
Terry...
have you told your wife how you got
a DNA test on your daughter,
'cause you weren't sure
that she was yours?
Mike, don't go telling secrets, man.
Oh, no, no. Come on, Marcus.
Y'all talking about me. Hmm?
You put my secret out there.
Let's put everybody's secret
on the table, shall we?
Dianne, have you told
your husband that
you got your tubes tied after you
had Kenya and didn't tell him?
Hmm? That's what Shelia told me.
I'm sorry, Terry,
but your chances of having a boy?
- A little slim to none.
- Mike, wait. This has gone too far.
You are getting really dangerous now.
You need to stop this.
Gavin. Since you guys are walking
around here like the perfect couple.
Will you please inform your wife
how you came crying at my house
asking, "How could she be so stupid
"and not strap your son
in his car seat?" Hmm?
- What about that?
- You are a lowdown, dirty bastard...
- Shut up!
- No. You shut up!
- Marcus, please. Please.
- Oh, hell.
Please tell this woman the truth.
And I pray that it sets you free.
I pray, brother.
But I'm telling you, tell this woman
how Terry had to give you
a shot because you had VD.
Let's talk about condoms
now, shall we, Angela?
Oh, so you got VD?
Checkmate.
- Who you been with?
- Angela, let's discuss this in private.
No. You know what?
It seems like you guys
have been talking in private enough.
How long have you had it?
A week.
Was it Keisha?
No. You didn't get it from her.
You got it from Walter.
What are you talking about?
I ain't gay.
No. I slept with him.
I got a shot.
I was just waiting
for you to say something.
Boom!
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Don't!
I hope he breaks
your throat. Touchdown!
Get off of me!
- Man, come on, man. Come on!
- Don't be putting your hands on me!
Arrest him!
Get him. You see he
trying to kill me.
- Let me go.
- Arrest him, Troy!
That's why I slept with her!
You so damn evil!
You know what? You put your hands on
the wrong one, Marcus.
- I'm out of here.
- Get out of here.
Now, that's the best idea I heard
since we got up here.
Let's cut this trip short.
Baby, go pack our stuff.
We outta here.
Look, I'm sorry
you had to hear this way.
Thank your friend over there.
It's over.
I'll be more than fair,
but I want a divorce.
Hey, you can have
the rental property.
I'll have Paco put
bars on there for you,
so don't thank me or nothing.
It's a rough neighborhood.
You can have your car.
And I'll figure everything else out.
Huh?
Whatever.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I hope he's dead.
I'll get my medical bag.
# Oh, oh #
# Mmm... #
# Oh #
# Oh, ooh, ooh, ooh #
# Yeah #
# Givin' up #
# It's hard to do #
# When you really #
# Love someone #
# Givin' up... #
Shelia, you know you had the key
in the door.
You came to arrest me?
Actually, I saw
your car out front.
And I just came
to check on you.
Did I kill him?
No. You didn't kill him, but, uh...
Heh. He's gonna have
one hell of a headache.
I should have killed him.
Shelia, you don't mean that.
Maybe you do.
I gave him my life.
You know, he emptied out
my bank account?
I have $87 to my name.
I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
Well, if you've got a minute,
I'd like to show you something.
Hey, guys, I'm really
sorry about everything, OK?
I love you.
I'll call you later.
Bye, baby.
If anyone hears from Shelia,
we'll let each other know, right?
- Yes.
- Bye, guys.
All right, daddy.
Give that man what he wants.
Have a safe drive.
Are we gonna talk about this?
Gavin, please.
Not right now.
Oh, you're not gonna...?
I'll do it.
What?
You wasn't even
gonna tell me, were you?
Why did you test our daughter?
Because you are so damn busy
that when you got pregnant,
we had sex what... once?
Well, what were the results?
What do you mean?
She's mine.
Really?
Huh.
What the hell is
that supposed to mean?
What the hell
you saying, Dianne?
Yeah, OK.
OK.
It's snowing a little bit...
but this is where
I come to clear my head.
I just come right here.
I pray. I scream. I yell.
Do whatever I need to do.
And it's just me and God.
You ever come here to cry?
Yeah. That, too.
I can't even...
describe to you the pain I feel.
It's like I've been hit by a car.
I keep trying to understand.
Why I'm... what did I do... so wrong?
Why he betrayed me?
It hurts.
I have no life without him.
I can't even pray about it.
You know, Shelia,
this is a great time
for a new start
if you want to stay.
Oh. I thought you were
still at work.
I took the day off.
I'm gonna get dinner started.
We need to talk, Patricia.
I don't think so.
I know you heard what Michael said
at the table.
So you're not gonna deal with it?
Look, Gavin, I have dealt with this, OK?
This is what I do for a living.
I'm a doctor. I've dealt with this.
Yeah, well, you haven't
talked to me about it.
So now you want to talk to me
the way you did Mike?
Now you want to cry
your eyes out to me?
It's not like you made
it easy for me to discuss this.
Yeah, we talk about...
Noah like has never here.
Can you look at his picture?
Patricia, please.
Please put...
Can you just look at his picture?
Gavin, I didn't know...
- I didn't know you blamed me for it.
- I...
OK. I blamed you.
I blamed... I'm sorry.
OK? I blame myself, too.
I blamed God, but...
It's no one's fault.
Baby, just look at the picture.
All right.
Steak or chicken?
Patricia, no!
Look at the picture!
No! You know what?
Stop it!
- Patricia, look at...
- Stop it!
- Patricia, Patricia...
- Gavin, just stop it!
Patricia, just look at the picture.
Stop with your pretending.
- I'm not...
- Stop. Would you...
you pretend that you love me.
Stop with all those lies!
- I can't take this.
- Patricia.
You know you hate me.
I hate myself for this!
- I don't hate you. Baby.
- This is my fault!
- No. Don't touch me!
- Baby.
- Don't touch me.
- OK. Well...
No. Will you just listen
to me for once, please?
- It's not your fault.
- This is my fault.
I walk around here
trying to act like "perfect Patty. "
You know, well,
perfect Patty messed up.
- OK?
- No one's asking you...
No. Will you just listen...
Listen for a minute!
- I'm not...
- Listen!
Perfect Patty messed up.
I was in a hurry.
And...
I strapped him in.
But I didn't secure it.
I didn't check.
Check to see
if it was secure. And...
It was raining. And...
I slid off the road, and now...
And now?
- Now he's dead.
- I know. I know, baby.
- I know.
- He's not coming back.
You know, Gavin, I can
deal with a lot of things,
but this...
I'm not strong enough
to deal with this, baby.
Hey, you don't have to be...
strong by yourself.
Just let me be.
Let me be strong for you, OK?
We can make it through.
Baby, I'll be there for you.
No matter what.
Please...
I need to see Marcus.
OK.
Hold for one second.
What the hell
are you doing here?
- I need to see Marcus.
- No. You better get out of this building.
I need to see Marcus.
No. I said you better get out
of this building.
Oh, no, you didn't touch me!
I'm gonna pack you out of here!
You know who you
messin' with, huh?
- What are you doing here?
- Look, I need to talk to you.
About what?
Do you mind?
Yes, I mind. Marcus,
you better get her
the hell out of here before
I throw her out on her face!
Marcus, you better get that ho!
You better check that ho!
- You know what?
- Angie, Angie, Angie.
Let me take care of this.
Yeah. 'Cause I know
how to handle it!
He got a handle.
He can handle all of this.
- Get her. Deal with her.
- All this!
He handles it. And well!
Well, Miss Press n' Curl. Ya ho!
Y'all know I don't take that.
I kick ass up in here every Tuesday.
Y'all know who you work for!
You know who you work for!
What is it?
Yeah. You know what?
She's right here in this office.
Angela, talk to her.
I think that's
what you should do.
I'm not gonna talk to her.
If she says one thing to me,
I'm going to jail for murder.
Well, I'm a lawyer.
I'll get you off.
- Shelia's on line two.
- Oh!
Guys, Shelia's on line two.
I'm gonna conference us in, OK?
But you know what?
If you got to be that damn tenderheaded,
why don't you get out
of my damn chair?
Get out of my chair
looking like next ghetto top weave.
- Oh...
- Shelia?
Are you OK?
We've been trying to reach you.
Yeah. I'm... Mike turned
my cell phone off.
Shelia, honey,
do you need some money?
Angela, I'm fine.
I got a job in a general store.
A general store?
Don't ask.
I'll be all right.
Do you need a place to stay?
You can live with us.
No, Patricia.
I spent too much time
letting other people
take care of me.
I've gotta find my own way.
Where are you?
Just know I'm fine, Dianne.
I gotta do this on my own.
I'm really proud of you, Shelia.
I'm gonna call you guys soon.
I love you.
We're really sorry this happened.
- Shelia, I'm so sorry.
- I'll be all right.
Honey, I love you, OK?
- We love you.
I love y'all, too.
Um, Dianne, tell Terry
I said happy birthday, OK?
Oh, my God!
Is that today?
Dianne, you didn't
forget, did you?
- Oh. I have to go.
- OK.
I'll talk to you.
Later.
Hey, Sheriff.
Hey.
Hey!
Thanks for getting me this job.
Ha! You kidding me?
If it wasn't for you,
this place wouldn't even be open again.
My daddy loved this store.
It's his lifelong dream, this place.
# Ooh, I want you #
# The right way #
# And I want you #
# I want you #
# But I want you to want me, too #
# Want me, too #
# Want you to want me #
# I want you to love me baby #
# Just like I want you... #
Oh.
You work out every day?
Not every day.
I should go with you sometime.
You know you laugh,
but you might actually enjoy it.
Keeps the stress down.
I couldn't run
from here to that door.
Maybe we can...
maybe we can start walking first.
If you want to.
No.
You know, Shelia,
you've been putting in
a lot of time in this place,
you know, getting it
to be open and all.
Want to go to
the movies later?
# I want you #
# But I want you to want me, too #
# To want me, baby #
# Just like I want you #
Shelia?
What did you say?
Movies.
Have some fun.
Laugh, smile.
You want to go?
OK.
- # Oh, sugar #
- OK.
# To share is precious #
# Pure and fair #
# Ooh #
Why the hell
was she at my salon?
She had to see me.
About what?
Angela, lay off.
I'm getting sick of this.
Oh, then leave.
You keep it up,
and that's just what I'm gonna do.
Oh, please, Marcus.
Please. You ain't going nowhere.
You know why
you ain't going nowhere?
'Cause... this is my money!
You need this money!
- I'm sick of you.
- Get out!
- What are you talking about?
- No, stop! Get...
- First of all...
First of all!
It was my money that
started the damn business.
Now, you think I'm with you
for the money?
I'm with you because
I love you,
but you too damn stupid to see it.
I was with you
when you didn't have a dime.
And I've always
been there for you!
Not afraid to let you shine.
It's a damn shame
when you women are so used to
losing you don't realize
when you've won.
Kids, get your stuff.
Your daddy here.
I know you did not
bring this trick up into my house.
I have told you...!
Just shut up! Shut!
Now, Keisha...
this is my wife.
And you are going
to respect her.
So don't call our house
or come by my job
unless it's got something
to do with the kids.
We're done.
Now, I have to have
a relationship with you
because of them, and that is it.
So if it ain't got
nothing to do with the kids,
don't you call me!
And I'm gonna tell you this one time.
You better stop talking
to my kids about her,
do you understand me?
Yeah.
Wow. It's about time...
Hey! Shut!
Now, both of y'all,
better learn to get along
for the sake of these kids.
And stop acting like
you're both damn 5 years old!
Daddy.
- Hi, babies.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey.
- Hi, honey.
Get in the car.
Hop on in.
OK.
All right now.
Better put your seatbelts on.
OK. Now, daddy's gonna
see you guys a little later, OK?
Put your seatbelt on.
Daddy loves you.
Baby. Marcus,
where are you going?
Oh! I am so sorry I'm late.
I just, you know,
I got wrapped up,
and it just slipped my mind.
It's all right, love.
You remember
what you want to remember.
Babe, I really am sorry.
OK. I will see you at
the office tomorrow, doc, OK?
OK, Pam.
Listen, thanks for
the cake and ice cream.
Anytime, Terry.
All right, darling.
- Happy birthday.
- Oh, thank you, Pam.
Ha ha!
Are you two having an affair?
I think I better go.
Yeah. You better.
And don't come
back to this house.
I'll see you at the office, Pam.
- OK.
- Thanks for being so nice.
Good night.
You fire her, and I mean it!
You don't come in this house
and give me any damn ultimatums.
What is going on?
You answer me
keep your voice down.
Our daughter is
in this room sleeping.
Don't you let
that whore back in this house again.
Now, look, I'm warning you.
That whore has
tutored your daughter,
went to her recital,
picked her up
when you left her sitting
on the school steps twice.
OK, and what has she done
for my husband, I wonder.
I have to work, Terry!
This is not about your damn job!
It's not? Then where
is this coming from all of a sudden?
What the hell are you
talking about "all of a sudden"?
This is not all of a sudden!
It's been... I don't even
know how long it's been
that I've been begging you,
I've been...
I have been begging you
to spend some time with me,
begging you for months.
And I have!
What kind of man has to make
an appointment to sleep with his wife?
Obviously, one who has
too much time on his hands.
Oh! What do you
want me to do?
What do I want you to do?
What I want you to do.
How about the obvious?
How about baking
a cake for my birthday
or spending some time
with me or your daughter, OK?
How about doing
what a wife does,
screwing me on a regular?
Can you handle that?
You know what?
I am all for solutions,
but maybe we could
come up with something
that doesn't involve me
stepping back into the fifties!
You are so selfish.
I am not selfish.
Oh, what the hell are you talking about,
you're not selfish?
Dianne, you laid there
and had your tubes tied,
and you didn't even tell me?
You don't think that's selfish?
Look, this is my body, OK?
You don't have
to carry a child, I do!
to miss work, I do!
Dianne, when you get married,
you give up the "Is" for us, OK?
You don't make those kind
of decisions without talking to me!
What the hell am I doing?
I don't even know why
I'm having this argument with you.
I'm tired of arguing about
the same damn thing with you.
It's clear to me...
one thing, very clear.
You don't want to be married.
Can I tell you
what this is about?
My entire career is
going way better than yours.
And you're having
some testosterone issues.
And you can't deal with it.
Have you lost your mind?
No.
But I'm about to lose my wife.
I'm moving out.
I'll be right back.
I really love your dad's place.
But I got to pay you back.
I do!
Naw. It's all good.
Don't even sweat that.
Mm.
Are my legs supposed
to be this sore?
No pain, no gain, right?
Huh.
Um...
I need to tell you something.
Yeah, sure. What's up?
I'm really vulnerable right now...
and, um...
we can't go to the movies
and hang out and stuff.
- What? What do you mean?
- I mean...
I just got to the point where I can say
Mike's name without crying,
and I don't want to get
caught up in what Patricia
and Dr. Phil call
"The Hero Syndrome. "
It's when somebody comes along
and they help you out,
and just 'cause
they were being nice,
you fall for 'em, and...
you're just being nice.
I don't know, Shelia.
I could have this same hero thing
going on with you, too.
What are you talking about?
I'm serious.
I mean... look at you.
This man was trying
to break you,
and every day I see you take some
of that power back.
I didn't so anything.
I just signed the papers.
I didn't even fight.
Sometimes signing the papers is
all the fighting you need to do.
Don't play with me.
I'm not playing with you.
I mean, Shelia,
you are amazing,
intelligent,
spiritual, sexy.
Strong...
strong and beautiful woman.
Not as big as I am.
You know, if you're
not happy about the way you look,
then change it.
Stop doubting yourself.
I mean, it's not attractive.
I don't like it.
And hell, it makes me
uncomfortable for you.
I'm sorry.
I'm just so used to...
Mike saying things, I...
try to beat him to it.
I ain't Mike.
Oh.
Mm.
Oh, Jesus.
Lord, have mercy. God.
I ain't thought that
in a long time.
Um...
OK.
I think I need to pray.
Um...
can we pray?
All right.
Well, I hope
she can help her now.
Well, if she can...
what are you two doing here?
Did something happen?
- No.
- Did something happen to Shelia?
- No, no, no. Don't worry.
- No, honey.
- Calm down. We're OK.
- Oh.
I thought somebody
had died or something.
What are you doing here?
- Girl, we got men problems.
- Man problems.
Thank God it's just men.
OK. That I can deal with.
What happened?
OK. You ready for this?
Terry moved out.
He got his own apartment.
He's so upset with me.
And I have never seen
Marcus so mad at me.
He went off.
He set me straight.
And Keisha,
but she deserved it.
And Angie, you didn't?
You know, if I didn't
know these men,
I would just think
that they were crazy.
- They are.
- Yeah.
Come on, you guys.
Will you call them
and talk to them?
Uh-uh.
No. I am not about to do that.
No. I'm not gonna be
all vulnerable.
You know, you guys
are just pathetic.
If you're not gonna
be honest with your husbands,
then who are you gonna
be vulnerable with?
- You!
Thank you very much, but...
this is the reason why
they're so upset at you.
Because you haven't
been truthful with them.
Tell them how you want them
to hold you at night
and how you're afraid
for them to leave you.
Y'all know this.
Is she kidding me?
I am not about to do that, period.
See, Angie, your problem
is you're afraid
that he won't do what it is
that you want him to do.
- You just stubborn.
- So?
I'll tell you what. I'm not ready to face
possible rejection.
- I'm just not.
- Me, either.
Rejection?
Look at you guys
sitting here looking like little
lost puppies.
Tell them what you
tell me all the time.
Tell them the truth.
Tell them what you're feeling.
Ew... she makes me sick.
She's always got
something smart to say.
Listen, I want you guys
to do this little lesson here.
- Uh-oh.
- Here we go.
Oh, come on.
You guys stop it.
Some big exercise.
It's gonna work.
Gavin and I just did this.
So it's really gonna help.
Take this paper.
On one side of it, I want you to list
all the bad he's ever done.
OK, and on the other side, I want you
to list all the good he's ever done.
Now, if the bad outweighs
the good, then so be it.
Don't hold on.
Just let it go. But...
but if this good
outweighs the bad,
then y'all need to be
big little women
and fix this.
This is not healthy.
I don't want to be
a big little woman, Pat.
I want to be a little girl.
You are not in college
anymore, Angie.
- Just grow up.
- Yeah. Thank you.
Well, I got to get
to class, guys. So...
I'll see you
at the ceremony, yes?
Oh, no, no. We can't make it. Sorry.
- She's joking.
- I'm playing.
- Of course!
- We'll be there.
I want you married
with your husbands, all right?
Well, I might be there
with my new boyfriend
- if this list don't look right.
- Angie.
If you do the work, it'll be fine.
- All right.
- Bye.
- Bye, baby.
- Thank you.
I tell you, I need a legal pad
to write this list, honey.
You know what I would do
if I was single right now,
you know what I'd be doing?
Sitting here having
a drink with y'all.
Thanks for giving me a call.
They are wasted, man.
- We need another round!
- Where's your help, huh?
Night off.
Man, I told him, quit.
What's up, fellas?
- Hey!
How you doing, man?
I got the hen, man.
Oh, thanks.
We were sitting here
thinking of a way to kill our wives
and wondering
if you could help us.
Hey, that always works.
Mm-hmm.
- Oh, man.
- Tell me something, man.
Why is it that when a woman say
she want a good man
and then she get one, she do
everything she can to drive him crazy.
I got the answer.
'Cause women don't
know what they want,
especially yours.
Am I right, Gavin?
I'm gonna divorce Dianne.
I'm gonna call her up and tell her,
"You know what?
We're getting a divorce. "
Yeah, right. You and Dianne
are made for each other.
No. No. I ain't gonna call her.
I'm gonna send her a text.
You want to piss a woman off,
send her a text like something.
Oh, stop it.
Stop it, man.
You got a good woman.
You need to work it out.
Good woman or not,
she got to be willing
to work it out.
I had a good woman once.
Hmm.
Anybody seen Shelia?
Boy, Angela talks to her
from time to time
- but...
- Really?
Sound to me like you miss her.
- I'm...
- What?
No! No!
I don't miss her.
You made a mistake.
It's OK to say so.
I didn't make a mistake, all right?
Who are you talking to?
Heh. I should of just, you know...
I should of just...
done a background
check on Trina.
Ha! Girl don't do nothing.
She don't cook, don't clean,
don't... wash clothes.
Don't do...
take the garbage out.
She don't do...
she just don't.
Oh, she can shop.
'Cause she burning up
my American Express.
All right! Whoo!
Quality. Quality.
Hey, Gavin. You know
what that sound like to me?
80l20.
I tried to...
yeah, right.
You think about that
with Dianne.
Man, I'm going back to her.
I'm just right now...
I'm teaching her a lesson.
Yeah. What lesson is that?
You know
what the lesson is?
I ain't gotta be there.
That's the real lesson.
I don't... I don't...
I don't have to be there.
I can go.
Boo-yah!
Yeah, that's great.
Yeah. That's gonna look good.
36 years old.
Out there dating again.
Mm. That ain't the good look.
Especially the way
you're missing your ex.
Hey, Mike. You got
what you wanted, didn't you?
What's all this for?
I just thought
I would cook for you.
Come on, baby. Sit.
Oh, just let me
wash my hands.
OK.
Hello?
Marcus?
Man, she has cooked.
She ain't said two words to me
since we got back.
I've been sleeping
with one eye open
and she cooked.
Well, if she ain't cooking grits,
you ain't got nothing
to worry about.
No, man.
She's trying to kill me.
Look, I'm calling you
'cause I want you to know
if something happens to me,
I want y'all to know she did it.
Just go eat
your dinner, all right?
Angela's not that crazy.
This is Angela.
You know what?
You're right.
She is kinda crazy.
Look, if anything tastes funny, spit it out.
OK, OK.
I love you, man.
I love you, too.
# Swift as a wind song #
# You sang the music of anhonest bird #
# I waited for some contradiction #
# Truth was ringing in your every word #
# And every moment since then #
# The one thing I can tell #
# Is that I belong with you #
# And no one else #
You haven't touched your food.
It's good, but...
I'm just not that hungry.
You know what I'm saying?
You're still lying.
I'm just saying, look...
you ain't said two words to me,
and all of a sudden
I come home and you cooked.
Marcus, look, I know
that I haven't been
the easiest woman
to get along with.
And I know it's been
hard for you.
But none of that matters.
Life is too short.
You're trying to kill me,
ain't you? Just cut to it.
Patricia gave you one of them
mind games to play on me.
Now, if it's about Keisha,
we can talk about Keisha.
Marcus, it's not about her.
It's about us, right?
Honey, I love you.
I just want us
to start over again.
Just me and you.
If that's OK.
You're serious?
Yes.
So...
if that is the case,
you gonna stop talking to me
like you crazy.
Done.
We're gonna stay
committed to each other.
And know that I am
doing my best.
I know you are, Marcus.
And I'm so sorry for making you feel
like you weren't.
One more.
You're gonna have to
stop drinking.
OK!
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Oh, one second. OK?
I love you, baby.
I love you, too.
Finished.
- I bought that in Africa.
- Did you really?
- Yeah. Me and Dianne.
- Wow.
Oh. It's gorgeous.
Come in!
It was last year.
Really?
Dianne, what are you doing...?
Let me just say this, please.
I am wrong.
I am so wrong
for not telling you, and...
I've just taken you for granted.
And I'll do anything.
I'll do whatever it takes,
whatever it takes
so that you can
just come home.
Because... I made that list,
and I realize that I need you
and I love you.
What list?
What are you talking about?
I'm gonna go.
No, no, no.
What are you saying?
Are you saying we can work it out?
Yes.
Let me ask you something.
When we were in Colorado,
we were in the car,
and I said, "I tested
Kenya because, so and so. "
And then you said, "Huh,"
like she wasn't mine.
- Were you having an affair or something?
- No!
Terry, I was just mad.
I just said that to get back at you.
To get back at me?
OK.
And we can work this out
through anything?
Yes.
OK. I guess that means
I'll tell you this then.
She's pregnant.
With twins.
Oh, OK, OK.
OK, you know what?
We'll work it out.
You mean it?
Yeah.
OK.
Well, just like you said
just to get back at me
I just did that
to get back at you.
- She's not.
- Oh, Terry!
- Dr. Brock.
- We have never, ever, ever had an affair.
There's nothing going on.
And my boyfriend
would be very upset to hear you say that.
Yes. He's a big linebacker.
Thank God you got a boyfriend.
- Yes, I do.
- All right.
Well, then can you
just come home?
Please take him.
Take him home.
I'm very sorry.
- I will lock up.
- All right. Lock up.
Hey.
- How you doing, Marcus?
- Mike, Mike, look at you.
Hey, boy, you looking
real sweet.
Oh, nice suit.
I know your bald-headed ass
did not bring her up in here.
- Baby.
- Yes, I did.
All right. Come on.
Come on, now. Hey.
- Hi.
- You look gorgeous.
Thank you.
So do you.
And where have you been?
'Cause Pat's having a meltdown
about hair.
- Oh, are you serious?
- Yes.
Come on. I'm gonna
show you where she is.
OK. I'll see you guys.
You look good. Bye, baby.
Mwah!
Why is your wife so evil?
You stop it. All right?
I'm playing.
So, how you guys
been doing?
- We're good. How have you been?
- Good.
- Great.
- Good. Good.
- You look good.
- Thank you.
Well, I'm gonna go to the ladies room
and freshen up.
- All right.
- Ooh! Lipstick.
Lipstick.
Don't kiss me.
Stop, stop, stop.
Shelia?
Heh.
- Trina.
- Wow.
You look amazing.
How... how are you?
I feel amazing.
Wow.
I wondered what I would do
when I saw you again.
If I would cuss you out
or stomp you on the street,
whup that ass.
And amazingly...
all I want to do is pray for you.
But don't tempt me.
Stay away from
the wine bottles, OK?
Have a good evening.
Sheriff?
Oh, what you doing here?
Well, we came to support Patricia
on her big night.
"We?" Who's we?
Me and my wife.
OK. I think I'm ready.
Shelia?
Hello, Mike.
Which way is it?
Right up here
to the left, honey.
- You look beautiful.
- Thank you.
Perfect!
Thank you. So much.
That's beautiful.
Divas...
Oh, my God!
Oh, you remembered.
- How could I forget?
- What happened?
Where? Oh...
Oh, my God!
We've been worried
about you, you know.
I'm fine.
That's this glow that
I see happening here?
I haven't seen that
in a long time.
I'd like to think I had a little something
to do with that.
Oh, hey, Troy.
How you doing, ladies?
What are you doing here?
Shelia?
I stayed in Colorado.
We're married now.
Get out!
You're about to make me
have a heart attack.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Troy, you gotta go.
Get out. Troy, get out.
We need to speak to our friend,
so she can tell us what happened.
- All right, all right. I'm leaving.
- Bye.
Oh, Shelia!
Shelia and Troy together?
Yes. They're together.
They're together
and they look,
you know, she look really good.
She looks what?
Did you hear?
I missed it, too.
I said she looked good.
OK, she looked really good. Mike.
- All right. She look really good.
- OK. Good.
So, I, you know... it was just...
I haven't seen her in awhile.
So it was kind of,
you know, ooh.
What the hell
are you saying, man?
I'm just saying
it was kind of surprising.
It was kind of
surprising to see her.
To see her what?
Yeah. I just haven't seen her
in awhile, that's all.
- You miss her?
- What?
Come on, man.
What, y'all drinking too much.
Troy.
How you doing, guys?
Hey, Sheriff.
What's going on?
Good to see you, brother.
Same here.
Well, congratulate him. You know,
him and Shelia got married.
Right.
Hey, congrat...
Can you believe
he married my ex?
To you and Shelia.
- To you and Shelia.
- Yes.
Thank you.
He what now?
Said he married my ex.
One man's ex can be
another man's treasure.
So, um, she had
that gastric bypass?
No.
Actually, we just...
we just worked out together.
Ooh.
You know what
that means, right?
L... I just can't
wait to see her.
I want to see her, too, man.
I can't wait to see
what working out will do for you.
I'm going to the table, man.
I can't play with y'all.
Hey, man.
Don't be bitter, man.
We're just... we're just
clowning around.
Working out, man.
Working out.
I thought...
I prayed...
that God would save my marriage.
But it wasn't built
on the right things anyway.
I thought if Mike
got right, you know...
if I lost the weight,
that everything would be OK.
It's been hard.
But it's me.
I did it.
I'm doing it.
That's right.
And it feels so good.
It feels so good.
Oh!
I thought that God
had given up on me.
Yeah.
Because...
here I am in this marriage
and it don't work.
He don't love me,
he don't like me.
But he brought me somebody.
He is an amazing man.
He is supportive.
He doesn't criticize me.
He walks with me.
He loves me through all of it.
You understand what I'm saying?
Oh, Jesus.
I didn't have that.
And I do now.
And...
I wake up.
I wake up with so much joy
in my heart.
Oh!
Oh, God.
Help us, Jesus.
He already has, huh?
I wake up with so much joy
in my heart.
Ah.
You are so beautiful, Shelia.
Oh, my God.
But you are not...
- with that makeup.
- Aah!
We need to get it together.
- This is.
- No, we can't do that.
Oh, my God.
OK, we got to get it together.
I need some tissue.
Oh, Jesus!
OK, give me some.
I need some powder.
First of all,
I'd like to thank everyone
for such a lovely, lovely evening.
I feel very proud to be
the first black woman
to receive this award.
I'm very blessed
to have won an honor
for a book that has given me
such gratification
and information...
and great vacations.
Hey, we really didn't
get a chance to talk.
On purpose?
Come on, Shelia.
Don't be like that.
What do you want, Mike?
I'm trying to listen to Patricia.
Look, I'm sorry about
how all this went down.
Dianne, Terry...
OK? I don't... I don't
want you to be mad at me.
Marcus...
forgiveness, you know?
I want you to forgive me.
Isn't that what
the good book says?
Yes.
I forgave you a long time ago.
Because if I had stayed angry,
I would have taken it
out on Troy.
And he is too good for that.
You understand?
Yeah.
- Yeah. He's too good for that.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Hey, I was your first.
You never forget your first, right?
You did think you were my first,
didn't you?
I just wanted to say
sorry and, uh...
you know, there's this, um,
there's this thing called the 20l80 rule.
Mike...
I know all about the 80l20 rule.
Look... I thank you for helping me
find myself then.
But the woman I am now
is done with you.
So turn around
and go back to Trina.
Your 20.
I say clear and loud...
for everyone to hear...
Gavin...
I love you.
And in closing,
I would like for everyone
to remember
the greatest achievement
for any human being
is to love God...
yourself...
and others.
Thank you so much for this.
Thank you.
# Why do you tell me this #
# Were you looking for my reaction? #
# What do you need to know? #
# Don't you know
I'll always be your girl? #
# You do not have
to prove to me #
# You're beautiful to strangers #
# I've got loving eyes of my own #
# Of my own #
# I can tell #
# You belong to me #
# Tell her you belong... #
# Can it be that you are not sure? #
# You belong to me #
# Thought we'd closed the book #
# I thought we'd locked
the door, baby #
# You don't have to prove
you're beautiful to strangers #
# I've got loving eyes of my own #
# Of my own #
# I know, darling #
# You belong to me #
# Baby #
# Yes, you do #
# You belong to me #
# Tell me, I want something, baby #
# I believe you know
what I want you to say to her next #
# You belong to me #
# Won't you tell her, baby #
# Tell her that I love you #
# You belong to me #
# Tell this woman #
# Tell #
# You belong to me #
# Everybody knows this, baby #
# All of your friends #
# You belong to me #
# All of your friends,
all of my friends, baby #
# You belong to me #
# Told me this was going on #
# Ah #
# You belong to me #
# I can't stand it, baby #
# What you doing,
baby, what you doing? #
# You belong to me #
# What you doing,
baby, what you doing? #
# You belong to me #
# Where you going, baby,
where you going? #
# You belong to me #
# Where you going? #
# Oh... #
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org