Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Now, no one tøse boy.
No, no ...
Well, then come. ready?
Yes.
You do not touch you.
It makes you not.
I am closer to you.
What the hell do you think?
I am. It makes you not.
You are an idiot.
That you can be.
Keep the pot.
Now, no one tøse boy.
Do not worry.
Okay ...
Yeah.
VENNERNE
Sorry.
PARRET
It has been nice.
I think it is nice,
that we can go out and eat ...
It was ...
Civiliseret.
Yes.
It was good to see you.
In the same way. Hello.
You ...
Thank you.
Okay.
Good night.
Getting into.
Bye.
Hello.
EKSERNE
Would you like to join up?
No.
It is not you. You are beautiful.
But it is late.
I also according to the girls at
work has warned you against me.
They have enough to say that I am a ...
I have a history with them,
and it would be best for both of us
if you learned my true self
to know first.
How old are you? 24? 25?
23.
I am 31 years.
Do you know what that means?
It means that I can not risk
around and bowl all kinds of girls.
Often I never talk with them again.
It is both rude and immature.
And it is shit embarrassing.
At one point you are
after more than just to have sex.
Do you know what I mean?
So I go. I am, and I ask,
I have to call later this week.
I follow you up to the door.
FØRSTEDATE
You are so sexy. How have I
caught in a girl like you?
It has been out here for four days.
You must stop
to live as a pig.
How often should I say this to you?
And what is it with shoes?
See them ... Clear, however.
See all the shoes!
They can not all be your?
If the shoe is, Dave?
No, I have said it 4000 times.
And it is not considered to be an idiot.
Oh God ...
You are so sexy.
Is she sexy?
We go in the room.
First, I have a little kagedej.
Should we enjoy ourselves with kagedej?
I shall, in any case.
What would you do?
Eat it.
What are you doing home?
Why are you not out of date?
What are you doing here?
You have freedom of tomorrow. Go However, in the city.
You can not just sit here and lumre.
It is Friday night! You are young!
Do you know what I mean?
Go out and knep.
It is Friday night!
Hello, it is the party?
Where is it?
BOFÆLLERNE
It is Tuesday.
Dave?
Dave!
Inez so good tonight, right?
Sexy?
Cool and sexy?
So I thought ...
Would you like to join in to my room?
Together with us?
OK.
I. OPTAKT
How did that happen?
It is still in progress.
Ken?
Will you do me a favour?
Look not in the toilet and outside. Okay?
I am not one who does not eat.
Fridge used to be full.
But I was a full day and lost
drikkepengene somewhere
so I could not buy.
I have bad news, and I hope
do not you think I'm strange.
But I have only cider.
Blege means of teeth?
Is that it?
In the toilet Community?
Do you think my teeth are too white?
It is a bra in the living room,
so you think enough, I'm sloppy.
My teeth are white, because I as
child slept under some special lamps.
I was mørkeræd, so my parents
bought some special lamps.
But they did just
my teeth very white.
"Berrycuda" ... Well.
Refreshing.
When you say "lights" ...
Well, that was a lie.
I do not know why I said it.
There were no lamps.
I'm just not used to be
guys with the home on the first date.
Listen here ... I've looked in many
toilet create while I "tisset".
You have probably not something in it,
that would scare me away.
You seem enough, I'm sloppy.
No. since.
Yes, I think you're sloppy.
But it is sgu just as much?
It is not, therefore I am here.
I am here because I think of you.
I could not care less messy.
Or that barnepigen from
Muppet. Babyerne have been here.
Relax. I am not playing detective.
Think not of what I think.
We must le, we must talk,
we must drink. Sound good?
Yes.
There is a problem.
What?
I would not drink it.
No, it tastes as coins.
Come here.
Sorry.
I am full. What about you?
Perhaps we have waited too long.
Imagine if everything goes ...
Do you think this is wise?
I understand you, homo, but pay attention,
I repeat it is not.
I would prefer not to date again,
for all my guys have deceived me.
Apart from me, because we have not ...
If I do not have sex, I fall
I just one of an idiot again.
And you are the only man
I can stand to look at right now.
And you were smitten in a møgluder ...
Run you right.
As dissed you for seven months
ago and was part against you in six years.
Six years and four months.
You need sex. In severe.
Just focusing on that you need to
have emptied bollerne. With the same.
It is the only thing you have to think of
for det her handler kun om det.
I just will not break anything.
Sometimes it means something.
Sometimes kærtegner Monday face,
Merging fingers,
and whispers sweet words in your ear.
And sometimes an explosion an explosion.
Run on empty bollerne and fall asleep.
And that is what we will do,
This is what you have friends.
Then follow the plan and beverage,
for then you get a blowjob.
Will you?
Are you ready?
Trimmet bottom?
Yes.
Give me five!
Lovely.
Yes, I got so much wine,
when I was promoted.
No, I thought this opportunity.
Oh well.
It also followed with promotion.
But wine is also good.
I am surprised,
of course, you hate wine.
Now I like it.
Jasmine beats me to death.
Why?
She is overprotective.
I have not told it to anyone.
I was afraid they would say,
that it was a stupid idea,
or be happy,
that we were together again.
Or something.
Are you still?
Sorry.
No. Continue.
I allowed just mouth run.
This is åndssvagt.
Can you see?
It need not be embarrassing.
I thought we would chat a bit
and then be a little horny.
And then we would go their separate ways.
It thought I also.
No, you did not.
Look at your blouse.
Look at your clothes.
Kavalergang.
I try.
The kind of blouses are designed to
to get guys like me home.
Guys like you?
Men, which appears on babser.
You are wrong.
It is designed to get guys who
you to want to come home.
Now, I understand.
Are you with?
Yes. You would fill me with remorse.
Anger is good.
And it was not your intention
to get me home?
No.
I feel a slow down.
It was nice to see you.
Greet Jasmine.
Greet your mother from me.
I will.
You will not do.
Andrew?
What?
What is it?
This is your birthday.
I would not take all
opmærksomheden. I love you.
You are the best.
I am not so bad.
Happy Birthday.
Good night, sweetheart.
Abby ...
Andrew.
I do not know
I feel like tonight.
Was that a question?
No. I am tired.
There has just been
so busy at work.
And I do not think
that the new glasses are good.
I get tired in the eyes,
and they hurt.
And we ate a lot of pasta,
so I'm just not in the mood for it.
When will you be in the mood for it?
Do you want a certain date?
What about tomorrow or the weekend?
We have not loved in three weeks.
It is not three weeks ago.
When we last loved?
Andrew!
Should I keep track?
The answer should always be "yesterday".
No one does it every night.
It makes Malcolm and Beatrice.
They are chiropractors, so they lie.
I love you.
I also love you.
I need orgasmer, Andrew.
I know this well.
Okay.
We do it.
We do it now.
I would do it. I'm ready.
I am pleased.
Taxes?
I thought you would start.
I begin always.
Will not you start this time?
You are already switched on. You can start
with me, so I make.
No.
For I know your number.
You never use your mouth first.
You wait until I do it.
And you're on, and passionate
and may you just
take me with the same
and jump opportune my turn.
I do not think it fits.
Gu makes it all!
How can you pretend otherwise?
What's wrong with us?
I would of course like to do it now.
You will have the passion and excitement.
I am running on!
What do you do?
It's great.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Are they new?
They look expensive. I thought
we should be united on expensive purchases.
Andrew ...
Sorry.
So?
I am not.
I said no,
but I just look at
and do my thing.
Well.
I have always thought that you were sweet.
Yes.
Okay.
We do not always agree on everything,
and sometimes I hate you sgu.
But we move soon, and we have
I will bring it here, and here you are.
I have always thought that you were ...
She has always said you were sweet.
And we love each other so much.
I love you.
You are so sexy.
Oh, how I love you!
You are the sexiest
woman in the world.
We will have new friends today.
There may be a problem.
Is it me?
She is sexy, no?
Yes, you are fantastic.
There is something that makes
that I might not
like it here.
Gord?
What?
It? Is this the problem?
That I knew very well.
It will be great.
Did you know?
Are you on?
How knew you?
Now you are in any case, no?
Should I?
Yes, certainly.
Oh god. It is so frækt.
You are so sexy.
Just get going!
It's great.
II. FORSPIL
It is so nice.
Oh god.
Do you?
I asked whether you believe it.
Absolutely.
Really?
Yes.
You believe that?
Jamie ... I have no idea
what you discuss.
Did you, as you said,
that you really believe me?
Yes.
It says you enough for all the girls.
Yes, I do.
Should I lie?
I say this to others,
but with you, I think so.
How should
I could know the difference?
I respect you enough
to pack it away.
Respect is the opposite
to think of any.
Not always.
This does not, as I thought.
Listen here.
I say simply that I think about you.
If we have sex tonight, that is fine.
But if you do not trust enough for me,
it is quite understandable.
And if that means that we must
make the big things on hold,
and go back to talk,
I can talk all night.
I want to know everything,
there is to know about you.
For example, what is it?
It is to rub cuticle.
How does it work?
Ken.
We do not need to talk.
I believe you.
Do you?
Does that mean that you do not
like you about my conversation?
I love the way you talk to.
We can talk afterwards.
Okay.
Thinking about others when we love?
What?
Sometimes I feel
that you are somewhere else.
Can you see what I do?
How could I be?
Sorry. You are right.
Continue.
Thank you.
Is it because I is not smooth?
Is it there for you not?
Who says that I am not?
I do my best.
I stopped using wax,
because you stopped to slikke me.
Do you want to talk about foot sex,
or should I just do it?
Okay. Sorry.
You never look at me,
when I'm down here.
All four times?
Thinking about others?
No.
You may well say it.
I do.
What? Why you say that?
Only sometimes. To do this, too.
Yes, I do.
Sometimes.
Who?
Who? Who's on your mind?
There are too many to list.
Is not it the same every time?
There is a sea of people,
I will never have sex with.
Thinking about the same every time?
Is it Malcolm?
Is it because you think he is a doctor?
It is not Malcolm.
Who is it?
Ian Ziering. He played Steve
Sanders in "BeverlyHills" ...
I know who he was.
Are you sur?
Let us continue.
Okay.
Let's just do it.
I'm ready.
Let us do it.
Yes!
Where should we start?
Would you like to start with a kiss?
Stop!
You must not.
What?
Do not look at me while.
I can not cope.
You said that you thought about ...
The other is: "A sexy girl look
on me when she was sucking on. "
With you is: "It is kris,
and she has my cock in the mouth! "
We drop blowjobbet.
Take the now calm.
Let us put some music on.
Some of the bass. Something high.
Can I just ...
We must have something kneppe music!
Fine enough.
We can skip over.
You are so homo.
It is you who are homo.
It is better. We can ...
I hate the song.
It was my and Dimitris song.
Jessica and I had no song.
I thought about it, but then began
idioten to play it everywhere.
and each time I should
be soft in the knees!
Can you see how excited you are?
You can pretend that I am him,
and then you can give me a hiding.
Rend me!
Sorry. It was stupid.
Do you want to talk about it?
There we have it.
Is it fair that I am here?
Yes.
I just want to have it resolved.
It's okay, right?
I will not feel
as a prick tomorrow.
It is quite okay, that you are here.
You've come over me?
Hold on. do not it.
You've come over me, no?
Yes, Mia.
It is just for fun, no?
Jo. Agree.
So it is in order?
Yes. Definitely.
Such. Hello, ladies.
Figures are not to my breasts.
I am just polite.
You would say that if you are still ...
If it was not in order?
Maybe you should just
stop talking.
So you did not
that this would happen?
You have not tangaer,
because this is pleasant.
Just flå it.
Just run!
What?
Just flå it.
Just do it.
It is already on.
Yes, now. But before ...
It gave the sense, as I said it.
She like,
that you take hold of her hair.
You must not hold you back.
Just the fleet and head on.
But it goes well.
I give you something. So when I
says something, you should do it.
I am here also.
It is also for my sake.
It is not as
to kneppe front of the dog.
I would not be an idiot.
I would like to see it go smoothly,
and that it is sexy and delicious.
So I sit here.
So I must address here?
It is great.
Just relax and do,
what are you naturally.
How?
Yes.
Such.
Who is it?
Who is your new friend?
What happened?
I put hårspray on there.
Parfumeflasken was empty.
You must apologize.
Okay! No more endearment.
It is no one like.
I think about it.
It makes no with the right to vote.
We kærtegner not even,
so it should not do.
So just go on and turn you loose.
Treat her as a piece of meat.
It's just fun sex.
It is the exploration and fun.
It is a erotiskforlystelse.
It is okay.
Take me.
Why do you see me?
Take her.
I love you, Gord.
It is so sexy.
Oh god. Continue.
How, indeed. It is delicious.
III. SEX
Can I tell you something?
I love your bedding.
It is good, yes.
I do not use something.
I know.
Do you have anything?
I am at something.
I am healthy. I often checked.
Otherwise, the girls had warned me.
I drag me out.
Just themselves.
I promise that. And I promise not
to destroy it totally cool bedding.
And you know what?
You are beautiful.
I believe it.
Your eyes are as nøddebrune lakes.
Excuse me, I ...
I do not usually go to ...
But you are beautiful shit.
Thank you.
I know the look.
The look I give the girls who say,
that they have never done it before.
I have destroyed it, right?
Kris ...
Oh, Kristine.
Kristine Armstrong!
I need a little brash talk.
The turn me on.
Okay.
Just tell it with conviction.
Come on.
I knepper you so deeply in the ass,
that your breath will smell of cock.
And then I come so hard in your mouth,
the syringes out of your ass!
I am ...
Gudfader.
Was it not what you wanted?
Why?
Because you are a dirty whore.
Sorry.
It is okay. It was my fault.
Just go.
Do you like it?
We should have sex, not talk about it.
Perhaps it is not our fault.
Lysten will be less with age.
We are 26!
It is not 19.
You onanerer, when we do not have sex.
Not every day.
Yes, but to have sex
is quite different from that onanere.
It is like a energibar
in relation to a meal.
And you eat energibarer.
I have seen.
Yes.
There you can see.
Crap! Yes, we onanerer both,
so why do we not?
Why do we not have more sex?
I think we both know that ...
I am not so interesting in bed.
I can not excite you.
And what is the purpose?
What?
I have never been a sexdyr.
I can two posts.
If you were not good, why should
I would be with you?
Because you are afraid to be alone.
What?
Do you think that the only reason for
I am with you, is ...
Oh god.
Do you think I only with you,
because I am afraid to be alone?
Is not it a little?
Ask you?
If you think the only reason for
that we are together ...
I thought it was because I did not
look so good as when we met.
No, honey!
I think, in fact, you seem better.
Do you?
Yes.
Really?
You have taken on, and ...
No, tax.
I think it is positive.
You've got to fill.
You does not look like a young girl more.
I thought ... I do not know what I
must say. What should I say?
I want it to work.
I will also.
Perhaps bored, we just
after so long.
I think not.
Admit it.
Yes, perhaps.
Should we try something different?
Okay.
As what?
Something exciting?
Okay.
Do you as to make it
in the bathtub?
I have a perfect idea.
You have to do anything.
Everything you want.
Do you speak to me?
Yes.
You can take her in the ass.
Had I forgotten me? Pause.
I did not ass.
I would not stop. I thought
I was close. I am. Continue.
Come on.
I did not in the ass.
Your hand ...
It is on me.
I would just feel the rhythm.
It was, therefore, I sneg me here.
Such.
No.
Gider you sit yonder?
Yes, of course.
Are you so in the ass?
He has done everything else with you.
What does it mean when you say:
"You have to do anything"?
I do not know. This means
not ass. I do not.
We two make it after all.
This is different. It is ...
I think she believes
that you are too great.
Is that what you meant?
A little slower.
If you want to control the pace,
you must be at the top.
When did you last toned stomach?
Slower. I believe it.
Is it too much for you, Nancy?
Call me not pigenavne.
Suzie. Debbie.
Keep up.
Team looked up!
I was just about to come.
But you were not here yet.
It is okay.
No. Excuse me,
I had to stop.
I knew what I did.
I would have
your first blob over.
Just relax.
We? you have something to drink?
It sounds good. Thank you.
What is wrong with you?
Do you speak to me?
No.
Værsgo.
Thank you.
Calls to you that "the first blob"?
You are better after the first.
So you must not hold back.
You are more present.
Dut rudder that you know everything about me.
You talked to your penis before, no?
Yes, I did.
IV. MELLEMSPIL
Can we keep a small break?
Ja da.
I will still fall a little down.
Okay.
So ...
Why me?
We shall shortly move.
And Inez know you. It is important.
She should really have a time prick,
and you are well equipped.
We have lived together a long time,
and I do not like about you more.
We were friends, but no longer.
When we do not live together, I will not
hate you more. You understand ...
It is easier for me to see her
do it with a ...
... I do not like.
And Gord think that you are nice.
Netop.
That here we had no problems
with. We were good at.
But everything else on the other hand ...
What do you mean by that?
You know you well.
Yes, but ...
But what?
When we did not love,
we had problems.
That does not mean
I do not need it.
Okay, but you
blame me for it?
Do you think that it was my fault?
This is not about you.
Tell me not what I think.
So you think it was my fault?
I know what you're thinking,
because you are so easy to read.
Keep up now.
I believe it.
Are you still with her ...
No, I am not.
No. I am not so good
to the standard conditions the past.
I have it all for fun.
I would not be here if ...
Are you with someone?
No.
As with his guy at work?
What of them?
"What of them?"
There were two.
The only thing you said to me,
was Tristan.
Very macho. Did he
tailor-made T-Shirts?
No. Keep up now.
What is the second sop?
It does not matter.
Is he one of my friends?
No.
So, what he says.
No?
Sig, hvad han hedder.
Saliva.
Is what he says.
However, F. Mac.
You must not say anything.
F. However, Mac?
It is his rap name
or his street name.
Or prison name!
What the hell is this?
See how jealous you are.
No. I try to find out,
what the "F" stands for.
Why are you so jealous?
I am not jealous.
I just want to ...
I just want to ensure me,
that you are being treated ...
I want you to be happy.
I am.
Well. Well done.
And you?
I am very happy.
Very happy.
Excuse me, I stopped.
The urgency is not. It is in order.
You have been in bed with all
the girls at work. Is it here?
I have not been in bed with everyone.
For example, not Mariah.
She began before you. And Christina
was beautiful. I never touched her.
Shakira ...
I lied. I read your CD. Covers.
Yes, I have been in bed with everyone.
I thought just not,
that there would be so much intimacy.
It is not,
because I do not think about you.
I said it too early. Maybe
one should not say it in bed.
I do not know what I do.
As usual you say?
"You have a great ass."
To help the self-esteem.
And what do you think of my ass?
It is great.
I believe it.
I do so also.
And believe me, for I am ass. Man.
It is a masterpiece.
I am with you in again
on one condition.
Drop sødsuppe. Talk,
for it is just not my style.
Is it an agreement?
Yes.
Well.
I know what you're thinking.
No, I do not know what you're thinking.
What you think?
In the first place:
How did you get it from?
It was a premium for Michelle
hen. I won it.
So you?
I have it on.
And then?
So I knepper you.
You like to get a finger up.
And you keep my hand there,
when you are full enough.
It is a little larger than a finger.
We use as glidecreme.
Really?
Will you not even try?
It is ...
You have a g. Point, as we do not
has found. Are not you curious?
What do I have? It knew I did not.
How do you know? Where is it?
What do I have?
I am sorry that I brought that up as well.
I put it away.
Relax and unwire.
And then we can ...
I do not know what to do.
What will you get out of it?
There is a small
vibrating things in it for me.
So you can get?
Oh yes.
Okay.
Do you?
Yes, okay.
Okay.
I just ...
lay you down.
Should we kiss a little first?
I do not think
it will make me wetter.
I just ...
Do not worry, honey.
It is just the tip.
It says they are all together.
Try to relax.
Taxes?
I am right here.
I go nowhere.
Okay. It is okay.
Happy Birthday, darling.
New plan?
Yes, just give me a moment.
Can I do anything?
No, it is not about you.
What's on your mind?
I do not know. Patter.
Jessica called themselves athletes
just because she jumped with horses.
What is it?
Springridning.
It is the horse, which is athlete.
It makes all the work.
This is equivalent to 100 meters. runners
Ol bar to a dwarf,
and then gave the dwarf medal.
Yes, it's fun.
I do not think about her.
Okay.
I believe it.
Should I?
No. I fix it.
Maybe we should just stop there?
I undertake to blame for this.
I thought it was a good idea.
Let us give each other hand
and giving alcohol to blame.
Nope. You do not remember it as
the evening, I could not get it up.
I'm just a little nervous.
Everything makes you nervous.
Everything? Slikkede I do not
20 minutes ago?
Only because you felt
that you had to it.
You were sorry blowjob. The failure.
Listen here.
None slikker of obligation.
I know how to think.
I am not a møgluder,
as during six years
do not bother teach you to know.
You played macho, because I always
driller you that you are svans.
You stuck in my neck,
because Dimitri always did.
We know everything about each other, and the
Therefore, you can not get it up.
You did not know that I was
smitten in you i4.klasse.
Yes, but I was
together with Morris.
I was smitten in you in high school.
I knew it well,
but I was with Jessica.
Did you know?
Now, I am.
This should never have happened.
I did not know that you knew it.
Where are my pants?
I thought
vi bare kunne gøre det, men...
Add as the pants from you,
to hell!
An explosion is just an explosion.
Did you might not it?
Did you or not?
Should I answer it?
Let us do it. Afterwards,
we have to be best friends again.
But right now is just a piece of meat.
A delicious fisse with feet.
And I should just be
a large cock with a face.
Come to bed.
It need not be so complicated.
It should not be so hard.
Jo.
Not if we
look at each other as meat.
I think it is tough.
Do you know what's going on here?
He points to you. He will
have you back in bed.
If he could do so,
he would do it.
Come to bed.
We must kneppe. And that is all.
I will not fall for a prick?
My engagement to be emptied.
We think only of ourselves?
A sexy ass with eyes and ...
Are you ready?
V. ORGASME
How is it, honey?
Fine. What about you?
Well. The vibrator is great.
Can I get longer?
So ...
Let me find your g. point.
My what?
How is it, honey?
Not bad!
Hold on. Stop!
I come!
Why are you so slow?
I do not know.
Should I do it faster?
Maybe chess, we do it faster?
Good work.
In the same way.
Yes, there ...
Do you like it, your møgluder?
I come soon.
I do so also.
You are wonderful.
It is better than I thought.
It is so good.
You are so beautiful.
I love you.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
You were incredible.
Was I?
I got you to come once.
I came three times.
Holy shit ...
Any comments?
There was a støn,
which was just excessive.
Jaså?
You know what I mean.
It was as ...
That you should probably tone down a little.
It seemed a little taken.
I shall remember for next time.
Do you know what you can do for me?
What? Well ...
No, I have to me.
Come not near me. I'm hypersensitive.
But you know what I need?
A portion is. And a cookie.
Put it in a bowl
and warm it in the microwave.
Do you want ice?
Where is it just sweet.
You may have to be washing a bowl.
I have nothing against.
And come with it?
With a cookie?
I am glad that we did it.
Hvabehar?
Of course I am pleased that we
had sex. I am just glad ...
I stop to talk,
because we are obviously agree on this.
I hope not, you need
a long pause, for I am ready again.
You forgot my cookie.
Lift her legs up.
How?
High up.
Yes! Oh god.
Now I come.
We did it.
See me.
It was fantastic.
In so sexy.
I know that we have had our
differences, but it was fat.
I was so cheeky.
I go outside for a moment.
If in need me ...
One sip juice?
During me no more?
Should I now buy a new carton?
Do you think I am stupid?
If you believe that you are smarter than me?
Take no clothes!
VI. EFTERSPIL
I did not hear
Microwave say Ding.
I am confused.
Masserede you nails band?
You said that you came four times.
Løj you?
No, I lied. I ...
What?
I can not.
I try and try. It is,
as if there is something wrong with me.
It should be like
be fun and non-binding.
But it is not.
For me it is so overwhelming.
So personally.
I think of how I look like
and what he thinks about me,
and what with the smell?
And then I just do not.
I can not.
I am just not enough
right sexually brought.
I'm sorry.
I am truly sorry.
It should probably go.
So when you say that you do not
is quite sexually brought ...
It was a lie.
A brittle lie.
Not sexually brought?
You lied sgu!
Take not the case on the road,
because you could not give me orgasm.
There are plenty of girls,
I can not give orgasm. Lots!
I left you, Jamie.
My name is Dora.
Dora is not a sexy name, so when I
moved, I decided Jamie.
Skiftede you name to Jamie Fox?
It is a sexy name. How could
I know that I would win the Oscars?
You are sgu insane.
Yes, it is crazy to tell a lie
to go to bed with someone?
I know you think of the innocent girls.
So I played innocent.
I would kneppes.
I anede not that you would
be soft and "love" with me?
How should I get?
You are not the man
I have heard of. You are a hypocrite.
You exaggerate your accent
and sticking peck in total with a toe ring.
Then you here
and fired a lot of sødsuppe,
and then call me a liar?
Everything you have said tonight,
meant that you had sex.
Hello.
Was it good?
No.
Was it bad?
I try sgu,
but it's just all the lies.
Never again.
I swear, never again.
But was it worth it?
Do not you hear me?
It was fantastic.
I said, wait.
I said stop.
I said no.
Look at you.
Sorry. But I was so close.
And it seemed as if you enjoyed it.
This is not what this is about.
. Not that?
If a girl says stop,
so stop Monday.
We should come closer to each other,
do something exciting together.
But you are in your own world.
You do not listen to me.
In the mind røvpulede you Ian Ziering.
Andrew ... Nut you?
Det er ikke det, det handler om.
You were given as a bold orgasm.
How do you know? You wonder ...
He had curly hockeyhår!
I know it,
because I could feel it.
Could you?
When I was up in you,
I could feel it when you came.
And also you have the
semen overall.
It was not bad. And it was
good to see you so excited.
It is long overdue.
And you made of the
some new sounds.
Tax ...
I am not bored.
Is it a question?
No. I say it.
I am not bored either.
It slipped my mind. Can we?
Yes. Sorry.
But then ...
I thought that was what you would.
I did also. I do.
You so fantastic, tax.
I love you so much.
I know this well.
Do you really?
She did it for you.
No. She was just as much
with at it as me.
She would just as much as me.
I would just make you happy.
To do this.
No, see me. I deserve
not a nice girl like you.
Everyone looks at us and think:
"What does she do with that guy?"
And you know very well.
I would just give you something you
really deserve, so you were happy.
When I see people,
which looks at such us ...
See for yourself, you notice it.
I knew it.
Yes, I notice it,
and I love it.
So I feel
I have a wonderful secret.
The fact that I know something that no other.
That you only min.
Look at him.
He has a solid ass and a nice nose.
And see just the stick!
Gider you just?
Yes. It was good, and he is sweet,
but I thought of you all the time.
Really?
Yes.
But I ...
I am a pervert.
I am also.
I, too.
I steal people's shoes,
because the smell of them ...
I love you.
You are so sexy.
What you said.
I love you too, honey.
What to do, just what you want.
I take you
in all ways right here.
I stick in your hair
and kærtegner you and loves you.
Love game with you overall ...
I think I smutter now.
Wait, Dave.
Excuse me ...
I would not be a jerk.
I know this well.
And thanks you
kneppede my girlfriend.
Fine enough.
No!
Our peck touching.
See you, tosser.
Good night, your perverse skid.
So ...
Is everything okay?
Yes. Love me?
Yes.
Will you take me?
Do you want to do everything for me?
Anything, sweetheart.
You know what? I looked at,
dal on favnede each other.
And it was good.
And sexy.
I have opened a new bottle. I
did not know what I have to.
Here.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Are you in?
I would not be a hassle.
And I will also meet early
tomorrow.
Fine enough.
I follow you out.
Yes.
Greet Jasmine.
I will.
And greet Fuck Dog.
Keep the pot!
Okay.
I can not call the next paragraph
time. I have so busy on the job.
Yes, me too.
It has been nice.
Yes.
Okay then.
It was fun.
Yes.
Give me five!
I'm so full.
I am also.
Good night so.
Matt, when I said that I ...
What is it?
I do not know. Some places
CDs in my player.
Just tell it.
I'm so camp, as you can be.
I love the song.
You?
Yes.
I'm not full.
I am not.
I am sorry that I call her
a møgluder.
She is a møgluder.
It says you because I said it.
You always say things when I have
I said it because you feel you should.
Well, I would not.
Do you see it, I said,
after you had said that?
Because I thought what I said.
Keep the pot now.
We must talk about it.
Keep the pot.
Hold now up to talk.
Will you?
We can do something else.
I can not comment on anything.
Dave?
Dave, you're awake?
You are awake, right?
You did it well.
Subtitle by
# "'MADDY"' #
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org