Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Are you all right?
Shit really hitted the fan.
That's a whole different study.
But if we knew that, we could...
We don't know that!
We gotta operate with
what we do know!
- I'm still dreaming.
- No, you're not.
My turn with the coat.
I'm triying to explain
exclusively the facts...
The guys on the crew are going crazy.
A couple of 'em flown the coop already.
I don't know how long
we can stay on the air!
Ok, check that camera!
Who has camera two?
Who the hell's on camera 2,
a blind man?
Roll the rescue...
Roll the rescue stations!
Got a report that half those stations
have been knocked out.
- Get me another list!
- Sure, I'll just pull it outta my ass, right?
I don't believe that, doctor.
- Do you believe the dead are returning to life?
- I'm not so...
Do you believe the dead are returning
to life and attacking the living?
I'm not so sure what
to believe, doctor
All we get is what you people tell us.
And it's hard enough to believe...
It's fact...! It's fact...!
It's hard enough to believe
without you coming in here...
You're not running a
talk-show here, Mr. Berman!
You can forget pitching an audience
the moral bullshit they wanna hear!
You're talking about abandoning
any human code of behaviour...
Frannie, get on the new list of rescue stations.
Charlie's receiving it on the emergency room.
- Rescue stations list?
- Half of those are inoperatives as of now.
Charlie, these are rescue stations.
We can't send people to inoperative rescue stations.
We've had old information on the air
for the last 12 hours.
- Kill the old ones.
- Givens wants to!
Kill'em Dick! Tell
Givens to see me!
... public figures like
yourself that this situation is been...
... you're
not telling me...
... by the public
You're not listening!
We've this situation for the last 3 weeks...
What does it take?
What does it take
to make people see?
People aren't willing to accept
your solutions, doctor.
And I don't blame them!
Every dead body that is not
exterminated becomes one of them.
It gets up and kills.
The people it kills
get up and kill!
Dave!
Sit down and type that up.
You're dropping my question.
I think Foster is right. We're loosen it.
Yeah, we're blowing it ourselves.
A dead body must be exterminated.
Either by destroying the brain or severing
the brain from the rest of the body.
- You must be out of your mind!
- This situation must be controlled before is too late.
...multiplying too rapidly!
What the hell is going on?
Who kill those supers?
Frannie, who told you to
kill those supers?
Nobody. I killed it.
They are outdated.
Do you know you're on air?
What the hell is going on?
I want those supers on
the air all the time.
Without those rescues
stations on screen...
every minute people won't
watch us. So they'll tune out!
Are you willing to murder people
by sending them out to
stations that haved closed down
I want that list up on the screen
every minute that we're on the air!
- Anybody need a ride?
- What the hell are you doing?
Get back on this console!
What is this? A news show or
a football game?
Get that idiot off the air!
Officer, stop those men!
Lucas, get back on this console!
Damn!
Get somebody in here that
can run this thing.
Get that fucking idiot off the air!
Triple pay!
We're staying on the air!
Fuck off! Fuck off!
Now, Doctor Foster. The public
needs facts. What do you have
to give us?
They kill for one reason.
They kill for food.
They eat their victims.
You understand that, Mr. Berman?
That's what keeps them going.
If we listened... If we dealt with
this phenomenom properly
without emotion.
Without emotion!
It wouldn't have come to this!
There is a martial law state in Philadelphia,
as in all major cities in the country.
Where's your badge?
Take it easy...
It's just crazy!
It's just completely insane!
Shit! I ain't...
Yeah, here's my badge.
OK, you can go.
Should we be unable
to check the spread.
Because of the emotional attitude
of the citizens because these issues of morality.
Jim, you take it!
It is the order of the O.E.P...
by command of the federal goverment...
the president of the United States
Citizens may no longer occupy private
residences no matter how safely protected...
or well stocked.
Citizens will be moved into central
areas of the city.
The bodies of the dead...
will be delivered over to
special squads of the national guard...
for organised disposition.
Frannie, meet me on the roof
at 9 o'clock. We're getting out.
I don't believe it...
We're gonna get out!
In the chopper.
- Stephen, we can't. We got...
- Careful!
- Nine p.m., all right.
- Stephen, we can't. We got...
We got to nothing, Fran.
We've got to survive.
Somebody's got to survive.
Now you'd be up stairs at 9.
Don't make me come lookin' for ya.
Go ahead. We'll be off the air by midnight.
Emergency networks are taking over.
Our responsability is finished.
Martinez!
You've been watching. You know we
got this building surrounded.
The bastard's got them moved into
one building. Dumb little bastard!
Looks like they're really gonna
try to fight us.
- C'mon!
- Martinez.
People in this project
are your responsability.
We don't want any of them hurt
and neither do you!
I'm giving you 3 minutes, Martinez.
Turn over your weapons
and surrender.
There're no charges against you.
There are no charges against you or
any of your people.
Yet.
C'mon, Martinez.
Yeah, C'mon Martinez. Show your
greasy little puerto rican ass...
so I can blow it right off.
I'll blow all their asses off.
Low life bastards. Blow all their
little low life puerto rican and
nigger asses rigth off!
- You're right?
- I'm right Roger.
How the hell come we
stick with these low lifes in these
big ass fancy hotels anyway?
Shit man! This' better than I got.
You ain't gonna talk 'em outta here.
You gotta blow'em out!
Just stay cool, ok? When you go
in there just don't pop off, all right?
- I'll be ok.
- C'mon!
Let's get on with it!
This is a waste of my time!
Let's go! Let's go!
Move it! Move it!
Goddamitt!
C'mon, you dumb bastards!
Come and get 'em!
Bishop, try to kill a thousand pigs!
Get 'em out of the road!
People, look out!
Hold it!
Don't go out there!
Masks!
Masks for the gas!
Work your way down.
C'mon, work your way down!
One floor at a time.
Keep going!
Hold 'em in the halls.
Hold 'em in the halls!
- Stay there!
- Damn!
James, slow down!
No, let me go!
C'mon, you little bastards!
Wooley's gone ape shit, man!
- Wooley!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Gimme a hand!
- Gimme a hand!
- Leave me alone, man!
What the hell!
Leave me alone!
Gimme a hand... Somebody...!
Step away from him!
Goddammit!... Help me.
He's crazy!
Step away from him.
Not that room!
Don't enter that room!
Holy Christ!
C'mon, for chrissake!
Shoot him, man.
Shoot him in the head!
It's one of them!
- Miguelito!
- Shoot him!
- Dios mío... Miguel!
- Hold it!
- Watch the girl!
- Miguel!
Mi vida... Miguelito...
Stand clear, for chrissake, stand clear!
You're in still one piece
in body and soul, boy
You were in Woley's unit.
Wasn't you?
I didn't see nothing.
I didn't see how he died.
You running?
I don't mean because of Woley.
I mean 'cause of all this...
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
Man, there's a lot of people runnin' out.
I could run.
I could run rigth tonight.
Friend of mine got this helicopter.
He ask me to come with him.
You think it's right to run?
Señores, please to let me pass.
Let's get him to the medics.
No, no please.
Just let me pass. I go up to
seven floor to find my sister.
Just let me pass.
The people of 107 will do
what you wish now.
Many have died on the streets last week.
In the basement of this building you find them.
I have givem them the last rites.
Now... You do what you will.
You're stronger than us. But sooner
I think they'll be stronger than you.
When the dead walk, señores,
we must stop the killing... Or loose the war.
C'mon open up!
Get in! Get in!
Jesus Christ!
- Hey, you ok down there?
- Yeah
This must be where they
dumped 'em in. Huh?
- You need more men?
- No is all done, man.
Is all been done.
Jesus Christ.
Why did these people keep 'em here?
'Cause they still believe
there's respect in dying.
C'mon, I need you.
I don't see Roger. We'll
give him ten minutes.
Steve!
I know.
Just wait right here.
Just like that. Like in the car.
Just hold her 'til she spits out right at you.
Dispatch come in.
Emergency call to Police Stop.
Hello HQ, this is Police Stop.
Operator's dead. Post abandon.
Steven
- I hope is Roger.
- What are you doing?
I'll be right there.
Just stay cool.
Hello.
C'mon skipper.
They got friends coming.
Who are you?
- We're with J.A.S. We...
- About a minute and a half on the car.
Now wait a minute. We're
just here to refuel.
Those men were already dead.
You were here... You know that.
Hey, you're J.A.S. Traffic Watch.
Steve Andrews.
Right. That's me.
I'm Steve Andrews.
- Yep, no shit.
- We got a lot further in this bird, Skipper.
Can't all fit.
How many will that thing hold?
Hey man, I ain't nowhere in nothin'
I can't drive myself!
That's true! Somethin' happens
to him and we'll be stuck!
Stick with the boat!
- We get a lot further in this bird!
- Hey that's a squad car!
It's okay, we're police.
Bullshit, man! Let's
get to the boat!
You're runnin', ain't it?
You and your friends are runnin'
in the J.A.S. Traffic bird.
- What's the problem, officer?
- Caught your friends here stealin' company gasoline.
What do you mean friends?
They know, Rog...
They runnin' to.
Now, it'd be crazy to start shootin'
one at another. Wouldn't it?
Sure would.
You guys are ok?
Who's he?
His name is Peter. He's alright.
C'mon let's hustle.
Hey, you guys. You better move out.
There's a report on the dock bein' knocked out.
Right. Good luck squad!
You sure this'll carry us all?
Little harder on the fuel,
but we'll be ok.
Hey, you got any cigarettes?
Any of you got cigarettes?
No, sorry.
Where do you headed?
Down river... We got an idea maybe we
can make it to the islands.
What islands?
Any islands.
What about you?
Where you headed?
Straight up.
Didn't have any cigarettes!
- How do I have a cigarette?
- I don't know
Hey, any of you got cigarettes?
- How I gonna go to the islands
if I don't have cigarettes?
Any of you leavin' people behind?
An ex-husband.
An ex-wife.
You Peter?
Some brothers.
Those... real brothers?
You know... real brothers
or street brothers?
Both.
How many real ones?
Two.
Two?
One's in jail... The other's a
pro ball player.
But we catch up to each other
once in a while.
Is he your man?
Most of the time, yes.
Just like to know
who everybody is.
Yeah, me too.
Any more water?
You know where we are?
Yeah, I know exactly
where we are.
Harrisburg?
We passed it about an hour ago.
Jesus. It's everywhere.
Still pretty close to Johnston.
Those rednecks are probably
enjoying the whole thing.
- Is that you again?
- My boy...!
- Keep movin'! Keep movin'!
- Hey ya, check it out!
I heard that by
10 o'clock we've briefing.
I got a couple extra watches...
Didn't they say when?
Great job. You did a great job!
Keep going, keep going.
Look out! Behind you!
Down! Get out of the way!
There! Behind the white car!
Get the gas tank.
- Shit!
- Yeah!
Hey, I got him!
Fuck, I missed it!
Yeah!
Shit! Damn near empty!
I got this one.
There's a lot of private planes
in farm country like this.
I guess they all hit the pumps
and they took off.
Yeah, to where?
Got some here.
- Can you handle that?
- Yeah, I got it.
I'm gonna see what's left
in the hangars.
Bunch of junk!
Steve?
Fran, Run!
Run!
Roger!
It's all right...
Peter!
Right... Fuck!
You never aim a gun at anyone, Mr.
Peter, my god!
What are you doin'?
Scary... Isn't it?
Isn't it?
C'mon.
We gotta find fuel.
Maybe closer to Cleveland.
No, we've gotta stay
out of the big cities.
If it's anything like Philly we
might never get out alive.
We might never get out
of any place alive.
- We didn't almost get out of there.
- We're gettin' outta here fine!
As long as there's not too many of
those things we can handle 'em easy.
It wasn't one of "those things"
that nearly blew me away.
We gotta stay in the sticks.
There's bound to be more little
private airports upstate.
There's the locks along the Allgheny.
Fuel stations there.
State. Private.
Those are probably still manned.
We don't need those hassles either.
They're just out after
scavengers and looters.
Oh, you got the papers
for this limousine?
I got J.A.S id.
And so does Fran.
Right! And we're out here
doin' traffic reports.
Wake up, sucker!
We're thieves and we're bad guys!
That's exactly what we are.
We gotta find our own way.
Jesus Christ! We don't even
know where we going
We don't have food. We don't have
water. We don't even have a radio.
Stephen you need to
get some sleep.
What the hell is it?
Looks like a... shopping center.
One of those big indoor lots.
Oh my God!
No chance. Forget it.
Let's get out of here!
Wait a minute. They can't
get up here.
Yeah, I we can't
go down there!
Let's check it out.
Most of the gates are down.
I don't think they can get into the stores.
I haven't seen any of then
up on the second floor.
The big departments stores
usually use both floors.
If we can ge it up top...
Ok.
Guess the power's not off in
this area. Could be nuclear.
What are they doing?
Why do they come here?
Some kind of instinct.
Memory... Of what they
used to do.
This was an important
place in their lives.
Hey... Look at this!
These don't go down to the mall.
What the hell is this?
How do we get down there?
Ok, c'mon Fran, let go.
Well, it's done.
Looks like a free lunch.
Spam!
Do you bring a can opener?
No, I guess I didn't.
Then don't knock it.
It got it's own key.
What do you think?
This is the only way up here.
You better get some sleep too, buddy.
There's an awful lot of stuff
down there that we could use.
I know it.
Big place. But they're pretty
spread down there.
I think we can out-run 'em
Hit and run?
Hit and run.
Are you crazy?
This place could be a gold mine.
We gotta a least check it out.
This is exactly what we're
trying to go away from... Look what...
Stephen!
Leave him be.
We're going ourselves.
That's ready to shoot. Be careful.
The trigger squeezes really easy...
but the weapon'll kick you good
when it fires. Be ready for that!
Anyone but us comes up the stairs,
you guys take off in the machine.
You'll probably hear some shooting.
Just don't panic, ok?
Here.
Keys to the kingdom.
Grab the walkie talkies.
It's Christmas time down there, buddy.
Fat city, brother. How we gonna work it?
We get into one of the stores up here.
They'll probably have their own escalators.
Let's check those keys.
Fifteen upper and lower.
Right here.
How about a little music?
What?
Might cover the noise we make.
Hit 'em all. Might as well
have power in everything.
We might need it.
Stephen?
Stephen!
What do you think?
Bag it or try for it?
- You game?
- I need lighter fuel.
You got it.
Jesus Christ! They're maniacs!
Wait...
Alright!
C'mon!
Stephen, don't go down there!
- Bastard!
- What happen?
Don't open!
Not working!
C'mon!
Don't open the door! C'mon!
Let her go!
Take care of the other one!
Stephen, for God sake!
We can't leave those
guys down there.
Well... We're in.
Now how the hell we're gonna get back?
Who the hell cares?
Let's go shopping first!
Watch it! Watch it!
Just let's get the stuff we need!
I'm gonna get us a television and a radio!
Ok, find the goods.
I got them! I got them!
Ok.
I'm gonna need
at least a couple!
Why not?
Hey man, we can't carry all that shit.
Oh, I see. We're just
gonna wheel right by 'em.
We gonna try brother. We ain't doin' this for
the exercise. We might try to get what we can.
Alright. Let's go brother!
The old okey doke!
- Hey, Ugly!
- Let's raise some hell... Hey... Hey...!
- Come here champ! Come here!
- Over here... Hey... Hey...!
- C'mon, over here!
- Over here! That's right!
C'mon, C'mon...
C'mon, C'mon...!
Alright, c'mon!
C'mon... Over here...
Just give it time...
give it time.
Ok. They're coming.
Go on up. Stay outta sight but
lemme know when is clear enough.
- Ok.
Come to papa! That's it.
Keep coming... Keep coming.
Peter, it's good. Let's do it.
Is it clear?
Not altogether... But they
spread out pretty good.
- I think we can move the wagon.
- I'm comin'
- What the hell was that?
- I don't know... Fuzz maybe?
Or maybe flyboy. Where's it comin' from?
I don't know. I can't tell.
C'mon. Open up.
- Maybe I'd go with you.
- Open up so I can get the wagon over!
- If it's flyboy, let's get him on our side.
- Ok.
- You just cover me good. You hear?
- You got it!
Hold it flyboy!
Don't go into the stairway!
Don't open that door, baby.
You'll lead 'em right up with you.
Run for it. Run this way.
That's it. C'mon! Run...
Run... Run... C'mon!
Now... Head for the department store.
Go!
Ok, downstairs again...
Same trick... Let's go!
- What do we do?
- Let them know we're here.
Whoooo Hoooo!
C'mon. Let's go... Over here!
You did alright this time, flyboy.
How about it?
- Whooooo peeeee!
- Over here.
Now is the time to make
savers in our weekend sales department.
Jesus Christ!
...dinning room fest
with a 40 by 60 burlap table...
Why pay more when
the sales are open right here!
We just gotta wait longer before we move.
There's always the chance of some
of 'em stayin' up on the balcony.
We can handle that.
We can break through 'em.
If any of 'em see or hear us. They'll
just follow us up. It's not good.
We can sure outrun 'em. Load up
what we can and get the hell outta here.
I've been thinking...
Maybe we got a good thing going here...
- Maybe we shouldn't be in such a hurry to leave.
- Oh, man!
If we could get back up there
without them catchin' on...
We could hold up for a while.
At least long enough to catch a breath.
Check out the radio. See what's hapenin'
- Oh, man!
- There's some kind of passageway
over the top of the stores.
I don't know if it's just heating
ducts or some kind of access.
I saw 'em on a map.
Upstairs... Let's go!
Ceiling is just lighting grids!
Is gotta be in this area.
It's on the map!
Elevator shaft...
Hold the doors!
It's here. You gonna need a screwdriver
or somethin' to stand on for down there.
I know where the tools are.
Why don't you grab the stool over there?
It's alright. We can get it off.
You found it, flyboy.
One stop shopping. Anything you
need right at your fingertips.
- Phillips?
- Here you go.
Stephen?
Shit!
Jesus!
I seen it. C'mon.
Don't shoot! They'll hear it downstairs!
Looks like we're gonna be ok.
You should see all the great
stuff we got, Frannie.
All kinds of stuff...
This place is terrific!
It's really esay to pick the profit.
All kinds of things...
We really got it made in here... Frannie!
Frannie?
What the hell time is it, anyway?
Not quite nine.
And nothing?
As long as we're getting the pattern
that's means they're sending the signal.
No longer seek ocupancy
in private residences...
... no matter how safe or
well protected they may be.
... the president today is
a the congress...
Is she alright?
She looks blunt.
- What do you expect?
- I mean, she really looks sick.
Phisically.
She's pregnant.
... the communications with
Detroit had been knocked out...
How long?
Three and half, maybe four months.
Jesus!
Steve, maybe we should
try to get movin'
We can deal with it.
Yeah, but maybe she needs a
doctor or somethin'
We can deal with it!
Doesn't change a thing.
Do you wanna get
rid of it?
- Huh?
- Do you want to abort?
It's not too late.
And I know how.
How your decisitions were made?
Do you want to abort it?
Do you?
Somebody better sit
watch all the time.
They'll never get through there.
Enough of 'em will. And ain't just
them things we got to worry about.
That chopper up there could give us
away if somebody comes messin' around.
What are gonna do?
Land another pilot to fly it out.
They're not gonna mess with a little bird
like that. They got enough in their hands.
So, I guess we forget
about Canada, right?
Nobody cares about my vote.
Oh, c'mon, Frannie
don't you sleeping.
You know... I'm afraid... You're
hypnotised by this place... All of you!
It's all so bright and neatly wrapped
that you don't see is a prison too!
Stephen, just let's take what we
need and keep going.
Do you know how many times do we have
to land for fuel on our way up north?
Those things out there are everywhere.
The authorities will give us just a
hard time... Maybe worse!
Fran...
We've got everything
we need right here.
Let's get some sleep.
... on other side, these creatures
function on a subconstious instinctal level...
You were the one that want to
set up a house.
... develops a chemical spray
from crop dusting airplanes...
... that doesn't have
effects on human population...
... normal question.
The first question is always...
... are these cannibals?
No, they're not cannibals...
... Cannibalism in the true sense of
the word implies an intraspecie activity...
... these creatures cannot
be consider human...
... they prey on humans.
they do not prey on each other!...
... that's the difference. They attack...
They feed only on warm human flesh...
... Intelligence? Seemingly little
or no reasoning power...
... What basic skills remain are more like
remembered behaviours from normal life...
... There are reports of these
creatures using tools...
... but even these actions
are the most primitive...
... the use of external articles
as bludgeons and so forth...
... I might point out that even animals could
adopt the basic use of tools in this manner...
... These creatures are nothing but
pure motorised instinct...
... We must not be lulled by the concept that
these are our family members or our friends...
... They are not. They would
not respond to such emotions...
... They must be destroy on sight!...
That was Dr. Miller Rush
from the O.E.P...
... and... later on... hopefully today
we're not exactly sure yet...
... I'm waiting for word on this
from some people...
... we expected get him here for a
liveshow. An actual live interview...
... so we can discuss things with him...
The semis are big enough
to block the entrances.
You sure we can start 'em?
You haven't spent enough
time on the street.
This report says they're
working on an analysis...
... of this whole phenomenom...
... from the point of view of a virus disease.
They've been doing various lab tests...
... to see if the can deal
with it in that way...
... and perhaps come up with some
kind of a workeable vaccine...
Hey Fran.
Acording to this report,
the problem they run into Atlanta...
... is that there not are
specimens available...
... it seems in that area
there aren't intact...
... We have a film report
shot in Atlanta but it's not arrived...
I would have made you coffee and
breakfast, but I don't have my pots and pans.
Also... Wait a minute...
There is another report...
May I say something?
Shoot
I'm sorry you found out I'm pregnant, because I don't wanna be treat differently than you'd treat each other
Hey, Frannie, c'mon!
And I'm not gonna be den mother
for you guys
And I want to know what's going on...
...And I want something to say about the plans.
There's four of us, ok?
Jesus, Fran...
Fair enough!
Ok. Now what's goin' on?
We're goin' out.
And you're not coming with us!
And you won't come with us until
you'll learn how to handle yourself
Something else...
I don't know about you two,
but I wanna learn how to fly that helicopter
If anything happens to you,
we have to be able to fly out of here
She's right, man
C'mon. Let's go.
And I don't want to believe
you're leaving me without a gun again
I just might be able to
figure how to use it
I'm sorry, Stephen
It's alright. It's alright
Stephen?
Yeah?
Be careful
Yeah, we'll be alright
In spite of everything you hear here
there's still some people with a sense of humour
How about it?
Gettin' it
I'm not too sure of this thing.
I'll just ride pick up
I grew up on one of these.
C'mon, let's go!
Alright!
Hey, your tail is to slow too?
Come in.
You look my size when you're
sitting in that truck
Well, I wanna know is how if we've both
have the same force together...
...yours be so enlarge?,
You know
Well, they told me it was
a midget force...
They needed somebody
to look out you
Hey, where's flyboy?
What's his twenty?
I just hope he'll fly
off that roof or we fly zero!
Ok, let's go! C'mon!
C'mon, Roger, Come on!
C'mon, c'mon, man!
- Like a charm, uh? A Fucking charm!
- C'mon, man. Three more, baby!
Roger!
C'mon, look, man!
Look!
Get its head up...
Get its head up!
Roger, get its head up, man!
Get down! Stay down... I got it!
Roger, move!
Bastards
You bastards
Roger?
We got 'em, buddy. Didn't we?
We got this, man.
We got this by the ass!
Roger?!
C'mon, man! Get your head together!
We got a lot to do!
Let's go, baby. Number two...
You alright?
Perfect, baby. Perfect!
Come on, here!
Let finish this. C'mon man!
Roger, c'mon. C'mon man!
Leave him, motherfuckers! Son of bitches!
- Oh, God! Oh, Jesus!
- What?
My bag. I left my goddam bag
in the other truck!
Alright. You better screw
your head on.
Yeah! C'mon, c'mon!
Let's go!
I mean it, man! Now you're not just
playin' with your life, your playin' with mine!
Now are you straight?
Yeah
Go, go, go!
C'mon, Roger, come on!
Watch it, man!
Watch out, watch out!
Roger watch it!
Damm!
That's it, man
- That's it
- Bullshit!
We gotta deal with that leg!
I'm dealin' with it... I'm just dealin' with
it fine! Don't you worry, buddy!
There's a lot to get done before
you can afford to lose me
It all depends on how many of
them are still inside
There's one hell of a run
we gotta make
If we have more flares,
or maybe some of those propane jobs
Guns are first.
Guns and ammunition
You sure you gonna make it?
Just hurry up with that!
Don't try to shoot
through those gates
Openings are too small. Bullet will
wind up chasin' us around in here
Don't worry. They can't
get through
- Ain't it a crime
- What?
The only person who could
ever miss with gun...
... is the sucker with the
bread to buy it.
You just wait
out there, sissies...
... we comin'
And we ready!
OK, let's go!
OK, the door is open.
Push, push!
That's it! Push! That's it!
We're inside. C'mon, let's go!
Hardware
Look here, man... I'm...
I know, shut up. Will you
Alright. The toughest part
will be gettin' by these right here
It's too far
There's no backing up now
We gotta lock those main doors
We'll never make all four entrances.
It's too risky
We'll make it. You just
be ready to open up for us
Wait a minute!
The car!
What?
One of those car? Why don't
you use the car over there?
You OK to start it?
OK, let's go
Close the door. Close the door!
The keys, Stephen... The keys!
C'mon, man.
Get out of there!
God dammit!
Keep 'em! Just keep 'em!
Lock yourself in there!
Jump in the back!
- You alright?
- Yeah
- Keep 'em at large and I'll do the lock
- Gotcha!
That's not 100%, but I don't
think they'll get through
Can't they smash the glass?
Safety stuff.
Pretty indestructible
They got no leverage under the truck
I hopin' they'll just go away
after they find they can't get in
I'll get the alarms.
You get in the car
We're OK. We got it made.
It's gonna work
How many you figure are already in?
I don't know.
Not too many
We'll get 'em easy
We get it all locked off.
Then we're goin' on a hunt!
We put up the wall here
This way we can still
get to the plumbing
Why can't we just
board up the stairway?
Sooner or later, it might
be a patrol through here
Looters maybe...
I don't want anybody to
even know that stairway exists
I don't know what else to do?
You're doin' fine
His leg is awful.
The infection is spreading quickly
Can't we do somethin'?
Can't we take him to a Med Unit?
I've seen half a dozen
guys get bitten by those things...
None of 'em lasted more
than three days
Peter where are you?
Right here, trooper
We did it, didn't we?
We whip 'em, didn't we?
That's right Rog
Didn't we? Didn't we whip 'em?
We sure did, buddy
We whipped 'em.
We whipped 'em good.
We whipped 'em!
We got it all!
Leave me alone. It's alright
It's my problem
Just get out of here.
I don't want you here!
I just don't want you
to see me like this
Stephen get out. Please!
This place is gonna be rotten
We gotta cleaning up, brother
You never know
What do you think?
Watch this!
They're still here
They're after us.
They know we're still in here
They're after the place...
They don't know why.
They just remember
Remember that they
wanna be in here
What the hell are they?
They're us, that's all.
There's no more room in Hell
What?
Sometin' my grandad
used to tell us
You know Macumba?
Voodoo...
Grandady was a priest in Trinidad.
Used to tell us...
When there's no more
room in Hell...
The dead will walk the Earth
Got him! Hurry up! C'mon!
Go on... I'll stay with him
You'll take care of me,
wouldn't you, Peter?
You'll take care of me...
when I go
Try to get some sleep.
Save your strenght
I don't wanna be walkin'
around like that
Peter?
Peter?!!
Yeah, I'm here man!
Don't do it, til you're sure
I am comin' back
I'm gonna try not to...
I'm gonna try no to...
come back
I'm gonna try...
... not to.
They use...
maybe...
five percent of the food
available on the human body
... the kind of things...
...with that food amount, the body
is usually intact enough
...to be mobile when it revives
What are you saying?
I mean... You scientists...
- Dummies, dummies!
- What are you suggesting?
Excuse me.
Listen, quiet! Quiet!
One wonders what
is worth saving...
...which is I do
For all I know...
The brain is already dead...
...is the idiots who still alive
Can I speak it up how
to stay alive too?
And I'm tryin' to help
you gentlemen
And you can help.
But what you do take...
- In a logical way...!
- ...is illogical!
Illogical hell!
Illogical hell! I'm showing you a way
that we can opt...
... to pull supplies twenty times!
To pull supplies for whom?
For a whole specimen that is
walking around there...
- ... in increasing numbers.
- We should feed 'em?
What else we
should with 'em?
Gimme an alternative!
I thought you
scientists can come up with that?
... actually, that way solve the problem of growing.
Feeding the oposition doesn't make any sense!
Well I can think on one alternative
I can think on another one, yes.
Since they seem to congregate
in heavily populated areas...
and since we haven`t touch
upon our nuclear resources
why don't we drop a bomb
in all the big cities?
- You probably can't be serious?
- I'm deadly serious! What are the choices?
- What if they run out of food?
- They don't run out of food. That's the problem!
And they won't run out of
food while we still alive
This kind of things, you know,
things that we're talking about here...
...sounds like just a bunch of
people talking crazy
- This is not figthing...!
- ... without actually picture it out!
This is not the
republic against the democrats...
...that got us in a hole economically.
Or lead us to another war!
... is more crucial that we go
down to the line, folks
...we're down to the line. There are
no divisions upon 'em and the living...
At least... At
least let him finish, please!
It`s really all over, isn't it?
...unemotional!
...we got to remain rational
- Logical... logical
- Scientist always think in those kinda turns...
...if it doesn't work that way
that's not how people really are
You've got
to remain logical. We've got to.
There's no choice.
It has to be.
It's gonna be that!
Here it comes!
- Oh nice!
- Wow!
- Bon apetit!
- thank you!
- Stephen?
- Thank you very much!
Peter, what about you?
Where you goin'?
This is just for the two of you
Enjoy
We can't Stephen. Not now
But we will...
Hey, when you finish the rove,
we wrapped it up the drugstore
Attention, all shoppers...
...if you have a 32,
we have a special treat for you...
...if you purchase is in the
next half and hour
...with an amount of
five dollars or more
...we'll give you a bar
of Hard Candy free!
There hasn't been a broadcast
fro three days. Why don't you give it up?
They might come back on
What have we done
to ourselves?
OK, now easy... easy
Stabilise it. That's right!
Bring 'er down. Down, down.
That's it! You got it!
- Hon, you got it!
- Yeah, I did it!
- Wow!
- They must get in through the roof
Son of a bitch!
- They have trucks blockin' all the entrances
- Yeah, trucks!
No sweat!
What do you think?
Hit 'em now or tonight?
Tonight
Hey, we know you in there?
seen the helicopter on the roof...
... how many of you in there?
We know you're up there.
We seen the whirlybird on the roof
Hey you guys shut up.
Cut it! Shut up!
Raiders
Could ya use some company
up there?
- They know we're here, maybe we should...
- No chance
Oh, change your mind...
Do you wanna try?
Alright, cut. Cut, cut!
Listen... How many of you in
there, anyway... there's three of us
- What if...
- Quiet!
- I think we should...
- Jesus Christ! Shut up and listen
We don't like people who don't share.
You just fucked up real bad!
Let's go
It's time.
Just three, huh?
Holy shit!
They'll get in. They'll
move the trucks
There's hundreds of those
creatures down there
C'mon man, that's a
professional army
Looks like they been survivin'
on the road all through this thing
Well let's not make
it esay for 'em. Come on!
What's happening?
There's fifteen or twenty of 'em.
We're gonna shut off the gates
- Stephen
- We're just gonna shut the gates
They'll never know
we're here
Downstairs first.
Got your talk box?
- Yeah
- Keep it handy
Shit... It's all taped up.
It's all ready for us
What the hell are they doing? There's a
whole fucking glass latch and won't open!
Yeah, everyone fucking
thinks like, Joe
Hey, the whole damm gate
locks won't open
Let's go blow the
goddammed gate locks!
Watch that guy with the machine gun,
you won't believe it!
Wacht out, dude!
They're in, flyboy.
They're opening the outer locks
When those doors will open, there's
gonna be a thousand zombies in here
They're gonna have their
hands full
Just let 'em fire it up!
Get up on the balcony.
Stay out of sight.
I'll meet you...
at the Information room
Alright guys, look out for yoursefls.
It's good for us. Let's go!
Hey you there!
Hello
Flyboy?
Flyboy, where the hell
are you?
C'mon man, you're too slow!
It's ours.
We took it
What the hell are you doing playin' around,
let's go upstairs and doin' him
Goddamit Flyboy,
what the hell are you doing?
Just stay out of sight!
They're after the place,
they don't care about us!
Alright, dammit!
Now we got a war!
Say goodbye creep
Where the hell are you
gonna watch that thing?
You alright, man
He's upstairs. Let's go!
C'mon, mother...
- Where he go?
- I don't know. Come on!
I see you!
Peter? Peter?!
Peter!
- I know he's in there!
- Come on!
Hey you! I see you up there!
C'mon, let's go!
Let's get out of here
Son of a bitch!
C'mon man. Let's get
the hell out of here
Peter? Peter are you there?
Where the hell are you?
The elevator
Those things are all over the place.
Climb up top...
I'll get you out the
grid on the shaft
I'm coming
Flyboy? Flyboy!
Stephen?
I heard his gun...
may he's alright
We'll just wait...
We'll just wait a while
It's almos light.
Let's go
He doesn't aswer the
radio for hours
For God sake!
- What is it?
- Stephen...
They're coming up
Go on... get out of here
- Peter?
- I said... get out of here
- Oh, Jesus Christ, Peter...
- I don't want to go
I really don't
Come on!
Get there! Move woman!
How much fuel do we have?
Not much
Alright
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org