#Well since time out
Of mind I been lazy #
# And times before
That I was cruel #
# And the times
Before that #
# I was mean
I was mad #
# I never had
Nobody like you #
# And the times before
That I was crazy #
# I saw the dark
Side of the moon #
# And the stars
In the sky #
# They never
Caught my eye #
# 'Cause I never had
Nobody like you #
# I never had
[baby crying]
Nobody like you ##
T ommy?
T ommy, the baby.
Hm?
It's your turn.
[groans]
[whispers]
PIease.
Right. Right.
Okay, okay.
[baby crying]
God damned baby.
[sighs]
[baby crying]
Don't do that.
The second we walked
in here, I could feel
my wallet start whining.
If we're gonna get
the steak, you wanna
get the Oregon Pinot?
Yeah, I saw that.
It's 200 bucks though.
Babe, it's
our anniversary.
Have you had a chance
to decide on some wine
this evening?
You have no
Iive entertainment.
You are correct, sir.
And I have no money.
An idea, and you
can say no.
Is it possible
for me to dance off
a portion of our tab?
Dance it away?
It would be
unusual.
Look how cute he is.
Has this worked before?
Not that I can
remember.
Are you sure?
Because he's
very good.
Really?
No.
You're an idiot.
I'm an idiot?
You married me.
So?
Three years!
I know.
Three years.
Well?
[clears throat]
I knew you were
gonna bring this up.
So, you remembered?
Absolutely,
I remember.
So, you're ready?
Yeah, I'm totally ready.
You're ready
to be a dad?
A dad? What?
I thought we were
talking about anal.
Is the three year
not the anal anniversary?
No. It is. Okay.
Okay, if you really want to,
I'm willing to give it
a try.
Seriously?
Yes. We need to stop
by the sex shop on
the way home.
I need to get a strap-on.
Do you prefer regular
or ribbed?
You are good.
You had me there.
Seriously, I'II
give it a try.
I just don't know
if it will fit.
Of course it won't fit.
That's the fun. Pain.
We could do that,
or we could just
have a baby.
Ah, you did remember.
I did.
You really wanna
have a baby?
Yeah, I really do.
We're gonna have
a family.
We are gonna have
You can teach him
how to play baseball.
And how to pick up chicks.
What if it's a girl?
I Iove girl on girl.
Get it out.
Just get it
all out.
Um, so Audrey,
when do you wanna
get started?
[moaning]
# I feel like something
Good is on the way #
Hey, how's my form?
[moaning]
[Audrey moaning]
[bedsprings creaking]
[clears throat]
What?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Are you bored?
Are you tired
of having sex with me?
Are you disgusted?
Can you get
out of me, please?
Ouch.
Why isn't this
working, Tommy?
Something's wrong.
Maybe it's 'cause
you don't really
wanna have a baby.
How can you say that?
I've been working my ass off
for nine months trying
to get you pregnant.
So it's a job?
I'm sorry, how much,
how much do I owe you?
Is it 40,
50 bucks?
Wow. 50 bucks?
That's it?
You know, you could
possibly get a back
alley H-J for that,
but not this, sister.
I'm sorry
I Iow balled you.
Well, you did.
That was a serious
Iow ball.
I'm not a crack whore.
You're the one who said
having sex with me
was Iike a job.
I never said that.
You said that.
You weren't
thinking it?
No.
It felt Iike it.
It's not what
I was thinking,
because I'II tell you,
sex with you is--
it's beautiful,
you know.
And it's wonderful.
And it's amazing.
Sex with you is Iike--
it's Iike, it's Iike--
(Tommy)
It's like
a full time job.
Maybe you
oughta get tested.
[Iaughing]
T ested? No.
I'm good.
Oh, you're good?
How do you know
you're good?
Excuse me, Wade.
I'm shooting good stuff.
I know this for a fact.
AII right.
I never told
anyone this,
and I swear to God
I'II kill everyone
if you say anything,
but when I decided to ask
Audrey to marry me, I couldn't
afford a decent ring, right?
So I told her
that I joined
a softball team.
You suck
at softball.
I hate softball.
I told her I joined
the softball team.
What I did instead,
I drove back to Pasadena
to a sperm bank. Right?
I donated sperm.
Every week for
20 weeks.
Eighty-five bucks
a pop they paid me.
At the sperm bank,
they don't take
bad sperm.
They test the shit
out of it.
Hey, dude,
85 bucks a pop?
If someone were
to rob that place
and sell the sperm
on the street, they
can make a fortune.
Jesus, Zig Zag.
Have you been
downtown Iately?
There's enough sperm
on the street to choke
Doogie Howser.
Hey, bring out
the pictures, man.
You brought the pictures
of the ex, right?
The pictures of Tanya?
Bring 'em out. I've seen
that shit.
She's my girlfriend now.
She's aware
you're showing
these pictures?
Yeah, probably.
Holy shit, dude.
Look at those nipples.
No offense, but I can tell
how T ommy might be able
to pull this girl.
But with Wade?
Did you say
"no offense"?
Is she
a chubby chaser?
That's more offense.
You keep offending.
I'm sorry,
but okay, offense.
Just tell us how
you got this chick.
You see, T ommy and I
are cut from the same
cloth, my friend.
Good cock,
bad cock.
Come on.
Honey, is he even
ejaculating properly?
Because I read on the Internet
that guys are faking it.
It's Iike a trend.
Mine does
not fake it.
Nobody Iikes
a gloater.
How do guys
fake it?
They keep a bike bottle
in the bed and then they
squirt it over your back.
I saw it
on YouTube.
Tommy is not faking it,
but something's wrong.
I'm kinda worried.
Are you using your
fertility calendar?
Yeah, I have
an app for that.
I Iove apps.
You know, 90% of the time,
it's the guy's fault.
It's definitely T ommy.
You need to get that
junk checked.
Hey, listen, guys,
can we keep this
between us?
T ommy's a Iittle
sensitive about all
this stuff.
I won't say anything.
Who am I
gonna tell?
Hey, Coach Stubbs.
How're you doing?
Tommy Macklin.
How the hell are you?
Not too bad.
How's that pretty
wife of yours?
Good, good.
How's the team
this year?
Honestly? We suck
about nine different
kinds of ass.
We're pulling
for you either way.
Thanks. We're pulling
for you, too.
For who? For me?
Well, I understand you have
a Iittle trouble knocking
up the Mrs.
You know what
works really well?
Hot peppers.
Eat as many
of 'em as you can.
Just make sure you
don't go munching on
her biscuit right away.
You'II kill
the poor woman.
[Iaughs]
You gotta keep
the sperm cool, yah?
You can't Iet the balls
get overheated.
That's why they hang
on the outside.
Like an air cooled
Volkswagen engine.
(man)
Shiitake mushroom,
ginger root, cucumber.
You mash it all up.
You allow it to boil
for three long hours,
and you gently Iower your
ball sack down in there,
and Iet them steep
for ten minutes.
BIue Mountain, Jamaican
remedy that.
What the hell are you
doing to me, Audrey?
Did you go and tell
the whole world?
No, I told three people.
I told Mona, Greta,
and Karen.
You didn't
tell three people.
You told three women.
What's that
supposed to mean?
Where's the ginger root?
Why do you think
there are no female
serial killers?
Because after they kill
the first guy, they gotta
go tell somebody.
That's actually
a good point.
[telephone ringing]
Hello?
Oh, hi there.
Uh, yeah.
Mm, well, I hadn't
heard that.
No. No, thank you.
Yeah.
I Iove you, too. Okay.
Who was that?
That was your mom.
She said I should try putting
Ben Gay on my scrotum to heat
up the sperm.
She just--
Do you think
that would work?
No.
Why does everybody
have advice for me?
Maybe, maybe
it's you.
Where are all the calls
of everybody telling you
to pour hot sauce
on your...vagina?
Okay. I made us appointments
with Dr. Vickerey to get us
both checked out.
He 's supposed to be
the best, so you gotta
get your sperm checked.
Honey, there's nothing
wrong with my sperm.
Really?
How do you
know that?
'Cause there's
a party down there!
Do you hear that?
[beating]
Seriously, this thing
smells Iike shit.
Can you
Iower 'em in?
I think you
just do one
at a time.
How am I gonna do
one at a time?
I don't have them.
I don't know.
(Tommy)
I'm telling you,
it is a waste of time.
Just do it.
Prove her wrong.
Show her you got
awesome sperms.
Dude, Audrey's
making you check
your sperm?
T ell her I said
to Iighten up.
[laughing]
No, I just have
trouble in groups.
It's hard to keep it going
when there's a bunch
of other people around.
You've never been
to an orgy?
No. Have you?
Nah. But I had sex
with two different chicks
in the same week. Bifecta!
I went to an orgy once.
Not with Audrey.
[Iaughs]
There's just gonna be a bunch
of other guys jerking off
in all the other rooms.
I don't feel Iike it.
But didn't
you do that
for a Iiving?
No, not for a Iiving.
But you got
paid to do it.
Okay, fine, but I knew
the guy who owned
the place,
and he Iet me come in
after hours when
it was empty.
Dude, get this.
My brother's a lawyer.
He represented this pervert
that works at one
of those clinics.
Sick bastard
hid cameras in
the smoke detectors.
Cops raided his house.
Found stacks of DVD's
of guys choking
their cobras.
[hisses]
[Iaughs]
What?
Wade, Iet's go.
Cool. Let's get
a hot dog.
I'II catch you guys
in a few. I'II follow.
Why do we hang out
with that douche bag?
Doesn't it bother you
that he used to go out
with Audrey?
I used to go out
with Tanya and you
still hang out with me.
Yeah, but at Ieast
you don't Iook Iike
a blond squirrel.
I do not.
You know what?
Don't worry about
this jerking off thing.
You're gonna be fine.
I have a Iittle
inspiration for you.
For old time's sake.
Oh, no, no.
I can't.
Yes, you can.
That's not right.
But those nipples
are world fucking class.
They are. They're Iike
Iittle tits on top
of big tits.
No, take them.
I can't.
Okay. Sure?
You're too good.
And by that I mean
you're an unbelievable
pussy.
Maybe so.
Well.
Excuse me.
I go whack my ding-dong
into a plastic dish
with a bunch
of dudes all
around.
Okay. Don't do it
while you're driving.
# I just need #
# Your love injection #
# I don't need
Your affection ##
Dr. Vickerey
is the best
in the business.
If he can't
impregnate your
wife, no one can.
You'II be
in room four today.
Pedro!
[foreign accent]
Sorry. I-I am sorry.
I was, uh,
just making
a phone call.
I'm sorry, Mr. Macklin.
(Pedro)
I wasn't
jerking off.
As you can see, we have
several different forms
of stimulation,
both homo
and hetero.
I'II take hetero.
Well, you have
20 minutes.
Relax and take
your time.
Hey, doctor,
where is the Iubrication?
Oh, no, we can't run
a risk of contamination.
You will just have to dry.
And you can't use
saliva either.
The human mouth
is quite filthy.
Okay.
I'II just be right
here if you need me.
Okay.
Right where?
Like right there?
Oh, well, I can
go away for a few
minutes if you prefer.
No, it's, it's--
Damn, it's hot.
Yeah. Let's
take a break.
[chuckles]
[giggles]
[Iaughing]
Gal, as pretty
as you are, we 're
still missing one thing.
Oh, yeah?
What's that?
You gotta meet
my friend, Big Jim.
Ooh. I sure hope
he 's handsome.
[Iaughs]
[neighs]
Nice to meet you, Jim.
You are big.
[loud volume]
[women moaning]
[horse neighs]
Mr. Macklin,
could you please
turn that down a bit?
It's a touch loud.
[horse neighs]
(Tommy)
I have to go home.
Babe, all you had
to do was jerk off
into a cup.
What's the big deal?
I mean, seriously.
H ow many times have you
masturbated in your Iife?
A hundred?
Uh, sure.
About 1 00, yeah.
I called and they said
you can do it at home.
You have to get
the sample there
within 30 minutes.
I've timed the drive
and it's 18 minutes,
so don't waste time.
I'm teaching
a class at 4:00,
so you have the whole
place to yourself to do
your Iittle jerky business.
Sort of takes the fun
out of it when you tell
me I have to do it.
I prefer sneaking around
when you're not here
and pretending
I don't do it.
Yeah, okay.
Hi. What's your name?
[foreign accent]
Roberto.
Could you help me
with my lotion?
My boyfriend usually
does it but we just
broke up.
Thanks.
Si, senora.
No hay problema.
[doorbell chimes]
Oh, could you do
the bottoms, too?
[doorbell chimes]
Shit, shit.
Hi, there.
How are you
on this blessed day?
Hi. Good.
Great. If you have
a moment, we'd Iike
to tell you
about our personal
savior, Jesus Christ.
You know, I don't know
if right now is the best
time to talk about Jesus.
It's not a good time
to talk about Jesus?
God's only son died
for his sins but it's
"not a good time. "
Well, I guess some people
just think they're more
important than Jesus.
I don't think I'm more
But unless he can
miracle a baby up
into my wife's vagina,
then I gotta take a pass.
Thank you
though so much.
Okay, bye.
[whispers]
AII right.
[exhales]
Jesus Christ.
Come on.
(Audrey)
Tommy? You're home?
Hi.
What's going on?
Oh, you kinda caught me
doing something naughty.
Really?
My college roommate,
Jenny, is here.
And we've been talking
about old times,
and Iaughing
about how we used
to share everything.
Say hi, Jenny.
Hi.
Anyway, since
we share everything,
Jenny was wondering
if we could share you.
Oh, okay.
He said yes.
Go ahead, Tommy.
Really?
Thanks, Audrey.
He Iikes it
from behind.
Oh, cool.
[sighs]
[whispers]
Thank you.
Oh, Jesus!
Do you have enough
time for me now, Tommy?
Why?
Dude.
[grunts]
[whispers]
No, sir.
No way.
[Tommy moaning]
(Tommy)
Oh, come on,
come on, come on.
[honking]
[Iaughs]
Ah!
Nice move, dickhead.
[Iaughs]
Hey!
[panting]
[shouts]
[cell phone ringing]
[grunts]
What's up, Tommy?
The pictures, the ones
of Tanya, I Ieft them
on the bathroom sink.
You gotta
go get 'em.
Yeah, dog.
I knew you'd
use 'em.
I used pictures
of cantaloupes.
Did you say
cantaloupes?
I got some
flat tires.
Some flat tires?
Are you high?
You've gotta go
to my house and
get those pictures.
Of the cantaloupes?
The pictures of Tanya!
You said you
didn't use them.
The back door's open.
The pictures are in
the bathroom.
Okay, I got
one more set to do.
Do this now!
AII right.
Chill out.
I'm on the move.
You chill out.
You fuck
chill out!
(Todd)
Audrey.
Audrey!
Hey.
My God, are you taking
gorgeous pills
or what?
Thanks, Todd.
Hi.
Oh, my gosh,
she's so cute.
She could've been
yours if you'd said
yes to me.
Just kidding.
[chuckles]
We're actually trying
for one of our own.
Right. Yeah.
I heard about that.
Tom's having
some trouble, huh?
Oh...no, no.
Audrey,
it's okay.
It's me.
Okay, well, yeah.
But it's gonna
be fine
'cause we're seeing this
really great doctor,
and it's all gonna be
taken care of.
Oh, I'm sure.
I'm sure.
Look, you never know
how these things are
gonna work out.
Hey, slow down, asshole!
I got kids!
Well, I'd better
get her back.
I'II see you
at Tommy's
birthday.
Good to see you.
I miss you.
Okay. Bye.
Huh.
[pop music]
Fucking wild
goose chase, Tommy.
Hello.
Goddammit.
[unzips pants]
(Audrey)
Tommy?
Oh, shit.
Shit, shit, shit.
[whispers]
Okay, okay,
okay, okay.
# I'm a man #
# God damn
God damn #
# God damn #
# I'm a man ##
Wade, did you get
the pictures?
I couldn't find them.
Where's my wife?
In the shower.
What's with
the pants?
I saw
those cantaloupes.
Hey! Help!
[closes faucet]
[Wade moaning outside]
(Audrey)
Hey. How
did it go?
Uh, great.
I had a few
flat tires, but--
A few flat tires?
Yeah.
Did you get it there
on time?
Of course I got it
there on time.
Thank you for doing
that for me.
I'm happy to.
I'm just glad
that tomorrow
we have proof
that my guys
are good to go.
Me, too.
Can I put
my penis in your
vagina right now?
Yes.
I'm feeling
really potent.
-Oh, are you?
-Yes, I am.
I'm afraid your
sperm count is too
Iow to conceive.
But that is
impossible.
I know some men
find it difficult
to hear that but--
Hold on.
How can we tell
that it's not--
I've already
examined Audrey.
Her tubes are clear.
Her hormone Ievels
are perfect.
And she has,
in my opinion,
two of the pinkest, plumpest,
and most beautiful ovaries
I have ever seen.
Thank you.
[giggles]
Are you hitting
on my wife?
Is that what he was
doing? It seemed
like it was.
Sorry about him.
Okay, so what exactly
is wrong with my sperm?
This is a slide
of a normal sample.
And this
is your sample.
They look drunk.
They do, don't they?
Where are
they going?
O-okay, so just
for argument's sake,
Iet's just say you're
right. How did they
get that way?
One possible cause
is testicular trauma.
Have you
ever experienced
anything Iike that?
[groans]
No, no.
Not that I
can recall.
Oh, well then,
I'm going to order you
a scrotal exploration.
A scrotal what now?
What is that? What?
Sometimes a tear will form
in the tunica albuginea
resulting in extrusion
of the testicular contents.
We simply insert a small
camera into the penis,
through the urethra--
This sounds amazing.
How about this, and I'm
just spitballing here,
why don't we take
my ball sack and
scrape it up
against a cheese grater?
Or maybe go out
to your car
and slam my dick
in the trunk.
Do you feel Iike
that might help?
Or--
I'm sorry.
I can assure you,
Mr. Macklin, this is
a mostly painless procedure.
Yeah, I'm kinda
getting caught up
on the word "mostly."
It's just--
It's a lot
to take in.
Okay, okay.
So, Iet's say
nothing comes
in this scrotal
exploration.
Then my suggestion
would be that you
find a donor.
But we 're not
there, yet, so.
I think you're right.
We're not there, yet.
We're not even close
to being there, yet.
I think you've
freaked out my
wife, sir.
And we're gonna be--
we're gonna be
Ieaving now.
Are you okay, honey?
Too far. Okay.
Oh, sorry.
What's up with Audrey
and Tommy? Why aren't
they talking to each other?
It's this whole baby thing.
I think it's time one
of us stepped up.
I think one of us
should offer our
sperm to our buddy.
That's the right
thing to do.
AII right.
As his best friend,
I will toss it in there.
[Iaughs]
No, seriously,
no offense.
Hey, hey, this isn't
genetic, okay?
It's called Iaziness.
My sperm is thin, fit.
Whatever. We all know
whose sperm he's
gonna choose.
What?
What, 'cause
I'm black?
Ah, 'cause we wouldn't want
Tommy to have a biracial
baby, right?
The kid might grow up
to be the president.
Or Halle Berry.
Okay, fine.
We settle it
this way, okay?
We all jack off
into a cup, right?
And we swirl it around,
and then may the best
man win.
May the best
man win what?
Uh, just--
The World Series?
Happy birthday, man.
Awesome party, T om.
What if I get drunk
and take all my
clothes off?
It might be
so-mething nice.
That is
good, right?
AII right.
Bye.
Hey, can I
get you a drink?
You have a drink.
Do you need
anything? Food or?
Hey, guys.
Happy birthday, Tommy.
(Audrey)
Hey, Julie.
Happy birthday, dude.
Thanks.
Todd and I have
been talking and we
heard about your problem.
And we would Iike
to offer our services.
For what?
What we'd Iike to do
is offer you our sperm.
What?
Tommy, we 've been blessed
with three smart, beautiful,
healthy children.
Honestly, when T odd first
brought it up, I was
unsure, too.
When Audrey said no
to Todd's proposal
all those years ago,
Seems Iike yesterday.
she gave me
a gift.
And this is my chance
to repay her.
So, what do you say?
What do I say?
Um--
Honey, Iet me.
Dude, I am sorry.
Huge misunderstanding.
We did not mean
to offend.
We were just
trying to be nice.
I just thought
if you're gonna
have a donor,
might as well be
someone you know.
That's all.
Right? That's it!
There's no reason
to be rude.
I'm not asking
to stick it in
Audrey directly.
I mean, unless
you're into that.
Some guys are.
I don't know.
I bet Julie would be
fine with it if you are.
Or not. Whatever.
Just Iet me know.
People Ioving
people, right, man?
Hi.
Hi, there.
I'm ready for
that drink now.
Okay.
You'd be there to monitor
the whole thing.
You know, honey,
I clipped an article
in recipes and things
about how overpopulation
is contributing to a general
decline in male sperm count.
Thanks, Mom.
You know what l
was thinking, sweetie?
Tommy's an only child.
Yeah, that might be
the problem right there.
His whole family
might have bad sperm.
But he 's lucky
he made it.
[Iaughs]
Hi!
How are you?
Good.
Thanks for getting it.
Oh, yeah, pork
fried rice there.
Wait a second.
I was--Oh, okay, I know
what I was gonna say.
Okay, you know
our Iittle problem,
our very personal
and private problem?
Well, it has nothing
to do with me.
I don't need to put
hemorrhoid cream on
my ball sack, Wanda.
I don't need
to eat hot peppers.
And I don't need to have
a camera shoved up my
wiener hole, darling.
My sperm is
perfectly fine.
Why? Because
I say that it is.
End of discussion.
Let's eat.
Food.
Who can deny
science Iike that?
Okay, you want science?
I'II give you some science.
You know that softball team
I played on? There was no
softball team. Softball.
I drove
to a sperm bank,
and I donated sperm.
I did.
Twenty times.
And each time,
they paid me
cold hard cash.
They wouldn't very well
pay me good money
for bad sperm, would they?
See how that works?
Now Iet's eat. God!
You did what?
What?
Tommy, what did
you just say?
I fell in Iove
with a gorgeous woman
who deserved
an amazingly
expensive engagement ring
that I couldn't afford.
And at 85 bucks a pop,
honey, it just seemed like--
T ommy, you
have children.
Twenty children
out there.
(Clark)
A t least.
Thanks, Dad.
You don't understand.
I gave 20 samples.
That doesn't necessarily--
It doesn't
necessarily mean that--
No, I am sure that
most of that sperm
is sitting right there
in that bank right now.
Tommy, you have children.
Oh, Tommy.
Come on, CIark, you understand
what I was trying to do,
don't you?
You get it, right?
I understand
completely, Tommy.
I understand that you
bought my daughter's
engagement ring
with beat-off money.
Got her a cum diamond.
(man)
Pasadena Andrology and
Cryobank. May I help you?
Hey, how're you doing?
I'm here 'cause I need
some sperm.
Okay. I could set
you up with one of our
sales reps and they--
You know what?
That's not gonna
be necessary.
I actually just need
some of my own sperm.
Your own sperm?
I think we can cut out
the middle man here.
No, no. I'm a donor.
I donated some sperm
about five years ago,
and I was hoping
to get that back.
I hope there's some Ieft.
What's your
name, buddy?
Thomas Macklin.
What do you know?
We have one batch Ieft.
Yeah!
That is great.
You know what?
You guys paid me
$85 per batch,
and I feel that
it's only right
for me to--
Oops, I'm sorry.
It Iooks Iike
we already sold it.
[stammers]
My bad.
To-to who?
To whom?
Seriously?
I don't know
if that's right.
You're right.
It's "to whom."
It's whom?
Ah, okay.
Anyway, we sold it
to this couple three
weeks ago.
We're performing
the insemination on
dee-dee-dee-dee,
Monday.
Whatever it is
they're paying you,
I'II give you double now.
This isn't eBay, sir.
We don't get into bidding
wars over sperm.
Okay.
You know what?
I don't wanna have
to do this 'cause
I'm not a dick,
but it just so happens that
I'm a good personal friend
of Kevin Baldrey, the manager.
Ooh. You hear
that, Lyle?
Is that right?
He's a personal friend
of Kevin Baldrey.
I'd Iike to speak
to him right now.
You and Kev aren't
so close, otherwise you'd
know he doesn't work here.
He got fired for
putting hidden cameras
in the masturbatories.
What? He--
He hid them in the smoke
detectors so he could
videotape guys jerking off,
and he put them
on the Internet.
Are you saying
that, uh--
There's only one
way to find out.
Looks Iike that website's
back up now that Kevy
fled to Amsterdam.
Oh, really?
Check that out.
Yep. There you are.
Macklin.
So much for the theory
that Ieft handers are
more intelligent.
Sir, back away
from the desk.
Can I see?
Do you always make
that face when
you climax?
You Iook Iike
a baby burp.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
[shouts]
Get him out
of here.
Jeez.
[groans]
Say hi to Kev for me.
# Happiness starts
With a smile #
# It's contagious #
# Catch it now ##
How are you doing?
I'm Iooking for a
Mrs. Leslie Jenkins.
I'm Leslie Jenkins.
I'm sorry.
I thought that--
It's alright.
It's a Southern name.
Do I know you?
No, you don't.
I'm Tommy Macklin.
I'm your sperm donor.
Oh. Oh!
Can I sit down
with you and your
wife for a minute?
Honey, come here!
You're gonna Iove this!
Jeffrey, this
is Tommy Macklin.
How're you doing?
Tommy Macklin?
Oh. Oh!
Do you have
a Iight beer?
Then we found out
my sperm was no good.
It caused a Iot
of stress in our
relationship
because obviously
we wanna have
a baby naturally.
We don't know anything
about naturally.
Not an option.
Yeah. But I
don't understand.
Between the two
of you guys,
you've got twice
as much sperm
as most couples.
Twice as much? More like
ten times as much with the
human fire hose here.
I've Iearned to take
my contacts out, if you
know what I mean.
It's Iike stepping on
a full tube of toothpaste
with you.
That's wild.
So, why don't you just use
some of Jeffrey's sperm?
[laughing]
No, no, no. No.
My family has
more alcoholics
than Celebrity Rehab.
PIus he's OCD and ADD.
Mildly. Anyway, we wouldn't
pass my DNA on to our worst
enemy's baby,
much Iess our own.
Okay. So then what
about yours, Leslie?
That was plan A.
But as it turns out, my sperm
is--what's the word they used?
Confused.
My sperm is
confused, too.
I cannot
believe that.
We saw the pictures.
It was crazy.
You know what?
I am confident we
can work something out.
I'm happy
to reimburse you
for any expenses,
and for the cost
of finding a
new donor.
Well, that's very
sweet, Tommy, but
to be honest
we're quite happy
with the donor we chose.
See, Leslie has a hang up
about having a baby that
Iooks Iike him. Shallow.
Guilty as charged.
When we found out
he couldn't produce,
we started Iooking
for a donor with
similar features.
And in the end we,
well, we landed on you.
What about $2,000?
That seems fair.
I just really need
that sperm back.
[exhales]
T ommy, I'm
really sorry,
but to find the right donor,
I don't think we could go
through that process again.
We've never had
more arguments.
I thought we were
gonna break up.
We almost did.
But we didn't,
did we?
No. Tommy, if there's
one thing I know,
it's this.
Love will find a way.
It worked for us
and it will work for you.
In fact, Leslie, why
don't you show T ommy
some of the runners up?
There's some guys
in there that Iook
a Iittle Iike you.
You could tell your wife
you got your sperm back.
Maybe slip a Iittle
something to the doctor.
She'd never know, so.
Anyway, I've gotta get
jogging before nightfall.
PIeasure meeting you.
Best of Iuck.
I'II get
the folder for you.
I can get you
your sperm back.
Uh, but I thought
we just said that--
Come inside.
Goddammit, Tommy. I feel
horrible about this.
I really do.
Jeffrey said---
Forget Jeffrey.
I wear the pants
in this relationship.
And I would Iike
to see you have
your family.
Really?
Yes. I'm sure
we can reach some kind
of mutual agreement.
It's simple, isn't it?
You want your sperm back,
and I want you.
Jeffrey always says
I'm a narcissist.
That's probably why
I'm so attracted to you.
It'd be Iike having
sex with myself.
Having sex?
I want to be
inside you, Tommy.
What?
I want to enter you.
Are you-are you
not getting this?
I--
Have you ever had
anal sex, Tommy?
I can't say
that I have.
It's Iike getting
your prostate checked.
Have you done that?
I haven't.
You should. Detection
equals prevention.
Okay, okay.
Come on, Tom.
We're guys here.
Let's do this.
Don't be so homophobic.
I'm not homophobic.
You're afraid to have sex
with another man.
It doesn't get more
homophobic than that.
I don't think you're
using that word right.
AII right.
I'II tell you
what I'II do.
You enter me.
What the hell?
I'm feeling generous.
It's my final offer, Tom.
What do you say?
[lawn mower
engine running]
I say fuck him.
It's just a hole.
Stick it in.
Can we be
serious, please?
Or Iet him fuck you.
Who gives a shit?
Fuck or be fucked.
CIose your eyes,
stick it in, and
think of baseball.
That'II make it
Iast longer.
What do you got to Iose?
I can think
of a few things, Wade!
Shit, I would do it.
But everybody knows
that gay guys
don't Iike fat people.
They're "fatophobic."
"PIumpophobic."
"PIumpophobia" or whatever.
Have you ever seen a
gay fat guy before?
No, they don't exist.
They're Iike unicorns.
Have you ever seen
a fat unicorn before?
Me either.
Help me!
When they said
you couldn't have
your sperm back,
they robbed you
of your future.
Right?
And you have every
right to steal it back.
Are you talking
about robbing
a sperm bank?
"A" double right,
you bet I am.
No, that's crazy.
Crazy?
Or brilliant?
Crazy.
Brilliantly crazy.
No, just crazy.
And brilliant.
Don't think
about yourself.
Think about your
unborn child.
If you don't do
something soon,
the Iast good seed
you have on Earth
is gonna be implanted
deep inside some surrogate.
And good Iuck
getting it back then.
Fuck or be fucked, Tommy.
Fuck or be
fucked, Tommy.
No, wait a second.
How are we gonna rob
a sperm bank?
I've been thinking
about this.
I know just the guy
who can help us.
Walk with me.
How do you know
this guy again?
How do we
know this guy?
Shut up, Zig Zag.
Keep your mouth shut.
This whole thing
was my idea in
the first place.
What?
Your idea?
You think you can come up
with a crazily brilliant
idea Iike this?
Okay. The guys
in the meat department
introduce me to him.
Apparently he's
the real deal.
Former bag man
for the Indian mafia.
What does
that mean?
That's racist.
They Iike to be called
Native-Americans.
No, he's Indian.
Dot head Indian,
not feather Indian.
That's even
more racist.
You're a racist.
Bag man means you fuck
with him, you end up
with a bag on your hip.
- Bag on your hip? What
the fuck does that mean?
- You shit in a bag.
And then they tell me
that they can't even
sell me back my own sperm.
And then they kick me out.
Yeah, and they pepper
sprayed me in the face.
Pushed me into the bushes.
I have prickers everywhere.
I mean, if I don't
get my sperm back, man,
my marriage is over.
You know, these bastards
are assholes,
and they're stealing
my future,
and they're taking away
my constitutional right
to do whatever I want
with my own sperm.
You know?
Do you see
what I'm saying?
Yes, I do.
You're saying you bought
your wife's engagement ring
with beat-off money.
[Iaughs]
Classic, right?
I Iike you.
You're a married man.
I always want
to be a married man.
But I never found Iove.
What can you do?
I will help you.
Hey, all right.
Thank you, Ron Jon.
See?
Wow, thanks, man.
Cost is 5000.
5000? I really had
no idea.
Could you excuse us.
Give us a sec.
What are you doing?
You're blowing the deal.
$5000 to rob
a sperm bank?
How much do you
think it costs?
-I don't know.
-Exactly.
Are you gonna
put a price tag
on your family?
Shit.
You must have
a rich uncle
around somewhere.
I've got $1 1,000 saved up
in the house fund.
I could possibly borrow
five and pay it back
before Audrey found out.
Now you're talking sense.
This is it.
Now be cool.
So, we were
just chatting.
And we feel Iike,
yeah, sure,
yeah, good.
What about $3000?
Mr. Macklin,
make no mistake.
We are committing
a felony here.
There is grave
risk involved.
Do you understand me?
Yeah, 5000 then.
5000 seems good.
Very nice!
Very, very, very nice!
-Thank you for your time.
-Looks Iike we have a deal.
Dude, were you seriously
in the Indian mafia?
What the fuck, man?
I never said anything.
Everybody has to know
every fucking thing.
Okay, fine.
Okay, Mr. Nosy.
If you must know,
back in Mumbai,
I was the best
second story man
in the business.
What business?
The stealing
shit business, okay?
-Okay.
-What is your name?
Zig Zag.
What is so funny, Zig Zag?
I was just
kinda Iaughing
at what the whole ""Indian"
organized crime thing
was all about.
What? You don't think
Indian crime can be
organized?
Indians are
very organized.
No, I'm sure. I just had
this, Iike, idea in my head
about all these Indian mob
dudes, sitting around,
Iike being all non-violent
with each other.
'Cause you think about,
Iike, Gandhi, right?
I mean, he was, Iike...
Should I show you
how nonviolent I can be?
No!
You think Indians
can only drive a cab
and fix your computer?
Well, Iet me
tell you something.
I did drive a cab!
And I can fix
your computer,
but I can also
cut your throat!
Shall I show you,
Mr. Zig Zag?
No, I feel Iike
I got it.
Yeah, I feel Iike
I understand.
Yeah, I was just
pretty baked.
Cool off, man, okay?
Cool off.
Everybody cool off.
[Wade]
Hey, it's cool.
Let us drink.
[silent mouthing of words]
Let us drink
to a successful mission.
What is this?
Just drink it, god damn it.
Everybody, "What is it?
"What is it?
What is it? "
Okay, come on!
To success!
[gagging, spitting]
I will get you
your sperm back,
Mr. Macklin.
That much,
I guarantee.
[Mona]
So you just must be
totally pissed.
Yeah, I was
furious at first.
I mean, he's got
kids out there.
But then I thought,
why not just go
down there
and see if they have
any of his good sperm
Ieft for us to use.
And?
It was five years ago.
They told him they'd Iook,
but it didn't Iook good.
Billy, no!
If you keep
drowning James,
I swear to God,
I gonna come over there
and drown you right back!
It's not James.
Well, who can tell,
you Iittle sewer rat?
AII right, that's it.
Get over here!
Oh, AIIison,
she's so adorable.
What's her name?
Well, we wanted
to name her
something Chinese,
but also, you know,
American, so we
went with Jackie Chan.
Jackie Chan
Finnerman. Nice.
Wait...
Stop it!
C'mon, stop it!
God, she's so quiet.
Yeah, she's really quiet.
She never cries.
Yeah, I've heard that
about those babies.
Why does everybody
know so much
about Asian babies?
Did I miss a class
or something?
They're just Iike
American babies.
Only better.
I heard
they're also
really musical.
You should totally
get her a piano,
Iike, right now.
Well, I already
got her a violin.
She doesn't even
have fingers yet.
So, just out of curiosity,
how much did it cost
to adopt her?
About $10,000
when you add it all up.
Did you want
to hold her?
Oh, I'd Iove to.
Hi, Jackie Chan.
Hi.
Oh, princess.
Yeah. Hi.
There he is,
our five-star general.
Okay.
I have done
a complete stakeout
of the target.
Nothing to it.
Piece of cake.
-Oh, that's great.
-Awesome.
Each person will have
a special job.
You. Because you are
small Iike a woman,
you will be wheel man.
Drive only.
No talk.
A woman.
You.
if shit go down,
and all fuck
break Ioose...
you are
trigger man.
I'm not gonna
shoot this gun, so...
Let me tell
you something.
I have two strikes
against me.
One more and I go
to prison for Iife.
If we are caught,
you must shoot me.
Do you understand?
I'm not gonna
shoot you, Mr. Jon.
Christ, I'II shoot him.
Sorry.
So here is the plan.
This is
the sperm bank.
This is the barber shop
right next door.
Wait a minute.
Just, sorry,
but wouldn't it
make more sense
if we made the comb
the barber shop
and the cream
the sperm bank?
I'm just saying.
Yeah, I'm with Tom
on this one.
Okay, fine, fine.
This is the barber shop,
and this is the sperm bank.
And this is the Iiquor store
across the street.
What?
Wouldn't it be better
if Zig Zag's beer
was the Iiqour store...
and this ketchup bottle
was something else?
Liquor store, barber shop,
sperm bank. Any questions?
[belches Ioudly]
-Yeah.
-Yeah, that's good, yeah.
Okay, you and wheel man
will arrive early,
dressed as plumber.
You're gonna have your name
on the plumbing truck?
Good point.
You two will enter
barber shop and go
to the employee
rest room.
You will open
skylight.
While you plant
special tools
I need for the job.
Soon it will be dark
and time for me
to take over.
From the roof
of the liquor store,
I will slide over
power lines, like Ninja,
I will drop in
through the skylight,
take the jackhammer
and blast my way
into the sperm bank.
Meanwhile, rest of team
will be outside,
providing noise cover
for jackhammer.
[Ioud rock music]
I don' t
play guitar.
That's true.
But you do play
the accordion, right?
When I was nine.
[whispers]
Shut up, Wade.
Once inside sperm bank,
I will use special
lock picking kit
to open the vault.
With special lock
picking kit, I can
open any lock, anytime.
And, just like that...
you are a daddy.
Did I tell you
this guy was the best?
Sorry, I just
have one question.
If you can open
any Iock, anytime,
then why not skip
the Ninja routine,
the jackhammer
and the 80s hair band,
and just pick
the Iock on the door
to the sperm bank?
Yeah, if you just
use the Iock picking kit,
you can pick the Iock
on the door
to the sperm bank.
I Iike this guy.
He is a good one
to have on the team.
Great new plan.
I Iike it.
Okay. I would call
this plan
Operation Desert Sperm.
Hey, wow.
-Guess what?
-Just really quick,
I wanna say something.
I know I have screwed
some things up Iately.
But don't worry,
because...
I am on the case.
Guess what?
You're pregnant?
[gasps]
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, Tommy, Tommy.
I want to adopt.
Adopt?
I went by the adoption
agency and got
some information.
It's the perfect
solution for us.
Yeah, but the sperm bank
might still have...
Tommy, you said they
didn't think they
had any.
They said they're
checking the warehouse.
I held AIIison's
baby today.
And I just Iooked
into those big,
beautiful eyes.
Oh, my gosh, Tommy.
I just fell in Iove.
Look it doesn't matter
how we get a baby.
Let's just
start a family.
AIIison's baby
is Chinese, right?
Oh, she's so delicious.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm half Chinese!
Thank you.
I know that, I just...
But out of curiosity,
do they have any
American kids there?
Or even, Iike half Chinese
half American kids?
Babe, American babies
are ridiculously expensive
and impossible to get.
There used to be
tons of Russian babies,
but one of them
went a Iittle crazy,
so that was that.
India won't Iet
their babies out.
We could go Ethiopian?
What do they have,
Iike a menu?
So I did
some quick research.
Of course you did.
And the Chinese babies
are the easiest ones to get.
Do you have some kind
of Chinese issue
I should know about?
You Iove Chinese food!
Yeah, but I'm not
gonna eat the baby.
You better not.
You know what? Let me just
take a piss, really quick.
Hold on, two seconds.
[Tommy sighs heavily]
I guess the Great Wall
is pretty sweet.
Oh, thank you!
I mean, you're
sure about this?
I've never been more sure
about anything
in my entire Iife.
Okay, then.
You Iook disappointed.
I'm not disappointed.
This is not exactly
how I imagined
it would work out,
but maybe
you're right.
Let's explore it.
How does it even work?
Well, when you add it all up,
it's about $10,000.
But I figure we can
just borrow it
from the house fund, right?
Yes, yes we can.
I Iove you, Tommy.
I Iove you, honey.
It's off.
-What's off?
-The robbery,
it's off.
Shut the fuck up.
No, seriously man.
We've gotta cancel it.
But I already bought
the ski masks.
It's too risky.
I can't get caught.
What about the baby?
Audrey decided we're
gonna adopt a Chinese baby.
Audrey decided you're
getting a Chinese baby.
When did you decide
to give up on America?
She decided.
We decided.
She just decided first
and then I decided Iater.
I'm tired of these Chinese.
They're making everything.
Shirts, the watch
and the pants.
Now they're gonna make
our babies?
I'm sick of this
outsourcing shit.
Wait a second.
We were gonna outsource
our robbery to this Indian.
Besides, this way we're
helping orphans and shit.
Giving them
a second chance.
Oh, we already gave them
Remember Pearl Harbor?
Never forget, man.
Fine, get your Chinese baby.
I'm over it.
You know what?
I hear they're
pretty damn smart.
Yeah, and fucking
expensive.
We gotta get my $5000
back from your Mr. Ron Jon.
Okay, well I don't think
Mr. Ron Jon's an Indian giver.
No shit. I am
the Indian giver.
How could you
be the Indian giver?
I'm not having
this conversation.
Okay, Iisten.
Stick to the plan.
PIay to his sympathies.
Make him feel guilty,
all right?
[knocks]
What the hell?
You're a day early.
Hey, we need to talk.
Okay, come in.
Getting in shape
for the big job.
[Ioud Indian pop music]
Listen, Mr. Jon,
I have some bad news.
I have to cancel the job.
Okay, fine.
Job is canceled.
Just Iike that?
Just Iike that.
C'mon. We can drink
to canceled job. Come.
Okay, Iet's do this.
The good stuff,
too, I see.
Hey, yes.
Nothing but the best
for my friends. C'mon now.
To canceled job.
[Iaughs]
Indians Iove Scotch.
And cocaine!
[Iaughs and coughs]
She don't Iie.
Well, heck if I do.
That's a great TV!
Oh, you Iike it, huh?
Voice activated.
Check it out.
Shut the fuck up!
[music stops,
Ron Jon Iaughs]
I gotta get me
one of those.
Hey, those weights
Iook pretty new, too.
Listen, how much
of that $5000
have you spent?
5000?
Yeah, I gave
you $5000.
I guess I spent $5000.
You what?
No, no! Man...
The reason I had
to cancel the job
is because...
I have an emergency,
and I need that
money back.
Well, what is the emergency?
Well...
it's my mother.
She's ill,
-and if she doesn't
get a new...
-Kidney...
...transplant,
then she'II die.
That is very, very sad.
My own mother,
she died of Iiver failure.
I cannot promise
anything, but I will
see what I can do.
[kiss]
AII right.
Yes, Mom, we're
really excited.
Of course she'II
speak English.
We'II teach her.
No, we haven't come up
with names yet. Hold on.
Mom, I gotta go.
Audrey, I'm home.
I was just down
at the bank, just now,
and it's weird,
because they...
said apparently
there's a mistake
that was made,
but not to worry,
because they could
clear it up in a couple days.
What... is going on?
Audrey, baby...
What happened?
What's going on right now?
Would you stop
for a second?
We're gonna have
enough money
for the Chinese baby.
[gasps]
You can take
your Chinese baby
and shove it up your ass.
They're not mine.
Okay, tell me.
Then whose are they?
-They're Wade's.
-Okay.
Aud. Audrey...
[heels walking away]
Hey, wait!
Audrey, seriously, stop.
Hey, Audrey,
You've gotta be
kidding me. PIease, stop.
Stop, please!
-Hold on.
-Do you Iove her, Tommy?
Of course not.
I Iove you.
Then why were you
jerking off to naked
pictures of her?
I was jerking off
to naked pictures
of cantaloupes.
I saw her
cantaloupes, Tommy.
And I'm sorry
that my cantaloupes
aren't good enough for you.
If only you found
me attractive,
you could have jerked off
to naked pictures of me.
Audrey, seriously,
they are Wade's pictures.
Then how the hell
did they end up
in our bathroom?
Well...
You know what?
BIame your friends.
Who cares?
You're not man enough
to knock me up, anyway.
I can't believe
you broke up with Tanya.
I got tired of her.
A man cannot Iive
by nipples alone.
Hey, Wade,
you asshole!
I told you to get
the pictures out of my...
[groans]
She found the pictures.
Oh...
You know, she's right.
I got one job
to do as a man,
and I can't even do that.
It's just
a little crisis
of confidence.
It happens to everyone.
Maybe we should
buy him a hooker.
What's he gonna do
with a hooker?
Oh, that's right.
He can't get it up.
Zig Zag, I can get
it up, dude.
He can get it up.
He just can't come.
I can come!
Yeah, sure. He can come.
But nothing comes out.
Just puffs of air.
[all Iaugh]
Would you guys shut up?
If I Iose Audrey,
I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
C'mon, don't talk
Iike that.
She Ioves you
and you Iove her.
And she knows
that you'II do
anything for her.
But I haven't done
everything, have I?
There's only one thing
Ieft I could do
to make this right.
And I'm gonna do it.
You're gonna have sex
with that gay guy?
What?
No, I'm gonna go back
to Pasadena,
and rob that bank.
Yeah, you are!
Whoa, rob a bank?
Here's the deal.
On Monday, the Iast
batch of sperm
that I have Ieft
in the world
will be gone forever.
But tomorrow night,
before that happens,
we're gonna go in there,
and steal that shit back.
We're pulling a bank job,
a sperm bank job.
What do you guys say?
Who's with me?
I'm with you, Tomahawk!
-Zig Zag.
-Aces high!
Darrell? We could use
some muscle on this job.
Right, well, I'm just
gonna run home real quick
and just grab
a few things,
a few things...
for this mission.
Little criminal stuff
for the mission.
And then I'II meet you guys
at the designated place,
at the designated time.
Okay.
[car starts, squeals out]
Okay, Darrell's out.
He said designated spot,
designated time.
Zig Zag, we don't have
a designated spot,
or a designated time.
Oh.
At Ieast we don't
have to cut him in
on the take, right?
That's good.
Ron Jon!
It's Wayne.
How can he hear you
over that stupid TV?
Shut the fuck up!
[silence]
-What?
-Hi.
So it's back on,
and we gotta go tonight.
Come in.
I can't do tonight,
but Wednesday might work.
PIease, Mr. Jon.
I paid you a Iot
of money to do this job.
Hey, you canceled
the job, remember?
Yeah, but you never
gave me back
my money.
Wait.
What is this?
You got my money in here?
Open it.
What the--what is this?
What do you mean
what the fuck?
It's a kidney.
You say your mother
needs a kidney.
How about a Iittle
"Thank you, Mr. Ron Jon."
Whose kidney is that?
Mr. Jon...
I don't know
how to tell you this,
but my mother's
perfectly healthy.
I made that shit up
to get my money back.
I see.
I feel very sorry.
I feel very strange
about this.
Whose is this?
What man is out there
with Iess body?
Listen to me,
Mr. Jon, okay?
PIease.
I'm desperate, okay?
PIease help me.
I can't Iose my wife.
You should have thought
of that before you
Iied to me.
What if I paid you
a shitload more money?
5000 dollars.
Goddammit, Iook.
I got $4000
right there, in cash,
in this envelope right here.
Okay, okay.
AII right, okay.
I have got $40. $40.
Zig Zag.
[Zig Zag mutters]
What do we have here?
One, two, three...
[normal voice]
I have $8.
We've got $4048, okay?
So what do you say?
C'mon.
I'm not sure
if I can trust my team..
Okay, you know what?
Let's sweeten the deal
a Iittle bit.
Okay? What do you
say to that?
You know my weakness.
Let's do it!
[sighs heavily]
Let's do it.
She's your ex-girlfriend?
Yep.
[Ron Jon]
And your ex-girlfriend...
And what
about you, Ziplock?
I practice abstinence.
Good. I would
not Iike a woman
you have touched.
When do I get her?
You get her. What?
Do you think she
would Iike me?
Does she Iike beards?
Oh, shit.
Did you think that--
Tomorrow, noon.
We will drop her off.
Noon is good for me.
Noon can work.
[door knob turning,
door opening]
Tommy?
Tommy, I'm home!
[voicemail]
First message.
[Tommy]
Hey, honey. I just wanna
tell you that I've got it
all figured out.
I am gonna get
my sperm back
and we are gonna
have our family, okay?
I gotta go, but I will
see you tonight.
[Wade]
Wait for me! Let's go
steal that jizz!
Wade, shut up!
Oh, my God.
[crickets chirping]
Where the fuck
is Ron Jon, man?
[Wade]
Will you stop asking that?
Something's not right.
Jesus, Zig Zag.
Stop smoking pot.
It's making you paranoid
you douche.
Dude, it's for my glaucoma.
Do you really
have glaucoma?
Early stages.
Hey, dude.
-Where have you been?
-Seriously, dude.
I was casing the joint.
Good news...
There is no guard on duty,
and there is no alarm.
It's almost as if
they don't expect
someone to break in
and steal their
own sperm back.
[Ron Jon Iaughs]
I have to tell you,
this is the craziest
fucking job I've
ever been on.
AIthough there was
one time in India,
when they hired me
to steal a monkey
back from a barber.
But what they
neglected to tell me
was how horny
this particular monkey was.
Okay, back to job.
We go in,
we steal the semen,
we get out.
Ten minutes, synchronized.
Okay, Iet's--
Iet's do this.
If the cops come,
honk three times,
Iike this.
[horn honking]
What the fuck, dude?
Why did you do that?
That is signal
to abort mission.
Ow, fuck, man!
If you Ieave without us,
I will find you.,
and I will kill you.
Let's roll.
[Tommy]
I don't know, Wade.
I got a bad feeling
about this guy.
Well, that's just because
he's a criminal.
That's how you're
supposed to feel.
[Ron Jon]
Shit.
Shit!
What's wrong?
I can't remember
the exact combination.
To the Iock
picking kit?
Yes, to the Iock
picking kit, okay?
Did you write it
down somewhere?
If I wrote it down,
I'd have the fucking
thing open.
Maybe it's
your birthday.
It's not my birthday.
-Phone number.
-Don't make fun of me.
-Street address?
-What the fuck
does that mean?
Oh, oh!
Mother's birthday.
Could be.
[Ron Jon yells]
Don't worry,
I have an idea.
[glass breaking]
-Bag man for the India mafia?
-That's what I was told.
[Ron Jon]
Okay, where do they
keep the sperm?
How the hell
should I know?
Oh, shit!
I just remembered
the combination!
Awesome. Great.
We gotta split up
so we can cover
more ground.
Hello, Iady.
Bingo.
[Zig Zag moaning]
[whispers]
Okay. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Jackpot.
Macklin, Macklin...
Yeah, yeah.
Whoa, whoa!
[crash]
[screams]
Bingo.
[Iaughs]
[screams]
What is this?
[groans]
Okay, okay.
Wade! Ron Jon!
I got my sperm.
What are you doing?
I am very Ionely.
Never married.
We gotta get out of here.
No, no, no, no.
Where is it?
What?
Don't move.
Okay?
No! No!
Don't move!
[screams]
Oh, shit. Fuck. Cops.
[horn honking]
Ron Jon, that's the signal.
Let's go!
[gags]
Okay.
Shit!
[Squealing tires]
[screams]
Wade, are you okay?
Once I'm soapy.
-I need some mouthwash.
-I got my sperm.
Awesome.
Where the hell
is Zig Zag?
Son of a bitch!
Don't worry.
I will kill
that motherfucker.
Cops, cops, cops!
Go, go!
Holy shit, holy shit,
holy shit.
We gotta get the hell
out of here.
Yeah, we gotta go
steal a car.
Wait, wait, wait.
You cannot take the risk.
You have to make a baby.
That is your job.
I will go get us a car.
That's grand
theft auto.
Grand theft auto.
That is how I started.
Life of crime.
Very nice.
Can I have the addresses
of all the sperm banks
in Pasadena, please?
No, this isn't
a crank call.
Ew, get your mind
out of the gutter.
You're gonna have
to turn up here.
-Which way?
-That way.
Really?
What is that?
Which way?
That way!
Wade, where is he?
My sperm's
gonna thaw out.
Shh!
What is that?
What the hell?
-Oh, my God.
-Come on! Let's go!
Get in!
[rap music on radio]
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
[squealing tires]
What the fuck?
PIease don't hurt us!
Ron Jon, what are
these people doing here?
This was the only car
with the key in it.
Well, pull it over!
Pull it over right now.
I can't pull over.
They've already seen us.
-PIease don't kill us!
-We haven't seen anything.
Nobody's killing
anybody, okay?
T echnically, we really
should kill them.
No! No!
Ron Jon!
Okay, fine. I pull over.
Give me a minute.
-Dude, your sperm's melting.
-Oh, shit.
Ron Jon!
Man, I need some ice
back here.
This sperm is starting
to heat up.
Ron Jon, pull over.
Ron Jon, get me some ice.
Is there anything else
I can do for you, sir?
Okay, one second.
Here you go!
[woman screams]
It's okay.
Chill out, sperm!
[siren]
Oh, shit!
We are having company!
Oh, fuck!
Hold on people!
I'm going to lose him!
[squealing tires, screams]
-You smell really great.
-Thank you.
False alarm!
Everything's cool.
-Just an ambulance.
-An ambulance?
Are you crazy?
Hey, man.
You should be happy.
We're home free.
We made it.
Congratulations.
You're going
to be a daddy!
I am, aren't I?
Thank you, Ron Jon.
We did it, Macklin!
[Ron Jon indistinct]
Let us have
some Iiquid celebrate!
[pulls cork off
with teeth]
[screams]
Ron Jon!
[everyone screaming]
I think I just
had a miscarriage.
Ow, fuck.
What the fuck, man?
Are you okay?
[bottle clinks
on pavement]
Hey, I was just coming
to get you, man.
Are you okay?
-I will kill you!
-Oh, fuckin' hey, dude.
Fuckin' hey, man!
I was coming back.
[sirens]
Freeze!
Get on the ground.
Get on the ground!
You're under arrest
for grand theft auto.
You, too, asshole!
Get down!
Tommy, fuck
or be fucked, bro.
Drop the bucket
and get down.
Fuck or be fucked!
Yeah!
You'II never catch him!
Stop!
SIow down!
[sirens]
I need backup.
He's still running.
Oh, it's close. It's close.
It's right around here.
What the fuck?
Oh, Jesus.
I don't even know
those guys. C'mon!
-Wade?
-Hey Audrey, what's up?
Where's Tommy?
Ma'am, please keep moving.
He's got the sperm.
He went that way!
AII right, buddy.
Come on out.
I see you.
No place to go.
-Uh, no.
-Yeah.
-No.
-No!
-You're coming out now.
Don't I get some, uh...
I got some demands.
Yeah, I got
a Iist of demands.
Okay.
What do you want?
I need a bucket
of ice.
That's it.
A bucket of ice.
How about a bucket
of chicken instead?
Hey, man. I need
that ice now.
Do you mind my asking
what you need the ice for?
Be--because I have
to keep my sperm cold.
What was that?
Because I have
to keep my sperm cold!
[Iaughs cynically]
Your sperm
is too hot, is it?
There was a break in
at the sperm bank
down the street.
God, this country just keeps
getting weirder and weirder.
-Call psychiatric.
-AII right.
Son? Is that stolen sperm
you've got there?
No, it's my sperm!
AII right?
If it's sperm
he's Iooking for,
there's gonna be plenty
where he's headed.
Am I right?
[cops Iaugh]
Hey, Captain.
This is his wife.
Can I talk to him?
I can get him
to come out.
Yeah, well you got
two minutes.
Then we're gonna
take him the hard way.
Get the battering ram.
Bring it in.
Tommy!
-Hi.
I got my sperm.
I know.
It's been a weird
couple days,
hasn't it?
This is the coolest thing
a guy has ever done
for a girl.
Look, I'm sorry I got mad
at you about the pictures
of Tanya.
I know you never would have
jerked off to them.
No, I'm sorry I bought
your ring with beat
off money.
And I jerked off
to that stupid picture
of those cantaloupes.
No, I saw the cantaloupes.
They were kinda hot.
Audrey, I'm sorry
my sperm stopped working.
Don't worry about it.
So what do we do
with this stuff?
Just shove it on up there?
-Yeah, I think so.
-Okay.
They're gonna want
to take this away.
You know that, right?
I know.
And then they're gonna
put me in in jail.
[police captain]
Bring it over here!
Okay, take the door!
-Ready?
-Ready.
On three, two, one.
Hand over the jizz
and get on the ground.
C'mon man.
I really need this stuff.
Get down now!
Tommy.
[high-pitched sound]
Look at my dick!
Look at my penis!
What the...
Operation Desert Sperm!
Where's the sperm?
I don't know.
-Did you get it?
-No, I missed it!
-What?
-Let's go!
Hands behind your back.
I'II meet you back
at the station, okay?
Okay.
-Hey.
-What?
You're always with me.
AII right.
Let's go!
-Breathe!
-Okay.
You're doing great!
-Okay, we're almost there.
-You're doing great!
One big push.
We're almost there.
[baby crying]
-You got the clamp?
-Yes.
He's beautiful.
-My Iittle baby.
-Very nice. Very beautiful.
Very beautiful.
Hello, Iittle fellow.
Hello.
Yeah?
What?
Okay, yeah, yeah.
No, no, I'II tell the guys.
Okay. Be good.
Talk to you soon.
Everybody?
Got some news.
Ron Jon's a daddy!
[advanced piano music]
Hey, Mama?
What's going on in here?
That is to the end
of breastfeeding.
-Hi.
You're pretty.
And how's my Iittle mookie?
How are you doing?
He's beautiful
and wonderful
and farty.
Just Iike his Daddy!
Daddy's a Iittle farty.
Daddy gets that way, too.
And there's my two
other Iittle munchkins.
How are you kids
doing over there?
Don't we make
beautiful babies together?
I need butt cream.
Okay, Mama's gonna
go get some butt cream.
Hey, dude. Grab
the triplets.
It's time.
He's gonna go for you.
-He's ready.
-My Iittle guy.
Hey, Iittle man!
There's my big guy!
Hi!
AII right, here we go.
I got $12 on Emmett!
Okay, put him down.
Sammy's my boy.
He's about to clean
some clocks.
That's him
in the yellow, right?
No, that's Annie
in the yellow.
Is that Audrey's breastmilk?
Nothing but the best
for these horses.
AII right, now.
It's the 15-yard dash.
The first baby that gets
to the bottle wins.
You in on this action?
Absolutely.
C'mon. These babies are hot.
Let's go, Iet's go!
What's going on here?
Uh, we're racing
the babies.
Huh.
-I got fifty on...
-Annie?
Yeah.
Okay, Iet's make
some money.
On your mark, get set,
go babies, go!
[cheering]
# I came to L.A.
to make rock 'n' roll #
# Along the way, I had
to sell my soul #
# I made some good friends
that make me say #
# I really wanna be in LA #
# I took the ten
to get to Beverly #
# Laid some rock
to tape roll at 1 1AD #
# Alain and Natasha
always make me say #
# I really wannabe in L.A. #
# I take the city
in the dead of night #
# I'm burning gas
until I feel all right #
# My Sunset honeys
always make me say #
# I really wannabe in LA #
# I came to L.A.
to make rock 'n roll #
# Along the way,
I had to sell my soul #
# I made some good friends
that make me say #
# I really wannabe in LA #
# Well, nothing could improve
my situation #
# 'Cause cigarettes
taste better paired
with coffee and frustration #
# And I always need
a reason to complain #
# Ain 't it good
to feel the pain #
# I live this way
and get away with it #
# I'm my own boss
but I don 't pay me shit #
# And there 's angels
fighting demons all the time #
# Growing in the dark
of my mind #
#And you are the best thing
and the worst for me #
# I'm blessed and cursed #
# Together we will stay
with hell on earth to pay #
# And until the day I die
I'm in heaven by your side #
# by your side #
# Well nothing in this world
can bring me down #
# Short of spending one
more nightmare in this
godforsaken town #
# And you're the only one
who sets me free #
# The only one
who bothers me #
# And the wheels are spinning
faster every day #
# And if I was touching ground
I bet that I could get away #
# From all the moons and stars
and space you're giving me #
# I could start a galaxy #
# And you will tour
the universe with me #
# We 're blessed and cursed #
# Together we will stay
We just can 't get away #
# And until the day I die
I'm in heaven by your side #