# Among the trees
and by the river #
# Lying there, my darling shivers #
# In her sleep
she dreams of winter #
# Whiter than her breast #
# I feel her heart
move through her chest #
# Warm and steady
as she rests #
# Hear water ebbing
with her breath #
# Lulling me to sleep #
# Ohh-ohh-ohh #
# And here in the sky #
# Lights flash before our eyes #
# And I feel your warm hand #
# Slipping into mine #
# And we lay... #
You okay?
# Will I come around? #
# Do I know
what you are feeling now? #
# This morning
we drove out of town #
# Into the hills
and looking down #
# Saw the ocean all around #
# As far as we could see #
All right, I have a secret
to tell you.
You're in the middle of the road.
I know.
Do you wanna hear it?
Do you wanna
move your car first?
No, not really.
Okay.
I just wanna tell you
one more thing.
All right.
What?
That's not gonna be good.
Okay, tell me.
I've been in love with you...
Hey, hey, hey.
Shh.
John Muir said,
"Let children walk with nature.
Let them see the beautiful
blendings and communions
of death and life,
their joyous, inseparable unity,
and they will learn that death
is stingless indeed
and as beautiful as life. "
That is my hope for Bennett,
that this amazing young man,
who was taken from us so suddenly,
who was so well-loved,
who was surrounded by everything
that was beautiful to him.
It is in this spirit
that we return Bennett
to that form from which God
miraculously created all life.
Come on.
Open the door, Ryan.
Hold on.
Come on.
Just let me... Ryan.
Just let me... Hey.
Come on, buddy.
Let me in.
Jesus Christ, Ryan.
Open up some of these windows,
would ya?
I don't care what you say.
Next time you're gonna
let Gloria up here.
Sorry.
Smells like something died
and went to heaven.
I didn't know she was here.
Well, she's not.
But she's coming back very soon.
Where have you been?
I've been here.
What, in the house?
Yeah.
Well, then just check in
from time to time, would you?
Your mother's worried.
Okay.
What I wanna know...
What I need to know is, um,
what were the 17 minutes like
for my son?
I don't know what to tell you,
Mrs. Brewer. I wasn't there.
You've spoken with every doctor,
every nurse, every paramedic,
every fireman
that was on call that night.
I don't know what other information
I can give you.
What about Jordan Walker?
Mr. Walker is still in a coma.
I know, but I have
a surveillance tape,
and in that tape
it looks as if they spoke,
that they might have had
a conversation.
Would he have been capable of having
a conversation with my son?
That depends on how slow
the bleeding in his brain was.
Uh, I mean, it's possible
that he could have stayed
conscious long enough
to carry on a conversation.
Then he would have been
the last person
to speak to my son
before he died.
Yes.
Uh, I have an appointment at 9:00.
I'm sorry.
When do you think he'll wake up?
Uh, as I've said numerous times
before, Mrs. Brewer,
I have given you
all the answers that I know.
But he could wake up.
I mean, what would be the signs?
I'm sorry.
Dr. Leonard, 2291.
Allen?
Hi. Hi.
How are you?
I'm sorry. I had a head
full of numbers.
Oh, you're sweating. Here.
Uh...
Yeah.
Yeah, thank you.
You're right.
I'll turn up the A.C.
Is this, uh...
Is this roster correct?
'Cause I don't have Linda
down here for the summer.
How are you?
All right.
You look like
you've forgotten to sleep.
I'm all right. I'm fine.
Thanks for the flowers.
They're not necessary.
I wanted to call so many times.
I didn't know what to do
in this situation.
I just want to be strong
for Grace, that's all.
- That's all I'm doing.
- Of course.
So, we got, um...
We got 30 students here.
Ready and praying to graduate.
Well, let's see what I can do, huh?
If you want anything,
anything at all,
just let me know.
I will.
Ah! I read about
an interesting idea today.
I even made a purchase.
There seems to be a lot of research
on the Web about grief,
and, uh, I stumbled across
a couple of interesting suggestions.
Oh, Allen, no, don't.
They suggested we use a bell.
We can ring this
when we're missing Bennett
or when we think about him.
You can put it anywhere
in the house you like.
Can I see the bell?
Hello.
- Rose, right?
- Yeah.
Come on in.
Just through here.
Would you like some tea,
soda, water?
No, I'm fine. Thank you.
I'm sorry for just stopping by.
No, no, not at all.
I'm glad you did.
I've wanted to talk to you
since the service.
Uh, yeah, I know.
I wish I could've given
your wife more answers.
I know how much she wanted them.
She certainly does want her answers.
She's very focused on the matter.
But, well, it's only a matter of time.
How are you feeling?
Oh...
Water.
Could I have some water?
Yes, of course.
Please, just sit down,
make yourself comfortable.
I've been trying to figure out
how you knew Bennett.
Are you part
of Youth in Government?
Uh, no.
Ah, you must be an intern, then,
at the paper.
No.
No? Um, community service?
Just tell me if I'm hot or cold.
Cold.
Well, not East Ivy.
I don't think he held on to many
of his friends from his junior high.
No, I'm the one he got pregnant.
Excuse me?
I'm pregnant.
I'm sorry. I'm...
I don't understand.
I'm three months pregnant.
Is it Bennett's?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Are you going to keep it?
She told me
they only spent one night together.
I just can't believe
she has nowhere else to go.
There must be somewhere
she can stay
until the paternity test.
Paternity test? I'm not putting
that poor girl through that.
- Why are you defending her?
- I'm not defending her.
I just don't see why she would
make something like this up.
- Because she's 18 and broke.
- Well.
I can't deal with this.
I just can't deal with this.
Grace, Grace, Grace.
Come here. Come here.
- We don't even know this girl.
- I know.
But she seems like a nice girl.
If it turns out to be his,
I'm not gonna be happy about it.
I mean, I don't want everybody
thinking that we're blessed.
You don't think we're blessed,
do you?
No, I don't.
She's probably the one
that dyed his hair blue, too.
He never would have done that.
Finish making the bed.
I'm gonna go down and gather...
Wait, wait, wait. Why does
she have to come to our house?
We're grieving.
That's not gonna be good
for the baby.
This must be her only choice.
Are you really pregnant?
Yeah.
That figures.
The one bad thing my brother does,
and he's not even here
to get in trouble for it.
I'm Rose.
I know, yeah.
I know who you are.
My brother kept your yearbook photo
on his bedside table.
- He did?
- Yeah, and I wouldn't touch it,
because he probably
jerked off to it every night.
So you're his little brother.
Yeah, the fuck-up.
He didn't tell you that?
He didn't tell you I was a fuck-up?
No, he never said
you were fucked up.
He was just being polite then.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine. Why?
Do I not look like I'm okay?
No, you seem a little jumpy.
I'm a little restless. Yeah.
You have a fever.
I don't know why.
I feel fine.
- Ryan?
- Yeah?
My mom just checked into rehab.
Bananas and Gatorade should help.
Yeah.
What would you say
if someone asked you
about this night?
Why do you want a compliment
from me so badly?
Because you haven't
given me anything.
I've given you everything.
Right, but I want more.
I want to know
what you're thinking.
Please?
I would say...
The greatest?
I like that.
I like those words.
I want my baby.
He's just... He's...
One appliance,
less than 1,500.
Somebody help me
find my baby!
Somebody help me find my baby!
See, I don't know where he went.
Have you seen my baby?
I can't find him.
- Calm, calm. Shh, shh.
- He's so small.
He was right here,
and now I can't find him!
Come on, sweetheart.
My mom takes walks
every night at 6:00.
I followed her two nights ago.
She just circles the block
over and over again
looking for James.
Hold that thought.
Hi. You must be Ryan.
Uh-huh.
Come in, please.
Sit down.
We were just finishing up
with Latent.
Feel free to listen or join in,
whatever you're comfortable with.
Okay.
Sorry, Latent.
When I asked my dad
where she was the first night,
he said she was looking for James.
Sometimes she'll just run
to his bedroom
and throw open the door,
like she expects to see him sitting
at his computer or something.
Often parents
that didn't view the body,
like your mother,
still look for their child in crowds.
Sometimes they even think
they see them.
It's normal, Latent.
The best thing you can do
for your mother
is talk about it with her.
I think it could help.
So, Ryan, hi.
Hi.
What brings you here?
Nothin'.
I just thought it was
the normal thing to do.
Are you experiencing
any symptoms of grief?
No.
Who are you here to see?
Jordan Walker.
I don't know why
they can't get this right.
He prefers the blinds open
during the day.
Does he really?
Did he tell you that
after he requested
the aquarium over there?
I just wanted a little life
in this room.
Uh, decaf caramel macchiato,
extra foam.
Sheila told me.
If you're trying to bribe me
into feeding that fish
on the weekend,
it's not gonna work.
No, it's fine.
I'll be here on the weekends.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, and, Toni, could you
ask Dr. Jacobson
to stop in when he gets here?
I have a few questions for him.
- Right away.
- Thank you.
- You give him the balloons, okay?
- Yeah.
Mrs. Rodriguez?
- Yes?
She's cool. It's my dad.
He thinks it's stupid.
You know, you don't have to share
if you don't want to.
You can just listen.
I highly recommend
not sharing, actually.
These people
are like grief vultures.
And why are you here?
Nowhere else to go.
And my sister Amy
blew her brains out
while we were at church.
Oh. I'm sorry.
What about you?
Oh, my brother, um...
He died in a car accident.
There are a ton
of car accidents here.
Latent's brother was in a car.
So was Sarah's and Jason's.
Uh, Hilary's sister O.D.'d,
and Jeremy's brother died
before he was even born,
and he's, like, the most
dramatic one here.
It's like, do you even
remember him?
So, you're the only suicide?
How do you know it wasn't murder?
Because you just said
she blew her brains out.
Oh.
Yeah. Only a suicide.
Really special.
You know, it does get easier,
or more interesting,
all the different layers
of fucked-up-ness.
I'm fine.
I'm doing okay, actually. Yeah.
Well, even if you're not,
the groups are really good ways
to talk about it.
Your friends are gonna start
avoiding you like the plague.
I'm not even really
talking about it with them.
Well, then I'm really glad
you're here.
Did you ever notice me at all
any of those times
we passed each other?
Did you at least recognize me
at some point?
Keep your eyes closed.
I'm almost done.
Okay, they're...
they're closed.
They're shut.
Good.
So, you won, like, "Most Popular"
or "Best All-Around"
or "Best Guy to Know," right?
Uh, right, yeah.
It was just "Best All-Around. "
So, you're a nice guy.
I think so.
Is that why you're here,
because you're nice to everyone?
No.
Okay, you don't look
like the prom king anymore.
Oh, shit!
My mom's gonna kill me.
I think it suits you.
Really?
Yeah.
You sure?
You're so pretty, Rose.
Just let us know
if there's anything you can't eat.
I can only imagine how sensitive
your stomach must be right now.
Oh, I mostly just crave
bean burritos from Taco Bell.
It was peanut butter
and bananas for Grace.
- Really?
- Right?
Right.
When Grace delivered Ryan,
we thought she was gonna
give birth to a banana split.
That was Bennett, actually.
Ryan, how are you enjoying
your summer?
Summer's over.
Right.
Don't know why I'm having
a hard time remembering that.
Okay, here's another one.
How's school?
It's good.
I got all the classes I wanted.
Me and the guys hung out
after school, went swimming,
and we might go see a movie later.
Excellent.
Why is it "excellent"?
Well, seems like a nice way
to spend a day.
All that's missing is a bean burrito.
I've got something for Rose.
Great. Let's see it.
So there's this Web site
where you can take
two people's picture
and see what their unborn kid
looks like.
I took you and Bennett's
yearbook picture.
According to them,
your kid will definitely
be riding the short bus.
- Ryan, that's not appropriate.
Let me see.
Oh, look. Look!
At least it sets the standards
pretty low, right?
That's enough, Ryan.
Thank you.
You'll still love him, maybe.
Look, he's got Bennett's eyes.
Anyone know if the weather's
gonna clear up for the weekend?
Why do you do that? Why do you
always change the subject
when Bennett's name comes up?
I don't.
Yes, you do.
- Grace.
- You do. Watch.
Did you dye our son's hair blue?
Rose doesn't want to talk
about this at the table.
- No, I...
- Why not? I just want to know.
Grace, leave it alone.
Why make a point now?
I'm not making a point.
I'm asking a question.
Did you or did you not
dye our son's hair blue?
I'm finished.
Yes.
You know,
when I went to the morgue,
I didn't think it was him.
I thought they got the wrong boy,
because, I mean, our son
would never dye his hair blue.
And I thought maybe
they made a mistake, and then...
I saw his face, and...
it was him, it was our son,
and he was dead... again.
It was like he died... twice.
I'm sorry.
You see, I didn't want
to make a point.
I just... wanted to ask a question.
I could come to your office hours,
if that would be easier.
No, no, don't do that, Dante.
Let's go again from the top.
I'll come back tomorrow.
I'll just make an appointment.
I'm fine.
Maybe you should think
about taking a little more time off.
I can find a midterm replacement.
No, no. Don't do that. I'm fine.
Just haven't had my morning coffee,
that's all.
Will you have dinner
with me tonight?
No strings attached.
We used to be good friends.
Remember?
L... I just need one night of sleep,
that's all.
That's my problem.
I just need one night of sleep.
What about the beach house?
It certainly is a wonderful place
to forget about the world
for a while.
Grace loves the beach house.
Right.
Well, when Rick's mother died,
I took the whole family
to Florida for two weeks.
It made a difference.
I can't talk to you anymore.
You know that.
I'm just trying to make sure
you're taking care of yourself.
It's not always about Grace.
Ryan, we're gonna go
to the beach house.
- When?
- I don't wanna hear about it.
The decision's been made.
The whole family's going.
I said, when?
Now. Today.
- Can I bring someone?
- Yeah. Sure. Who?
- Ashley.
- Fine. No drugs.
Please, Dad. Why not?
I'm serious, Ryan. Okay?
Now help your mother pack.
Do you think she wants a sample
before we go?
Please, Grace.
Turn that off, would you?
I don't understand
how the car crumpled like that.
Maybe we should show this
to Bill again because, you know,
maybe something was wrong
with the frame of the car.
There wasn't.
And he gets out of his truck,
then he goes towards Bennett,
and he's...
It looks like he speaks to him.
I mean, why...
That's Ryan's sample.
If you want to test it,
he'd love you to test that.
...talk to him.
And then he gives him his jacket.
Are you gonna
test the sample or not? Huh?
He was alive for 17 minutes.
Aren't you just even
the slightest bit curious
about what happened
in those 17 minutes?
Oh, you know, maybe this is
a good time to stop the testing.
You know?
I mean, Ryan's looking good.
Best not push it.
What do you think?
I think it's really important
to be consistent.
All right.
I was just thinking that it's
too much for you, you know.
It's fine. I'm fine. I can do it.
You didn't take her
to the beach house, did you?
Of course not.
# Wrapped around each other #
# Trying so hard to stay warm #
# That first cold winter together #
# Lying in each other's arms #
# Watching those old movies #
Mmm. This is a great song.
Has anybody ever made love
to this song?
Mom has.
She's laughing.
# You were my leading lady #
# We had it all #
# Just like Bogie and Bacall #
# Starring in our own late,
late show #
Am I sitting on his bed?
Yeah.
- It's creepy.
- Yeah.
Did you guys get along?
Uh... yeah.
I mean, we did
when we were little.
My mom says I used to follow him
around all the time.
He is really cute.
My mom thinks that he was
the greatest thing that ever lived,
but, uh, he actually could be
a real cocksucker
when he wanted to.
He won a lot of shit.
Yeah.
Yeah, he did.
You probably would have
wanted to date him.
- No.
- Yeah, you would've.
Trust me.
He had that effect on people.
I think my mom even wanted
to date him sometimes.
What about you?
What about me?
Who wants to date you?
I don't know.
Uh, you, maybe?
Maybe.
Gonna win!
Gonna beat you down there!
Then you're going in the water!
Hi. Grace?
Do you have a minute?
Uh, sure.
Uh, I bought a book.
I have this baby book,
and there are so many questions
I don't know the answers to.
And so, I was hoping you might
like to help me fill it out?
Is now a bad time?
It's fine.
What do you need?
Um...
Okay, let's see.
Uh, his name.
How did you come up
with Bennett's name?
Tony Bennett.
The singer?
Mmm.
Oh.
I'm having a really hard time
thinking of baby names.
Allen and I couldn't agree
on the girl's name.
I wanted Ruby, and he wanted
something more traditional.
Ruby. That's pretty.
So, I hope that helps you out.
Do you wanna feel?
You know, aren't you gonna go
swimming with everybody?
He always kicks
when he hears your voice. Feel.
- I'm fine, thanks.
- Please?
It's strong.
Yeah.
Again.
I never thought I'd get pregnant.
I didn't even think
you could the first time.
Who has that kind of luck?
Think it was Bennett's first time?
Yeah, I think so.
It's funny, isn't it, that...
you're the only one
who will talk about him with me?
I'd love to, more than anything.
I have so many questions.
I think you should go swimming.
I'm Bennett.
It's nice to meet you, Bennett.
You too.
- Okay.
- Hey, wait.
- Where are you going to college?
- Barnard. You?
I thought you were going to N.Y.U.
No, I'm going to Barnard.
They gave me a scholarship.
All right. Great.
Yeah, I'm going to Berkeley.
No scholarship... yet.
I have to go to work
'cause I'm always really late.
All right. Okay. Uh...
Uh, please don't go.
It's taken me, like, a year
to get the courage to talk to you.
Please don't go.
You've waited till 3:15
on the last day of school.
Right. Yeah.
I never said I had good timing.
I have to go to work.
Uh, can I maybe come...
Can I come with you?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry. L...
- Yeah? You sure?
Yeah.
Ryan!
There's strong currents
out there! Back!
Come out of the water!
What?
Don't question me!
Don't! Just come out
of the water! Now!
I know how to swim!
Goddamn it! Come out now!
Right now, and I mean it!
Do you understand me?
Come out! Please!
Goddamn it!
Come out now!
What are you doing?
You know what I was doing.
I know how to swim.
You know better than that.
Hey.
Oh, hi. Hi.
Hi.
Did you swim?
Yeah. Yeah, I...
Yeah, I did. It was a...
It was good. It was good.
A bit cold, but it was good.
You okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Just fine.
Nothing like an ocean breeze,
you know.
I know. I always wanted
to live by the ocean.
My mom thought it was
too close to the moon.
Oh, that's a good one.
Doesn't make any sense.
No, not really.
You know, your mother
is more than welcome
to come and stay with us
if she wants.
That wouldn't work.
My mom's not really sane.
Oh, I don't think that would
scare anyone in our house.
The truth is,
I haven't told her I'm pregnant.
Why not?
Because she'll... she'll tell me
I've chosen the wrong path.
I don't wanna hear that.
I don't think you've chosen
the wrong path.
I'm not 100% sure why you chose it,
but I'm not sorry you did.
I know there are other options.
Listen, we would have
supported you either way.
I'm not against any of them.
It's... Of course not.
It's just...
I don't know.
You don't have to...
No, I do know.
Come here. Come here.
You don't have to know.
It's okay.
We can talk about this
at another time and...
Should we catch a movie?
Ryan!
Allen!
Do you wanna see
my only party trick?
Sure.
Okay. Hold that.
Mm-hmm.
Look at that.
That's good.
I've never actually
done that at a party.
I wonder how that comes up
organically.
Do you have any party tricks?
Um...
I don't know if it counts,
but I never forget people's numbers.
Hmm.
I... tend to memorize numbers.
What are my numbers?
Well, you have 18 years,
216 months, 864 weeks,
25,920 days,
311,040 hours.
You came to our doorstep
on 8-14-2008 at 4:30 p. m.
Your due date is 2-12-2009,
which leaves 119 more days,
2,136 hours,
128,160 minutes.
And you have two heartbeats.
As I get to know you,
I'll tell you more.
That's a much better party trick.
Price check
on register four, please.
Jesus Christ!
What happened?
Where's Grace?
She's fine.
She's out back, waiting.
- My son?
- He's upstairs. He's fine.
Okay.
What, exactly, happened?
Your wife had a difficult time
at a grocery store
and needed assistance.
- And she's out the back?
- Yes.
All right, thank you, officer.
This is Rose.
Are you all right?
I called a taxi.
Why didn't you call me?
'Cause your phone was off.
I'm sorry.
I was at the movies.
You went to the movies?
Yes, with Rose.
It was nice to get out.
Well, how could you
turn your phone off?
Grace, it was only
a couple of hours.
But anything can happen
in a couple of hours. Anything.
What happened
at the grocery store?
Was it a funny movie?
I mean, did you laugh?
Or was it sad?
Did you cry?
Ouch.
Oh, God, Allen, don't do that.
I can't stand that "ouch" thing.
Ouch.
Really. I'm warning you.
Don't start with that.
I just wanna know what happened
at the grocery store. That's all.
Well, I've got an idea for you.
Why don't the two of you,
you and Rose,
go off to Paris or Rome
or somewhere really romantic
and just get a vacation
from all this death?
Hey, hey.
That's not fair.
No, you know what's not fair?
It's not fair that you can go
to the movies with her
and I can't even pass
Bennett's favorite cereal.
Come on, Grace, please.
Just don't... don't do this.
- Don't... Just don't...
- Allen, stop it.
- Goddamn it!
- Allen!
Allen! Where are you going?
No, don't!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Let me help you.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I really am sorry.
I love you. I love you.
Grace, I love you and no one else.
Do you understand me?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry I was gone so long.
But I'm back now.
And, oh, wonderful. Look.
They can't even follow
the simplest instructions.
How many times have I told them
that you need the light?
But okay. Enough of that.
Let's read our Ellison again.
I don't even remember
where we are.
Is it the seventh
or the eighth chapter?
Let's see.
Eighth chapter.
You know, we're gonna finish
this whole summer reading list,
which is a first.
And I gotta tell you
that the high-school one
is much more boring
than the college.
Okay. Where were we?
Let's see.
"He started toward me
as in a dream,
trembling like the needle
of one of the gauges
as he pointed toward the stairs,
his voice shrieking.
I stared. Something seemed
to have gone wrong.
My reflexes"...
You know, Allen...
he hasn't always been like this.
I don't want you to judge him.
He's actually a very kind man.
And you would see that
if you met him.
He's never loved anyone less
than he should. Never.
I want you to know that.
It's just a phase. It's a phase
that we're going through. That's all.
Just like any other.
"'What's the matter? ', I stammered,
my voice low and my"...
He's all yours.
Wait, what's going on?
Wait a minute. What?
- Mr. Walker's being moved.
- What? Where? Why?
Mr. Walker has warrants
out for his arrest.
We're taking him to County Hospital,
where there's 24-hour security.
- Must be a mistake.
- There is no mistake.
Stop it! What about all his things?
You... You...
He's not gonna need any
of his things where he's going.
He's gonna be so terrified
if he wakes up and doesn't have his...
What do you think this kind of man
is gonna add to your life?
Stop it! No...
The minute he wakes up,
if he wakes up,
he's being shipped
straight to Rikers.
Are you gonna visit him there, too?
I think Grace might be
having an affair.
No.
I wouldn't blame her if she was.
I don't think she would do that.
I did.
I had one.
I needed to know
that she loved me.
Our entire married life,
I've always felt like...
we were on our first date.
Hmm.
I never deserved her.
Never.
Do you want to go
to a party with me?
There's three kegs.
- I don't think I'm dressed for this.
- Oh, don't worry.
These people are
pretty nonjudgmental.
Oh, my God! You're huge!
I didn't think it was possible
for you to stretch like that.
Shea, this is Allen.
Allen, this is Shea.
Hi. How are you?
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Wait. You guys did realize
this was
a "Wear Something You'd Never
Be Caught Dead In" party, right?
No. But I'm wearing Grace's
old maternity clothes,
so that kinda works out.
- And you?
- This is it.
Well, you're actually
kind of perfect, so...
Come on in.
Come in.
- Yeah, man!
- Oh, boy.
- Right on.
- Oh...
Hey, hey.
I wouldn't be caught dead naked!
Yeah!
Hey, um, are you a pregnant teen
or something?
Yeah, I am.
Do you live under a freeway
and are gonna have
a homeless baby
and use it to raise more money?
No, I'm just a regular
pregnant teen.
Oh. Right on!
I wouldn't be caught dead
having a baby!
Hey, is it okay if I just
come a little closer?
Sit next to you guys for a second?
I just... I gotta tell you something.
Dude, I'm on acid.
I'm trippin', y'all.
That's the way
Britney Spears would say it.
She'd be like,
"I'm trippin', y'all. "
- We can go somewhere else.
- Yeah.
No, wait, wait.
Dude, wait. Stay.
Say something familiar, man, please.
Just say something familiar.
I'm just seeing too many ghosts.
I don't know.
French fries.
Yeah!
- Mr. Bubble.
- Yeah.
Monkeys.
The ones that rip your balls off
for not sharing birthday cake,
or the nice ones?
No. The nice ones.
Yeah!
What... That's...
"Go, baby, go. "
Yeah!
Let's go.
All right. Let's go.
Bye.
What'd you do?
People signed my belly.
Oh.
It seemed sweet at the time.
"Have a great summer.
Good luck with the new kid. "
I was never into yearbooks.
Do you want to sign?
Um... all right.
Don't you think it might
just be easier
if you talked about it with Grace?
Floodgates.
I don't know what I'd do
if they opened.
I'll talk about someone,
but it'll really be him.
Why would you do that?
Because there are things
I need to tell you.
Okay.
I knew this boy.
He was really wonderful to me.
Is that okay?
Yes.
The first time I saw him
was in freshman English.
He wore a baseball hat
on the first day of school,
and our teacher made him
take it off.
And his hair was all pasted
on top of his head.
And he smiled at me
while he tried to fix it.
We watched each other after that.
And I started to feel
like I knew him.
I looked at his
yearbook picture so often,
I knew his face by heart.
Our senior year, I took piano,
and he had soccer,
so we would pass each other
every day after school
in the exact same spot.
And it became something
I looked forward to,
so much so that I could tell you
all the days he was absent,
because those were the days
that I was disappointed.
And sometimes
he would look at me.
Sometimes he would turn away.
And sometimes
it would be so intense
that we would start looking
at each other
from the very beginning
of the steps.
And then on the last day,
he talked to me.
And everything he said was exactly
how I pictured it would be.
And he felt the way he felt
in my dreams,
and I thought everything
was happening
exactly the way
it was supposed to.
And I was the happiest
I've ever been...
happy and scared
all at the same time.
And if he had signed my belly,
he would have written
something comforting.
That's one of the most
difficult integrals
I've ever solved.
Took me three years to do it.
And I was in love with him.
That's why I'm keeping this baby.
I was in love with him
for four years.
I barely knew him,
but everything
was exactly how I imagined it.
Everything was
just how I pictured it.
And I have to keep this baby.
I think he was the love of my life.
I'm very tired.
I can't fight it anymore.
I'm so tired.
My mom says it's cool.
Yeah.
That was a good story.
Thanks.
No, I mean... I don't...
I don't mean it that way.
I mean, it was good to hear.
Not good for you,
but good for me, I guess.
So what was
your brother's funeral like?
I don't remember.
It's all just a blur?
No, I really don't remember.
I was too fucked up.
I didn't know you get high.
I don't.
My mom tests me every two weeks.
It's pretty much
the only thing they do
that proves they know I'm alive.
Need a ride home?
Yeah, sure.
Baby is head down,
which means
you're getting very close.
How are you feeling,
Mr. Brewer?
You look like
you could use some rest.
Oh, I'm fine.
Thank you.
How's the baby?
Just where we want her
to be right now.
It's a girl?
I'm sorry.
I thought you knew.
It's a girl?
Oh, congratulations.
Is she healthy?
Doesn't get any stronger
than that heartbeat.
You've taken
really good care of her.
Oh, this is wonderful.
This is wonderful.
Wonderful.
Excuse me.
It's wonderful.
Okay. I'll be right back.
A girl.
A girl. Okay.
What is wrong with you?
I just need a minute.
So, take a minute.
I'm going back in.
No.
I don't want this baby, Allen.
I don't care if I sound horrible.
You sound horrible.
If Bennett were alive,
she never would have kept it.
- I can't be grateful to her.
- You don't have to be.
- I won't.
- Fine.
- I won't do it. I won't.
- Don't. Don't.
Don't do anything.
I don't care anymore.
Don't I have the right
to tell you how I'm feeling?
Not when everything you say
is sounding so ugly.
You're right.
Losing a child is ugly.
You don't have a patent on grief.
You're not the only one
who knows how to do it.
- Other people grieve.
- You don't.
- You haven't shed a tear once.
- I'm gonna go back in.
You used to get misty when
you would go to his sports events.
Listen. Somebody has to
stand strong in this family.
Somebody has to be together.
If I fall apart, everything
goes to hell in a handbasket.
Well, I am so sorry that I can't
handle anything but my grief,
and I don't treat this family
like a goddamn army.
It's not all about you
and your grief, Grace.
There are people in our lives
who need our attention.
Well, you don't give a puppy
to someone who's just lost their dog.
You just don't do that.
So what do we do?
Give her back? Hmm?
Give her 20 bucks?
Wish her luck?
Don't praise her like she's a gift
that was given to us,
like it makes it okay
that our son is gone.
It doesn't soften the blow.
She does for me.
Yeah.
Oh, well, I'm so glad for you.
I'm so glad that the girl that is
the reason our son is dead
softens the blow for you.
That's unfair.
What was he doing
in the middle of the road?
If he'd been with his friends,
if he'd been with us,
would he have been
in the middle of the road?
Answer me that.
You don't know anything about it.
You haven't made the slightest
effort to get to know this girl.
I don't want to get to know her.
Why can't you understand that?
It should have been her
that died that night.
It should have been her!
Hello?
- Hi.
- Can I help you?
Yeah. Ashley left
this scarf in my car.
Um, who are you?
I'm Amy. I live here.
- Amy.
- Yeah.
Ashley's older sister Amy?
What'd she tell you?
I grabbed a live wire?
Fell overboard
on our family cruise?
What'd you tell him this time,
you freak?
- Ryan...
- I'm telling Mom.
- I hate you!
- Freak.
Ryan! Ryan, please.
Wait. I can explain.
- Ryan, please just listen to me!
- Uh-uh.
Look. They don't pay
any attention to me in there.
- I might as well be dead.
- You have no idea what it's like.
- Yes, I do. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- No, you don't. No, you don't.
You're a liar!
That's what you are!
Look, it's all bad! Trust me!
You have no idea what it's like!
Say it! Say you have no idea
what it's like.
I have no idea.
Open the gate.
Open the fucking gate!
Ryan, look, please. I'm sorry.
I just wanted you to like me.
Fuck you!
Hello?
# Wanderers this morning came by #
# Where did they go? #
- What have you done?
- I called Gloria.
You said we were
gonna talk about it!
I couldn't live with the house
so neglected.
Now, come on.
Please. Hey!
- Idiot!
- What is wrong with you, Grace?
- How could you do this?
- Come here a second.
Wait. Whoa. Whoa.
What is this?
Hey! Grace.
- You washed his shirt?
- Yeah.
- You're fired! Get out of here!
- Don't do this! Grace!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
I'm sorry.
Grace.
You've erased him.
You did it on purpose.
What are you doing?
You're acting like a child.
I've done nothing like that at all.
I wanted to be able to see
his pictures and to smell him
now that he's gone.
Grace, he's here.
He isn't here!
He's dead! He's gone!
I know that, goddamn it!
Don't you...
Don't...
There's nothing to hold on to!
Don't you understand that?
Just shed one tear.
I mean, what is wrong with you?
Can't you just cry one tear?
# Dear shadow alive and well #
# How can the body die? #
# You tell me everything #
# Anything #
Allen? Allen?
Allen? I'm s... I'm sorry.
# Into town one morning I went #
Oh, my God, Allen.
# Staggering through
premonitions of my death #
# I don't see #
Mrs. Brewer?
He had all the symptoms
of a heart attack...
difficulty breathing,
tightness in his chest,
heartbeat changes, dizziness.
But it wasn't a heart attack?
Not as far as we can tell.
His E.K.G. Looks normal.
What was it?
Well, his body's under an incredible
amount of stress, Mrs. Brewer.
He has high blood pressure.
His sinuses have led
to an ear infection.
He's suffering
from extreme sleep deprivation.
But it was not a heart attack.
Sometimes patients
manifest real symptoms
because it's easier to feel
physical pain than emotional.
Ryan. I wasn't expecting you.
Can I share?
My... My, uh, story.
My whatever... whatever it is
you people do here.
- Yes, of course.
- Okay.
Um, where do I start?
Where do you want me to start?
- You start wherever you like.
- Okay.
Can I say my brother's an asshole?
You can say whatever you want.
Okay. My brother
is an asshole, right?
And now he's some fuckin'
martyr god now that he's dead.
He's dead, by the way.
He's... He's dead, right?
Did you not get a chance
to see the body?
I, um...
No, I was too fucked up.
My mom came in to get me,
and I couldn't even move.
I couldn't move my head.
So I didn't get to say good-bye.
I just, uh, laid there in my bed
thinking about all the attention
he was gonna get
whenever he came home,
and how all of his stupid friends
were gonna sign his cast
and how he'd probably get
a pity lay out of it.
So, um, I didn't get to say good-bye.
And now... You know,
the thing was about Bennett...
Um...
The thing was, he, um...
He...
He was never an asshole.
He was actually really cool to me.
And he could have ratted me out,
like, a thousand times,
and he never did.
Me and him used to do
all kinds of fun shit together,
and the truth is,
I wanted to be just like him.
I loved him more than anything.
And I was too fucked up
to say good-bye.
And in the end,
that's all I ever gave him,
was nothing.
Do you know how that feels
to have your one shot
and fuckin' just blow it?
It's gone. I'll never get
that chance again.
I just miss him so much.
- Hey, Mrs. Brewer.
- He woke up.
Yesterday morning.
Nobody called me.
Is he all right?
He seems okay.
He's getting transferred over
to Rikers in about 10 minutes.
Can I talk to him?
Make it quick.
Hello.
I'm Grace.
Brewer.
Bennett's mother.
The boy in the car.
So?
So, you were the last person
to see my son alive.
Yeah, well, I had the green.
I'm gonna sue your whole family.
You remember?
Um...
Are you feeling better?
Does it look like
I'm feeling fuckin' better? Huh?
Uh... Um...
I saw the surveillance video,
and it looks like
you spoke to my son,
like you comforted him
after the accident?
I didn't comfort anybody.
Okay?
Now, I got some other shit
on my mind, if you didn't notice.
Do you remember
if he was in pain?
I'm not doing this, lady.
I have waited a very long time
to talk to you. Please.
- Just go. Get out.
- No, please. I can't.
- Get out!
- I can't.
He didn't die a hero or anything,
if that's what you want to hear.
It isn't.
I don't know.
It happened.
It happened fast.
He asked me if it was his fault.
And then you told him
that it wasn't?
I told him not to worry about it.
And what else?
You really want
to know this, lady?
More than anything.
His body was caught in between
the front end of my truck
and his door.
There was so much crushed metal...
I don't know.
Maybe it was
holding him together.
I didn't want to move him.
I don't think I could
even if I tried. Uh...
His right arm
was so... far behind his body,
it looked like
it wasn't even attached.
I never seen anything like it.
And I had to climb out
over the top of my truck, uh,
just to get to him.
I don't think he was in pain.
I just, uh, think he was cold.
And then you gave him your jacket?
Yeah, but it didn't make it
any better.
It was, um...
The... blood...
The blood was making him cold.
How much blood?
How much?
More than, uh, I've ever seen.
Was he scared?
Uh, I don't know.
I mean, there was, uh...
fluid everywhere, but...
A bunch of stuff coming out
of him, you know?
Uh...
He might have been crying,
I guess. I don't know.
Was he crying
because he was in pain,
or was he crying
because he was scared?
- What's the difference?
- Which one was it?
Scared, I guess.
Do you think
he knew he was dying?
Did he know he was dying?
He knew it was bad,
but it's not like we were talking
about God or anything.
I just told him,
"You listen for those sirens.
Once you hear the siren,
everything will be all right. "
Oh, God.
He needed me,
and I wasn't there.
I should have been there
to make sure that he wasn't afraid
and tell him that I loved him
and hold him and...
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
Hey, hey, uh, you want some,
uh, water or something?
He needed me,
and he called out for me,
and I wasn't even there.
Oh, he didn't call for you.
He called out for her
over and over again.
That, uh, girl in his car.
Rose?
Rose. All he cared about
was Rose...
if she was hurt,
if she was in pain,
if she was asking for him.
He kept telling me
over and over again,
"You've got to help her.
You should be taking care of her. "
But, uh, I thought she was dead.
He asked for Rose.
He even asked me
to turn up the radio.
This poor kid, he's got blood
coming out of his ears.
He wanted her to hear
this song that was playing.
He thought she might like to hear it.
I have to go.
Relax. You can stay here
as long as you want.
And, Rose, I've called my mom
from women's correctional facilities.
This is, like, tiny, I swear.
Hi. Lydia?
Yeah. Hi.
Uh, this is Shea.
I'm Rose's friend from work.
Tell her I'm okay.
Rose is absolutely fine,
and, um, she actually wants me
to tell you something which...
Okay. Well, we're not gonna need
a lot of your time, so...
Oh, I... I didn't know.
Um, she lost her job?
Ah.
And she only has 15 minutes left
on the phone.
Um, I'm really sorry
to hear about all that,
but, uh, Rose wants me
to tell you something,
which is that she is pregnant.
Yay! Um, I'd say just like
three or four months.
Yeah.
Oh, she's keeping it.
She put off Barnard for a year,
and, um...
Yeah. She's just, like,
handling it like a total Republican.
And, um, she wants you to know
that she is not at all scared.
And, uh, she's getting support
from the father's family and...
Um, I don't know.
I guess just whatever she needs.
Okay.
Um, she wants me
to ask you something.
Tell her it's okay
if she wants to come here.
Tell her it's fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Uh...
What?
Um, she wants you to ask
for 10,000 up front.
She says that she'll come help you
if you can get the 10,000 now,
'cause, um, well, she thinks
it's what you'll need.
She seemed, like, really glad
to hear that you were doing okay.
That's fine.
Doctor said you could go?
Yeah.
Good.
You talked with Jordan Walker,
didn't you?
Yes.
What did you learn?
Bennett loved her, didn't he?
Oh, yes. Oh, yes.
I wanted him to call for me.
Is that such a terrible thing?
I call for you.
I call for you every day.
I'm here now.
Oh, my God.
Poor baby.
- Oh, my God, my poor boy.
- It's okay. It's okay.
Oh, my poor, poor, poor,
poor boy.
Okay. It's all right.
It's okay.
Yes, it's okay.
All right.
Yes. It's all right.
I know. I know.
It's okay. It's okay.
That's it.
I wasn't there
when he needed me the most.
Had I... I could... I could...
I could have saved him.
Allen...
I had 17 minutes,
and I could have saved him, Grace.
No. Listen to me.
Look at me. Allen.
Honey, you couldn't.
Listen to me.
It was a mistake.
He died on impact.
He didn't suffer at all.
You couldn't have done anything.
He didn't suffer.
There was no suffering.
There was nothing
you could have done to help him.
- Really.
- Oh, Grace.
Oh, Grace.
It's okay.
Oh.
Grace, we have to bring her home.
- We have to.
- Okay.
All the places
she could have gone.
I'm gonna go look for her.
We'll go with you.
Okay?
I'm ready. I'm okay.
Come on. Let's go.
Good work.
After you.
No, don't...
Shea.
Hi. It's Allen Brewer here.
Wow. You really would be
caught dead dressed like that.
- I'm looking for Rose.
- You lost her?
- In a way.
- I don't know where she is.
I'd like very much to find her.
We're very worried.
So, please, if you can
tell us something, at least...
It's about time.
All right.
Try the place
where they crashed.
She goes there in the afternoons.
Okay.
Rose!
- Rose! Wait!
Don't worry, the baby is fine!
Rose, we were worried, okay?
Why? Why would you be
worried about me?
Because I'm reading old yearbooks
to try to learn about my baby's dad?
Where you going, huh?
Hey, look, you're gonna miss her.
Because the most disgusting stuff
I've ever seen
just came out of my body
on a bus?
Did your water break?
Are you in labor?
I'm fine!
Really wonderful progress, Rose.
A beautiful way to end the year.
We were concerned about you.
You just disappeared.
Don't worry. I can do anything,
and this baby will be okay.
Bennett!
Let us take you to the hospital,
and if it's too soon,
then we'll just, uh...
we'll take you home.
I don't want to go home.
I don't want my baby to grow up
in your messed-up home.
Am I supposed to raise her
without ever talking
about her father?
Tell her she can't even mention
his name in front of her grandfather
because he hasn't completely
acknowledged that he's dead?
Or worry at night
that her grandmother
is gonna smother her
in her sleep
because she'd rather
she didn't exist?
Or that her uncle will leave
urine samples next to her crib?
I'm sorry. That wasn't fair.
I like you, Ryan.
I like you, too.
Thank you.
Look, I promise I won't
smother her in her crib.
I know I wasn't very helpful to you
in your situation,
and if I had to do it again,
I would do it completely differently.
Rose.
Look.
Once you have this baby,
you'll understand
that the most horrible thing
that can happen to a mother
is to lose her child.
I'm sorry...
for what happened between us.
I really am.
Please, Rose.
Give us a chance here.
Just... Just get in the car with us.
Please.
I don't even know who he is.
What do you want to know?
We'll tell you.
I want to know everything
I would know if he was still alive.
I want more memories of him.
Yeah.
We'll tell you everything
you want to know about him.
We'll just keep talking
till the baby comes.
There's a picture of Bennett
on the track.
Was he fast?
Is my baby gonna be fast?
Yes.
How fast?
50-second 400-meter fast.
Wow.
Okay. Okay.
He was voted Best All-Around.
Why did they...
Why did people like him so much?
Tell me!
Uh, because he was a nice guy.
In third grade
when his friend Jack got glasses,
Bennett felt so bad for him that
he took Allen's reading glasses...
- You remember?
- Mm-hmm.
And he wore them to school
the next day
so Jack wouldn't be the only one.
Okay. Okay.
Um, who's this girl he's with?
That is his prom date,
and he only went with her
because she gave good head.
- Ryan!
- That's true!
No, that's good. I like that.
That's information.
I think she was a very smart girl.
They studied English lit together
one summer at Oxford.
- She gave good head.
- What else?
- Ryan!
- It's true. It's true.
What else? What else?
He hated to have his picture taken.
Whenever I went to take his picture,
he'd always make this horrible face.
- What was the face?
- Oh, it was a...
Show me the face!
That's terrible.
He'd eat anything off his plate
as long as it was separated.
That's true.
He'd take all the toppings
off his pizza
and he'd eat 'em in order.
It was really...
It was really weird.
Well, he was a little O.C.D.,
but in a very sweet way, right?
Mm-hmm.
Very sweet.
When he used to eat Cheerios,
he'd eat them in pairs
because he didn't want them
to be alone in his tummy.
Ah, God, this hurts!
I used to give him shit
for that all the time.
And he never flossed.
But he did wear an enormous
amount of cologne
once he discovered it,
and his room smelled
like a men's magazine.
Ow!
Oh! It's happening.
Yes, sweetie, it is.
I know, sweetie.
It's all right. It's all right.
Bennett lived for 18 years,
3 months, 7 days,
2 hours, 36 minutes.
He broke 6 bones in his lifetime
and had a 3.97 G.P.A.
He never had a girlfriend
before he met you.
His highest temperature was 104.3.
And uh, he knew how to count
before he said his first word.
Which was?
- Wow.
Thank you.
Of course.
You're doing great.
Just keep breathing.
That's it, sweetheart. Okay.
Squeeze my hand if you have to.
You're doing great. That's it.
Just keep breathing. That's it.
# Cryin' into your sleeves #
That's it.
We're gonna be there soon.
That's a girl.
You're doing great.
# 'Cause you miss
those lovin' arms #
It won't be long. That's a girl.
That's it. That's it.
# A lullaby keeps on playin' #
# You're thinkin' it's a dream #
# 'Cause you miss
those lovin' arms #
Oh, my God.
Her name is Ruby.
# And you've got a good mind
to pray #
# They say it's all part of his plan #
# But what if he's got
slippery hands? #
# Well, it's a sad face
you're wearin' #
# Like a burned-out sun #
# 'Cause you miss
those lovin' arms #
# You'd think a grown man
would care #
# About his bootlace undone #
# But you just miss
those lovin' arms #
# Yeah, you miss
# And you got a good mind to pray #
# They say it's all part of his plan #
# But what if he's got
slippery hands? #
# Well, goddamn #
# You're a boy, not a man #
# When you miss those lovin' arms #
Hey.
Hi.
# Everybody wants to know you #
# They float all around your head #
# Like a mobile #
# Hell, you don't know
what they're sayin' #
# Oh, but can't you tell #
# You're a golden egg #
# Of all the ways
I said your name #
# A hundred times,
but now it's changed #
# And little things
I didn't have #
# Are going off #
# Like bottle caps #
# A light,
catch a reflection #
# A cold night,
want some attention #
# I give without thinking #
# That's the way it is now #
# Soft spots,
our hearts made for breaking #
# Tie knots,
show me what you're making #
# We fight for a reason #
# Now it's off to bed #
# If I could help you
as much as I wanted to #
# But, hell, you don't know
what I'm sayin' #
# Oh, but can't you tell #
# I love you #
# Of all the ways
I said your name #
# A hundred times,
but now it's changed #
# And little things I didn't have #
# Are going off #
# Like bottle caps #
# Going off like bottle caps #
# A light,
send a reflection #
# A cold night,
want some attention #
# I give without thinking #
# That's the way it is now #
# Soft spots,
our hearts made for breaking #
# Tie knots,
show me what you're making #
# We fight for a reason #
# Now it's off to bed #