God bless America!
We made it back!
Times Square, believe me,
is wall-to-wall people,
human beings bent on having
the greatest party ever
and being in on a bit of this history.
What a night this is!
What a thrill!
Our boys are coming home,
and a lot of them are here right now,
right in the middle of this chaos.
I've talked to them.
They're from Arkansas, ;
Colorado, ; Seattle, Washington, ;
Los Angeles, ;
Aberdeen, Washington.
Looking around Times Square
at this very minute,
people are deliriously happy.
They're holding up newspapers
with huge 8-to-10 inch headlines...
"V-J Day," it says,
"War's End," "It's Over."
Now they're hugging
and kissing each other,
shouting words
of cheer and encouragement.
And still, paper by the torn keeps
flowing out of the windows
high, high above us.
...and the USO shows, too.
Our hats are off to all of those
people in show business
who traveled the world
entertaining our men and women
overseas and here at home.
Times Square is happy,
New York is happy,
the United States is happy,
and the world is at peace.
Tommy, I know all America
wants to thank you
and your wondertul organization
tor all the great war bond drives
you've put on,
and tor giving ot your time and talent
tor that wondertul radio show,
The Treasury Star Parade
starring T, D,
Thank you, It's been a pleasure
doing our musical bit
tor the peace ot the world,
We all love you,
- Swinging band, huh?
- Yeah,
Swinging band, man,
Really jumps,
- You here by yourselt?
- No,
- Aww,,, who you here with?
- My boytriend,
Oh,
Listen, it I wanted to get in touch
with you anyway, could I?
Let me take a minute ot your time,
I know you trom someplace,
We met a tew years ago at a party
or a dance, I can't remember,
We had a long conversation,
We really liked each other,
The problem is,
I want to see you again,
My mother and tather are down there,
my brother and sister,,,
Jimmy! Jimmy! Hey, Jim...
Hey, Jim!
Catch you later, right?
Hey, where you been?
Where's your unitorm?
I threw it out
the goddamn window!
Hey, look at those easy boxers!
Did you jump trom Hawaii
or what?
Jump trom Hawaii?
Man, I won these in a card game,
This guy had three deuces,
Little did the sucker know
that I had three 3s,
- Oh, three 3s, Yes!
- Three 3s? Three 3s?
- Three 3s!
- Card game, huh?
- Card game,
- Jackpot!
Jackpot! Jackpot!
Glad to have you back, boys,
Glad to have you back,
- I know you trom someplace,
- No,
- You don't remember me?
You don't remember
we met a tew years ago?
It was at party or a dance,
We had a long conversation,
- You can't remember that?
- No,
I just want to explain to you,
tirst ot all, my parents are over there...
my mother and tather,
my brother and sister,
I got to see them because I just was
two years in the service, you know,
so they haven't seen me,
Now, I want to get your phone number
so I can tell you tomorrow
about what I was thinking about,
There's something very, very important
I've got to talk to you about,
- No,
- No what?
No, no, You don't understand,
Give me your number,
You got a pencil?
No,
I have a photographic memory,
Just give me your number,
and I'll remember it,
- No,
- Yes,
Can I meet you at Central Park?
I'm serious,
I know, No,
I mean, come on,
There's no way...
No!
That seat's taken,
I know it's taken, but I'm gonna
sit here and tigure out another angle,
You can skip it, because I've
heard every angle here tonight,
- Oh, yeah?
- Oh, yeah,
How about this one?
"Gee, that's a,,,
,,, swinging band,"
Look, I don't mean to be rude,
really I don't,
but I do have triends,
and they are coming back,
so why don't you just leave?
Why don't I leave
as soon as they come back?
Why don't you just leave now?
It I leave now,
I'll never get to know you,
I'll never get to know what
a wondertul, beautitul chick you are,
I'm serious, Even though
I'm giving you a line, I'm serious,
- And I know you know that,
- I know that,
And I mean that trom
the deepest part ot my heart...
which is not too deep,
Look, why don't you just go
someplace else and try it again, huh?
All right,
Pardon me,
Was that tellow in the Hawaiian shirt
and the white pants,
was he disturbing you?
'Cause I know him,
I see him around, He's a little crazy,
No, he's not crazy,
He's just pushy,
Well, you know what
he said about you over there?
What?
Nothing,
Stop it,
Look, all right,
all right, all right! Enough!
Look, I'm going to get serious,
When I walked in there
and I saw you,
I realized
I tought this war tor a reason,
When I was in my toxhole,
when I was, like, not knowing
whether I would live or die,
in the mud, dirty,
who the hell knew...
I didn't know anything,
Is it all right? Take only
a minute ot your time,
Now, when I walked in there,
I knew! I knew!
You knew what?
I knew that I wasn't
gonna get anywhere at this table,
Now I'm impressed,
Well, I guess a little small talk's
in order here now,
Can it get any smaller?
I can take a hint,
- Can you also take a walk?
- You want me to leave?
Yes,
- I'll leave right now,
- Bye!
You expect me to leave atter
the way you talked to me just now?
Will you go away?
I don't want to,
I want to stay here
and annoy you,
Go away!
Look, let's avoid all this, huh?
Let's get down to business,
It's getting a little tiring here,
Give me your phone number
and we'll avoid all this,
Why don't I not give you my
phone number and we'll avoid all this?
- What's to be avoided?
- You,
But that cannot be avoided,
It you had one ounce ot
a gentleman in you, you'd go away!
Well, I'm not a gentleman,
- Oh, well, that explains everything,
- Who said I was a gentleman?
Do I look like a gentleman
in this shirt and these pants to you?
Well,,,
Even a louse would go away,
Why can't you just
give me the phone number?
What am I gonna do with it?
Call it!
Please?
All right, look,
I give up, I give up,
I'll take a rain check,
Maybe next war,
What makes you think
you'll win the next one?
Hey, Evans!
Friend ot yours is calling you,
Remember me? Paul's triend,
- Uh,,, Troy, right?
- Arnold,
Arnold!
Oh, Arnold, I'm sorry!
"Arnold, I'm sorry,"
The Ray Bolger show, USO,
Hey, Evans! Evans! You should have
come with us to London,
We had a great time,
great hijinks,
- You're beautitul,
- Thank you, Arnold, How's Paul?
He's here,
I saw him a second ago,
- He's here?
- Yeah,
Where?
Paul! Hey, Paul!
Look who's here! Francine!
Hi, Paul!
Remember me?
I'll call you, tomorrow,
Keep on plugging, Francine!
Don't ever change!
You're beautitul!
Don't ever change, Francine,
You're beautitul,
Francine, I want you to meet
my new monkey,
- This is Eddie DiMaggio,
- That's Di Muzio,
Only you don't
look like a Di Muzio,
I said, it's tunny, you don't look like...
Skip it,
Oh, but he's a territic dancer,
I mean, he dips and everything,
don't you, honey?
You better believe it, baby,
Have tun, Francine,
Tommy Dorsey!
Tommy Dorsey and the Orchestra,
ladies and gentlemen,
Right atter we pause tor
station identitication around the country,
we're going to switch to,,,
Come on, you could
do me that tavor,
Hey, where you been?
I been looking all over tor you,
Where have you been?
I've been looking all over tor you,
We're over there,
The guys are waiting tor you,
- Where are the broads?
- They're over there,
Wait, I gotta ask you a tavor,
You using your room tonight?
Ot course I'm using my room tonight,
You want to use the room?
I tell in love about a halt hour ago
with this chick over there,
I think she's a protessional dancer,
She's got some pair ot legs,
You know, very leggy,
You know what I mean, don't you?
- How long you gonna be?
- An hour, maybe two, maybe less,
All right,
but use the bathroom,
Why didn't you bring them
over to the table?
There's only two,
The other two had to go to work,
So there's one tor me and one tor you,
- Oh, okay,
- All right?
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
Are these the girls?
Yeah, why?
- These are the broads right here?
- Yeah,
Which one is yours?
- I got the blonde,
- You got the blonde?
That means I have the brunette,
She's a total pain in the ass, man,
You know how much time I just
spent with her trying to make her?
I spent 20 minutes
giving her every routine I knew,
It didn't even work,
There was nothing! Nothing!
- The one over there?
- Yeah, the one over there,
That one, the WAC,
What's the matter with you?
Maybe the other one will go,
You know how girls are...
one goes, the other doesn't,
You got the good one,
I got the bad one,
I'm excited,
It's V-J Day, man!
You know, I want to get laid,
What's happening here?
Oh, look at her now,
Oh, ho ho, look at that,
Look how cocky she is,
You know what I'm going to do?
You go over there,
and you tell her that
I was wounded in action,
Tell her I was wounded in action,
I just got out ot the hospital,
and I'm a little shy
and a little nervous,
Tell her I'm sensitive,
Lay it on like I'm a war hero,
- A war hero,
- Okay,
Not too heavy, Indirect, okay?
I'll wait here,
and then I'll come over,
Lay it on her real well
because I want to get her,
You understand? I'm gonna
really screw with this one,
Leave it up to me, okay?
Wait, wait, wait...
all right, okay,
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
Tell me what you're going to do,
Don't worry, Leave it up to me,
You know how I am with girls,
What else about
the other thing, though?
I'm sensitive,
Sensitive, sensitive,
Sensitive, Oh, you're sensitive,
Oh, right, right, right, okay,
Wait, wait,
What am I doing?
For her, I'm doing all this?
I'm gonna go over,
Just introduce me to her, I'll handle it,
This is Francine Flannery,
Over here, Jimmy Doyle,
Pleased to meet you,
Ellen Evans,
Wrong, I'm Francine Evans,
This is Ellen Flannery,
Remember her? You've been
dancing with her tor the past hour,
- Come on, honey, Let's go,
- He's such an animal,
Where are you go...
be caretul,
I'll be right back,
Mind it I sit down now?
Atter all, we've been
tormally introduced now,
We're old triends,
I was just gonna say, it you and I
had danced and had some tun,
it might have been a nice time,
I just gave the key to my
hotel suite to my triend there
because I think he tound
someone he's really hooked on,
Well, that's very generous,
Yeah, I thought so,
Seems you give things away
easily, huh?
- Did you have something in mind?
- For what?
What you just said betore,
You said that
I give things away easily,
I said, "Did you have something in mind,"
meaning I would give anything
ot myselt easily to you,
which I could do very easily,
He'll only be there
tor an hour or two,
Got any Juicy Fruit?
Sure, sure,
Bye-bye,
I get it,
Eddie, it nothing happened
atter tour hours,
you expect something to happen
in the next hour?
I'm gonna be there in one hour,
I'm don't wanna argue, That's it, Bye,
I'm sure it's Doyle,
I'm sorry, There's no Doyle
registered here,
You see, a triend ot mine
is in that room,
A triend ot his, Ellen Flannery,
It's quite urgent
that I get ahold ot her,
I see,
Could you just look one more time?
Sure, Ellen,,,?
Yeah, she's atraid ot heights,
I'm worried about her,
It she's on a tloor that's too high,
you know, she gets dizzy,
That would be awful tor the hotel,
Acrophobia,
Excuse me just a second,
Mr, Powell?
That's him, Mr, Doyle!
- Mr, Powell,
- Mr, Doyle,
Which one is it?
Mr, Doyle, Jimmy Doyle!
I'd like to talk to you
tor a second, please,
Step right up over here, please,
There happen to be a problem?
This will only take
a minute, Mr, Powell,
Where's Ellen?
What luck, running into you,
Fancy meeting you here!
Boy, you're a winner,
Every time I run into you,
you're always causing me great problems,
- Pleasure, Good to know you,
- What are you talking about?
You just ruined it tor me,
Do you realize
he's calling the manager now?
He's calling the manager,
He's calling the manager
because I'm here under an alias!
And they're upstairs in the room,
We're all gonna get arrested,
You have to go up there now
and wan them,
and you have to get my suitcase
and get my sax under the bed,
because I have an audition now,
I have an audition, and it you mess
that up, I'm gonna get even with you,
I don't care how, but I am
gonna get even with you,
'cause you ruined it!
Get up there right now!
I said do you mind?
I'm having a talk with my sister,
It's a tamily crisis,
Do you mind?
Yes, I do mind,
Well, you're gonna have
to wait a minute, that's all,
Sis, oh, please, sis,
Now, Mommy's waiting,
When I went home on my leg,
she was worried tor a tew days,
Mr, Powell, please, you've run up
quite a bill with us,
You've only been here a week,
Would you mind telling me
where you were betore that?
- Where was I?
- That's right,
Do you mind telling me where you were?
Because you know where I was?
I was in Anzio!
Anzio!
I remember now!
All right, tine, Mr, Powell,
Wait a minute, I get
carried away, Sorry, Listen,
Five nights at the Commodore,
three nights at the Saint Regis,
25 minutes at the Plaza,
Enjoyed room service at each,
In one case, use
ot the hotel limousine,
Why do you switch hotels
so otten, Mr, Powell?
You don't even know
what you're talking about,
First ot all, how could I
even sign these checks?
These are your signatures right there,
But this is my signature hand,
It doesn't even work,
You see this?
You see that?
There's no lite in that arm,
I might have it amputated tomorrow,
and you're telling me
that I signed these bills?
How? Did I sign
with my lett hand?
I'm right-handed,
How can I sign with my lett hand?
Look at that signature,
Look at it,
Isn't this your sister?
She oughtta know your signature, sir,
Listen to this,
He's telling me I signed this,
- Is that my signature?
- Yes,
That's your sister,
She oughtta know your signature,
- That's not my signature,
- Yes, it is,
That's his signature,
She's a little crazy, She's wacky,
You know, in the WACs?
Yes,
Sis, you gotta go home,
No,
- West 55th Street,
- What? No!
- I'm not gonna do this,
- Go home, now!
- All right,
- Remember Anzio, on the beach,
No, No, no, It's this way,
It's this way,
And right away!
And I'll meet you later!
Mr, Powell, I think it advisable...
This is a mistake!
This is harassment!
I'm not coming to this hotel,
I'm gonna put in
a complaint with the manager,
- Where is the manager?
- Would you lower your voice, please?
I think you have a lot ot nerve,
You see this?
When that happens,
and you can't explain why,
You want to see my leg?
It's all wood,
- That's terrible,
- You can knock it anywhere,
You can drive nails through it,
It's the best kind ot wood,
but still, it's a wooden leg,
You have a cushy job,
I lost this leg just so you can accuse me
ot not paying bills in a hotel?
I can't believe this,
Would you push it ott, please?
I can't even control it,
Honey, are you all right?
Oh, yeah, I'm just great,
Well, do you have any last words?
She... sorry,
Did I scare you?
No, no,
Listen, I've had her
tor three years on two tronts,
She's had every germ
known to man,
I hope you're not
one ot them, DiMaggio,
- It's Di Muzio,
- Is this Jimmy's case?
What's the matter?
Can't you take a joke,
tor crying out loud?
Well, whatever your name is,
take good care ot her,
What'd you say about germs?
What germs you talkin' about?
Killers,
Just...
Forgotten, but not gone,
- Uh, 242...
- Hotel Olcott, please,
Wait just a second,
2842 Flatbush Avenue, Brooklyn, please,
Do you mind it I take this cab?
Well, yes, I do,
but do I have a choice?
No, you don't have a choice,
I have an audition,
Do you have an audition?
I'm late tor the audition,
Why don't you come along?
You have nothing better to do anyway,
How do you know that?
I was thinking ot doing my nails,
What's it going to be...
Brooklyn or what?
I just said it's gonna be Brooklyn,
2482 Flatbush Avenue,
2842 Flatbush Avenue,
Same thing,
- What did you say about your nails?
- I said I was thinking ot doing them,
Well, why don't you do them?
Oh, why you so serious?
Oh, come on, loosen up,
Come on, You gave me
a hard time last night,
really a hard time,
Loosen up a little bit,
Oh, come, come,
Let's have some gum,
This way, you keep your mouth shut,
lt'll keep you occupied,
No, thank you,
Bet you're really enjoying this ride,
aren't you?
I'm having a hell ot a time,
Well, I'm nervous because ot
this audition and everything,
so I've got to chew,
Relaxes me,
Oh, God,
I'm so nervous about this,
You make it worse, too,
So what did you say
your name was?
I didn't say,
- You didn't say?
- No,
- Would you do me a tavor?
- What?
Would you hold something tor me?
What?
Give me your hand,
- For good luck,
- For good luck?
Oh! That's very tunny!
You got a real
sense ot humor, kid,
Boy, I can't believe it,
Listen, I want to
ask you something,
You want to know what
interests me the most, Frances?
One is music,
number two is money,
and number three is,,,
I got it,
Uh-huh, Got it,
- What's the matter?
- I don't want it,
They always in that order?
Sure they're always
in that order, unless,,,
you happen to come across
someone who grooves you
and you want to groove with...
Say, you,
And it things work out,
and you start acting
a little more intelligent,
then possibly, then I'll make
number three number one,
number one
number three, and,,,
number two,,,
Now, wait,
Now, now, wait,
Now I'm getting contused,
You put it where, uh,,,
You put it where number three is,
That's the way it would be,
Let me start all over again,
Let me get this,,,
Number three
would be number one,
And number two and number three,
Exactly,
and when you have that,
you have what you call
a major chord,
What's a major chord?
A major chord is when everything
in your lite works out pertectly,
when you have everything
you could ever possibly want,
Everything,
You have the woman you want,
you have the music you want,
and you have enough money
to live comtortably,
That's a major chord,
Oh,
A 1, 2, 3, 4!
That's enough, Doyle,
Hold it,
Doyle!
What?
I got a hangover,
That's a little loud,
A little loud? What do you mean?
You didn't dig those sounds?
You didn't even let me tinish, man,
You didn't let me tinish the chorus,
Jimmy?
Uh,,, Jimmy, could I talk to you
just tor a minute?
I'll just be a sec...
Look, you know what's happening?
You're playing territic,
Yeah,
I think you should play it
just a little smoother,
like a ballad or something,
I think this guy's got
that kind ot attitude,
You know, the whole joint
screams that sort ot thing,,,
Well, that's all right,
Are you my agent?
Want 10%, huh?
Sit over there,
I said when we came to sit over there,
Now sit over there,
Just rude, Rude,
See what you did?
Come here,
Come here, Come here,
Don't do that
in tront ot everybody,
We do this all the time,
Don't talk to me like that
and don't touch me,
I just want to say I'm sorry,
I just got annoyed at him, you know,
Sometimes I put my toot in my mouth,
- How about my toot in it?
- How about putting your horn in it?
- Well, that's what we're here tor,
- How about giving me a break?
Come here, Doyle,
I want to talk to you,
- Get a load ot this guy, huh?
- He wants you to come over there,
Come on! Come here, come here,
Go there, go there, go there,
Go ahead,
Yeah,
Try and understand
my situation, will ya?
What I got is a boy singer
and an eight-piece polka orchestra,
you understand?
Try Chevalier,
You know any Chevalier?
The guys come back trom France,
they like that sound,
Chevalier?
Yeah,
Hey, man, I play that stutt,
I kill people, you know?
This isn't 1917, You look
a little more hip to me than that,
I'd rather get a job in a post ottice,
In that case, Doyle,
let's torget it,
Yeah, let's torget it,
That's what I said,
- No, that's what I said,
- No, I said torget it,
- No, I said it, I forgot it,
It the nightingales
could sing like you
They'd sing much sweeter
than they do
'Cause you've brought
a new kind ot love to me
Play!
It the sandman
brought me dreams ot you
I'd want to dream
my whole lite through
'Cause you've brought
a new kind ot love to me
I know that I'm a queen
and you're a king
Still I understand
that undeneath it all
I'm a girl,
and you, you are a man
I would work and slave
my whole lite through
It I could hurry home to you
'Cause you've brought
a new kind ot love...
Can you dance?
Not you, her,
What's the matter, you crazy?
Let's see the legs!
The legs!
How I'd work, I'd slave
my whole lite through
Just to hurry home to you
'Cause you've brought
a new kind ot love to me
Ho, ho, ho
You've brought a new
kind ot love to me!
New love
That's it!
We make it a boy-girl act,
You start tomorrow night,
Three shows nightly,
You're ott Sundays,
Listen, baby, we ought to
work on some material tomorrow,
I have to go in, It's so late!
Stay with me a little while,
It's early yet,
No, I'm getting soaked!
Jimmy, look, why don't you
just call me tomorrow?
- What time?
- Noon is tine,
Okay, I'm going, I'm going now,
Good night, Jimmy,
- Okay, I'll call you tomorrow,
- Okay!
- All right,
- Where to, buddy?
Quiet just a minute,
I'm looking tor something,
Oh, Miss Evans?
Miss Evans?
- What?
- Telephone,
It's your agent,
He's been calling all night,
- You can take it here,
- Thank you,
Hello? Tony,
- Yes, sir, may I help you?
- I'd like to check in,
Fine, It you'll
just sign the register,
Do you have
any more bags outside?
Yes, I do, I have
one in the cab over there,
It you wouldn't mind
waking up the belhop,
I don't want to disturb him,
Wake him up and send him outside
and just pay the bill also,
and then you can put it on this bill,
We'll wake him in a tew minutes,
I'm sort ot ready to go back to work,
I'd like a little bit ot a rest,
"Mr, M, Powell,"
Excuse me, sir,
- What are you doing?
- I'm checking in,
- Why here?
- Why not here?
Because I'm gonna get blamed
when you don't pay the bill,
and you know
you're not gonna pay the bill,
Well, torget it, I'm checking in,
Anything else you'd like, sir?
I'd like some Scotch
and some vodka,
It there's a liquor store around here,
maybe we can send the belhop over,
We'll just put that
on the bill, okay?
When he wakes up,
we'll send him out,
All right, Jimmy,
Look,,,
take this,
This will be enough
tor a room tor tonight,
Just go anyplace else,
It's a lot easier it I just come up
and we start working on the material,
I'll sleep in the bathtub,
I told you, a lot easier,
No, Will you please take this?
- It's a lot easier,
- Just take this, Jimmy,
- 12:00?
- Yes, 12...
I promise,
- All right,
- Suite 415, sir,
Forget it, I'm not gonna take it,
He doesn't even wake up,
- I don't want it, I'm not interested,
- Sorry you teel that way, sir,
That's a great suit,
Oh, thank you very much,
Miss Evans,
Tony?
What do you want?
Right, Frankie Harte,
7:30 tomorrow morning,
No! No!
Beautitul, Beautitul,
Hey, Pops,
are you Jimmy Doyle?
Want to play the blues?
Are you Jimmy Doyle?
No,
You're the sax player, ain't you?
I'm a sax player,
but I'm not Jimmy Doyle,
Do you think it's possible
that you can communicate
with Jimmy Doyle
the sax player?
Depends on what
you want me to communicate,
I have a very important missive
tor Jimmy Doyle,
- A what?
- A billet-doux,
- A billet-doux?
- A Billy who?
I'll elucidate,
A tender message
trom a certain temale party,
For me?
- For you,
- For him?
Precisely,
Take it, Doyle,
It's trom Francine,
She said she had
a wondertul time,
Hey, wait, I'll be right back,
- Where you goin', baby?
- Be right back,
That girl ain't comin', is she?
- I'm getting her now,
- Ten minutes, or you're tired,
What do you care?
There's no one here anyway,
You had your jam session,
and now you're not coming back!
Hey, man, hold it,
Hey, Daddy, hold it, hold it,
Hey, can I talk to you tor a minute?
- Did you read this letter?
- Ot course not,
What do you think I am, crazy,
read letters?
- Your name is Tony Harwell?
- That's right,
- You're an agent?
- Yeah,
- You're her agent?
- Ot course,
She says, "Just ask Tony
it you need any help on anything,
He's a wondertul cat,
and he appreciates talent,"
- Let me see that letter,
- I can't show you the letter,
It's a personal letter,
but that's what she said,
She also said that she's
with Frankie Harte's band,
she's on the road, and there's
a possibility ot a spot tor me,
- Is that true?
- Possibility,
- A possibility?
- That's right,
You're an agent?
I reiterate, yes,
It I went down there,
would you be my agent?
No,
Why not?
I ain't interested, I'm satistied
with the list ot clients I got now,
You're makin' a mistake,
but okay,
I made a lot ot mistakes,
So I'll make another one,
This one's on me,
Well, where is she?
Why should I tell you where she is
it she doesn't tell you in the letter?
Then why do you take the time to come
out to Brooklyn to give me this letter
it you don't think
she cares enough about me
to let me know where she is,
or to let you know
to let me know where she is?
Doesn't that make sense to you?
It should, but it don't,
- They're in Asheville,
- Asheville?
But don't mention my name,
It Frankie asks me, I don't know you,
I'll say I never even met you,
I don't know you,
- Where is Asheville?
- Where God lost His shoes,
Where God lost His shoes,
That's a good answer,
Thanks a lot, I'll tind it,
Asheville is a mountain resort
in North Carolina,
Thanks tor telling me,
You got any other advice tor me?
Yeah, Stay ott the junk,
and you'll go tar,
Fine, Thanks a lot,
Swell ot you to say that,
Once in a while
Won't you try to give
one little thought
To me
Though someone else
may be nearer your heart?
Once in a while
Won't you think ot the moments
I shared with you
Moments betore we two
dritted apart?
In love's smoldering embers
One spark may remain
It love still can remember
That spark may burn again
They lett? Where did they go,
do you know?
Roanoke?
It is? It's the Maytair Club
in Roanoke, Virginia?
Hello?
All aboard!
Thank you!
Thank you very much,
Come on,
You are my lucky star
I saw you trom atar
Two lovely eyes,
at me they were gleaming
Beaming
I was starstruck
You're all my lucky charms
I love,,,
- Keep the change,
- Here's your change,
No, no, that's tor you, Keep it,
- Ah, it's only a nickel,
- That nickel's tor you, It's a tip,
Ah, take it,
- You don't want the nickel?
- No,
All right, I'll take it,
You are my lucky charms
I'm lucky in your arms
You opened heaven's portal
here on earth
For this poor mortal
You are my lucky, lucky star
Look at that tive-star pain in the ass
out there, will ya?
Look at him clap,
I'm goin' over there
and stutt him in the garbage can,
No, It's all right,
He may be a vet, you know?
- I think I know him,
- He's a dummy,
Okay, hold it,
Hold it! Hold it!
Please, Now, look,
you go back up on the bandstand,
I'm gonna come
right back up there with you,
Jimmy, I'll talk to you
atter the set is tinished, all right?
Atter the set? Okay, Sure,
But tirst, I'm gonna have
a word with him,
All right, you're upset because
I didn't come to you in person
and say good-bye, right?
Right, Which brings up another thing...
you don't say good-bye to me,
I say good-bye to you,
In no way, shape, or torm
do you say good-bye to me,
- I say good-bye to you,
- Oh,
- Fine! Go ahead and say it,
- Say what?
Say good-bye, Go ahead,
Come here,
Oh, I see,
I'll just have to wait
until you say come here, right?
And then when you say come here,
I'm supposed to come here,
Look, look,
You think I came all the way down here
to argue with you, huh?
You think I came all the way down here,
chased you, to argue with you?
I'm just contused,
Didn't you understand when I said
"major chord" that I meant it about you?
Sometimes you really are
hard to understand, You really are,
You're hard to understand,
Don't change the subject,
I love you,
I mean, I don't love you,
I dig you, I like you a lot,
and, you know,,,
I wouldn't come all the way
down here it I didn't like you, right?
Yeah,
Oh, Jimmy,
How do you teel about Texarkana?
How do I teel about Texarkana?
What do you mean?
What I'm sayin'
is that Frankie said
that it you came down,
you could audition,
I could audition? No, torget it,
I'll play tor him, I won't audition,
Okay,
Don't, Jimmy,
Jimmy, come on,
Jay, will you, please?
It's slippery out there,
We don't want to slide into town,
we want to drive in,
Leave me alone,
I'm tryin' to take a nap,
All right, The points,
Give me some quarters,
He's beating the pants ott me,
I'm glad I'm working tor you,
You should be glad
to work tor anybody,
You're not the greatest piano player
in the world, you know that?
It's gonna be one ot those nights,
I'm a good musician, man,
You really are,
Coming trom me, that means nothing,
Maybe someday you'll
write something tor me, too,
I am writing something tor you,
I'm writing this tor you,
What? You think
I check out each room?
- The last time I got a room...
- Will you get ott my back?
When you play cards,
you go crazy,
Why don't you guys zip up?
Clam up, will ya?
You don't even let me
read what you're writing now,
let alone your tirst poem,
lmagine you giving me
your tirst poem?
Now let's go into the bridge,
It you let me read it,,,
It you let me read some ot that,
I'll let you write the lyrics to this,
That's blackmail,
Right,
Oh, Jimmy,
Aw, come on, Come on,
let me see what it is,
- No, I don't want to,
- Aw, come on,
- No, it's private,
- It's only a poem,
Well, it's my poem,
and it's tor me,
You never let me
see what you're writing,
Well, I'm embarrassed,
You wrote all this about me?
It's all about me?
Well, most ot it,
It's all about me, though?
It's not about anybody else?
It's all about me?
That's right,
Get your shoes on, Come on,
- Are you all right, honey?
- Yeah,
I know it's not very good, but,,,
Come on, get 'em on,
Come on,
I don't know
what we're doing now,
Wait a minute,
Here, pay me,
We're gonna be right back,
Few minutes,
- No, pay me now,
- I'm not gonna pay you now, man!
You think I'm not gonna have a cab
standing by in the middle ot nowhere?
We'll be back in a second, I think,
Pull it back with your hand,
Jimmy,
You all right?
You want a handkerchiet?
- It's nothing,
- Here, I've got a handkerchiet,
- You knocked?
- Yes, I'm sorry,
I'm terribly sorry about that,
Are you the justice ot the peace?
That's right,
You are? I'm sorry about the window,
It's just, you know, we're a little anxious,
Is there a possibility that
we could be married now?
We're in a bit ot a hurry,
I can't even explain to you why,
I wish I could,
You can see the way we look,
- Please close this up, honey,
- Now?
Could you please? Just take
about two minutes ot your time,
We'll make it worth your while,
and I will pay tor the glass, too,
- Could you, please?
- Well,,, I guess I could,
Oh, yeah, we can arrange it,
We can arrange it,
Come on in,
No, Uh,,, just a minute,
- Can I talk to you?
- Aren't you sure?
Yeah, just one second, please,
- You're kidding, right?
- Kidding what?
- That was it?
- What was what?
Your proposal?
"Get your coat on, Put on your shoes,
Come on, let's go," That was it?
What's wrong with that?
- They're not sure,
- Sure, we're sure,
What's wrong with that?
I thought it was gonna be ditterent,
It is ditterent,
It's the way I do it,
Anything wrong?
There's nothing wrong,
They're not sure, believe me,
No, I just thought,,,
What?
Nothing, I just thought
it would be ditterent,
Ditterent? It is ditterent!
I know it's ditterent, It's not
the kind ot ditterent I had in mind,
The kind ot ditterent I had in mind
was maybe sweet and calm...
It is calm!
- All right, That's good,
- I'm sorry, I'm just a little,,,
- And pretty, you know?
- What?
- Pretty,
- It's pretty!
But you can't say that,
You can't say it's pretty,
I want to marry you!
What are you talking about?
Please go inside, go inside,
This is private,
Would you wait one second?
I'm coming,
- Did you hear what I said?
- Yes,
I want to marry you,
Okay, Okay?
What's the matter now?
What do you want me to do?
You want me to kill myselt
over this, darling?
All right,
Listen, when I say "now,"
you back up,
- That's it,
- Jimmy, I,,,
Wait a minute, don't back up!
Don't move!
Now!
No! No!
Don't shitt,
don't do anything, Just stay,
Will you please
get out trom under...
This happens all the time,
Will you,,,
Will you marry me?
I love you, Will you marry me?
I don't want
anybody else to be with you,
I want to be with you,
do you understand?
I don't want anybody else
to be with you except me,
I love you,
Look at me, I love you,
Oh, I love you, too,
Wait a minute,
See, that was territic,
You liked that?
Yeah, I really liked that,
It was a lot better that way?
- Yeah,
- Aw, good,
Hey, no! Stop! Please!
You missing a man?
Yeah, Fowler,
Did you tind him?
The house dick did, Caught him
in his room with a local chick,
Big deal, So what?
What do you mean, big deal?
She's 13,
Fowler grabbed the guy's gun
and started shooting out all the lights,
Cops got him now,
Thanks,
Jimmy, take over tor me,
will you, please?
I gotta go bail Fowler out again,
This guy's driving me crazy,
Think I could do a couple
ot my arrangements?
Please, not tonight,
Just play the usual, huh?
Come on, man,
There are only tour people
in the audience, What's the ditterence?
I don't care about that,
I'm only asking you to tront tor me,
Now, do you have to
give me griet, too?
All right, all right,
Frannie, I'm gonna cancel
the rest ot the tour,
Again?
What do you mean "again"?
Well, this is the titth time
that you've cancelled,
But this is the tirst time I meant it,
I really mean it now,
Then I was jivin' you,
I mean it, I'm gonna
really pack it in, Yeah, yeah,
Oh, come on, you remember,
we used to go out and do 80,
85 one-nighters in a row,
Yeah,
All those joints... they're not
ballrooms anymore, baby,
They're like parking lots,
skating rinks,
The theaters,
they're all bombed out,
I really did, I thought a lot about it,
thought about tinally letting
somebody else tront the band,
you know,
take a piece ot the action,
Play there,
not have to litt a tinger,
But there's only one guy
who can tront this band,
I know... Jimmy, right?
No, me, and it I go,,,
the band goes,
It's game over, You know it,
You sure you won't have
a little taste?
- No, you have it,
- Oh, beautitul, I will,
Maybe Jimmy,,,
would consider,,,
You said he's good,
You think he's good,
He's not only good, baby,
he's a bitch,
He blows a barrel
tull ot tenor,
Oh, but he's some kind
ot pain in the ass,
- I don't want to start this argument,
- All right, okay, all right,
But he's a top pain in the ass,
and that's the truth,
A top pain in the ass,
You want to say it once more...
three times tor luck?
Three would groove me,
It's my tavorite number,
Top pain in the ass,
Well, maybe you're right,
but he's good,
I'm sorry, Mr, Doyle,
It's not quite what I had in mind,
Yeah, sorry, tellas,
He wants garbage,
I don't know,
Look, Mr, Horace,
I know it's not Frankie Harte,
We can do that stutt too, man,
but this is a ditterent sound,
I think you should listen to it,
Just give us another chance,
This guy must be crazy,
I made a deal with
Frankie Harte and his orchestra,
not Jimmy Doyle
and his tlying zacamaniacs,
But this is Frankie Harte
and his orchestra, without Frankie Harte,
In tact, it's even better,
Frankie wouldn't give us the band
it he didn't think it was gonna work out,
That's true,
You know how Frankie is,
What do you have to lose?
Come on, give me a chance,
What do I have to lose?
What does this look like to you,
a peanut gallery here?
Looks like a place that
needs someone like me,
that's what it looks like,
Give us halt a chance,
Where's the girl singer
you're supposed to have?
Is she stunning?
Blonde? What?
She's stunning, blonde, everything,
She walks, she talks, dances,
She'd better be good,
All right, tellas,
get on number 358,
Horace, have you gone crazy?
You've already listened to the band,
You didn't like 'em,
Why do you want to listen to a singer?
Ot course I'm crazy, How do you think
I wound up in this business?
Hello, Mr, Morris,
Okay,
When the mellow moon
begins to beam
Every night,
I dream a little dream
And, ot course,
Prince Charming is the theme
The he tor me
Although I realize as well as you
It is seldom that a dream comes true
To me, it's clear
That he'll appear
Someday he'll come along
The man I love
And he'll be big and strong
And when he comes my way
I'll do my best to make him stay
He'll look at me and smile
I'll understand
And in a little while
He'll take my hand
And though it seems absurd
I know we both won't say a word
Maybe I will meet him Sunday
Maybe Monday
Maybe not
Still I'm sure to meet him one day
Maybe Tuesday
will be my good-news day
He'll build a little home
Just meant tor two
From which I'll never roam
Who would? Would you?
And so all else above
I'm waiting tor
The man
I
Love
Thank you, Francine Evans,
"But the real winner is
singer Francine Evans,
"a spirited tilly who sports musical paces
as smooth as her torm,
Miss Evans seems headed
straight tor the winner's circle,"
Jimmy, did you see this?
Yeah, I saw it,
I saw that, yeah,
The guys are all excited,
Everybody's all buzzing around
and everything,
and Paul had a good idea,
He said that we should
take one ot the quotes...
like the best quote
about the... your band...
and put it outside,
Maybe even take something
in Downbeat or Variety.
Very good idea,
Yeah, that's a good,
This is a good thing, We might get
another week out ot this hotel with this,
Did you get ahold
ot that trumpet player?
The trumpet player,
did you get ahold ot the,,,?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I called his wite,
He's in Virginia on some gig,
She'll give him the message
when he calls,
It he's not gonna call,
let's go with Charlie Baxter,
Yeah, I like him,
Okay,
I don't know it he's
gonna go tor the money
that we're gonna be able to pay him,
Well, that's your problem,
You get him, That's your department,
Okay, I'll see you later,
Thank you, Paul,
We've never made the papers
like this betore,
It's really wondertul,
Thank you,
It's really good, It's great,
Here I go again
I hear the trumpets blow again
I'm all aglow again
Taking a chance on love
Here I slide again
I know, I know, I know, I know,
Hold it, tellas,
Jerry, you're not cuttin' it, man,
You are not cuttin' it,
It you...
- What is the problem?
- It you'll just...
Excuse me,
You're not cuttin' it, man,
Do it as written, okay?
How do you really
want it to sound?
The way it's written, and the way
I explained it to you, Come on,
I'll try,
No, don't try, do it!
Don't try, do it, do it!
- You playin' by yourselt?
- I don't think so,
'Cause I can put you
in a room somewhere,
you can play all by yourselt,
You sound like
you got hooks tor hands,
Funny,
Funny, I know, but you're being tunny,
and you're costing us a lot ot time,
That's a little rough, wasn't it...
hooks tor hands?
You'd get much more out ot him...
- Are you the bandleader?
- No, I'm not,
Okay, you're not the bandleader,
theretore don't tell me how to do it,
- 90% ot all drummers are crazy,
- I know that,
Look, Jimmy, we only got
15 more minutes in this room,
then we gotta get out,
I gotta do my hair,
I gotta press your shirt,
we gotta call Tony, I gotta do my nails,
I got a lot to do,
so we should really go ahead,,,
don't you think?
- Ready?
- Yeah,
1, 2, 1-2-3-4,
Here I go again
I hear trumpets blow again
I'm all aglow again
Taking a chance on love
Here I slide,,,
Where on earth
are you going, Nicky?
You're rushing that thing like we're
at the racetrack or something,
Listen, I'm pickin' up
the tempo trom you,
Did you have a tight
or something today?
- No, I didn't,
- Well, then, what's wrong?
You're not pickin' up
the tempo trom anybody, man,
You're doing exactly
what you're always doing,
Your wite is slowin' it down,
- What am I doing?
- Wait a minute, Stay out ot this,
- Wait a minute!
- She is slowing it down?
- Yes,
- I am not slowing it down...
- I can handle it, I can handle it,
She's not
slowing down anything, man,
We have been through this
50 million times,
You always do this, man,
You always give me a hard time,
Can't you read this
and just do it right?
Now I can't read, huh?
You can't read
it you can't do that,
Listen, I studied
at Brooklyn Conservatory
and the Staten Island Conservatory
ot Music tor three years!
You did?
Well, it doesn't show, man!
It does not show?
Well, maybe this'll show,
I'm packin' my axe and my hooks,
and I'm cuttin' out!
That shows, Okay, I'm gonna
show you something now,
I want to show you something, See?
Okay? Happy?
Yeah, I'm happy,
Are you happy?
Yeah, now I'm happy,
That's tunny, I'm happy, too,
Got it all out ot my system,
- Feel better?
- Yeah, much better,
It's very good out, now,
Okay, get your drums ready,
Can we start all over here?
- I teel much better,
- Good, good, Okay,
I'm sorry, Look,
I know we've all been working hard,
and we've been working too hard,
but like the man says,
it we get this thing right,
we'll blow the root ott this place,
you know?
So why don't we really try?
- You ready?
- Yeah,
Good, I'm glad,
1, 2...
1-2-3-4,
Here I go again
I hear the trumpets blow again
All aglow again
Taking a chance on love
Francine, Come here,
- What?
- Come here,
No, I want to hear this,
Don't ever do that again,
You do not kick ott the band,
I kick ott the band,
you understand?
Don't ever do it again,
Ever again,
Let's go,
From the tag,
1, 2, 1-2-3-4,
Come on,
Taking a chance,
taking a chance
Taking a chance on love
- Like that?
- Yeah, it's good,
Oh, ah, gee,
what are your charms tor?
What are my arms tor?
Use your imagination
Just you
Just me
I'll tie a lovers' knot
I'll tie a big, tat knot
Round wondertul you
- Thank you, ladies and gentlemen,
- Thank you,
Thank you, Francine Evans,
Thank you,
- You okay, baby?
- Yeah,
Hand tor Francine Evans,
ladies and gentlemen,
- You all right, baby?
- She's all right,
What's the matter?
- I teel territic,
- You sure?