I heard you have a much better chance
Of getting in if you come by cab.
You're really worried about getting in?
Yes.
I thought you'd been
here several times before.
Not the front way.
They were private parties.
We came in the back.
We look really good tonight.
I'm sure we're going to get in.
Man: Get back.
Let's get a cab.
Maybe you're right.
When we get out, don't
stop where the crowd is.
Just follow me right in.
When we get out, we just follow you in.
Jimmy: Yeah.
Why don't you put this on?
What?
Just until we get inside.
I don't get it.
We're all together.
Van!
Only him.
We're together. Come on, Van.
This is important.
These are my friends.
You can go in, but they'll have to wait.
Hey, nice coat.
Don't worry, Jimmy. We don't care.
I can't believe it.
Yeah, what an asshole.
You know, that had nothing to do
With you guys.
Van just wanted to put me in my place.
Apparently, it happens all the time.
Jerk.
It's happened to you before?
No, but it was overdue.
You know, none of us
really wanted to go anyway.
Yeah, we're exhausted.
No, I really wanted to go.
There's Jimmy Steinway.
I can't believe it...
He's already leaving?
You like him?
I could never be interested in anyone
Who worked in advertising.
Charlotte: God. You were right.
This place has gotten
really hard to get into.
Who's the other guy
you were interested in?
## Doctor's orders ##
## Say there's only ##
## One thing for me ##
Phew. Oh, god. We made it.
This is the last time I'm coming here.
I always want to be able to say,
"I got into the club."
Of course we got in.
Who was the second guy
you were interested in?
Tom Platt.
Oh, well, that's a lot better.
How do you mean?
Well, Tom Platt's
smart and somewhat cool,
A lawyer involved in
environmental causes...
Not to mention tall, dark, and handsome.
## Emotion every day ##
## A lovin' spoonful to be taken ##
## It's the only thing ##
## Stoppin' this empty heart of mine ##
## From breakin' ##
## Won't get better ##
## Till you're back ##
Man: Nina!
Please... stop!
Nina!
Please... stop.
Hey, McGrath!
Van: Come back here!
It's not what you think.
I'm...
I think I'm gay.
What?
That's not possible.
How?
It's always been there, I guess.
I've only begun to acknowledge it now.
You really think you're gay?
Taxi.
I was just starting law school
When the first up-tempo
Philadelphia international hits broke:
Some people don't
consider that disco...
Because
it's good...
But I remember feeling
absolutely electrified.
You feel electrified often.
No, but this was different.
I loved the idea that there'd be
All these great places
for people to go dancing,
After the terrible social wasteland
Of our college years. Uhff.
You've been to a lot of discos?
No. In fact, practically none.
For me, law school wasn't easy,
And I haven't had much of a social life
Since coming to the city, either.
But I still consider
myself a loyal adherent
To the disco movement.
It's a "movement"?
Sort of.
What I found terribly encouraging
Was the idea that when
the time in life came
To have a social life,
There'd be all these great places
For people to go to,
Because, as you'll remember,
For many years, there were none.
Yeah.
What I didn't realize...
is that it gets so
impossible to get into.
Man: Let's call it a night.
No, wait. I have an idea.
Man: Jimmy.
Here take this. Jimmy!
Take this. Jimmy!
Oh, hi.
Hi.
You're Des's friend.
Yeah, hi.
Where are Marshall and Steve?
They've gone back to the hotel.
Jim, come on.
I can't believe it.
Jim, let's go.
They wanted me to apologize for them.
They were really bushed.
What a disaster.
No.
I can't believe it.
Wow!
## Your body ##
## Your body, my body ##
## Everybody ##
## With nobody ##
Charlotte: Do you like nightmares?
No.
Well, I do.
It's not obviously connected, but...
I think that's what made
me a little more tolerant
Of the guys at Hampshire.
What do you mean?
You were a bit critical.
The guys there preferred
women more..."laid-back."
I'm laid-back.
For whatever reason,
You didn't have much
of a social life there.
I had a
social life...
Just not one of those
terrible pretend-marriages.
The Hampshire guys were jerks,
hippy-dippy suburbanites
with all this hair...
And extremely dim
intellectual interests.
I'm sorry, I don't
consider the guy who did
The Spiderman comics a serious writer.
Alice, one thing I've noticed
Is that people hate being criticized.
Everyone hates that.
It's one of the great
truths of human nature.
I think it's why my
parents got divorced.
I'm sorry... it's just
that you're so terrific...
It makes me sick to think
that you might get in
That terrible situation again,
Where everyone
hated you...
Hated me?
You're wonderful.
Maybe, in physical terms,
I'm a little cuter than you,
But you should be much
more popular than I am...
it would be such a shame
If what happened in
college repeated itself.
Why would it repeat itself?
You're right.
I just think it's so important
To be in control of
your own destiny...
Not to fall into that fifties cliché
Of waiting by the
phone for guys to call:
The right ones never do.
Those who do,
You have to make the most
ridiculous excuses to:
The nice ones get hurt
feelings and hate you;
The jerks inevitably corner you
Into going out anyway.
Late at night you find yourself
With some awful guy
with disgusting breath,
Thrusting his belly up against you,
Trying to stick his slobbering tongue
In your mouth. Ugh, yecch.
Thank god this is a
whole new era in music
And social models!
We're in complete control.
Look down.
There are a lot of choices out there.
## One night in a disco ##
## On the outskirts of Frisco ##
Fantastic. This place is better
Than I could have imagined.
It's too bad Steve and
Marshall didn't come...
They really would have loved this.
Don't worry about it. So what.
It's so stupid.
Charlotte: I'm sure it's Jimmy.
I think it's much better to wait
Until things happen naturally.
Forcing things never works.
That's not true.
Forcing things usually
works beautifully.
You know, even if he's in advertising,
Someone will want him.
I just think it's so important
That we be in control
of our own destinies.
Client: It doesn't matter.
Marshall's a really good guy.
He doesn't really care
about this kind of stuff.
I can't believe it.
Uh, excuse me...
has anyone ever told
you you look just like
Kate Preston's brother rod?
Who?
Rod Preston. Do you know him?
Uh, no.
Have you ever noticed that
people who look just alike
Never seem to know each other?
Hunh.
Hi.
Hey. How've you been?
Fine. How are you?
He's really depressed.
God, isn't this place great?
It's fantastic! I love it.
I really like this song.
Yeah.
Do you like to dance?
W-W-Would
you?
Sure. Great.
Shall we all go?
Client: I... I think he's
too depressed to dance.
Hey, Jimmy, we're
going to dance... come on.
I'm too depressed to dance.
Go ahead.
What's wrong?
Absolute disaster.
What?
I had to get some clients into the club,
So I gave the boss
my coat to wear...
"Here, wear this."
It's really stupid.
I can't believe what an idiot I am.
Why? Your coat's nice.
Well, that's just it: It is nice.
But this guy's...
Marshall's...
Clothes are hideous.
It's famous.
But to give him my
coat to put over them...
It's so stupid.
It's just really stupid.
It's not stupid.
This club's really hard to get into.
It was unbelievably, incredibly dumb.
He's a really nice
guy, and I insulted him.
This nice guy that I stupidly insulted
Is basically my boss.
God, it was really stupid.
Guess you're right.
It was pretty stupid.
Uh, can I get you a drink?
Yeah, thanks.
## If we lose our love ##
## It's a shame ##
## Ooh, wouldn't want ##
## To live with the pain ##
## Gonna take it ##
## Every night ##
Des, you're a wonderful man.
Take care of yourself, Des.
Ok, Van, what's up?
Keep that ad guy friend
of yours out of here.
Woman: Hi!
What do you mean?
When I turned him away
with a group of his clients,
He snuck around back,
where you let them in.
I didn't let 'em in.
They're inside.
Rick just saw them.
Is this really important?
I'm not out here on jerk patrol
So you can let them in the back way.
Bernie promised me he'd fire you
If that guy's in the club.
I can't believe that.
You made Bernie promise to fire me?
You really think Bernie
keeps his promises?
## Aw, freakout ##
## Lefreak ##
## Tres chic ##
## Freakout ##
## Aw, freakout ##
## Lefreak ##
## Tres chic ##
I need to see Bernie.
Bernie's not around.
He's pretty mad, Des.
Van told him you were letting people
In the back again.
When you let people in the back,
Is a cover being charged?
Because that money
should be coming here.
Of course we're not charging
a cover in the back. God!
## Big fun ##
## To be had by everyone ##
## It's up to you ##
## Sure they can be done ##
Uh, Bernie...
this thing that Van's saying
About your promising to fire me
If Jimmy Steinway's in the club,
That isn't true, is it?
No, it's true. I can confirm that.
This Jimmy Steinway,
I don't want in the club.
Why?
Come here.
## Aw, freakout ##
You promised to quit
letting friends in the back.
No, you said we could
still let in people
From the list.
Don't contradict me, Des.
I don't want a lot of
ad people in the club,
Particularly not this guy.
Well, I didn't let him in.
If Van didn't either,
he's not in the club.
Did I ever tell you that my first job
Was in
advertising... at Y&R?
In those days, the big thing
was to be nice to everybody...
To the secretaries, to
the "media department,"
To the art director,
to the client...
Well, I don't think it's that way now.
I don't care.
I don't want that element in the club.
Jimmy is, like, my best friend.
And you've been a good
friend to him, Des,
But this Jimmy is not
a good friend to you.
He's out of control.
He's an egomaniac.
Uh, Jimmy.
Where were you? What a nightmare?
Listen, I don't know how you got in,
But you'd better go.
What?
This way.
You're asking me to leave?
Van has gone crazy.
He made Bernie promise to fire me
If he found you here.
Bernie hates ad agency
people. It's nuts.
I can't believe it!
That's like something out of the Nazis!
Come on. I will get
you back on the list,
But tonight, it's best if you go.
Could I at least go tell my client
That I've
got to go...
No.
Please.
Tell him I got ejected.
His name is Hap.
Ok.
And that's for this irritating girl
Who's occupying my booth. Alice.
She's irritating?
I thought she seemed nice.
Jimmy: You know her?
Well, she's been here 2 times before.
How is she irritating?
I can't believe it.
You're really gonna throw me out?
Yeah.
Thanks, Des! You've really
been a good friend to me!
Hey.
Join us.
It's ok.
## Everybody dance ##
## Ooh, clap your hands ##
## Clap your hands ##
## Everybody dance ##
Josh: Think we'll get in?
Tom: This usually works.
## Everybody dance ##
Des, I think we need to talk.
Yeah... there's something I
have to talk to you about.
## Ooh, clap your hands ##
## Clap your hands ##
## Music ##
## Never lets you down ##
## Puts the smile on your face ##
## Any time, any place ##
## Dancin' helps relieve the pain ##
## Soothes the mind ##
## Makes you happy again ##
## Listen to those dancin' beats ##
## Close your eyes ##
## And let go ##
## It don't mean a thing ##
## If it ain't got that swing ##
##
Bopp-shoo-wop ##
## Everybody dance ##
## Ooh-ooh clap your hands ##
## Clap your hands ##
## Everybody dance ##
## Ooh-ooh clap your hands ##
## Clap your hands ##
## Everybody dance ##
## Ooh-ooh clap your hands ##
## Clap your hands ##
## Everybody dance ##
## Ooh-ooh clap your hands ##
## Clap your hands ##
## Spinning all around the floor ##
## It's as if sadness and despair ##
## Turns to life without a care ##
## Strutting to obey the dream ##
## At the top ##
## Always ends too soon ##
## It's got us dancing ##
Alice: Who's she?
They call her "tiger lady."
It's actually a cheetah
pattern she's wearing.
At some point, she wore a tiger pattern.
It's always something
very slinky and sexy.
You consider her sexy?
Ah, yeah.
The banquette.
Where's Jimmy?
I don't know. He went to get drinks.
What would you like?
Uh, vodka-tonic.
Me, too.
Hap: I'll go with you.
Des: Ever since I was 6 years old or so,
I sensed I was somehow...
different.
Then, every time
you made love to me...
You must have wanted to vomit.
No. No, no.
Oh, you're beautiful!
You don't have to be some sweaty, horny,
Hetero he-ape to admire
and... and appreciate...
female beauty...
only very, very recently
Did the final realization come.
Exactly when did the
final realization come?
2 days ago.
I get up late and
usually turn on the TV,
Sort of as a reflex.
Wednesday afternoon,
There was a rerun of wild kingdom,
Mutual of Omaha's nature
program with marlin Perkins
And that... attractive, younger guy.
It triggered something.
Suddenly everything fell into place.
I'm gay...
and always have been.
You only found out you were gay
On Wednesday?
Only then definitively.
Wednesday was...
gay day for me.
Finished eavesdropping?
I wasn't eavesdropping.
Come on. Anything interesting?
Shh. God!
Listen, it's much better
you're with Tom than Jimmy.
You two really look great together.
You think so?
It's too bad we weren't
closer friends in college.
I think I could really
have helped you there.
For most guys,
Sexual repressiveness is a turn-off.
You're saying this for my benefit?
You're a good conversationalist but...
there's something of
the kindergarten teacher
About you.
It's really nice, but...
the guys you like also tend
to be on the ethereal side.
It can get pretty far away
From any kind of physicality.
This is gonna sound
dumb, but it really works.
Whenever you can,
Throw the word "sexy"
into your conversation.
It's kind of a signal.
Like, um...
"there's something really
sexy about strobe lights."
Or, uh...
"this fabric is so sexy."
Yeah, it is.
## That you and I could
make it on through ##
## ## But somethin' went wrong
Des: Josh?
Uh, hi.
What are you doing here?
In New York or in the club?
In the city.
I'm an A.D.A. in Morgenthau's office.
An assistant district
attorney for Manhattan.
They call us "A.D.A.'s."
You're a prosecutor?
God, how did you get that?
It's not such a big deal...
I'm perfectly competent
to do the job, Des.
Great. Good.
I wasn't implying anything.
I was just surprised to see you here.
Going to Harvard must have been great.
Well...
the people at Hampshire were nice,
And pretty smart, in
a nontraditional way,
But I was out of place there.
I'm sorry, I don't consider the guy
Who did the Spiderman
comics a serious writer.
Yeah, I thought it was the green hornet
People took more seriously.
Um, excuse me, are you Alice?
Jimmy Steinway gave me this
vodka-tonic to give you,
But I'm afraid I sampled it.
I'll get you another.
Jimmy's gone?
You're "Hap"?
Yeah, he wanted me to
tell you he's sorry,
But he was ejected from the club.
He was ejected?
Apparently he snuck one of his clients
In the back of the club.
That's odd he knew
I drank vodka-tonics.
I never told him.
It's uncanny.
You mean, it's a complete cliché?
"All women recent college
graduates drink vodka-tonics,"
Or something like that?
Well, maybe.
So Jimmy think's I'm a total cliché
I ordered a vodka-tonic,
too... so what?
You're plenty original
Without having to
order some weirdo drink.
Yeah, I wouldn't worry about it.
Can I get you another?
Thanks. Actually, if you don't mind,
I think I'd prefer...
uh, uh, a whiskey sour.
Des: Ok.
## The tide is high ##
## But I'm rollin' on ##
## I'm gonna be your number one ##
## I'm not the kinda girl ##
## Who gives up just like that ##
You're going already?
It's really late.
I didn't peg you as such a nightcluber.
I mean, you really seem to like it.
I do. This is a great place.
It's what I always dreamed of...
cocktails, dancing,
conversation...
Exchange of ideas and points of view...
everyone's here...
Everyone you know
And everyone you don't know.
You should be proud, Des.
This is quite an accomplishment.
Yeah. I am.
Who's the girl you were dancing with?
Oh, Alice Kinnon.
Des: Oh.
Thanks a lot for getting me in.
Great.
I'm a little worried about that guy.
I think he might be having
A manic episode of some kind.
Now, Des, don't get started on that.
So you're one of the club's managers?
Yeah.
## Every girl wants you ##
## To be her man ##
## But I'll wait, my dear ##
You knew Tom would be
here tonight, didn't you?
God, you're much
craftier than I thought.
No, I didn't.
We're going to check
out this after-hours club
Jimmy told Hap about.
Why don't you come?
Jimmy might be there.
I don't know.
## But I'm rollin' on ##
## I'm gonna be ##
## Your number one ##
## Number one ##
We were all at Harvard together.
How did you get involved
with environmental causes?
I think that's great.
You're interested in the environment?
Very much so.
Actually, there's one theory
That the environmental
movement of our day
Was sparked by the re-release of Bambi
In the late 1950s.
For many members of the
baby boom generation,
It was traumatic...
the hunters killing Bambi's mother.
Yeah, it was terrible.
For 6-year-olds,
it's devastating.
To this day, no one wants to identify
With those hunters.
I think you're right.
You're living in some women's residence,
Aren't you?
Yeah. It's terrible.
No guests.
Huh.
Wow.
It's really nice.
Thanks.
Would you like anything to drink?
What?
Um...
could I have...
a pernod?
Sure.
This is supposed to be good
For cigarette mouth.
Do you smoke?
When I drink or go out at night,
I usually smoke.
I live dangerously.
On the edge.
I'm no kindergarten teacher.
What's this?
Um, I collect original edition
Scrooge McDuck comics.
It sounds a little odd.
Not at all.
This is original artwork by Carl barks,
Who created the uncle scrooge comics.
He's considered a bit of a genius.
There's something really
sexy about scrooge McDuck.
You really think so?
## Ooh ##
I love uncle scrooge.
## How do you like your love? ##
# ## But if you want to know #
## How I really feel ##
# ## Get the cameras rollin' #
## Get the action goin' ##
## Baby, you know ##
# ## My love for you is real #
## Take me where you want to ##
## Me and my heart, you steal ##
## More, more, more ##
## How do you like it?
How do you like it? ##
## More, more, more ##
## How do you like it?
How do you like it? ##
## More, more, more ##
## How do you like it?
How do you like it? ##
## Ooh ##
## How do you like your love? ##
Charlotte: "the author's brother is,
"According to Tibetan Buddhism,
"God.
Recommend..."
"Very kind decline."
Anything interesting?
Not really.
What time did you get back?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I didn't check.
Well, was it light or dark?
Why do you care what time I got in?
Sorry. No reason.
We've got to get an
apartment of our own.
Do you know how long it takes
To become an editor?
You mean associate editor.
Yeah. Associate editor.
What's the minimum amount of time
To become an associate editor?
How many years?
That's hard to say.
Approximately.
Maybe 4 years.
But more than years,
Before you can become
an associate editor,
You have to have a best seller.
How can you be sure
you'll get a best seller?
Zenia: You cannot.
But what if you don't find one?
You have to.
Show them the outline.
You might want to see this.
It's the Scott Meredith
best seller outline.
"Create sympathetic characters,
"With whom readers identify.
Give them problems,
make these problems big."
Could I photocopy this?
Yes, but I need it back.
I'd like a copy, too.
That stuff is such crap.
This does describe a
lot of best sellers.
That's true.
It's completely formulaic.
Of course it's
formulaic. It's a formula.
That's why I prefer nonfiction.
It's good you want to
be an editor so much.
In this era of television,
You are devoted to the printed word.
Actually, ultimately,
I'd like to work in television.
But right now, what I need's a raise.
Alice and I have been
looking at apartments,
But we can't afford one on
what we get as assistants.
That's so comical.
What?
That girls like you really
worry about paying rent.
Aren't your fathers heavily subsidizing
Your living expenses
with big allowances?
They're not big at all.
In a few years, you'll marry
Some incredibly rich corporate lawyers.
It's not as if you really
worry about paying the rent
Like the rest of us.
Oh, you worry about paying the rent?
Yeah.
Then you're way ahead of us
'Cause we don't even have an apartment.
What if, in a few years,
We don't marry some corporate lawyer?
What if we marry some meatball like you?
But not you personally,
But someone with similarly
low socioeconomic prospects?
Can you believe that?
They really think that way.
Disco sucks.
What a dope.
Would you ever go out
With anyone who worked in the company?
Fortunately,
There's absolutely no temptation.
Josephine: Charlotte, telephone.
It's a man.
Hello?
Oh, hi.
We were thinking of having
some people for dinner
Saturday night.
Wanted to know if you could come.
About 7:30.
Man: Ok. Where?
Actually, I'll have to
call you back with that.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Ok.
Bye.
That was Jimmy Steinway.
He's coming for dinner Saturday night.
You called him?
I thought you said you
could never be interested
In anyone who worked in advertising.
No one could say something
like that seriously.
It was obviously a joke.
Anyway, it's not like
it's a date or anything.
He's invited as part of a group.
It's really important
There be more group social life,
Not just all this ferocious pairing off.
You like Tom.
Invite him.
We don't even have an apartment.
How can we have a dinner party?
Well, it's another incentive to get one.
Does the Lexington avenue
express stop at 86th street?
I think so.
We'd better hurry.
Do you really think we
know each other well enough
To room together?
Well, maybe that's good.
It's not just that we
don't know each other well.
I'm not even sure we
really like each other.
That's ok.
You know, Alice,
I'm not so much of a
bitch as I might seem.
You'll find Holly's a little sensitive
About her intelligence.
She's dumb?
Harvard guys, even the ones that
Seem reasonably cool on the outside,
Are all essentially wimps and bookworms
On the inside.
They love being seen out
with this lovely girl,
But after a date or two,
Rather than risk rejection,
They pretend to drop her,
Going around complaining
about how dull she was.
Is she dull?
A little, but that's not the point.
Once you start worrying
about something like that,
You're lost.
Holly was devastated.
She stopped dating entirely,
And weekends either went home
Or just hung around the
library at pine manor.
What do you think you're doing?
Shove off, Mack!
Deviant!
Creep! Off!
So I wouldn't develop any illusions
About Harvard guys.
They can be amazing creeps, too.
Ah, there you are.
Hi.
Our friend still isn't here.
Sorry. I forgot which
way the numbers went
On the east side.
It's what's called a railroad apartment.
It's long and rather
narrow like a railroad car.
Each room opens directly onto the other.
It's very nice.
Agent: The closets are here.
This is the other bedroom.
The bathroom is back here at this end.
And the kitchen.
So to get to the bathroom
from the living room,
You have to clomp through both bedrooms?
Well, there are 2 outside doors,
So in theory,
You can use the exterior hall
To go between the kitchen
and the living room.
Huh.
Even with 2 roommates, the
layout is a bit awkward.
You can't afford something bigger?
We all work in book publishing.
Couldn't your parents help?
They already are.
So what do you think?
I think it's really nice.
Isn't the layout a bit awkward?
Well, I think we should take it.
Here you go.
It's good to see bourgeois girls
Building up a sweat.
Why is that good to see?
You live around here?
There was a guild
meeting at asphalt green.
A guild meeting?
The newspaper guild
is organizing clerical
And editorial staff for book publishing.
I'm supposed to organize our department.
Oh, my god. We're all
gonna lose our jobs.
You should support this.
You were just complaining
how lousy the pay is.
Are you rooming with them?
That's gonna be really tough.
Aren't we behind schedule?
Nope. This recipe's extremely fast.
Hello.
Uh, it's Dan.
Dan?
Hi. Come up.
Dan from your department.
I invited him.
Departmental Dan?
You know...
he went to Harvard.
So?
Yeah, I've got to meet
some clients at 10:00
And get them into the club.
Tom isn't coming?
If he does, he'll be very late.
Isn't this what they
call a railroad apartment?
Uh-huh.
People always say how terrible they are,
But it seems pretty nice.
Well, the layout's not so good.
It's amazing the little things in life
One doesn't appreciate
until they're missing,
Such as hallways.
These apartments were actually planned
In the last century as tenement housing
For working class families.
Now all the yuppie roommate combos
Are crowding them out.
Well...
that's just tough.
Fight!
Rumble!
Actually, I was thinking I'd go home.
What?
You should come.
I don't know.
I'm not really a disco type.
Well, who is?
I probably wouldn't get in anyway.
Of course you'll get
in. Holly's gorgeous.
## There's a new me comin' out ##
# ## And I just have to live #
## And I wanna give ##
# ## I'm completely positive #
## ## I think this time around
## I am gonna do it
like you never knew it ##
## ## Oh, I'll make it through
# ## The time has come for me
to break out of this shell #
## I have to shout ##
## That I am comin' out ##
## I'm comin' out ##
## ## I want the world to know
## I got to let it show ##
## I'm comin' ##
## I'm comin' out ##
Thanks, Jimmy.
Have fun, Jack, Harry.
Thanks a lot, Des. I
really appreciate it.
Fine, cool.
I'm starting to realize how
important eye contact is.
I can't talk to people in this thing.
They get nervous. They
don't know who I am.
Well, that's the point.
You think tonight would be a good time
To talk to Van?
Try to patch things up,
get a reprieve of some sort?
Uh, no.
My job's sort of on the line, Des.
And not all clients
will be such good sports
As Harry and Jack.
If it's a question of groveling,
I can do that.
Just point me in the right direction.
Shh! God!
Can I show you something?
Sure. What?
You know something
about banking, don't you?
Yeah. Manny Hanny used to be a client.
Manufacturers Hanover.
I know what Manny Hanny is.
Note...
no lock.
10 is the cover charge.
God. Paying a cover
charge to get into a club?
How humiliating.
That's your reaction?
Look at this.
Kind of worrisome, don't you think?
Yeah.
To me, shipping cash to Switzerland
In canvas bags
Doesn't sound honest.
To me, it suggests possible illegality.
Well, what are you gonna do?
Well, I'm not going
into that room anymore.
Alice: Uh, gimlet, please?
Domestic beer or bud?
Um... whiskey sour?
Excuse me.
You're Alice Kinnon, aren't you?
Yeah.
We met at that party in sag harbor,
Labor day weekend.
You were just coming
in as I was leaving,
And you asked me where the kitchen was.
Do you remember?
I do remember getting to the kitchen.
Uh, excuse us.
We're here sort of as a group.
If you don't mind?
Excuse me.
Why did you say that?
I didn't like the look of him at all.
Didn't you notice how
he was eyeballing you?
Creepy.
Frankly, I thought he
might've been the guy
That bothered me on the subway.
I'm sorry if I overreacted.
Poor guy.
It's no big deal.
That kind of thing happens all the time.
Anyway, you've got Tom.
## I don't wanna lose you ##
## This good thing ##
## That I've got ##
Hey.
I'm sorry I'm so late.
How did it go?
Fine.
You know, they closed the airport.
We had to land in Washington
Until LaGuardia reopened.
## Than any love I know ##
## Is like thunder ##
## Lightning ##
## The way you love me is frightenin' ##
## You better knock ##
## Knock ##
## On wood ##
## Baby ##
## Ooh ##
## Ooh ooh ooh ooh ##
## Baby ##
## Ooh ##
Do you remember the conversation we had
Labor day weekend?
Had a huge impact on me.
Really?
Jennifer and I had been talking all year
About either acknowledging
The permanence of our
relationship and marrying
Or finally just breaking up.
I had no idea you were
even dating anyone.
I thought you knew.
No. We've been together since college.
But the weekend after labor day,
We had this long talk.
Jennifer proposed a trial separation,
Which normally I'd have
considered ridiculous,
But I couldn't help thinking of you
And went along.
Out of some sort of
Residual loyalty to Jennifer,
I didn't call you immediately
And instead started coming to the club.
I'm not a very
good dancer, but...
No, you are.
I was also curious if
the sexual revolution
Went as far as everyone said it had.
But emotionally, I couldn't handle it.
I got so depressed, and...
when I saw you that night,
You were... a vision,
Not just of loveliness, but of...
virtue...
and sanity.
What?
I shouldn't talk about it.
I'll just end up sounding like an idiot.
No, what?
You're very sexy
And good-looking and modern and hot.
But what I was craving
Was a sort of sentient individual
Who wouldn't abandon her intelligence
To hop into bed with every guy she meets
In a nightclub.
Why... why is it that when people have
sex-with-strangers
on their mind,
Their I.Q. Just drops, like, 40 points?
All that affected
Sexy seductress slinking around?
And uncle scrooge is sexy?
I mean, my god, is there no limit?
No. That
was to...
Do you think I'm an idiot?
I'm so sick of all
the lies and nonsense!
Alice?
Alice, what's wrong?
What happened?
McGrath! Where is he?
I'd say it's definitely not a good idea
To approach Van tonight.
Man: There he is.
McGrath!
Drew McGrath.
You're out of here right now.
What?
Bernie. Bernie!
Where is he? Here he is.
Bernie, this guy's through.
What's going on?
We had a public safety
situation in the front.
This jerk comes out,
trying to make it worse.
Is this true?
Public safety situation?
Give me a break.
It was a joke. I'm sorry.
We had a public safety situation.
The cops came. It was no joke.
I tease him a tiny bit.
No teasing, Des.
No teasing?
Either he goes or I do.
Come on, Van. Des, grow up.
Cut it out.
Ok. Sorry.
It's the ad guy.
So, it's the dancing ad man.
You're finished.
Ok, I work in advertising.
Is that a crime?
What's happening in this country?
Man: There they are! Get 'em!
Get the tin man. Get him.
Get this jerk out of the club.
You're fired, Des. You're out of here.
You can't fire me, Van.
Only Bernie can fire me.
Ok.
You're fired.
And take this yuppie scum with you.
Van: Good riddance!
Yuppie scum?
In college, before dropping out,
I took a course in the
propaganda uses of language.
One objective is to deny
other people's humanity
Or even right to exist.
In the men's lounge,
Someone scrawled "kill yuppie scum."
Do yuppies even exist?
No one says, "I am a yuppie."
It's always the other
guy who's a yuppie.
I think for a group to exist,
Somebody has to admit to be part of it.
Of course yuppies exist.
Most people would say you
two are prime specimens.
We're not yuppies!
You think we're yuppies?
You're seriously saying
you're not yuppies?
No.
Yuppie stands for "young
upwardly mobile professional."
Nightclub flunky is not
a professional category.
Contrary to popular belief,
junior-level ad jobs
don't pay well at all.
I wish we were yuppies:
Young, upwardly mobile, professional.
Those are good things, not bad things.
Where we going?
Rex's. Oh, no.
What's wrong with Rex's?
Well, you can't dance there,
And it's full of boring preppies.
Oh, and we're so interesting.
You can dance at Rex's.
Yeah, but why Rex's?
Why not some other place?
Well, for one thing,
Everyone at the club
knows that I go there,
So when they come looking for me,
I wanna be there.
Why would they come looking for you?
What happened tonight was a mistake,
Which even now Bernie's
probably very much regretting.
He's a smart guy.
Not without good qualities...
even if very few.
I wouldn't be very surprised
if he's already called Rex's
To retract my dismissal.
How can you be so sure of that?
Well, I'm not sure of it.
## Opportunity ##
## Whoa, opportunity ##
## ## Yeah, yeah, baby
## Opportunity ##
## Whoa, opportunity ##
Hey. Hey, Rex.
Welcome to Rex's.
Alice, you look like you've seen
The dark side of the moon.
What did Tom say?
No. I feel much better.
I love your idea of
social life as a group,
Without all this ferocious pairing off.
I couldn't have stood
being alone tonight.
I thought Bernie was smarter than that.
What a blunder.
When they do call, we'll
get you immediately.
Thanks, Rex.
Rex is such a great guy.
Yeah. Charlotte says she can
tell if a guy's gay or not
Just by looking in his eyes.
How?
Maybe it's related to
how they look at you.
It's hard to define,
But I think women can tell.
I can't.
Are Jimmy or I gay?
Come on, don't.
Jimmy?
No.
Well, not your eyes,
But you do have a gay mouth.
A gay mouth?
I have a gay mouth?
What does that mean?
Just what I said.
It's true, Des. Your
mouth does look gay.
God! How moronic can you get?
What nonsense!
Don't think I don't know your whole act.
Excuse me?
Pretending to be gay
To get sympathy from women
While cruelly dumping them,
And to seem cooler
than you actually are.
I despise your whole pathetic act.
You're not fit to lick the boots
Of my real gay friends.
Well, I don't want to lick the boots
Of your real gay friends.
You know, I could be gay.
I see through you completely.
Oh, you see through me completely.
Yeah, I do.
That's the dark side of feminism.
Charlotte: What?
You have a kind of free pass
to make any kind of wounding
Or derogatory comment you want.
I am hardly a militant feminist.
No, you're not.
A militant feminist
would be a lot fairer.
It's women like you
whose attitudes to men
Are so dehumanizing.
Like what?
That men are swine,
Obsessed with large breasts
And the sex act,
Devoid of any idealistic
or romantic sensibility
When in fact,
We have that idealistic sensibility
In spades.
For instance, you have no idea
What men really think
about women's breasts.
What do men think about women's breasts?
Well, it's not something
you just blurt out.
It's far more complicated
and nuanced than that.
Ok, I'll tell you a story.
When I was in college,
There was a girl I had a crush on
Who always had older boyfriends,
Invariably some senior.
Finally, they all graduated,
And one night we went
back to her room alone.
Suddenly, her shirt was off,
And I was confronted with these breasts,
Which turned out to be
completely surprising
And frankly, disconcerting.
They were rather large and not ugly
Or especially strange-shaped,
But in all the time that
I had thought about her,
These breasts had never figured.
She took off her shirt so quickly,
There was no time for adjustment,
And I said something arrogant about it,
As if her abrupt unveiling
of her largish breasts
Was somehow going to
slay my swinish male self,
As if I hadn't already been slayed
On a much higher level.
Her name was Alice, too.
Oh, come on, Des.
You know that's not true.
What do you mean, it isn't true?
Her name wasn't Alice.
Well, I'm not gonna use her real name.
Would you like to dance?
Do you mind?
## When you wear your high ho boots ##
## With your hip-hugger suit ##
## Huh, it's all right ##
## You're outta sight ##
If what's bothering you relates to Tom,
I wouldn't take it personally.
Did you know Tom and Jennifer
Had a trial separation,
Which was to end tonight?
What you might not know
Is that about a week ago,
They started seeing
each other on the sly,
Cheating on their trial separation.
How do you know that?
Working at the club,
You find out all kinds of things.
You know, this is the way
people used to dance in bars
In the old days.
Do people ever really dance in bars?
I thought that was a myth.
People my older brother's
age, uh, they did.
Your brother must be a lot older.
Before disco,
This country was a dancing wasteland.
You know the Woodstock
generation of the 1960s
That were so full of themselves
And conceited?
None of those people could dance.
Huh.
## I'm crazy 'bout you ##
## Now go ##
## Now with your bad self ##
Alice: What happened over there?
I think she noticed
That, for a moment, I flinched.
She dropped me like a rock.
I was crushed.
I couldn't take it, so I dropped out
And got in the night
club business early,
Thanks to which
I probably owe my success today.
Charlotte: Let's share a cab.
We're thinking of going.
You're all going?
Yeah.
Have they called yet from the club?
I don't think they will call.
Bernie will probably send some emissary.
That's more his style.
What should we do with the oz costumes,
Just, uh, bring 'em
by the club tomorrow?
Actually, those costumes are mine.
Just get 'em back to me when you can.
I thought we were here as a group.
You talked about the
tremendous importance
Of group social life.
Well, it's really late.
Yeah, Alice, it's getting really late.
We'd better get going.
Hey, thanks again, Des.
Ciao.
Des: Bye.
Dan: Bye.
All week Charlotte's been talking about
The tremendous importance
of group social life,
Opposing all this ferocious pairing off.
Well, group social life has its place,
But at a certain point,
Other biological factors come into play.
Our bodies weren't really designed
For group social life.
A certain amount of pairing off
Was always part of the original plan.
God, I can't believe you'd say that.
What?
What did I say?
What you mean to say is
that they've all gone back
To screw their brains out?!
No, I didn't say that!
I said they were going to pair off.
Well, wait, don't go!
I didn't mean to say anything
Anyone could be offended by.
Oh, thank god. He's here.
Des, Bernie regrets what happened.
It was a mistake, and he wants you back.
I'm sorry. I know why you're so upset.
I mean,
I know what really happened with Tom.
What?!
That he thought
You were really slutty or something.
That's so stupid!
You can't worry about
what misinterpreters think!
That's so unfair!
Come back to my place. We should talk.
Nothing will happen!
I just need somebody to talk to.
Maybe you do, too.
89th and first.
Hi.
## Sexy baby ##
## Good-lovin' daddy ##
## Ooh ##
## Let me be your rockin' chair ##
## Just a-rock me away from here ##
## Let's get it on ##
## Come to me, baby... ##
Alice, what would your
dream book to publish be
If you could publish any book?
Anything that might become a bestseller.
Aside from that. Your dream book.
I'd say... a collection of
new J.D. Salinger stories,
But more in the direction
of the laughing man
Or raise high the roof beam, carpenters,
Nothapworth 16 Orseymour:
An introduction.
Did you know that, in his own day,
Mary McCarthy and Alfred Kazin
Wrote devastating pieces on Salinger?
No.
Yeah. They really destroyed him.
## Sexy baby ##
## Good-lovin' daddy ##
## Ooh ##
## Let me be your rockin' chair ##
## Just a-rock me away from here ##
## Let's get it on ##
## Come to me, baby ##
## Ooh ##
## Let me be your rockin' chair ##
## Just a-rock me away from here ##
## Rock me gently ##
## Make me feel like
a cloud in the sky... ##
Dan: Maybe we should go
the outside way like Alice.
Holly: I'm sure it was Jimmy.
It's very quiet.
Charlotte: Get out! Get out!
Dan: That was pretty bad.
Holly: God!
What's the matter now?
What?
All the
noise...
Clomping around, banging pans.
Sorry. I didn't realize it.
You obviously intended it.
What do you mean?
That's very aggressive.
You don't clomp around, banging pans
For no reason.
Like what reason?
You know perfectly well.
Because I only bang pans?
Well, frankly, that's not what I heard.
Ok. Anything I did that was wrong,
I apologize for.
But anything I did that was not wrong,
I don't apologize for.
God, Alice is such a Scorpio.