OK.
Jackson came over to play.
Superheroes!
I was Black Power Ranger.
He was Batman.
Jake, are you OK in there, buddy?
I'm OK.
Can I ask you a question?
OK! Time to hit the sack.
- An important question.
- There we go, big guy. Come on.
- Can I wear bugs?
- Bug pyjamas... are all the way downstairs.
But fire trucks are here.
- Bugs.
- Fire trucks.
- OK, bugs.
I'll be right back.
Does it hurt to be dead?
- Animal.
- What did I do now?
- Can I tell him?
- If you wanna die.
- Well, your beer-addled sperm still work.
- Lisa!
- You impregnated my sister again.
- Bitch!
- I thought you wanted me to?
- I said "Don't"!
The kid could have been born
before he'd notice.
- You're not pregnant.
- I feel "Congratulations" is more appropriate.
- You told her before you told me.
- She's a witch!
She took one look at me and guessed.
Say something!
Bummer.
Something else!
So... she's six weeks pregnant.
That means the baby's due in April, May,...
...June. Gemini. That's cool.
Einstein was a Gemini.
- So's that Scottish gal from Garbage.
- Will you go help Jake with his pyjamas?
- If she's late...
- Lisa, I swear to God,...
...start with the Dionne Warwick stuff,
I'll throw you out the fuckin' window.
- So please help him with the pyjamas.
- Love you, too, Tom!
Hey, this is great. I mean it.
It's about time we had another kid.
I was gonna bring it up myself.
- Really?
- Absolutely!
- This time, you gotta take some time off.
- Please! We can't afford that!
- We can. I'm gonna hit the overtime again.
- I don't want you to work those hours again.
You come home in a trance.
You're completely useless to me.
I'm gonna be fine, OK?
I'm just gonna tell Teddy
to get somebody else for the thing.
- Oh, God! Oh, Tom!
- What?
I'm sorry. I completely forgot.
No wonder you're pissed off.
I'm not pissed off. I just...
No, I'm... I'm not. I'm not.
I'm a grown man. I shouldn't be screwing
around with some shitty band anyway.
Hey, look, I-I... I gotta go change.
You know, put on something cool.
I love you.
I'm... I'm a happy guy.
You know, I'm not gonna be a lineman
forever, I promise you that.
Whaddaya mean?
I clip... clip wire all day.
A monkey could do it.
Yeah, but they're gonna
move you into the office soon.
No, I meant, when we first got together, I said
a lotta stuff about what I was gonna be,...
...and I just wanted you to know that, uh...
I wasn't giving you some kinda line,...
...that I meant it.
I didn't marry you because I thought
you were gonna be famous.
I just liked the way your ass looked in jeans.
I never wanted to be famous. I just, uh...
I didn't expect to be... so...
What?
I don't know.
Ordinary.
Shhh.
Hang on! Hang on!
You know, I hope it's a girl.
I'm kinda sick of all these balls
around the house. Except for yours, babe.
What are the odds on an educated single man
being at this thing?
And I don't mean a GED!
- Does it matter if he's on the boner pill?
- I wouldn't look a gift-boner in the mouth.
Nice - that's very nice, Lisa!
- Hey! How you been?
- Hey, Tom, Tom, Tommy! How ya doin'?
Oh, you would not believe the day I had.
- Take this. I'll get another.
- Thanks.
- Harry.
- Tom. Taking care of the place for me?
We're drilling holes all over your floors!
I hope you don't mind.
Tom, you know my squaw Sheila.
Bobby, Vanessa.
- Thanks for having me.
- Drink up! Take your medicine.
Tom, how do you like the neighbourhood?
I grew up in Bridgeport,
so it's not like it's a foreign country.
You're goddamn right.
This is the best neighbourhood in Chicago.
We all look out for each other. That's
saying a lot as we approach the year 2000.
- Are you running for mayor?
- Hey, did any of you guys...
- ...see them crank dealers...
- What is Lenny doing here?
Bobby, did you tell him you had a party?
- Vanessa made me. We invited everybody.
- To actually invite this jack- off...!
Oh, yeah, laugh it up!
When you wake up dead with your throat cut,
don't come crying to me!
Not attracted to.
Not drunk enough for.
Frightened by!
Argh!
Don't touch me. I'm fine.
Haven't you heard about people being
operated on when they're under hypnosis?
Yeah, but I don't believe in any of that.
People who say they were hypnotised
were just playing along.
- Certo.
- Really?
Then how could they have a scalpel stuck
into their throat without even bleeding?
- Bullshit!
- You never saw that happen!
- That's bullshit!
- Learn another word!
Yeah, what about "narrow-minded"?
I saw a guy in my class get a two-inch needle
stuck into his arm by my instructor...
- ...when he was under hypnosis.
- Horseshit! That better, honey?
I saw a picture of it the next day.
It left a mark.
What I don't understand is
how a person that's been to college...
...can believe all that superstitious crap.
- It isn't superstitious!
- Come on!
- I'm practically a licensed hypnotherapist.
- "Practically"?
Isn't that like saying
"I don't have a licence"? Ow! My arm!
This may come as a surprise to you, but just
because you lived here for your whole life...
...doesn't mean that there isn't
a whole larger world out there,...
...doorways you haven't even opened, things
you wouldn't have any understanding of.
Doorways... OK, OK. All right, Kreskin,
prove it - hypnotise somebody.
- Yeah! Do me.
- No.
- Why not?
- For one, you're hostile.
I'm not hostile!
Do I seem hostile to anybody?
- Uh... yeah.
- Thanks for having us. It was a great party.
Nah, nah, this is just getting good.
Come on, Lisa. Hypnotise me. Come on!
- No. You're drunk.
- I'm not drunk!
You're not supposed to mesmerise
somebody who's been drinking!
Mesmerise! No! Stop!
Oh, please! I'm begging you.
Educate the savages.
It won't work with
that kind of uncooperative attitude.
I swear to you, I'll follow
every instruction to the letter.
It still won't work.
Come on.
What's the worst that can happen?
- Somebody turn out the lights.
- Oh, yeah!
Whoo!
All right, just relax. Put your arm down.
Just rest it comfortably. Just lean back.
Just be very comfortable and relaxed.
Trust me. OK?
- Close your eyes.
- Certainly, Lisa.
Now... just listen for a moment.
Listen to the sounds of the room around you.
I don't know why, but I'm scared.
Now I want you to pretend
you're in a theatre.
A movie theatre,
You're the only one there.
It's one of those great old movie palaces.
When you look around,
it's a huge, empty theatre.
You notice that the walls of the theatre
are painted in black.
The seats... are covered in black.
And in the whole pitch-black theatre,...
...there's only one thing you can see,
and that's the white screen.
You'll notice there are letters on the screen...
tall, thick, black letters.
But they're out of focus, so you drift closer
to them in your chair, trying to read them.
You're very comfortable now.
It's your favourite chair.
You're drifting closer and closer,
staring at the letters.
Very relaxed now. Your legs are relaxed.
Your arms are limp and heavy.
You're almost close enough
to read the letters now.
They start to come into focus.
The letters spell "sleep".
Sleep.
No!
- What the hell was that?
- What? What? What?
- Are you OK? You had to be faking it.
That was the weirdest goddamn thing
I've seen in my life!
Congratulations, Tom!
You're one of the lucky eight percent!
- You still have tears on your cheeks.
- What the hell did she do to me?
- Christ, I'm thirsty.
- Whaddaya mean? What eight percent?
There's only eight percent of the population
that's, like, highly hypnotisable.
Almost anybody can go under a little,...
...but not way under -
not freaky under, like he did.
- How's your hand?
- Whaddaya mean?
I stuck a safety pin in your hand and asked
you to bleed on one side, but not the other.
- Which I can't believe you did!
- You were very cooperative.
It was a side of you I hadn't seen before.
- That happened?
- You said it didn't hurt.
To hell with the pin!
I wanna know more about your Joey Luca.
Yeah, right!
- Who?
- Joey Luca is the kid who...
...used to pound the shit out of you
when you were 12.
You told us all about it. You were crying.
It was hysterical!
- Shut up.
- It was very moving, Tom.
Joey Luca! Jesus Christ,
I haven't thought about him...
Hey.
Can we go home? I... I feel kinda strange.
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Close your eyes.
Uh!
What's the matter?
Don't stop.
- Don't stop.
- OK.
Ugh! Jesus Christ! Oh, my God!
- What?
- I-I... I'm seeing things.
What do you mean?
Oh, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
I-I can't right now.
- Then you were faking it extremely well.
- Ohh...
Wait. Stop, stop, stop! It's too weird.
Baby, that wasn't weird.
I could show you weird.
I felt like I was being attacked.
Thanks!
I'm sorry, I didn't...
I didn't...
I-I... I'll be right back.
What the fuck...?!
Ah... Agh... Agh!
Arghhh...
Argh!
Agh! Agh!
- Hey, Jake.
- You're awake now, Daddy.
Are you OK?
Yeah. Yeah, I guess.
I just don't feel so good right now.
Don't be afraid of it, Daddy.
- What was it, then? An hallucination?
- Yeah, a bunch of 'em.
It's like all these thoughts just kept coming.
You believe this? I got seven calls.
Well, if it never happened before,
it had to be the hypnosis.
I had this headache and I was thirsty as hell.
Jake! I know you're not watching
that monster tape again!
Who was the woman?
I don't know. Maybe somebody I was just
remembering. She didn't look familiar.
- Did you fuck her?
- You gotta be kidding.
No. I mean, was she someone
you used to go out with?
You're jealous of my hallucination?
Hmm, you are pregnant!
- You should call Lisa.
- No, she's the one that fucked up my brain.
- Then she has to unfuck it.
- Ooh! Agh! Fuck! Fuck!
Don't swear so much!
Hang on, hang on!
Let me get my bearings here.
I have... I have absolutely no caffeine
in my system, you know.
OK. You're asking me if I gave you a post...
...posthypnotic suggestion.
Did you leave anything else behind
when you were inside my brain?
- Nothing!
- Tell the truth, Lisa.
Tom! Please, this is insulting.
You know, I have done this before.
OK, good. I-I was... I was just making sure.
It was just a harmless one anyway.
- What?
- Did it actually work?
- What did you say?
- I don't wanna tell you. You're grouchy.
Lisa, I swear to God...!
Well, you know I've always said I think
you need to be a little more open-minded?
- Yeah...
- So I just said that.
"After you wake up, your mind will be
completely open, like an open door,...
...open to receive everything around you."
- What's that supposed to do?
- Fuck if I know! I never said it before.
- Why? Did something happen?
- Jesus Christ!
Relax. OK? I opened a door, that's all.
You know, therapists do it all the time.
It releases repressed memories,
whatever you got back there.
- For you, it was probably old Mannixreruns.
- I gotta get back to work.
OK. Alrighty, then!
No! No more calls for Lisa!
Hey, Lise, it's me.
Call me when you wake up. Is there any way
you could baby-sit for us on Friday?
I did! I told him!
What's your name?
OK.
...but then I gotta hear about it for a month.
I called everyone who could possibly do it
and no one's free.
- Call Vanessa.
- Huh?
I said, call Vanessa and ask her about Debbie.
Anyway, call me back. Bye.
Debbie? That's the girl
who baby- sits for them?
Yep.
Oh, great idea. Pray she's free.
- How'd you know about Debbie?
- Samantha told me.
Hey, Vanessa.
Are you guys going out Friday night?
Hi. I'm Debbie.
Kozak...?
Tom Witzky.
- Hi, Debbie. I'm Maggie.
- Hi.
Thanks for coming. Jake's asleep already
and he hardly ever wakes up.
A band could play in his room
and he wouldn't hear it!
His room's upstairs, kitchen's back there.
Just help yourself if you want anything.
Here, have a seat.
This is the baby monitor.
It's on B in his room,
so you should hear everything.
- You wanna watch a movie?
- I got a book.
It shouldn't be later than midnight,
if that's OK.
- Perfect.
- Great. I'll just grab my coat.
Hel-lo!
Ready?
- Yeah. Just about.
- OK.
Hey. Uh... where'd you find that girl Debbie?
Vanessa gave me her number.
Everybody uses her. It's cool.
- Another headache?
- Too much caffeine.
Oh. OK, let's go.
Bye.
I think that Damon kid
is doing a great job and everything,...
...and yeah, the kid's got a decent arm,
but high-school football is about...
...power, it's about running the goddamn
football - it always has been.
What did you play in high school?
- Piano, mostly.
- Oh, Jesus! Sorry. Here, you want some?
Anyway, Adam...
and I admit that I am biased,...
...but my kid is having a helluva season
and it's like nobody even notices.
If they gave him the ball,
he could break a thousand yards!
And that's in an eight-game season.
Jesus Christ!
Why don't you just lick 'em
when they walk by?
Frank says the average guy carries around
a hard- on two hours out of every day.
- Three for him.
- See, now I got a picture of that!
One of these days, she's gonna find
one of my .38s and pop a cap in my ass!
He'll stick it in a bowl of soup
if it's still warm.
Go! Go!
- Are you OK?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
Over a thousand yards,
we're talking college scholarship!
Hey, come on...
The kid can write his own ticket.
And that's good for everybody. It's good
for the whole goddamn neighbourhood.
He's gonna go a helluva lot further
than lever did.
Look at the quality of tail he gets. He passed
me in that department when he was 14.
Come on! While we're young, huh?
You scared me!
She's downstairs, I think.
I don't know.
I haven't seen her yet.
Jake?
- What's the matter?
- Something's wrong.
What?
I have a secret to tell you.
Promise, promise, promise?
Samantha says it's always dark where she is.
Who did you say?
Samantha.
You... you talked to Samantha?
Yeah!
When?
All the time.
- Where?
- Here. In my house.
That's not true.
Go.
Go!
- It isn't true.
- I don't tell lies!
Samantha was here? Here, in your house?
- You're hurting my arm!
- Was she here?!
- Let go of me!
- Come on, you're coming with me. Let's go.
She's taking him away.
Put me down! Put... me... down!
Tom!
Jake!
- What the hell...?
- She took him.
- What?!
- The fucking baby-sitter.
Oh, my God!
He's... He's not in there.
- Where are you going?
- I don't know!
He's in there.
- Jake!
- Daddy!
- That's him!
- Wait! Where do you think you're going?!
Take it easy! Stop! Stop!
Take it easy. Take it easy.
- Gimme my kid.
- Tell me where she is! No!
You tell me where she is!
- Keep your hands off her!
- Hey! Hey, hey! Everybody shut up!
- Are you OK?
- That girl kidnapped our son.
- Is that your child?
- Ask about Samantha.
I'm asking about the boy,
who doesn't look like he's yours!
I can explain this.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to her.
- Is that boy your child?
- No.
She was baby-sitting for us. We never...
What you've done is a felony.
You can go to jail for this!
- Where were you taking him?
- I wasn't taking him anywhere!
- Then why did ya bring him here?
- I wanna press charges.
She came here because of me.
I'm her mother.
- Her mother?
- When are you gonna ask about Samantha?
- Who?
- My oldest daughter. She ran away.
No, she was kidnapped,
and the little boy said he saw her!
We haven't heard from her in a long time.
We filed a police report.
- Nobody returns our phone calls.
- Jake said he talked to her.
He said Samantha is in their house.
Is that her?!
- Stay away from him.
- Look at the picture.
- Let go of me!
- This is ridiculous.
- Will you look at the picture, please?
- I have never seen her before in my life.
- What about you?
No. I'm sorry. I've never seen her.
- No... No. No, they're lying!
- You wanna file charges?
- Yes!
- No.
- What?
- Come on, let's just, uh... forget about it.
Let's go home.
Are you nuts? What about
the next people she baby-sits for?
It was her. Samantha.
That girl in the picture,
she's the same girl I saw on our couch.
See, why... Why did you ask that girl Debbie
to baby-sit for us? Why her?
I couldn't find anybody else.
I was on the phone and Jake said...
Jake? Do you remember the other day
when we were talking in the kitchen?
I was looking for a baby-sitter, remember?
You said Samantha told you about Debbie.
Do you remember that?
Mommy's asking you a question, bud.
Is Samantha someone
who talks to you sometimes, Jake?
- Can you remember...
- Don't ask the boy any more questions.
Talk to me.
- What did you say?
- Huh?
Jake. W-what did you say just now?
- Nothing.
- Let me hear that voice again.
- Come on. Say it again. Use that voice again.
- Tom!
Come... Come on, Jake. Come on.
Use the voice again.
- Tom!
- Make the voice again, Jake. You can do it.
- Tom, don't!
- How do you...
- Tom, please!
- It's all right! It's all right!
- OK!
- What are you doing? Hey! Hey!
I'm talking to him!
- Hey, what's the matter with you?
- What do you think?
Well, I... I'm just trying
to have a conversation with my kid.
A perfectly normal conversation
for a five-year-old!
- Don't be afraid of it.
- Why the hell not?
I don't know. That's what he told me.
This is where it happened.
This is where I saw her.
- You're different. You feel different.
- I leaned back and there she was. She's 18.
- Longish hair. Is that what you saw?
- I wish you...
- Maggie, please!
- God!
Or... or maybe you don't see her, huh?
You just hear her? Is that what it is?
- Tom, stop it!
- I need to find a way to make her come back.
- Maybe if I hang out here long enough,...
- I'm talking to you!
...maybe she'll come back. Maybe
you could talk to her. Help me out here.
- Hey, come on! Hey! What's the problem?
- Knock it off!
I don't wanna talk about this
because it scares Mommy.
- Turn it up, man.
- What?
Turn it up. Up!
Tom is looking especially together today.
He grunted a very pleasant greeting
at me, actually.
He's becoming sort of monosyllabic.
Nothing wrong with that guy.
Nothing a little lithium couldn't cure!
- I'm a jerk. I'm sorry.
- No...
Are you OK?
Over there! In the door!
If you live on the base,
your room and board's covered.
- You still gotta get up early.
- I'll retire, make a coupla down payments.
When I take off the uniform,
I'm a landlord already.
Five years later, I got three houses.
- Hey. Hey, Har.
- How're ya doin'?
Whaddaya know
about that girl Samantha Kozak?
Samantha Kozak. Why do I know that name?
Brownish hair, 16 or 17 years old.
Used to live around here.
- Oh, yeah, yeah. I remember her, I think.
- Let's go.
Hey, Kurt! Come here for a second.
Like he ever tells me anything, right?
Get over here!
Say, you know that Kozak girl?
- Uh... Debbie.
- No, no, no, the other one. Samantha.
Oh, you mean the retard.
Yeah, she ran away.
Yeah, that's right. I remember that.
So, what about her?
Oh, I... I just been thinking about her a lot.
Why?
Her sister baby-sat for us.
Oh.
This is the first time
he's been out in a week.
He hasn't gone to work.
He sleeps 12 hours a night.
He's used up all his sick days. If he doesn't
show up on Monday, they'll dock him. I...
I can't get him more than six feet
from the couch.
- Why?
- That's where she appeared to him.
Ah.
I'm not shocked that there's another woman.
Of course, the fact that she's dead
gives one pause.
We are talking about a ghost here,
aren't we, Maggie?
She took off, uh... last March.
With a black guy, I think.
Hey, Harry. Did she ever live in our house?
No, no, no. I just... I just bought that one.
You're the first tenants.
Tom and Jake, it's like they have
this private club or something.
They sit in the living room and whisper,
and, as soon as I walk in, they both shut up.
You know what you need to do? Find a
young priest with smouldering good looks...
...who can guide you through this.
I'm kidding, but I'm not.
Look, I give Tom a lotta shit, but the truth is,
you guys are the best couple on earth.
This is on you now, Maggie. Get some help.
Find out why this is happening.
There is a reason.
You won't be the first woman who's
had to hold an insane family together.
Tom's not crazy.
Oh, yes he is. But at least
he's getting interesting.
Sports flash! Sports flash!
211 yards rushing on Friday night.
That's a total of 894 yards,
with two games to go.
The kid needs 106 yards. That's 53 a game.
He could walk through the next two games
and still break a thousand!
- Frank, what about you? Do you know her?
- Who?
Tom was asking about that Kozak girl
from over by Baldwin.
- You remember: the one who ran away?
- The retard.
Shut up, Lenny. Don't use that word.
- He's just kinda slow.
- What? Retard?!
Goddammit, Lenny,
shut your fuckin' pie hole!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Heads up!
- What are you doing?!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Somebody's always gotta ruin it.
They can't ever just be nice.
Frank. What are you doing here?
They're gonna kill you, Tommy.
You and Maggie both.
Why would you
say something like that, Frank?
This is a decent neighbourhood.
Hey, are you OK?
Where's Sheila? Is she at home?
Listen, I'm gonna go see if Sheila's at home.
OK?
In the house! Come on, both of you!
Come in!
Hi. Is your mom at home cos your dad's...
Hey... you wanna see what I've got?
Sure.
That's great. Is that one of your dad's?
Not today. Come here.
Oh, why don't you just
put the gun away, Adam?
- Come on, man. Come here.
- Those things make me kinda nervous.
- Then this will make you really nervous.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! Don't do that!
Don't!
Argh!
Please don't be under there.
Oh, boy.
Frank?
In the house! Come on, both of you!
Adam!
Adam! Open the door!
Oh, my God. Oh, God!
Help!
Am I awake... or asleep?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God, my baby!
- Hold on. Hold on.
- Let me... Let me go!
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- Is he alive? Is he alive?
Oh, my God, Adam!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Adam! Adam!
I'm gonna take him for a walk or something.
- Come on, sweetie pie. Let's get your jacket.
- Where are we going?
Ha-ha!
- Well! Hello, there!
- Well, hello... there.
Listen! Music!
It's beautiful!
Hey! Jake, wait up!
I don't think we're supposed to be here,
sweetie. Come on, let's go. This way.
Whoa! This place is cool!
Come on, honey. Let's go get some lunch.
Mom! What's this thing?
- I don't know. Let me take a look.
- It looks like some kinda stone.
- Either that, or it's a medal.
- Yeah, I think it is.
- "Served in the..."
- Look. A flag.
- Everything OK?
- It's fine. Just fine.
- We're not supposed to be here?
- Hm?
- Oh, no. It's fine. Really.
- Oh.
OK. See you later.
The boy's got the eyes on him, doesn't he?
X-ray.
Not you, though.
Possibly Daddy?
They're not the only ones.
Tell Daddy to come by and see me
a little later tonight.
He might learn a few things.
Bye, Jake.
Bye, Neil.
His name is Neil.
Try that, Daddy.
Why do I know that song?
I'll be home right after the movie.
I know it. I know it!
I said, I won't be late.
OK.
Bye, Mom. Bye, Maggie.