It's about that time, man.
Here.
Let's go. Bay one.
That's a pulse.
Code three.
It's an involuntary admission, okay?
Okay, we're gonna intubate this guy.
And fix the hole in his heart.
Got it.
Looks tight.
Pressure's holding.
Okay, call CT Surgery, tell them
they got a sick one coming up.
Here you are, Natasha,
right over my shoulder.
I certainly am.
Natasha, is you?
Boris, how could you
mistake me for a possum?
I help it if you
put on weight?
Where's the bedroom?
This is your bedroom.
And your kitchen, your
dining room, your study.
It is real
New York living.
And there's a bonus.
The view is amazing.
Go ahead.
This is a great view?
Interested?
Hello?
Excuse me?
Hi.
Um, someone called
about a rental here?
It's not ready yet.
Well, could I see it?
You're looking at it.
Oh.
I can't afford this.
It's thirty-eight.
What?
The place,
it's thirty-eight.
Thousand?
Thirty-eight hundred.
Wait, what's the catch?
Are you putting a nightclub
down on the first floor?
Well, utilities
would be separate.
It takes a lot to heat
a place like this.
So, expect Con Ed to stick
it to you in the wintertime.
Right.
This would be the best
view in the building.
Are you the super?
Owner, actually.
Oh. Right.
My family bought
the building in the '40s.
And to answer your question
no, there is no nightclub.
A lot of my tenants
started to move out
and so I'm renovating
the apartments.
Until then, it could get
a little noisy around here.
I don't- I don't mind
noise. I'm an ER doctor, so-
When we sleep,
we really sleep.
Well, a couple things
about the building, uh
it doesn't get the best
cell phone reception.
Okay, I'll- I can
figure that out.
And there's
the F Line.
- Jesus.
- Yeah.
There's a maintenance track that
runs directly under this building.
Usually at night.
All right, I'm gonna need your Social
Security number and three references.
Oh, I can get you all of that,
including records of my taxes...
...for the last five years, if you'd like.
I prefer no pets.
Of course.
All right.
The heaters bang
loudly in the morning.
You haven't checked
my references.
I will.
Take a look around. I'm
gonna get back to work.
I gotta be uptown
in exactly 100 minutes
so you got 60 to get the
shit out of this rented truck
or I gotta charge you
for another day.
Take a deep breath, I don't want
you to strain yourself talking.
What, did you hire the only moving guy in
New York who doesn't actually move furniture?
Yeah, right?
Well, you travel
pretty light.
Oh, I got rid
of a lot.
I would have liked to have sawed
the bed in half and burned it
but I need a place
to sleep at night.
Well-
Not easy at forgiving.
Change is good.
Should we go get
that mattress?
Hi.
This is, uh, my grandfather.
August, Juliet. Juliet, August.
She's our new tenant.
Hi.
Got any pets?
No.
Are you loud?
No, not at all.
Sorry I scared you.
Nice to meet you.
Max?
Oh.
Fuck you!
It's crystal meth.
Stop it!
It's all right,
it's all right.
Don't do anything.
It's going to be alright.
No! Don't touch me!
It's gonna be fine.
No.
You're gonna
be all right.
Oh, my God.
Hey.
Heard you had
a long one.
M m. That was
an insane day.
Rob and I are going out
today, you want to come?
No, thanks. I think I'm just
gonna go home and get to bed early.
You have got to stop
thinking about him.
The love of my life cheated
on me. I n my own bed.
Every time I look at myself all I
see is someone who wasn't enough.
You were enough.
You are enough.
More than enough.
He's an asshole.
I gave up my dream
to move to New York
City to be his
and he just
threw it all away.
It's an art opening.
It's not gonna kill you.
And you're going.
We can handle this, it's
gonna cost you a little extra
'cause of all
the unused space.
Grandfather doesn't want to change
the integrity of the structure.
OK. No problem.
We'll take care of it.
All right,
thank you.
Hey.
Hi.
About to start making
a lot of noise?
If I can get
the city's approval.
There are a lot of "l"s to dot
and "T"s to cross around here.
Yeah, I bet.
Oh! Thank you
for the gift.
It was so kind and,
and really thoughtful.
The gift that was
outside my door yesterday?
Yeah, that uh,
that wasn't me.
August.
Oh, there you are.
Hi. I wanted to thank you for
the incredibly thoughtful gift.
I'm just putting myself in your shoes.
I thought,
"If I were a woman
"alone, in a new apartment
"surrounded by strangers
what would I want?"
I don't get much company.
Oh, l- I'm sorry.
L- I should really go.
Thanks.
Great.
Oh, excuse me.
Max?
Hey.
Hey, I didn't recognize you
outside of the building.
- Who's this?
- You, too.
Oh, this is Max.
This is Sidney,
we work together.
Very nice
to meet you, Sidney.
Nice to meet you,
too, Max.
I haven't
heard about you.
Hm... Nice day,
isn't it?
It is. Um, you know, sometimes I
feel like all I ever do is work.
And, I don't know, I just
thought I'd stop and come out
and feel Brooklyn, you know?
Yeah.
Well, Max, would you like
to have a drink with us?
No. No, thanks. I'm actually
getting ready to leave.
It was very nice
to meet you.
Great to see you.
You, too, Max.
Shh! He's my landlord.
So?
And I'm his tenant.
Oh, meh. You mean like
what if it sucks
and you can't get away
from each other?
Yeah. It's not recommended.
So you thought
about it?
Shh!
Hey, Max?
Hey.
Um, do you, actually
do you mind
walking me home?
I'd love to.
Great. Okay.
Bye.
See ya.
He's cute.
Thanks.
Bye, you guys.
Bye-bye.
August, uh, he worries
about me, you know?
People from his generation were married
with ten kids by the time they were my age.
Yeah, he is kind of
a unique guy, isn't he?
That's- That's
one way to put it.
Unique. Uh, difficult.
Pain in the ass would be
another way to characterize him.
Is he okay?
Well, up until
a year ago
we were partners in the building.
We did everything together.
Fixed everything together,
made all the decisions together
and then
he had a stroke.
Oh. What about
your parents?
They, uh, they, they died when
I was, when I was very young.
What about, uh, what about your family?
Um. Let's see, my parents, they're
kind of, uh, after-the-fact hippies.
I guess that makes you the
black sheep of the family, huh?
Definitely. Yeah.
For me, uh, rebellion was
going through med school.
Free love sucked,
as far as I could tell.
It led to a quick divorce
on my parents' part
so I was every other
weekend with my dad.
I never really knew
where my home was
not until Jack and I
moved in together.
Jack?
My ex.
Yeah.
So I thought all
hippie kids had weird names.
Oh, you do,
don't you?
What's your
real name?
Juliet. It's
my real name.
What's your
middle name?
Wanna sit here?
Are you ignoring
my question?
No.
No, I just thought
we'd take in the view.
Uh-huh. Okay.
When I was little, um, I used to
walk around the neighborhood at night.
And look into windows
at families
around televisions
brothers, sisters, parents,
meeting, you know, talking.
And, um, you know, I
knew I couldn't have that.
But, just watching them
it somehow made me feel
like I was part of it.
Seeing all these
families, it's sweet.
Yeah. Yeah.
Bliss.
Bliss?
Yep.
Oh, my Jesus.
"Dr. Bliss."
Doctor Bliss.
Yep.
Very nice.
Thank you.
Sorry.
No, don't be
sorry, Juliet.
God, I'm an idiot.
Of course it's a bad idea.
That's- That's
not what I meant.
I'm just confused.
Reading the wrong signals.
Jesus Christ, Juliet.
Calm the fuck down.
I don't know
what I was expecting.
You were expecting
rebound sex, honey.
Hot. Landlord.
Rebound. Sex.
You're crazy.
See you later.
Bye, girl.
Jack.
You picked up.
What do you want?
I just called to say hi.
Well, hi.
Can I see you?
Juliet-
I'm sorry.
I gotta go.
Look, I don't think it's a
good idea for us to talk yet.
Juliet. It's Max.
Max?
Listen.
Um. I'm sorry
about yesterday.
Well, I was wondering if
I could make it up to you
with, with dinner tonight?
You like old things.
I suppose I do.
You know, I'm not really one of
the text message, Twitter crowd.
Technology seems to be about telling
everybody your deep, dark secrets.
And, uh, I don't know, I guess I
think secrets should be secrets.
What?
It's just-
It's starting to feel like home.
Safe.
Warm. I nviting.
You did that for me.
Good.
So what's your secret?
Why aren't you married?
I guess I just never
found anyone that-
Anyone that?
That got me, I guess.
Or that I got.
And the truth is, um
I'm not very social.
You know, it's probably
the way I, I grew up.
You know, I spent my whole life
taking care of my family's building
and recently,
my grandfather.
And because of that, I just
I never had a
relationship that mattered.
You know, going to that, that
art opening thing the other day
That was- That was
a big deal for me.
I'm sorry about that day.
No.
No, I was just
surprised that
that you-
That I what?
That you wanted to kiss me.
Why wouldn't I?
Landlord.
Tenant.
Messy.
That's a pulse!
He thought he was dying.
It's another stroke, isn't it?
I called in a scrip for Klonopin.
He should see a psychiatrist.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Someone called
about a rental here?
Excuse me.
Max?
Hey.
Hi.
Who's this?
Oh, this is Max. This is
Sidney, we work together.
Sometimes I feel like
all I do is work, and, um
I don't know,
I decided to stop
and come out and
feel Brooklyn, you know?
Yeah.
Hey, Max,
do you actually
do you mind
walking me home?
Sorry. I'm confused.
Reading the wrong signals.
Sorry. God, I'm an idiot.
Of course, it's a bad idea.
I'm confused.
Reading the wrong signals.
Jesus Christ, Juliet.
Calm the fuck down.
Max?
What?
Max.
I can't do this.
I can't get him out of my mind.
Jack.
I still only know his smell.
And the way he touches me, l-
I don't want it to be like this.
I understand.
Yeah, yeah, you understand, right?
I'll call you later.
Okay.
I know everything
that goes on in this building.
that goes on in your head.
You think I don't know
how your brain works?
Just like your father.
Jealous and perverted.
That's enough.
Your mother.
She was beautiful.
She married a weak man.
Then she gave birth to another.
Hey.
Um. L-I've been meaning
to talk to you.
Yeah. Look,
I'm- I'm sorry.
It suddenly felt weird, l-
It had nothing
to do with you, I just-
I need more time.
That's okay.
You know, that, that tells me you
take being with someone seriously.
And, you know, I like that.
Um, but, you know, I,
I was thinking about it
and maybe we shouldn't have
done that, you know?
Meaning that we live in
the same building, and all.
Really?
No offense, I just-
I just needed company, I guess.
I'm so glad you feel the same way.
I just-
It's meant a lot to me
the last couple weeks.
Well, l-
I should go, l-
Yeah. Okay.
Okay. I'll see you.
Have- Have a nice day.
You, too.
What's the matter with you?
Why didn't you
stand up for yourself?
Just like your father.
Your mother, she was beautiful.
She married a weak man.
Then she gave birth to another.
Oh.
This place is driving me crazy.
And I thought I knew everything
about this building.
I never realized your kitchen
had an old wine closet.
Hm...
August's old place had, uh
had one of these, but, uh, this
they must've covered
this up years ago.
Well, I think it's really cool.
Can I use it?
Yeah. Absolutely. Um.
Why don't I just fix it up for
you and I'll get out of your hair.
Well, I have work.
That's, that's okay.
I can, I can do it
while you're gone.
That's really sweet of you.
Thanks for being
such a good friend.
Hi. Hi, no, let me
help you with this.
Oh, no.
That's okay.
No, no, no.
I should help you.
That- It's sweet.
Uh, it goes,
it goes in the kitchen?
Yeah.
Okay, good. Yeah.
Got a lot of stuff.
You, uh, you cooking?
Yeah.
Maybe I'll, uh, I'll
stay and help, yeah?
You, you
- You don't have to do that.
Uh, Juliet,
I wanted to
I wanted to try to speak to
you about, about something.
Um, it's been a little
confusing for me
because you, because
you kissed me first.
What?
Yeah, you made
the first move.
You kissed me first
and, um
and now you're acting
like nothing happened.
I'm sorry, l-
Um, we were just getting
to know each other.
You know, seeing if things
worked or, or didn't.
I mean, that's what,
that's what people do.
I don't do that.
You shouldn't
do that, either.
Hey.
Yeah. Ten minutes
is perfect.
All right,
I'll see you then.
Bye.
Hey.
Oh!
Amelie, hi! I missed you so much.
Hi.
Uh-
What happened
to her?
She's been picking a fight
with a German shepherd at, um-
Oh?
Yeah. I didn't
know what to bring
to a dinner
like this, but-
Thank you,
they're beautiful.
Let's sit here,
in the living room.
Place is huge.
And cheap.
How much?
Thirty-eight hundred.
Anything available
for me?
I don't know if we're
quite ready for that.
Right.
Thanks.
Tell me about
the German Shepherd.
She's been having a hard
time at doggy day care.
Why are you taking
her to doggy day care?
Been traveling a lot
the past few weeks.
It was business.
I wasn't thinking that.
Look, I could
tell you everything.
I don't want to know.
You were never home.
I literally never saw you.
Please don't tell me you slept with
someone else because I work too hard.
I was with someone else.
It was just a flirtation, but
it felt amazing for a moment.
I want to be clear
about something.
He was nice
but he was never you.
It's the guy
with the beard, right?
How do you know that?
I followed you one night. I
was gonna ring your bell, but-
You followed me home?
I wasn't good anymore.
My life, without you
I missed you.
I missed you,
too, Jack.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
dinner burned.
I'm not.
I want you to stay.
I can't. I've got
a 7:00 AM.
I'm in no way prepared.
I'm gonna be up all night.
You want to keep
Amelie tonight?
No pets allowed.
Here, keep this.
I love you.
All right, come on.
Bye.
So what's going on? I
heard you were late again.
Yeah, I slept through my
alarm three times in two weeks.
And I
never oversleep.
So, you been
out late?
No, no.
There's just-
There's something creepy
about my apartment.
A guy gives you a gorgeous
apartment, at an unbelievable price
cooks for you, and is an absolute
gentleman, and that's creepy?
No, no. There's just
something about it.
I can't wake up
in the morning
and I don't know-
It's- it's a feeling.
If I were you,
I'd keep the apartment
get a louder alarm.
So the record feature's
triggered by movement.
So any activity
in your apartment
will be recorded in up
to ten-minute intervals.
It's a wireless system which can
be accessed through your computer.
This position, and the
position in the living room
will cover as much of
the apartment as possible.
But that still leaves the kitchen
and the bathroom uncovered.
That's okay. As long as I have
the front door and my bedroom.
Well, you got that.
These things have automatic night vision,
so you've no need to leave a light on.
These babies will catch
anything that moves.
So, you gonna sublet?
I'm sorry, what?
Most people put these in
if they're going to sublet
or have a party,
or even for babysitters.
You know, so nobody
steals anything.
I'm gonna sublet.
Here we go.
Well, that's it.
So, um, call if you
have any questions.
Thanks.
Grandfather?
Max?
What're you doing?
It's my life now.
I'm sorry
to rush.
Okay.
Hi. It's Juliet Devereau. I'm
sorry, I somehow seriously overslept-
I'll be there in, uh, ten.
Uh, I need a TR on these, ASAP, please.
Okay, got it.
Thanks.
Mr. Franklin, please return
to the emergency room.
Ooh.
Shit.
Thanks.
This is Juliet.
I faxed the toxicology
report you ordered.
Great, thanks.
Jack, don't go
to my apartment.
I don't know how the fuck
it happened, but somehow
Shit.
Jack?
No.
Juliet?
Hi, there.
You just get home?
Yeah.
Look what I found.
This great old bottle of wine
from August's wine closet.
I'll, I'll open it.
No, no need.
I already cracked it.
I wanted it to breathe
a little bit. Do you mind?
No, that's great.
You have a rough
day, Juliet?
Yeah.
Well, here. Drink this.
Maybe it will help.
Thanks.
Come sit down.
So, to...
to our friendship.
Cheers.
You're not
going to try it?
I'm not, um-
Juliet, are you okay?
Just, I'm exhausted. I'm
not really sleeping well.
I like this wine a lot.
It's good.
I'll be right back.
Juliet.
Can you please
put your phone down?
Just-
Why are you calling him?
Where is he?
Why did you give him
keys to my building?
You know where he is?
Why did you
betray me, Juliet?
Sit. Down.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Juliet.
What did you do to him?
What did you do?
Hey.
Juliet.
You're so beautiful.
This time you get
to be awake.
to remember.
Damn.
Help!
Come on!
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Oh!
You bitch!
God!
Jesus Christ.
Juliet!
There's nowhere for you to go.
Juliet.
I thought
I thought you could pull me
out of these walls.
I didn't want this.
I didn't want this at all.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I was never gonna hurt you.
But you fucking betrayed me!
No.
You bitch!
Jack?