Hiya.
Arthur, it's Harry.
I've been trying to get ahold
of you for three days.
- What's the matter?
- I gotta see you.
Now. Please.
- One hour.
- Arthur, I've got big trouble.
It just doesn't
make any sense, Arthur.
They said I broke the agreement.
Day before yesterday,
they stopped answering my calls.
What can I do?
Give 'em a call.
Say a few words on my behalf.
I wouldn't know who.
Why should they listen to me?
I'm no part of that.
No, but your father was.
A very important part.
His brains helped put the whole
thing together for 'em.
They still talk about him
like he was a patron saint.
You've got his name.
Please, Arthur?
It's all I've got.
Thanks.
Save it.
Come on outside.
Let's have a drink.
You know,
I've given a good many years.
Me and your father both.
How many friends you think
I got right now, huh?
What?
I was just thinkin'.
Remember that fishin' trip...
that you and me and your father
took up to Canada?
You was about eight, right?
Seven or eight.
You fell overboard.
You couldn't swim.
Your old man says,
"He'll learn pretty fast."
You were floppin' around.
You looked like a drowned rat.
But you didn't say a word.
You didn't yell for help
or nothin'.
You just kept lookin'
at your old man...
and he didn't make a move.
Well, pretty soon
I had to reach out...
and grab you by the hair
and pull you in the boat.
You looked like a drowned rat.
Your old man,
he laughed like hell.
That was a long time ago.
Hey, what are you drinkin'?
We've got vodka...
we got scotch, bourbon.
Arthur, this is my son Steve.
Steve, this is Mr. Bishop.
Hi. How are you?
I need some bread, Dad.
What are you talkin' about?
Why, just this morning I was...
I only need a thousand.
Besides,
my asking you for money...
makes you feel
I'm dependent on you.
Kinda ties us together.
Fast, huh?
Chromosomes will tell.
He's got a point.
My father gets uptight
when I ask him for money...
he steals from other people.
Steve, that's enough.
Don't get excited.
It's bad for you.
Nice to meet you.
Drop by any time, huh?
Any friend of Big Harry's...
I know you gotta go.
I'm sorry about that.
Forget it.
I just don't understand him
anymore.
It's just so...
Well, call me
when you know something, OK?
OK.
Take care of yourself.
Arthur Bishop?
I have a special delivery.
Certified. Please sign here.
Mr. Bishop?
We would like you
to go ahead... anytime.
- Nothin' else, huh?
- Nothin' else.
You're to wait down there...
and I wait for you
at the top of the hill.
Well, could you tell anything
by his voice?
I mean the tone?
Harry, stay loose.
Yeah, sure.
It's like you say, if they're
willin' to talk, well...
Harry, I'll be parked
right up there.
Say, don't you think that...
Hello?!
Well, I'm here!
Come on, let's talk.
You said we were gonna talk!
Harry, run to the car.
- It's a set-up.
- I can't!
I'll try to get behind him.
Run!
Oh, God.
I can't...
Keep going!
I can't.
You?
This is it, huh?
Finish it, Arthur.
You or me.
Finish it.
I had a feeling.
Can I come in?
Oh, my darling,
it's been so long.
I said I wasn't gonna do this.
I had it all worked out.
I go to the door,
there you are.
I smile, very poised,
as if I just saw you yesterday.
I'm sorry.
Nothing's changed.
It never does.
OK, I think
I've got it together.
You know...
I think you've lost some weight.
I wrote you a letter.
I couldn't mail it.
I didn't know where.
I keep movin' around.
It's true, you know.
I do always know
when you're near.
ESP.
Maybe.
What's the matter, baby?
Well, I've been here
about three minutes...
and you've managed about
one recrimination a minute.
I can't seem to feel anything
but hurt when you're not here.
I guess when I see you again,
I just have to hurt back.
Did you really
write me a letter?
"My dearest love...
"I'm once again alone."
I can't hear you.
"And the silence in this room...
"presses against my ears
until I'm deafened.
"This is the way I live
until I see you again...
"and then you're here
and there's no past.
"Only the two of us.
"I know these words hurt you...
"because you can't give
anything but the moment...
"but I have to write them now...
"because somehow my need
for you must find its voice.
"And you... what of your pain?
"If you could only
let me have...
"one small part
of the weight of it."
Don't read anymore.
Don't you see?
Even that would be a comfort
to me when you're not here.
Oh, my darling,
I love you so much. I can't...
Don't.
It's gonna be all right.
Oh, baby, I love you.
Oh, my darling.
Darling, take us to bed.
Baby, I missed you.
I'm so glad you're here.
I love you.
It'll be a hundred more
this time.
The letter took me
a while to make up.
All right?
Yes. The letter was good.
Try to think of something
like it for next time.
OK, I will.
To his community and church...
he gave his resources,
his faith, and his spirit.
His good works comfort us
in the going.
We commit his remains
to your earth, O, Father...
and we pray you
vouchsafe him eternal life.
I've always been interested
in primitive rituals...
like tucking the dead away.
Glory be to the Father
and to the Son...
and to the Holy Spirit.
Glory be to the father,
Harry McKenna...
fixer extraordinaire...
pusher, pimp, thief, arsonist.
You liked him a lot?
Oh, yeah.
He was my kind of man.
What was your connection
with him?
He worked for my father
a long time back.
He thought I could
do him a favor.
So, your old man was in, huh?
And you?
Don't you think you should be...
Yeah, you got somethin' goin'.
You're pretty sure of yourself.
I live in my mind, Mr. Bishop.
Sounds like something
I read someplace.
And so do you.
Could I have a ride home?
Sure.
Amen.
Come on. Steve's got
the whole place outside.
Good old Steve!
What are they celebrating?
Well, this is all mine now.
My father never really
liked my friends...
and I'm not so sure I do,
either.
Hey, we've got a call here
from Katmandu.
Hey, Katmandu's calling, Sam.
Yes, I placed a call
to Sydney, Australia.
We got the White House.
Yes, I want to speak...
Yeah. No, listen, I live there.
I know he's there.
It's all in the bubbles.
Yeah, emergency.
I must speak to him. John Lenn...
Hey, Steve,
Louise is on the phone.
Sounds important, man.
- Afghanistan here.
- No, I didn't call Afghanistan.
- Hello, Louise?
- Are you with her?
- You don't love me.
- That kinda talk is foolish.
I'm gonna kill myself.
I wanna die.
- Louise, please.
- I do.
- Well, go ahead then.
- I will. You don't care.
Yeah, that's right.
I don't care.
Right...
My friends are so happy,
they're killing themselves.
Would you come along?
Who's he?
He's a friend of the family's.
I thought
you'd already started.
Oh, no.
I wanted you to watch.
Now, let me see
if I've got everything.
Ice cubes, wine, razor blades.
How long does it take?
I don't know.
Sure you do.
You know everything.
Louise,
you called me because...
either you don't want to do it,
and you want me to stop you...
or you want to lay
the guilt of it on me...
and I'm not buying either one.
So go ahead on.
Hold on.
Mind if I have
a little wine first?
You son of a bitch.
Mr. Bishop?
Not for me, thanks.
You really don't believe.
Baby.
I call you baby because
your innocence touches me so.
Those really are sharp,
aren't they?
I always said
that you had guts, Louise.
About how long will it take?
Mr. Bishop?
How much do you weigh?
110.
Two and a half to three hours.
At first you'll get cold,
and then sleepy.
You're a son of a bitch, too.
Louise, I haven't had
anything to eat yet today.
What you got in the fridge?
Thanks.
I know he'll stop me.
I know he will.
I know he feels something.
I know you.
What?
I didn't hear you, baby.
What'd you say?
I said you'll stop it.
Listen.
If you don't care anything...
about your own life,
then why should I?
You do care. You do.
And you do, too.
I'm cold.
I'm getting colder.
Psychosomatic.
You've got an hour
and a half left.
Please, Steve.
I don't want to do it.
If you kick it...
you can probably make
the sheriff's station...
in Malibu
in about fifteen minutes.
Would you have let it happen?
Would you?
Look, I was just an observer.
You haven't answered
my question.
Well, what do you think?
We'll never know, will we?
Well, say
that I just sat there...
or we just sat there
and watched her check out.
Think that
would have been crazy?
Irrational, maybe.
Is there anything wrong
with that?
It just means that you
have your own rule book.
I can dig that.
Is that so?
It takes a very special
kind of person...
to pick up the tab
for that kind of living.
You say you dig it,
but you're talkin' about...
something you really
know nothing about.
And you do?
Do I?
Very slippery.
When he's cornered, he answers
questions with questions.
What's your action, Mr. Bishop?
You've been watching
too many late movies.
Well, it's been interesting.
Thanks. Maybe another time.
The underwater feeding show...
by Marineland's staff diver
in the giant fish tank.
The giant fish tank
is to your left...
Next of kin?
None.
Anybody we can notify?
How about an acquaintance?
Are you finished, doctor?
No, there's a charge.
You can take care of it at the
cashier's window one floor up.
I suggest that you make
an appointment with your doctor.
That is, if you have a doctor.
What do you think?
What'd you feel
before you passed out?
Couldn't get my breath.
Palms sweating?
Nausea? Heart beating fast?
Sounds like an A.R.
Acute anxiety reaction.
Classic neurasthenic pattern.
See a doctor, Mr. Bishop.
Have some tests.
If they come back negative...
maybe you should think
about seeing a psychiatrist.
In the meantime, take these.
They'll help a little.
I need a signature, Doc.
Hey, you were really
out there for a while.
The cashier, you say,
is on the first floor?
Dr. Richmond
wanted in Emergency.
Watch your backs, please.
Thank you.
You waitin' for me?
How long you been here?
Since last night, about 12:00.
Must be important.
You said another time.
I said maybe another time.
That's right.
That's what you said.
Come on in.
So this is what it looks like
inside your head, huh?
This place must've cost
some bread.
Are you still trying
to figure my action?
I inherited enough.
It is nice to be comfortable,
isn't it?
Is there something specific
you want to talk about?
No, I just...
Well, yeah, there is.
What happened the other night,
that was pretty far out...
and you were saying
some things about it.
So?
So, how 'bout some answers?
To what?
For openers,
suppose I say I think...
I'm the kind of person...
that can pick up the tab
for what happened?
What's the rest of it?
What makes you think
I can answer that?
You said that...
I said that you didn't know
anything about it.
It doesn't mean I do.
Now you see him, now you don't.
Is my time up?
There is something
I have to do.
Can I come?
What do you want from me?
That's incredible.
Yeah. It keeps me sharp.
Balance,
problems of orientation...
sometimes you have
to think in reverse.
Here, you take it.
That's not bad.
How long you been flying?
About twenty seconds.
My father
was what they called a judge.
He would settle arguments
on the council...
and his word was final.
It was never questioned...
until one day
some hothead from Chicago...
took exception
to one of his decisions...
and put a contract on him.
The guy that got him
was a shooter from Topeka.
That was all.
How old were you then?
Your age.
Maybe younger.
I was still in school.
You find this interesting,
don't you?
Are you kidding?
My father used to do
front numbers even for me.
Like if he did that,
maybe it wouldn't rub off.
Never talk about that stuff.
He was beautiful.
Only trouble was,
I really wanted to dig it.
He wanted me to be
a part of his front, too.
So, what happened
after they burned your old man?
I finished school.
And?
That's all. Then I grew up.
Did your father ever tell you
anything about the operation...
like how it worked?
What's with those guys, anyway?
They all act
like they're ashamed.
My father wasn't ashamed.
He was the best.
Game.
You're pretty good.
- Play to win, do you?
- You know any other way?
Let's make it two out of three.
OK, but I'm telling you,
I'm genius at this game.
Yeah?
You go get the ball, genius.
What's going on?
That old man is Yamoto.
He's here from Japan,
where he's a master.
The other guy is Kori.
Very dangerous and very fast...
but he's got some new tricks...
that are sort of an insult
to the old style.
Yamoto thinks these tricks...
are useless
against a classic fighter...
and he's here
to prove his point.
The object of these fights is
total concentration and control.
They don't actually
hit each other...
otherwise one or the other
would be dead...
and that's against the law.
I thought he wasn't
supposed to hit him.
Probably
one of Kori's new tricks.
You haven't said three words
since the match.
He practically
murdered that guy.
Murder is only killing
without a license...
and everybody kills.
Governments,
the military, the police.
Do you think
that Yamoto's a killer?
He's a killer who doesn't kill.
It's funny.
For him,
the rules are important.
That's your expert opinion?
That's my opinion.
OK. Don't get uptight.
- Not me.
- Bullshit.
Look, every time we're on this
subject, the same thing happens.
As long as we're rapping it out
on your terms...
everything's OK, but the minute
I have a question...
or I want to know
something specific from you...
you either shine me on
or go out for coffee.
What the hell is going on?
You're pressing pretty hard.
You'd better be damn sure
you want to know.
This is not
freshman philosophy time.
I'm sure.
You ever hear
the term "mechanic"...
used outside
of its normal meaning?
Where?
My father used it.
It's a dealer.
A guy who works game tables.
Anything else?
Sure. It's a shooter.
A hit man.
So?
So there we are.
And that's your action?
Yeah, that figures.
I'm telling you this...
because there are times
when I could use a backup.
Wouldn't have
to spread myself so thin.
And you seem
to have the aptitude.
You do this for money?
Money is paid,
but that's not the motive.
It has to do with standing
outside of it all on your own.
I'm gonna teach you all I can.
After that, you can choose
how you want it to go.
- You in?
- Do I have an alternative?
There are alternatives
to everything.
You've got a partner,
Mr. Bishop.
Associate.
Point the gun as though it were
an extension of your arm...
and keep both eyes open.
All right, you ready? Pull.
That's better. Much better.
Pull.
Winchester.
300 Magnum, 180 grains.
Muzzle velocity.
Pull!
3,070.
Drop at 200 yards.
Two minutes low. Pull!
300 yards.
Pull.
5.3 inches.
300 yards, 150 grains.
4.8 inches.
Pull.
Doubles.
There are killers,
and there are killers.
To tell you the truth...
they all have
a different book of rules.
To get away with it
depends on the book of rules...
you have in your pocket
at the time.
Your own country,
somebody else's country...
or your own personal
book of rules.
All this... heroes.
Half of them were killers.
Napoléon was one, you know?
Pancho Villa, Genghis Khan.
And then we have
our own domestic brand...
like Billy the Kid, Jesse James,
and John Dillinger.
Yeah, they're about as famous...
as our own
honest-to-goodness heroes.
Don't tell me
that's gonna make us heroes.
I wouldn't tell you
anything like that.
All I'm saying is that people
who stand outside the law...
oftentimes end up as heroes.
What's with that ball of wax
I see you squeezing?
Sometimes you have
to hold the mark.
It develops the strength.
"In the ages
between 45 and 64...
"of the total deaths
by accident...
"10,431 were from falls."
You know, falls from
high places are very clean.
What's that?
That is your first involvement.
Taking the Zoo Drive turnoff.
Now they're going west.
There's one camera.
Another.
Two cameras
covering the main gate.
You couldn't
get within 100 yards...
without tripping
that alarm system.
The guards sleep in shifts.
One of them awake all the time.
What about number one?
Midnight till 4:00
in the morning.
We need more.
We'll have to stay in closer
until we find something.
I want you to rent two cars,
a Ford and a Volkswagen.
This looks like
it might be something.
Turn this on.
Comes across the border
at 1 a.m.
I can have it to you
at 7 a.m. tomorrow.
How?
In a Chicken Lickin' truck
right to your place.
OK. You check the goods
when it comes, then wake me.
I'll make the test.
Better not be crap.
You know where to find me.
Well, they'll have
to turn off the alarm system...
to make that delivery.
Where'd you learn
how to do that?
One of the tools of the trade,
my friend.
Allied Plating. This is Frank.
Listen, I've got a bumper
that needs re-chroming.
If I brought it in tomorrow,
can I pick it up by Saturday?
We don't work
on Saturday down here.
Monday afternoon the soonest.
Monday's all right.
I'll bring it in tonight.
Since there's no guard
on the weekends...
at the Allied Plating plant...
we could put the bodies
in these nitric acid tanks.
Mr. Bishop?
We would like you
to go ahead with this one.
We go.
I'm gonna check you for iron
before you go past here.
- Come on, get out.
- What's the matter?
Come on. Get out of there.
What the hell is this?
Chicken Lickin'.
Chicken Lickin'
is lickin' chicken.
Wise guy.
Get the bodies in the truck!
Do you know my dog
got a birthday card today?
I didn't. Just my dog.
Archibald, those kids
on the hill there...
how can you live here
with all that noise?
I called the police,
but there's nothing they can do.
Daddy, it's getting worse here
every weekend.
In forty-eight hours...
everything will be in solution.
It was...
What?
Well, it could've been
so simple...
but that guy
came out of nowhere.
Those things happen...
but remember it the next time.
Could you spare a few minutes,
Mr. Bishop?
Yes. When?
Now. I'm at home.
All right.
I have to do something
for a while.
I'll see you later.
Mr. Bishop is here, sir.
Show him through.
This way, sir.
That was very untidy,
Mr. Bishop.
We'd like to know how
Harry McKenna's son figures.
He'll be working with me
from now on.
You think this is wise?
You telling me
I need your permission?
Information is all I want,
Mr. Bishop.
We like to know things.
An organization survives
only because its members...
are willing to sacrifice
certain personal choices...
for the good of all.
A very democratic principle,
Mr. Bishop.
We survive
because we have this rule.
What you or I want
is unimportant.
Only the rule.
Someone trained by me
could be of value to you.
Nobody lives forever.
You take
full responsibility then?
This one has to be done fast.
Very fast.
I'll handle it
the way I always do.
There may not be
time enough for that.
The word is, he's getting ready
to talk to some people.
The problem is considerable.
I'm not some wild
Cleveland shooter.
I don't cowboy.
If he talks, things
could get complicated... sloppy.
That would disturb a lot of us.
It's not really open
to discussion, Mr. Bishop.
This business
of McKenna's son...
has upset
a few of our associates.
I understand it...
but these people
see it only from the outside.
A quick, clean job
would go a long way...
in putting everything
back into proper balance.
Yes, I understand.
I knew you would.
Your man's in Naples.
We've given you
a name in Rome...
for any equipment
you might need.
Good. You're still up.
I called you about 9:00.
Yeah, well,
Louise picked me up and we...
It's good for the nerves.
She has this thing she does...
Spare me the details.
Look, if I'd known
you wanted to work...
You are a free agent, my friend.
The only thing you have to do...
is fulfill the requirements
of the Association.
And that means
your occasional presence...
some intelligent responses,
some skill at your work...
and nothing more.
You've got that,
so what's buggin' you?
We got one, huh?
They want him to be cowboyed.
Explain.
They want me to get him now...
any way I can.
That doesn't sound very cool.
What are you gonna do
about that?
I'm too far along
to change my habits.
I'll do what I've always done...
in Italy.
Italy? Am I gonna go?
Why not?
Steve McKenna.
Mountain View Drive.
Age twenty-four.
Height...
five foot, eleven inches.
Weight... 165.
Right-handed.
Hair... blond.
Distinguishing marks...
small scar on right arm.
Interests... girls, freaks...
physical fitness...
fast cars...
and killing.
Just like the postcards.
Let's go to work.
What time?
It's 11:47.
Good?
Last time I had this
was ten years ago.
They make it right here,
you know...
But not enough to export.
Casa de fiori doesn't travel.
It's not bad.
Slowly.
The time you take
is very important.
Savor it.
Even what we're doing now.
See, you must
figure it carefully.
Don't rush.
Know every move, turn it
over and over in your mind...
until you're sure
there are no holes.
But you have to be
dead sure... or dead.
No second chances.
I'll try and remember that.
Remember, don't try.
Dead sure... or dead.
The room's not going
to get any bigger.
I think I'll take a walk.
Is that all right with you?
What now?
It looks like
they're going south.
We could follow
on the Coast Road.
Excuse me, sir. Would you take
a picture of my wife and me?
Thank you.
It seems he doesn't do the same
thing the same way twice.
Except spend Friday
and Saturday night on that boat.
A diesel leak explosion
might be nice.
Yeah, but how do we
get close enough?
You scuba?
Yeah. Sure.
Good.
I'll go down to Rome,
pick up some equipment...
and be back tomorrow night.
Meanwhile, you study this chart,
especially this area right here.
Memorize the beach area,
offshore formations...
the depth, that sort of thing.
You got it.
You really expect
this kind of action?
You begin to lose odds
out in the open like this.
You straight on everything?
Where does our man sleep?
Forward bunk, starboard.
His friend?
- Aft, starboard.
- Engine hatch?
About four feet aft
of the bridge.
Let's go.
It'll be light soon.
It's a setup.
Duck!
Speed boats.
- How can they know?
- Give me that.
Those friends of yours?
Come on, man,
what the hell is going on?
They were sent
by the people I work for.
Explain.
When I brought you in,
I didn't check with 'em.
I broke a rule.
That was fast of you
back there. Thanks.
How long till she goes?
Just about... now.
Marcello, Cergei.
They're very thorough.
You drive.
Hey, man, this is getting
just a little bit hairy.
Yeah. I'm gonna try something.
That ought to take care of 'em.
One of 'em had a walkie-talkie.
He was in contact with somebody.
There they are.
It's a road block.
Slow down.
When you're about
200 feet from them...
put it in first
like you're going to stop...
but keep it rolling.
Wedge this
against the gas pedal.
Jump when I say so.
All right,
jam it on the gas pedal now.
All right. Ready, jump!
I'm empty.
Same here.
What do we do now?
Our friend back there
has picked up a machine gun.
Hey, pick it up and let's go.
You might not get back
for another ten years.
This really is a beautiful city.
What the hell. Let's go.
Brucine.
You'll be dead in a few minutes.
Listen,
you'll really appreciate this.
This stuff is absolutely clear
when it's in solution.
I just coated the inside
of the glass with it...
and let it dry.
And when the wine hit it...
it went right back
into solution... no trace.
Looks just like a heart attack.
You said every man
has his jelly spot.
Yours was you just
couldn't cut it alone.
Was it because of your father?
You killed him?
I thought he just died.
You see? There you are.
They told you who to hit.
It kept the whole idea from
being what we talked about.
You needed a license.
Their license.
I'm gonna pick my own mark.
Hit when I want.
Just like you said.
Standing outside.
See Naples and die.
"Steve, if you read this,
it means I didn't make it back.
"It also means
you've broken a filament...
"controlling a thirteen-second
delay trigger.
"End of game.
"Bang. You're dead."