[Man] All right,
bowl bid ridirhere for ESU.
Fourth down on the Georgia Tech 18.
Four ticks left.
- [Player] Set!
- Kane sets 'em down.
Blue 80!
[Crowd Cheering]
Hut!
[Grunting, Groaning]
- Arrgh!
- Uuh!
- Huuh!
- Aah!
[Grunting]
Uuh!
- Shit!
- [Whistle Blowing]
[Man] Coach, this is the
second year in a row you've
failed to go to a bowl game.
Do you feel your program's
in decline?
I think we have a young team
on the verge.
We'll be goir to
a major bowl next year.
[Reporters All Talking
At Once]
[Reporter]
Coach, there are rumors
that you might be replaced...
- if you fail to get to a bowl
game again next year.
- Hey, Joe.
Good throw.
It was there.
Another year home
for Christmas.
Next year...
Next year we sell out.
Next year we dominate.!
[Reporter] You still need a
deep threat or a breakaway back
to go with Joe Kane.
So, what are you gonna do
to address this need?
Well, stop wastir my time
talkir to you guys, for one thing.
- Coach, any media...
- [Reporters All Talking At Once]
[Man] I'm not going to lead you
into the fog here, Sam.
I'm concerned
about our program.
It's always been a source of pride
to our students and alumni.
Two so-so seasons
is having a damaging effect
on our fund-raising,
both public and private.
Just let me get this straight.
What you're trying to
say here, Grant...
is that after 12 years,
my job's in jeopardy.
I'm not prepared to discuss
your job right now.
I just want you to be aware
of the situation.
The alumni and the legislature
are unappy...
and they vote
with their checkbooks.
I don't pretend to be
an expert on football, Sam,
but I do know
we need to win next year.
[Man]
Tickets are in your bag.
Itinerary and player profiles
are in your briefcase.
You've got a 9:00 tomorrow
morning in Philly with this kid,
Darnell Jefferson.
Damn. Looks like I lost
some weight.
This kid could be the game-breaker
we're looking for.
He had a 108-yard
kickoff return against Taft.
Michigars been down
to see him twice.
- What was the
name of that high school again?
- Taft.
Taft.
[Muttering]
[Coach] Now, Darnell,
you have the potential
to start for us as a freshman.
That 108-yard kickoff return
you made against Taft?
That was probably
one of the greatest runs...
I've ever seen
a high school player make.
Now, [Clears Throat]
Michigan, they're set.
A tailback for two years.
But with us and Joe, here,
getting you the ball
in our thunder right.
Ah, hell... Excuse me, Reverend.
You could be an All-American
by your sophomore year.
Yes, but I'm more concerned
with Darnell's education.
He came here late.
He's got some catchir up to do.
Well, education is the first
priority of our program.
That's why all my players are
smarter than me. [Chuckles]
[Man]
Merry Christmas, Mama.
It's very pretty, Alvin.
When I turn pro,
I'm gonna get you the house
to go with it.
[Whispering]
Thank you, son.
[Man]
Runnirlow on brew.
Didrt expect you
home this year, Joe.
- Wort be here next year.
- Yeah, well, we won't rent
your place on the couch.
[Indistinct Sports Announcer]
Merry Christmas, Dad.
Yeah,
merry fuckir Christmas.
[Marching Band]
[Cheer Squad]
Woo, hey, ESU
Wejust wanna welcome you
Darnell, ESU
Wejust wanna
welcome you
Darnell, ESU
We just wanna
welcome you
Darnell, ESU
We just wanna
welcome you
Darnell, ESU
We just wanna
welcome you
[Whooping]
- Hey, man, good to see you again.
Welcome to ESU.
- Glad to be here, man.
I got somebody
I'd like you to meet.
This is Autumn Haley,
and, uh, she'll be
showir you around.
- Hi, Darnell.
- How you doir?
- It's nice to meet you.
- The pleasure's all mine.
This is it:
Wolf Den Stadium.
Damn!
[Man Over P.A.]
Now for the starting lineup
for the ESU Timberwolves.
At tailback, number 20,
Darnell Jefferson.
- They got that right.
- [Imaginary Cheering]
Yo, thanks for showing me
around the campus.
I don't get the chance to meet
too many girls like you.
You got a lot of class.
Real efficacious.
[Nervous Laughter]
Thank you.
You're welcome. Hope I can see you
in the fall.
Me too.
Good night.
[Door Opens, Closes]
[Chuckling]
[Darnell]
ESU is where I'm goir
I'll be number 20,
but we're indubitably
gonna be number one.
[Chattering, Shouting]
[Brakes Hiss]
- Hey, man, good to see ya.
How you doir?
- What's up? All right.
This is Bud-Lite Kaminski,
DarnellJefferson.
- How you doir?
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Let's head out.
- Hey, I got a question
for you, man.
- What's that?
- What happened to the band
and the dancir honeys...
and all that good shit y'all
used to make me come here?
Oh, yeah, well, uh...
Uh, regular students
don't come back for
another two weeks, so, ah...
[Chuckles] Not that they
would be here anyway.
See, ah,
we got you now, so, ah...
- Just another wormshit
freshman, man.
- Oh, I see how it goes.
- Welcome to college.
- Ha-ha!
[Revving]
[Blues Rock]
- Hi!
- [Man] Hey, Joe.
- Hey, Mary.
- Hey, Joe!
- Goddamn, the lead dog is back.
- How's it goir?
There goes my cover
of the media, guys.
- That's DarnellJefferson.
Bobby, Lat.
- Hello.
Hey, Josie, can I get
a couple ofTequilas? Thanks.
Hey, Joe, you know, I was hoping
you might've rolled your bike
or something this summer.
You know, nothing serious,
just enough to keep you out
for the season.
Well, no such luck,
backup man.
But, um, perhaps could
engineer a few blowouts,
give you a little mop-up time.
Much obliged, Joe.
My God, Lats,
you put on some weight, huh?
- Gained about 35 pounds.
- Shee!
Tried of watchir you guys play,
so I spent my summer in the gym.
I intend to start this year.
You get any bigger,
you can play offense.
Yeah, but don't I have
to get dumber then too?
- Is that really possible?
[Chuckling]
- [Groaning]
- [Joe]
Here's to a new season.
- Come on.
Hey, you still seeir
Louanne?
Uh, yeah. Now and then,
you know, when the tide rises.
Don't want her thinkir it's
some kind of exclusive deal,
now, do I?
Coach finds out your nailir
his daughter, you're gonna
be playir dorm ball, buddy.
I'll bail before that.
'Sides, that's what coach
gets for not startir me.
- [Bud-Lite] You never learn,
do you, Collins?
- Heh! See you boys.
- It's pathetic.
- Alvin.
- Hey, dog, have you seen this?
- Oh, my God!
- [Alvin] You must be
one badass motherfucker.!
- Like you didn't know!
I knew there was gonna be an
article. I just didn't know
it was out already.
[Alvin] Shit.! We do all the work
and you get all the pub.
Too bad we ain't allowed
to hit you in practice.
Be fun to kick the shit
out of a Heisman Trophy candidate!
- Yeah, maybe you'll get your shot
in the pro's, huh?
- Uh-hoo! Damn!
- Hey, beer boy, gimme some peanuts.
- [Chuckling]
- Are you serious?
- Does it look like I'm serious?
This is one of those
rookie things, right?
[Chuckling]
[Lats]
Listen to this. ;
"ESU has a solid
nucleus returning.
But the Timberwolves,
"coming off
two disappointing seasons,
will only go as far...
as the strong right arm of
Heisman candidateJoe Kane
will take them."
Is that right, Joey?
You gonna lead us to the
promised land like that says?
Oh, yeah,
I'm gonna lead.
- Question is,
can you boys follow?
- Ooh-ooh-ooh.!
Autumn!
Yo, Autumn, wait up!
- It's me, Darnell!
- Hey, Darnell.
Whatcha doir here?
I thought the students hadrt
come back for two weeks.
- I came back early to see a friend.
- That's cool.
And if I may say so myself,
you are looking good!
You look like the package of
pulchritudinous, girl.
Let's get together later tonight.
Let's get some pizza,
let's kick it,
let's just hang out.
- I can't tonight.
- What about tomorrow night then?
Darnell, I don't think
it's a real good idea
that we see each other.
What, I'm not good enough
for you all of a sudden?
I'm too young, that's it.
I'm not as young as you think I am.
They held me back a year, you know.
- That's not it.
- What is it then?
I have a boyfriend.
[Sighs] Did you have this boyfriend
when you showed me around?
Yes.
Well, um, it didn't seem
to bother you then.
- I'm willing to overlook it now.
- I was mad at him then.
- For what?
- I caught him with another girl.
- A white girl.
- A white girl?
You're still with this nigger?
You won't gimme no play?
Look, Darnell,
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to lead you on
in any way, but I'm really
glad you came here.
[Whispers]
See ya.
Wait, hold up,
hold up, hold up!
I can at least walk with you, can't I?
Ain't no crime in that.
- I'm in a hurry.
- I can keep up. I run the 40 in 4.3.
- [Man] Woo-ha-he!
- Hey, Autumn.
- Hey, Ray.
- Where you been?
I was just talking to a friend of mine.
Ray, this is...
DarnellJefferson,
tailback.
Ray Griffen,
starting tailback.
Yeah, I know.
That's why they recruited me.
[Griffen] The two boys they recruited
before you are washing cars now.
- You better start
strengthenir your wrist.
- Huh!
This guy's kinda funny.
Listen, man, just make sure
and give your best to Miss Lily for me,
all right?
Stay black, bro!
What in the hell
is that supposed to mean?
[Instructor]
Twenty-one minutes remaining
in math section two.
Twenty-one minutes.
[Low Chattering]
Hey, when are we
gettir them scores back
on our placement test?
Who cares?
I flunked three times before I got in.
Long as you in the program,
they'll get you through.
Maybe not with a degree,
but they're gonna
keep you eligible.
Just don't do nothir embarrassir
they can't cover you for.
Hell, they even give Alvin here
copies of his test in advance.
Sells 'em for 100 bucks a pop
to people in his class.
'Course he, ah, still gotta have
somebody read 'em to 'im!
Fuck you, doughboy,
I can read! See that shoe?
It says "Adidas."
I taught him that.
Still, don't know, man.
Promised the Rev I'd get a degree.
I don't wanna
let him down.
What do you think, nigger?
You gonna be on the Supreme Court?
All you need to know
is how to sign an NFL contract.
- Period.
- [Lats] Yup, yup.
I think both Joe
and the university
are best served...
by a straightforward
Heisman campaign;
nothing too gimmicky.
In order to capitalize
on the momentum created by
the Sports Illustrated cover,
we've compiled a mailing list
of around 1,300 opinion makers:
Newspapers, football writers,
sports anchors.
First we send them a packet
on Joe and his achievements:
Bio, stats,
plus human interest stuff;
committed to academics,
charity work, etc.
Then we update it
each week with a postcard.
Heisman voters hate opening envelopes.
You really think
this is won'th it?
I mean, you think I got a shot
at winning this thing?
Certainly.!
Plus, it's a good thing
for the program.
Publicizes the school,
gives a boost to recruiting...
And it's a great thing for you.
Jumps up your draft position,
the size of your
first contract, everything.
- It's a great opportunity.
- And all you gotta do
is back it up on the field.
And we have no doubts
about that, 'cause we know...
"Kane is Able."
- [Whistling, Shouting]
- Break!
[Coach #1]
Play Ball!
[Sam] No, no, no. Keep that
index finger on the ball.
On the ball, all right?
Joe's too pumped up,
tryirto win a Heisman
on every damned throw.
- I don't think he's ready
for all this hype.
- Little late to worry now.
[Coach #2] If we don't do
something to follow up...
that Sports Illustrated cover,
it's gonna look like
we don't believe in our peers.
Hey, you let me worry
about it, please?
Yeah!
Set! Blue 80!
Blue 80! Hike!
[Shouting, Grunting]
Hah!
Uuh!
Huuuuhh!
[Darnell] Too high, big boy.
So long, sucker.
- Yeah!
- Comir to get ya, field boy!
- Come on. Yeah!
- Lights out, baby!
[Grunting, Shouting]
Lattimer.!
Whaddya...
You cut out that
necktie tackle crap.
What're you tryir to do,
make a highlight reel, huh?
That man left you huggir air!
You take this helmet
and you put it right
in his numbers, okay?
Drive it through his guts.
I don't wanna see nothir
but snot bubbles in his nose.
All right, let's move
that drill down 15 yards,
let's go. Come on, boys.
[Coach] All right, let's go.
Let's move it guys.
[Shouting,
Chattering Continues]
- Jefferson, are you injured
or are you hurt?
- What does that mean?
Well, if you're hurt,
you can still play.
If you're injured, you can't.
So are you hurt
or are you injured?
Uuuh,
think I'm just hurt.
That's good.
Then get up.
[Grunting]
Oh, shit!
Now, that was a hell of a run
you just made.
Think how good it would have been
for us if you still had the ball.
This is a football. I want you
to carry this with you always.
Never let it out of your sight.
Hey, boys, listen!
Jefferson here's gonna be carryir
this football on campus.
Anyone of you guys see him,
I want you to try to
slap it out of his hand.
All right, try to knock it out
and recover it.
Anybody but you...
return this ball to me,
you'll wish you were never born.
All right,
let's step it up.!
Welcome to thejungle
we got fun and games
We got everything you want
How do we know
Just 'cause we are
the people that can find
Whatever you may need
Whenever we're together,
honey
Grows thatjungle seed
Jungle
Welcome to thejungle
Wort you come along
Na-na-na-na-na-na
Please, please
Welcome to thejungle
won't you pass here every day
Learn to live like an animal
who's noble when we play
Got you locked up
with what you see
Tag it and you leave
You can have
anything you want
But you better not
take it from me
In thejungle
Welcome to thejungle
Wort you come along
Waah
I'm gonna watch you bleed
[Moaning]
[Grunting]
Shit, Lattimer's an animal all
of a sudden. He's gotta be on somethir
Steroids?
How come you always think my guys
are the ones juicir, anyway?
[Coach #1] He's on
the punt return team for three years, ;
then he gains 35 pounds of rip
in one summer...
- and an attitude to go with it?
- Gentlemen,
we're not doctors.
The NCAA has a testing program
for this kind of thing.
I suggest
we let them handle it.
And it's not that hard
to gain 35 pounds over summer...
if you hit the gym
real hard.
[Groaning Continues]
Uuh! Uh-Uuh! Aah!
[Muttering, Chuckling]
Hey, how's your arm, man?
- It's pretty good for the first day.
- Cool.
- Hey, Bud?
- Uh-huh?
- How come you never ask me
about my arm?
- You have an arm?
Wanna hold this for me?
I'll meet you outside.
No problem.
Don't strain yourself.
- [Whirring Sound]
- [Grunting]
[Clinking]
How ya doir?
Fine.
- It's a little late
to be workir out, isn't it?
- [Sighs]
It's the only time I could get
in here when the football team
wasrt using it.
Yeah, well, if it wasrt
for the football team,
you wouldn't have
all this nice equipment to use.
So what, are you firmir up,
or what?
I don't need to firm up.
I'm strengthening my knee.
I had orthoscopic surgery.
Yeah, I had my knee
scoped once too.
So, uh, you wanna go out
for a beer or something
after you're done?
I don't go out with football players.
They're all full of themselves.
I saw you on the cover of
Sports Illustrated, so you're
probably worst than most.
Huh! So you won't consider
doir anything with me?
No.
All right, well, at least tell
me what happened to your knee?
What'd you do, fall out
of your convertible?
You know what?
There is one thing
that I might consider
doing with you.
Oh, yeah?
What's that?
[Grunting]
Shit!
Uh...
Thanks for the game, Heisman.
You took it real well.
I want a rematch.
- A rematch?
- Yeah, that's right.
Some other sport.
I took my beatings.
You owe me one, right?
Either that
or you go out with me.
I'll think about it.
Give me a call.
[Chuckling]
- How'd I do?
- That was a real good date, Joe.
Remind me to take her out sometime!
Ha-ha!
Damn! Fuck.
Yo, my man. Can you tell me
where Gaines Hall is at?
- It's at the end of Douglas Quad.
- Thanks a lot, yo.
Where the hell
is Douglas Quad?
Darnell, I've reviewed
your placement test...
and I'm afraid you've failed
to meet our requirements...
in several areas.
Does this mean
I can't play ball?
No, it means you're
going to have to take
some remedial courses.
Specifically,
Math 0, English 0,
plus an American history
survey course.
You won't get college credit for them,
but they will help you
prepare to take...
the placement test again
at the end of the quarter.
If you pass at that time,
you'll be able to take regular
college-level courses.
But first things first.
To start, I'm approving
a tutor for you.
Tutor?
I don't need no tutor.
Any tutor.
And yes, you do.
What's up, Autumn?
Hey, Darnell.
What are you doir here?
Hey, nothir
I'm just kickirit.
I was talkir to my advisor
and he seems to think I need a tutor.
Just to get me over
a couple of rough spots, that's all.
I was lookir on this list
right here and I saw your name.
I figured if you can't keep
my attention, nobody can.
[Laughs]
I'm sorry, Darnell,
but you're going to have to get
yourself another tutor because
I've already been assigned.
- I'm tutoring Scott Sherman.
- Not anymore.
I asked Coach Winters to switch us.
- Coach Winters wouldn't do that.
- Yes, he would.!
Yo, I'm a much bigger prospect
that Scott Sherman.
Would you look at him?
Look.!
He ain't nothir but a big,
fat, pork rind-eatir lineman
on the scout team.
Come on, now, girl. You could
teach me some real erudition.
You know what I'm sayir?
Will you stop using those big words?
It makes you sound ridiculous.
What are you talkir about?
I'm improvir myself.
Every day I learn a new word
out of the dictionary.
Mendacious, pejorative,
antithetical, commensurate...
And you don't even know
how to use 'em right!
Pretending to be smart
is not the same thing
as being educated.
It's just a con
that makes you sound stupid,
no matter how big
a prospect you are.
Okay. But that's even more of a reason
for you to be my tutor.
You just
taught me somethir.
[Bud-Lite]
Oh, Mr. Heisman?
- Joe? We got a present for you.
- [Joe] Oh, no.
Carryir you, as usual.
[Bud-Lite] Kinda looks like you,
but not as skinny.
- Joey, you're our hero.
- [Snorts]
[Sarcastic Groaning, Laughing]
[Sighing]
[Ringing]
Uhh.
- Hello?
- Hi, it's Joe Kane.
It's 3:00 in the morning.
I wanna know
what you decided.
[Sighs]
I don't know.
I couldn't think of any other sports
I could beat you at.
Then I'll pick you up
tonight at 6:00.
Wha...?
- We're goir on that?
- Yeah, I thought we might take
a little ride.
I promised my Dad
I'd never get on one of those.
What are ya, one of those
trust-fund princesses?
It's okay for me
to play a game I don't know,
but I ask you to try somethir different
and you hide behind your daddy?
Okay. We go slow.
No cowboy stuff.
[Engine Starting, Revving]
- Am I goir too fast for ya?
- What?
Am I goir
too fast for ya?
- Oh, no, this is fine.
- Good. Let's get it!
- [Screaming] Stop!
- [Howling]
- Slow down!
Goddammit, slow down!
- Yeah!
Where are we going?
This isn't even
a real road.
Joe, are you
listening to me?
[Screaming]
Joe, slow down!
Joe, look out!
[Screaming]
Jo-o-o-o-oe!
Uuh!
Goddammit! You crazy?
How could you do that?
- You could've killed us!
- Woo!
[Joe]
Uh, that could've been ugly.
- Goddamn!
- I've done that
100 times before.
- Never with anybody on the back,
but it was fun, wasrt it?
- [Gasping]
You just wanted to scare me.
Are you happy now?
Yeah. Actually, the scream
was even better than I thought.
You got just about every dog
in hearing distance
wantir to mate with you.
[Dogs Barking Faintly]
Do you come here a lot?
Now and then.
Why?
Well, it's not exactly
a campus favorite.
This is more like
hidir out.
[Man]
Nice shot.!
I like to go places
where nobody knows me.
Why, is this
too low-rent for you?
No, no.
- My father owned a place like this.
- Your father?
- Mm-hmm.
- What, you mean he owned
a chain of these?
No. You know,
not everybody who plays tennis
grew up in a country club, Joe.
My dad could never afford
to send me here.
When I hurt my knee I was afraid
I was gonna lose my scholarship.
So, you're a full-ticket jock,
just like me?
Yeah.
Are you disappointed?
No, I just never went out
with a jock before.
Huh! Is that what's goir on here?
We're goir out?
What do you think?
Come on.
I think you're, ah,
crazy for jeopardizing
your scholarship...
and a pro career
by jumping motorcycles
off of highways.
Just tryir
to keep my edge.
-  If you don't know me by now
- Hmm!
See, the guys, they...
They look to me 'cause they think
I'll do anything.
If I lose that,
then I'm just another guy.
Then we'd get
the shit kicked out of us.
If you don't know me by now
If you don't know me, baby
you will never, never never know me
-  No, you won't
- You scare me, Joe.
Ah-hey
If you don't know me by now
You will never, never
never know me
The keys.
Look, I told you. During the season,
no unnecessary risks.
Any guy that's up
for the Heisman should be
able to remember that, no?
Thanks. Good night.
Now, using the things
we worked on yesterday,
I want you to write...
a two or three page
essay about some aspect
of your life...
other than football.
What's in my life
besides football?
I don't know.
Your father.
You could write
about your dad.
I don't know
much about him.
He was off in Detroit
workir in a car plant
when I was born.
Got laid off.
Tried to rob a liquor store
to get us some money.
Got caught.
Died in prison.
Some kind of heart problem.
Well, maybe you can write
about your mother.
She was usually
workir two jobs.
One night she stopped
at a grocery store
to get me some root beer.
She got caught
in gang cross fire.
Shot three times.
Died on the way
to the hospital.
Want me to write
about that?
No.
That's good,
'cause ain't none of that true.
Gee whiz, Darnell!
What kind of a thing is that
to do to somebody? It's not funny.
I had you goir,
didn't I?
No, you did not have me goir!
Why would you make up
something like that?
Sounded more interesting
than the truth.
I never knew
who my dad was.
When I was 12, my mother
took a vacation in Chicago
and never came back.
Well, then, maybe just this once,
you can write about football.
I've seen a lot of
shitty things in life, Autumn.
That's why I know
when I see something good.
Okay, let's review the chapter
I read you yesterday.
Which two city-states
fought in the Punic Wars?
I don't know.
Detroit and Buffalo?
- Oh, come on, Alvin.
You're gonna be tested on this.
- [Chuckling]
Rookies, you pay attention.
This is what I expect
out of you. Alvin, you ready?
- Yes, sir.
- All right, this is
Mississippi State's offensive set.
Second and two on our own 24.
What defensive set might we call?
Eagle, zipper, hero,
unless the setback shifts into the I.
Good.
Third and seven.
- Oakie, thunder, lion.
- What's your assignment?
Kill the quarterback.
Hit the tight end so hard
his girlfriend dies.
- Kill everybody.
- There you go.
Ready?
[Grunting]
Uuh!
Very nice game.
Well, you owe me a dinner.
But you're takirit real well.
Now, George Washington
won a few skirmishes,
but he never actually
won a real battle.
- Still, he won the war...
- Shit!
[Men Shouting]
Fumble.! Fumble.! Fumble.!
- [Instructor]
What the hell's goiron?
- It's mine!
- I got it, man!
- I got it, I got it!
[Instructor]
Return to your seats, gentlemen,
this is unacceptable behavior.!
- Gentlemen...
- [Grunting, Groaning]
- Gimme the ball!
- Got it, punk!
Get yo' butt outta my face!
[Men Muttering]
[Man] You lucky, chump.
Catch you slippir
Sorry.
I lost my ball.
[Chattering]
[Man]
You in there, buddy.
Yes! Yeah!
Starting defense!
Place at the table!
Woo-oo-oo!
Woo-oo, yeah!
[Coach #1]
Looks likeJoe's comiraround.
He should be ready for Saturday.
[Lats Grunting]
Place at the table!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
- Yeah! Woo!
- [Alarm Wailing]
Jesus! You think
we oughta tell coach?
Hell no, he don't
wanna know about this.
- Woo! Yeah!
- [Alarm Wailing]
Make sure you tell Lattimer
that the NCAA will be
testing on Saturday.
Yeah, baby!
Starting defense! Woo!
[Sam] As my upperclassmen
know, we have Pride Night every
year before our opening game.
So I'd like each of you
to talk about what you
like best about football,
and what you're most proud of
off the field.
Now, I've asked some
of my veterans here to start.
Lattimer?
I don't know.
It's the battle.
The goir to war
with the other guys.
- [Quarterback] Set.!
- [Lats] Hangirtogether.
- Blue 80.! Hut.!
- Havirour own dorm.
Stayirin hotels
the night before the games.
Settirourselves apart.
Beirdifferent
than everybody else.
Havira chance
to be somebody.
To do somethirthat people
look up to you for.
Your strength.
Your courage.
Not everybody
can play football.
We're the lucky ones.
[Darnell] The thing
that I'm most proud of myself for...
Just that I'm here...
and not in jail
or dead.
I ain't no statistic.
Well, the great thing
about football is, uh,
that you can lose yourself
in it.
There's no time to think
or to worry.
You just, ah,
you just move and react.
Hell, everything else
fades away.
Best thing
is when you get a guy.
Know it's... killir him.
But you feel great.
It's just him and you...
and he's the one
that's hurtir
[Men Chattering]
[Grunting]
- Yeah!
- [Man] Game's on.!
[Crowd Shouting, Chanting]
[Whooping]
[Bud-Lite]
Don't be late!
- Hey! This big enough
for you, baby?
- Hell, yeah, I'm with it!
[Announcer] Welcome, everybody,
to the Wolf Den...
where the ESU Timberwolves,
led by Heisman Trophy candidate
Joe Kane, open their season...
against
the Mississippi State Bulldogs.
[Whistle Blowing]
The Bulldogs have won the toss,
so the T-wolves will be kicking off.
And we are underway.
Kick coming down to
Tyler in the end zone.
- He's gonna bring it up.
- [Grunting]
Back to the 15...
to the 20.
- Brought down at the 22-yard line
by Powell and Ellswon'th.
- [Whistle Blowing]
- Now we'll see
how the ESU defense,
- [Cheering]
Led by All-American linebacker
Alvin Mack does...
- in its first test
of the season.
- Yeah! All right!
- Hit squad is in the house!
- Yeah, it's party time, baby!
- All right now, baby, all right.
Sixty minutes, balls out.
- Yeah!
Let's open up the whole can of kick ass
and kill 'em all.
- Let the paramedics sort 'em out.
- Yeah.
- Right.
- Razor, bear claw, stinger. Ready...
- [All] Break!
[Announcer] Bulldogs coming
to the line of scrimmage,
T- wolves in their standard 4-3.
Hey, 23! Don't think
I don't recognize you,
you poo-butt motherfucker!
Hey, pay attention
when I'm talkir to you, nigger!
- What?
- You're the guy who shot
my mother, aren't you?
Shut up, man.
You know I never knew your mother.
- Hut!
- You were tryir to steal her
fuckir car, you cocksucker!
You didn't think
I was gonna find ya, did ya?
But I got you now, nigger.
I'm gonna bust your gut open
and watch you die.!
- [Quarterback] Hut!
- [Alvin Screaming]
- [Announcer] Lock pitches
to Tyler, sweeping left.
- [Alvin] Say your prayers!
- [Announcer] Mack cuts 'im off.
- Aw, shit!
[Lats] Come back here,
you little pussy.! Uuuh.!
- [Grunting]
- [Announcer] Oh.!
Tyler crunched by Lattimer.
- [Announcer] Fumble.!
- No! It's mine! It's mine!
It's our ball, it's our ball,
it's our ball, it's our ball,
it's our ball.
[Announcer] They unstack 'em and...
ESU has got it.!
- Hell yeah! Hell yeah!
- All right!
Beautiful thing, baby!
Gettir your nose in there!
Atta baby, B.A.!
Good pop, Lats.
Stay it, buddy.
Joe, Joe, come here.
Joe!
Let's go up top.
Take the team right away.
Z-3 motion, let's go!
[Announcer] So we'll see
what Kane does here...
as the Wolves attempt
to capitalize on the turnover.
- [Player] Come on let's go.
Let's do it, now.
- Let's take it to 'em now.
Trips right, motion Z-3.
Let's put the women and children to bed
and go lookir for dinner, boys.
- On four. Ready?
- [All] Break!
Yippee ki-yi-yo
Git along little dogies
It's your misfortune
and none of my own
Shut up, snowflake!
You think you're on Star Search?
Nope. We're roundir dogies
into the end zone and the trail
runs right over your ass.
Bullshit! You gonna be my bitch!
You gonna be my punk bitch, baby!
[Grunting, Groaning]
[Announcer]
Kane fades back to pass.
Ha-ha! You'll never be
half the man your mama was! Aaah!
[#75] It's your misfortune now,
fat boy! Take this! Eat it!
[Announcer] Looking down field...
Ward has a step on his man.!
Kane going for it all.
Fires for Flea Ward
in the end zone...
Great catch.!
Touchdown, ESU.
- Yes! Yes!
- Hold on!
Get off me!
Stop it! Get off!
- Play is over.!
- 'Scuze me. My dogies
just reached the end zone...
- and I gotta do some celebratir.
- Fuck you.!
- Yeah! That's it, Flea!
- It's on the money, right there!
[Bud-Lite] Hell of a pass, man.
Wish I'd seen it.
[Announcer]
2.;05 left in the game.
Wolves up, 28-20.
Jefferson,
get in there for Griffen.
DarnellJefferson making his first
appearance at tailback.
Kane brings him up
to the line of scrimmage.
- Hike!
- [Grunting, Groaning]
[Announcer]
Pass toJefferson up the middle.
Out to the 35-, 36-yard line.
Nice game for the freshman
who had a little bit
of fumble-itis in fall practice.
Hey, hey...
Hey.!
'Scuze me, son, but we're
gonna be needir that football
for another couple of minutes.
- [Chuckling]
- Right, right.
- [Player] Huddle up.!
- [Blows Whistle]
[Announcer] Eight seconds left.
Last chance for Mississippi State.
- Hike!
- [Grunting, Groaning]
- [Announcer]
Lock fades back to pass.
- U-u-u-uh!
[Announcer] Lattimer coming
from the left side... Oh.!
- He almost takes Lock's head off.
- Looks like you lost
your bonnet, baby!
Yeah! Yeah!
Woo!
Yeah! Aha-ha!
[Announcer] And that'll do it.
The game is over...
as the '93 season
gets off to a good start
for the Timberwolves...
with a 28 to 20 win over
the Mississippi State Bulldogs.
- Get to keep the car,
got the house for another week!
- [Laughing]
- [Chattering]
- One at a time. Go ahead, Rhoda.
This performance today,
two touchdown passes,
another you ran in.
Where do you think this puts you
in the Heisman race?
Well, I really don't
know about that.
That's up to you guys.
[Rhoda]
This way.!
And now, let's turn
to our Heisman watch.
We begin with Sports Illustrated
cover boyJoe Kane of ESU,
who led his team to an impressive
victory this afternoon.
Though the real test will come
in four weeks...
against Michigan and their
Heisman hopeful, Tim Waymen, ;
Tim "he could go
all the" Waymen.
He'll be lookir to do so
against the Timberwolves.
And of course, the "able"
Kane will be looking to do so as well.
[Clinking]
Hey, Darnell. Did a really
great job out there today.
- Way to hold onto that pigskin.
- Thank you.
Little something for ya.
Keep up the good work.
- Played a hell of a game, son.
Proud of you.
- Thank you.
- Let me talk to you for a second.
- Thanks again.
- Yo, some guy just gave me $50, man.
- Don't worry.
You'll get about $500
or $600 once you start,
dependir on how you play.
But I thought we werert
supposed to take any money.
Ain't that a violation?
You cannot live
on no $500 a month
scholarship money.
The NC-double assholes
won't let us havejobs,
so you take your money
where you can get it.
As a matter of fact,
let me hold this for you
'til you see the light.
Shit, oughta be
payirus anyway.
Athletic department gets
$3 million just for goir
to a bowl game.
- [Chattering]
-  ["Pretty Little Funky Thang"
ByJameyJazz]
Pretty little funky thang
nothirlike I ever I seen
Woo.!
Pretty little funky thang
bouncy little play by play
nothirlike I ever I seen
Hey.
Forget it, nigger.
No chance for you there.
- How do you figure?
- [Grunts]
Griffers goir
to medical school.
She likes that light-skinned
respectable shit.
You? You just
a ghetto toy.
- Can I have this one?
- Hey, I don't think so.
What you worried about, boy?
You haven't lost your
startirjob just yet.
- Hey, you got a problem, buddy?
- Ray, just one, okay?
All right, just one.
Take it easy, Darnell.
You are putting me in
a very awkward situation here.
[Darnell] I had a little encouragement
along the way.
Listen, I want
to see you, Autumn.
Not in a study hall;
not like your student.
- I want to be taken seriously.
- Darnell, I do take you seriously.
But if you haven't noticed,
I'm still with Ray...
and I cannot just go paradir around
town with you.
We don't have to go paradir.
We can go someplace different;
- someplace that nobody'll see us.
- [Sighs]
Why am I even considering this?
It's crazy.
Hey, genius. You all caught up
on your arithmetic?
Yeah, yeah. You only gained,
uh, 37 yards on 12 carries.
- Hey, hey! Come on!
- You want some of this? Come on!
- Hey!
- Easy.
- Come on!
- Cool.
Just calm it,
buddy, Darnell.
So much for
team unity, huh?
- Yeah.
- You didn't have anything
to do with that, did ya?
- Hell no! You know me.
- Chshh! Right!
Come here.
We need to talk.
Look, I'm gettir
a little sick of that
asshole, Autumn.
I don't like you
hangir out with him.
It's embarrassing.
- I don't hang out with him.
I tutor him.
- Then have him get another tutor.
I can't do that.
I promised him I'd help him pass...
his qualifying exam,
and I can't go
bailir out on him now.
What the hell difference does it make?
They'll grease him
through no matter what he does.
Nobody's ever gonna see
that boy graduate.
Hey, don't tell me
you've fallen for this guy.
He's nothir.
He's just another gangbanger with speed.
I'm tryir to help him out.
What're you more afraid of, Ray?
Losir your girl
or your position?
Maybe you better think
a little bit more about
what you're in danger of losing.
Well, maybe I will.
[Crickets Chirping]
So, where you
wanna go?
- [Autumn Laughing]
- [Darnell Imitating Girl]
Whatcha find?
[Darnell]
Now, you gotta make it all the
way around at least once, girl.
You're right, Darnell.
I don't think anybody
would find us here. Ha!
Hey, I figure the key
is to go places
only white people go.
- [Laughing]
- I think next time we'll go bowling.
Plus, I saw this on
Rocky, you know.
I always used to wonder
how a guy...
who's supposed to be
such a great athlete
was skatir so bad.
Nice form, Jefferson.
You all right?
Thank you, Darnell. This is fun.
Well, sort of fun.
Nah, you were good
for your first time.
Well, actually,
this isn't my first time.
My dad took me skating once
when I was little.
- Hey, your pops used to play ball
for ESU, didn't he?
- Yeah. How'd you know?
I saw his picture
on the Wall of Fame.
You know, you got his eyes.
Luckily, you didn't get his thighs.
[Chuckling]
I know!
Make sure you mean it,
all right?
[Whispers]
Yeah.
Excuse me.
What's your name?
Bobby Collins.
Could I see
your I.D. Please?
[Winters] You took someone
else's test? Damn it, Louanne.!
I mean, how could you be
so stupid, stupid!
- He was behind,
he needed help. I'm sorry, I just...
- Sorry?
I mean, you weaken my authority
with the players.
It looks like I'm runnir a dirty pro...
And Bobby Collins!
Of all people,
Bobby Collins! Why?
I don't know.
I thought
that he loved me.
Loved you? Loved you?
This guy loves anything
that wears a skirt!
This little rat bastard.!
Now you're both expelled.
If I tried to use my influence
to get you back in,
it just destroys my credibility
with the university.
- I just can't!
- I don't want you to.
I'll get in someplace.
[Knocking]
Come in, Collins.
Come in.
Coach.
Listen, I just want you to know
that I'm real sorry about this
whole thing with Louanne.
I was real glad to hear
she's gonna be goir
to junior college here...
Shut up.
I could, uh, pull some strings
to help you out here.
But I won't.
You've embarrassed the school, ;
you've embarrassed me, ;
and you embarrassed
my family.
So, as of now, you are no longer
a member of this university
or its football team.
Now, go clean out
your locker.
You get outta here before I knock
the piss outta you!
Have you seen this?
You got a "D" on your math test.
I kinda figured that.
I had some trouble on the last part.
Darnell, we went over this
entire chapter last week.
Look, I thought you wanted to learn.
But if all you wanna do
is fake your way through,
then you're gonna have to
find yourself another tutor
and waste her time.
Autumn, we just had a good time.
Why you gettir all riled up
about one test?
- So far it's the only test!
- [Man] Shh.!
Look, I don't wish to be cast
in a pejorative light.
Therefore, I am
dedicating myself...
to achieving on a level
more commensurate with my abilities.
Hmm! You're amazing.
[Lynn Swann]
Joe, relax. Look right at me.
Pay no attention to the camera, okay?
- Okay.
- You ready?
All right,
here we go.
Joe, this game is being billed
as a potential Heisman shoot-out.
Did you feel any additional
pressure this week, knowing...
- that you'd be going head to head
with Heisman rival, Tim Waymen?
- Set! Hike!
[Joe] Oh, I'd be lyir
if I said I didn't, um...
The, uh...
I mean, you try to block it out
but it's basically impossible.
Everybody seems to be
talkir about it.
The radios, the newspapers
and all the interviews, you know?
Then there's the TV, always tryir
to get some sort of hype goir.
- Hold it, hold it!
- Sharon, what're you doing?
What you're saying is true,
but I don't think it's
the message you want to send.
It makes you seem a little nervous,
like the pressure
might be getting to you.
This game is nationally televised,
so most Heisman voters will be watching.
I think a more casual approach
is better.
Controlled, modest, casual.
- Okay.
- Okay, thank you.
[Swann] I'll make this take two.
Here we go, Joe.
Joe, this game is being billed
as a potential Heisman shootout.
Did you feel any
additional pressure this week,
knowing you'd be going
head to head against
Heisman rival, Tim Waymen?
Well, to tell you the truth,
Lynn, I hadrt really
thought about it.
[Swann] So there you have it, folks.
Joe Kane remains unfazed...
before his battle against
Heisman rival, Tim Waymen.
Odds makers have installed Michigan
as a three-point favorite,
but the Timberwolves will have
the advantage of playing...
in the friendly confines
of Wolf Den Stadium.
[Sighs]
Hello, Dad? No, I was
just callir because, uh,
Michigan game is on TV tomorrow
and I thought you might wanna watch it.
It's broke?
Well, can't you go over toJackie B's
and watch it with Jerry?
Oh.
No, fine. Well then uh...
I hope you feel better.
Yeah. Bye.
Are your parents coming
to the game tomorrow?
My mom died
when I was young.
My dad's never
seen me play.
Why not?
I don't know.
I guess he doesn't like football.
- You're one of the best
players in the country.
- He's just not into it.
Okay?
Okay.
Kane fades back...
sees his man...
[Clanging, Glass Clinking]
[Sighs]
Bad hands.
What's goir on,
Joe?
You asked me out here like you
wanted to talk about somethir,
but you're not sayir anything.
Are you worried
about tomorrow?
What do I have to be worried about?
I'm a Heisman candidate, remember?
[Sighs] Joe, why are you thinkir
like this?
You're havir a great year.
You've got millions of dollars
waitir for you in the pros.
How do you know
what's waitir for me?
You don't
even know me.
I don't know you?
How could you say that?
'Cause if you did,
you wouldn't be with me.
You only know the guy
who's supposed to be
makir millions in the pros.
That's what you think?
That I'm with you for the money?
- I don't know why you're with me!
- Fuck you!
You know, maybe you're right.
Maybe I don't know you.
[Bell Ringing]
[Horn Blowing]
Joe!
Joe, what are you doir?
Get off the track.
Joe!
No!
Joe! Joe!
Oh, my God!
Joe!
Oh, God, Joe.! No.!
Joe, are you all right?
You okay?
- Yes.
- [Panting]
- Just lettir off some steam.
- Why do you do this crazy shit?
- [Panting]
- You should've got away from me
while you still had the chance.
I don't wanna get away from you.
What's wrong, Joe?
I'm a Kane,
Camille.
We're just a bunch
of drunks and fuck-ups!
It's what we do.
It's in our blood.
My dad, my uncles, my brothers.
We all drink and sooner
or later, we all fuck up.
Sometimes I just feel like
I'm waiting for my turn.
You don't have to be like them.
You can give all that up.
Then what?
Then what would I be?
You'd still beJoe.
And that's enough.
[Announcer]
4.;29 to go and it's been a great one, ;
two undefeated teams
goirafter each other.
Michigan up by four,
24-20.
But the lead has changed
hands three times.
And, Bo, you get the feelir
that whoever has the ball last
is gonna win it.
Well, it's been billed as
a Heisman Trophy shoot-out.
And it's been all of that.
[Chanting]
E-S-U, E-S-U, E-S-U!
[Crowd Cheering]
[Announcer] Third down and eight,
ESU at the Michigan 20.
- [Man] Slot right.
- Set!
[Crowd Cheering Continues]
[Kane]
Blue 80! Motion, motion!
- Blue 80! Hut!
- Watch the blitz.
- [Players Grunting]
- [Announcer] Kane back to pass.
Can't find anybody.
Gets away.
Gonna run it himself.
[Grunting]
At the ten...
the five.
- [Grunting]
- [Kane Groaning]
Touchdown, ESU.!
What a run by Kane.
And Kane is still down.
He took quite a shot from Ryan.