Don't-Don't.
Damn.
Destiny's a pretty big concept
when you think about it.
Where you are in life,
how you got there...
what would have happened if one
thing or another had been different.
To be honest...
I never gave it
much thought, myself...
until today,
June 14th...
my 35th birthday...
and without a doubt,
the strangest day of my life.
Do you remember
the old story that starts...
this guy
goes into a bar?
Well, I'm the guy,
and here's the story.
But wait a minute.
I'm getting way ahead of myself.
To tell
this story right...
I should start
where it really begins...
20 years ago today,
as a matter of fact.
June 14th, 1970,
my 15th birthday...
and also
a very strange day.
It was the all-state
high school championship game...
bottom of the 9th,
2 outs.
Our school hadn't made it
to the finals in 25 years...
so out of a town
of 30,000 people...
38,000 showed up
for the game.
Fillmore High
had us by a run...
and it was
a 3-2 count.
Fenwick was
standing on 3rd...
like the bag was getting ready
to explode under his feet.
The championship had
come down to one batter...
Yeah, you guessed it...
yours truly,
Larry Burrows.
Haskins was
throwing fastballs...
because that was
the only pitch he ever threw.
So I was ready
for the next one.
Paste it, Lar!
You can do it.
Have an eye!
Swing, babe,
it's all yours!
Then something
weird happened.
Don't ask me
what it was...
'cause it only happened
for a split second.
But that was enough
to change my life forever.
Strike 3!
Why is it when you do
something terrific...
9 times out of 10
you're alone...
but when you
screw up really big...
the whole world
is watching?
I wanted to crawl under
home plate and never come out.
As usual...
my best friend, Clip Metzler,
tried to cheer me up.
Clip's very big
on novelty gags.
Aren't they cool?
I scared the crap
out of my baby sister.
Want to
try them on?
Thanks, Clipper...
but I'd kinda
like to be alone.
Sure, Lar.
Whatever you say.
I'll call you later.
We'll see a movie.
We could see
Bonnie and Clyde again.
- What do you say?
- Sure, Clip.
Great!
I'll see you
later then.
It was the worst
moment of my life.
God, I felt bad.
Looks like you could
use one of these.
Yeah, I must've gotten
some dust in my eyes.
There was a lot
of dust out there.
- Thanks.
- You can keep it.
My aunt sends me
2 dozen every Christmas.
What's E.J.R. Stand for?
Ellen Jane Ripley.
What's your name?
LarryJoseph Burrows.
Nice to meet
you, Larry.
I thought that
was really sweet...
her not saying anything about
me crying like a big baby.
Really sweet.
- Larry?
- So I married her.
I've been calling you
for the last 5 minutes.
Not right then, of course,
but several years later.
Honey, were you
thinking about...
that silly
baseball game again?
No, no,
not at all.
I was working on
my '55 Porsche Spider.
I was, really.
Ain't it a beaut?
James Dean used
to drive one of these...
only his was
much bigger.
Ellen and I have
a pretty regular life.
We have a 2-bedroom
house in the suburbs...
that isn't
quite finished...
and a contractor named Guzelman
who doesn't want to quite finish it.
Hey, Mr. Guzelman,
how are you?
I haven't seen you
in the past 6 weeks.
I thought you were
captured by some aliens.
I got your message.
Problem with something?
Uh, yeah,
it's the driveway.
What's wrong?
Well, do you think
maybe we can pave it?
Well, you can't pave
until the mud is all gone.
Then we just have to get
rid of the mud, right?
I don't do mud.
You need
a mud guy for that.
- "A mud guy"?
- Yes.
- They have that?
- A mud guy, yes.
- Anything else?
- Now that you mention it...
it would be nice
to have a front lawn.
I need a check
for that.
- How much?
- $1,000.
- Don't you know another number?
- $2,000.
We have
a dog named Sammy.
I found him in an alley,
so I brought him home.
Sammy peed
on the rug again.
Way to go, Sammy.
He has a nervous bladder,
but a good heart.
We're out of Wheaties.
Do we have another box?
No, I forgot
to buy any. Sorry.
I've had Wheaties for breakfast
every morning of my life...
since I was
6 years old.
Is it too much to ask that
we keep an extra box on hand...
in the event of
a crisis like this?
You gave Guzelman
another check.
I did not give Guzelman
another check!
You're pissed off,
so you're taking it out on me.
Okay, okay, so I gave
Guzelman another check.
Don't you hate it when
somebody knows you that well?
You can't get
away with anything.
But I guess that's
just part of marriage.
So's the occasional argument.
They're tearing down
"The Golf of Mexico. "
- That's where we went on our 1 st date.
- That was our 2nd date.
It was our 1 st date.
You tripped over the grinning
bandito and split your pants.
Our 1 st date
was at Mr. Pizza.
You ate anchovies
and belched all night.
That was our 3rd date,
and I just burped a few times.
But we never argue
about anything important...
and we always make up.
Okay, okay, okay.
All right,
see you after work.
I forgot.
I'm gonna be late tonight.
There's a union meeting.
Another one?
What for?
They want me to be chairman
of the strike committee.
Somebody has to stop
these management creeps...
from laying everybody off.
But it's
my birthday.
What'd you say?
Never mind.
Forget it.
She forgot.
I need some coffee.
Nothing had happened
to make me think...
that this was
going to be...
anything more than just another
routine day at the office.
As usual,
by the time I arrived...
there was
no coffee left...
and no water.
Great.
So I did the only thing
I could think of.
I've gotta
have my coffee.
Why is it when you have a mouthful of
freeze-dried, your boss walks in on you?
How they hanging?
- I'm not interrupting anything, am I?
- No, Mr. Bumpers.
I'm having
my coffee.
Lay off the
"Mr. Bumpers"crap.
How many times
do I gotta tell you?
We're both on
the same team.
Jackie's a sweet guy, but kinda
dumb for a company president.
In football, they
called me "Cement Head,"
but you can
call me. Jackie.
Yes, sir,
Jackie.
I was going over
the quarterly reports.
Damn fine work.
A real touchdown.
- Just doing my job.
- Don't think I don't appreciate it.
A quarterback's only as good
as his linemen, right?
Yep.
I'm just a big, dumb jock who got
lucky and married the boss'daughter.
It's guys like you that
make me look like a hotshot.
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
Well, Lar...
just keep up
the good work, huh?
I just came by to see
how you were doing.
Now, that's funny.
Toilet paper in the nose.
Why didn't
I think of that?
I'm trying
to get a promotion!
Will you relax?
Your suck points are safe.
Believe me, Cement Head
didn't notice a thing.
Oh, Clip,
you kill me.
Happy 35th,
buddy.
Thanks, Clip.
I honestly didn't think
anybody remembered.
This is great.
Wow.!
- Artificial puke.
- That's the stuff we used to throw...
into the girls'
locker room...
so they'd get scared and
run out in their underwear.
This is the actual stuff?
Mr. Green confiscated this.
He did...
next day, I broke in
and confiscated it back.
- We had fun in those days.
- We sure did.
Well, where's my
"thank you" kiss?
No, Clip.
- No kiss.
- Just one.
We're in the office.
Stop it!
Why is it when your best friend's
kissing you on the head...
a beautiful woman
comes along and catches you?
Hi, CindyJo.
How are you?
What a coincidence.
Jackie was just here.
You know,
your husband.
How've you been?
We've been fine.
Clip and I
are pretty good.
Work, work,
that's all we do.
How've you been?
I've been fine.
Thank you for
asking... 3 times.
Uh, well...
I just wanted to make
absolutely sure.
Cindy. Jo's father
owns the company.
She's married
to. Jackie.
That's how a guy named "Cement
Head" gets to be president.
Did Jackie
go to his office?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sure he did.
He had lots of work to do.
Touchdowns
and all that stuff.
It was nice
seeing you again.
Bye, Clip.
Nice seeing you, too, Cindy.
Maybe it was because
it was my birthday,;
maybe it was seeing Cindy. Jo,
I don't know,;
but I'd been thinking about
what it would have been like...
if my life had
turned out differently.
Do you ever have
any regrets, Clip?
About how your life
has turned out...
or about
choices you made?
No!
- Oh... no.
- Oh.
But I figure I didn't make
all that many choices.
You know what my policy is?
Do nothing and see what happens...
- and things always seem to turn out fine.
- Yeah, for you.
Your problem is that nothing's
ever good enough for you.
You've got
the perfect life.
You've got a wonderful home,
a terrific wife, a good job...
and the best friend
money can buy.
What else could
a guy want?
A little excitement
would be nice.
I am so mad,
I could scream.
Maddie and Heather
were both laid off...
due to slow sales
or some bullshit like that.
They are laying people off,
making us work double shifts...
- to keep production levels up.
- She's got a point.
I did an inventory check,
and there's a surplus.
Technically, we should be
cutting back on production.
Can you check
into it, Larry?
The next person
to be laid off could be me.
Looking back,
I should have said no...
but I didn't.
I'll look into it.
Because
I'm an idiot.
Honey,
come on.
What?
She always kisses me.
I'm eating.
When the head of my
department, Niles Pender...
announced he was
raising production levels...
I couldn't keep
my big idiot mouth shut.
Ahem.
A comment, Burrows,
or phlegm rising in your throat?
Um, well...
just a thought
here, Niles.
Why do we need
more product...
when we have
a surplus inventory?
On what are you basing
this so-called surplus?
On the fact that...
that I recently counted
every box in the warehouse.
I would say we have a problem
with our perception of reality.
Sorry to barge in.
DoJackie and I
need to be here?
Not at all, Mr. Hansen.
Just production details.
Leo Hansen owns the company.
He's a very sweet man...
but he doesn't have a clue
about what's going on.
Then it's off
to the golf course.
Jackie's gonna show me
how to get rid of my slice.
I speak for all
of us when I say...
that is
wonderful news.
What time is that meeting
with Mr. Nakamura?
8:00, sir.
But we have a dinner
reservation at 9:00.
We have some important
business to finalize, sir.
Well...
Well, maybe I'd better
cancel the reservation.
That's an
excellent idea.
That's what I'll do, then.
Good-bye, y'all.
Touchdowns, everyone.
Incredible.
Since we seem to have
a disagreement over the inventory...
I suggest you
check it again.
Well, that would take
about 3 or 4 days.
I don't see
a problem.
Do you see
a problem with that?
Well...
do you, Burrows?
No, sir.
I should have told Niles
about the surplus myself...
but the guy scares
the shit out of me.
Don't worry.
He's an asshole.
I'll make it up
to you somehow.
Guess what's playing with
In the Heat of the Night.
- What?
- Bonnie and Clyde.
We haven't seen it
in about 20 years.
- Do you want to go?
- Of course I want to go.
Great. I'll see
you later then.
All right,
Clip.
Oh, and Larry?
You shouldn't
be talking to me.
After all, you've got
a lot ofboxes to count.
- Thanks for reminding me.
- Heh-heh-heh.
Get outta here.
What a jerk.
Excuse me. Would you
mind stepping back?
You wouldn't want me to
fork you to death, would you?
No.
No, we couldn't
have that.
After all, we hardly
know each other.
Since when
does that matter?
All right, you,
get back to work.
I know what
you're thinking.
Sometimes,
I get the feeling...
I'm missing out
on something.
What she's got, you don't need.
You sure?
Not absolutely...
but if I tried
to find out...
your mother
would kill me.
You're the dad
every kid dreams of.
Don't be such
a wise guy.
Petey Fleckman
just got canned.
That's 3 guys
since yesterday.
Something stinks,
and I don't mean...
the meat loaf
in the cafeteria.
Yeah, I know.
Hey, hey,
look at this.
That's the same bunch
he had down here last week.
- Who are they?
- Who knows?
Niles is trying
to pass them off...
as some championship
baseball team from Osaka.
One of them thinks Mickey Mantle is
something over a mouse's fireplace.
You're in
management.
- Check around a little, will ya?
- Yeah.
- I'll see what I can find out.
- You're aces, kid.
Looking back, I should
have said no to Dad...
but I didn't.
I was beginning to think that
maybe something was going on.
I decided to look
around Niles'office...
to see if I could
find anything.
I'd been an idiot
all morning, anyway...
so I figured,
why stop now?
Shit.
"Leveraged buy out
via Metasport. "
What the hell's
Metasport?
Shit.
Why is it, every time you
break into your boss'office...
he always
walks in on you?
Lose something,
Burrows?
Something
tells me I have.
Well, that brings me
back to where I began...
In the middle of nowhere
with a car that won't start.
All things
considered...
it had turned into
a pretty rotten birthday.
But nothing
in my wildest imagination...
could have prepared me
for what came next.
Evening.
Hi.
You got
a pay phone?
Right there.
Thanks.
Yeah, hi.
It's me again.
I'm gonna need
another tow.
I'm on the corner
of Cross and 3rd...
next to a bar.
Yeah, the station wagon...
the big blue
piece of shit.
I'll get
a new car.
All right.
"Get a new car. "
I've gotta get a new life.
Car trouble,
huh?
Yeah.
Tow truck will
be here in 20 minutes.
- Can I get you something?
- I could sure use it.
Light beer,
no glass, right?
Yeah.
How did you know?
Just a guess.
Say, don't I know
you from somewhere?
You seem familiar
to me, too.
Name's Mike.
Larry.
Larry Burrows, right?
You're the kid...
who lost the high school
championship in 1970.
Jesus heavenly Christ.
If I'd known
it was a sore point...
I wouldn't have
brought it up.
Forget it.
I'm getting used to it.
This whole day's
been a nightmare.
- Care to talk about it?
- It's lots of things.
I didn't have my
cereal this morning.
Didn't have
my coffee at work.
I got fired.
It's my 35th birthday,
and everyone forgot.
Almost everyone.
I got vomit from Clip.
Well...
- happy birthday.
- Thanks, Mike.
35 years old,
and my life is shit.
It can't be
that bad.
It's not
that it's bad...
it's just that
it's ordinary.
I do the same
thing every day.
Go to work,
come home;
build some model cars
or go bowling;
fall asleep
in front of the TV.
If I'd have just hit
that goddamn ball...
my life would have
turned out a lot better.
Some people
believe that...
things are the way
they are for a reason.
The reason
eludes me.
Can I have
another one?
Listen...
I've got just the thing
for a sober cynic...
like yourself.
It's a little something
of my own design.
I call it...
"The Spilt Milk. "
It's the one drink
there's no use crying over.
Very clever, Mike.
It does the job.
Try it.
So you think your life
would have been better...
if you'd hit
the ball, huh?
Yeah...
a lot better.
I swung too late,
that's all.
Yeah.
If I'd just started
a half-a-second sooner.
I did it,
I did it!
Yeah!
Half-a-second sooner,
and I would have been king.
A lousy
half-a-second.
I think I'll go outside
and wait for the tow truck.
Thanks for the
sympathetic ear, Mike.
Anytime, Larry.
That's what I'm here for.
Oh, great.
They towed
my car already.
You'd think they could've
at least come in and told me.
Is he closed
already?
Ah, damn.
Hey, Mike!
Mike, I need
to call a cab!
It's paved.
What do you know?
Old Guzelman
came through after all.
Must've found
a mud guy.
Hey, Ellen?
Let me in, will ya?
I gotta use the can.
Come on, honey.
My key won't work.
What the hell are ya doin'
banging on my door?
Who are you?
What's going on here?
What have you done
with my wife?
What are you
talking about?
Look, take whatever
you need and leave.
If you don't hurt anybody,
I won't call the cops.
Cops?
Man, I am a cop.
Just what's
your problem?
I don't have a problem.
I live here.
What are you doing
in my house?
Your house?
Show me some I.D., pal.
Yeah, okay.
You're gonna
feel like a fool.
I've lived here
for over a year.
"LawrenceJ. Burrows...
"11653 Bonny Meadow Lane...
Forest Hills. "
Where'd I get
this license?
Probably from the D.M.V.
Where everybody gets theirs.
This is my house
and I want to see my wife.
Now step
outta my way.
Try to come in
and I'll kick your ass.
I don't care.
I'm coming in.
- No, you're not!
- Yes, I am!
- You're not.!
- I am.!
Larry?
Mike!
- What are you doing here?
- We need to talk.
I gotta get
in my house.
That's one of the things
we need to talk about.
You don't
live there.
What?
Even the cab driver
knows you don't live here.
Now beat it!
It's all very simple, really.
You know that
little incident...
you didn't like
about your life?
The baseball game?
- It's been changed.
- Changed?
What do
you mean?
You hit
the 3-2 pitch...
out of
the park.
That's why I don't
live in my house?
Exactly.
When that moment changed...
everything else
in your life changed.
Ha, ha!
I get it.
I get it now.
This is great,
just great.
What did they
pay you for this?
- What does who pay me?
- Ellen and Clipster.
This is some kind
of birthday gag, right?
This is really great.
Who was that big guy
at the house?
Another actor?
Boy, he scared
the shit out of me.
I don't think
you understand.
Shhh, I don't want
to hear a thing.
I just want to
play along with it.
Do you do this a lot,
change people's lives?
I've been known to make
a few adjustments now and again.
I live in a hotel?
It's a private home,
and it's all yours.
Yeah, right.
Wait here until
I get to the door.
- You wouldn't want to miss the expression on my face.
- Not for all the world.
I assume you're
taken care of...
but here's $5.00.
You were really great.
Wow, this must've
cost them a fortune.
I'm here at the door
to my new home.
I'm Larry Burrows,
but you probably already know that.
Yes, of course, sir.
Is my wife here?
As if I didn't know.
Of course she is.
Wow, nice setup.
I didn't know you could rent
places like this for parties.
- What's your name?
- It's Boswell, sir.
Good name.
You pick that yourself?
Here, here.
Here's a fin.
Get yourself
something nice.
- "A fin"?
- Boswell...
watch how surprised
I'm gonna be.
Get ready with
the Academy Award.
Honey, I'm here!
It's me!
You're home!
I was so worried.
Daddy, Daddy,
did you bring us something?
Ludwig went
to pick you up...
- but they said you'd already left.
- CindyJo.
What are you doing here?
Are you in on this?
Where's Clip
and Ellen?
Who are Clip and Ellen?
What are you talking about?
- My surprise birthday party.
- It's in 2 hours.
You told me you didn't
want it to be a surprise...
because you
hate surprises.
Darling,
what's wrong?
Nothing... is wrong.
Will you excuse me
a minute?
Whew!
Mike.!
What the hell's
going on?
Why is CindyJo
calling me sweetheart?
Who are those kids?
What is this place?
This is your house.
Those are your children.
CindyJo's
your wife.
No-o-o!
Yes.
- Are you all right?
- No, I'm not.
I mean, this kind of thing
doesn't happen every day.
It is remarkable,
if I do say so myself.
I don't
understand.
How can my life
change so much...
just because
I hit one baseball?
You see, Larry,
one's destiny...
is a very
complicated thing.
Every incident
in a person's life...
affects everything else
that follows it.
Instead of missing
the baseball, you hit it.
Then you became a hero,
married the prom queen...
and so on
and so forth...
until you find yourself
exactly where you are.
So you see...
hitting
that baseball...
has spun your life off in
an entirely new direction.
Are you an angel
or something?
Not exactly, no.
What are you?
Have you ever been
faced with a decision...
and you weren't
sure what to do?
Sure, plenty of times.
And then something inside you made
you choose one direction over another?
Yeah.
So?
So that's me.
I make the suggestions,
and you make the choices.
That's how
destiny works...
very subtly.
Welcome to your
new life, Larry.
I hope
you like it.
Mike.
Hey, wait a second.
Mike, hey!
Mike! Mike!
What am I supposed
to do now?
Hi, it's me again.
Larry Burrows.
Why did you
run out of the house?
Um...
I forgot to
tip the cabbie.
You took a cab?
Why didn't you wait for Ludwig?
Ludwig?
Oh, Ludwig,
good old Ludwig.
I didn't wait for
Ludwig because...
I can't remember his...
face.
You must be very tired,
sweetheart.
Yes.
Go into the library...
and have a nice drink
before dinner.
Okay.
By the way,
where's the library?
It's over there.
Great.
Yeah, thanks.
So, I'll just
be in the library...
having a drink.
Thanks again.
Geez!
I must belong to
the Book-of-the-Month Club.
Oh, Boswell!
How you doin'?
Am I glad to see you.
Your evening drink, sir.
- What is it?
- Armagnac.
1953.
Whoa!
I'm going to pass.
What I could use is
a nice cold brewsky.
- I'm parched.
- A brewsky, sir?
Light, if you've got it,
no glass.
Can you tell me
where the can is?
Had a couple of drinks
after work. Know what I mean?
- The can, sir?
- Yeah, the bathroom.
Well, sir,
there are 15 bathrooms.
15 bathrooms?
Did you have any
particular one in mind?
No. Nothing special.
The nearest one will do.
Through that door,
down the hall.
Thank you.
Brewsky.
A closet.
Another closet.
15 bathrooms,
you'd think I could find one.
Maybe this is it.
My God, I've died
and gone to heaven.
Excuse me, sir.
Would you like to go
for a ride before dinner?
No, thanks.
Tell me, who do
these cars belong to?
They belong
to you, sir.
- Get the hell out of here!
- As you wish.
Hey, wow...
a big hunk of cheese!
It's just what I wanted.
- It's Stilton, L.J.
- Thank you, Mr. Stilton.
It goes great with tomato,
mayonnaise, and pumpernickel.
Thank you for remembering
my birthday.
The gifts are terrific.
Thank you, Mr. Stilton.
- And you, Mr. Steuben, for the big hunk of glass.
- My pleasure.
Hey, L.J.
Dad, you're here.
Many happy returns.
Swell shindig!
Say hello to Gina.
Gina, my kid.
Very nice to make
your acquaintance.
We met in Morocco, Club Med,
know what I mean.
Will you excuse us?
- Go have more caviar.
- Okay.
Nice to have
met you, L.J.
She loves caviar.
Thinks it's salty candy.
I haven't told her
it's fish eggs.
Are you crazy
bringing her here?
What if mom found out?
She'd skin you alive!
Relax. We signed
the papers a week ago.
I'm free and clear.
What do you think... hot stuff!
What papers?
Divorce papers.
You and mom
are divorced?
Of course.
Nothing lasts forever.
You told me so.
- I said that?
- You were right, too.
Can you spot me 10 grand?
Gina's killin' me
to take her to St. Bart's.
You're aces, kid.
Your guests are wondering
if you're all right.
What's
the matter?
My parents
are divorced.
Of course.
Everybody's parents are.
Go be a good host.
Excuse me a moment.
You didn't tell me
they were divorced!
This is quite good caviar.
My parents are divorced,
for Christ's sake!
I know.
I didn't expect that!
Is there anything else
that will come as a shock?
It all will,
to some degree.
- To what degree?
- You'll see.
Things changed. You have to
take the bad with the good.
Didn't think everything
would be perfect, did you?
Well, I...
I suppose not.
This is your life,
Larry.
Learn to enjoy
what you've got.
A brewsky, sir?
Good night.
Bye-bye.
I've got some great friends,
don't you think?
They give
terrific gifts!
You have
one more coming.
I'll see you upstairs.
CindyJo?
Are you in here?
I'm over here.
Happy birthday, darling.
God help me.
Morning, Bos.
Sleep well?
I didn't,
if know what I mean?
I know exactly
what you mean.
This house has
a lot of big rooms.
Isn't this a little drab
for such a happy guy?
You always wear blue pinstripe
to board meetings.
Board meetings?
Son of a bitch.
I'm married to CindyJo!
That means I'm president
of Liberty Republic.
Indeed, sir.
For some time now.
Oh, yeah.
I mean,
I knew that.
I'm so happy about it,
I like to remind myself.
Oh.
Good morning, kids.
Morning, Father.
Ah, crescent rolls!
Very nice.
Very nice,
indeed.
Larry Burrows.
How you doing?
Nice to
meet you.
What's this?
Cream of Wheat?
It's cappuccino, Daddy.
Italian dark roast coffee
and steamed whole milk.
Right, I knew that.
That'll keep you up
the rest of your life!
It's nice. Should you
kids be drinking this?
We always do.
I guess it's
all right, then.
Morning!
Hi.
You were wonderful
last night.
So were you.
I had no idea you could
do that with Cool Whip.
Wow!
I told you we could beat
that train through the crossing.
So you did, sir.
Give yourself a raise.
One hundred bucks a week!
You're all right.
Wow!
This is my office?
This will take
some getting used to.
Nice desk.!
I wonder
how it works.
There's got to be an
"on" switch somewhere.
How about that?
The desk is wired to my ass.
Good morning, Mr. Burrows.
- Hi. How are you?
- Can I get you something?
No, I'm fine.
Coffee!
I'd really like
a cup of coffee.
Right away. Mr. Pender and
Mr. Flick are on their way.
You're kidding!
Those jerks still work here?
- Pardon?
- Nothing. Nothing at all.
Do me a favor.
Find out if Clip Metzler
or Ellen Burr...
Ripley... Ellen Ripley,
work here.
Metzler works in accounting.
I'll have to check on Ripley.
Thanks, and tell Pender
and Flick that, uh...
I can't be disturbed.
- I'm too busy. I've got lots of buttons to push.
- Yes, sir.
Over and out.
Let's see.
Where's the bar?
I'm going to love
this place.
All right!
The good stuff.
I know you.
You're the forklift girl.
Great, thanks.
I've been trying to get
regular coffee for days.
Then again,
maybe I don't need coffee.
Where the hell
were you last night?
I waited until midnight,
and went to bed... alone.
I'm sorry.
Jewel!
Forgotten
my name already?
Jewel,
I knew that.
I'm real,
real sorry.
I guess I
couldn't make it.
- I had this party...
- Couldn't make it?
Were you out with that
Ripley bitch?
Does she works here?
No, she does not
work here.
If she suddenly
starts working here...
you're going to live
to regret it.
What do you say
we double your salary?
I know what
you're capable of, L.J.
Don't mess with me...
or you'll find out
what I'm capable of.
Am I making myself
perfectly clear?
- Perfectly.
- We need to talk.
Whoa.
Hi, guys.
Come in.
I'm glad to see you.
About the plan, I've got
to tell Bob either way.
I think it's a big mistake
to set up New Jersey.
We need to talk
about the country club.
We have to go over
the Nakamura deal...
before we sign the papers.
Are we on?
- For New Jersey?
- No, for golf.
Excuse me.
Am I disturbing you?
Mr. Hansen,
come in.
Come in.
Mr. Hansen!
Come on in,
please.
What can I
do for you?
I wanted to apologize for
not appearing at your party.
My ulcer
was acting up.
You didn't miss a thing. I got
some cheese and a glass thing.
- A what?
- You know...
Excuse me.
We should go.
We tee off in 15 minutes.
Oh, right.
Would you like to
golf with us?
- I play golf, you know.
- Really?
- You want to play golf with me?
- Sure. Come on.
I can help you get rid
of that slice or whatever.
It slipped.
Can I use yours?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
It's not like
a baseball bat.