"DEAD SEASON"
It was 57 weeks ago.
Got a standard cardiac arrest call.
I went out... couldn't revive the guy.
Pretty normal.
Then after a couple of minutes...
That's when it all started.
Three days later Pittsburgh was
on lockdown. Then the state,
and everywhere else.
A couple of months before all this,
my wife, she left me. She got the kid.
I had no way of contacting them.
There were no phones or internet of
course... So I went out to find them...
I buried them.
I just kept walking... 62 days,
I didn't really know what else to do,
you know?
Anyway... A guy I used to work with
retired to coral cove in Miami.
It's a small marina.
I contacted him a few days ago and
I guess he's made a living
helping people get boats
and escape into the waters.
And I figured, hey, why not try
my hand at that?
You're free to join.
Elvis? Elvis? You still there?
Yeah, I'm Here. Sorry about that.
So what about you?
About the same as yours, I guess.
Been on my own about a year now.
Two months ago I met this kid,
and we worked our way down to Florida.
Who's the kid?
His name's Cody. He's pretty quiet,
but he's a tough little dude.
Look, I don't know how much longer
we're gonna last here on our own.
You know, just the two of us.
I could always use some company.
Probably be working
our way down south soon.
Maybe we'll stop by your place
for a beer or something.
Alright, but you're gonna have to
pick some up, cause I'm all out.
Need anything else at the store?
Some whiskey? You have my address.
Any chance I can get your name?
Guess Not.
Stop!
Didn't mean to scare you.
Here, eat this.
I'm not hungry.
Huh? Alright.
Here you go Buddy. Lean up.
My name's Elvis.
What's your name?
Tweeter.
Tweeter?
OK. Tweeter... So how old are you?
Ten.
Well, that's cool.
Well, if you want, umm, you two can rest...
I've got more blankets in the closet.
King Me.
You are good at this! You know...
I didn't have any parents growing up either.
I used to get really lonely.
I don't feel that way anymore.
My turn?
Yeah.
Elvis? You there? Elvis!
I'm here!
Well, your boat's ready to go.
It's got a full tank too.
Thanks, I really appreciate this.
Just to let you know,
I got a list of people waiting.
I'll be there tonight with everything.
Alright, see y a then.
Thanks.
How far away is this guy?
I dunno... six hours,
eight hours... Half a day maybe.
You trust him?
Yeah, I do trust him.
If he can get us to a place without
walkers... I'm willing to take
that risk. Coming? Or staying?
Yeah? Who is it?
Elvis.
Elvis? Who are they?
They're fine. They're friends.
Still good?
Yeah... Come on in. - Oh, man!
Haven't had those in a while. Yum!
The only way out
is down through the warehouse.
Sabrina Lee. She's at the end
of the pier. Everything else...
Is in here.
The map is from the warehouse to the pier.
The other is to the island.
The fish are toxic,
so ration your food.
Don't get surrounded. You'll be fine.
You know you might want to consider...
Maybe coming with us.
Man, I got too good of a thing
going here.
Alright. Take care.
Awesome. We have to go through em'.
Just stick with me OK?
You know the drill.
C'mon, Cody.
Cody!
Go!
The boat!
Hey, Cody, There's Probably
a bed down there.
Damn it!
Oh God!? Cody, let me see are you OK?
Come here. Come on. Let me see.
You're tough.
Arrr I gonna turn into one of them?
I'm not gonna let that happen. OK?
Hey, Cody?
I don't feel good.
I know sweetie. What's this?
My mom gave it to me.
It's for good luck.
Come here, sweetie.
It's time to go Cody.
You gotta go, Cody.
Elvis?
You gotta let go, Cody.
Come here buddy. Come here.
You got it?
Disgusting.
You alright?
Tweeter?
Yes.
Alcoholic.
Hey, I'm on vacation. hey y a know...
See if you can find any of those
silly straws, or those little umbrellas.
I'm gonna go check the back for food. Watch my back.
I'm watching your back...
and you're good.
Elvis!
Tweeter!
Where are the weapons?!
On the table!
Get on the bar! Get on the bar!
Grab the machete!
Away!
Elvis get down!
This side's clear!
Over here too.
Up on your feet! Nice and slow!
Put your gun on the counter, sir.
Turn around, hands on the counter!
Wakey, wakey. Eggs and Bakey.
The good news is you're both alive,
which means you're not bit.
So now I'm going to ask
a couple questions.
Ladies first. Name!
Name!
Want to play the bitch card... Fine.
Hey! Wait.
Put her in three twelve.
Good Evening
My name is Kurt Conrad.
I am the administrator of this facility.
Up front I want to apologize
for any bumps or bruises,
I think you can understand our need
for security... and
my need to ask you some questions.
So... Let's start with...
how you got here?
What exactly do you hope to achieve...
by not talking to me?
You think you're going to gain
some power over this situation?
My daughter pulls that shit.
She's seventeen.
Is that what you're doing?
Are you pouting like a teenage girl
about the end of the world?
World still here.
Let's try it again, something simple.
What's your name?
Elvis.
Where you from, Elvis?
Nashville, Tennessee.
By way of Tupelo, Mississippi.
I kind of lost my accent
along the way.
I was good... wore a cape...
sold out a lot of concerts.
It was insane, man.
Well the state of Pennsylvania says
that your name is Aaron Strawbridge.
They also say that you are
a highly qualified E.M.T.
You're a medic.
I guess this was your wife.
And that was your son.
And by the fact that they are not here
I assume they didn't make it.
We are the last surviving
human community, on this island.
Our survival is held in a very
delicate balance.
It's my job to maintain that balance.
So it falls on me to determine,
if and how, you can be
of benefit to us.
Now in your case it is very simple.
You're a medic. We just lost
our medic. But, your lady friend.
I'm not sure what she brings
to the table.
All we know about her so far,
is that she has a loud mouth,
and she's quite unpleasant.
Two qualities we don't really need.
Look, my priority is
keeping myself and loud mouth
as you call her safe.
Leave her alone and I'll see
what I can do, OK?
Are you Aaron... or you Elvis?
I'm Elvis, man.
But you can call me "King" if you want.
Okay Elvis. See you in the morning.
Come on.
What are your neighbors like?
Pretty nice, right? We're trying
to do more than just survive here.
Come on.
And there's the beach you came in on,
goes from east to west.
Those structures up there
are all death traps. Avoid those at all costs.
We have a solar panel,
got electricity, but not much to use with it.
We collect rain water
from all around the compound,
and we purify it, and we store it...
in thanks tanks in the hill.
This infrastructure is all courtesy
of the U.S. Navy.
Before that it was a gunnery range.
Dropped all kinds of nasty shit here.
Depleted uranium, phosphorus,
tested nukes here.
And that's the down side,
because most of the stuff that grows here you can't eat it.
I mean don't even think about
eating the coconuts.
Get the problem?
See, that's the thing, we have
a limited ability to feed people.
Which is why we have to go through
this screening process,
before we bring in new members
of the community.
So what happens if they don't pass
the screening process?
We cross that bridge
when we get to it.
So how many are you now?
Ah, there's sixteen of us.
Jason. Now we were walker free
in this island,
since a few months ago
when a Dutch cruise ship
crashed right off the coast there.
Since then all kinds of things
have been washing to shore.
Booze, supplies, Walkers.
So we sweep the beach daily to salvage what we can.
Kill what we need to.
This is our life,
if you want to be part of it,
pitch in where you can.
Work hard, and ahh,
just don't be afraid to get your hands dirty.
Hey, how about a cold beer?
You've got cold beer?
Umm... Ah here we go. It's delicious.
Please, help yourself.
What is it? Jerky?
Cargo from the Dutch.
Bet it's been a while
since you've had some meat, huh?
Say more than a while.
Been a long time.
So, how did you two meet?
Wanna tell him?
I'm sure it's quite a story.
Where ever you came from,
it's a long ride.
Yeah. I used to babysit her.
So light bulbs are scarce,
so please be resourceful.
And, uh, no hot water.
It's broken at the moment,
but tomorrow morning
I'm gonna try and fix it.
Thanks
Yeah, try to get some rest,
busy day tomorrow.
Good night all.
- Goodnight... Timberlake.
Kurt.
What about him?
You tell me.
He's crazy. Watch him.
Sanz. Cigar Castro dude.
Whatever.
Ignore. Alex?
He's just a dumb kid.
Yeah but he's cute. Tommy?
Balding, tribal Tattoo.
Watch.
Here's the compound. This gate
is basically the only way in.
Keeps the Walkers out. This barricade
separates us from the rest of the island.
Conrad believes that your boat
is here on this beach.
Did you pass a pier, when you came in,
a lot of Walkers?
I don't know.
How about there's a brick saw mill,
did you go through there?
Yeah, we went right through it.
Alright, and then after that
did you go over a road?
Yeah.
If you curved this way,
your boat could be on this beach.
Anyone! Is anyone out there?
Please identify your location.
The military base... just outside London.
The Walkers are running.
I don't know why
but they die, they get up, and they-
Running... you serious?
Listen, we need a way
to evacuate immediately! Seriously!
Hello?
Todd. Take these two over
to North Beach, look for the boat.
Uh... Fine gimme a second.
Sure this is the right beach?
Yeah. - Bullshit, man!
Hey, I don't know what to tell y a.
This your idea of entertainment?
Like life before the internet.
- And TV.
Or life after the internet and TV.
Can the chatter. We do this because
it's important.
Our lives are important. Watch... See.
It's slow!
You keep active and move,
you're going to be alright.
Toss the bat.
Now, I don't care what it is.
Machete, Bat, wrench.
Use it to create separation.
I protect myself.
I can evade. I can leave!
Now. If you want to have a strike
evasion, use the technique,
step to the side...
Try to hit right between
the fourth and fifth vertebrate.
Snap the the neck in half.
That's a good day. Alright, who's up?
You! Lets go.
No thanks.
Alright. Why the fuck don't
you do that?
Nice job back there. Showed some skill I'm impressed.
Why because I'm a chick? Sorry to say, I don't fit the
normal female mold around here.
Look, for this to work, everyone has
to contribute and be effective at it.
These women are very effective
in their roles.
With the male to female ratio
being four to one, they're greatly valued.
What is this, some weird Mormon thing?
It's the exact opposite.
Look I'm going to ask you two,
to reserve your judgment
until you are more deeply integrated
into the community.
Colonel! - What's up?
It's Rachel. I think she's sick.
Is she sick, or is she in a mood?
I don't know sir.
Rachel. Rachel.
This is Elvis, he's your new doctor.
Hi Rachel.
She fainted. Prior to that
she was delusional.
You a real doctor?
Yeah, something like that.
I'm fine.
No sweetie... no you're not fine.
She doesn't eat.
What's your normal diet consist of?
The island diet is primarily meat.
And she doesn't want to eat meat.
It's just, you know, a phase.
A phase? - Yeah it's a phase,
You are going through.
Well maybe if you gave me some real
food then I'd eat.
Rachel, can I run a few tests on y a?
Let's put this down here.
Here we go... alright.
Can you look at me?
Look to your right. Look to your left.
Close your eyes, and open your eyes... good.
Squeeze my two fingers for
a five count, as hard as you can. Ready?
Go. One. Two. Three. Four. Five. Good.
You play any sports or anything?
Yeah it's called stay in my room
all day and stare at the wall,
it's fucking awesome.
Seriously, do you get out?
No.
Look, if I had my gear I could do
some other tests. As far as I can tell
she's healthy. Ok.
I mean physically,
but she does need to eat more.
Yeah.
How long has she been in this room?
Ten months.
Ten months? - Yeah!
Like has not left this room
in ten months?
Listen to me. She is not ready
for what's out there.
Come on, you got eyes.
Okay... she's confused,
she has cabin fever,
and she probably needs
somebody to talk to.
She's got me to talk to.
Someone else.
Okay, I mean when was the last time
she had a conversation
with another woman?
It's been awhile.
Everyday, it's something different
with her.
Could you just go in,
and just talk to her?
What am I supposed to say?
Whatever girls talk about.
Just... you know...
Let her in.
I'm Tweeter.
You're Rachel? How old are you?
Seventeen. What kind of name
is Tweeter?
What, that's my name.
Your parents named you "Tweeter"?
Well... No... it's...
Oh. So you made it up.
Look, I'm not here to talk about
me okay?
They said you needed
someone to talk to.
I just want to go outside!
He thinks I'll die,
or get raped or something.
- So... when you do go out...
No! I don't go outside.
He doesn't let me leave! Ever!
Are there any other girls
here your age?
Just you and those whores.
I had a sister though...
And a mom...
Do me a favor and tell my dad
it's girl stuff or something.
Yeah, OK.
Who the hell does he think he is?
Yeah, who the hell does he think
he is?
Seriously, we were fine without them.
Really? We've been living off of
gas station food.
Potato Chips... Canned Ham...
Fuck there was a week I had
to survive off of dog biscuits.
Look, it's not that bad. We're safer.
Bigger numbers.
I mean, doesn't anything make you
happy?
Hey, I dunno, what makes you smile?
OF course stuff makes me happy.
Well tell me! I don't know
anything about you. I don't know your name...
I know this is kinda third grade but
do you have a favorite color?
You know, I'm gonna guess that
it's red.
Nope.
Do you have a favorite food?
We'll start there.
What's your favorite food?
Hot dogs and pancakes.
That's all you came up with?
Hot dogs and pancakes?
So its hot dogs with pancake buns?
Nooo! Gross!
Today's a straight up S and D.
We're putting them in the mix.
So, Mike you're on point.
Alex, you got the rear.
Todd, You're in the middle with them.
Teach them what you know.
Tweeter sandwich.
Stow it, she's weapons and
re-con now. Treat her as such.
You each get three rounds...
These are to be used only
as a last resort.
Alright. You will insert
on the east end of the beach. Sweep west,
keep the sun at your back.
Use your heads.
No mistakes. No drama. No heroes.
Come back safe.
Hand me that gun, Backstreet.
Yeah, you like it.
Yeah, the coconuts are pretty much
gone, the Mangos are gone,
most of the shit's rotten.
Soaked in radiation.
And the only thing worse than
the fucking food...
Is these god damn bugs.
A bag of marshmallows
washed up about a week or two ago,
shit, but that's about it.
Flotsem and Jetsum!
Hey Tweeter, you still off limits?
Fucking disgusting, man.
Hey! Over here! - Hey guys, c'mon.
I need help! Come on! Help!
Are you bitten?
No I'm not. It's my wife.
She's broken her leg.
She's over here.
Okay.
Slowly.
Come on.
We first got here and,
we were sent here from Miami. We were told
this island was walker free.
We first got here and...
Stop! Keep walking.
Keep coming.
Help! Help, I'm down here.
This is completely against
everything Kurt's told us.
We're going back.
Get out of my way.
Where are you going?
You going with her? That noob?
Yeah, I'm going with that noob.
L 90'! post.
Are you bit?
No. - She's lying.
She's not bit. OK?
Put the gun down, It's not necessary.
Put the gun away. Put the gun away!
My husband.
He's up there and he's safe.
We're gonna get you out of here OK?
You got any water?
I need you to cut down some branches
and we're gonna have to splint this OK?
What's your name? - Emily.
Hey, drink some water.
Just a little bit of water. A little water.
I'm gonna straighten out your leg
a little bit. It's gonna hurt.
Okay.
Just a little bit. It's OK.
I know it hurts. I know it hurts.
We've got walkers!
Shit!
We gotta go! Up, up, up, UP!
Behind you!
Fuck.
Fuck!
Emily, come on.
Shit!
Take her!
You fucking shot me, Alex!
One, two, three, up!
Go, go! Go, run! Get up! Go, get up!
Move it!
Keep up!
Where were you?
Some more steps!
Get in!
This way, this way.
Stay with me, stay with me.
Where's the blood bank?
- The fridge!
Take off his bandage,
take off his bandage.
What's your blood type?
- A-negative.
A-negative, alright.
Get her some water,
we're probably gonna have to amputate okay?
Get her some water!
B-positive... Nothing!
There's nothing here!
Elvis! I'm O-negative.
Sit down, that'll work.
You're universal. Gimmie your arm.
AW shit.
It was quick man. Honestly, I'm alright, I'm alright.
I'm O-negative. - Perfect, sit down.
Hey, look up, look up. Count backwards from 100. Okay?
Okay? Lemme hear you. Start counting.
100, 99, 98,
97, 96, 95,
94, 93, 92...
Ow Shit! - Walker!
Aw fuck!
We go over this, everyday.
You keep your distance.
They can't hurt you unless
you let them get close!
What idiot thought it was
a good idea to go into the jungle
with one way out.
Huh? Whose idea was that?
It was me, sir.
You walked 'em into a deathtrap.
How is he?
He's fine. Well, he'll live.
What about our guest?
Quarantine.
You just traded two of my best men
for a worthless old fuck.
Sergent Alex Waterman.
He was an army ranger. A damn good one.
He served two tours of duty
in the middle east,
and brought his skill set here.
We owe him a lot.
He will be sorely missed.
My grandfather, died in Vietnam
In the jungle. Much like
this shithole I'm sure.
My father, John Waterman...
Took direct RPG hits in Kuwait.
And I'm proud to follow them.
Keep her close.
Ok doc... So into the camera.
Why is this going to work?
Well, the bites don't cause
this phenomenon, but they do kill.
And as soon as they do,
they come back.
Now I think it may be bacterial.
My dad's bit, this is our only shot.
Just hurry up
and do it.
If we had more time,
what we'd do is we'd locate all
the major blood vessles,
tie them individually,
and normally we'd use a bone saw-
Despite some complications,
the amputation was successful.
Unfortunately,
whatever toxins are in the bite,
once they get into the bloodstream,
it's already too late.
Okay, work quickly.
Get as much of the body as you can,
and you might net 50 pounds per procedure.
I can't quite say
what would happen over long term
consumption, or what would happen
if someone eats this contaminated
meat and turns into one of them.
They seem to be getting
more agressive.
Eventually we're all gonna turn.
I need to step outside.
Oh no no no! You stay right here...
Okay, so we're here,
here's Costa Rica.
It's basically due South.
Now, how do you find due South
in the southern hemosphere?
Southern cross. Right?
Tip of the Southern cross that's due south.
Okay. So... these are your turn points.
Duration of your tac is 70 miles.
How do you determine
your speed at sea?
Drop the buoy and measure
the knot over time.
That's why it's called a knot.
See? Simple as that. It's brilliant.
You're mom was a hell of a navigator. You're just like her.
Come on. Talk to me.
Talk to you about what?
Anything. How was your day?
It was awful. Same as always.
Over and over
and over.
I get it. I get it. I just need
you to be patient with me.
Now your mom and I had a plan.
Mom? You wanna talk about mom?
Let's talk about her.
Do you wanna talk about Stacy?
We can talk about her too.
We'll finish this later.
I want you to look at each other.
Good look.
One, or all of us,
will not be here in a month.
It's taken less than twelve months
of this infection
to wipe out the population of
this planet, and reduce us to this.
But yet, you treat your survival
with an astonishing
lack or urgency. You're lazy,
you're sloppy,
and unbelievably, you're fat.
How does that happen?
It's a lack of discipline...
and that's my fault.
If any one of you has lost
confidence in me,
or thinks he can do a better job
than me, pick up my gun,
because things are about to change.
All right.
Starting today, we will double
our salvage operations.
All food stores
will be under lockdown,
and I will ration it as I see fit.
My sister drew that... it's our boat
The one that sank?
Can you do something for me?
What is it?
See if it's still there?
According to my dad, it sank.
Holy shit! Where did you get this?
My dad gives it to me.
I've just been saving it up so
I can get outta here... but I'm obviously stuck here,
so I need you to go check.
I'll draw you a map.
You have to go the long way around
the barricades so you can avoid the guards.
Thank you.
Bye.
Hey Elvis. - Yeah.
Mind taking a ride with me?
I need your opinion on a couple things.
What do you need to talk about?
Health issues around the camp.
Don't worry about it. He's a big boy, he can take care of himself.
Yeah, sure. You good?
How are you doing, Elvis?
You all right?
Used to it.
So you think I'm a hard-ass, huh?
Elvis?
A lot of people do. If we do not
strip down to our primal wiring,
we're not gonna make it.
I had two daughters. And a wife.
A couple months after
we came to shore,
my oldest, Stacie... she got sick.
She was weak from malnutrition.
My wife was in denial about it.
She just couldn't wrap her head around
what was happening to her kid.
So I let it go.
The day she turned, I was on patrol,
and my wife,
she just had to have that last hug.
You know, as like it was gonna
fuckin' fix somethin'.
So by the time I got home,
they were both gone. And I had to...
You did what you needed to do.
Rachel's all the family I got left...
and I'm not gonna let her starve.
Good evening, Mr. Vernon.
My name is Kurt Conrad.
I am the administrator
of this facility.
I apologize for the inconvenience
but we need to hold you here until
we are certain you are not infected.
I'm sure you can understand.
Sorry for your loss.
Hey.
That's it?
That's all you're going to say?
Look at him.
Of what possible benefit is he to us?
You guys, I should have taught
you how to wrap presents a little better.
Yeah we're all ready, right?
Dad, we're almost ready.
Are you ready?
Can I come in yet?
No!
Light the candles!
One second, I get the matches.
What are we doing here?
I think you know what
we're doing here.
We're here to harvest Mr. Vernon.
Don't pull that shit on me.
I have seen you walk in the darkness.
I know you're comfortable there.
All I'm asking you to do
is shine a light on it and own it.
I know. A lion kills a gazelle.
It appears to be cruel, and heartless.
You follow that lion home.
You're gonna see that all it was doing
was feeding its family.
That's all you and I
are doing here!
We're feeding our families!
I can't do that.
Yeah, you can. Because you have to.
You're the only one
who has the skill! The moment he dies,
he turns!
That means that meat is useless to us!
No. Fuck you! Fuck you!!
Fuck!!
What do you think you're here for?!
Shit.
Elvis, have you not heard
a single word I said?
I lost my wife, I lost my daughter,
cuz I didn't do
what needed to be done,
when it needed to be done!!
You have got to feed your family.
Tweeter is your Rachel.
They can't do this! We can.
You wanna be a king, Elvis?
You gotta act like one.
Mr. Vernon. You're doing well.
That's a good sign.
Gonna get you out of here.
First I gotta give you a vitamin boosters,
I need you to just turn your head.
Thank you.
Gonna feel a little pinch.
Gotta move fast.
Harvest large to small.
Start with the legs, buttocks,
shoulders then the arms.
Make sure you tie off the arteries,
limit the blood loss.
Where're you going?
This is a bridge you cross on your own.
When you're done,
put the cuts in the saline solution.
Be right outside.
How sad is this?
And now?
Are your ready?
Calm down!
Just one second. One moment.
It's your birthday.
You're gonna have to... Alright alright.
I think it's already ruined, mom.
I know but we can still pretend.
Alright, here I come.
Come in.
Alright, ready?
What am I? I wish...
Dad you don't look a day of 85.
I have a knife in my hand, okay?
Seriously I have a knife in my hand
and I will do serious damage.
Back of that old man,
this fat old man thing.
Not true!
You gotta back off so quickly.
Right baby?
No!
Give it Stay! - Okay.
I don't mind.
Happy birthday! - Happy birthday Dad!
I want to open presents.
Please make quick.
Yeah let's bring 'em
in the living room.
I am happy when you are here.
Happy birthday Dad!
You're the best dad in the world.
Really? - You know that.
No come on dad.
I gotta take this, honey.
I wish I could tell you that
it gets harder,
but it doesn't.
Thank you. I got it from here.
What's going on?
The more I think about it
the more the man makes sense, you know?
And the more this makes sense for us.
Don't be ridiculous! We're leaving,
and we're taking Rachel with us.
No no no. He's doing what
he has to do, okay? He's doing
what he has to do to keep the people
that he loves alive.
And the people he doesn't
as their food!
There's fucking nothing out there
for us anymore, okay?
This is it!
You think you're going to go
to another island that has food?
Another island that has TV dinners?
You don't even have a boat.
This is the first time since
I've met you
that I'm scared of something
other than those fucking things.
Don't know if I can trust you anymore.
Don't, don't say that.
If you could sail anywhere
where would you go?
Anywhere away from here.
Let's take the boat and get out
of here.
Think we can sail it just
the two of us?
Yeah, yeah we could figure it out.
I'm gonna start getting shit together.
Hang in there okay?
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I was taking a hike.
What are you doing?
Huntin' redheads. You know it's kind
of dangerous for you to be hiking
all by yourself.
- Come on let's getback.
Stay away from me, you touch me and
I'll scream and alert every fucking walker within a mile.
You scream and we both die.
So why don't you just keep your
mouth shut.
Take off your belt!
Fuck!
You bitch!
Don't leave me.
Fuck!
Give me your gun. Give it to me.
Open the gate.
Fucking now! Hurry up! Fuck!
Open the fucking gate!
What's wrong?
They can fucking run now.
We have to go.
Who can run? Calm down, calm down.
The fucking walkers.
What happened? Ok? Whose blood
is that?
It's Tommy's. I was at the compound
and he followed me.
Okay.
And he said he'd try to... he'd kill
me if I didn't let him... fuck me!
I killed him. I killed him,
and he got up and he fucking
started running!
What do you want me to do?
I have to get Rachel.
- Okay.
There's a boat at the end of the pier,
but Kurt's gonna try to stop us.
I'll talk to Kurt, okay? Listen. Stop.
Calm down.
We'll be fine, okay?
You get Rachel
and we'll meet back up, okay?
Okay. Okay, let's go.
Zankou chicken, man that shit is great.
You keep talking about chicken
I'm gonna
shoot you right now.
Walkers broke through the gate.
Hurry up!
Time to get inside. Go, move it!
Movie it!
Oh my god.
Come on out.
- What?
We're talking the boat for a swing.
Right now?
We're leaving the island!
Don't waste time!
Come on, Rachel, let's go! Come on!
All right, Sanz, you come with me.
Stay close, boys!
Okay!
Stay close!
Stay close, boys!
Idiots! Stay here!
Stay close, Mike! Reloading!
To the gate! - Come on!
Fuck!
Move! Move!
Move!
Go away!
Fuck!
Get away!
Come on!
Wanker!
Rachel, wait! - Why?
This Way!
Rachel!
Tweeter! Should we move?
Beach. Let's go.
Hold him up! Hold him up!
Rachel, please help me!
Tweeter get him off me!
Go go 90 go!
Whatever! Come on, you make it!
You okay? You okay?
This island's fucked.
We gotta move. What's this?
The boat! Give that to Rachel,
she knows what to do.
Take it...
I'm armed!
Kurt, asshole!
Get away!
Okay!
I come in a second!
C'mon, Rach!
Tweeter, come on!
Rachel!
Get inside! Quick! Rachel?
Rachel! - No!
Come in!
Oh Elvis! Rachel!
Oh god oh! I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry! C'mon!
Okay, c'mon!
C'mon!
Tweeter, maybe you need this!
The pier's a half-mile downshore.
I'm gonna lure'em one way,
and I'll meet you at the boat.
Okay? Come on!
That's good, Elvis!
We will see. Come on! Run!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Come on! Come here!
Come on!
The boat!
Tweeter! Get down!
Rachel's all fixed up, Tweet.
My name is Beth...