Five minutes,
my little lambs.
Has anyone seen
Bliss Cavendar?
Pash, this can't
be happening.
Why aren't you
backstage, Brooke?
You know how it is.
They get to a certain age,
they don't want you back there.
She said
she'll meet me here.
Really? That's odd.
Mmm-hmm, mmm-hmm
It says "temporary."
It did a minute ago,
I swear.
My mom is
gonna kill me.
Now, Miss Amber Black
If I could have dinner with
anyone, it would have to be God.
Because what they say
is true. God is great.
Don't tell them
that I did it, okay?
Those are the rules,
you're not allowed to tell.
Let go.
I'm your only friend.
Corbi Booth,
ladies and gentlemen.
If I could have dinner with anyone,
it would have to be my grandfather.
I love you, Papa.
And now, also from Bodeen,
Miss Bliss Cavendar.
If I could have
dinner with anyone,
it would be
Amelia Earhart,
because not only was she
a pioneer of aviation,
but she was a great woman in history.
Thank you.
So enlighten me What was
that little stunt all about?
Are you trying to
sabotage your chances?
Or was it just your biological urge to
make your mother look like a jackass?
It was just a dare.
Oh How did that
work out for you?
Not so great?
Corbi
Congratulations, honey
Well-deserved.
Thank you.
Thumbs way up.
Thank you,
Mrs. Cavendar.
Bliss is so hard
to beat. Usually.
Well, the Blue Bonnet pageant
is right around the corner.
And we'll be there.
Come on, honey.
Oh See you later
See you.
I'm sorry that
these pageants
don't live up to your high
moral standards, Bliss,
but there's a lot you
can learn from them,
no matter what you
go on to be in life.
You think you're being
judged up there on that stage,
but no one's asking you
to be Miss America.
I wanna be Miss America.
And you're gonna be the
best one ever, sweetheart.
Teeth.
Eyes.
Trudy, bless your heart
for fitting us in.
Well, hell.
Shit happens.
Let me get my foils.
Now, what were you
thinking, getting blue hair?
Fourteenth
drive in the red zone.
They have now given up
nine touchdowns
and three field goals. We'll
see how this one ends up.
He's only had one take away
in the red zone.
Hey.
I won another one.
Lord, child,
you are unstoppable.
And had I known what you were up
to, I would have bought a ticket.
Earl.
I mean, dang it, girl,
what has gotten into you?
Just defective, I guess.
Nice parenting, Earl
Come on, now
Ooh, I'll see you later
Dinner.
Seriously, out of all the
places to go to in the world,
who would come to Bodeen?
Them
I mean, they're smart,
at least they just
pass through.
Go ahead
and mock it.
But without the Blue Bonnet
factory, this town wouldn't exist.
You know what, Birdman,
I think I preferred you
before you got promoted.
You know, now
you're all corporate.
I know. I miss the old Birdman. Yeah.
Ladies, don't let the tie
fool you. I'm still one of us.
But y'all are gonna have to
start calling me Dwayne now.
It's more dignified.
No.
Birdman is the only thing
you have going for you.
That's what you think.
Really?
Yeah.
Hey
Make sure they
tip you this time.
Hey, what can I
get you guys?
Hey, Corbi
So what are you, like,
alternative now?
Alternative to what?
What's the name of that thing that
if I eat it real fast, it's free?
That's the Squealer You have to
eat it in three minutes or less.
Yeah, you bring me
a Squealer.
And I don't mean Corbi.
Let's go, buddy, pick
it up Come on, come on.
Oh, yes You got it, you got it.
I can't believe you
used to share a bed with her.
Baby, baby,
get it, yeah.
You make it sound very dirty.
It was just sleepovers.
Come on Come on
Baby, do it. Do it.
Go. Go. Go.
Come on Come on, Colby! Yeah.
That's my man.
Come on, Colby.
It's free, bitches.
It's free. It's free.
I was thinking
maybe we could go to
Austin and do some shopping.
Really?
Teach
them well and let them lead the way
Show them all the beauty
they possess inside
...them a sense of pride
to make It easier
You hate them.
Well, they don't have duct tape
on them That's an improvement.
Hi
Thanks.
Ooh!
Pretty vases.
They're great
for tulips, really.
Um...
Thank you. Yup,
I changed my mind.
No, please, Bliss.
Come on.
Don't...
Don't be embarrassed.
It's funny.
I'm supposed to buy you
shoes from a head shop?
Does that really strike you
as responsible parenting?
Fine 'Cause shoes
are a gateway drug.
For gosh sakes, Bliss.
It goes out
of bounds near the 42 yard line.
There is a flag down.
Yeah, it's Earl.
Hello, Earl
Can you please explain
to your daughter
why it's inappropriate to
buy shoes in a head shop?
Dad, it's not like that
You took your
mother to a head shop?
Are you off your nut?
You know, if she wasn't
here and I used my own money,
it wouldn't make a difference
That's not the point.
Look, I am in the middle
of a deal here, okay?
So whatever you all
work out is fine with me.
Give me that
Okay?
Earl, do you know
how hard I have worked
to raise these girls in
a drug-free environment?
Yes, I do.
Exactly.
Hi. Hey, girls. What's up?
Hello. Dropping my flyers off.
Perfect.
Hurl Scouts-Holy Rollers.
See you then
Thanks, girls. Bye.
Come on All right,
let's go. Come on.
Screw you and your
grandma's Chevy Celebrity.
Here.
No, what are you doing?
Yes, yes, yes You got stiffed
on your tips again, just take it. No.
Just take it, take it.
No.
What is this?
Roller derby?
This is...
This is tomorrow.
This is in Austin.
Yeah, I know
Will there be
cute boys there?
Hey, Mom, Dad, we're gonna
go to a football game.
It's an away game, but...
The team
kind of needs us.
No, no, no, not "kind of," they do.
Well, sure
Hey, I'll tell you what,
I'll take you.
No, it's cool.
You have your car.
Yeah, I have my car.
No, but I mean, you know,
we can watch together.
Earl, let the girls go on
and have their fun.
And then you and I
can nuzzle.
I kind of feel bad
lying to them.
I don't. I give my
parents straight A's.
I get freedom.
She's a punk
punk, a punk rocker
Punk punk, a punk rocker
Well, the kids are all
hopped up and ready to go
They're ready to go now
They've got their surfboards
And they're going to
the discotheque a-go-go
But she just couldn't stay
She had to break away
Well, New York City
really has it all
Oh, yeah
Don't say I never
gave you anything.
Sheena is a punk rocker
Okay, everybody, and welcome
to skate night at the Warehouse.
I'm a little hung-over
tonight, so I...
Anyway, let me Introduce you
to our first team.
Coming to you from
the streets of Austin,
men, hold on to your
cookies, it's the Hurl Scouts.
Number 99, captain of the
Hurl Scouts, Maggie Mayhem.
Number 69, Bloody Holly.
Number 3, Rosa Sparks
Number 2, Smashley Simpson
Razor Magee's Hurl Scouts have come
in last place three years running.
This league has five teams,
each with their own theme.
What outlaw do we have
skating against the Hurl Scouts
this fine Texas
evening here?
I'm talking about the girls so bad
that even God can't keep them in line.
Give it up for the
undefeated Holy Rollers.
Last season's champs
are led by their captain,
the league's leading
scorer, Iron Maven.
Yeah, she's the one
from the flyer.
I'm feeling hot in these
polyesters right now, baby.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's play some
roller derby.
A jammer scores
a point in this course
by passing members
of the opposite team.
Maven gets a great jump.
That's fast.
And she's out
to an early lead.
Iron Maven,
ladies and gentlemen.
Folks, the ones to watch
tonight are the jammers.
Those are the ones with
the stars on their helmets.
Some of you might remember watching
derby on TV back In the '70s,
but it was reborn right here
in the heart of Texas,
a true Austin tradition.
Maven's heading up on the outside
but It's real crowded in there.
That's a big
hit by Rosa Sparks.
Jackie Daniels Is down.
Lucky for the Hurl Scouts
this is only an exhibition bout
because the Rollers
are in control.
Thank you, Maggie.
I just wanna tell you all
that you're my new heroes.
It's your
first time here?
Yeah.
Well, put some skates on,
be your own hero.
The last time I wore skates,
they had Barbies on them.
Hey, you know, none of us knew our
ass from an elbow pad when we started.
You should come to
tryouts on Tuesday.
You have to be 21.
You're 21, right?
Two... I'm 22.
Yeah, I just had my...
I had my birthday, so...
Great, it's this
Tuesday at 5:00.
It is?
Yeah.
I'm Maggie,
Maggie Mayhem.
I'm Bliss,
but I can change that.
Yeah, you'll have
to change that.
Don't be late.
"Twenty-two.
Just had my birthday."
Twenty-one,
it's a red flag.
Twenty-two's way
more believable.
I guess, 'cause you're not actually
gonna do it, so I guess it makes sense.
Why don't
you and I try out?
Excuse me?
I didn't have a
Barbie-roller-skating phase. Okay?
I had a fat-kid-sits-inside-
and-reads-a-book phase.
You know that.
Well, what makes you
think I won't try out?
Because you'd
be scared to go without me.
And those roller derby
girls, they're tough.
And you are not.
Ow!
Geez!
How dare you?
Not to mention
your mom.
She doesn't
have to know.
You don't have
the balls.
I can grow the balls.
No way.
Mmm
Hey.
Do you have room
for one more?
I like your hair.
Thanks, hon.
I do it myself.
All right, next
stop, downtown Austin.
Hey.
What's your derby name?
Pocket Rocket.
What's yours?
Jaba the Slut.
Hey, you made it.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm glad
you came.
Thanks.
What is that?
That would be Razor.
He's our coach.
He's a good guy. And he
really knows his derby.
All right, ladies.
Let's roll.
Ooh, jean shorts
Every single day.
Meet the
Manson sisters.
Gift from the Ottawa Women's
Hockey League to the Hurl Scouts.
They both seem
really aggressive.
Maybe we can finally
win a few this year.
Maybe.
All right, listen up,
fresh meat.
There's a lot more to derby than
fishnets and picking out a tough name.
This is a sport.
Now, the league
has six spots open.
So whatever shred
of talent you have,
hope you leave it out
on the track for me today.
Okay, what is it?
Sorry
Just what are the rules?
Derby 101, people.
Four blockers from each team
are lined up on the track.
Ten feet behind them,
two jammers are lined up,
one from each team.
We're the ones
who score.
First whistle blows
and the pack takes off.
Then a second whistle blows
and the jammers take off.
Some of us faster
than others.
Once the jammer
breaks through the pack,
she hauls ass around the track
a second time and tries to score.
For every player on the
opposing team the jammer passes,
she gets a point.
Most points wins the game
every single time.
Now, line up
and get you some.
Get up
Go, ladies Move it
Up, up, up Go
Looking good, Barbie.
It's roller derby,
not cotillion.
Come on,
put a hit on somebody.
God damn it, Diane
Hey. That move will get
you tossed from a game.
There's no place in
this sport for that.
What?
Okay Sorry
But I like the aggression.
Is it bad?
Mmm-mmm.
Mmm-mmm
No. Mmm-mmm.
Forty-one, gotta improve
on that 39, 32, not bad
Twenty-nine. Let's go.
Twenty-three?
Looks like you've
got some competition.
Yeah, yeah, wake me when she
learns how to throw a hit.
Or take one.
Hey, you're
Iron Maven.
That's right,
kiss-ass.
Why don't you suck up
a little harder?
There's still part of your face
that doesn't have doodie on it.
Nice shorts.
Help.
Can somebody help me? I...
Just kidding.
Hey, by the way, you made
it, you're a Hurl Scout.
Nice work out there.
I never knew
there'd come a day
When I'd be saying to you
"Don't let this good love
slip away..."
Your feet are on fire.
They're on fire.
Seriously, look,
they're on fire.
You're changing
your schedule?
Well, I have to.
You know, for practice.
Don't leave me alone
with Birdman.
You can change
yours to mine.
I can't. I'm actually taking
an SAT class, remember?
So caught up in you,
little girl
That I never did
suspect a thing
So caught up in you,
little girl
That I never want
to get myself free
You caught me
Baby, you taught me
How good It could be
Shania, I am not cleaning Salisbury
steak sauce off of that fringe again.
Hey, I just wanted
to let you guys know
that I'm gonna change
my work schedule
to Mondays, Wednesdays,
'cause I wanna take an SAT
class on Tuesdays, Thursdays.
I'm impressed.
Me, too
I like smart girls, that's
why I married your mama.
Well, that and I
knocked her up.
So caught up in you,
little girl
You're the one that's
got me down on my knees
So caught up in you,
little girl
That I never want
to get myself free
And, baby, it's true
You 're the one
Who caught me
Baby, you taught me
How good It could be
Fill your days
and your nights
No need to ever
ask me twice
Oh, no
Whenever you want me
Shouldn't... Shouldn't we,
like, be practicing soon?
Yeah, hurry up, you guys,
we don't wanna be late.
Careful, Pee-Wee here might
get the idea we actually win.
You don't?
Hell, no Never
All that "We're Number 1"
corporate crap doesn't apply.
Our bad attitude's
an asset here.
Okay, ladies
Check it out.
Hot off the presses, brand new
playbooks compiled by yours truly.
Your hands clean?
Yes, my hands
are clean.
Pay particular attention
to Play Number 3.
I think it's gonna
blow your doors off.
Smashley,
you're late as per usual.
I know.
Well, then you must also know that
there's nothing cool about being late.
Hey...
Let's hit the track.
Who's up for Lovejoy's later
tonight? $2 pitchers. Beer?
I'm in.
Me, too
I'm in
You weren't invited.
I'm still in.
There's no such thing
as a scrimmage.
We practice
the way we play.
Maven, you know
what to do.
Bliss, show me
something good.
You ready?
Am I ready?
Let's go,
ladies. Skate.
Don't block your own player,
let's go.
Crossover the turn, stay
low Crossover the turn.
Bend those knees. Bend
those knees. Bend those knees.
Ow!
What the hell
was that?
You had Maven beat,
but she smoked you
'cause you're too
scared to throw a hit.
And then you quit.
I need you to
be a lot more...
I want you to start
being a lot... Ruthless.
Yeah.
That's right, you little peanut,
I need you to be ruthless.
This is
a contact sport, Bliss.
Eventually I'm gonna
need you to make contact.
Next group up.
Back off, Razor
Just ignore him
We do.
Seriously
I mean, he's right.
I'm not cutting it.
You know what I like to
think about before every game?
My ex.
Little piece
of advice, Bliss
Don't fall for your
regional manager
and think that he's not
gonna give you crabs
because he cheated on you,
'cause it happens.
And when I think about myself in the
shower, using that special shampoo,
which, for the record, doesn't make
anyone feel very special at all,
I really, really
wanna hit somebody.
You have to find that thing that
really pisses you off and you use it.
Have you ever had crabs?
No.
No Okay My doctor said
it was really common, but...
B-man, come on.
What do you say?
Pash has to come. You
know, it's my first game.
Yeah, well,
what about me?
I mean, did anybody
bother to think,
"Hey, Birdman might appreciate hot
girls in fishnets and roller skates
"beating the crap
out of each other"?
No, they did not.
Do you wanna come, too?
Yeah, but I can't.
I have a prior engagement.
I'm covering for Pash.
Yes. We love you.
Birdman.
Yeah? You know we love you.
Thank you. We do.
You know that, right?
Yeah, yeah. Not enough.
We're crazy about you.
Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
You can never have
too much eyeliner.
Or Lash Blast.
Here's a little gift
from the team.
Safety is sexy
You'll need these, too.
Those are just sexy.
Guys, thanks
Let the bout come to you.
So, are you ready
for your big debut?
Has anyone ever thrown up
on the track before?
Yeah.
Let's get them.
Kill them dead.
Skate fast, skate hard
I'm gonna puke.
During the day,
they go by Peggy, Francine,
Tammy, and Rachael,
but here...
All right, let
the bout come to you.
Okay
One, two,
three, kick ass
And they're off.
Jamming for the Widows, Eva
Destruction against the Hurl Scouts.
Bloody Holly who makes
her way out to the pack.
And, oh, she passes the block
with a beautiful backward skating.
But wait a second,
from out of nowhere,
Eva Destruction shows up
right on her tail.
Each girl the jammer passes,
they get a point.
Pass a girl,
get a point.
And she's gotten the first
seven points of the game.
And the Widows
take the lead.
Hey, Black Widows, my
spidey senses are tingling.
About to make a sequel
in my pants.
Yeah,
Spider-Man 3 and a Half?
Yeah, it is three and
a half inches wide.
Air trombone, yeah.
Nice jam, man.
That was amazing.
Thanks.
Yeah. Thank you.
Where did you learn
to skate like that?
Well, I once tried out
for the Olympics,
but that didn't
exactly work out.
You gotta maintain the
triangle configuration.
I've been over it and
over it with you guys.
What do you want
to do? Come on.
I don't need to do the triangle
I need to get up there and...
It's the second quarter
and we have Manson Number 1
jamming for
the Hurl Scouts.
This is a rough
contact sport.
These girls are lean,
mean skating machines.
And they gotta go fast if they
wanna get past the blockers
who are trying
to knock them down.
And by "knock them down,"
I mean "beat them to a pulp."
Eva's gonna grab
another four points,
bringing the Widows' score to
26 over the Hurl Scouts' 10.
Team captain Maggie Mayhem doing the
honors for the Hurl Scouts, but... Oh!
Getting Widows jammer Honey
Suck it back for that rail check
and Whiskey sweeps Manson
Number 2 out of the way,
making room for Honey
to widen the gap
to collect another three points
there as we go into halftime.
That makes the score 29-10. Come on.
They say the Scouts have
the most loyal fans,
and being the worst team in the
league, Lord knows they need them.
Oh, Rosa Sparks,
no, you didn’t.
God damn it.
Okay, folks, the Widows
have a pretty comfortable lead here
late In the game.
Hurl Scouts coach Razor
still sticking with Smashley
Simpson as the jammer.
She's up against the Widows'
speed woman, Honey Suckit.
Oh! The Wldows' jammer
hip-checks Smashley.
Well, our favorite
Whole Foods checkout girl
is about to bag her some Honey. Hey.
Clean-up on Aisle 5
With time left for only one
more jam, and the game out of reach,
Smashley Simpson
is out of here.
Okay, you're in
Show me why they
call you Ruthless.
Go get you some
Okay, Austin, get ready to
meet your newest Hurl Scout.
Here she is, Number 22, the fastest
thing on eight wheels, Babe Ruthless.
Babe Ruthless? All
right Go, Babe Ruthless
All right,
It's the final jam of the night.
I like the taste
of fresh meat.
And Razor, with nothing
to lose, throws the rookie
into the last jam on
her very first game.
And dang.
Babe Ruthless gets a double shove
to the rail served up by Whiskey.
But she's back up
like a Weebie.
Okay, okay, that's good
She darts down the inside
and heads towards the outside
and makes a run for it
out of the pack.
Oh, but here comes Eva
Destruction, still skating strong,
hoping to ruin
Babe's debut.
Ruthless is out of the pack She's
coming around for her points.
That's my best friend.
Rumor has it that Ruthless blew
away the judges in speed trials,
and you could certainly see why tonight.
And now Manson Number 1
takes out Eva.
Feeling the heat
Ruthless is bringing,
and she gets through
for the score.
And Ruthless
gets four points.
Go, Babe Ruthless
Babe Ruthless scored the
last four points of the game,
but the Widows
take this one home.
Congratulations,
you still suck.
That's great. Celebrate
mediocrity. That's fantastic.
Yeah, it's all a big joke.
We came second.
You came second.
We came in second
out of two teams. Nice.
We're
Number 2 We're Number 2.
We're Number 2.
We're Number 2. ROSA:
Razor, come on You did good.
Well, I didn't
throw up.
That'll do.
Good thing.
Hey.
Oh, my God I take back what I
said about you not being tough.
You kicked ass.
Really?
Oh, yeah And I saw that
guy you liked You did?
Mmm-hmm.
But then I lost him.
Bliss.
Hey, Hot Tubs.
Oh, I can't I gotta
get home to my man.
No.
Yes. Great game.
Yeah, man,
that was good.
What's Hot Tubs?
Yeah?
Oh, well, here at the
Warehouse, he's Johnny Rocket.
But here he's
"Hot Tub" Johnny.
Even though he's not allowed in,
we started calling him "Hot Tub"
until he got us one.
Huh.
All right.
Check it out.
No, that's
the thing.
Coke?
You swallowed?
That's hilarious.
Not in this
lifetime, Johnny.
Or the next one.
Hey.
What's up, ladies?
Should we help him?
Nah That's her fiancé He
loves it SMASHLEY: I love you.
That's my fiancé
Hey.
You know, there's some stuff
I'm pretty sure I could teach you.
Johnny.
Y'all check it out.
He's not even in anymore, man.
...I need you
tonight, tonight
It's gonna be all right
'Cause you are in my sight
All night, all night
Tonight, tonight, all night
Hey, sweet thing,
will you please bring
That one thing.
It makes my heart sling
Why? 'Cause I need it
Hey, man,
check this out.
That's not a bruise.
That's a bruise.
Yeah, you look
pretty good That's nice, huh?
Pash?
Nice choice.
Yeah?
Yeah, and I love
this one.
So where you from?
Well, I hail from the bustling
metropolis known as Bodeen, Texas
Uh, the tiny town, right?
Off of South 84?
That would be the one.
You live alone?
Roommate.
Me, too.
Four of them.
Why Bodeen? If you don't mind
me asking What do you do there?
By day, I work
at the Oink Joint.
But by night...
Oliver. Oliver.
Oliver.
One second.
Get your ass down here You left
Jasper's guitar in your car.
All right, dill weed.
Shut up, douche bag
Nimrod.
Tampon.
Tool.
What are you doing in approximately
five and a half minutes?
No official plans.
Great.
I'll go bring
you something.
There she is.
All by herself.
Hey.
Don't fight it.
Let's get a beer.
Oh, my God
Okay, you can make out
with him But that is it.
Who are you,
my mother?
Pash?
Savage and I have been
looking everywhere for you.
Yeah, I bet
My belly hurts.
There's a storm
in there.
It really does, though.
Come on Hold on
Hold on. Let's get this.
It's cool.
I swallowed it.
No, come on. Just stick
your fingers in your throat.
No, you stick your finger
down your throat.
Pash. Have you ever thought
about your parents making love?
Your dad's naked body?
What?
His balls jiggling.
Sweaty
No.
That's not fair.
Could you get me
a washcloth?
Yeah.
I'm sorry I ruined
your kind of date.
But I want dirt.
His name's Oliver
It's a great name.
Yeah, if you like wayfaring
Dickensian orphans.
You're gonna have to roll over
You smell like a dead goat.
Sorry
Ugh.
Hey, girl.
How was the sleepover?
Fine.
Bliss,
are you ready yet?
The Blue Bonnet brunch
is in an hour.
Did you forget?
You think you have all
the time in the world,
but there's not many girls who
are both smart and pretty like you.
And I hate to admit it, but the
pretty part doesn't last forever.
You got to make the most of
what you have while you can.
Nobody tells you that.
Mom, you're still
really beautiful.
Save your sarcasm
for later.
How's your inspiration
speech coming?
I'm working on it.
You want me to read it?
Not yet.
Later?
Bodeen, Bodeen,
Bodeen, Bodeen
Someone get me
out of here, Bodeen
It's depressing
in the sticks
I'm all over
these racist hicks
And I'm jonesing
for an Austin fix
Yeah. That's right.
Bodeen, Bodeen,
Bodeen, Bodeen
Oh, my God,
it's him.
What do I do?
Go ask him if he
wants a Squealer.
Are you stalking me?
No, ma'am
I happen to be here in Bodeen on
business craving some barbeque.
And, yeah,
I'm stalking you.
Okay
Can you take a break?
You owe me. I wasn't even
supposed to work today.
I love you.
Is this you?
Technically, it's my brother's
band But, yes, I am in it.
And I'll be taking
that from you now.
Wow. From here it kind of looks like
you're wearing a Stryper T-shirt.
Stryper? Yeah, '80s
Christian heavy metal.
I mean, "In the name
of Jesus, we rock."
Well, I suppose if
it's in His name then.
What's this? What's this three
million five hundred and...
Oh, that's nothing
You wanna know?
I wanna know.
It's a little thing
called a high score.
At just the right...
Go. Nice shot.
Is this what you do
with all the girls?
You take them here to
show off your skills?
Yeah. And it
usually works, too.
Oh, yeah?
Maybe we should do
something different.
Stars at night
are big and bright
Deep In
the heart of Texas
I should probably
get to practice.
Shit.
Um...
I think I might
have lost my keys.
Marco
Polo.
Marco.
Marco!
Polo!
Found them.
Cool, I guess
we can go now.
Oops
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm gonna tear you up.
I know.
I am going to...
I realize this.
Holy crap, you guys
We almost won that one.
Yeah, almost
You know, Razor's play
actually worked.
Man, maybe we ought
to learn new plays.
What's up,
Hurl Scouts?
That was so
good out there.
It was really cute to see
y'all trying so hard.
I hate her.
Bliss.
Yeah?
Remember all that stuff I said
about winning not mattering?
Forget it.
I wanna beat
that cocky bitch.
Me, too
On my team. Yeah!
Look what Corbi did.
With all that
combined brain power,
this is the best
they could come up with?
They got
your freckles.
That they did.
Hey, are you all right?
You can't do that.
She just did
We deserve
better villains.
Just a few minutes gone by,
but the game Is already
falling into a familiar pattern,
giving the Fight Attendants
an 18-to-6 lead.
Okay, ladies, we're getting
beat, but we got the playbooks.
Time to show these Fight
Attendants a few tricks of our own.
Let's run Play Number 3.
Stampede.
Number 3?
Yeah. I think we only
got to Number 2.
Like, one and a half
You didn't learn
a goddamn thing, did you?
What's it gonna take for
you guys to pull it together?
You know what?
That's it. Hold this.
Did he just
take Number 3?
Come on That's all I'm
saying Just skate on through.
Hey, what's up, Razor?
Ready to forfeit?
Forfeit my ass.
Run this play.
What do I look like?
An idiot?
Anyway, I've got
my own plays.
Here's $20 You know
how little money I have.
You run the play. You don't
score at least three points,
you got another 20 coming
at the end of the bout.
Just run the play, Jeff.
You all right? Let's skate Yeah.
Ladies, we've got a change of plan What?
Hey, don't let that traitor throw
you. Let's hit him where it hurts.
Did Razor just coach the other
team or did my peyote just kick in?
I don't even know
what's coming on
'cause I don't know what's
coming around the corner.
Fight Attendants are
about to take on the sky.
Whoa! Holy crap,
a 180 turn.
Kami Kaze makes her way through the
rubble to score an easy four points.
Fight Attendants, 22,
Hurl Scouts, 6.
Is that Play Number 3?
Works pretty well,
doesn't it?
You suck.
You turncoat.
Want me to give them
Play Number 4 now?
No.
Okay Take a knee
Okay I wanna put what
just happened behind us.
I know I've moved on. We're
gonna run Play Number 2.
Fire and Smashley, you at least
know the first half of that, right?
Yes.
Okay
Then get out there
and get you some.
Hey, Scouts You mind finishing
your little Family Feud huddle?
Survey says you're
wasting our time.
Let's go ape shit.
Yeah.
Coming out of halftime
and an alternate universe,
Coach Razor puts former figure skater
Bloody Holly in the jammer position,
who launches furiously
into the pack.
The team Is on their game now,
pushing Bloody to the front.
And she makes it through
Bitch and Cooke Flake
grabbing a total of eight
points for the Hurl Scouts.
Come on, come on
The Hurl Scouts are catching up
in points for the first time ever.
As this space
oddity continues,
Babe Ruthless uses
her speed to fly by...
Oh! Axels of Evil
knocks her down.
But she's back up. Here
they come around the turn.
A choreographed move
from the Hurl Scouts.
Has to be from
Razor's playbook.
That makes
the score 58-58,
a first In the history
of the Hurl Scouts.
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but the Hurl Scouts are tied.
We got a tie game
here, folks.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, but Smashley goes down.
Really?
Bitch. What the... No.
Ooh, watch out, Tammy
No. No.
Here comes Smashley
Get off me,
you psycho.
We've got two girls
brawling on the track.
I don't know whether to break It
up or break out the video camera.
Hell hath no fury
like a woman fouled.
That's not legal.
By day, these ladies are your
favorite waitresses, nurses, teachers,
but by night these girls give
the crowd what they came for.
Smashley Simpson Is out of
here We're only moments to go
and the Hurl Scouts have
managed to squeak out in front.
We're at a 70-67.
Hurl Scouts.
Okay, grab her wrists,
hold on tight. Go.
Play Number 8.
You ready for the whip?
Put your arm out,
I'll be there.
It's the final
seconds of the game.
Manson ramps Cookie Rumble,
and the Hurl Scouts attempt
a classic move in derby.
Maggie.
Babe and Maggie go for the
whip, and it's effective.
Nothing gives you
speed like the whip.
A whip. Ruthless Is
flying into the pack
while her teammates are doing
a downright professional job
of clearing the way. She picks
up one, two, three, four points.
Break out
the merit badges. 74-67.
The Hurl Scouts
have finally won one.
Fight Attendants, this
Is your captain speaking.
It's gonna be a long, bumpy ride back
to Loserville. So if you have your...
You win the game. If you
run the plays, you win the game!
How about them Hurl Scouts?
Yeah How about them Hurl Scouts?
Touché, ladies Touché
We got to run the plays. We
run the plays, we win the game.
We'll do our
homework Every time.
There're only 10 of them.
It's not... Not rocket science.
Let's get those
Holy Rollers.
Yes.
I put a bomb in your fire
You say oh-oh-oh-oh
Murray. Murray.
Murray!
There Is a way to predict
the outcome of people like you
You are a sheep in sheep's
clothing and you know, you know
I am a-coming to get you
You say oh-oh, oh-oh
There is a way to predict
the outcome of...
Please tell me you did not
shove Corbi Booth over a rail.
Actually, I did.
Corbi has a huge
bruise on her leg.
I know that you're just
too bohemian to care,
but she has to
cheer tonight.