One female in her late thirties
and three minors.
Multiple stab wounds
and blunt-force trauma.
What about the ex-husband? Court said
the wife had a restraining order against him.
Dylan Bennet. He spent the night
with a bottle of Jack Daniel's.
- It was his first Christmas without
his family. - All the more reason.
Well, you didn't see him
when he ID-ed his family.
Looked like he'd
been hit by a freight train.
Seeing his kids like that. All the blood.
Yeah, it was definitely a nightmare for him.
If this guy did it, he gets my vote
for a goddamn Academy Award.
Let's say the stepfather,
this Grady Edwards did it.
- What do we got on him?
- Nothing.
Said he was from Kansas.
Except we can't find a match
in any database.
And he stopped the newspaper
to have time to disappear.
And we think
he might have done this before.
Three years ago in New Jersey,
a wife and three kids.
Gunshot wounds to the back of the head.
The stepfather disappeared.
Lived in a rented room
where he met the victims.
Both rooms were owned by older women.
One of the women
who lives in New Jersey said,
"He's a wonderful man,
always paid his rent on time and in cash. "
So, of course,
she never asked him for any identification.
No, he's smart. The Toyota Land Cruiser
that we found abandoned?
Paid for in cash. No driver's
license required for registration.
No credit cards, no anything. Which means...
- No photo ID required.
- Always a divorced or widowed situation.
I'm telling you, this guy's a monster.
Even if this is your guy,
it's been six months.
He could be anywhere by now.
Mom, Beth says I can't get these.
- Sean, we're not getting these.
- Hey! You two stop arguing.
Why does she always get to pick
the kind of cookies we get? It's not fair!
Life is not fair. Life is about the woman
getting to pick the cookies.
Sorry, they get
a little out of control sometimes.
They're just kids.
But the sooner you figure out the cookie
deal, the easier your life's gonna be.
I'm just saying.
It's a woman's world
and we're just guests here.
Wise man. I'd say your wife is very lucky.
I'm not married anymore.
I still wear it, but I lost my wife
and daughter in an accident last year.
- Drunk driver.
- God, I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
- I could use a little help, though.
- Sure.
Where is the peanut butter?
I just moved to Portland
and I don't know this store yet.
- It's actually two aisles over.
- This way? Thank you.
You're so welcome.
Remember what I told you.
What?
If I didn't know better,
I'd think you were following me.
No. Hey.
I'm not usually this forward,
but I'm recently divorced and...
I'm taking my kids for pizza,
so I thought maybe you might want to go.
- Pizza?
- The truth is,
I'm just dying for some adult conversation.
Well, I'm not usually this easy.
David Harris.
Susan. Susan Harding.
- It's very nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you.
I still can't believe she didn't come
to the airport.
I told you, she had some things to do.
- A little help here.
- Yeah.
At least you have me.
So, have you met this guy?
Yeah, a couple of times. You know,
when I came by to say hi to your mom.
- He seems cool.
- Okay, but she's only known him since,
- what, like, after Christmas?
That's so fast. - Well...
Come on, give it a chance. You know?
Before you do something stupid.
- Like what?
- I don't know. Like,
irritating your mom
and getting sent back to military school.
I'm just saying, it seems like
she's rushing into things. Don't you think?
I think it's her business what she does
with her personal life.
And she tends to screw that up, mostly.
Come on, Michael, chill on this one, please?
No fights with your mom.
- Okay.
- Okay. I got something to show you.
Surprise!
Well, this is a surprise.
This is a surprise. Thank you.
- I'm so happy to have you home.
- Hey, Michael. What's up?
- Hey. Sean. Holy crap, you're huge.
- Thanks.
- I missed you. Come here.
- Beth. I missed you, too.
- Welcome home.
- Hey, Aunt Jackie.
- Leah, hey.
- Hi, sweetie.
Let me look at you.
Your hair's gotten longer.
- Yeah. They ease up on you after a year.
- You look so...
So much like a man. I was expecting a boy.
That's what the military does. Builds men.
Good, strong men.
Michael, this is David. David, Michael.
- Is that a regulation cut?
- No.
It wasn't real military.
It was just a school for screwups.
Well, good to finally meet you.
I've heard so much about you.
Everything seems to be going great.
- Sean and Beth love him.
- What's not to love?
- Yeah, he's almost too good to be true.
- Don't start, Jackie.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I like him.
Do you think I'm crazy to be engaged
to someone I've only known for six months?
You've always been crazy.
That has nothing to do with him.
He seems a little crazy, too, about you.
- Everyone have enough to eat?
- Yeah...
I would like to propose a toast.
First of all, I want to thank
Susan and Sean and Beth,
who, in a very short time, have taken me in
and made me feel at home.
This is... It's a dream come true for me.
Thank you.
And to Michael.
Your return makes us complete.
Family is the most important thing.
Without it, we have nothing.
- Welcome home, Michael.
- Hear, hear.
Hear, hear, Michael.
I think I'm a little nauseous after that.
Stop it.
- You want something to drink?
- No, no, no, I got this.
We have a surprise for you, too.
- Really?
- Jackie pulled a few strings
and she can get you a job
working with her as a real estate agent.
- I couldn't.
- Wait a minute. Of course you can.
Okay? Just follow me around
and I'll get you all set up.
It's a great opportunity for us
and she really went out of her way.
Well, I can't say no to my bride-to-be
or her sister, can I?
- Thank you, Jackie.
- Don't thank me. Thank her.
Because she's the one who convinced me
to get you off the road
- so she can keep an eye on you.
- Did you?
Thank you.
I'm gonna go have a word with your son.
God, I hope Michael takes to him.
He will.
He's just been blindsided by the divorce.
He'll bounce back.
Michael. Give me four minutes.
Meet me in the basement.
So, what'd he say?
He said he wants me
to meet him in the basement.
- In the basement?
- Yeah.
Why?
I don't know.
Well, I guess I'm about to find out.
Those two are mine.
But you're welcome to use the others.
What's all this for?
Well, I'm a bit of a wannabe carpenter.
I built these storage cabinets myself.
And I'm working up in the attic right now
on some termite damage.
I think we need a real toast.
Just the guys.
This is where I keep the good stuff.
There we go.
Now, don't let your mom know
I've got a tequila stash.
I've worked my ass off
trying to convince her I'm perfect.
I know this must be a bit of a shock,
your mom and me getting married and all,
but I want you to know, I want us
to be a real family.
Because without it, we have nothing?
Okay. Touché.
So I get a little corny sometimes,
but I meant what I said.
You just let me handle your mother,
and I'm gonna make sure you stay right here,
where you belong.
No more military school.
We're gonna put this family back together,
you and me,
- father and son.
- Stepfather.
Stepfather
and son.
That's smooth, isn't it?
So your mother tells me
you're one hell of a swimmer.
Yeah, I do okay.
You know, I used to swim in competition.
In college, at U of O.
Your senior year is gonna be very important.
You could maybe get
a college scholarship swimming.
You should be training this summer.
It's kind of hard to train
in a backyard pool.
Maybe. But I hear your old school
has a summer swim program.
It does, but I can't use that pool anymore.
That's the past.
Here is to the future.
Remember, I have to go see
my grandparents tomorrow.
- Yeah, that's right.
- But I'll be back the day after. I'm sorry.
No, that's all right. I mean, it's the day I get
back, but that's fine. I'll call someone else.
Shut up. I'm sorry.
Listen, I want to get my license.
So, can you take me by the DMV?
- Maybe. I'll think about it.
- Why not?
I kind of like having you
dependent on me, actually.
All right, get in the car.
- Good night.
- Good night, Leah.
- Bye.
Glad you're home, Michael.
Thanks, Aunt Jackie. I'm so glad to be home.
Thank you for coming.
Do you think David meant what he said
about getting your mom to let you stay?
He said he was gonna make it happen,
so we'll see.
Sweet. Bye.
A lot for one day, huh?
No, no, it was... It was nice. Thanks.
I'm trying too hard. You can say it.
Look, Michael, I know it's difficult
to come home to another man in the house.
I just need you to try and get along, okay?
Mom, can we just hold the lectures, please?
I've been home for two seconds.
Okay.
He's a really good guy.
And he cares about me and we're
trying to start a new life together.
- And you don't want me to mess that up.
- Well, that's not fair.
No, no, no, I get it. I'll try not to
inconvenience you and your new life.
- Michael.
- I'm sorry. I...
I'm pretty tired, Mom.
Okay. Okay.
Good night.
Maybe he should stay there his senior year.
- But his place is here with his family.
- Yeah, but you don't know what he was like.
The kids he was hanging out with, the lying.
His temper was out of control.
Believe me, I want him here
more than anything in the world.
I just hope he's ready.
You're right.
Are you ready?
Well, it depends.
Are you ready for it?
- That smells good.
- Hey.
- How was work?
- Work was great. These are for you.
- Thank you.
- Michael.
- What's this?
- Your locker key to the boys' gym
at your old high school.
The swim team starts training
first week in July.
Wait, how did you swing this?
I had a little chat with Mrs. Rivers,
the athletic director,
a very open-minded woman.
David, that was so sweet.
Yeah, that's incredible.
It's just a probationary period for now.
There's no guarantee they'll let you back
in the fall. But we'll work on that later.
- It means a lot. Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
So, what are we having here?
Okay, I just think it's so cool that he
actually did what he said he was gonna do.
I know. I know.
See, I told you
everything was gonna work out.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
- Hey, we still going to the DMV tomorrow?
- Yeah. I'll be by around 10:00.
- Yeah, that sounds good.
- All right.
- Good night.
- Night.
Hey, Sean, turn that down, please!
Yes!
Sean, turn that down now! I mean it!
Your mother said to turn it down!
Do you think it's a good idea
they're so passionate at their age?
They've known each other
since grade school.
She's a good influence on Michael.
You should stop being so old-fashioned.
I think it's so lucky
that your mom met David.
Why is that?
He is gonna be your ticket
to staying here with me.
Maybe I don't want to stay here with you.
Maybe you want to go back
to an all-boys military school.
Maybe.
- But I like looking at you.
- That's why we make a good couple.
Because I like you looking at me.
You okay, Sean?
Yeah, I'm okay.
- You sure, buddy?
- This is great.
I've missed family dinners like this.
You've missed them?
Does that mean you were married before?
David lost his wife and daughter
in an accident.
Yeah, a drunk driver.
I had no idea. I'm sorry, David. I'm sorry.
I guess that's why
family is so important to me, Michael.
Well, family is important.
We haven't always had
such great experiences as a family.
- Hey, it wasn't all Dad's fault.
- No, I didn't say it was.
But, you know, our family wasn't that bad.
I saw on TV this woman who drove off
a bridge with her three kids in the back seat.
That is so not dinner-table conversation,
young lady.
- They all drowned.
- That kind of thing really gets to me,
that someone could do that
to her own children.
It makes you wonder, though, what it takes
to make someone do something so sick.
- Okay. Can we change the conversation?
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
Dad!
Maybe they disappointed her.
- Hey, how are you? Let me take this.
- I'm good. Thanks.
- Hey, sweetie.
- Hi, Dad.
- Aren't you gonna say hello to him?
- No.
- Shotgun!
- What?
There's no way you're getting shotgun.
- Hey. Hey, work it out, guys. Work it out.
- Hey.
Back on Sunday. They're going to camp.
- We have a million things to do.
- I know they're going to camp.
I'm only in town a couple days.
I'm taking the kids to a Blazers game.
They can spend the night with me
at the hotel. I'll have them back tomorrow.
- Where's the co-ed girlfriend?
- That's over.
Actually, she was working for a Ph. D. She
wasn't that much younger than you were.
She just took a little better
care of herself, that's all.
- Is Michael home?
- He doesn't want to see you.
- Those his words or yours?
- His.
"Your check is late" are mine.
Just make sure you don't spend any
of the money on my replacement in there.
It's not necessary to replace you, Jay.
You're not missed.
Good to see you, too, Susan.
You guys ready?
Everything okay?
He's just always such an ass.
So, Michael, Jackie has me covering
an open house in the afternoon,
but let's you and me have lunch tomorrow.
What do you say?
That'd be really nice.
- Yeah, that'd be good.
- Great.
Hey, Mrs. Cutter, how are you?
I'm fine, Susan.
There was a police sketch...
I can assure you it's not David.
Don't worry. It's so not him.
Okay. If you see it,
come over and let's talk about it.
- Okay. Thanks, Mrs. Cutter.
- All right.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
That was Mrs. Cutter. She's known
in the neighborhood as "The Cat Lady. "
Stopped by with one of her gazillion cats.
- They make my allergies go crazy.
- What'd she want?
Wanted to tell me that she had seen
this story on America's Most Wanted
about this killer and that
the police sketch looked just like you.
It was all I could do
not to laugh in her face.
You know Erica Harmon, right?
Okay, so a couple years ago,
she tells Erica Harmon's husband
that Erica is having an affair because
she sees this man sneaking into their house
every morning just after he leaves.
- And was she?
- Well, yeah.
- Well, there you go, then.
- Well, it wasn't any of her business
and she told the entire neighborhood
before she told him.
Great. This'll make me a hit
with the neighbors, huh?
I gotta go.
I think I'd rather be the mystery man
sneaking into Mrs. Harmon's house.
- What's she look like?
- Stop it.
Hey, where are you having lunch?
Because I need to drop Michael off.
There's a diner across from the office
and I'll bring him home
on my way to the open house.
Have a great day.
- Hey, Mom.
- Hey, sleepyhead.
- Want something to eat?
- Yes, please.
Okay.
- Where's David?
- You just missed him.
Good morning, Mrs. Cutter.
Okay, anybody got a sweet tooth?
- Do you want dessert?
- No, no.
- You sure? Some more tea? Anything?
- No. No, I'm fine.
- All right. Just the check, please.
- No problem.
- Thank you for lunch, by the way.
- Absolutely. So...
What I really wanted to talk to you
about was...
Well, I need a favor.
Well, what kind of favor?
I'd like you to be my best man.
- Me?
- I'd really be honored if you would.
There's no one else I'd rather have.
I know sometimes I get a little carried away
with the whole family thing,
but, you know, truth is,
I'm really happy you're home.
And like I said,
I'm gonna make sure you stay home
and this family stays complete. Right?
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
So,
- what do you say?
- Well...
I know it would make
your mother very happy.
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
That's great. That is great!
You know, without sounding
too sentimental, I want to tell you,
meeting your mother that day
in the supermarket changed my life.
It was hard, you know,
after what happened
to my wife and daughter.
My little Michelle was my whole world,
my whole life.
Watching her grow up was everything.
You'll understand what I'm talking about
when you have kids of your own.
Not that you and Kelly should be
rushing into anything. Okay?
No, no, no. Don't worry.
You got years to go if you're smart.
When it happens,
I think you'll see what I mean.
They're everything.
Lisa would have turned 11 next week.
- Who's Lisa?
- My daughter.
- Thanks.
- Pleasure.
I'm sorry.
I thought you said her name was Michelle.
Did I?
It's Lisa-Michelle.
You must have heard it wrong.
I'm sorry.
Yeah. 11 next week.
Damn it!
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
- Hi!
- Hello, there.
- We're the Baldwins.
We called about the house.
Mrs. Baldwin. Mr. Baldwin.
Good to meet you. I'm David Harris.
- Mrs. Baldwin, do you have any children?
- Three girls.
Three girls? You're gonna love this place.
Stay here. Finish your dinner.
Okay. I'm coming.
All right. Yeah.
Come on. Come on, baby. Come on.
Yeah. Let's see who it is.
Midnight? Midnight?
Where is that cat? Where is he? Midnight?
Where is that Midnight?
Come here. What are you doing?
What's the matter?
So, are you?
Am I what?
Gonna be his best man.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess. I said yes, so...
What?
I'm about to get another father.
You know,
and I can't talk to the one I have now.
Well, maybe you should start.
What's wrong?
- Didn't you close your door?
- Yeah.
Beth? Is that you?
Sean? Sean?
No, there's no one here.
What?
Jesus, David.
Hey, come on. Where you going?
- I better go home.
- You don't have to leave.
No, it's okay.
Were you just watching us?
Doing what? I just got home from work.
I'm gonna take a shower
and get ready for dinner.
You and Kelly have been together
for a long time.
All I'm saying is,
I just want you to be careful.
She seems like a very nice young woman.
Which is why a young man should be
more discreet with his affections.
- Meaning what? What does that mean?
- People might get the wrong idea about her.
You wouldn't want that, now, would you?
What do you suppose people think
about you
- moving in with my mother?
- Michael.
Excuse me. Apologize.
- No. For what?
- Being disrespectful.
It's okay. It's okay. It's healthy to have
open family dialogue, right?
Yeah.
How was your day?
It was busy.
Was Mrs. Cutter here today?
No. It's probably from the house
I was showing. They have cats and...
Sean. Beth...
Hey. If you ever lay a hand on one of my kids
again, it'll be the last thing you ever do!
What are you talking about?
- This bastard tried to choke Sean.
- I didn't choke anybody.
Sean says you put your hand
around his neck and it hurt.
His mother told him to turn down his video
game and he wasn't listening to her.
I was just trying to show him
a little discipline.
From what I've seen,
that's lacking a bit in this family.
If you ever touch my family again,
- I will kill you! I swear to God!
- Stop it.
- Come on...
- This is not your family anymore, Jay.
- What do you even know about this guy?
- Stop.
- What do you know about him?
- Stop it!
I know he's not sleeping with his secretary!
You don't know a goddamn thing!
- I'll call the police if you don't leave!
- Not a goddamn thing!
You heard what I said.
You touch my kids again,
you got some big trouble coming.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. Come here.
He had no goddamn right grabbing Sean
like that. No goddamn right!
You can't do this anymore! Come on.
Calm down, please.
Dad, here.
You dropped this. It fell out of your pocket
when you were going at it.
Thanks.
You stopped me from doing
something really dumb in there.
Yeah, I probably did.
I don't like this guy.
I don't trust him.
I mean, what do you know about this guy?
Not any more than you, really.
You got taller.
Yeah, well, you know, it's been a year.
Hey, hey, come on.
- Talk to me for a second, will you?
- What do you want?
I don't know. I want to talk to you.
Your mom says you don't want to see me.
Is that true?
I don't know, Dad.
You know, I'm not the one who left.
I left your mom. I didn't leave you.
You kids are the most important thing
in the world to me.
Well, yeah, yeah, you have a funny way
of showing that.
Hey, I know. I screwed up. I feel really bad
about that, but I'd like to make it up to you.
What, you're not gonna see me?
You're not gonna talk to me?
No.
Are you okay, Sean?
Yeah.
I guess I shouldn't have told Dad.
- Well, what...
- No, it wasn't your fault, Sean.
I shouldn't have done what I did.
It wasn't right.
I'm not your father.
Maybe someday, but...
This is all new to me again.
I'm gonna make mistakes.
And I just hope
you can forgive me when I do.
Can you do that?
I promise,
it'll never happen again, okay?
Friends?
- Friends.
- Yeah. All right.
I shouldn't have done it.
It's just that
I see a family without a father and I know
how easy it can all fall apart.
If I'm ever gonna be a part of you,
I need to gain their respect.
And trust.
I don't know how you were raised, David,
but my family never used physical force.
It's not okay with me.
Sure.
You're right.
I can't keep... I can't... I
can't... I got to make this work...
It's all right. It's all right.
I'll tell her I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's just...
Thanks.
- David.
- Yes. Something wrong?
No. No, in fact, everything's great.
Your enthusiasm with the buyers
at the Reeves' open house made the sale.
Great.
- We need these filled out.
- What are they?
Social Security, payroll insurance,
workman's comp.
And we need a picture ID. Personnel said
that they gave you the forms to fill out,
- but they just never got them back.
- No, no, I never got anything.
Don't worry about it. We need them, though,
so we don't have to keep paying you
under the table.
- I'll get all this done right away.
- Great.
It just wasn't something
I enjoyed doing, that's all.
Well, I don't understand,
because Jackie said you were a natural.
Real estate is just not me.
Well, what does that mean?
That you want to go back on the road again?
- I don't know. We'll see. We'll see.
- No, wait. I...
I thought you enjoyed family.
I mean, dinners like...
I know how much you hate me being gone,
but it's what I know best.
Let me get on your computer
and look around.
Maybe I can find something
that doesn't require much travel.
- Dude, you better turn it down.
- Are you worried about David?
He's not gonna touch you, all right?
I'll make sure.
I'm just useless.
Hey. I'm walking out the door right now.
Okay, see you.
How's it going?
Couple of things down in Eugene.
Okay, well, I'm gonna go meet Jackie
and Leah for a drink and plan the wedding.
- Would you like to come?
- I don't think so.
When I'm done with this,
I'm gonna go for a run.
Okay.
David...
I didn't mean to make such a fuss
about your work and all.
I don't want you to do anything
you don't want to do.
I
want you to be as happy as I am.
Have fun.
- Susan's not here.
- How about the kids?
Beth's at a friend's. Sean and Michael
are upstairs playing video games.
Look...
I'm sorry about the other night.
I made an ass out of myself.
It's just when Susan and I fight...
I was headed to the airport.
I wanted to say goodbye to the kids and...
Well, I'd like to apologize to you
for being a jerk.
Apology accepted.
Come on in and say goodbye.
Hey, Michael tells me you used to swim
for the Ducks?
A long time ago.
- Yeah? What year?
- '92.
Really? I went to U of O myself.
- I got to grab that. Excuse me.
- Sure. Sure.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Jay had left a message on my cell phone
saying he was gonna stop by there
to say goodbye to the kids.
- Did he come yet?
- No. Not yet.
Okay, well, if he does,
will you just stay out of the way?
All right. I'll see you later then.
Hey, you want to hear something funny?
I called the alumni office
and they told me they only had four guys
named David Harris
graduate in the last 30 years.
And two of them are dead
and one graduated in '87.
And the other one was that
All-American running back.
You remember him?
Of course, he's a little darker
than you are, wouldn't you say?
So...
It's just...
It seems like you might have lied to Michael
about college and swimming.
And now it's got me wondering
just, you know,
what else you might've lied about.
Hey, look, I told Michael
that I would do some checking on you
and, to be honest, I'd like some answers.
Hey. You hear me?
Yep.
- What?
- I heard something.
What was it?
I don't know. It's nothing.
I don't understand.
I'm kind of confused, because...
About?
Well, the feedback
from the buyers was great.
He just felt that it wasn't
what he thought it was gonna be.
You're okay with him on the road?
He's gonna try to find something
where he doesn't have to travel that much.
And I just want him to be happy.
If he's happy, I'm happy.
There you go. I just want to get his bags.
- Pop the trunk?
- You got it.
This is Jay Harding. Leave a message.
Hey, Dad. It's me.
Where are you? Call me. Bye.
David!
Yeah, what do you need, Michael?
Nothing.
You know when you asked me
at Michael's party
if I thought you were rushing into things?
I'm thinking now that maybe you are.
I mean, how much
do you really know about David?
The same day that I ask him for details
about his past, he just up and quits.
- You don't find that strange?
- No, I don't.
You know what I want to do?
I want to go to Vegas
- and have one of those 10-minute weddings.
- Nice.
David wants to have a church wedding.
That's great. What church? I mean,
do you even know what religion he is?
I don't care what goddamn religion he is.
Okay, you're starting
to sound just like Jay.
He's accused me of not knowing anything
about David. You know what I do know?
David has been good to me.
He's good to the kids. They love him.
He's made my life worth living again.
I mean, I...
For the first time in a long time,
I'm looking forward
to the future with a smile.
I just wish everybody would be
happy for me. Is that too much to ask?
No, it's not.
Personally, I'm with you. Hey, I'd have
my teeth cleaned in Vegas if I could.
Right?
- Go! Go! Go! Watch it! Wow!
- I just missed that car.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Hey, Mom.
- How'd it go with Jackie and Leah?
We decided we should go to Vegas.
- I'll be right back.
- Where's Michael?
He's in his room.
I think he's a little upset
that his father never showed.
That is so typical of Jay.
- Honey?
- Yeah.
I have a confession to make.
I accidentally broke the crystal vase
that was in the living room.
That's okay.
It was a wedding gift from Jay's sister.
I never liked it anyway.
You didn't?
- Or her.
- Then I don't feel so bad.
You don't think it's a little weird
that I ask for some background information,
and suddenly,
he doesn't want to sell real estate anymore?
Not necessarily.
I like David. He's a gentleman.
He always picks up the tab.
Jay was so cheap.
Do you know what I do think is weird,
though? He always pays in cash.
Who doesn't want the miles?
You know, I never thought
I would ever say this,
but I think I'm gonna give Jay a call.
I mean, if he's not buying this either,
then maybe it's worth checking into.
Hey. He didn't show up?
No.
I'm so sorry.
- That's okay.
- No, it's not okay.
He's never been there for you
like a father should be.
And part of that's my fault
because I never should have allowed it
to go on as long as it did.
That's why David's so important to me.
Because he cares about you kids.
He wants you to be here
and be part of your lives.
He's so perfect, isn't he?
Take those off.
I thought you'd be able to see
how happy David makes me.
He is part of this family now.
I want him in my life and our lives
and you need to understand that.
- Do you understand that, Michael?
- Yeah. I understand. Okay?
Okay.