- How about a tall cool one?
- Can't serve you nothin' before noon.
Get you a beer right down there.
They got air conditioning.
But it's a hot spot.
50, 70, 75, 80 out of a hundred.
Thank you.
I appreciate all your help but I'm
just not sure if that's what I'm lookin' for.
You're not payin' for a lot of things you
don't need. No power steerin' or nothin'.
I think it's about in your price range.
Yes, sir.
- Why don't you just give me a call?
- OK, then.
- It's a hot day, isn't it?
- It sure is.
- What's your name?
- I'm Mr Haynes.
Mr Haynes. Harry Madox. I noticed you
walkin' away from this new car here.
- Are you interested in a new car?
- Yes, I am.
You obviously know automobiles because
we've had this one come back to us twice.
But I got one here I wanna show you.
This is the same car that I drive. I have not
had one minute's hard time with this car.
Come in here. Jump right in there
and see how that baby feels. Hop in.
Yes, sir, the stylin'
on this car is tremendous.
Who the hell is that guy out there?
Darned if I know.
I gotta git. I'm late for Little League.
- I like the headroom.
- Isn't that something?
It's like this car was made
for a cowboy hat.
Let me run inside and see
what kind of deal I can work for you.
I'll just wait right here.
Wave your hands around
and talk like you own the place.
I do own this place.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
- Sellin' a car.
- Like hell you are.
I just did.
I got $100 off your down payment.
The price is gonna have
to stay the same, partner.
But I want you to look at
that low monthly payment.
- That's the best you can do?
- You're not gonna beat that anywhere.
- We got a deal.
- All right, you old rascal, you.
I'll tell you what. I believe you've got
the finest automobile we've got on the lot.
I believe it's my personal favourite.
# Gotta find my baby
# Or my heart is gonna break
unit five, I got a report
from unit six. They say they're sufferin'.
They got lane number one.
You and Elmer take lane three and four.
Well, I would assume then
that the truck is in lane two.
So that's a roger. Keep me in mind.
I'm expected.
- Where do I park this thing?
- It's good, right where you're at.
I'm Gulick. I'm the other salesman.
You must be Mr Madox.
Harry.
- How's business?
- Pretty fair.
Tyre kickers couldn't have much trouble
finding the place, that's for sure.
Shouldn't chew that stuff.
It's bad for you.
Madox, I want you to go out
with Miss Harper this morning.
Who's Miss Harper? And go where?
There's a repo out in the county.
Deadbeat by the name of Sutton.
And don't take any guff.
I'm tired of chasing that son of a bitch
all over, the first day of every month.
Sorry, nothin' doin'. Our deal
was for straight commission, remember?
What the fuck are you talkin' about?
I don't make any money
running errands for you.
- Maybe you won't like this job.
- Maybe I won't.
Mr Harshaw?
Gloria.
Gloria Harper. This is Madox.
Mr Harshaw,
maybe I could just talk to Mr Sutton?
I've always managed to collect before.
Forget it. You've got better things to do for
me than run that SOB down every month.
- I just thought...
- Dammit, Gloria.
Who's runnin' this place?
Get the hell outta here.
- I'll get Lon to drive you.
- I'll take her.
Oh. I thought you were sufferin'
from too full a schedule.
It cleared up.
Why don't you make up your mind
who you're workin' for?
- This is a business, not a club!
- Where's the green LTD?
Think we ought to come in like this
when he's not here?
Probably not.
The man married?
I don't think so.
He... He gets his drinkin' water
from a spring down behind the house.
I'm just gonna go down
to see if he's there.
- I'll go with you.
- It's OK.
I'm OK. You can just wait here.
- We can come back later.
- Oh, no, I found him.
He was down at the spring.
And he paid me. Both payments.
Must be a fast talker.
Glad I don't owe you any money.
Hey! You folks lookin' for me?
I need to talk to you...
Well, surely, Miss Harper.
A man of my type always enjoys talkin'
to a woman of your evident quality.
- Sutton?
- The same. The very same.
Miss Harper, ain't you gonna introduce
me to your gentleman acquaintance?
No.
Another time, perhaps.
Please.
I'll take care of this thing. I always do.
I think I can live with that.
Sure you folks won't stay for lunch?
Another time.
Wow.
That was about as much fun
as kissin' a passed-out drunk.
I guess I just don't have Sutton's charm.
You liked him so much you had
to go back and talk to him twice.
- Once at the spring...
- All right, I lied about it.
Now can you just leave me be?
Sutton a relative of yours?
OK, kid. Maybe I got it wrong.
Maybe I got it wrong.
I hope that's not that sleazy hotel I'm in.
Forgot to get my suit insured.
Come on. Move it on through.
Gloria...
- Miss Harper.
- It's my baby, Harry. Remember?
Did you get that car?
No. The guy paid Miss Harper.
Gloria! You'll just have to do the whole
damn thing over again next month.
I hope not, Mr Harshaw.
What was the fire down there? The gin?
No. Hamburger joint this side of it.
Maybe I'll go take a look.
How about hangin' around
while I go to lunch?
Sure. As soon as I get back from mine.
I suppose now you wanna go to lunch?
- What the hell did I do?
- Just watch it.
Mr Julian? Mr Julian?
Where the fire, Mr Julian? Where the fire?
- Mr Julian?
- Nobody here, Dad.
Mr Julian must be. He always here.
Damned if I see him.
I hear the hook and ladder
and all the people toin' and froin',
but I can't discover the fire.
- You say you know where the fire is at?
- A hamburger shack down the street.
Thank you, sir.
Well, I hope I didn't keep you waiting.
I guess I have to learn how not
to take a crap when the sirens go off.
All my boys are at the fire.
All volunteer firemen.
Used to have a woman worked here
but... she quit.
Damn.
I have got to get
that surveillance equipment working.
We hooked it up for the insurance, but
the damn thing never has worked right.
Jesus Christ!
Lucky you wasn't a bank robber.
What could I do for you?
I'd like to open an account.
Of course.
Always happy
to welcome a new customer.
Let me find a pen to write with here.
A pencil will do.
Now, was that checking or... savings?
Took your time, didn't you?
I'm going to lunch.
Why don't you give Gulick
a hand with that car out there?
The hell with that.
What the hell is the matter with you?
You got a grudge against the worid?
Nope. I'm a car salesman.
When I want a job cleanin' cars,
I'll get one.
That may be a lot sooner than you think,
the rate you're going.
What are you, anyway? 35? 36? Huh?
Around there.
Well, you sure as hell
haven't set the worid on fire so far,
or you wouldn't be
hangin' around a place like this.
Yeah, but I got ambition.
I figure if I stick around selling jalopies
for another 30, 40 years,
somebody'll give me a testimonial
and a $40 watch.
You wanna watch that stuff with Harshaw.
He's a good man, but got a temper.
Is that a fact?
Course, maybe he's got a reason.
Hi. Can I help you?
I was just lookin' for George.
- George?
- Mr Harshaw.
I'm his wife.
You must be the new salesman.
Madox. Harry Madox.
Sorry, Mrs Harshaw,
but your husband's gone to lunch.
Oh, damn.
Is there something I can help you with?
Well, I hate to ask you.
I mean, you're workin' and all.
I'm not hurtin' myself.
Well, if you really wouldn't mind,
I've got some papers and clothes
that need unloadin'.
Sure. I'd be glad to.
Well, get in.
I have a pair of shoes like those.
I ought to wear 'em more often.
They seem to be more effective
than I remembered.
It's awfully nice of you, especially since
George shouldn't carry heavy things.
- Why not?
- He didn't tell you? About his heart?
He's had two attacks already.
The doctor says he's got
to cut back on everything.
- That's why he hired you.
- No, he didn't tell me.
Well, George never did like
to go admittin' certain kinds of reality.
- Ain't you gonna put 'em down?
- What?
Mustn't know your own strength. Here.
- So what you gonna do in our town?
- Whatever there is to do.
Well, there are only two things
to do around here.
- Have you got a TV?
- Nope.
Well, now you're down to one.
Lots of luck.
- Good morning to ya, Lon.
- Howdy, bud.
What are you
in such a good mood about?
Lon, it takes a lot of money to be free.
And I'm gonna sell one of these to
the first sucker that walks in here today.
- You are, are you?
- Yes, sir.
Well, now. How do you
reckon to accomplish that?
Sheer willpower.
In this life, you gotta take what you want.
You damn sure can't stand around
and wait for somebody to give it to you.
"Gotta take what you want."
That's good. I like that.
- You know what I always say?
- What's that?
Look before you leap.
Mr Harshaw's gone for the weekend.
Huntin'. Said he needed the rest.
Yeah, and I got a notion from what.
I met her yesterday.
Mr Harshaw met her in a real small town.
Huntin' trip, I think it was.
He always said
that she just sort of happened.
Mm-hm.
The smart thing would've been to get out
and let her happen to somebody else.
- Harshaw Motors.
- Mr Madox?
This is Mrs Harshaw.
I hate to be a pest, but I was wonderin' if
I could ask you a teensy-weensy favour?
Well, sure, Mrs Harshaw.
What do you need?
- Mr Harshaw's cap.
- What?
Hi.
Well, come on in.
The least I can do is buy you a drink.
Sorry the place is such a mess.
I gave the girl the weekend off.
Oh.
That one thought he was stalkin' George.
Did he ever get a surprise!
Bang, bang.
I hope you like mai tais.
So...
How are you standing the excitement?
Maybe it picks up on Saturday night.
Yeah, it does. They show two vampire
operas at the movies instead of one.
I could buy a TV.
Or you could join the Ladies Club
and collect trash.
Now there's a hot pastime.
I doubt if I could pass
the credentials committee.
Not if you approached 'em one at a time.
You'd be lucky if you ever
got your credentials back.
Which one lives over there?
Mrs Gross.
She's the one with the binoculars.
What do you think of the view?
Better all the time.
That's where the pool was gonna go.
George said I could have one
if I was good.
But... he said his family hadn't had one
and what was good enough for them
was good enough for us.
I meant to ask you... about findin' me.
Did I give you the right directions?
I could find it in the dark.
You sure?
I think you'd better leave.
Like hell.
I thought you said
you lived in a small town.
Then you'd know that bitch over there
watched you arrive.
And she's watchin' right now
for you to leave.
Who cares?
I do.
Bad boy.
Bad, bad boy.
I'm going to bed. You can let yourself out.
- How much?
- A dollar.
- Thank you.
I need a double order
of grits and some more toast.
What you reading?
Oh! Oh, nothing. It's...
it's just... silly.
Would you...
Would you like a soda? Yeah, a soda.
- You don't want a soda.
- Yes, I do.
Yes, I do. What could be nicer on a hot
afternoon than a tall, clean, cool soda?
All right.
"He was a stranger in town.
A rough man, mocking, sometimes cruel."
"But Miriam saw past the tough facade
to the bitter wounds that made him
- hide his true self from the worid."
- I told you it was silly.
Oh, Junior, better not read that stuff.
It's bad for you.
I'm sorry about the other day.
I must've had the book open
to the wrong place.
Oh, please.
I realised later what it must've looked like.
My life's just been a succession of jams
over floozies of one kind or another.
I forget how to treat a real lady.
What do you say
we forget about the whole thing?
Start over. Make friends.
How about tonight? Wanna go for a ride?
Hey, look... I have to get back.
I'll drive you.
- It's just walking distance.
- I'll walk you.
She's a wonderful woman,
the woman who raised me.
She's always takin' people in.
Always feedin' the whole neighbourhood.
She had a daughter,
a little bit older than me.
She was my best friend
in the whole worid.
"Was"?
Yeah, she died.
It was a bad time.
Spunky. Hey!
Look who's waitin' here!
- You're very pretty.
- Oh, I'm just ordinary.
Ordinary?
Well...
Well, what?
Well, don't you ever knock?
Only when I'm not expected.
You were expected all right.
That was pretty ballsy of you, Harry.
Just comin' in my house like that.
What would you have done
if I'd have screamed?
But you didn't scream, did you?
Why don't you pour me another drink?
There isn't any.
The hell there ain't.
What happened to it, I wonder.
Maybe it leaks.
You know, Harry.
We're a lot alike, you and me.
Cos we got these hard, hard outsides.
- But inside...
- We're hard, hard, hard.
Harry?
Do you think I'm fat?
Of course not.
Well, you sure as hell oughta know.
I don't know what the hell I'm doin' here.
You seemed to like it at the time.
What's my batting average
always been for stayin' out of trouble
when it's baited with this much tramp?
Even zero.
- You're insultin'.
- You'll live.
I don't mind a little insult now and then.
Long as I'm sure it's just a little love play.
It isn't.
- Where you going, Harry?
- Nuts.
# Knocked out of my brain
# Since I fell for you
# Now I've come down
# With the heartbreak blues
# It's gonna take a doctor
# With a special degree
# Cos I need a love doctor
# I'm your Love MD
Recognise these?
The shoes, I mean.
I always wanted to be
put up on a pedestal.
You are crazy.
What about your husband?
Oh...
I take my opportunities where I find 'em.
Wanna look at mine?
You can come up real close
and get a real good look.
That was more fun
than eatin' cotton candy barefoot.
It's late. I gotta go.
Is it late, Harry?
Oh, God.
Got a light?
Hey! Home for lunch, back at two.
Now, y'all come over here. Come on!
This one here is my personal favourite.
Never mind this door bein' open.
I'm just airin' out the back seat.
Climb up in there and have a look at
the size of that seat. It's absolutely huge.
You could have half a dozen
kids in there. You'd lose half of 'em.
Don't you love a big seat? I know I do.
Lon, I'm gonna go check out the fire.
I'll give you the combination number.
Just don't kill me.
It's 397... 6557.
There's plenty in there.
357...
395...
3957...
Mr Julian! That you?
Mr Julian!
Mr Julian? You in there?
You in there, Mr Julian?
Mr Julian?
Can y'all please just keep your distance?
- Give him a hand with the hose!
- I got it!
Hey! Help!
Help! Help!
Oh, God! Somebody help me!
Fuck.
Hose me down! Hose me down!
Who the hell is he?
Are you all right, Mort?
He didn't hurt you?
And in thee shall all families
of the earth be blessed.
He was driven to part from all men.
So Abram departed, as the Lord had
spoken unto him; and Lot went with him:
And Abram was 70 and five...