Bruja.
Please don't hurt me.
Oh shit. Thanks. I
didn't even see that.
Neither did I.
People saw, seeing is believing.
But for me, that's not entirely true.
I lost my sight when
I was five years old.
Those memories of
what I have seen...
Have faded so much, I doubt that
I'd even recognize
myself anymore.
Now I see using my other senses.
I can smell the rain before it drops.
But I can't watch it fall.
I can feel the sun on my face.
But I can't see it rise or set.
I want to see the world
like everyone else.
To see the sun, the
rain. And music...
I bet music looks beautiful.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Taste's good.
Happy Birthday.
Thank you.
Evening Miss Wells.
Hi Miguel, thank you.
You're welcome.
Lilies?
New just this morning.
Myself, I prefer roses.
But you're the first
one that's noticed.
Nervous about tomorrow.
No.
Actually... I've never been
so scared in my entire life.
Listen, the night
before my mother's...
surgery, she drank
two glasses of sherry.
Steady as a rock the next day.
- Thank you. Goodnight.
- Goodnight.
This is Doctor Haskin's office
calling from County general...
...your procedure is
still on schedule...
for tomorrow. Be sure to arrive...
...at the hospital four hours before
for pre-op. Thank you.
Hi sweetie, it's your sister.
My flight gets in at 5 am...
The whole crew's got a lay over...
...so I'll find someone
to give me a ride...
straight to the hospital.
I love you Sydney.
Can't wait to see you. Bye.
12:10 AM
Hello?
Shh...
Martha will hear you.
She's on from 12 'til 6
And she takes away my M&M's
if I get out of bed.
I'm Alicia.
I'm holding out my hand to shake.
I'm Sydney.
I know, Sydney Wells.
I kinda read your chart.
You're the cornea transplant.
How old are you?
9 and 1/2. There's this
like... golf ball thing...
inside my head?
It made me so dizzy...
...I couldn't ride my bike.
So the doctor's are
trying to get it out.
When do you get to see?
Pretty soon I think.
Good. I'll come back.
- And you can take a look at me.
- Okay.
Bye, nice to meet you.
Bye.
I'm starting to lose the feeling
in my fingers.
Me too.
Ok, if you'll excuse me please.
All right...
All right, Sydney.
I'm going to take the bandages off.
Okay.
- ...you ready?
- Yeah.
That's one.
That's two... Okay, now I'm going...
...to help you open your eyes.
Very slowly.
Okay.
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
Okay, now tell me what you see.
I can't...
I'm going to hold up my hand.
And I want you to tell me
how many fingers I have up.
Five. Those are fingers.
Yes they are.
All right, here we go.
All of them?
Yes. Very good.
- Sydney...
- Yeah?
I want you to try and reach out
and grab my hand.
Okay?
Okay, it's okay.
Not everybody can
do this right away.
It burns a little. Is that normal?
Yes, it's perfectly normal.
Very good.
Thank you.
Am I how you pictured?
I don't know, you're really blurry.
I wish mom and dad were here
to see this.
Yeah.
I think I wanted
this more than you,
Sydney.
Not when you were 12.
I waited for this for 15 years.
I thought I'd feel a sense of...
It's sort of like...
It's not your fault. Hey...
It's not your fault.
I'm sorry...
You just need time.
You'll see.
Goodnight. I love you.
I love you too.
Sydney?
Can you see me?
Don't feel bad if you can't.
What's that on your head?
It's a bandana,
my grandpa gave it to me.
You know maybe tomorrow
we can take a walk...
And I can show you
the park outside.
The palm trees...
Alicia.
Oh, coming...
Sasquatch, I got to go.
Bye.
Please... I don't want to go...
Mrs. Hillman?
Mrs. Hillman.
Where are you taking her?
Mrs. Hillman?
I'm freezing... I'm freezing...
Freezing...
I'm freezing.
Where's Mrs. Hillman.
Oh, I'm sorry.
She passed away last night.
Everything is just perfect.
You are recovering quite nicely.
And the tearing stopped?
I think so, yeah.
Good.
So whose eyes were these?
Excuse me?
My donor?
I'm afraid I can't help you with that,
Sydney.
These are your eyes now,
and they're working.
It shouldn't matter
where they came from?
Does that hurt
A little?
Okay.
When will I be able
to see more clearly?
Well it varies with each patient.
Couple of days, couple of weeks.
But your vision itself
isn't the issue.
Since you've been blind so long,
I'm going to refer
you to a specialist...
...Paul Faulkner, he'll help you.
It's okay, I got it.
All right, have a nice
day off tomorrow.
Thanks Sydney.
Hi.
Hey.
Are you ready to
be my tour guide?
You're leaving?
Yeah, I'm afraid
they've had enough of...
me here. This is my sister, Helen.
Helen, this is Alicia.
Hi. Hi.
Hey, can we get a
picture together?
Of course.
- Here, I'll do it.
- Okay.
I know you're scared,
Sydney, don't be.
The world, it's really beautiful.
Okay, smile.
My carry-on's in the trunk,
And clean, go to
some art galleries.
Is it too much for you. Should we...
...pull over or something,
just say the word, okay.
No, no. We can talk everyday,
you can come over
and check on me.
I just... think I really
need to do this...
on my own, okay?
Okay. I understand.
Got some new lamps
for your place.
Oh, thanks.
I put them in.
- Here, I'll do it.
- Okay.
Surprise.
This is too soon I know,
I don't know what I was thinking.
No, no, it's okay. It's okay.
Do I know any of you?
Welcome home.
Oh hi Jim.
How are you doing?
Great to see you.
Nice to see you too.
Sydney, it's Bret. Welcome home.
Hey Syd it's me,
Alex, from upstairs.
Oh Alex... Wow, nice to see you.
It's your cousin, Sarah.
Oh Sarah, it's been so long.
I'm so happy.
Recognize my voice.
Oh, hi Cynthia.
How'd you know it was me?
How could I not, Cynthia.
What's up girl?
Oh, Richard.
So, this is what bald looks like.
Hey Sydney. How are you?
- Miguel.
- Yeah.
- How are you?
- you look good.
It's Amanda.
Hey, are you okay,
do you need some
water or anything.
Yeah, I'm going to
go to the kitchen,
why don't you stay with the guests.
1:06AM...
- Hi.
Sorry I'm late. That's Henry.
I'm Paul.
Sydney.
Have a seat.
You damaged your corneas
when you were 5?
Yeah, my sister and I
were playing with firecrackers.
I tried a transplant when I was 12...
But I rejected them.
Stem cell research
changed the game.
Is that why you tried again?
No, my sister was
really the one that...
kept up with all that stuff.
These are Doctor
Haskin's test results.
There's nothing physically
wrong with you...
The operation went flawlessly.
But you're probably in for a shock.
Why?
You already filter
information from sound,
smell, touch. But now...
...you're going to be
assaulted by a million...
things you never
even knew existed.
A whole new level of confusion.
Do I look here, or
here. Is that bright...
thing important or this dark one...
...moving towards
me or away from me.
Dangerous or not?
As long as your eyes are open
there's just too many distractions,
I mean, how do you concentrate.
I'm talking to you, and you're...
...looking at that
woman. And you're...
thinking is she going to eat that.
That's a pineapple by the way.
You cut it open...
I like pineapple.
Anyway, because you
can see people...
...you're going to expect people
to do things you can't do.
Read signs, recognize
body language.
Recognize facial expressions.
Get out of their way.
Your eyes will want to dominate
how you perceive the world.
But you can't fully
trust them. Not yet.
In the next few weeks,
I'm going to help you...
see the world like it really is, okay?
A lot of it is going to be difficult,
but the main thing
is to be prepared.
And that's where I come in.
Okay? We're in this together.
Oh, you scared me.
Hey...
Have you seen my report card?
Your report card?
Do you live here sweetie?
My Father will be so mad at me.
Have you seen my report card?
I'm sorry.
Let's take five.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
Relax.
You're pushing too hard.
You know when I first
went to London...
to work with the Philharmonic.
I was so nervous. In Prague,
I was a big fish. In London...
...one of the hundreds.
But you did so well in London.
I never thought I would be ready.
But when it was time to go on,
everything faded away...
It was just me and the music,
face to face.
I wasted so much
time being worried.
But there was nothing
to worry about.
And now our spring
concert series...
...is almost upon us. Sydney?
Will you be ready?
We're all counting on you.
I'll be ready.
I'm sure you'll be.
Number 42.
42, that's us. You sit
tight, I'll get it.
Thanks.
42?
Oh I ordered a salad.
Can you change it?
Yes.
You think I'm just
going to let you go?
You think I'm not
going to do something.
That's it, right?
I'm gonna do it.
I'm sorry?
I told you I was going to do it.
Don't go.
There was a woman,
she came at me.
What woman? What woman?
Christ's sake,
get a hold of yourself, please.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
It's all right.
Well, from the latest results,
there's nothing
wrong with your eyes.
Well maybe there's
something wrong...
with the tests.
Tests only gauge the fact that
you gave no abnormal responses.
Creative ones, yeah,
the kind that artists
and musicians give...
...but the last I checked,
you are a musician.
I'm sure other musicians don't see
what I've been seeing.
Come with me.
I'm not an idiot,
I understand what
you're telling me.
My brain is having to relearn...
how to decode the
world around me.
But that's very different from me...
seeing things, that
don't seem to be real.
How...
Look, you're real...
Okay...
You're here.
My perspective and
focus is off, but...
You're real. I can see you.
We see what we look
at. But the way that...
we see things is affected
by what we know...
And there's a lot around you...
That you can't make sense of yet.
What are you saying to me?
You think, I'm making this up?
You think I want this
happening to me?
I think you're not
going to be able to...
push through this...
I think you were better off before...
All special, well you
just discovered...
you're like the rest of us.
Stop it.
You know when we first met.
I didn't think you
were such an ass.
That's because
you didn't know how to spot one.
See...
Progress.
Have a good evening Mrs. Chueng.
Ahh, Miss Wells. Your
new TV is here...
...my buddy from
the cable company...
hooked you up.
Thank you Miguel.
And welcome
to the 200 channel universe.
Thanks.
- Bye.
- Good night.
Hi, this is Helen,
I'm out of town until Saturday...
...so if you need to contact me,
do so after the beep.
Hey, it's Syd. Please call me.
What are you doing.
Call 911. Somebody call 911.
She's not breathing.
Hi, you've reached...
the cell phone of
Doctor Paul Faulkner...
...leave a message after the beep.
Hi Paul, it's Sydney.
I'm at a Chinese Restaurant...
...at the corner of
4th and Figueroa.
Something's happening to me.
I need you to come, please.
Excuse me.
Sydney, Sydney. It's
me. It's me. It's me.
This place...
No, no, no. I was just here...
I was just here.
What are you talking about?
This place...
There was a fire in
here, there was a fire...
in here weeks ago, five
people were killed.
It was in the newspapers,
it was all over the press...
- I was just here...
- Hey...
What's wrong?
Everything's wrong.
My apartment keeps changing.
It was filled with smoke and
I was attacked...
What do you mean
you were attacked.
...by this man... He
was on fire then...
he was gone.
Everything was gone...
So I had to get out of there.
And I was walking
down the street...
And...
...this woman walks through me.
She walked right through me.
And I saw the shadow...
I saw it before...
...at the hospital.
It's some kind of escort...
That takes people away when
they're dead.
There's something so
angry about them.
They don't want to be seen.
And then, this...
I see people...
...like nothing's wrong.
When they...
...don't seem to see me.
Sydney, listen to me.
I'm seeing things that aren't real.
I'm seeing things
that I shouldn't see.
I'm dreaming things,
I've never seen.
This surgery was supposed to
make me normal.
Sydney... Your eyes
are not the problem.
These eyes are not my eyes.
Yes, they are.
- No, they're not.
- Yes, they are.
Listen to me.
You've got a disorder, all right.
We've got to teach your brain
how to separate out...
...these ghost images
from the real thing.
You're not listening to me.
I'm not seeing ghost images.
I see...
What? Dead people?
Rooms that change...
Phantom escorts...
Whatever it is that you
believe you're seeing, it's not real.
It's not.
It's not real.
You don't believe me.
I want to help you.
How can you?
How can you, if you
don't believe me.
You gettin' on or what?
It's not real...
Have you seen my report card?
No. I already told you.
Stop asking me.
No.
Have you seen my report card?
It's your sister Helen,
I'm on my way to the
airport. Are you okay?
Will you call me, on my cell,
okay. Please.
You're scaring me
sweetie, pick up.
Okay I'm going to call
someone, I'm going to...
call someone unless
you pick up, Sydney.
Sydney?
Miss Wells.
Sydney? It's Paul,
are you in there?
The doorman's going to let me in,
all right?
Will you give us a minute.
Sure.
Your sister called, she said...
you hadn't answered
the phone in days.
What is this?
You want to be blind again?
At least do it right.
When you were blind,
you had a life, you...
were engaged in a
world. You had a job,
what is this?
You get scared and
you just drop out.
Run back to your room,
turn off the lights.
What now?
I'm going to take you
to the hospital and...
get this cut sewn up.
Is it really necessary?
Yeah.
I think you should keep her here
over night,
here's my telephone number.
Sydney Wells? You're back?
Alicia?
What are you doing in here?
The golf ball's gone, Sydney Wells.
- What?
- I have to go now.
Wait. Hang on.
Alicia?
I know you're scared, don't be.
Because the world
really is beautiful.
No.
No. Alicia.
Don't go with him.
Alicia.
How are you?
Whatever's happening...
There's nothing that can't be fixed.
Morning.
How's the hand.
It's fine.
Alicia's mother wanted
you to have this.
Said, she talked about
you all the time.
She was smiling up
until the very end.
Who is she?
That's you, Sydney.
That's not me.
Of course it is...
...who else would it be.
Sydney...
What are you doing?
Sydney, you're scaring me.
What do you see?
Cellular memory,
based on the theory that all...
...living tissues have
the capacity to...
remember...
...cellular memory explains
how energy and information...
...from a donor's tissue
can transfer consciously...
...or unconsciously
to the recipient.
Recently, recipients of
organ transplants...
...have begun to report
episodes of newfound memories...
...thoughts, emotions
and characteristics...
...that are often associated to
the original donor
Paul.
Sydney, I can't talk right now,
I have to go to a meeting.
Listen. There's no history of
schizophrenia in my family.
I've never suffered from
any mental condition,
not depression,
migraines, nothing.
So, for argument's sake
Let's just pretend I'm not crazy.
All right, walk with me then.
There have been cases
of transplant...
recipients who've
actually showed...
...characteristics of the donor.
Right. Cellular Memory.
There was a liver
transplant patient...
in Kentucky last year...
...that almost immediately felt
the urge to pick up smoking.
A health nut all her life.
The donor was a chain smoker.
Down to the same brand.
And a few years ago this
little girl helped...
the police solve the
murder of the person...
she got her heart from.
She kept having
visions of the crime.
There's some kind of
chemical... It's...
Peptides.
It's how the mind
and body communicate.
So it's not too big a leap
to suggest memories...
can be accessed from
these organs, too...
No, because corneas aren't
a major organ,
it's like changing the
windshield of a car.
But there's still a
chance isn't there?
I... I need that chance.
I need to find out
who the donor was.
I see her in the mirror every day.
I have to find out who she was.
That is confidential information.
You can't ask me to do that.
I could lose my license.
Your license...
Well by all means...
...hold onto that license.
Sydney?
Sydney, come on.
Thank you.
What floor?
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Thank you.
He's here, isn't he
My Tomi.
What was that about?
Who's Tomi?
Her son.
Where was he?
He's dead.
Who are you?
What do you want?
I want to help you...
...but how can I...
...if you won't tell me.
Sydney, are you okay?
Sydney, open up.
Open up.
What the Hell is going on.
I need to find out who she is.
- Who?
- My donor.
Her eyes, my eyes.
I've seen what she saw.
I'm seeing what killed her.
Sydney, please...
Helen, don't.
I love you,
but there's no way
you can help me.
You're not making sense.
It's all happening to
me. Everything that...
happened to her, is
happening to me.
Until I find out who she is...
And what she wants...
it's going to keep happening.
County General please.
Hey, hey, hey.
The only...
...cornea transplant that
matches the date of your surgery...
...came from a Clinica Saint Javier,
Los Llanos.
Your donor was from Mexico.
Do you get car sick?
Why?
It's a 15 hour drive.
Thank you.
The file says your donor was
Anna Christina Martinez.
One living relative, mother.
Worked in a ceramics factory.
Hopefully we can track her down.
So what made you
change your mind?
About what?
About coming down here with me?
Can't you just let me sabotage
my career in peace.
I was just wondering why
you changed your mind, that's all.
Is it because you believe me?
Paul, stop the car.
What do you see?
There was a fire here.
I keep seeing fire.
Hey, maybe they know something.
Hola chico. - Hola.
All the doors were locked,
and nobody could get out.
He lost a brother.
How did it happen?
He says something about a witch.
You see that, bruja?
Yeah, actually I've seen it before.
That means, witch.
I don't think anyone's here.
Hola.
Hola, Senor Martinez.
No. I work here.
Is someone from the
Martinez family here,
that we can speak to?
Senora Martinez is here,
but she is resting.
Oh well we could
wait, it's important.
Emilio.
Come in...
- Come in.
- Thank you.
Please don't be
long, She's not well
Mrs. Martinez...
My name is Sydney Wells.
And this is my friend
Dr. Paul Faulkner.
What do you want?
Well we would like to talk to you
about your daughter.
I was wondering about...
...how she died.
What business is this of yours.
It's hard to explain...
...see I have a connection.
With your daughter.
You have her eyes.
I'm sorry for how I
look, there was...
...a fire in the factory where I work.
Did your daughter die in the fire?
No. But many others did.
If they had listened to Anna,
they would have been saved.
What do you mean by that?
It doesn't matter now.
Did Anna ever see things
she couldn't explain.
Do you see things?
Things that are not real.
Yeah...
It's a terrible thing to see
the spiritual world, isn't it?
The souls destined...
...to repeat their death, everyday,
unable to find peace.
Yeah...
Anna was always alone.
People around here,
they were always afraid of her.
They would blame her.
Why would they blame her?
One time when she was a little girl.
She would sit in front of
the person's house and she...
...would just cry. And soon after...
...somebody in that
house, would die.
I know that she wasn't
doing these things...
...she wasn't bringing
death to anyone.
But she could just...
...see death.
This is a small town.
Many superstitions.
Bruja.
The graffiti outside.
As if they have nothing
better to do all day...
than cover your house...
- Call an ambulance.
- What?
Call an ambulance.
Every night... Every night...
...she does it again, and again.
Please, save her...
Save her... Save her... Save her...
What happened.
She's having a heart attack.
We got to get her to a hospital.
Help me put her in the car.
You ready, got her?
- Where's your keys.
- My right hand pocket.
Open the door.
All right, bring her around.
Set her on the seat.
Go around to the other side.
Pull her in head first.
Will you hold her legs for me?
I got it.
Please...
All right, all right, close it.
Close the door.
Emilio, you take the keys,
you drive, you know the way.
Come on.
I need to stay here.
What?
I'm fine, just go.
We'll be quick, don't go anywhere.
All right, Anna. I'm here.
What do you want me to see?
Mama.
Bruja.
Bruja. Bruja.
Paul?
Paul, is that you?
Anna?
Anna...
Please help me.
No. No. No.
No. No.
No.
Come on. Come on.
What am I supposed to do. Please.
Tell me.
Your mother asked
me to save you,
but I don't know how.
What am I supposed to do?
I don't know what to do here.
What?
What do you want from me...
...tell me.
I believe you...
I see what you saw...
I know what you went through.
It was never your fault.
How's Mrs. Martinez?
She didn't make it.
Thank you.
Hey buddy, what's going on?
Some high-speed chase down
the American side...
...has the whole border shut down.
Nearly an hour now.
Might as well make
yourself comfortable.
Great. Thanks.
How long was I out?
Not very long.
Oh, it's freezing.
What's going on?
There's some kind of...
...chase on the other
side of the border,
we could be here all night.
Really?
Wanna play a game?
Mommy.
All right, come on,
let's get back in the car.
Come on, you're scaring
the little girl,
let's go.
Wait.
Look at her,
you're scaring the Hell out of her.
Let's get back in the car, now.
Come on.
What?
Oh God.
Sydney.
Sorry man, are you all
right? All right...
I see the shadows.
They're everywhere.
Excuse me. Excuse me please.
Open up.
Open up please.
What is going on.
There's going to be a accident,
we don't have a lot of time.
Please, just let me
talk to the driver,
okay.
Oh my God.
Don't you understand.
This is what she wanted me to see.
Everything I dreamed wasn't from
Anna's life, it was from this...
Right now. She let me see
that this was going...
to happen, so I wouldn't
end up like her.
She wants me to
save these people.
That's what she wants me to do.
You have to believe me.
You need to get off this bus.
Everyone needs to get off this bus.
All of you. You can't stay here.
Everyone has got to
get off this bus.
You need to get off
this bus, right now.
Is it like a terrorist thing?
- Yes.
- Get up...
That's exactly...
...what it is.
There's a bomb on the bus.
There's a bomb. Run. Move it.
Run, come on, get out of the car.
Come on, get out.
In the car... Run. Go.
Out of your car.
Wait here, sweetie.
Mom.
Run. There's a bomb.
Run, get out of your cars.
Get those people out
of there right now.
Get out of the car.
Come on, you got to
get out of the car.
Come on.
Go, go, go.
Help me. Mom.
Hey. Hey. Hey. Are you all right?
Get my daughter. She's inside.
Open the door.
How. Please.
Help me.
Help.
- Paul.
- Help.
Stand back, I'm going
to break the window.
Close your eyes.
Stand back.
- Hurry.
- Stand back.
Come here, honey.
Paul, let's go
Hurry up. Run.
Come on. Run. Run. Ru
You saved them Sydney.
You saved them...
Some say, seeing is believing.
Now I know what they mean.
Anna Christina tried
to prevent death.
But she was ultimately
powerless to stop it.
Anna and I shared both a blessing
and a curse.
I know, now, I don't need eyes
to see what truly matters.
The gift of Anna's
sight made me see...
what I was afraid to.
To use...
...that vision to not
only save myself...
and others...
But to give Anna the peace...
...that she never found in life.