Quick, honey. We have already closed.
- This is not acceptable.
As I've discussed it yesterday.
A massage at sunset with Tanya.
It should be Tanya.
I need to know that the bank safe.
Trust me. I have dozens of banks
updated. It'll be fine.
I need guarantees.
- Gordon, you do.
It's a security update.
Not the end of the world.
I swear, if I leave again
Cooperstown should work and I miss...
I burn the whole thing flat.
- I see you. We all have plans.
Mr. Sullivan, it is always a pleasure
to see you.
I have this massage
one month ago planned.
No, I want Tanya.
Her hands and small pneumatic drills.
Who can I get?
Jonathan?
He has strong hands?
Look at you.
How may I help you?
- One hundred dollar exchange.
How would you like it?
- Seven pennies, 31 quarters...
...and 919 cents.
- What?
That's too much money.
Than 107 pennies, 839 pennies...
...29 quarters and half dollars 7 pieces.
Is that Chile?
Brazil.
- The U.S. dollar half I never use...
I can 101 pennies,
157 cents and 557 cents.
That's a joke.
- No, I did something with coins.
I love the weight, size
and how they ring in my pocket.
That's pretty weird.
- What?
The figures that you enumerated.
101, 157, 557...
...these are all primes.
- That no one ever noticed.
I work with numbers all day.
You do so in your head?
- Yes, good with math trick.
I suppose so.
- What's your name?
Kaitlin.
- I'm Tripp.
Actually...
...we do not hand customers.
Mobile phones on.
Where are you located?
- How do you know?
My wedding presents.
- That's quite a few.
Are you going to marry
Jay Z or something?
My fiance's wealthy.
Wealthy?
Over two days, they married in Brunei.
My husband takes me disagree
along to the Sizzler.
He is rich. But is he happy?
- We are very happy. Glad you asked.
Darrien present.
- Weinstein present.
Gates present.
- We go. Unlock the weapons.
That's the door.
Use the remote control.
Come on.
One, two, three, four, five...
...six and one seven.
Anything else I can do for you today?
No, thanks.
Thank you chose Credit International,
required a great day.
You squeaks.
- I need my medications.
Is there a pharmacy nearby.
- Two blocks from here.
Nice to meet you, Kaitlin.
Likewise, Tripp.
Good luck with everything.
You are being robbed.
What are you doing?
This is a robbery.
What are you doing here?
- What does it look?
You rob the bank.
This is obvious with
the weapons and stuff?
No, this is our work.
Go back.
I see your name on the board outside.
Unless his name is Credit.
Given all the weird names that the parents
give their children these days.
The alarm does not work.
- The phone does not.
What do we do?
- Proceed as planned.
Select the security update.
If the system is rebooted,
The entire bank closed.
We know. Turn on the quiet,
or I'll shoot you in the face.
Wait a minute, boy.
Do it.
You have exactly three seconds
to go back...
...or will shoot at you.
- There are plenty of ATM machines.
A...
- Two blasts off on it.
I heard that.
- Two, three.
It's now or never.
He saves not.
- Go down.
What?
- Hello?
I know your heart sitting in a firefight...
...there is a wounded.
I look as if everything is okay.
I come down.
Do not shoot.
I can shoot.
- We.
Go back.
- Wait.
Has anything ever happened to you?
- Certainly not.
He's dead.
- That happens sometimes...
...in the crossfire situations.
Do not look so hard for.
You are here for the safe, right?
- Who is this guy?
He talked about cracking ATMs?
- Maybe.
What's the problem?
Imagine now that we really
to rob the same bank?
Yes, why not?
Pretend it's two different banks.
- He has gone mad.
You do not here about it?
I do not want to add more murders
more add to my list perpetrator.
He wears shorts in a bank robbery.
We need to murder him.
How old do you think?
- We need to murder him.
Why do we have guns?
I want to shoot him.
The guns were meant for hostages.
That was the plan.
Now we have two hostages.
- What is our plan?
If they want to bank with us rob, we do it.
If they want to murder us,
We then murder them first.
Cool plan.
- Listen. We take them to the vault.
If the ATM you want, fine.
Leave us alone.
- Roger that, big guy.
That mean you do not?
What does he want?
- That we come to him?
It's good. Come here you.
- Keep an eye on him.
You're crazy.
Want to come?
Put the guns down.
Come here.
Let us introduce ourselves.
We can still be friends?
I'm Peanut Butter and this is Jelly.
Those are our real names.
We wanted something that
sounded good together.
Milk and Cookies, and was already in use.
That mean you do not?
I want the hostages have now gone.
Cell phones, pagers
everything that you or off the power.
Of course guns. Thank you
guards are worthless.
Guys, I have here.
Obviously you here.
You're a hostage.
Get on it.
Shut up and touch nothing.
Go to that door.
May I...
- Stay away from that door.
Please do not kill me on the toilet.
What kind of assholes that here?
Are not you ashamed?
Those guys are great.
- Fantastic.
We apologize on behalf of the bank.
Equally correct.
It really sorry.
Please, Rex.
- I'm Rex Neubauer.
I work for loans and we are lucky.
I am a certified consultant robbery.
I got to 75 survivors of bank robberies
advice given.
We'll work it out.
Our first goal is...
...for a peaceful co-unity.
Can I help you?
Our goal is to come live here.
As an expert in standard
bank robberies procedures...
This bank robbery is not standard.
Two robberies in progress.
And one dead. A guarantee that the robbers
come and murder us.
Do not say that.
- I do not want to die.
Let's stay calm.
This bank is open five hours.
Then I and my colleagues have long gone.
We're all trapped.
Even if you come out of this kitchen
then you are not from the bank.
So sit down and shut up.
- If we often go to the toilet?
There's toilet break.
You will not try to escape...
...or contact with someone
outside the bank. And no noise.
Alarm on your watch?
Are you in the sixth grade?
It runs every hour.
In memory of my medications.
Unfortunately I have not.
Or has anyone Deprocaine?
I have Xanax.
- I have Ativan and Prilosec.
I have a couple of Ritalin.
- I have maybe some Prozac.
I Adderol and Nassonex.
- Are you kidding me?
Shut up.
I just said, 'not talk'.
What's going on?
- Is Oprah's book club here?
Should I beat up someone? - No.
Have you turned off the
cameras and computers?
Do I really did not beat anyone up?
- I just said that.
Go get the scrambler.
That's ridiculous accent.
Before we get to work,
let us first look at the other boys.
I will start shortly with the lance,
ensure that the time slot is ready on time.
No problems. We came
just look at your toys.
You look so great.
- Did you see my face?
Did you see my face?
- No.
Admit it. Do not lie to me.
You've seen my face.
I may have seen your face.
- I've seen it too.
A very attractive face.
- Shut up.
You are damn kids.
You are worse than my kids.
You do not know...
...what you are doing.
Have you ever rob a bank?
A lot.
- We had the job with...
The Calahan brothers in Dubuque.
- What are you doing?
That's what I mean.
Say nothing about those other jobs.
And nothing about the people
you've done it.
Rob no bank without a mask.
Come on, guys.
That's asking for trouble.
Like your tattoos.
- Like them?
Look at this.
You can try to tie me...
...but it does not.
He did not understand. Do it again.
- I understand it really.
I think I need to talk slower.
Criminals usually try
their characteristics are not showing.
Duce not identified be.
You can try to tie me,
but it does not.
Go away.
All two.
Go away before I shoot you both down.
You may have spouses
and wives who will panic...
...when you get home tonight.
You may leave a ring.
You say that with
a friend to stay overnight...
...and you will be persuasive.
Otherwise I'll shoot you mess.
Who is first?
You?
You? No?
You then, with that ugly tie.
Honey?
Number two is done.
Now, number three.
We are 49 minutes behind schedule.
- Copy that.
I always got that blue stuff...
...this was on sale.
- I love that you're so economical.
Maybe we should be sure
read the instructions.
Is that Korean?
- No, Chinese.
Chinese are icons.
- Is that so? Explosives are explosives.
I come tonight to the airport...
My mother is sick and I stay with her.
Maybe we can go tomorrow. I love you.
I have no one to call.
- No one? That is pathetic.
Fuck it. This is the saddest
group of hostages that I have ever seen.
Sit down and shut up.
- I just said that.
I just left a message.
As I predicted,
They have not killed us.
Tripp was it?
Do you want to apologize, because
You have provided us a terror?
Why did they kill us?
- Why would they have to murder us?
They have been convicted of a murder.
Why not...
...all the witnesses murder?
I would do.
Might think the robbers are
the other did it...
...so they do not need to murder.
- It's express shot.
We must find out who he is
and why he killed Jack Hayes.
How do you know his name?
Driver's license.
- You have a dead man's wallet stolen?
Great.
Gates, you're up.
Like a gun in a brown paper bag need.
Tell me about it.
Do you see a clue?
- I do not know what profession they hold.
His business cards are credit card,
his transfer pass...
Those are the Citibank, but
not just international.
Why do we check him as he
has no business card?
Maybe he has a new account opened.
Gordon, the computers
stood by the mainframe.
Madge's money counting.
A strict security guard at the door.
Looks at the lady...
...held by the Office of the loans is.
Kaitlin is in her area.
And Jack Hayes was...
Jack Hayes opened any new accounts.
He was to ogle at the desk.
Otherwise he was to
a bank employee went.
What was he doing here?
I have no idea.
I feel your breath.
What are you doing?
Hello, Tripp.
Looking for a way out.
- Did not you think they will murder us?
I may just have your ring?
How long have you been engaged?
That way we'll find out.
Why your wedding with Max?
You know him do not agree.
- I know he is rich...
He can not meet your
appetite for adventure...
...meet and your sense of humor...
He sexually satisfy you.
She told me that he
his pants had been found. - Madge.
She knows him for two months,
and I have not met him yet.
Enough.
There are four pictures of you on that drive.
Three from Brazil. You're an adventurer.
Max is totally irrelevant.
He was with the Banana.
He was badly burned. He
remained in that day.
The worst part is yours and Max for
his mansion.
You are so small compared to that house.
He loves the house than yours there.
Who are you?
- The most interesting thing about you is...
...you are still working,
even though you do not need the money.
You're an independent woman.
I like that.
Count on that.
- If I did not use medication...
I'm not very good with...
- People?
Certainly not one I wants to bed.
And then I say such things.
Stop it.
Because of you we are all killed.
Be still there.
They call me Mr. Clean.
Where are you from?
No English.
- That I have been. To 'No English'.
That is close to 'No problem'.
The trip.
It can.
Come on it.
Now we have to murder him.
- Calm down.
Does your computer have?
Yes, that still works.
- How much time do we lose them?
Approximately one hour.
Let us remember that safe
and we murder that shit.
Then we crack ATMs.
- That is the blue color.
This is the blue color.
- We need to do murder...
This slows us only.
A bullet in their brains.
We have blown up the ATM?
The biggest job you ever did.
You have just three bars...
...dynamite eaten.
- Do we have blown up the ATM?
Let me see.
Do you want the good or the bad news?
The good news.
- That is, we have blown the door.
The bad news is,
that the ATM is intact.
Two doors.
I have not even pulled the trigger.
That thing just went off.
On your knees.
Facing forward.
Hands behind your head.
You're going to die, so you have
no extras required.
Do you have any ideas?
- See you on the other side.
You have to focus on the brains?
Then you have less junk or something?
It was fun, man.
Very nice. I had to no one else to do.
In practical terms, this is not a good idea.
- You said we could murder him.
Let me see the place.
- If you blowing something next time...
...let us know.
- You got it.
I want to personally thank
that you do not murder.
Are we going to murder them?
Are you crazy?
Why are you out of the kitchen?
- We have to murder them all.
You have missed.
He has to grab you?
- What?
Your ear.
- My ear?
I mean that.
Get ready to die.
Shoot him.
- I will.
Then I will shoot you down, and this circle
violence may continue forever.
Come on, dick.
Do it.
You want them to shoot me.
Shoot him down.
We are better than that.
Then I walk back.
Gates, bring the hostages to that office.
Do it.
Is it, good butter cookie?
Why talk to a hostage against me?
Somebody killed him,
and they will soon again a murder.
The man with the jacket.
I was not. I was not in the right corner.
Who had the good or corner?
Are you Dwayne?
Pay attention to the hostages.
Take it easy.
You're hyper.
You need a sedative.
What is wrong with you? I have a gun
on the back of your head.
What were you talking about?
- They wanted to know...
...if I thought you're the man
the jacket had been murdered.
Really?
- Yes.
Have you done that?
- No, we're professionals.
If one of us the guy was killed,
The hostages would be dead.
Why are there two bank robbers
killed at the same time?
Are you kidding?
- No.
At seven hours that computer guy
the whole security system is restarted.
This is a new protocol. The whole
security was two minutes flat.
That no more bank robbers
were here tonight I'm surprised.
Darrien should know.
He knows that right?
You tried to pry information out of me?
- Yes.
You are Jack Hayes?
- In all my years of taking hostages...
...you're by far the most annoying.
I'm sorry.
Go inside.
Hello, computer man. Why you busy
but ten keys when you phoned your wife?
What are you talking about?
- When she used the phone...
...expressed in all ten buttons
and then connect. For eleven keys.
You expressed only ten. I count everything.
Why do you do if your wife call you?
You sold the information when the alarm
off was one of the criminals.
Then you are greedy and you sold it again.
Double money, double robbery.
Why did you not call your wife.
Should I beat him up?
- Good practice when the police come.
, We'll 'water boarding'.
I saw how to do it on Discovery Channel.
I only need a mop and a pair of pliers.
- Wait a minute.
I have sold the information.
- What?
I've only done once.
And I do not even know to whom.
I have the information faxed.
They gave me cash.
You have to believe me.
- Why should you trust?
No reason. But I swear I
did not want anyone injured.
And I did not kill Jack Hayes.
- Says no.
We would already be.
- We need to break into this vault.
And I've had it.
Shut up.
I am a genius.
Ten left.
It is not. According to
the vault specifications...
...would be two inches thick.
That is much thicker.
How long does it take
to burn through them?
I do not know. Two hours?
Are all your chores so bad?
Should I worry if there is enough
gasoline in the van is?
Look at me. We have cracked the time slot.
We need you no longer need.
You threaten me, little bald Jew?
Jews have more small bald for humanity
done more than anyone else. Flicker is on.
We will not do crazy things.
Hurry.
Relax.
It never stops.
3000 years we pick that shit already.
I know.
I am not an accountant or
a comedy writer...
...or something very Jewish.
I am a bank robber.
Do you know how many Jews
there are bank robbers?
Not much.
Not very much. Even in this environment
they see only bagels and schmear...
...and Goldman Sachs.
We link or by fires.
It just takes a little longer.
I do not know, D.
We always said we would stop
if the information is incorrect.
That safe specifications are incorrect,
We are behind schedule...
...and then that idiot still Lancelot.
Hillbilly two in the hallway with weapons
play and explosives.
They have seen our faces.
Ten years ago we were stopped.
Ten years ago there was no recession.
In a few years we have 40.
That's 80 years in criminal.
I'd already be inside.
I need the money more than ever.
My little girl has just one bracket.
That Invisalign.
Not that cheap ceramics.
9000.
And they call us criminals.
We had to be dentist.
- Actually it orthodontist.
Keep the hostages away, I start to
the link. It's us succeed.
It always works.
We stop the door from the C4...
...and blowing out the door.
- Like an open beer can.
You are the dumbest bank robbers
I have ever seen.
You have my ear 15 minutes ago shot off...
So sorry, your comment goes one ear
and in my other out again.
What?
- You only have one ear.
That is a saying.
Are you doing with him?
They can not come between us.
They're trying to lower in rank.
You Muppets have ranks?
- Absolutely.
We've put you down.
- Want to bet?
Go ahead.
- Come on it.
That ranks them on the web.
- Are you still in Riverside?
We are the Internet thundered.
Has that ever happened you?
No, I've never the Internet thundered.
I have mixed feelings
about this whole experience.
You see more clues?
- No, I have to get closer.
How do you do that?
- I work on it.
Does it?
- Yeah, sure.
Do you have ADHD or something?
- No.
'm Not going on the defensive.
We all have stuff.
I take no coincidence Sanax.
- Why do you Sanax?
I do not know.
Nerves before the wedding I think.
Max is not true for you.
- Yeah, that must be it.
What you swallow?
- What I do not swallow.
Illegal or prescription?
- All prescription.
Illegal junk I do not trust.
Where you take it for?
Well, then you tell me.
It turns the TV off.
- Interesting.
Would you tell?
- How do I explain that?
I've seen hundreds of doctors.
They have hundreds of diagnoses.
Not that I'm crazy,
but it's like...
There are a lot of TVs and they are
All other station...
...a normal person...
...concentrate on one, I take it
all at once to me.
Can you expand?
- No.
I wish I could.
I've tried everything.
Switch channels?
- No.
Tricky.
- Yes.
You know what they say.
Normal but the kitchen
sink and washing machine.
A fool would say,
not a normal person.
This is the list of the FBI for
most wanted bank robbers.
Number one, Vicellous Drum.
He's overrated.
I do not know.
He was never caught.
The most stolen.
The largest ratio.
Jobs are running smoothly.
Like fat people who run to the buffet.
Look at the Baltimore job.
20 people dead. That's pretty excessive.
He takes it into millions.
Number two is Mick Nylon and his gang.
Number three, Alexis Black.
She is good for a girl.
And Darrien and Weinstein at 12.
They have been doing it 15 years.
They have much more
recognition than I am.
I am.
68 place as a bank robber.
But if four cyber criminal.
Now I can say...
My ear is shot off
the fourth cyber criminals in the country.
Will you be shooting my finger?
Hit me just now?
Where are we?
Number 674?
They have probably...
Excluding the international job.
We had a Kwik-Fit robberies in Winnipeg.
Who is here.
You have been arrested in Sagamore...
...when your car broke down.
We had blown the engine.
- Once you have raided a Kwik-Fit?
So ironic it's not for us.
I have broken their chains.
They're going to murder me.
You can still state witness,
then enter the prison.
Should I feel better?
The tank is not so bad.
There are not many gay men.
For you maybe.
You do look delicious.
Disgusting.
Come and help.
They have already learned that you
the detector are?
Come on.
Get out.
Gates, you rule the toilet breaks even.
I gotta give this guy some Rennies.
Sorry, guys.
See you later.
We put the things on edge.
Tonight it will happen.
You need the latest bloated.
You have also taken one for the team,
with your ears and stuff.
I have an idea.
Can we borrow one of the hostages?
Half of us anyway.
- You want to choose?
All.
I take that beauty.
- They are all beautiful.
I take that cue and mustache Remans.
That black chick, that creep,
gay and who goes with you.
What?
- I must go to the bathroom.
Should you piss again?
Is there something
wrong with your pecker?
I have some kind of problem.
Then go ahead.
In connection with the
team spirit we welcome...
Mystic Lightning.
Not Mystic Lightning.
I hate that name.
'Ties' is cool? Who are blind tunnel.
Rodents living on garbage and excrement.
These are not inspiring animals.
You should choose Peanut Butter and Jelly.
I choose this.
Well.
For our first activity...
We need a very special tie...
...that, if possible, can read Chinese.
For some totally harmless explosives
for us to explode.
So if you ask, we get not volunteer.
What?
- I can see Jack Hayes.
See?
He's dead. You can do nothing for him.
- You love me.
I'm not crazy about you.
- I have heard no gunshot.
How will Max react to this?
You mutilate yourself. I do not care.
Get out.
I'm not gay.
- Now is the time for it.
This must happen.
You put the primer in the C4.
You run to a safe place...
...and I push in the igniter.
This is really happening.
Igniter in the C4.
A gigantic explosion.
You will be thrown by the bank,
and we find you than in the rubble.
Success.
Go ahead.
He is not the smartest.
- No.
New rules now we only rob people.
This is absurd.
Of course they are locked.
Why this man hates us?
I found a few pennies.
Pennies.
The dumbest currency on the planet.
It looks a bit better.
I just found some pennies.
That way.
Drop the gun.
You heard him. Drop it.
- Put the gun down.
Put that gun down.
Put it down.
Drop the gun.
Now let the gun fall.
- What is it?
Drop the gun.
- It? Who was with him.
The origin of the gun I'm not interested.
Put it on the ground.
You're kidding.
We are the youngest team here...
We want you to your guns
us, if we focus on your gun.
This is an FBI gun?
- FBI? That's interesting.
FBI agent tried this bank also to rob?
Or someone he studied?
There are at least five...
...wanted criminals. -
What is happening here?
Got it?
- No.
I have that missing piece found in your ear.
If anything you, I care for you.
Peanut Butter and Jelly were
to the front door.
Darrien and Gates came down the stairs.
Bullets flew from north to south.
Blood splattered from east to west.
We were stuck in the crossfire.
North, south.
Darrien and Gates took the wrong exit.
Peanut Butter and Jelly too.
The FBI came, Jack Hayes was the pipe.
Only two people had it so
shoot. Mitchell, the computer guy.
He was unarmed.
If you omit this option...
...there is only one other possibility.
The killer must...
Be Weinstein.
Weinstein? Are you sure?
- Yes.
What is your source?
They each shot.
No, he can not be faster than Weinstein.
Where does he get a gun and
a silencer from?
Weinstein was furious
because the computer guy...
...two parties invited.
And that computer guy is furious because
Weinstein that FBI guy killed.
They confront each other, pulling
their guns and go both dead.
Why Weinstein confront him?
Why would an FBI guy Weinstein
murder in the middle of a bank robbery?
That asshole surprise.
- The computer guy has two bullets in it.
Maybe someone, someone else
surprise in a different way.
If it was not a confrontation,
if they were friends?
Watch what you say,
when you talk about my friend.
He would never betray me.
We have been together 15 years.
That means something in this kind of work.
There people had access to the kitchen,
Peanut Butter and Jelly where only...
...and you, Gates had access to the kitchen.
- And the hostages up in the attic.
Crawling up the hostages
are now in the attic around?
This job is over.
Wait here.
Darrien, listen.
That's odd.
What do we do now?
I have nothing.
I'm just this piece of ear...
...in the freezer.
- I swear...
...if you're a woman,
I would marry you.
I am not.
You go with me down.
Where's the remote?
We need them to get out of this.
A few more corpses.
We change the plan.
Therefore let this job go.
- You know what they say about plans?
If you want God to laugh,
tell him all about your plans.
Believe me, who is himself
there are broken laugh.
Nothing in this rotten bank
goes according to plan.
Where's the remote?
- Weinstein him.
What has he left?
- I do not know.
Take it easy and listen to me.
We had to go away long ago.
It's over. - We have
needed to break the link.
I need to get away.
I want to stay here and rob that bank.
- The bank job is fucked up.
You and me on a desert island,
drinking, lots of chicks...
Think about it.
The boat is gone, only
the engine is still there.
This affects your common sense.
I thought you had balls.
You're a disgrace to the black criminals.
Tonight was a fucking mess.
But not anymore.
There's only one gang robbers.
Three of us.
Mystic Lightning Can we be?
- No, you're Muppet.
No excuse, no more favors,
no gentle treatment.
It is now for real.
Because there is only one army,
There is even a general.
I am the General.
I have complete control.
Nothing happens without my say so.
Come on.
What is your cross?
Bring the hostages out of the office.
Hurry.
- You heard him.
The stairs.
Do you have thermal lance disabled?
You do not appear?
- No.
What's next?
We begin with the vault...
...or murder us all hostages?
- Definitely the vault.
Hostages may be useful.
You can use them as human shields...
...things they can get you.
As the money from the bank. Or snacks.
We start with the safe.
On one condition...
...if the time has come to do it,
I do it alone.
That should not be a problem.
We are not like the mass murders.
If you are in being so,
is not a problem for us.
Come on then.
Back to work then.
Does it?
- Excellent.
This is so much better than first class
flying, drinking champagne and...
...and go to my wedding.
If you can walk out the
bank with the money...
Max would you still need?
- You must let go.
I can not let go.
I'm obsessive.
If you had the money,
Max would still be?
He holds the door open for you?
He hugs you at night?
I do not like to cuddle? - Is he
the weekend to Mom and Dad?
My mother loves him. - Everyone...
...says you can not buy
happiness with money.
Nobody really believes that.
Your tenacity is touching.
As I exit I go back to Max.
I continue with this for five hours.
- No, I'm saying.
The thermal lance is blown,
so we use the c4 for the link.
We are all to the controlled explosion.
That would be something different.
I want you to know that I am
not use your explosives.
We know.
Go look at it.
No unexpected things,
No dynamite...
...or apache helicopters
and no nuclear weapons.
Now go and see.
Whoever it is, shoot them.
Why he always throws scissors?
Why, Jelly.
Why?
Do not throw scissors, but with stones.
Is there anyone?
I know you're there.
I will not shoot you, Tripp.
I just want the bank but robberies.
I do not know what happens.
- With the raid?
Yes, with the raid and everything.
I would now be the happiest guy
world should be.
I have a great job, working with
my best friend. The hours are ideal.
We have never been on people
having to shoot.
We've never seen anyone need to murder.
Can you come out?
It's strange to all those things against
a photocopier to say.
I will not be negative.
I'm just saying...
Maybe I'm not good at bank clerk.
Perhaps Jesus has me here
not put on earth.
My grandfather sold illegal liquor.
My father was a sex offender.
Criminals is in my blood.
Between you and me, it
was always my dream...
...been to work at a water park.
I hear you.
For what it's worth, I find
a great bank robber.
Are you serious?
You say no, because I have a gun
I focused on your dick?
Nothing that went wrong is your fault.
You are sabotaged.
Take it easy.
I let you see something.
Where did you get that?
Which I took from your suitcase stolen.
Look, even if each transmitter
suffer from interference.
The ignition should work.
No.
Who has changed?
Leader, are you okay?
- Who is your leader?
I must not tell you.
- Who has it changed, to murder you.
It's like leader,
or Peanut Butter.
Peanut Butter is a brother to me.
Peanut Butter and I are like best
gay friends in a bathtub.
We are so close.
A lot of money in the bank.
You need it from different angles.
He knew from the freezer, even though
we not been in that kitchen.
Let me tackle it was in the kitchen.
Who is your leader?
You can trust me.
Here.
Take a look.
Vicellous Drum.
We have never met him.
The text is clear, the information is correct.
Never has our face. Just a fax.
Is that normal? Receive a fax?
- You thought surely emails?
The police pull these things after.
They store about anti-fax technology.
Everyone loves the comedians
the hard copy.
I do not want to scare you.
Do you think there is something
the conspiracy theory?
I want to wipe out anyone's character...
I have Rex as he caught the vault
the measure was.
I asked what he was doing,
and then he said...
...that he was watching and lots of space
was for the new foreign currency.
What weird.
He would know if the system was flat.
He would have known.
He has repeatedly told us that he
an expert in the bank robbery procedures.
You're right.
- It's so crazy.
That is so.
Has anyone seen my insulin injection?
Grab a chair.
Does anyone have sugar?
- I do not candy.
Hold his head.
Fire.
Where?
- The man...
Glucose is necessary or he dies
and I get it anyway. Come on.
All right.
Where's the fire?
You often work with Vicellous Drum guy?
- Yes.
We were once decoys for 'm.
We had from him a bench robbery
while he 's safe in the big city did.
It was unfortunate that no money was,
out of 80 Canadian dollars.
Mr. Blythe's got low sugar.
We should seek immediate glucose.
Where's my gun?
Look over the edge.
As we crossed into the cell.
Wait, have you ever been?
And you monitor his bank?
Yes, I have some omission on my resume.
What have you been?
- Bank Heist.
And other offenses.
I have often done to mail fraud.
They were not big banks.
- How much?
A few. Twelve.
- My God.
Take it easy.
I am rehabilitated and stuff.
Are you single?
I think it is.
He must wake up normally, right?
He starts to open his eyes.
He's a tough old man.
Would you sit up?
- Ready?
I close the doors for the last time. Clear?
Is that clear, assholes?
I do not like that word.
- What did you just say?
I hate the K-word.
Say that again and I cut you...
- I said I hate the K-word...
...and use in America we never.
The Australians are damn.
He has the same gun as you.
- That's my weapon.
This is what you need fixed?
- What is the hell?
That is our way.
What do you want? Part?
- We talk outside.
Hands behind your head.
Out.
Calmly.
- Maniac.
You've made your point.
- Why?
Unless you have something to be
negotiate, say.
Weinstein was our informant.
I have never met our leader.
How have you contacted?
- That I will not say.
Would you leave?
Answer to my question.
Look, we have only this fax.
I switch on the remote.
Calmly.
- Get up.
Give me the remote.
Now give me the damn gun.
- It's Jelly his weapon.
It was from his mother.
Is it 's weapon of your mother?
I give it to you.
I'm sorry.
You lose that damn gun now?
- No.
Are you fucking crazy?
You lose your gun privileges.
Forwards.
Jesus. And you.
I do not want to hear from you.
One word, and you're dead.
Go back.
- Thanks.
Back to work.
My god.
- What was that about?
I like the remote exchanged with this fax.
And that 's good deal?
- No idea.
That's why I kept the battery with me.
Mr. Blythe told me he saw Rex
the vault of the measurement was.
I have seen.
Where is the Swiss girl?
The Swiss maid is not there.
- It happens.
What then?
Faxes, the night vision?
- What are you talking about?
Five, six...
- Stop counting.
Tripp, stop.
What?
- Why did you do that?
Because you might as bright...
- No, it does not work.
For God's sake.
- I think of a thousand things.
And now I have the kiss
think. Are you serious?
My God. My brain will explode.
He's crazy, but has talent.
Indeed, he is a criminal genius.
We are blessed.
- Can we help?
A soft drink without sugar?
Go somewhere else.
One more hour.
We will make it.
The only people murdered
criminals are provisional.
They can kill themselves.
We are heroic survivors,
as I call it.
Starting tomorrow, everyone
one week vacation.
I have next week Fri
- Then we'll have 'a week business.
We're not safe.
- You want me just do not agree.
No.
What's in her bra?
- I take it well.
Wait.
Do it.
- This is disgusting.
Forward, pull it out.
She works in a Swiss bank?
What a waste.
It is especially sad like a nice girl dies.
If an ugly girl dies
was their life sucks anyway.
But if a nice girl dies is it really 's tragedy.
Indeed. Nice girls are
unicorns and gnomes.
Rare and valuable.
They must be protected.
My god.
- What?
This is not a bank robbery.
You're fucking dead.
Hakuna Matata, asshole.
Listen, and I give you back primer.
Well.
These are the two faxes to you
these bank robberies.
This is the fax to the Swiss girl.
They are different...
...except that they are each 81 mm
have a blank line.
The printer had a scratch.
- I do not understand.
Neither do I.
- Printed by the same device?
By the same person.
- Who?
Vicellous Drum.
- Who is that?
The number one criminal mastermind.
Those clever bastards.
This is an organized trap.
Vicellous Drum has a problem.
He goes' n lots of people killed
associated with him are...
...but it may not seem that he is behind it.
Each of us is connected with the criminal?
Yes. Let me explain.
If this is true, the FBI agent searches
Drum for years.
Darrien and Weinstein have already
previously worked for Drum.
The Swiss bank representative
Drum money laundering.
Mitchell Woolf is his Drum
computer hacker.
Peanut Butter and Jelly
have him working as decoys.
They may be able to reveal all.
And all the rest, who knows...
Perhaps Mr. Blythe met Drum
alone, making him angry.
He was offended. Maybe flirt Mr Clean
with him in a prison shower.
A blowjob in prison he does not survive.
Perhaps we are here by mistake.
Collateral damage.
- You're kidding.
Hoping that we kill each other?
This is sloppy, especially for Drum.
That's why he is here, personally.
Come on.
- Think about it. The thermal lance.
The explosives went off at the exact time.
The FBI agent was the largest Drum threat.
He left Weinstein him first kill.
Yes, Weinstein worked for Drum
from the beginning.
Like Mitchell, who knew ceded as security.
Drum and then killed them.
Drum had the best possible
in a double murder seems...
...but the remote Weinstein
his mouth was very suspicious.
I guess Weinstein him in
his mouth was blocked...
...to avoid the real killer,
Vicellous Drum, the bank could escape.
Then inactivated by Darrien Drum.
And then shot Drum Swiss girl dead.
Five dead, eight to go.
What a fucking bullshit.
Nice story.
It's not open.
The money is yours to fly paper
here to lure and kill you.
There is no money.
- Of course there is money. Shut up.
Really, we've been working too hard.
- This is not a bank robbery.
Damn.
This is the best bank robbery ever.
- You said there was no money, eh?
It's just fly paper.
- Yeah, I guess.
Jeez.
My god...
So it does not matter
that the money is here,
Drum because everyone is dead?
We love to 't be.
I do not know who of you Drum is...
...but keep me away.
Grab a gun?
- No, it does not matter.
Drum his plan was always to everyone
murder. We must be smarter than him.
How to kill so many armed people?
Lights, night viewers,
and kill everyone.
Why do I get there not?
- You said something about night vision.
In the bathroom there is one.
- What more do you need then?
Which man will get night vision goggles,
Drum's.
Or any woman.
How do we get it all in there?
How much do you think this is?
- Four or five million.
Let us begin.
Really? Now go save the Bank?
- No, I want with you.
There is 'one damn killer.
I'm going too.
- Me too.
Do not forget me.
- We are all here.
Let each other holding hands.
Seriously. You never get away.
Do not say Amen to that sort of thing.
You will frighten Jelly.
Tripp is actually right.
That remote has no battery.
Are you kidding?
What bastard has the battery?
Vicellous Drum.
You took the battery to us here to keep.
No.
- You wander through the bank.
You could at any time someone
have slain. The perfect crime...
...you solve yourself.
Unbelievable that I kissed.
You should not take a genius to
to come under your skirts.
Flatter yourself that you would get this far.
If the rest of you idiots had
Attention, did you realize...
...that all the evidence point to Madge.
Not true.
Who turned out the light?
- Come on. Not again.
Shoot everything that moves.
Vicellous Drum.
Where is he?
- We 't seen.
Come out.
Forwards.
I'm not Vicellous Drum.
I took the lights off because I knew...
...that the real viewer
would drum the night out.
Then I went to the bathroom and I waited.
A bank manager a golden heart.
Everyone is surprised
when they hear it's you.
You think?
Those clowns in the lobby thinking
that you're Vicellous Drum.
They will kill you,
so they are more a hero like.
If you kill me,
you seem even more Drum.
So, you're lapping anyway.
A very entertaining story,
but nobody believes it.
Come on out.
Enough lies, it's game over.
Not so fast.
Tripp and I have run into you.
We knew that when the lights would go out,
that the offender would go to night vision.
You can kill all of us, right?
No.
Every one million U.S. dollars.
Undetectable.
All.
Two million.
Put the weapon down.
Put it down and we talk.
Damn.
And then there were about six.
Thank you, guest.
That solves it in me.
Take 't. It is insured.
Blessed new appointment.
Thank you, Badger.
I say one more thing:
From now on, Jelly and I do not
more criminals.
That's right.
I almost forgot my ear.
And ultimately, Peanut Butter
Jelly and with the money going to run?
Crazy, huh?
They went to Winnipeg or something.
Thank you.
You may go.
Close everything.
- Your medication, sir.
I take everything.
I would the word 'hero' is not used.
I led my team of hostages
through the darkest time of their lives? Yes.
I want two months paid time off.
I want to wear jeans five days a week.
Not just on Fridays.
And I want lenses in both eyes.
That you must not do.
- No problem.
Thank you.
Please, ma'am.
Congratulations.
Thanks again, officer.
What is this? A toaster?
A controlled boat?
Some people like to get money.
I thought you were never true story.
Then I remembered that
Weinstein said he...
...two bank robberies Tonight was shot...
...and then I realized that
are basically three robberies.
A pretty good plan.
Kaitlin Nest?
She married the wrong guy.
What a touching story.
You fake fiance, Max...
...explains your expensive taste.
It explains your exotic travel
and your exorbitant demands.
And you have your wedding gifts
walk outside with heaps of money...
...no one asks questions.
You did you make a move
about seven hours...
...when the security went out...
...but Derrien, Drum and everything else
ruined your plan.
But you waited for it right now.
And when I turned off the lights,
You did your move.
Take 't. It is insured.
It's really brilliant.
Nobody goes to the wedding present
of a woman opening...
...and the policemen carry the
still in the trunk of your car.
I honestly love you.
Is that too early?
What do you want?
- I want to join.
Is that so?
- Equal partners. No violence.
Why should I not murder?
- You are not murderous.
I feel like me.
- You think?
Yes, it's fun.
We are a great team.
What do you think?
Are you going to flip?
- What do you mean?
The last time I kissed you,
You freaked out. That was pretty sad.
What is your real name?
- Alexis Black, No. 3 in banks.
That's so...