- Hey, sweetie.
- Hey, Dad.
I hit the Internet cafe.
You know how many e-mails
I had in my box?
Eighty-three.
- Oh, you're a popular guy.
- Very.
Of course, 60 of them were ads
trying to get me to buy something.
Sarah, did you leave
these tools on the ground?
I might have.
Let's get them in the bag
and bring them in the house, please.
We don't want it to rain on them.
Oh, I checked your Facebook page.
What's-his-name
wrote on your wall again.
God, I should
never have added you.
Yeah, he, um...
...wants to get back together.
Of course he does.
I told you.
Princess, he doesn't deserve you.
There you are.
- And there you are.
- Here I am.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, uh, we have a problem.
- I've barely been gone an hour.
- What now?
You'll see.
- Great. Do I have to?
- Yeah.
Hey, I was looking for you.
Did you go into town?
- Mm-mm.
- I didn't think so.
- Where were you?
- Outside.
Working very hard on the garden.
Oh, we have a garden?
Ahem. I had a headache.
Haven't you heard that one before?
I did!
I know, honey.
You all better now?
Yes. Thank you, Uncle Peter.
So what is this big problem?
All right, all right. This way.
Why can't you just tell me about it?
No, this is something
you have to see.
I'll give you a hint. It's in here.
Funny.
What do you think?
How are you supposed
to tell anything from that?
What, you need binoculars,
old man?
Just get your face up there.
Look in there.
Okay. Oh.
That's really... Is this necessary?
I made a hole! What are you...?
Are you impressed with your dad?
I'm impressed with your dad.
Now that, little brother,
is a hole.
Nicely done.
That is not good.
No, not good.
- What is it?
- Oh, it's mould.
Honey, you know what? I want you
to stand back. This is really bad.
I don't want you breathing it in.
It can make you really sick.
Just looking at it
is making me sick.
This whole house could be infected,
for all we know.
Affected, not infected.
Affected, infected, whatever.
Well, if you cover it up,
who'll ever know, right?
That's true.
Just a minute ago,
we had a tiny hole to deal with.
Now we have a big hole.
Well, the insurance'll cover it.
It's obviously part of the leak.
Did you remember to bring the, um...?
- Boom!
- Ah, great minds think alike.
So... what do you want to do?
Why are you asking me?
We're outta here in a few days.
Oh, okay. See here,
this is where it gets tricky.
You're gonna dump
this whole thing on me.
But it comes with the perk
of you not being here.
So dare I complain?
It's what you do best.
All right, I'll deal with it.
Just don't give me shit later
when you find out how.
Well, if you do it right the first time,
I won't have to.
Have you checked the wall
all the way down to the basement?
I just figured out
that it got down here.
Okay, come on.
Bring the work light, please.
Have fun.
Uncle Peter, don't do that!
Come on. You used to love that
when you were a little girl.
Any day now!
I'm coming!
How are you, Sarah?
- I'm okay.
- Yeah?
Yeah. How are you?
Look at you.
I can't get over
how grown up you are.
You gonna come down here,
or what?
Bite me! See you later.
- Sarah?
- Yeah.
Wow, I can't believe you're here!
You don't remember me, do you?
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm Sophia. We used to play together.
Oh, of course. Yeah.
How are you?
I'm quite good, actually,
especially now that I'm finding you here.
Why is it so dark in here?
The power's out.
My dad thinks rats
chewed through the wires.
I'd invite you in, but there's...
really no place to hang or anything.
- That's okay.
- I can't stay long anyways.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
How long's it been
since you were out here?
A long time, years.
Yeah. I come by once in a while,
and I've seen other people here,
but never you.
Yeah, other family
come out now and then,
but no one's really been here
this last summer.
Well, except for the people
who keep breaking in
and messing the place up.
- That's terrible.
- Yeah.
Well, they broke almost all our windows.
My uncle had to call the police
to run them off and...
So what are you doing here now?
Fixing it up. We're gonna sell it.
That's too bad.
And aside from selling this house,
what are you up to?
Nothing much.
Are you in school or something?
No, me and school
don't really go together.
But I'm working for my dad
and thinking about doing something else.
Yeah, it's tough
getting any kind of job these days.
There's so many things I want to do,
but I never seem
to be able to do any of them.
Can you believe how long it's been?
Remember when we used to play dress-up
and do makeovers?
- Did we?
- Yeah.
Oh, my God.
It's been so long,
I swear, sometimes,
I think I have holes up here.
- I have a pile of photos around somewhere.
- I'll have to find them.
Yeah.
You always had the best hair.
So how long are you around for?
We've already been here a couple days,
and my dad thinks
we're gonna head out soon.
Really?
Well, you maybe wanna hang out later?
Yeah, that could be good.
Oh, the phone lines
aren't set up, though,
and our cells don't work up here.
It's okay, I'll just come by later.
Okay.
I didn't know if I'd ever see you again.
It's so good to see you.
Yeah, it's good to see you, too.
I'll see you later.
You know, I do remember you.
How could you forget?
See you later.
John, if you care so much
about the way it's done,
you can do it yourself, okay?
Just do it yourself.
Just trying to be helpful.
You're an asshole.
- What? What'd I do now?
- Sorry. I gotta get outta here, Sarah.
Whoops.
Can I have the keys to my car, please?
Uh...
- You know where they are.
- Give me the keys.
When you're done
with your temper tantrums,
see if you can get the electrician
on the phone, please.
That would be awesome,
if he could come out here.
We could use his needle-nose pliers
to get that stick out of your ass.
- What was that?
- I love you, brother.
I don't know why my brother always
has to make everything so difficult.
Yeah, when he doesn't do
what you want him to.
Exactly. You see,
if everyone would just do what I say,
we wouldn't have any problems,
would we?
Uh-huh.
- Do you need any help down there?
- No, it's okay.
Okay.
Hey. What are you doing?
I just thought I heard something upstairs.
It's probably the damn rats.
God, don't remind me.
No, it sounded like someone was up there.
Maybe it's your uncle.
No, his car's not here.
I know how you think, sweetie.
Would you like me to go upstairs
and have a look?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Wait! I'm gonna come with you.
Jesus!
I get you?
- Yeah, you did and that hurt.
- I'm sorry.
What, you're trying to be funny?
A little bit.
- What's that?
- Uh, it's just...
It's just nothing.
It's photographs for the insurance.
I don't know why your uncle
just leaves things laying around like this.
Ridiculous.
Sorry.
Honey, you're gonna really have to start
making some progress in this room.
You haven't even started on this closet.
Most of it isn't mine.
So, what, it's just gonna stay here?
What are you doing in here?
I don't know if you got the fact
that we're packing it up to get out?
Yes, I do understand that.
That box is completely empty.
If your cousins don't wanna help out,
just keep what you want,
throw everything else out.
Okay.
- At least that's empty.
- Right, but what about the noise?
- Honey, it's an old house.
- They make noises.
I'm sure it's nothing.
But I'll keep looking around, okay?
Thank you.
I want you to sit down,
go through that stuff,
and start throwing things away.
I wanna come back here
and see full garbage bags.
- All right.
- You hear me?
Yes.
All right. I'll be right back.
Daddy?
Yeah?
What's going on?
Nothing's going on.
What's going on in there?
Are you packing?
Yeah, I'm throwing stuff out.
Good. That's what I wanna hear.
Dad?
Daddy?
Come on, Dad.
Oh, my God.
Daddy, what have they done to you?
Daddy.
Daddy, wake up.
Oh, my God.
Wake up. Wake up!
Oh, my God. You're alive.
You're gonna be okay.
Oh, my God.
Okay, the key. Where's the key?
You're gonna be okay.
I'm gonna come back.
Daddy, hang on.
Okay, I'm gonna go get help.
Sarah, what are you doing out here?
- Why aren't you back at the house?
- Uncle Peter!
Hey. Sarah.
It's okay. Hey, what's going on?
Sarah, tell me what's going on.
They got Daddy!
- Who got...?
- You have blood all over you.
- What is going on, Sarah?
- They fucking killed him!
Sarah, who hurt your dad?
Somebody was back at the house? Who?
There was just a girl.
A girl? I don't see any girl.
Sarah, you gotta tell me what's going on
so I can help you.
What is going on?
Where is your dad?
- He's at...
- He's in the room, on the floor.
- Is he back at the house?
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Hey, where are you going?
- To get your dad.
Are you fucking kidding me?!
Uncle Peter, we need to go get help!
If your dad is hurt,
we need to help him right now.
We don't have any time
to go back into town, Sarah.
No! Please!
Tell me how many people
you saw back at the house.
- I don't know!
- Just give me an idea. One, two, three?
- Tell me what I'm dealing with here.
- There was one man...
- Back at the house? - And then
there was just a girl by the road!
Jesus, goddamn squatters.
Please, stop!
- It's okay, Sarah.
- I'm not gonna let anyone hurt you.
I don't wanna be here!
Sarah, come on, calm down.
God...
Here.
Your wrist is bleeding.
We'll tie this up first.
I got something here. C'mere.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I know that hurts.
All right, just put pressure on that.
Hold on to it.
Sarah, honey, it's gonna be okay.
All right?
Where are you going?
- I'm gonna get your dad.
- Just stay in the car.
- What are you doing?
- I'm getting my gun.
- You can't leave me alone here!
- I'm gonna be right back!
- Just stay in the car, Sarah!
- No!
No!
- Stay in the car and lock the doors.
- Lock it!
All right.
Uncle Peter!
Uncle Peter?
Jesus, Sarah!
What are you doing?
I told you to stay in the car!
- You left the trunk open!
- No, I didn't! I closed the trunk!
Someone got in the car!
What?
- You can't open it.
- I locked him out.
No!
- Do you have my key?
- Yeah, I'm not giving it-
- Give me the key, Sarah!
- I'm not gonna give it to you!
Please don't! I don't want to!
- I don't wanna go out there.
- Okay. Okay...
Okay...
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about before. I didn't know.
You all right? You sure?
Yeah.
Can you show me exactly
where you last saw your father?
I looked around,
but I didn't see anybody.
I looked quick, but...
Here, take this.
- How's your wrist?
- It's okay.
All right, we're sticking together now.
- What if he gets in the basement?
- Forget about it.
We're gonna get your dad,
we're gonna get outta here.
Get right behind me. C'mon.
C'mon.
John?
He wasn't in that room.
Where was he?
He was... in there.
Okay.
Let's look again.
He was right here.
Oh, Jesus.
Sarah, how was your father
when you last left him?
Could he have gotten up?
Could he have moved somewhere?
I can't... see how.
Okay, well, maybe he...
Maybe he came to.
Uncle Peter?
Over here.
I don't think there's anybody
on this floor.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
What? What is that?
Uh, it's...
It's garbage. Here.
Gotta get this outta here.
Did you check upstairs?
Quickly. Let's...
Let's look again.
Wait! Stay close to me.
Give me your hand.
It's okay.
What?
That wasn't on before.
They took him.
I'm sorry, Sarah,
we looked everywhere.
Uncle Peter.
Uncle Peter...
Uncle Peter!
That's good. That's right.
Just like that.
Good. It's okay.
Yeah. It's just a little game
we're playing.
Nice.
Don't be shy.
Hmm.
That wasn't so bad.
Hmm? Was it?
How about a little snack now?
No!
There you are.
Sophia. What are you...?
Thought we had a date, didn't we?
Are you looking for this?
That's not the key to this door.
That's not the way out.
Daddy? Daddy?
What did you do to him?!
Not nearly enough.
Daddy want his favourite drink?
No? I think he's gonna need it.
- Who are you?
- Why are you doing this to us?
You have trouble remembering, Sarah.
You have holes up here.
You have the key.
Did I...?
No...
- Finish what you started.
- No.
- Leave us alone!
- Ah!
Stop punishing yourself, Sarah.
- Sarah, plea...
- Shhh...
You have to be quiet,
or you're gonna wake up Mommy.
And then I'll have to punish you.
So you want to play with me now?
- Honey...
- Shhh!
- Why are you making such a big deal?
- It's just a game. Don't be such a baby.
Don't... Don't...
Please stop! Please stop!
Ow, Daddy, it hurts.
It hurts.
Daddy would never hurt you.
Liar!
Look. Look at what you did.
Look at what you did to me!
How could you?!
Look at what you did.
Sarah... honey...
you're seeing things...
...people that aren't there.
You're making things up that didn't happen.
But we can get through this, baby.
You're gonna have to do what I say.
Okay?
I can help you,
but you're gonna have to untie me first.
Sweetie...
Honey?
It's okay. It's okay.
Come on. That's right.
Just take it easy.
Oh, God. Thank you.
Now just give these to me.
All right. All right.
Okay.
Honey, it's all right.
It's okay. It's okay.
All right. You okay?
No, Daddy! Ow!
- You're making me do this, Sarah.
- No!
John...
Just leave her alone.
Leave her alone?
Just shut up, Peter.
Shut up and enjoy the show, huh?
Just like you always did. Huh?
- Right, Sarah?
- Let her go!
"Let her go. " What is this, a joke?
Ah! Ah!
You're such a loser.
Pretending to be dead.
And then you attack me?
This'll be our special little secret.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, Sarah. Please.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
It was so long ago.
I should've stopped it,
I should've stopped him.