I married Mickey Holler
when I was 15.
He was 20 years old, Mickey...
real name, Mervin.
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Are you happy, baby?
Oh, sure I am, Mickey.
Welcome to the family, pumpkin.
Mm.
It sure is gonna be nice
having you around
with my knuckleheaded
nephew here.
- You did good, bub.
- Yeah.
If your mama were alive today,
she'd be proud of you, too.
Congratulations.
I sincerely hope it works out
for the both of y'all.
Thank you!
Yeah!
Hold on. Don't fall, baby.
Get on my back.
I came from a series
of foster homes,
where my so-called "daddies"
would end up fooling with me.
Here we go!
My foster moms would beat me
for no reason...
and every reason...
so I married Mickey.
I'll see you later, Uncle Phil.
Thanks, Aunt Kay.
Bye.
Mickey seemed
like a dream come true.
All I ever had to do
was say what I wanted,
like go to a movie
or get a grilled-cheese sandwich
with a chocolate shake,
and it became
his whole purpose in life.
Uncle Phil's gonna give me
some more routes soon.
I was thinking that, you know,
when you finish schooI
and we save up some money,
in a few years,
we should start to think
about getting a place of our own.
In a few years?
Well, yeah.
I mean, Uncle Phil and Aunt Kay
don't mind.
I mean, you are family now.
Well, I know.
It was just...
I was kind of hoping
we could get our own place,
like, in a few months.
Well, hey, my baby
wants a place of her own,
my baby's gonna get
a place of her own...
in a few months.
Really, Mickey?
Yes, Ma'am!
You don't gotta worry
about nothin' no more.
He loved me...
and that was a plus.
Even if he didn't know
much about it.
# I was a wild-eyed, skirt-chasin' #
# Love-takin' troublemaker #
# Built Ford tough,
every square inch a hell-raiser #
# The bar-room king of this town #
# And then... #
# Baby, babe #
Hey, hey, everybody!
# Here comes the bride #
# All dressed in white #
Mm.
Ain't she just the prettiest thing
you ever seen?
My, my.
Mickey Holler, I think you've got
horseshoes up your ass.
That's for sure.
I'm the luckiest guy alive.
I'll say.
Excuse us.
Mick, I hate to break this to you,
knowing it's your weddin' day
and all,
but we're a little shorthanded
tomorrow.
I'm gonna have to have you
fill in for Leroy.
- What?
- Yeah. His mama died.
Tomorrow?! Well, shit!
Hey, you're a married man now.
You have a wife to support.
I know, but, Uncle Phil, come on!
- Are you a man?
- I...
Mick, are you a man,
or are you a mouse?
I... uh...
Mick.
Philip!
Yes, dear?
Burgers... they're on fire.
Oh, shit.
Well...
This will be your new home...
for now.
Mm.
There's spare sheets and blankets
in the closet.
Towels are in the bathroom
under the sink.
Thank you, Ma'am.
Do you know how to cook?
Oh, of course, Aunt Kay.
I'm not your aunt, Jolene.
Please, call me by my name... Kay.
Of course, Kay.
Mickey, I don't think
your aunt likes me.
Hey! How can you say that?
Uncle PhiI and Aunt Kay,
they think you're real special.
And you're my wife, for chrissakes!
Hold on!
Give your husband a kiss good-bye.
Now go learn something for me...
...and teach it to me later.
Okay.
So, what do you think?
I don't like it.
It doesn't seem real.
Then try drawing
what you've seen or experienced.
Most of the things I've seen,
I'd never want to draw.
Then draw the rest.
Okay. I'll try.
You have talent, Jolene.
It'll come to you, if you let it.
Great meal, Jolene.
Yes sirree.
Ain't she a peach?
What is that special sauce on top?
Well, whatever it is,
it sure is gourmet-like.
Where did you learn how to cook?
I taught myself.
Well, you don't need to learn
anything more about meatloaf, sugar.
It's gourmet-like.
Thanks, but I got to save
some room for dessert.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I- I didn't make any dessert.
That meatloaf was so sweet-tasting,
it was like having dessert
and dinner all rolled into one.
Maybe you could think
about making a-a salad
or a vegetable next time.
Well, if you're still hungry,
Aunt Kay,
we can run out
and get you some ice cream.
No, thank you, Mickey.
I'm full.
Anyway, don't forget
to clean up, okay?
Oh. If you want, Kay,
I can make you a sandwich.
Oh, my.
Maybe she should do
her own damn cooking.
It wasn't that bad, was it?
Oh, God, no, baby.
It was great.
You almost done with that?
Yeah.
I'm tired.
Good.
I got somethin' for you.
Go ahead. Open it.
My birthday isn't till tomorrow.
I know, but... this is for tonight.
Gee...
Mickey, it's so nice!
I picked it out myself.
Aren't you gonna try it on?
The ladies at the store were
asking me all sorts of questions
about your sizes and everything.
And I just hope that I got it right.
I got it from Berman's
if you want to return it.
No, I like it!
Thanks, Mickey.
I'm sure I'll grow into it.
You look good, baby.
Real sexy.
Come here.
Oh.
I wish my ma could have met you.
She'd love you just the same as me.
Mick?
Yeah?
How'd she die?
I don't want to talk about that
right now.
But I'm your wife.
We ought to be able
to share everything.
I know. We ought to.
I just don't want to talk
about it right now.
Okay.
What's the matter, Mickey?
I'm just so lucky I found you.
Happy birthday.
I'm sorry.
I love my present, Mickey.
Thank you.
Jolene?
Shh.
Here.
He had no ambition.
He no longer talked about
getting a little place of our own
or moving toward anything
that would make things different
for us than they were then.
He was a day-to-day person.
Wakey, wakey!
# Tonight's the night
I've been waiting for #
# Because you're not a baby #
# Anymore #
# You've turned into
the prettiest girI I've ever seen #
# Happy birthday, sweet 16 #
# Happy birthday, sweet Jolene #
Mm.
Get your skinny ass out of bed, boy!
"Boy"? Don't be callin' me that,
old man!
Hey, hey, hey.
Why do you gotta get
all sensitive about it?
I don't want you callin' me that
in front of my wife.
Huh? What?
I hate to break up
the happy little party here,
but, um, the kitchen floor
is an absolute mess,
and, well, being as you cooked
last night, Jolene,
do you think you could possibly
manage to clean it up?
Sure, Kay.
I ain't got nothin' better to do.
Oh, and, by the way, happy birthday.
Uncle PhiI was always
tryin' to show off around me,
and he gave me great big hugs...
that lasted way too long.
# Oh, everybody #
# Get on the floor #
# Let's dance #
# Don't fight your feelings #
# Give yourself a chance #
# Shake, shake, shake #
# Shake your booty #
# Oh, shake, shake, shake #
# Shake, shake, shake #
# Shake your booty #
# Oh, you can #
# You can do it #
# Very well #
# You're the best in the world #
# I can tell #
# Oh, shake, shake, shake #
# Shake, shake, shake #
# Shake your booty #
Happy birthday, pumpkin.
# Oh, shake, shake, shake #
# Shake, shake, shake #
# Shake your booty #
# Oh, oh, yeah #
# Shake, shake #
In my whole life,
I'd never been to where
I couldn't wait to see someone.
I tried to contain myself,
but I couldn't.
I don't know.
It was just that way with PhiI.
It was so intense and constant,
so ever-present and undeniable
that PhiI was no longer laughing.
It was every day now,
and always between the hours
of when Aunt Kay left for the bank
and when Mickey
would drive her home.
Poor Mickey.
I just felt so sorry for him.
I could keeI over right now
and be perfectly fine with that.
Hey, I wouldn't be fine with that.
I think this must be one of the most
beautifuI places in the world.
See that ridge over there?
We could build a house up there.
Just you and me, pumpkin.
Look out over the valley every day,
and as long as you were there,
it would be the most beautiful place
in the world.
Kiss me, baby.
Let's make it real.
Stop it, Phil.
It hurts too bad.
What hurts, angel?
Look at me.
I'm looking.
Can't you understand
I'll wait for you, Phil?
However long it takes.
Even till after Kay dies.
That's how much I care.
I love every little inch of you,
Jolene,
and I'm not gonna give you up
for anything or anyone.
But we got to be sensitive
and careful.
I can be sensitive and careful.
We got to think
about Mickey and Kay.
We don't got to think
about anything right now.
Do you hear something?
It's probably just the TV.
No, I hear something.
It's something
that's very, very important.
We have, back again,
a blood-pressure monitor!
Okay, here it is.
Information not...
Oh! Kay!
You little whore!
You little bitch! Damn you!
You heinous little bitch!
The next time you want
to ruin someone's life,
make it your own!
Aah!
How could you hurt Mickey?!
No, no, no.
Hey! Hey! Put that down!
Put that down!
Mickey, I'm so sorry.
No, Mickey, please.
Mickey!
I didn't mean to hurt you!
Mickey, no!
Well, it's your damn fault!
Mickey!
Ohh!
When they told me
about Mickey, I cried for days.
I'm gonna give you a mild sedative
so you can sleep tonight.
You're just gonna feel
a little pinch.
Aah.
Now, why don't you go ahead
and lie back on down?
Come on.
Protective services want to see you
in the morning.
They want to talk to you
about what happened.
But it was an accident.
I told you.
I know, honey.
Try to get some sleep.
They put me in a moteI
by the interstate
untiI they could figure out
what to do with me.
They called me a home-wrecker,
but also a widow,
but also a juvenile delinquent
with no living relatives.
I guess everything they said
about me was true.
They sent a psychiatrist that worked
for the county to interview me.
Tell me your feelings about Mickey.
He loved me.
Nobody ever did before.
Did you love Mickey?
I miss him.
And Philip?
It was the double cross of all time.
He recommended I be sent
to the juvenile loony bin
until such time I was to become
a reasonable adult.
I had told my story in all honesty,
and for that I was sent away...
...to be punished for it.
My name is Mrs. Ames,
and I'm the head nurse here
at South Sumter.
And this is Cindy.
She's your attendant.
She'll be looking after you,
along with all the other girls
in your ward.
I'm here every day except Friday.
Follow the rules,
and we will get along just great.
Do you have any questions for us?
C- could I have some paper
and some colored pencils
to draw with?
Unfortunately, pens and pencils
are not allowed in our facility.
But maybe we can get you
some Crayolas.
Would that do?
Yes, Ma'am.
Do you have anything to add?
Just the pills.
Here you go.
Take these.
But I'm not sick.
Don't worry.
Everybody here takes 'em.
Come on.
Good girl.
After a few days,
I learned that this was no place
to get back your wits,
even if you never lost them
in the first place.
Your Honor...
About two months later,
I was called upon to prove
to the judge I was 16...
However, we do reserve the right...
...which made Phil
a statutory rapist.
Thank you.
Very well.
The witness is excused.
At first...
...I didn't know
what was different about him
until I realized
that his hair was gray.
Phil.
He must have been dying it
all this time.
Hey, Red.
Here.
I can't imagine you mixed up
with that creep.
He ought to be taken out
and hung up by his balls.
Fuckin' child molester.
No, it was my fault.
Now, that's a load of crap.
You know, in my opinion,
all men are pigs.
Hey.
Practice with these.
Come on, take 'em.
Now, just don't tell the doc, okay?
Now, Red,
don't let anything they said
about you back there bother you.
Okay?
You're just a pretty girI
that got taken advantage of.
I don't belong here, Cindy.
Oh, I know you don't,
but it's just how the system works.
It's killing me.
Well, you just do your time,
and before you know it,
you'll be starting all over again.
Come on. Let's get you to bed.
Kill the lights in five minutes.
I heard that Phil
got sentenced
to 18 months in state prison.
I really couldn't care less,
being in one of my own.
Fuck! Aah!
Hey!
We got a bleeder!
No! Let me die!
Let me die!
We got a bleeder here!
We got a bleeder!
Let me die!
Let me die! Damn it!
Hey. Pill time!
I'm gonna take a break.
You want to go for a smoke?
Won't I get in trouble?
Hey, you're with me.
Oh, of course.
Hey, Red.
Geez, this is good!
I wish I had me some watercolors.
Let's go.
Just a sec.
Isn't it amazing
how you can still find beauty
no matter where you are?
Mm.
I don't know if I ever told you,
but I'm pretty good
with hair and make-up.
I've even been called
an artist before.
I mean, not in the same way
as you, but...
I bet I could make you
look reaI pretty.
I mean, prettier
than you already are.
Now, what I would never do
is cover up those freckles.
They give your skin
little dots of sunlight.
You know, some people call them
little kisses from God.
But, you know, if you keep pulling
your hair back in a ponytaiI,
it's gonna recede.
You might go bald.
But what I would do
is cut it a little shorter
so it'll frame your face just right,
and you'll be just as pretty
as one of your pictures.
Sorry.
It wasn't too bad
being loved by a woman.
Once you get going,
it doesn't matter who it is
and what they've got.
All you have to do
is close your eyes.
I think you might need these.
Thank you, Ms. Ames.
You have Cindy to thank.
She told me about your drawings.
It's good therapy.
Keep it up.
Nice to have an artist in residence.
I'll pay you a dollar
if you paint my picture.
If they didn't have a mirror,
they had me.
Some of the likenesses
weren't very good,
but since in most cases
they were better than the originals,
nobody much minded.
Shh!
Aah.
I'm gonna lose my job
if you keep this up.
Shh!
Ohh.
Mm.
Oh, I want it to be like this
all the time, don't you?
Mm.
You're damn straight I do.
Then get me out of here, Cindy.
You know, I've been thinkin'...
I might have a plan.
But you just have to
promise me something.
You gotta live with me
and stay with me forever...
don't ever leave... never ever.
I mean it.
I'll never leave you, Cindy.
You promise?
I swear.
Oh, shit.
Good night, Dan.
Good night, Cindy.
Goddamn it, Red.
You look beautiful.
Wow!
I look like somebody else.
You are somebody else, baby.
You're my woman now.
Don't you ever forget it.
Oh, shit, I gotta go!
Oh, they're gonna know
you're missing by now.
They're gonna be asking
so many questions.
Well, what time do you think
you'll be back?
Soon, honey, soon.
I got the next two days off.
We'll spend it in bed!
Can we go to the beach? Please?
No!
We gotta lay low
till this whole thing blows over.
Jesus Christ.
I don't want you
looking out that window.
You got me?
Okay.
I'll just watch TV or something.
That's a good idea.
Listen, honey.
In another year you're gonna be 18.
They won't be able to touch us then.
Just don't worry
about anything, okay?
I'm gonna take care of you
from here on out.
You always have.
I love you.
Mm. Oh.
Lock the door.
I didn't mean to,
but I'm sure I hurt Cindy reaI bad.
I had saved almost $100
from my watercolors,
just enough money
to get me out of the town,
out of the county,
and out of the state
of South Carolina forever!
For the first time in my life,
I was really free.
# Jolene, Jolene #
I had all kinds of jobs.
There was always a YWCA,
where I could stay out of trouble,
and out of sight.
Hop in, darlin'.
Get your pretty little butt up here.
But I did have to take
a deep breath on occasion
and sell it once or twice
across the country.
# When you dance on that... #
I was just 17,
but I carried myself
like I was 10 years older.
# I wonder, do you know #
# How many hearts
you're gonna break #
Yeah!
Ahh!
# Jolene, Jolene #
# Yeah, you strut
just like a queen #
# You make all the boys
jump and shout #
# Jolene, Jolene, yeah, yeah #
# If you want to be happy
for the rest of your life #
# Never make a pretty woman
your wife #
# So from my personaI
point of view... #
All right. Y'all got
two queenie burgers,
fries, and a royal shake.
$8.17, please.
Keep the change.
Hey, thanks!
# So from my personaI
point of view #
# Get an ugly girI to marry you #
# A pretty woman makes
her husband look small #
# And very often
causes his downfall #
# As soon as he marries her,
then she starts #
# To do the things
that will break his heart #
Hey, how come it's only
the guys that tip?
'Cause the girls are jealous of you,
that's why.
# An ugly woman
cooks her meals on time #
# She'll always give you
peace of mind #
# If you want to be happy
for the rest of your life #
# Never make a pretty woman
your wife #
# So from my personaI
point of view #
# Get an ugly girI to marry you #
Oh, that freak is here again.
I can't stand him.
He gives me the creeps.
Oh, come on, Kendra.
He's funny.
Funny?
Funny-looking maybe.
No, I think he's kind of cute.
Ew. Did you ever take a good whiff?
I don't smell the customers, Kendra.
Well, he reeks.
Seems like he eats here every day.
Duh. He's not here
for the food, Jolene.
He's got a crush on you.
He does not.
It's so obvious.
Why do you think
he's always asking for you?
I don't know.
Because I'm a kick-ass waitress?
Don't worry.
I'Il take his order.
What can I get you?
You can get me Jolene.
I want her to wait on me.
She's busy with other customers.
Doesn't look too busy to me.
I can wait.
# Never make a pretty woman
your wife #
# So from my personaI
point of view #
# Get an ugly girI to marry you #
Just tell her I wrote her a song.
# Never make a pretty woman
your wife #
# So from my personaI
point of view #
# Get an ugly girI to marry you #
# If you want to be happy
for the rest of your life #
He wants you to take his order.
He said he wrote a song for you
or something like that.
I can barely understand
a word he says.
He wrote a song for me?
He's a loser. I bet he deals.
Oh, I don't think he's that bad.
Fine. You take care of him, then.
I was only trying to help you out.
I can take care of myself.
Nice to see you again.
You sure must like this place.
Where else in Phoenix
can I get service like this...
from someone so charmin'?
I'd like to formally introduce myself.
I'm Coco Leger.
Originally from New Orleans.
I'm Jolene.
It says so right there
on your name tag. You mind?
"Jolene. "
# When I wake up in the mornin' #
# And I drive out to see Jolene #
# But my tongue gets tied
around a chili dog #
# She's my desert queen #
# She skates over to my window #
# A sweeter rack I've never seen #
# So you better not complain, girI #
# That I love you, Jole-e-e-ene! #
Thank you.
I got to get back to work now.
You want to take a ride
in my Deuce Corona later?
Maybe some other time.
You wanna go dancin' with me
on Saturday night?
# Whoo! #
# Super highways #
# Coast to coast #
# Easy to get anywhere #
# On the transcontinental #
# Overload #
# Just slide behind the wheel #
# How does it feel? #
# When there's no destination #
# That's too far #
# And somewhere on the way,
you might find out who you are #
# Whoo! #
# Living in America #
# Oh! #
# Eye to eye #
# Station to station #
# Living in America #
He was no rock star,
but he was a gentleman
and a good dancer,
and he didn't mind
making a fooI of himself.
I kind of liked that.
# I feeI good! #
But mostly...
...he made me laugh.
And I hadn't had a reason to laugh
in a long time.
Well, this is it.
This is who I am.
You own this place?
Whose name do you see up there
in the lights?
Wow!
Started it up with a grand
and a prayer.
That is so cool.
Are these your designs?
Art don't belong to anybody.
We are merely the fortunate vessels
that channel it.
You know...
...I draw.
Oh, yeah?
I've been told I'm pretty good.
Oh, I bet you have, darlin'.
Here, take a bang.
No.
See? It's a little like
paintin' with a needle.
Intense...
and complicated.
And that's why I call it an institute.
Come on, give it a try.
It ain't gonna hurt ya.
Let's get institutionalized.
I just love art.
Any kind.
I especially like
doing portraits, but...
Oh.
Say "ah. "
Ahhhh.
Be my apprentice.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I'm serious.
I just fired the chick
who worked for me.
She had a face
like a smacked ass.
You can start with stock tattoos.
Time will tell whether you truly are
also a fortunate vesseI.
I'm a fast learner.
That's what I'm sayin', babe.
Now, sit tight, and let me show you
what Coco can do when he channels.
Ugh. That is just so gross.
I can't believe you let him
touch you there.
I think it's sexy.
I guess that makes it official.
You're just mad
'cause I'm moving out.
I don't mind you moving out.
I just wish you would've picked
somebody else to move in with.
You've only known him
a couple weeks.
He gave me a job.
I have an artistic job.
You think that little heart
on your ass is artistic?
I knew you wouldn't understand.
He believes in me.
It's an act.
You're gonna get hurt, Jolene.
I see what he sees in you.
Thank you.
But I cannot see
what you see in him.
Coco was right on.
Nice.
Trust, Sid.
All you got to do is have the trust.
I told you she had talent.
Yeah, if she didn't,
I'd kick your ass around the block.
Hey, uh, you hang on to that woman.
All right, man?
She's ripe.
Fuck off.
You did it, baby.
You made Coco proud.
Let's just do it.
Was I wrong here?
No.
It's just that I was
already married once,
and it didn't work out so good.
I mean, it's sweet, Coco.
It's real, real sweet.
But I don't think so.
But you're the one, babe.
Babe, I've heard that before.
Not from me.
No, I'm an orphan in the storm
just like you are.
Now, they didn't much like me
where I came from.
Hell, as I understand it,
neither of us has a past
to write home about.
I think we both know...
there's more to life than...
...that.
What counts is this very moment...
and the future moments.
And all the other moments
is just bullshit.
See what I'm saying?
We artists gotta stick together
if we're gonna survive.
I love you, Jolene.
Please say yes.
I knew nothing
about him...
his past, his family.
I knew nothing.
But when I said the name
"Jolene Leger"
secretly to myself...
I do.
...I thought it had a nice ring to it.
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
# If I give my heart to you #
Whoo! Yeah!
# Are you gonna break it? #
# If I give my hand to you #
# Are you gonna take it? #
# Jolene, my desert queen #
# Gonna take you to heaven
on the love machine #
# Gonna fill your vesseI
with my Coco cream #
# You're the finest piece of ass #
# That I've ever seen #
If you shaved his beard,
scrubbed off the tattoos,
got rid of his boots
with the lifts in them,
and gave him a haircut
and a pair of glasses...
...he would've looked
a lot like Mickey.
That looks mighty fine.
And so does the tattoo.
It better.
Where are you off to?
Just business.
When you coming back?
Where's he going in such a hurry?
I don't know.
He's away in his stupid car
half the time.
What do you think he's doing
in there all this time?
Duh, he's dealing drugs
just like I told you he was.
No, he wouldn't do that to me.
Get real, Jolene.
What else do you think
is going on in there?
I'm gonna find out.
Are you insane?!
Get back in here!
Whoa, whoa! What the hell
are you doin' here?!
Are you out of your fuckin' mind?
You're gonna get yourself killed!
Are you dealing, Coco?
Just calm down, all right?
Just keep it down.
Answer me. I want to know now.
Are you dealing?
Babe...
it's the only way
to keep the shop going.
Dealing, Coco?! Why the hell
do you have to do that?!
You don't question me!
Do you hear me?
I'm doin' the best I can
for the both of us.
Come here.
- No.
- Come here.
No artist in the USA can make it
if he didn't lubricate his vesseI
with a little somethin' on the side.
You're so full of shit.
Oh, come on, baby.
Coco would never do anything
to hurt you.
"Oh, baby," nothing.
You better not hurt me, Coco.
Or I might hurt you back.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for Coco Leger.
Is he here?
No.
Well, do you know
when he'll be back?
Who wants to know?
Mrs. Coco Leger, the wife.
You... you mean ex-wife, right?
He didn't tell you, did he?
Whoa!
Listen, you little slut!
I have spent
every fucking cent I have
tracking down that bastard!
Do not waste my time.
Fucking find him!
I told you, he's not here.
Will you look at this!
Here. Fucking hold him, please.
That son of a bitch.
Uh...
Damn, girI.
Where have you...
Bastard!
...been?
Asshole!
Now, Marin, just be cool.
There's an explanation
for everything.
You got one for me?
Let's see you sweet-talk your way
out of this one, asshole.
Now, Marin, believe it or not,
I am greatly relieved
to see you and, um...
- Coco Jr.
- Mm.
So if you just like to come this way,
we can take a ride.
Are you kidding me?
Just sit tight, Jolene.
I'll be back soon. Hmm?
Step to the right, honey.
Ugh!
You know, I draw!
911. Please state your emergency.
Hello? This is 911.
The weirdest feeling
came over me.
I felt like a child again,
like I was only a pretend adult
and that I was never
Mrs. Coco Leger.
For the first time in a long time,
I wondered who my reaI parents
might have been,
if they were still alive,
and why they bothered
to name me Jolene...
only to leave me
to the authorities to raise.
# Since you've gone #
# I spend each lonely night #
# Dealing out the cards
from left to right #
# And the king of hearts
is there to remind me #
# That I'm all alone,
playing solitaire #
# Love was just another game
for two #
# I see now that's all
it meant to you #
# And my heart got lost
somewhere in the shuffle #
# So I'm all alone
playing solitaire #
# In each romance #
# There's an element of chance #
# A gamble to win or to lose #
# You play to win #
# Then you find
you're playing in a game #
# With no rules #
# Just made for fools #
# Now the joker
has a laugh on me #
# 'Cause I've played my hand
so carelessly #
# And untiI you want to share
that old feeling #
# I'll be dealing time away #
# Dealing time away #
# With solitaire #
SaI, this is Baby.
She's one of our finest dancers.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Hello.
Can I buy you
a glass of champagne?
I'd rather give you a dance.
That's not necessary.
I just want to talk.
Why don't you ask your boss
if you can sit here
and join me for a little while?
Anything for you, Sal.
Thanks. Sit.
I'm Sal Fontaine, and you're... Baby.
Actually, I'm Jolene.
Jolene?
Well, Jolene, I was really taken
by your performance out there.
You're a very gifted dancer.
Did you study somewhere?
No. I just like music.
Well, it certainly shows.
You're stunning.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm trying to decide
if I like "Jolene" better
or "Baby" better... I don't know.
SaI was a gentleman.
He never sat at the stage
to stare at my ass like the others.
He was highly respected
in the community
as the owner of Sal's Line.
He gave people advice
on everything...
like about horses
or like who would be
the next president,
and he was usually right.
That was the kind of solid citizen
Mr. Sal Fontaine was.
You live in a museum, Sal.
This place is incredible.
You know, they have a wonderful
museum right here in town.
I can take you there if you like.
That'd be nice.
All right.
Where'd you get
all these beautiful things?
I have a habit of collecting things.
I can't help it.
When I see something I like,
I buy it.
So, you like art?
Mm, I love it.
I can see.
Oh, my God, it's like Christmas!
It is Christmas, princess.
Come on, let me show you.
Come on.
You must be reaI happy
living up here in your sky palace.
Under the right circumstances,
you can be happy living anywhere.
Come on, I want
to show you something.
Come on.
Give me your coat.
Beautiful, isn't she?
It's my greatest possession.
Hmm.
Reminds me of you.
You did all this for me, didn't you?
All for you, princess.
Who are all these people, Sal?
Oh, relatives, kids.
Do they live here?
No, they all moved away.
Do you ever get to see them?
Not too often.
That was my wife.
She's beautiful.
Thank you. She was.
She died a long time ago.
The pictures are old, like me.
You're not so old.
I'm not so young, either.
I don't think age
makes any difference.
You know what?
I don't think so, either.
Life is about moments.
When you find a good one,
you don't let it go.
Let me ask you a question, Jolene.
What are the odds of you
moving in here with me?
I'd say that'd be
a pretty risky bet, Sal.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Jolene, stop dancing
and move in with me.
Are you serious?
I told you once...
I never say anything I don't mean.
And I never go back on my word.
This is for you.
There's no limit on it.
You could have
your own beauty parlor,
Olympic-sized swimming pool, spa,
maid service every morning.
You could order food 24 hours a day,
whenever you want,
whatever you want.
All you have to do is say yes.
Why me? You could have
anybody you want.
I don't want anybody else.
I want you.
You don't want me. Trust me.
Don't sell yourself short, Jolene.
You deserve the best there is,
even if you don't know it yet.
Let me take care of you,
and in return, I'll have
the pleasure of your company.
And you can walk out that door
any time you want...
no strings.
What do you say? Huh?
Hmm?
Merry Christmas.
He believed, or pretended
to believe, my life story.
Merry Christmas.
The parts that were made up,
as well as the parts that were true.
# Heavenly shades of night
are falling #
# It's twilight time #
# Out of the mist,
your voice is calling #
# 'tis twilight time #
# When purple-colored curtains
mark the end of day #
# I'll hear you, my dear,
at twilight time #
It's so beautiful here.
You should have seen it
30 years ago, princess.
The Sands, The Flamingo.
They were hotels.
That was Vegas.
Not like it is now.
All these hotels...
they're amusement parks.
Back then, everybody
was dressed up...
tuxedos... we'd drink martinis,
share our olives together.
What do you mean?
We would drink our martinis,
and at the end,
we would share our olives.
It was a sign of friendship, respect.
# Here in the afterglow of day #
# We keep our rendezvous
beneath the blue #
# Here in the sweet
and same old way #
# I fall in love again
as I did then #
# Deep in the dark,
your kiss will thrill me #
# Like days of old #
# Lighting the spark of love... #
I would tell him I loved him,
and at the moment I said it, I did.
# Just to be with you #
# Together, at last at twilight time #
# Here in the afterglow of day #
# We keep our rendezvous... #
What's the matter, princess?
Well, I'm just a little nervous
about meeting your friends,
that's all.
Are you kidding? Come on.
They're gonna love you.
Let me tell you something.
Everybody loves you.
# As I did then #
Hey. Frank.
- Sal, good to see you.
- Jimmy.
How you doing?
- This is Jolene.
- Hey, Jolene.
- Nice to meet you.
I guess we're not talking
business tonight.
Come on. You know the routine.
All right?
Hey, Sal, I was just hoping we could
talk about the new accounts.
Can we have a nice night? Huh?
Let's have a nice night.
Sal, with all due respect...
Are you deaf?
Hey, SaI,
Frank has a few propositions
he wants to run by you.
I'm running things
for 25 years one way,
and that's the way it stays.
Hey, all he's asking you
is to keep an open mind.
We don't have to talk about it now.
No, we don't have to talk
about it now...
or ever.
Okay. Whatever you say, Sal.
That's right. Whatever I say.
You having a good time, honey?
Mm-hmm.
Hey.
SaI was usually out
doing business.
He was always stressed.
But he allowed me to do
whatever I wanted.
My life had become
comfortable, secure.
It was like eating cotton candy
all day long.
What's the matter, Sal? You okay?
I love you, princess.
I love you, too.
Come here.
I just want you to know
that you never have to worry
about anything.
You'll always be taken care of...
even after I'm gone.
You're not going anywhere, Sal.
I know, I know, I know.
You're becoming an artist,
princess.
A real artist.
Did you see everybody staring at you
when we came in? Huh?
Yeah.
Are you happy, princess?
You make me happier
than I've ever been.
Good. That's what I want to hear.
Hey, SaI.
Aren't those your friends?
Yeah.
Should we go say hello?
No. Tonight's your night.
I don't care
what New York says.
I told you a thousand times,
this is Vegas.
I do things my way here.
What?
Yeah. Now? All right.
Come on up. Yeah.
You want to do it now?
Let's do it now.
Yeah, okay.
- Jolene.
- Hmm?
Jolene, wake up, baby.
Come on, baby, wake up.
- Ohh.
- Come on.
I want you to wake up.
All right? Wake up.
I want you to get dressed.
I want you to go downstairs
and wait for me, okay?
Why?
Because I've got a meeting
with the guys right now.
- Now?
- Yes, now!
I can't blow them off anymore.
I got to see them.
I'll just have some juice
and go back to...
No! You're not staying in bed.
You're gonna go downstairs,
you're gonna get dressed right now,
and you're gonna wait for me,
all right?
And do not come up here
till I come and get you.
Come on. Come on. Let's go.
Come on. It's all right.
It's gonna be all right.
Go ahead.
Jolene!
Frankie? Jimmy?
Sal?
She's not here!
Check the other room!
Life changes fast.
Lightning strikes,
and in an instant,
everything that was...
is not what is.
And you find yourself
sitting on a rock
at the edge of the desert,
hoping some trucker will come by
and feel sorry for you
before you're found
lying dead there...
...like any other piece of road kill.
Two years later,
I was living in Tulsa.
I waited tables,
shelved library books,
and eventually landed a job
as a receptionist
at a firm that leased
oiI-drilling equipment.
I hadn't been involved
with anyone in a while,
and it was good for me.
I was making it on my own.
Finally, I felt I was right
where I was supposed to be.
Where are you going
in such a hurry?
Oh, I'm sorry, Peggy.
I just got a call for a catering gig,
and I cannot turn it down.
What about happy hour?
I'll be happpier making
a quick hundred bucks.
We'll do it tomorrow?
But I wanted to get wasted tonight.
Be brave. Go solo.
Hey, maybe you'll meet
the man of your dreams.
There we go.
Thank you, dear.
- Hi, Burns.
Oh, hi.
Just when I thought this party
was a totaI bust.
Excuse me?
Well, you're the first person
under 60 I've seen here all night,
and by far the prettiest.
Wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on.
You can go fill your tray now.
Not our pastor.
Asshole.
You're allowed to talk to me,
you know.
We're not supposed to talk
to the guests.
- Thanks, anyway.
- You're welcome.
But I'm actually giving you
permission to talk to me.
I'll keep that in mind.
Oh, oh, you... you don't know.
This is my parents' house.
It's a very nice house.
Bradley, dear, I have been
looking all over for you.
There's a young lady
that your father and I
would like you to meet.
Not now, Mother.
Tell me your name.
- Bradley.
- Mother, I'm busy.
Tell me your name.
Jolene.
Mother, this is Jolene.
Jolene, this is my mother.
Mother, please give Jolene
your permission to talk to me.
My name's Brad. Brad Benton.
I think mother likes you.
Hmm. Just as I thought.
Redheads have
their own special scent.
Kind of like warm milk.
I've never heard that one before.
I really have to go.
She loves me.
Could you sign right here, Jo-o-lene?
Wait. Are you sure?
That's what it says.
Thank you.
Who are they from?
I don't have any idea.
Well, I can tell you.
"May I have the honor
of your company for dinner tonight?
Brad G. Benton, 555-5677."
Oh, my God.
You know Brad Benton?
Do you know who he is?
Mnh-mnh.
Only Brad G. Benton
of Benton International, Inc.?
H- his family owns
this entire building
and about half of Tulsa.
Oh.
That guy.
He's richer than God.
Call him.
Call him now.
I'll call him for you.
Oh-ho. Peg, take a breath.
Are you crazy?
He's a Benton, for God's sake.
Well, then, you go ahead
and go out with him.
Jolene, let me tell you something.
Nobody says "no"
to a Benton around here,
especially if you want
to keep your job.
They wouldn't fire me
for not going out with him.
Uh, bring us a bottle
of your finest Pinot.
Of course, Mr. Benton.
You prefer red, right?
Actually, I like white.
Liar.
What do you think of the club?
It's not my kind of place,
but for what it is, it's nice.
I figured you might be impressed.
I hope you are.
'Cause I'm certainly impressed
with you, Jolene.
Thank you.
I mean, you just...
you just appear into my life,
and... bam... here we are
all dressed up,
discussing our favorite wines.
Speaking of which,
where is that incompetent waiter?
He must be new here.
He doesn't know the score yet.
Did you forget something?
No, sir. I'm sorry.
But we have to go into the cellar
to bring the very finest Pinot noir...
- Uh-huh.
- As you requested.
Don't be smart with me, understood?
Yes, sir. Of course.
- You're new here, right?
- Yes, sir, I am.
Right. What's...
what's your name?
Benjamin, sir.
Benjamin. Benjamin.
Well, Benjamin, it's really nice
to have you waiting on us.
Keep up the great work.
You always this rude?
No. No, I'm not like that.
He deserved it.
I hope I didn't embarrass you,
but, really, he'll be
a much better waiter now.
So, Brad, what exactly is it
you do with your life?
Well, technically, I'm a stockbroker,
but it's just a hobby.
I never have to work
another day in my life.
I make truckloads of money,
get paid ridiculous bonuses
for no other reason than I'm me.
But forget about me.
Let's talk about you.
I feel I must tell you,
you're one of the strangest people
I've ever met.
No, I'm not.
I'm actually really
quite a simple guy.
I hope this isn't inappropriate,
but have you accepted
our Lord Jesus Christ
as your personal savior?
Are you seriously asking me
that question?
Yeah, I'm absolutely serious.
That would be my business, Brad.
Okay.
I'm sure we can figure it out, then.
Oh, listen.
I'm sorry I got a little worked up.
This is our first date,
and I really wanted everything
to be perfect.
Uh, I hope I haven't offended you.
Oh, quite the contrary, sir.
You were right to complain.
The evening's on the house.
Hey, thanks, man.
That's really great.
Write yourself in a big tip, okay?
I think we're having
an absolutely fantastic time,
don't you?
I think you're absolutely crazy.
Which means you probably
really like me a lot.
You're not kidding, are you?
Why don't you figure that out
on our next date?
Wednesday is great for me.
I hope that works for you.
Well, I'm gonna have to get back
to you on that.
I felt blessed the minute I saw you.
You don't know anything
about me, Brad.
But I know when my prayers
have been answered.
At first, I couldn't believe
Brad G. Benton was serious.
On the other hand,
this was the Bible Belt,
and I'd met
some very sincere people.
Though he was a little weird,
Brad was a perfect gentleman.
He was never inappropriate
and always considerate.
After a couple more dates,
I actually started to enjoy
his eccentric personality.
And he was always
going out of his way
to show me that he cared.
Where are you taking me?
What an amazing view.
Tulsa's so beautiful from up here.
About as close to heaven
as you can get
without leaving Oklahoma.
Thank you, Brad.
That's very thoughtful.
You're welcome.
Are you as happy as I am?
Mm-hmm.
I hope you'll remember today forever.
I've got a surprise for you.
What's this?
I don't know. Open it.
It's addressed to you.
I fired you from Benton.
You'll never have to work
another day of your life.
But I like my job, Brad.
You're not seeing
the big picture here.
You can make your paintings,
you can raise our kids.
What's wrong with you?
Why the hell would you fire me?
Jolene, just calm down and listen.
The Lord told me that one day
I would meet the right person
to spend the rest of my life with.
The Lord also tell you to fire me?
I want you to be
the happiest woman on earth.
Will you marry me?
Please say yes.
Uh...
It's not that simple.
You don't know me.
I want to tell you about my life
before I met you.
It's... it's important
you know who I am.
No. What matters is us,
here and now.
I know I love you,
and I want to spend
the rest of my life with you.
But, Brad...
That's all I ever want
or need to know.
I don't care where you've been
or what you've done.
That's the past.
This is our future.
Yeah.
You're skipping a lot of steps here,
like meeting your parents,
moving in together.
Jolene, I am asking you to marry me.
I understand that.
It's very touching.
It's just, I can't say yes
unless I know I mean it.
Of course you need time.
I understand that.
But we can spend
the rest of our lives
getting to know each other.
Why complicate something
as beautiful and simple as our love?
Jolene, we'll be so happy together.
I swear to God.
Uh, this is getting too strange.
Okay, okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
Listen. I'm sorry.
I know. I know.
Guys, stop the music!
Get out of here!
Just go! Leave!
Now!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Listen to me.
It's taken me a while to grow up,
to be ready for something
as special as this.
You are the first woman
I have ever been in love with,
and the first
I've ever asked to marry.
And I know in my heart
that you will grow to love me
as much as I love you.
It's so obvious. It's perfect.
Jolene, I really... I really am
a simple kind of guy.
That's intense.
Don't fight it. It's bigger
than both of us. Marry me.
I can't.
Yes, of course you can.
Together we can do anything.
Brad, I can't marry you.
# Hallelujah #
I now pronounce you man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
# Hallelujah, hallelujah #
# Hallelujah #
Brad, honey,
where are your parents?
Who cares?
The Lord's here.
# Hallelujah, hallelujah #
# Halle-luja-a-a-ah #
No, no, no, no.
Brad, please!
- No, I don't like it there.
- Jolene, shh, shh, shh!
No, I don't like it there.
Aah!
Ew.
Ah, this is so fucking beautiful.
Thank you, Travis.
Who's that?
That is my father.
Your father?
Mm-hmm.
Brad, shouldn't we go over there?
Nah. If he wants to meet you,
he can come here.
But I want to meet your parents.
It's a complicated thing.
Trust me.
They think if they ignore me,
I'll just go away?
No. It's not really
about you so much.
What kind of parents don't show up
for their own son's weddin'?
Proud, inflexible, arrogant ones,
like those two.
But they're not all that bad.
Brad, when we have kids,
I want to love them no matter what.
Oh, we will, honey.
We're gonna have a huge family,
all of our own.
- Brad.
- What?
Are you...?
Mm-hmm.
Really?
Yeah.
Hallelujah!
- I'm gonna be a daddy!
- Oh!
I knew if I wanted
to prove anything to Brad's family,
if I wanted any kind
of social acceptance in Tulsa,
I would have to work for it.
I embraced their style of life,
their manners,
their ways of doing things,
and I was patient,
but always kept
my eyes and ears open.
Excuse me, son.
It's good to see you.
You too, Dad.
Uh, Jolene, honey, this is my father.
It's a pleasure to finally meet you,
Mr. Benton.
It's very nice meeting you.
And I believe
you remember my mother.
It's nice to see you again,
Mrs. Benton.
- So, the baby's due any day now.
- Mm-hmm.
Is it a boy or a girl?
A boy.
- Jolene.
- Hmm?
Wake up.
What?
Brad, are you all right?
You've slept with other men,
haven't you?
What are you talking about?
Why are you asking me this?
It's just something that's
been bothering me a lot lately.
But when we first met,
you said that it didn't matter.
Babe, you were right.
I tried to tell you,
but you wouldn't listen.
Why are you interested
all of a sudden?
Just... just answer the question.
No. Not until you answer mine.
How many?
Are you kidding me?
You want a number?
How many?!
You have no right to ask me that
without an explanation.
There have been that many?
Wow.
Brad, you knew I wasn't a virgin
when we married.
You see, Jolene, it's easy for me.
I can count mine on one hand.
Now, if you had been with one guy
or maybe even two guys,
ah, that's the kind of thing
you wouldn't forget.
But if you'd been with a lot of guys,
then I guess it gets kind of hard
to keep track of that, right?
So, what are you saying,
that five is okay
but six is too many?
How many have there been?
Sweetheart, please,
let's just go back to sleep.
10?
Brad, please.
I never loved anybody more
than the way that I love you.
20, 30, 50?
Hundreds! Thousands!
Do you feel better?!
Never mind that I had tried
to tell Brad about my marriages,
my life on the road...
he never wanted to hear it.
Brad, honey?
I just don't know where all this
is coming from.
I have nothing to hide.
If it's that important to you,
of course...
Ohh!
Dear Lord, please bless our family...
for we have sinned.
I hurt my wife...
because she hurt me.
Sweetheart, I love you more
than anything in the world.
I will never ever do anything
to hurt you ever again.
Lord, please, please forgive us.
It was as if his wildness,
his independence,
his personality was being driven
from the Brad I loved.
For the very first time in my life,
I had something I wanted.
I was Jolene...
his mother.
And I could believe in God now.
What shall we eat?
I know.
It was those parents of his
gradually absorbing him
back into their righteousness.
Jolene, can you feed him
in the nursery
or let him go to the nurse?
- How am I supposed to eat?
- Brad, he was hungry.
- I'm trying to get him to go to sleep.
- Where the hell is Rosie?
- We gave her the day off.
- Well, let's get her back.
We need her to take care
of junior today.
Grandpa and grandma are coming
to see Mr. Nipplebee today.
You need to make yourself
presentable.
What, they're coming today?!
For lunch.
And to see the Bradley.
Brad! Why didn't you tell me?
This place has to be cleaned!
They just called.
What was I supposed to say,
that we weren't here?
Look, I can't see them today.
I've got too much to do.
That's okay. They probably don't want
to deaI with you anyway.
That's the truth, isn't it?
Of course it is.
Don't act so surprised.
Jolene, save the drama
for another day.
You fucking whore!
Brad! No!
Oh, my God!
Mrs. Benton! Oh, my...!
Oh, God, what did he do to you?!
Oh!
Mrs. Benton, are you okay?
Aw. Shh.
The nurse at the hospitaI
didn't need to ask how it happened.
Shh. Come on.
She wrote out the name and address
of a women's shelter,
and the shelter gave me
the name of a lawyer.
He's a dangerous man.
I can't have him in my life.
I don't care about the money.
I just want out.
I'm afraid I'm...
not going to be able to help you,
Mrs. Benton.
What do you mean?
I mean I can't take your case.
Why?
Did his family threaten you
or just buy you off?
This has nothing to do
with the Benton family.
He beat me. It's simple.
I'm afraid it's not that simple.
You didn't tell me you had a past,
including a stretch
in juvenile detention.
That was a long time ago.
To say nothing of a previous
as yet un-annulled marriage
to a convicted drug dealer.
You entered into your marriage
with Mr. Benton
under less than honest
circumstances.
I'm very sorry.
No one at this firm
will take your case.
Oh, my darlin'.
Uh, Mrs. Benton.
There's some people here
to see you!
Come on. Come on.
Oh! Look at you. Yes.
What? No, where are you going?
Wait! Stop!
You... you are under arrest
for the kidnapping
of Bradley Benton junior!
- No! No! No!
- Come quietly.
Come on, lady, move.
No!
I know that you feel
like you've been wronged, but...
Wronged? They took my child.
Unfortunately, Mrs. Benton,
they have a really solid case.
I mean, the law clearly states...
Fuck the law!
No one's taking my child!
Do you understand that?
Mrs. Benton, I'm gonna work
really hard on your case.
I promise.
The legaI aid guy
was way out of his league,
and, without giving it
a second thought,
the judge ruled
that I was an unfit mother
and granted Brad sole custody
of my little boy.
I mean, you do have
a checkered past.
I had choices.
I think you should hope
for the best, but...
I could kill Brad G. Benton,
but then my child would be raised
by the Benton family.
I could find a job
and see my baby
every second Sunday for one hour,
as allowed by the judge,
and find the right moment
to steaI him back.
Or I could let him grow up
thinking I was something other
than an embarrassment,
a poor relation...
...or a victim.
He could daydream
about his real mother...
...living somewhere out there...
...away for a time...
...but never forgotten.
She'd be beautiful...
...smart...
...and more talented
than she could possibly ever be...
But so reaI to my boy...
My baby boy...
My son.
These days, I have a job illustrating
for a small comic-book company.
Except they don't call them
comic books.
They call them graphic novels.
Because most of them
aren't funny at all.
They're very serious.
The guys are gonna flip.
These are wonderful, Jolene!
Someone once told me
to draw what you know best.
Good advice...
I think.
Well, I'm out of here.
Meet you before work tomorrow?
Farmers' market? Usual time?
Sounds great, Maya.
Some ppeopple tell me
that I could act in movies,
because even though I'm 25,
I look a lot younger.
And they like my voice that I have,
courtesy of my ex-husband.
I mean, why not?
Don't they say
if you wish hard enough,
your dreams might come true?
And when I take myself back
to Tulsa in my limousine...
...Brad Junior would be there
to answer the door...
...and there would be
his movie-star mother.
# Jolene, Jolene #
# When you dance on that stage #
# I wonder, do you know #
# How many hearts
you're gonna break #
# Jolene, Jolene #
# Yeah, you strut just like a queen #
# You make all the boys
jump and shout #
# Jolene, Jolene #
# If I give my heart to you #
# Are you gonna break it? #
# If I give my hand to you #
# Are you gonna take it? #
# If I give my life to you #
# Are you gonna take it #
# And break it
into a million crystals? #
# Make me desperate for you #
# For you #
# Out of the ashes #
# The phoenix rises #