Some fairy tales are true.
Most other stories we make up
to help us deal with real life.
It all depends
on your point of view.
But here are the facts.
There was once a princess
who lived in a castle
high above the streets
of an enchanted kingdom.
The king and queen
were long gone.
But they left her
with their treasure
so that she could stay
a princess forever.
On the eve
of her 22nd birthday.
A great celebration
was planned.
Molly's machine.
Speak your piece.
Oh. Birthday girl.
Pick up. Pick up. Pick up.
Huey and I
are just sitting here waiting.
- You better be on your way.
- Money down she's still asleep.
Molly. Wake up!
Molly's machine.
Speak your piece.
Hey. Molly. It's Justin here.
Callin' from the studio
to wish you a happy birthday...
Give me five more minutes,
baby, and I'll rock your world.
Love ya!
You can't turn the hallway
into a greenhouse, Miss Gunn.
Good evening, Mr. McConkey.
Please say hello
to your wife for me.
Bye. Have a nice night!
I've alerted the management
company about this.
Oh, my.
I put the flowers upstairs for you,
but this is out of hand.
Got a girl, Tony?
Not one that could fit
into this dental floss.
Be a darling and send all this stuff
to the Salvation Army!
You're the greatest, Tony!
- Molly?
- Hey, Ingrid, it's me.
- Where the hell are you?
- I'm sorry. I passed out.
- I was watching TV.
- That was a premeditated nap.
You did this to me on purpose.
You're my best friend
in the whole universe.
How could you possibly think
a thing like this?
It's like stabbing me in the heart.
Thank you!
Forget it. Okay?
I didn't want to tell you.
But our little night out has grown.
Huey and I are here
with a few of your closest friends
waiting to wish you a...
Happy birthday?
Happy birthday.
I tried calling you from home.
The girly to end all girlies
is in the house.
Happy birthday, Molly.
- We got you, Molly!
- We got you, didn't we?
You did. I thought it was
gonna be just us guys going out.
Hell, no! What kind of friends
you think we are?
Look at this.
This here is a party, right?
You're 22?
I just turned 19
and I thought I'd kill myself.
You look good, though.
Buy you a drink?
No, thanks.
I wanna connect the dots, baby.
Look at the babes, Molly.
They're, like, beautiful
and natural and sexy, right?
Beauty like that is universal.
They really do look young, huh?
The thing I love about women
is that you are willing
to accept each other
for who you are.
There you are, sweetie.
You remember Julie and Holly
from the MOMA Junior Committee?
Happy birthday.
I love your solid hair scrunchy.
- Thanks.
- Issey Miyake?
Home Depot.
You can get Botox injections
for that forehead wrinkle.
Face Factory.
No appointment necessary.
Why would I have
a worry wrinkle?
Why would you think
anyone would care?
Excuse me?
I had shoes like yours once,
when I was five.
That was what,
like three days ago?
Try three years.
Excuse me, Thumbelina,
but you're still a little underage
to be clubbing, aren't you?
You're a little overage to be
wearing a lampshade in your hair.
Bright idea?
You brought your own
personal soap?
You want to pick up
bacterial meningitis or polio,
you go ahead
and be my guest.
Whatever diseases
you're already carrying
probably make those
sound like a joke, anyway.
There you are. I finally found
your little monster butt.
Come here!
I know you have trouble
reading something as simple
as a sign on the door, Gooey Huey,
so let me help you.
This is the ladies' room.
- Really? What's your excuse?
- Give me my purse.
My boss' kid.
They can't keep a nanny.
They fired their
third one this month today.
She had dirty fingernails.
It was her or me.
- That hurts.
- Where's my purse?
In my hand.
- Ing, am I hideous?
- What?
As my best friend,
it is your duty not to lie to me.
Please tell me,
am I turning into a hideous hag?
You can have any guy here
with the snap of a finger.
What's gotten into you?
Oh, my God.
Molly, let me show you something.
Come here.
- Sit down.
- Great. You again.
I want to thank you all
for having me here.
I've heard there's a birthday tonight.
Where's that birthday girl?
All right.
This one's for you.
The lights beam
down from the stars
And it takes my breath away
And the tears of glee
in my heart
End up voicing words to say
All I feel is invested in this...
Oh, my God.
Who is that?
That's my boy Neal Fox.
I found him playing
at a dive in the Village.
He's smokin'.
Can I have him
for my birthday?
No, Molly, I brought him here
so Roma could check him out.
Besides, he's 100% girly free.
He's celibate, like Morrissey.
He's all about the music.
You wouldn't know real music
if Mozart hit you on the head.
Quiet, the both of you.
Quiet? This place is so loud,
it is giving me a migraine.
My call of love
Then she'll rise with love...
Mom!
No, your mom's over there
talkin' to my man Nas.
We been tryin'
to sign him for months.
- Could you please keep it down?
- Mom, I wanna go home now!
- Night, Molls.
- Bye.
- Good night, Molly!
- Bye!
- I finished my new record and...
- That's great, Duncan.
- Nice to see you. Where is he?
...give me your two cents.
Huey said this guy
is practically a monk.
What the hell
are you trying to prove?
The only reason you're looking
at this guy is because you can't have him.
He's a rock 'n' roll
poet sex god.
You'll toss him in a week.
No, Ing, this one's different.
I can feel it.
That was good.
Kid, I haven't heard
blue-eyed soul like that
since Jeff Buckley's record.
See what I'm sayin'?
What did I tell you, Roma?
He's smokin', right?
- You did good, Huey.
- I need eight hours, Mom.
If I don't get eight hours,
my immune system crashes.
Record something more up-tempo
I can get on the radio.
- Let's go.
- Work it out with Huey.
Go...
That's what I'm talkin' about.
She gets it.
I get it.
You don't get it.
- Wait...
- Neal, you need to get it.
I think we got ourselves
a Grammy!
I hate that...
Kids! Always hogging
your attention.
- Hi.
- Hi. Birthday girl.
- Yeah, happy birthday.
- Thank you.
Is this demo thing for real?
She's about to sign you!
I can feel it in my bones.
Rocket to the moon, baby.
Rocket to the moon.
Oh, my.
Are you really
Tommy Gunn's daughter?
Seriously?
Can you hold my purse, please?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Jesus!
I guess there is
a certain family resemblance.
- His guitars are in there?
- You wanna come see?
Yeah.
Can you just wait here
just one second, please?
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Right.
Welcome
to Le Chateau Chez Molly.
Nice.
What on God's earth is that?
- Mu.
- Don't you mean oink?
No, "Mu" means "pork" in Thai.
He was going to be my curry dinner
one night in Bangkok,
but we fell in love.
If you wait here,
I will fix us some
bonbonnieres confiseries.
Oh, my God.
Looks like you found it
on your own.
I can't believe it!
This is it.
This is the acoustic Muddy Waters
gave Tommy Gunn.
- He played it at Budokan.
- Summer of '8.
Daddy's little girl
That's you.
Paints the world
with her magic wand
Please don't sing that song.
"Molly Smiles."
He opened the showwith it.
For me
And then he
and my mom died.
Listen, I didn't mean to...
Okay. Yeah.
So what's next?
How about dessert?
Am I gonna be able
to pronounce it?
I don't know.
Can you say..."Pez"?
I'm just not supposed
to act impulsively, you know?
Part of my whole sobriety thing.
Made a vow,
haven't broken it yet.
Pez.
I haven't had a drink
in 224 days.
I'm also not supposed to have
romantic relationships my first year.
Pez.
It's called
the Law of Contrary Behavior.
If I want a drink,
I don't have one.
If I want to skip a gig,
I force myself to go.
If I meet a girl
and I want her to come over...
...I send her home.
Pez.
Those are vows
I haven't broken.
Ships crossing like ghosts
in the night
Night names,
unremembered faces in sight
Took what we can
in need to survive
Oh, my God, I love it!
It's the most
lyrically advanced thing I've done.
No, purple means
rock 'n' roll royalty,
and it picks up
the highlights in your eyes.
You're too hot for those
earth tones you've been wearing.
What about the song?
Is it too fast, too slow, what?
It's kind of like the same thing
over and over again.
Is there, like, a hook
or a good chorus or something?
- A hook?
- Yeah.
- I don't do hooks.
- Okay.
I'm not a sell-out. I don't
wear purple and I don't do hooks.
I said okay, okay?
Names... names unremembered,
faces in sight
Molly. I thought you were dead.
- Neal's in the other room.
- That guy is still there?
You always do this.
When are you gonna grow up?
He's never going to leave.
All he does is mope
and play these loser songs.
Help me, please.
I don't know how to get rid of this guy
without breaking his heart.
Hold.
Just a minute!
Oh, my God,
I'm being totally suffocated.
Yeah?
Can you take those off?
Ing, I'll call you.
Baby... I'm not a love machine.
No, my boxers...
can I have them back, please?
Thanks.
What's going on?
- Listen, I've got to go.
- Go?
Go where, go?
Home, Molly.
The place where I live,
where I have a life,
where I do my laundry,
get sleep, try to make music.
Why can't you
make music here?
This is a world gone mad,
like I've stepped
through the looking-glass.
There's a week's worth of leftovers,
a month of laundry.
- Look at this place.
- We'll call maid service.
You call maid service.
I've got to rejoin the human race.
No!
I don't understand.
Listen, I just feel
like I'm suffocating.
- I need some air.
- We can open the windows.
It's not about the windows.
I need my shirt back.
Damn! I forgot
to get new strings.
I have, like,
five gigs this week
and I have not done
a single thing.
I have got to get to work.
I'll call you later, I swear.
Oh, my God.
This place is beyond
its normal grotesque.
It's post-nuclear.
Ninety-eight messages?
Molly, your machine
has 98 messages on it.
Write them down for me,
will you?
He's gone.
I have no life.
What?
"Of course you have a life."
"I don't need to tell you that."
That's what you're
supposed to say to me.
Sorry.
As your best friend,
it's my duty not to lie to you.
Besides,
you wanted him gone, remember?
I did?
What are all these
final notices?
I'm gonna call him.
I think now is
a good time to call him.
Would you hand me the phone?
I'm gonna call him right now.
Focus for one second.
Your electric has been canceled
and so has your gas.
Who pays your bills?
Bob.
Bob who?
I don't know.
My parents' guy Bob.
Your phone's dead.
These rooms...
...sound so empty
without the sound of his music.
Bob's number
has been disconnected.
Oh, God.
I'm sure it's little consolation,
but you're not the only one
who got taken, Miss Gunn.
Bob Kopalski had ten clients,
assets equaling over $100 million,
when he disappeared.
You're telling us
that none of it's insured?
What a disaster.
Thank God for the residuals.
Actually, Kopalski took such heavy
advances on the royalty income
that by the time
the account recoups,
Miss Gunn will be
on Social Security.
Where does someone disappear
with $100 million?
The best we can guess
is South America.
Can't you just sue?
My God,
how could he do this to her?
He'll be back.
They always come back.
If he does, he'll be looking
out the back of an FBI van
on his way
to a long prison term.
It'll be years
before you see a dime, if ever.
Mr. Feldman, as a lawyer,
may I please ask your advice
as per what to do in the meantime
as far as, you know, money?
Get a job?
"Dear prospective employer,
"although I've had
no previous employment, ever,
"the following is a partial
but significant list
of personal recommendations,
including contact information."
The Dalai Lama, Tibet?
900-thread count
Egyptian cotton.
No man can resist
Tibet is a country, Molly,
not contact information.
Why not add "earth"
in case someone
needs to know where Tibet is?
This is not a resume.
It shows I'm a people person.
Focus on the interview.
Hello.
Pleasure to meet you.
I will work overtime, weekends,
holidays, Yom Kippur, Christmas.
- You name it, I will be here.
- I'm sure that won't be necessary.
Ingrid says you guys met
at Darlington?
I was valedictorian there
two years in a row.
That's so neat.
Tell me, what is the price
on a set of these?
$1,369 plus tax.
You're in denial.
You're broke, remember?
Trish, hon, tell me, do employees
get a discount around here?
Ten percent, and some employees
are among our best customers.
I'll take them.
Ing, this is the greatest job ever.
- Who is it?
- It's Molly!
I was just out shopping
in the neighborhood.
- At midnight?
- It's the city that never sleeps.
You can't do this.
I have to be at the studio at 9:00.
- I can't act like a kid anymore.
- Really?
Neal, I haven't seen sheets
like this since the third grade.
Rocket ships?
You wouldn't have my jacket in there?
It's like my lucky jacket.
I never get onstage without it.
I left it behind the other day.
No.
I guess you're gonna have to
come over and look for it.
I can't disappear
from the world again.
I can't lose myself in this obsessive-
compulsive irrational behavior.
Feel.
- Excuse me?
- Feel.
Egyptian cotton...
...900-thread count.
All right, I'll tell you what.
Maybe we can, like,
date, okay?
Okay.
But it's gonna have to be
a mature adult relationship with...
- alarm clocks in the morning...
- I love alarm clocks.
...and work during the day.
We eat with silverware,
knives and forks...
...drink out of glasses...
...do the dishes.
Is it bedtime yet?
Molly, wake up.
I'm sorry.
It's not going to work out.
You spent all night at that guy's
house doing God knows what,
then you come here
and crash at work.
I can't believe you did this to me
after all the strings I pulled.
I know that I'm
an undeserving creep,
but can we please
talk about it over lunch?
No! Our lunch date is canceled.
You can't afford lunch.
Fine, see if I care.
I'll live off of water and sunshine.
You won't have to.
Once again your main man
is gonna come through for ya.
You're gonna get me
a record deal.
Not exactly.
- Hi!
- Oh, my God.
You're my new nanny?
- Hi, Laraine.
- It's Ray.
Nobody calls me Laraine.
Okay, Ray, I'm Molly.
We met at my birthday party,
remember?
You're late.
By, like, a second.
By three and a half minutes.
I have to take my Aciphex
by 4:26, and it's... 4:18 right now.
- We'll take it when we get home.
- That's when I take my Colitin.
The agency must really be
getting desperate.
I actually am uniquely qualified
for this position,
having spent so many years
developing my skills
as a people person.
Mission accomplished?
Fruit punch?
Why don't you
just drink cyanide?
At least it's quick.
Damn.
Hang your coat up in there.
What is this, The Shining?
- Who is that?
- Nobody.
- What's wrong with him?
- None of your b-i business.
Shoes!
This is your room?
There's no fooling you,
is there?
It's so...
...orderly.
These are so neat!
I remember when there were
only four models.
I can't believe this.
She's beautiful.
- Look at these legs.
- That's Plieing Polly.
Put her back!
How cool is this?
Look at this little tea set!
You don't touch that unless
I happen to invite you to tea.
Look at these cute little scones.
Get away from there.
Well, I say, Lady Sassafras,
would you like some creme fraiche
to go with
your darling pastries?
You just got your germy drool
over my plastic scone, you freako.
Kid, have you ever been
to a shrink?
Since I was three.
What?
Good afternoon. Miss Ray.
Dinner is ready.
There's just nothing
like good help.
You missed a spot.
Isn't doing the dishes what the maid
is supposed to be for?
She doesn't know how to dry
without leaving spots.
You don't know how to dry
without destroying the environment.
For every roll
of paper towels you waste,
a tree in the rain forest dies.
I'm gonna die of botulism
from the germs on that gunky
towel, you tree-Ioving hippie.
At least I don't prefer tofu
to normal hamburgers.
I'm not the one who's gonna get
mad cow disease and go nuts,
though you don't seem to have
a brain to fry in the first place.
Maybe not, but at least I'm not
holding the germ-infested towel.
Give me that plate.
No, sorry.
You might infect it.
Why don't you get your plastic
baggie and dig up some penicillin?
- No!
- Come on.
- Give me the plate!
- You want it?
How bad do you want it?
Get a broom.
You get a frickin' broom.
When you work for me,
you leave when I say you can leave.
For your information,
I do not work for you.
I am employed by your mother.
Yeah?
Take a look around.
Do you see her anywhere?
News flash... you're not gonna
unless you make an appointment
with her assistant
or hang around her bedroom door
at 3:00 in the morning.
In the meantime,
you're workin' for me.
Is that so?
News flash, Mussolini...
I quit!
Swinging door.
- Are you all right, Miss Gunn?
- Just great.
Baby!
Baby, what are you doing outside
all by yourself?
How did you get locked out?
Mama's had a day.
I've lived here for 20 years.
How can you do this?
Aside from that...
This is a family building,
Miss Gunn.
I suggest you find somewhere
you'd be more welcome.
Like Los Angeles.
You will be allowed back
into your apartment
only so long as you are accompanied
by a management representative
and only long enough
to gather your belongings.
That is, those personal belongings
we don't insist on holding
as collateral for the rent
and utilities you owe.
You are otherwise barred
from the premises.
I know this is
a big change for you,
but it'll feel like home
in no time at all.
This is the bedroom...
my bedroom, of course...
but there's plenty
of drawer space if you need it.
I can't believe those creeps
would throw a destitute woman
into the street.
Chivalry is so dead.
This is the bathroom.
I hung up your towels for you.
I've been here
a thousand times.
You know the kitchen.
Julie and Holly come over
Thursdays for our weekly bake fest.
Mondays, Penny and Ethel come
so we can do yoga with Rajiiv
right here in the living room.
But this is going to be
a problem.
Ing, don't you think it's weird
that Neal hasn't called me?
No, but I think it's weird
that you're wearing his jacket.
I told you just bring
the essentials, Molly.
You can't keep all this stuff.
And he definitely has to go.
Mu, what are we gonna do?
Downsize, Molly.
Purify.
Streamline,
find your center.
You're right, Ing.
We're gonna get you the best
housewarming present ever.
Don't be silly.
It's gonna be hard enough on you
coming up with half the rent.
Wonderful, girls.
Tomorrowwe start rehearsing
for next month's recital,
but I think we still have
five minutes.
How about a little freestyle?
You sure looked great
out there.
I just, you know...
Yelling at you
the other day and all...
I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
I called Roma, your mom...
...and she said that if you said
that it was okay,
I could have my job back?
You're on probation.
Act your age,
not your shoe size.
How come you left
dance class so early?
That freestyle at the end
looked like so much fun.
Freestyle is for moronic little kids
and hippie freaks.
It's fun.
Fundamentals
are the building blocks of fun.
Says who?
Mikhail Baryshnikov,
who I'm sure you've never heard of.
Ballet is about precision,
discipline, and poise.
They made us take ballet
at Darlington.
I couldn't wait to get out there
and make up all my own moves.
Figures.
Such a sloppy doofus.
Figures. You're such
a pill-popping little tyrant.
Don't ever do that
to me again.
- You're hurting me.
- You hurt me.
Take it back.
Fine.
I take it back.
It's a good thing you did.
Otherwise you wouldn't
have gotten your surprise.
Surprise.
I really hate surprises,
and I sincerely doubt
there's anything you could give me
that I don't already have.
There's no harm
in trying, is there?
Ray, are you all right?
My glands are swollen.
I'm having an allergic reaction.
My immune system
is crashing.
Mu stayed with you
one measly little night.
Come on.
And that's all
he's gonna be staying.
Wasn't it fun, though,
sneaking him in and out for his walk?
It was like a real, live adventure.
You know you had fun.
I'm not a swineherd, kook.
Excuse me.
How much is this putter?
This putter is not for sale.
Sorry. This is a mistake.
- You don't golf.
- Tiger gave this to me.
Essentials, remember?
You've got to get rid of this junk.
It's essential.
- Twenty dollars.
- Ten.
Sold.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Come through here.
Do me a favor, all right?
Watch your step.
This is Kelli.
Kelli, this is Molly.
Pleasure to meet you.
Looks almost as good on her
as it does on you, doesn't it?
Gooey! Looks like Mu isn't
the only pig you hang out with.
Go away!
It must be really hard
getting rid of all this neat stuff.
No, I'm actually loving it.
- Really?
- It's very refreshing.
Everybody, once in their life,
should do this
and slough off all the bad...
Wait!
Sorry. This is... mine.
- No, I just bought it.
- How much did you pay?
- Thirty dollars.
- My friend Rosella gave it to me.
I'll give you 50. 75!
Enough!
We're downsizing, remember?
Sloughing off the excess
to find our center.
You want this, Molly.
Close your eyes
and repeat after me.
I want this.
Miss Gunn?
We're ready to pack this room up
for storage, ma'am.
Can I have just
five more minutes, please?
- Okay, sure.
- Thank you.
Is that you?
Dad's a rock star?
Was.
He's dead.
Bet this stuff
is worth a bundle.
I can't just sell it, Ray.
It's my parents' stuff.
No, you're gonna box it up so it
can lay in storage gathering dust.
God, you're pathetic.
That man in the library
in your house...
...nurse said he's in a coma
from a massive stroke.
That's your father, huh?
Was.
He's a vegetable now.
Soon he'll be nothing.
That's kind of harsh.
It's a harsh world.
Watch where you're going!
Neal, I really hate talking
to your machine.
Where are you?
I'm still holding on
to your jacket for you.
I know you've been going crazy
trying to reach me,
but I've been
in a transition right now.
I'm, like, Miss Proletariat now.
Mop the floors, spank the brat,
pick up the paycheck on Friday.
I am a woman.
How about you?
Shit!
Get under the tail.
I'm not putting my hand
under his heinie.
Do you want him
to stay here or not?
Oh, God!
Oh, my God!
I'll get him!
Very good.
Now come out of plough.
Very nice.
Breathing. Good.
Pull up under. Very nice.
Molly, out of plough.
Come on, Molly.
Let's go.
Could you please help me?
This is starting to hurt.
Oh, my God.
73... beautiful.
74,
75... very good.
76,
77...
Let me put a few more on.
Ing, here we go.
Waist.
Molly, you get to be in charge
of the chocolate chip cookies.
They're already mixed,
so all you have to do
is put them in the oven
and time them.
Salmonella.
You're letting her do this?
Relax, girls.
It's just cookie mix.
How badly
can she screw it up?
Put it out now!
Put it out!
I'm trying!
Oh, gosh!
This is Neal's jacket!
- Put it out!
- Get it out!
Take it back!
- Oh, my God!
- Take it back now!
What are you doing, Ray?
Have you gone mad?
There is never, ever an excuse
for hitting another person.
What's going on?
She was laughing at me
because her "au pair"
said that my new nanny
was a slutbag whore.
Go!
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
You've reached Ingrid.
Please leave your number
and the time of your call.
Be specific.
Hi. It's Neal calling for Molly.
I hope this is
the right number.
I love Ingrid
with all my heart
and all her cute
Martha Stewart-wannabe friends,
but it's a real estrogen-fest
over there.
A girl needs a testosterone injection
every once in a while.
Not that I think
of you that way.
You're super-sensitive.
Don't be a silly goose.
Please let me
patronize the arts.
Well, actually...
I just signed a deal
with Schleine Records.
Oh, my God.
What?
Oh, my God!
Neal, that's incredible!
That's amazing!
Why didn't you say anything?
I would have, but this is
the first time tonight
I've managed
to get a word in edgewise.
I...
So how did you seal the deal?
Ships crossing like ghosts
in the night
Names unremembered.
Faces in sight
Take what we can
in need to survive
I know this one.
This is the deep one.
Words exchanging kisses
in view
Leave me scarred.
Feeling confused
I'll see what unfolds
Don't hide what I need
Girl. Now. I love you so
Sheets of Egyptian cotton
Sheets of Egyptian cot...
I guess I looked
deep down inside
and... found that inner hook.
You certainly did...
...and that calls for...
...an outer hook to go with it.
- What's that?
- Your lucky jacket.
My lucky...
- What have you done to it?
- A few minor improvements.
- Improvements?
- Yeah.
- You mutilated it!
- No, I fixed it.
Look how great this is. I told you
purple was your magic color.
We have to talk.
Those are the four
most hateful words in English.
I can't see you anymore.
- I'm sorry about the jacket.
- It's not about the jacket.
I just can't see you.
That's all.
Right. You just do
the rock star's daughter
so you can tell
your pop star-wannabe mates,
then ride off into the sunset
with your crummy guitar...
It's not like that.
I'm just not in a place...