You had your whole life
to prepare for this moment.
Why aren't you ready?.
I'm tired, sir.
Do you wish to quit?.
If your mission is to quit,
there's no better time than right now.
You can quit now, get it over with.
I can't catch her.
I understand.
Just take those numbers off
and put them in my hand.
Forget that!
You better catch her.
- Well done.
- Sir.
You looked back for my sign.
Well done.
- I don't even know why I did it.
- Yeah, well...
...you know what Napoleon said:
- "Give me a man who's lucky."
- Yes, sir.
- What they got you teaching, sergeant?.
- Edged weapons, sir. Knife fighting.
Don't you teach them knife fighting.
Teach them to kill.
That way they meet some son of a bitch
studied knife fighting...
...they send his soul to hell.
It's all in the mind, sergeant.
That's where the battle's won.
Mr. Scott.
Black, Jacqueline A., U.S. 24341924.
I hope you'll remember and reach out
for me, if you could use me.
- Sergeant?.
- Sir.
Thank you.
You guys cleaned up good.
- It's good to see you.
- What's happening, brother?.
You ain't looking too bad
yourself there, big boy.
In one piece.
Hey, check it out.
I see you.
Talk to me.
How you doing, sir?.
What's that then?.
This was my father's.
- He carry it over there?.
- Yes, sir.
- He come back?.
- Yes, sir, he did.
You carry it then.
Maybe it'll save your life.
Light a fire with it or something.
Hey, Bobby! Bobby.
- Yeah, give me that.
- Thanks.
Sir.
- I would like to say, to meet you-
- You haven't met me.
You've been up for a week.
You been seeing snakes.
Fall out of the bleachers!
Grab your bags.
All you men are returning to unit.
Let's go.
Have your number in your right hand.
- Can't imagine how they live with it.
- Your number in your right hand.
Can't you?.
I thought I saw you considering it.
- What the hell is that?.
- That's a wedding ring, sir.
You hear that?.
The sentry you're sneaking up on,
he can hear it too.
You've been around long enough
to know that.
- Thank you, sir. My name's Curtis-
- Do I need to know?.
If I want camaraderie,
I'll join the Masons.
There's just the mission.
- He got the letter from his wife.
- Yeah?. How's she doing?.
Sir.
- Orders up! Get your eyes in the boat!
- All right, I want your numbers.
- Get these fucking numbers off.
- You heard him.
You don't need them no more.
Come on, now. You think I have all night?.
I've got two things for you boys.
That's a stiff dick and bubble gum.
And guess what,
I'm out of bubble gum.
Are you deaf or are you just trying
to try my patience?. Get those numbers off!
Let's go.
Number nine and number 12.
Who the fuck is that?. Stand up, now!
You two are the first two.
On me.
Pick it up, people. I don't have all night.
- Yes, sir!
- Thanks for coming down, master gunner.
Sure thing, boss.
Here you go, sir.
- Grossler?.
- Yes, sir.
- Curtis.
This is the final selection event.
Follow my instructions.
Nothing more, nothing less.
On my command, execute.
The last man standing, walk out that door.
You will be admitted to the unit.
Execute.
- It's not current.
- Why not?.
It seems she got a makeover today.
We're working on it.
- Four p.m., Cut n' Curl?.
- They gave her a crew cut, dyed it blond.
- Any idea why?.
- Nope.
And then met with the boyfriend at 9.
- Then?.
- We don't know.
But your man was on post
till he turned her over to night watch.
- He says he was.
- What else you got?.
I gotta get you on a landline.
We got the boyfriend, Michael Blake.
- Where is he?.
- We're shaking the trees.
And Professor Gerald Sloane,
notably chummy with his female students...
...of which she was one.
Weekend home, Martha's Vineyard.
I'm light. I'm light, people.
I need another team on the professor.
- I need an over-watch on the boyfriend.
- ls the phone up?. Get the phone up.
Got it. We're up!
- You just come from Cadre?.
- Yes, sir.
- How long since you've slept?.
- Not significant.
I don't have the bodies.
Call them in. Call them in.
His post was Harvard Yard.
Harvard Yard, northeast corner,
Lowell House, across from her dorm.
Night watch relieved him there, midnight.
Want to help me out?.
- You understand?.
- Yes, sir.
- I'm making myself clear to you, right?.
Okay, then. Once again.
She had lunch with her father.
Lunch with her father.
You were seconded to that?.
- No, sir, I just had her.
- You just had her?.
I had her all day.
Tucked her in at 10. And she-
Yeah, she had a tiff with her boyfriend,
Michael Blake.
- What was it about?.
- I think it was about her...
- Her haircut. So it wasn't a serious...?.
- No, no. No.
- And then I held the post until relieved.
- Well, then we've got a little problem.
I was there.
2312 hours, 19 May, Harvard Yard,
northeast corner, Lowell House...
...reveals no Secret Service presence.
Neither his post, nor adjacent.
A second tour, 2330, reveals similarly.
- I was there, sir.
- Who's lying, you or him?.
You son of a bitch, I got 15 years in.
I got two kids.
You're not gonna sit there
and lie away my pension.
- I was-
- Do not say you were there.
I was on post.
Get up, motherfucker!
Don't you say you were on post!
Get up! You son of a bitch!
- Get up! You motherfucker!
- Get the fuck out! Get the fuck out!
Okay, sit down.
Shall I tell you what's gonna happen
to you when we find you out?.
Were you fucking her?.
- We're gonna find out.
- No, l-
Where is the girl?.
Where is your principal?.
We're gonna have to take this
from the top again.
- Okay, Mr. Gaines?.
- Yes, sir.
I want the clock up.
Let's get the clock up, please.
We got until her Monday-morning class,
then it's Meet the Press and "Where is she?. "
The professor.
Who's got the professor?.
- Where is he?.
- Martha's Vineyard.
- Who's got him?.
- Parr and Shannon.
Wake him up, shake him up.
He don't wanna talk...
...here's what we have him doing with his
female students. Show them to his wife.
- We got the state cops on the scrambler.
- The photo.
This is the last known photo of the girl.
Sir!
It's the professor.
- You had him at his home.
- We were in error.
- Where is he?.
- Best guess puts him on his boat.
Last seen, West Tisbury,
Martha's Vineyard.
- Show me.
- Right here.
Find him. Put the guard on him.
Get me an overflight.
- I hear you.
- I'm 25 men light here.
- Who's got the Coast Guard?.
- I got them.
I need an overflight.
Coast Guard Search and Rescue.
Coast Guard on the red phone.
New Bedford!
- What's the name of his boat?.
- The Colophon, out of West Tisbury.
Sir.
- It's the boyfriend. He's moving.
- I need a stalker on the boyfriend. Now.
- I've got him.
- Call it out. Hold surveillance.
I've got two days to run in
before the press wakes up.
Yes, sir.
Let me see your hands, son.
Right now.
Drop it.
Did you lose your mailbox key, son?.
- You a student here?.
- Yes.
Can I see some identification, please?.
- Section 12, this is-
- No, please. Please.
Calm down.
It's gonna be what it's gonna be.
Can I talk to you for one minute?.
Just one minute, all right?.
This- It's not what it looks like.
I broke up with my girlfriend.
This is her mailbox. It's Laura.
- Laura Newton.
- Laura?.
- Yes.
- Newton?.
The Laura Newton?.
That's right. We broke up.
- They know who I am.
- They?.
- The Secret Service.
- Secret Service?.
That's right.
They know who I am.
They cleared me.
They didn't clear you for this.
Let's go.
- Okay-
- Let's go.
- I was just trying to retrieve the letter.
- This is not very nice language.
"You deserve everything
that's gonna happen to you."
What's gonna happen to her?.
Did you hurt her?.
Did you hit her?.
Hit her?. No.
- I called her a whore.
- What's this sign?.
What does this sign mean?.
Right here.
She signs all of her letters with that.
It's because she...
- ...sees things cockeyed, like Picasso.
- Picasso.
She says they call her Picasso.
Why did you fight with her, son?.
She got her hair done.
Dyed it blond. She cut it off.
I called her a slut.
Wait. We've all seen the pictures.
Beautiful young girl like that...
...what do you care what color
she dyes her hair?.
Now why does that make her a slut?.
She's fucking another guy.
You want to talk about it?.
If you want to talk about it,
I will give you one minute.
Nothing hurts worse than that,
if she's sleeping with another guy.
There's this...
This teacher that...
I shouldn't be telling you this.
She's sleeping with a teacher?.
Well, she says she isn't.
I said if she wants to fuck old men, she
should go to the Back Light, go all the way.
- Back Light?.
- Yeah. It's this club by the Fenway.
It's like a joke at school, like a rumor.
This girl or that girl went with
a businessman for one night...
...made a thousand bucks.
This is a lovers' quarrel, all right?.
I said something that I regret.
I sent a note that I regret.
I can assure you, officer...
...if you see your way clear
to give me a break, it'll never...
The Back Light.
It's a club in the Fenway.
A club in the Fenway.
No morgue. No hospital. No note.
The parents?.
The mother, you know where she is.
She's a drunk. He's holding up.
- He was in town yesterday to see her.
- He was?.
- We snuck him in and out.
- How long were they together?.
- Parker.
- One second.
- He copped to it.
- Copped to what?.
Left his post. Punched out early
to go boffing his girlfriend.
Hope she was worth it.
- Sir.
- All right. Let's get back on it.
Okay. Back Light.
A restaurant, The Black Night...
...The Black Light, a bar,
a supper club.
Black Light, that's it.
Put up the graphics on the girl.
Take a look at this.
We ran it up from a description
of the colorist from the beauty parlor.
Show him what we got.
Transport is under command of State.
We refer to section two.
Yeah, I understand.
- May I have your jacket?.
- Right, I got it.
Yeah.
Get their guys off the perimeter.
Get our guys in.
I need $5000.
- Annie.
- I heard it, $5000.
- Scraping the bottom of the barrel, huh?.
- Yes, sir.
Five thousand dollars.
Need you to sign for it.
You sign for it.
All right.
- What happened to your wedding ring?.
- I took it off.
Did you go off your wife?.
No, sir, I'm working.
Keep your mouth shut, your eyes open.
And form on me.
Move aside. Move aside!
Oh, Jesus.
All right, then. Who saw it?.
I believe he had a hideout piece.
Who frisked him?.
Who frisked the son of a bitch?.
The girl he went to see, get her in.
The one he was fucking.
- Two guys to her house, right now.
- Seal the room off.
Check out the file.
Seal the room off.
He was off post when
he snatched the girl?.
Yeah, well, apparently he felt bad
about it.
- Show me a set of keys.
- I ain't got them.
Here, you take the chain.
You've got the over-watch.
Swing the chain.
You're a guy walking the dog.
Loosen your collar.
Told me 2:00.
It's closing time, gents.
Time to pack it up.
Don't gotta go home,
but you can't stay here.
Closing up.
Can't sell booze after 2 a.m.
No, I just wanted to pay you
that money I owe you.
- How about them Sox, huh?.
- Yeah, what are you gonna do?.
Yeah. "Curse of the Bambino,"
isn't that what you call it?.
That's right. Where are you from?.
Yeah, well, actually,
I was just trying to find my niece.
Oh, that's what you're looking for?.
Because a lot of guys come in here
looking for someone else's niece.
No. Girl like that...
...been in tonight?.
- Pretty girl.
- Yeah, that's my type.
Girl like that been in?.
You sure you're looking
for your niece?.
Because a lot of guys come in here and
go home with some rather younger girl.
No, no. Why-?.
Why would...
...a younger girl like that
want to be with a guy like me?.
Howdy, pard.
I was wondering
if I could ask you a favor.
I love you, baby,
but the season's over.
Your friend said you
were sort of a matchmaker.
Look, you can't believe
everything you hear.
- Catch you later.
- You know it.
Okay, lock it up.
Drive safely, now.
- Yeah?.
- I was looking for a girl.
For a young girl.
Well, aren't we all?.
My question was, why would
a young, pretty girl like that...
...go out with a guy like me?.
And if you could answer that...
Look, bub...
What is this?.
What's this?. It's Rohypnol, is it?.
Is this Ro?. Is this Roofy?. Is this a
one-sided conversation?. What's his name?.
- Jerry Zimmer.
- Jerry. Jerry.
Where's the girl?.
Where's the girl, Jerry?.
- Jerry, where's the girl?.
- What girl?.
Dose her?. You dose her, Jerry?.
- Hey.
- What?.
- About 10, 15 thou.
- What's that for?.
- I think you broke my arm!
- Where's the girl?.
I think you broke my arm!
Now it's broken.
Where is the girl, Jerry?.
I never saw that girl.
Where's the girl?.
Where did you take her?.
Where did you take this girl, Jerry?.
That's not the girl.
Take your knife out.
Where did you take the girl, Jerry?.
Take his eye out.
You bet your life.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
I took the girl.
I took the girl to...
Three units remain on the perimeter
until further instructions.
The sniper is to stand down.
Plainclothes, transport in the south alley.
I got it.
- ls that right?.
- Yes.
We run an escort service. There is no
impropriety here. There is no illegality.
- Who is she?.
- Nadya Tellich.
Serb. Green card,
five years ago.
They sign a contract
with us for personal services...
...and they pay us so much
for each call, and the girls pay us.
- They show you proof of their age?.
- Of course. What do you think?.
- Have you seen this girl?.
- I have not.
Here's the first one.
Was this girl here?.
She's new.
This is her first night.
How about that?.
Put some fucking clothes on.
I want my lawyer.
You don't need one.
We need the girl. Give us the girl.
This girl was not here.
I'm entitled to my lawyer.
You're entitled to shit.
You're entitled to tell me what you know.
If the girl was here...
...if you cooperate,
I'll see what I can do.
I think I can help you,
if you tell me now.
Why would I not tell you
if the girl was here?.
The girl is new.
They told us
that it was her first night.
But look here.
There's two pinholes in the photo.
They moved it over.
Photo's missing.
Where is she?.
- I don't want to get in trouble.
- You don't know what trouble is.
I'm not even sure that was her.
She was sick.
She was not very well.
- She came in here and...
- She came here?.
They took her. I told Nadya
she shouldn't be here. They took her.
Who is "they"?.
They took her?.
Where did they take her?.
Honey, you got all the slack
in the world until I leave this room.
And then I'm going to zero you out.
Two men.
They gave her a shot.
I think that was her.
- Where is she?.
- I'm entitled to my rights.
- I'm entitled to my phone call.
- You don't understand.
You'll leave your life, or you'll
leave the information in this room.
Where is the girl?.
They'll kill me.
Who did you call?.
How did you know
to come pick her up?.
How did they know to get her?.
Who did you call?.
It's just a number-
Write it down.
Write it down. I'm gonna see what I can do.
Just give me the number.
I don't understand.
She's just some girl.
Oh, my God.
They don't know who they've got.
Sir.
Where's the girl?.
Sir, we believe she was
abducted from this club.
That she was taken to-
That she was taken to a bordello.
- Here in Boston?.
- Yes, sir, and that- That-
- Let's hear it.
- She may have been delivered for sale.
May have been sent down
the pipeline, overseas.
- To get to her father?.
- No, sir.
We believe they don't
know who she is...
...that they just took some girl.
- Just some girl.
- Yes, sir.
How certain are you she was
the girl in the whorehouse?.
- We-
- She dyed her hair.
They see that red hair...
What do they do, her hair grows out,
when they see that red hair...
...somebody recognizes her?.
What do they do when
they realize who they took?.
They kill her.
You're fucking-A right, they kill her.
Okay.
Now, let's talk some common sense.
Who is he?.
What can you do for me?.
I need it now.
I need it before the press gets it on
Monday, because they will kill her.
The press gets this, the jackals start
a feeding frenzy, and she's dead. Help me.
This is the number of a public phone
in downtown Boston.
It's a cutout between
the bordello and the abductors.
A call is placed when they
have a package.
- Stake out the phone.
- We have a watch on the phone.
But more importantly, NSA reports
calls placed to that phone regularly.
- They can track calls to the pay phone?.
- Yes.
- How?.
- They were made from a federal prison.
This is Tariq Asani.
He's a Lebanese national
serving life without for kidnapping.
He's the second man
in a sex-slavery scheme.
And where is he?.
He's in Florence Federal Penitentiary.
He placed the calls to the pay phone.
- We have a plan. I hesitate to-
- Give it to me.
Got some action on the pay phone.
Who's walking up on us?.
He's Boston P.D.
In the city, always a reflection.
In the woods, always a sound.
What about the desert?.
You don't want to go in the desert.
Let's go. Let's go.
We're moving.
- Where's he going?.
- Hold on. Hold on.
One-five-four-nine Alpha-Sierra,
Mass. registration, William Barak.
- Somerville, Mass.
- ls that where he's going?.
Owner of record in Essex.
Is he heading toward Essex?.
What kind of place would it be?.
It'd be a beach house.
Get me there.
Get it on the Net.
Everyone off.
Call everyone off. Just me.
Just me and him.
Indicate you heard me.
State Police' atanding by.
Turn off the white car.
The ahootera are going to the beach.
Team of two going to Eaaex.
Confirm' aaaault team of two
to the beach.
- Withdraw and hold at condition two.
- State Police' requeat verify.
We believe the hostage is-
Six-five and Mobile 4 are RTB.
Acknowledge.
Stand down and aquawk on your A VX.
Get me there.
If the girl's in the house,
I'm taking her out.
If it ain't me or her, kill it.
Clear.
Well' I hope you both feel better
in the morning. Good night.
- Yea?
- Doea an Alan Palmer live here?
- Yea' my huaband'a at work.
- Thia ia juat a routine check' Mra. Palmer.
We have a licenae-plate number'
but we 're not aure of the accuracy.
May I come in?
- What the fuck?.
- I heard the TV, so I came in.
Why the hell do you got the TV on?.
There's no one here.
I don't want to hurt you.
I just want to know why the TV's on.
I just came to-
That's what I want to know.
I'm telling you why I came in.
What do you make of that?.
That's the thing. This time of the night...
Do you hear what I'm telling you?.
- question.
Even it up. Where's the girl?.
Where is the girl?.
It's not too late.
Look at me. Look at me.
Where is the girl?.
Where is she?.
It's Curtis. I'm coming in.
Abort. Abort. Abort.
Cold LZ. Cold hole.
Stand by. Await instructions.
She aeta the atylea.
She bringa ua amilea.
She'a Betty Coed in college
and ahe'a in the newa again.
- Shit.
- She had her hair reatyled' cut and dyed.
- We caught up with her atyliat...
- Turn it off.
...and have reconatructed that new look.
And you 're looking at it.
I ' m out of time.
Keep it locked up.
What about if we had to go
off the meter?.
I need a man, a man who can
unquestioningly follow orders.
The door is closed, sir.
I need to ask you to do something.
I am here to get the girl back, sir.
And there is nothing I will not do...
...to get the girl back.
This man...
...placed a phone call yesterday...
...from the phone bank at Florence
to the Copley pay phone.
Here's the cutoff point. Here it is.
This man, Tariq Asani,
is to be transported tomorrow...
...with another convict,
a man on death row.
A man on death row...
...for their medical procedures.
I'll take you step by step through what
we've envisioned is gonna happen.
Diapatch acknowledgea Florence Unit 5
ia Code 7 at Highway 15.
You fellas all right?.
Hey, help me. Help me, man.
Buck me up, man.
- Hey, I need some help.
- Yeah, I'll help you out. Get out.
Me and my brother need
some shit right here.
- You marked him paid in full.
- Yeah, that's what I did.
Hey, give me a cigarette, man.
Wait over there. I'll be right back.
Yeah, but break me out of this.
Hey, yo, just throw me the keys,
and I'll do it.
I gotta do some cleaning first.
Motherfuckers want to hook me up
to some injection machine, man.
Motherfuckers want to take my life
who just got well here, you know?.
Who just got well.
Then the hand of God came down with
an outstretched arm and freed my ass.
You know?.
Hey, baby, pass me some my way,
you know?.
Sorry, my man. Traveling light.
No, wait. Wait. Don't shoot me.
Don't shoot me.
I can get us out of the country tonight.
Oh, God, please don't shoot me! No!
I swear on my mother.
Look at me. Please.
No.
I swear to you. A seaplane, tonight.
Help me.
Please, believe me.
Now, why in the world would l
believe a lying convict like you?.
I can get us out. I swear.
Help me. Help me, and I will
treat you like a brother.
My brother used to beat me.
Nice guess, though.
No, no, hold on! Wait.
Just make one phone call.
One fucking phone call. Go into the house
and make one phone call.
An aviation company.
Tell them the word I say, and they will say
the plane will meet us tonight.
I swear. The plane will meet us tonight.
You a fag, my friend?.
- No, I'm not.
- Then what are you looking at me for?.
I was just thinking how fucking
surprised you're gonna be.
Because, baby, you just did
that fucking good turn.
I'm gonna make you rich, fat and happy
for the rest of your life.
No, just get me on the plane.
You like girls?.
Better question: Where you been
so long, do you like girls?.
We have- You will have...
- ...the most beautiful-
- Yeah, beautiful women.
Not women, baby.
Girls. You got to trust me.
All young. All blond.
And this all takes place where?.
In Dubai. In Yemen.
When we get to Maskala.
And now, what's Maskala?.
- When we get to Dubai.
- What's Maskala?.
It's where we clean them up.
We ship them rough...
...we make them nice and smooth,
and everybody's happy.
You're just a philosopher, then, huh?.
How about making me happy tonight?.
If there's a girl in the pipeline tonight,
you shall have her.
What do you say to that?.
I say you're a stone-cold whoremaster.
Fuck.
I'm bleeding bad, my friend.
- what you need?
Need aome tailoring toola.
If I had a wiah liat' I'd get you to
a drugatore. I'd get aome morphine.
That'd get you back on Happy Street.
Then you get me on that plane tonight.
- Where's the gauze, ma'am?.
- Right behind you.