Unh
Yeah
Life in the city
Street life is a hustle
Go on every day
This life in the city,
three strikes in the city
Childhood go hard,
street life ain't pretty
Young soldier watching
the block's vultures
Whips, women and paper
dominate the culture
Rocks, pills, weed, flocking,
pimping and pandering
Checks, credit, betting,
whatever hustle they handling
Lost morals for mayors,
undercover patrol
Scores of hos reside,
resident evil
Everyday sequels
Sony reds with bird's-eye views
or hood blues
Get pinched
or shine through-- snitches
Street life is a hustle
Go on every day
This life in the city,
three strikes in the city
Childhood go hard,
street life ain't pretty...
The Queensborough Court
is now in session.
Jonas Maldonado,
Lucas Ryan, A.D. Valburn,
you're charged with criminal
possession of narcotics.
How do you defendants plead?
Due to mitigating circumstances,
not guilty, Your Honor.
The defendants have no priors.
We request bail.
Bail denied.
Street life is a hustle
Go on every day
This life in the city,
three strikes in the city
Childhood go hard,
street life ain't pretty...
In light of the new information
presented by ADA Vecchio,
the three defendants are hereby
remanded to his custody.
Bailiff.
Street life is a hustle
Go on every day
This life in the city,
hood strife, it's a pity
Childhood go hard,
street life ain't pretty.
Come on, man. You see me trying
to give a speech here.
Some of you have known
my best friends and l
since we were delinquent
altar boys in grade school.
Hey look, you can keep your
little giggles to yourself, all right?
I know things about you too.
You know,
it might've taken me a bit longer
to decide to join,
but thanks to some help--
you know, I just wanna say my pop--
if I could be
- half the cop my pop was--
- Aww.
Well, I hope I can be
half the cop my pop was.
I just wanna thank everybody
for coming out
and supporting me
and my buddies who are
taking the plunge with me--
and of course, other cadets.
Yeah, other cadets.
You know, um, let's party.
- Let's have a good time.
- Yeah! Let's party!
You're dangerous, boy,
you're dangerous...
- Hey you.
- Hey. What's up?
Congratulations, Jonas.
I'm very proud of you.
But it's been years.
Why did you invite me?
You still crushing on me, Jonas?
I'm still trying to piss
your brother off.
I'm just kidding.
I'm still crushing on you a little bit.
- Okay.
- Is that okay?
Well, I was kinda
hoping we could settle
some unfinished business tonight.
Coincidence.
I was thinking the same thing.
All right, here we go--
four shots of tequila.
- Uh-oh.
- Ow.
- Remember what happened last time.
- Right.
- Uh-huh.
- Let me know if you need anything else.
- All right.
- All right, so may we be
each other's eyes, ears and fists.
- To my boys.
- Hey, may we continue
to stay on the right side of the law...
- for once.
- To the ultimate hustle.
- Hey.
- Cheers.
Whoo!
- Ooh.
- Hit me up.
Hey, who invited Lydia?
- Who's the cougar?
- The cougar's how we got
in the academy.
I mean she helped us.
Your dad being a cop wasn't enough?
Remember when we were wild little kids?
I remember my brother
not being too happy
about some thug trying
to be my boyfriend at 1 6.
I remember slinging rock
for your brother.
- I remember your brother whipping--
- Mrs. Vecchio's husband
is the assistant DA.
We went to school with their son Kenny.
Anyway, after your brother
beat Malo down,
he snitched us out to the pigs.
That feels weird wearing
this uniform right now.
Will you tell this fool
we're cops now?
- Law enforcement officers.
- What?
Yeah. Angie-- he--
he set us up with the police,
you know, while we was
carrying his product.
Mrs. V had her husband
pull some strings
to get us out of jail
and into the academy.
- Why would she do that for you guys?
- Dick for dollars.
- What's dick for dollars?
- Shh. Nigga, you crazy.
- Just-- shh shh.
- Yo, she was a freak.
She used to pay these two
to smash her once a week.
Now I never got to tap
the ADA's wife,
so I invited her.
I figure I'm due, right?
- You are an idiot. You know this.
- Maybe.
- Yeah, there's something wrong.
- Congratulations to all of you.
Oh God, you've still got
a fine ass, Mrs. V.
- Thanks for coming, Mrs. V.
- You didn't invite me.
- Can I please have a word with you?
- I got a word for you.
I got you here.
The least you could do is
sit down and talk with me.
I could speak to you.
I know some things
that you need to know.
We know it wouldn't be possible
to be here without you.
We know what you
and your husband did for us.
- How is he?
- Dead.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Now that I have your attention--
Why don't you just pull up a seat?
Just come grieve
over here for a second,
Iike right in this area.
Call me.
Would you still bend that over?
No. You?
Liar. Me too.
- In a heartbeat.
- He fucking tells everything, man.
Compliments
from the gentleman in the back.
- Who's that?
- I don't know.
I'ma go check it out.
Sit down.
- Ah.
- Congratulations, Jonas.
- Thank you.
- No, you don't know me.
- But you know me.
- My name is Captain Joe Sarcone.
I head the Street Vice
Crimes Task Force.
Your dad and me were partners.
Now when you're done here,
I want you to be at this place--
just you.
God, you look just like him.
Sharkey's?
I'll leave a light on for you.
You like what you see?
Uh-huh.
For seven years, me and your old man
were as thick as thieves.
I promise this isn't
some polished-up hustle to entrap you.
It's all part of your birthright.
Welcome home.
By the end of the night
they're gonna know our names
But we never pay
'cause we'll all go up in flames
Put it on my tab
All the women and wine
Put it on my tab...
Let me know if I can
get you anything else.
Thank you.
Oh!
You know, I'm not the type of man
to ask a big question
without knowing the answer already.
Remember that.
Besides honoring
the memory of your father,
- why did you become a cop?
- I don't know.
Get a little respect
in the neighborhood,
maybe a little payback.
Eh, one look at you,
I already know
you got respect on the street.
- Right?
- Yeah, a little bit.
I'll ask you something else--
what's your life worth?
If you had to put a price tag on it,
what would you say your life's worth?
I don't know.
I never thought about that.
- Would you say 46 grand?
- I don't know.
Well, that's what the city of New York
seems to think it's worth--
since you gotta go out there
and risk it every day.
Personally, I feel my life's
worth more than that.
A pat on the back
and an extra 1 0-grand-a-year raise
for a job well done isn't worth my life
or any of the lives of my men.
Either way, we gotta
get the job done, you know?
What we do here...
Iet's just call it the bonus system.
Corruption in this city,
let alone in this country,
is far beyond what
any of us can imagine.
You confiscate a large sum of money--
trust me, everybody takes their piece
as the money moves up the ranks.
All we do here is we take our cut--
a finder's fee, that's all.
I spread it amongst my men,
everybody's happy.
Look, you wanna be on your own,
nickel and diming on the street,
that's your business.
But know this-- we are deep
and we are invisible,
all the way up
to the mayor's office.
There's the Maldonado seed.
- You hungry?
- I can always eat.
Kitchen never closes
and everybody eats at my table.
Hey, guys, what's it gonna be?
You really trust everybody in here?
That door you just walked through...
only works one way-- in.
Once you're in, the only way out
is to the sounds
of gunshots and bagpipes.
Don't ever force my hand.
That's your FTO,
Lieutenant Dennis Lureu.
Don't ever question Lureu.
Be like him.
He's been my right hand
since your father left us.
I'll get your boys assigned
to the same precinct.
As for you--
no uniform, no beat.
You work for me starting now--
if you accept.
Your father always said
"Everybody's gotta stash
a bit of sock money for a rainy day."
To your father.
Tonight we celebrate.
Pick a girl. Have some fun.
- Thank you, sweetie.
- Yup.
What can I getcha?
How you doing?
I'm the new guy.
Hi, new guy.
I'm sure you're really nice,
- but I don't fuck cops.
- I just got here.
You're starting rumors
about me already?
- What, you're not a cop?
- No, I'm not a nice guy.
- Ah.
- Jonas Maldonado.
Everybody calls me Malo.
"Malo"-- that's cute.
You're like a Puerto Rican bad guy.
Well, my mom's black.
My father's Puerto Rican.
- I don't do Puerto Ricans either.
- Damn.
- Mmm.
- Where you from? What's your name?
Don't you have some nice girl
waiting for you somewhere?
- Come on.
- I don't want a nice girl.
- I want you.
- You're a charmer.
- Puerto Rico.
- You like peanut butter?
- Yeah, I like peanut butter.
- Me too.
See, we got all this in common.
Wanna fuck?
- Unbelievable.
- I know a place.
Yeah, where?
For peanut butter or for fucking?
- Both.
- Yeah, I bet you do.
I don't know why
you're playing hard to get.
Oh!
Yeah, you motherfuckers
play too much.
- Arrest me, officer.
- Come back and get in your pocket.
Good morning.
Coffee? It's hot.
Man, you look soft.
What?
Badge ain't what protects us out here.
It's having the balls to use it.
You look like you're missing one.
Let's get on outta here,
see if we can find
that missing ball, all right?
Hey.
What? What's going on?
Let me ask you something.
You think any of these
young brothers out here
got the same good sense you got
to try to better themselves?
I mean, most of them look like
they juvenile delinquents.
What you think? Right?
Hmm?
I mean-- l-- I don't know, sir.
You know? Well, maybe.
I mean, l-- I don't know.
Yes, no. You know?
No no no no no no no.
No no no no.
Don't do that.
- Do what?
- Choke up.
"l don't know. I don't know."
No. You know, you breathe
the same air as me, right?
- Yeah. That's right.
- You a black man just like me, right?
- Yes, sir.
- Learn to speak your mind, young blood.
Don't be no stumblebum.
Now only thing I ask is that you keep
your eyes and your ears open, all right?
Maybe be careful.
You might learn something.
But you learn to speak your mind.
Come on, babe. Let it go.
Oh, damn.
You see the ass on that?
Who wouldn't hit that? Who?
Yo, I feel you on that.
Just gotta double bag
in respect for the wife, am I right?
No disrespect,
but you would nut in your pants,
- she let you get a whiff of the tasty.
- What?
- Look, English in the cruiser, please.
- Not like you'd do anything
with her man handcuffing
her right now.
- This motherfucker--
- What, you mean the gorilla?
Watch this.
What's up?
- You got a problem?
- Come on, baby.
That's right, keep walking.
It's not worth it.
Enjoy your day.
That's some bullshit.
And that's how
you keep control of a filthy nigger.
Oh, it's like that?
Yeah, it's like that.
You got a problem with that, rookie?
- You want a bump?
- No, I don't want none.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
Buy, break it, bag it, sell it
Buy, break it,
bag it, sell it...
- This is--
- Look at that.
Ain't got no home training.
Come on, sir.
Kids are gonna do what they want.
When I was a youngster,
doing what you want was
a privilege reserved for grown folk.
You gotta remember
that our strength,
our downfall,
lies with these youth.
Who they mimic is who they become,
and you know what they show.
So we gotta be aware
of what we show,
stop giving them grays
a reason to hate our ass.
Hey, y'all, move. Let's go.
- What?
- No, I said move.
Oh my--
Excuse me, sir-- the grays?
Yeah, the grays.
As in the gray-skinned,
gray-haired Caucasian crackers
that you see smiling they smiles
on the TV talk show,
talking the nonsensical bullshit about
why the Negros call
each other the "N" word.
Huh? You heard that?
How they say it's because
we basically don't like ourselves
or each other.
But that's all right
that we don't take responsibility
for our actions
because, you know,
we don't know no better.
- Yeah, grays.
- Personally,
I've never had a problem
with the word "nigga," sir.
- You know, where I'm from, we--
- Oh!
Oh, you-- so you must be one.
I-- l--
I knew I smelled something.
Oh, man, come on.
I'm riding in the car
with a full-blown nigga in a uniform.
- Nigga in the uniform.
- Hey.
You play ball, Mr. Nigga?
Yeah, I play a little hoop.
You know, but football was my thing.
- I was a wide receiver in high school.
- Yeah? Good.
I want you to come down
to a playground
where I coach some kids
in the PAL team.
- They would love it, you know?
- Uh-huh.
You'd get a chance to meet
some proud young black men,
not like the ones you know.
What's up, Lureu?
Got some new shit.
Always need a backup.
Sometimes you need
a backup for your backup.
Go ahead, get something
for yourself, a'ight?
Hey, you can't use the N-word.
Why the hell not?
'Cause you ain't got a pass.
What, you do?
Hell yes, I got a pass.
Let me guess-- you got
some African-American buddies?
Some brothers?
Look, I was assigned
as your training officer to train you
so you don't have
to learn the hard way.
I got 1 5 years in the cruiser.
You got five hours.
I'm trying to give you
the benefit of my experience.
Buddy, you can throw
yourself under a bus
to save one of these
fine African-Americans,
Puerto Ricans, lndians,
Asians, Muslims-- whatever.
Me, I'm gonna stay in the car
and I'm gonna live,
have dinner with my wife and kid,
bang my girlfriend
and collect my pension.
I could care less
about these monkeys.
- Fuck.
- And understand--
these animals will eat you alive
if you give 'em a chance.
Are we gonna have problems, rookie?
Hey.
When we're in this cruiser,
you better have my back
and you better do exactly
what I tell you. You got me?
Shit can get real crazy
out here really quick.
So when the time comes,
you better get down like I tell you.
All I got is this game
And all I got
is my soul
I'll give you all I got
until it's gone...
Wait in the car, all right?
'Cause all I know
is just pain
Done lost it all
but remain
'Cause truth be told,
a nigga know at the end of the day
You gotta lose
before you could gain
That's how you grow
Gotta move, gotta get it,
gotta hustle, man
And be an overachiever
when they don't understand
'Cause we got the upper hand
whenever they shuffle
I bet I'll royal flush you...
What the fuck you think you doing,
selling drugs to kids?
- Come on, man!
- Fucking punk!
Forgot the rules of the block, huh?
Say it.
Say the rule.
- No candy for the kids.
- Mm-hmm.
- I should book your little ass.
- Hey! Yo, hey!
What are you doing?
Come on!
Hey!
What the fuck do you
think you're doing?
- He was selling drugs to kids.
- I don't give a shit
if he was selling crack
to your grandmother!
If I tell you to wait in the car,
then you--
you wait in the car. A'ight?
A'ight.
You're on the street now, Malo.
I never left the streets.
It's a pretty easy first day.
Don't get used to it.
Man.
Jonas, you know that I love you, right?
Yeah, Pop.
I love you too.
You're a good kid.
I like driving around with you, Pop.
Oh, I bet you do.
Jonas.
Yeah, I figured you'd be here today.
- So you remembered.
- How could I forget?
You haven't called.
Can we talk?
- About what?
- You don't think about me?
I do. All the time.
You know that.
I'm not gonna wait on you forever.
Still working at your father's diner?
Yes.
If you'd come around
more often, you'd know that.
He needs me there.
He doesn't trust anyone else.
- What about your brother?
- Angie-- the wannabe gangsta?
Please, don't even
get me started on that one.
Still trying to be a tough guy?
I just wanna be happy, Jonas.
I want you to be happy.
Why did you invite me
to your celebration at the bar?
It's complicated. I--
I can't even explain it.
Look, I gotta go to work, Cyn.
Jonas.
Do what you feel you gotta do, Cyn.
Officer requesting backup,
Parsons Boulevard.
- That's right around the corner.
- Yeah, I know where it is.
Put the pin.
Pull it, nigga, pull the pin.
- Shut up, both of you!
- Come on, nigga!
Hey, shut up, both of you!
Shut the hell up!
Hey, put the gun on the ground
and step away from it!
- Do it now!
- Fuck you, nigga! I'm ready to die.
- I know that guy.
- It's Felix.
- No no, Ricky.
- Shut the hell up!
- I'll shoot you and your fucking dog.
- What?
- Fuck you.
- Control that dog before I shoot it.
Three witnesses over here, son.
I run the block!
You feel me?
And I don't need no pussy-ass cops
for this Puerto Rican bitch.
Hey, put the gun on the ground
and step away from it! Do it now! Now!
I'm Detective Lureu.
What is this?
- Trying to figure it out, Officer.
- I'm Morrison.
So we come around the corner,
these two come spilling out
of the bodega, arguing.
Out of nowhere, the big--
the black guy
takes a swing at the little guy
with a knife in his hand.
Little guy pulls a piece,
we draw weapons, you guys show up.
I didn't even see where the gun
came from, it happened so fast.
A'ight. I'm gonna take it
from here, uni.
Put the gun down.
Put it down.
It ain't going bad today, not today.
Put the gun down, buddy.
Come on, put it on the ground.
Right there.
Right there on the ground.
Put the gun down.
All right, it's your turn.
Hey hey! You next, let's go.
Tie the dog up,
- lay on the street. Let's go.
- Fuck you!
If it's all the same to you, Officer,
I'll take it from here.
No, it's my collar, my cuffs. No.
Officer Burke's got rank here,
he decides.
He's looking at me
like he wants to eat me.
I want this monkey in my car,
my cuffs on him.
I'm not asking you.
I'm telling you.
Partner, draw your weapon
on Officer Redneck over here.
Right now, do it.
You out of your fucking mind?
The fuck you doing?
I'm in control here.
You holster your weapon
or my partner's gonna
shoot you where you stand.
You wanna die?
- Billy, I think--
- Shut the fuck up!
You wanna die?
Tie your dog on the--
on the pole over there.
I want you to turn around
and I want you to kneel down
and interlock your fingers
behind your head.
Take the kid over here,
then you hand him over to Officer Burke.
Let's go. On your knees.
On your knees!
Hands behind your head.
Do it now!
- Hey hey hey.
- Tough guy, huh?
You're lucky I didn't
haul your ass off, punk.
Hey!
- Oh my God!
- What's up now, pussy? Huh?
- I ain't even do nothing, son.
- Fuck.
This motherfucker wanna eat me.
You think I'm a monkey, huh?
Ricky, you know me, man.
Don't do this.
Don't test me, Malo.
Don't test me.
You're right--
dude wants to end you.
I ain't gonna let it go like that.
Easy, let the OG take you in.
Put the gun down.
Come on, son.
It's gonna get bad for you out here.
You oughta be locking up that cop!
You're welcome.
On your knees. Let's go.
- On your knees.
- Hey.
- Easy.
- Hands behind your head.
Hands behind your head!
Hey hey hey!
Stand down.
They're not messing around.
Don't think I'm not
reporting this, Lureu.
Yeah, we all watched you
assault a perp
and my rookie bail
your bitch-ass out,
so why don't you put that
in your report?
You're mine.
Get in the fucking cruiser.
Punk.
Do me a favor--
uncuff him, will you?
Uncuff him.
- Do you really want me to?
- Yeah.
- He's my new partner Malo.
- 'Sup?
- Yeah.
- You carrying?
Of course, Lureu.
You know I always got you.
You lucky that I showed up when I did,
'cause you know
that redneck was gonna
rape you with a stick.
You know that, right?
All right, you owe me.
This your stop. Get out.
- You sure you don't party?
- Not with that shit.
Yeah well,
when you've seen enough shit
and you've done enough shit,
you change your mind.
Till then, don't judge me
if you're gonna be
- sitting right next to me.
- I'm not judging you.
You will soon.
Just once I'd like to know
what it feels like
not to have a brown face
in the back back there.
Now your mama gotta hide her face every
time she go out on the street, huh?
Uncuff him, Officer.
Excuse me?
I said take the shackles
off the young boy's wrists.
And give this to him.
It's his stuff.
Come on, man.
And look,
keep your head on you, okay?
- We're letting you off this time.
- Hey, come on.
It ain't always gonna be like this.
Wow.
I thought we were supposed
to keep cats like that off the streets.
- No.
- You know, I thought that--
No no, tell me,
what would you have done, Officer,
if you had six guns
pointed at your head
and a crazy-ass cracker
trying to take you in? Huh?
- Remember Abner Louima.
- Why did we let him go?
- I mean, he--
- No, he's gonna be better off
out here than he is inside that system.
Trust me on that.
But that's not
our decision to make, sir.
- No. Look, let me tell you something.
- You know, that's--
A few years inside that system
and he would've
been desperate enough
to pull that trigger
just not to go back inside.
Now this lesson just ain't for him.
It's for you too.
Yes sir.
I'm getting money,
yeah, I'm getting money
You niggas 'bout a dollar,
I'm 'bout a hundred
I'm getting money,
yeah, I'm getting money
Mr. Hundred Grand, popping them
dollars out of rubber bands
I'm getting money,
l-l-l-- I'm getting money
I'm getting money, l-l-l--
I'm getting money
I'm getting money,
l-l-l-- I'm getting money
I'm getting money, l-l-l--
I'm getting money...
Cash on delivery,
they call me the Postman
I'm a stunner,
bread and butter...
You tap Joey yet?
What?
Joey, the bartender?
I only met her a week ago.
Did you tap Joey yet?
Of course I did.
I knew that shit. Punks.
Everybody in that bar been trying
to crack that ass ever since
she got up in here.
Then you come in here in a week,
slinging your shit around
and you got that.
A couple stacks
in my religious
To help my jeans sag
The chain so icy,
the kid playing freeze tag
She say she like my swag,
I think she got it bad...
Whoa whoa,
what we got up here?
- Let me get that.
- Sit down, rookie.
I'll make the first move,
then you show me what you've got.
Ladies.
You lose your keys?
Shit, I know you ain't trying to holla.
Y'all are too fine to be police, baby.
- What's going on, ladies?
- Her man crazy.
- He ain't my man.
- Your man crazy?
Yeah, so we was out here
last night just chilling,
smoking a blunt.
So I need to holla at my man,
but my phone battery had died,
so I ask Eddie can I use his.
So he let me use it,
but then he's stressing me
on these minutes and shit, right?
So we got to yelling.
Then po-po rolls up, talking about
disturbing the peace and shit
and that they about to take us in.
Anyhow, Eddie got put
in the system last night,
got locked up with the key to this house
and my shit's still in there.
You know what?
Enough of that, a'ight?
- Show me some lD.
- What you want my lD for?
Just give me some lD, all right?
Hey, shit.
Here.
What does Eddie do?
Eddie sling rock?
Answer my partner.
No, Eddie sells weed.
There's somethin' in here.
You smell it?
- Get your shit and get outta here.
- Hey, gimme a fucking minute.
Wait a motherfucking minute? Shit.
Make sure these ladies
get outta here, a'ight?
God.
- Just a minute.
- Just get your shit and let's go.
God damn it.
Where is my fuckin'--?
I don't fucking know.
Maybe he took it.
Yeah yeah,
I don't see my shit. Any of it.
Am I fucking seeing
my man's shit, anyway?
I thought you said
Eddie wasn't your man?
Okay, all right, look--
Hey, man, what the fuck you doing?
Oh shit.
I'm not gonna tell.
I ain't gonna say nothing.
I swear I'm not.
She ran off with your balls, kid.
Help me!
Oh, no no!
Please!
Holy shit. Shit.
Grandma, is she dead?
Move back.
Somebody call 91 1.
First time seeing a face get split?
No.
Here's your cut plus
a little cherry-popping bonus.
Another good day.
- How about my cut of the weed?
- Yo.
No no, we'll sell Eddie's stash
to one of his competitors,
we make a bundle of cash-- unless you've
got a better idea. I'm all ears.
Let's bail Eddie out,
sell his product back to him.
We put him back in business
working for us,
take a cut off the top.
Win-win for everybody.
You know,
I was right about you.
You're charmed.
I love this kid.
Today was a good day.
You guys go out,
have a good time, celebrate.
Welcome to my shade, here.
- This is your spot?
- This is it.
"D" is for the diamonds,
"O" is for the owes
"P" is for the paper,
"E" is for everything...
Hi.
Take a seat, all right? Relax.
I see you brought a friend.
To the back.
I'll get you set up.
Oh. Enjoy, a'ight?
It's on me.
Thank you very much,
you are very welcome
For not supporting
and never helping
I live the dream, so when I sleep
there's only nightmares...
- Thanks.
- Like when the police found
That cocaine in my Nike Airs
I went from steel handcuffs
to diamond bracelets
When no one else
would bail me out
My nigga Johnny Blaze did
That's why I take him
everywhere with me
Even let him blow my last 50
No problem
On my way to heaven
to fuck your goddess
And if we ever go broke,
pray to the snow gods
Here go some money, baby,
have a good time
I gotta go change the world
one pound at a time
Selling dope,
"D" is for the diamonds
"O" is for the owes
"P" is for the paper,
"E" is for everything
Dope gave me everything
Dope, thanks for everything
"D" is for the diamonds,
"O" is for the owes
"P" is for the paper,
"E" is for everything
Dope, you gave me everything
Dope,
thanks for everything.
I like driving around with you, Pop.
Yeah, I bet you do.
Show me your hands.
It's dead out here.
We got a little carried away.
We didn't mean any harm.
- Have a safe night.
- Jonas,
you know what your pop
does for a living, right?
You're a good guy, Pop.
That's right.
This badge makes me bulletproof.
In this life, sometimes you gotta
take what should be given.
You understand?
Always keep sock money
around for a rainy day.
Come on in.
You want that respect?
It's not about the power,
it's about the form.
Practice makes perfect here.
There you go.
that's nice for-- whoa!
Oh! What's going on, man?
What's up? Yo, what's up?
What's going on?
- What y'all doing over here?
- Everything good?
- Yeah yeah.
- Hey, watch your elbow, man.
You gotta make sure
he get the forms right.
Hey hey, listen to this man.
He was a dope QB in high school.
Yo, this is so you right now.
It feels good.
Hey, let's get out of this sun, man.
- Oof.
- It's hot out there.
Yo, remember when
we used to get out of doing laps
by bribing Coach Bishop with bagels
from Cyn's dad's diner?
Yo yo, actually, speaking of Cyn,
- you talk to her lately?
- Nah, I ain't speak to her.
Yo, all I know
is that your TO is fucking crazy.
- Look who talking.
- Yeah.
Yo, would you have
really shot Morrison
if your TO told you to?
Man, y'all got no idea
what goes on in my squad.
Dudes is eating,
and they're getting real money.
People in the mayor's office
answer my boss's calls.
- The shit is crazy.
- I thought we were supposed to be
- each other's eyes, ears and fists.
- Mm-hmm.
That's why I gotta
get y'all on this squad.
Yo, can you please
make that happen
before my crazy TO gets me killed?
Yeah, I'm down.
I'm heading over there later.
Lemme see what I can do.
Yo, lemme get some.
Yo, I guess you didn't get the message
the last time, you little bitch.
Oh shit!
Fuck.
Hyah!
Fuck you!
Get up.
I'm doing right by this kid, right?
Yeah, you doing right by him.
I understand.
Having junior around helps
keep your conscience clean.
You trust him, all right?
- Hey, what's that?
- Homework.
John Jay, student,
criminal psychology.
Do you remember anything?
No.
- I wanna test him.
- Yeah?
Just give him something to do,
give him something small.
- Something small? Yeah. Mmm.
- Yeah.
This is why I don't date cops.
They're too self-absorbed.
- What?
- Nothing.
So you arresting thugs
on the street now?
You can't call yourself a man
and deal drugs to children
and mothers pushing strollers.
That's a piece of shit.
You calling me a piece of shit now?
Huh? Ah!
I'm fucking with you.
But don't fuck
with our representatives
on the street--
that's most important.
- Huh?
- Cool.
You want a chance to move up?
No doubt. You know that.
Go here...
come back with my money.
You mind if I bring my boys with me?
That's how we do it here.
You vouch for 'em, sure, it's okay.
- They're like my brothers.
- Okay.
It's the first time
you're gonna meet this guy.
I want you to lean on him
and be felt. Understood?
Yes sir.
Important.
- Go ahead.
- Whoa whoa whoa whoa.
You ready, Malo?
Go ahead. Go go.
Hold the fuck on!
Ah!
Oh fuck!
- Whoa, fucking slow down.
- You Sully?
- Yeah, I'm Sully.
- G'day, mate.
Do I look like a fucking kangaroo
to you, you prick?
- Who the fuck are you guys?
- We're the new crew.
- Is that right?
- Whoa whoa whoa.
- Easy easy now.
- I wish you would.
Whoa.
We're here to collect Sarcone's money.
Sarcone.
- Where's Lureu?
- Like the man said,
- we're the new crew.
- Just tell us where the money's at.
On the table.
Yeah, we good.
Let's get out of here.
- Listen to your partner.
- Or what?
Or I'm gonna get really pissed.
You ain't scared, huh?
Are you some kind of tough guy?
You hiding something from Joe?
I ain't hiding nothing
and I've got too much
on Sarcone to worry about him.
So let me tell you this:.
fuck you, fuck you
and fuck you!
Oh shit! You're gonna go
fucking down, you fuckers!
- You're gonna pay for that!
- Come on, grab his foot!
- Get me up, you motherfuckers!
- Are you scared yet, motherfucker?
I'm scared for you.
- You gonna fly, motherfucker!
- I'm gonna drop your ass.
- You ain't talking shit now.
- Get me up, you fuckers!
- You ain't talking shit now, right?
- You motherfuckers!
Help me get him in.
Get your ass over here.
You gonna tell me why
you ain't scared of Sarcone,
or I'm gonna fly your ass
out that window like a kite.
I'm more worried about Baez.
Who?
You work for Sarcone,
but you don't know who the real boss is.
His boss, my boss, your boss--
Gabriel Baez.
What you know about Sarcone--
times it by 1 0,
don't even come close to Baez.
- Sarcone got a handler?
- Everyone's got a boss.
Baez has been importing product
into the city for 20 years.
He pays Joe to make sure the traffic
route is all nice and friendly.
Joe used to be the escort.
That's my job now.
I pay him on the back end.
I know spots
of cash that Sarcone--
- he doesn't even know about.
- Go check the other room.
- You keep talking.
- A few years back
a Queen's ADA tried
to put the squeeze on Joe.
Even got an old cop to rat on him.
It didn't stick.
He's still walking the streets.
The aftermath--
everybody that was involved
- went to an early grave.
- You a cop?
No. You just don't get it.
You're his new trained dog.
He'll get you used
to the white powder.
And he'll use you just like
he has all his other dogs.
And you thought Joe was your friend.
Jackpot, baby.
This ain't the half of it.
Who does this belong to?
Technically, my boss.
If he's skimming from Baez
and hiding it from Sarcone,
then that's none
of our business, Malo.
Come on,
we did what we came to do.
Man, let's get out of here.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
New deal-- you're gonna tell me
where those cash spots is at,
you hear me?
Or I'm gonna tell Sarcone
about your new little side hustle,
and you already know
what he gonna do.
You work for me now.
Here's the money from Sully.
What's the worst thing
you ever did, Joe?
The worst thing I ever did
was trust the wrong man.
How do you know when
you trusting the wrong man?
You're questioning me?
Huh? You little shit.
I always made my decision
with my head, not my heart.
I got to where I am in this world
by taking advantage
of people's trust,
and I'm not ashamed of that.
I have a question for you.
Are your boys loyal to you?
- Absolutely.
- Yeah?
I'm not asking you
to vouch for them.
I'm asking for you
to bet your balls, literally.
- I understand. I do.
- Yeah, do you?
'Cause usually
it's the guy closest to your balls
who winds up kicking you in them.
I have a rat inside these walls.
That's the news straight
from One Police Plaza.
Someone in my confidence
is cheating on me.
Don't make me wrong to trust you.
I love you like a son,
but if you or anybody near you
double-crosses me...
as long as I have breath in my lungs,
I will find you and I will cook you.
- You don't have to worry about me.
- I'm not worried, kid.
You're confusing worry and concern.
Sometimes it's a woman who winds up
kicking you in the balls the hardest.
- Is that why you're not married?
- You're damn straight.
I don't trust no bitch,
neither should you,
especially not some bitch shaking
her ass for tips in a fucking bar.
- Understood.
- You gotta do what you gotta do, kid.
Use your head, always, and keep
your balls covered. Remember that.
- Am I clear?
- I hear you loud and clear.
- Shots!
- You got it.
Yo, what's the word?
Are we in or what?
Sarcone'll get at me
when he's ready, man.
- Don't stress it.
- Yo, that thing Sully said
- about an ADA from Queens--
- Yeah?
--what are the chances
he was talking about Vecchio?
- Who the fuck cares?
- Gimme two.
If it's true, Sarcone and Baez
got more to lose by not bringing us on.
Am I right?
I'll talk to Lydia tomorrow,
see what's up.
Yo, I seen this fly Spanish girl. Whoa!
Yo, what's up with Cyn, man?
You talk to her lately?
Now you know she loves you.
How long you gonna make her pay
for her family's bullshit?
Look, man,
Cyn's doing Cyn.
Me? I'm doing me.
Let's move.
Yeah, whatever.
But just-- you know, just in case.
Hey. How you doing?
- I'm good. How are you?
- I'm good.
You come here with these clowns?
No, my girlfriend knows
one of the guys.
I just met them.
Is that okay?
Yo, do I know you?
Yo, I'm talking to you.
- No, son, you don't know me.
- Wanna party?
- Ooh. A cop, huh?
- What the fuck?
Shit. His motherfucking badge
don't mean shit in here.
I think she liked it.
- Yo, who invited you here?
- Man, fuck you.
What?! Who the fuck you think
you're talking to?
- Whoa.
- Coming in here with that badge,
thinking you running shit?
- I gotta go.
- You a punk, huh?
You scared? You nervous?
You nervous?!
- Oh shit!
- Pop off!
Why you pulling the gun, white boy?
We all got guns.
Pop off!
- You nervous?!
- You gonna shoot all of us?
- You scared, white boy?
Get out of the way!
- Police! Get the fuck down!
- What did you do?
What the fuck?
Man, put this shit down. What the--
Stupid, man.
We gotta get outta here.
- Come on, man, get out of here.
- Yeah, fuck you!
- Let's go! Let's go! Come on!
- Fuck you!
- What do we do?
- What they gonna do?
They gonna--
they gonna call the cops?
Hey, man,
he's outta control, man.
It's always the same shit
with this dude.
Mix some up.
You really think
I wouldn't have found out
about your boy shooting
two people at a party?
In front of witnesses? Huh?
- Huh?
- Answer the man.
Your fucking boy's an idiot.
He's a fucking idiot.
You understand that?
He ain't under
my protection like you.
He can get you fucked up.
He can fuck me up.
- He got excited. I'll calm him down.
- He got excited?
He got excited?
I made some calls.
Last night never happened.
I like you, Malo.
Up until now I trusted your judgment.
I know you want him around
because he's your friend,
but if I ever hear
of him fucking up again,
that's it.
It's over.
You understand?
- Let me hear you say it!
- Yes, I understand.
Let me tell you something right now--
you work for me!
Only me, not yourself!
You do what I say!
Snort that line.
Snort the fucking line!
The other one.
- You just don't get it.
- Your boy's a fucking idiot.
- You're his new trained dog.
- He's a fucking idiot.
That thing Sully said
about an ADA from Queens.
He'll get you used to the white powder.
He ain't under my protection.
What are the chances
he was talking about Vecchio?
He can fuck you up.
He can fuck me up. I like you, Malo.
Up till now, I trusted your judgment.
You work for me!
Only me!
Let me hear you say it.
Get outta here.
This fucking kid.
Hey.
I knew you'd call eventually.
You got your wish.
I appreciate everything
you did for me, Lydia,
but I called because I needed
to talk to you about your husband.
What happened to him?
How'd he die?
Kenneth was very ambitious.
He was looking for something big,
something that would
make him a legal rock star.
Then he'd be DA or mayor
or God knows what. Governor?
- So what happened?
- He got what he wanted.
He was approached by a DEA agent
who wanted help in
building a case against
corrupt New York City cops.
Kenneth jumped at the chance.
So how'd he die?
Not well.
They called it a no-note suicide.
Not leaving a note
for me I understand, but...
nothing for his son,
his daughter?
No, that's not Kenneth.
I met Agent Robert Jude
at Kenneth's wake.
He showed me what Kenneth kept
locked away in his office--
a dossier
on one Captain Joseph Sarcone.
Audio, video surveillance,
notebooks with names,
dates, locations.
Basically, he was
a drug dealer in a uniform.
And he had two partners.
Baby, don't be naive.
My husband found
your father's weak spot.
He convinced him
that you were in danger.
He got him to talk on record about
Sarcone and all the shit
they'd been involved in.
That's why my husband
got you into the academy.
He felt guilty.
Guilty for what?
How do you think your father died?
How do you think Kenneth died?
Sarcone's not your friend.
Sarcone's been like a father to me.
Yeah? How long is that gonna last?
My name is Daniel Maldonado.
I'm a detective for the New York City
Police Department.
And the reason
you've come to us here today?
My partners
Dennis Lureu and Joe Sarcone,
and myself,
work for the drug cartel boss
Gabriel Baez.
While on duty,
we transported cocaine, marijuana
and worked as bodyguards
and hired guns
for Gabriel Baez
for the past seven years.
And now I'm afraid
for the life of my wife and my son.
- I love you, Pop.
- I love you too, Jonas.
If Sarcone found out I was
talking to ADA Vecchio,
trying to build a case against him,
they'd fucking kill me.
Climb in the back.
Climb in the back and hide on the floor.
Come on.
And keep quiet. Not a peep.
- Oh yo, man. It's you guys.
- Get out of the car.
Come on, I'm just picking up
a little sock money. It's nothing.
Don't force my hand here.
Danny-- you crossed the line, Danny.
Now get the fuck out of the car.
Your dad and me were partners.
I love you like a son.
If this is about the money,
here, take a piece.
It's not about the money, Danny.
If it ain't about the dough,
then what the hell is it about?
It's about loyalty.
You son of a bitch.
Why? Wait! Wait a minute!
Pop, how can I get you out of there?
I'm fine.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Don't worry about me.
Now get out of the car.
- No, Pop. No. I'm not leaving you!
- Get away from here!
Do it now!
Jonas, do what I tell you, son!
So I want this recorded
in case something happens to me.
Thank you, Karen.
Send him in.
Have a seat.
Daniel Maldonado's son
finally reaches out.
There's no such thing
as coincidence, right?
Your phone number was in the file
Lydia Vecchio gave me.
That's right.
All those pictures,
my father's confession--
none of that was enough
to put Sarcone away?
I want Sarcone more than anyone.
Sometimes in my business,
you do what you can...
- hope for the best.
- That's bullshit.
Something's telling me there's
a little more than hope involved here.
Your father was trying
to do the right thing.
So why are you here,
Officer Maldonado?
Tell me plainly.
I wanna serve Sarcone
to you on a platter.
Aha.
I just need to know how to do it.
- Who is it?
- It's Jonas.
Get to the point, Jonas.
What do you really want for us?
- What I want?
- Yeah.
Why are you here, Jonas?
Huh?
I mean, am I really what you want?
Come here.
Don't be like that.
I want you, Cyn.
It's always been you.
Tell me.
Jonas, you never tell me
that you love me.
I need to hear you say it.
Say it.
You're a piece of shit.
- Come here.
- Get out of my house.
- Don't you fucking touch me.
Get out of my house.
Yeah
You looking at me
then you see what you see
I'm like, hey, oh yeah
And in my city
I'll be running with bulls
I'm like, hey, oh yeah
You can watch it
from the sideline, oh
Sideline, oh, sideline
People watching from the sideline
Sideline, hey
Hey, nigga, you know I'll be good...
Morning, baby.
You want some coffee?
Coffee?
What? What's up?
I just don't trust many people.
I got a lot going on right now.
a lotta things
I gotta get done, that's all.
A.D., what's up?
What you got for me?
I shook Sully down. I found out
that Baez launders money
at the Queens Raceway.
Yo, you ain't gonna believe this.
You know Cyn's brother Angie?
He's running the place.
Find Lucas and wait
for my call, all right?
- A'ight, I'm on it.
- A'ight.
- Hey.
- Lureu.
- What's going on?
- I got something.
Yeah, it's major.
No, Sarcone don't know nothing about it.
You trust me, don't you?
I'll pick you up in 10.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- Hey.
- How you doing?
I've been really lucky today
if you need any suggestions.
Well, I'm actually here
on official police business.
I'm gonna need you to buzz us
into that back door.
Let me call upstairs about that.
Look, if you make that phone call,
you might as well be an accomplice
to everything that goes on here.
Yo, they don't pay me enough for this.
Go around that counter
- and I'm gonna buzz you in.
- All right
Brother, stay the fuck down.
- Where you going? Where you going?
- Fuck.
Stay there or I'll kick you
in your fucking head.
Chill. Yeah yeah.
What are you doing with these guys?
Especially this asshole right here?
- Yo, keep fucking with me, old man.
- You wanna try me?
I can make you vanish.
Poof! You'll be gone.
Just say one more
fucking thing, all right?
Yo, my deal, my crew.
Fuck that.
This isn't good, kid.
This isn't good.
You wanna test Joe?
I can't save you.
- Get your ass up.
- A'ight, man.
- What the fuck, Malo?
- I knew it was just a matter of time
- before I see you again, Angie.
- Wait, you know this guy?
- Yeah, I know him.
- Why you didn't tell me you know
- this guy? What the hell's going on?
- My high school sweetheart--
this is her brother right here--
Angelo. Angie the Greek.
He's the one got us started in the game,
hustling a corner, slinging.
- Right, Angie?
- This is the thanks I get
- for starting you out?
- Found out his sister fell for me,
beat her within inches of her life.
Remember that, Angie?
- A real class act.
- Go to hell, Malo.
You think I forgot about that autograph
you signed on my forehead
with that baseball bat? Huh?
You know who
this place belongs to?
Gabriel Baez.
You ever hear of him?
This is Gabriel Baez's place?
You know who Gabriel Baez is?
We work with this guy, for God's sake.
A'ight, a'ight, look,
Iet's-- let's just get outta here.
- Don't touch a fucking thing.
- Easy easy.
- Whoa whoa whoa.
- You gonna let 'em put guns in my face?
You gonna put a gun
in my fucking face?
You better listen to him, Malo,
'cause when Baez finds you,
he's gonna watch me
fist you with this hand
right before he kills you.
Are you high?
You wanna make a move on Joe?
After Joe's finished with you,
there ain't gonna be nothing left
for Baez to hurt.
- Do you hear me, kid?
- You're a cop?
That's funny.
Come on, Malo. There's enough money
to go around for all of us, man.
- You ain't gotta do this.
- Shut the fuck up.
- You still mad? That was years ago.
- Now look at you.
- For Christ's sake, do something!
- Don't do it.
- Shoot that pig!
- We ain't here for that, man!
Do it!
- Shit!
- It's a big mistake, kid.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
What are you thinking about?
Yeah!
What the fuck, man?
Get some rope or something.
Tie him up.
- Take all that shit.
- Oh shit, man.
Adios, old friend.
I don't know, man.
- You sure about this, Malo?
- Of course I'm sure.
- You got something you wanna say?
- Yo, I don't give a fuck.
Come on, let's go.
We are exactly where
we're supposed to be, my friends.
The sky's the limit, right?
I don't think so anymore.
Hey, remember when we were kids
and we used to play cops
and robbers in the rain?
Yeah, you never wanted
to be the cop.
I do now.
For all the wrong reasons.
Yo, what the fuck is
that supposed to mean?
I don't wanna do this anymore.
What, you ain't down for us no more?
No, I'm not down for this shit anymore.
- Oh yeah? Yeah?
- Yeah, you heard me.
- You got a problem with that?
- Shut up, man.
Both of you just shut
the hell up, all right?
Chill the hell out, man.
Look, if you want out,
A.D., you can go.
It ain't gonna change nothing.
Badges ain't change us.
We're still us.
You know, badge or no badge,
this is bullshit.
Just as bad as Sarcone is, Malo.
And the crazy thing is you like it.
And this asshole over here wants
to grow up to be just like you
if you don't get us all killed first.
That's how you feel?
I'm done, man.
- I'm out.
- Was it really that bad?
You think I'd leave if it wasn't?
Don't listen to that pussy.
You got it all under control
like you always do. Right, my dude?
Shut up, Lucas.
You've been telling me what to do
since we was little kids.
I'm tired of it.
What do you think she'd do
if she knows you killed Angie?
You think Cyn would forgive you
for killing her brother?
And what about Sarcone?
What do you think he'd do he knows
you're stabbing him in the back?
Don't you play all high
and mighty with me, bitch.
'Cause you can't fuck with me,
but I can fuck with you though.
You remember that.
Gabriel.
How does this happen?
Completely unacceptable.
Yeah yeah, I know,
I know, I know.
- You need to fix this now.
- Yeah, don't worry. I got it.
How could the racetrack get hit?
- What am I paying you for?
- Yeah, I got it.
- You need to make this right.
- I got it.
- You have two days to find my money.
- Okay okay.
It's Lureu.
At the beep, say it.
- I'm out.
- Oh yeah.
- Hey.
- Where the fuck are you?
Something very messy just went down.
You sound worried, Joe.
- Have you seen your partner lately?
- No, why?
I'm in a spot
where I can get touched real bad.
An associate just got jacked
for nine digits
and that just don't happen
without me knowing about it.
I don't know what the fuck is going on.
Lureu's not picking up his phone
and I can't find him
and I don't know what to think now.
Sounds like you know
who the rat is, Joe.
- How much did he steal?
- I can't cover it.
- And I didn't say it was Lureu.
- But you think it is.
- Want me go find him?
- Nah.
If he don't wanna be found, he's got a
million places to lay up and stay high.
- That's what I'm worried about.
- Want me hit the streets,
- make some things happen?
- No, what I want you to do
is I want you to meet
my friend Gabriel Baez,
and I want you to calm him down.
Okay, whatever you want, Joe.
Fuck Lureu.
I got you, right?
That's right.
You can always trust me.
Okay.
My name's Jonas Maldonado, Malo.
Are you wearing a wire,
Mr. Maldonado?
- No sir.
- Joe speaks very highly of you.
Thank you, sir.
It is disrespectful of him
to send a messenger in his place.
Don't you agree, Mr. Maldonado?
Speak, messenger.
You think Joe sent me here
to pacify you,
but he sent me here to lie to you.
Where is Joe, Mr. Maldonado?
Somewhere counting your money.
Please do choose
your next words very carefully.
Explain.
None of what
went down was my idea.
Are you about to admit
to stealing from me?
I was there, yes,
but it's Sarcone that's screwing you.
He's trying to use me to do it
and I don't wanna be in the middle
when you screw him back.
But you're still in the bed,
aren't you, Mr. Maldonado?
Now where is my property?
Sarcone has it, but I can get it back.
- All of it.
- Why do you betray your patrn?
These are the transcripts
from the DEA's wiretaps
inside Sarcone's bar.
He's over a barrel.
He'll give everyone up
to save his own ass.
All they really want is you.
Robbing you is just his way
of fucking you a little deeper
before he hands you over.
So are we in business?
What do you want, Mr. Maldonado?
I want Sarcone's seat at your table.
First my property.
Half the money
and the product is with Lureu.
Here's an address, key to a car--
half your stuff is in it.
Sarcone has the other half.
I'll bring him out in the open so
you can deal with him how you see fit.
I'm really resourceful, Mr. Baez.
You're dismissed.
Stay close, man.
- Motherfuckers!
- You stay down!
You drive.
- Joe.
- Did you find him?
No, I ain't find him,
but I found half the money at his place.
- It look like he did it.
- Ahh.
- Baez is gonna be pissed.
- I know, I know,
but relax, man.
Baez don't know who jacked him.
He should be happy
you found half his stuff.
Maybe ask for a finder's fee.
- Remember who's doing who a favor.
- A'ight.
- Hello, this is Jude.
- Hello.
Agent Jude, I think all the pieces
are falling in place.
I just need a few more things.
You know, I understand you wanting
to avenge your father's death and all,
but what happens after that, huh?
I mean, you ever actually thought
about respecting the badge?
Perhaps aiming some
of that angst in the right direction?
No, I ain't thought about that lately.
So what do you need?
Kill me?
You wanna kill me?
You ain't got the balls to face me
man to man! Huh?
Oh, so you're gonna take me out?
It's like that?
Well, come on then! Come on!
Piece of shit.
- Is that the rest of my property?
- It's right there, sir.
Like you predicted, Joe did call--
add insult to injury.
You're clever, Mr. Maldonado.
You satisfied?
Remind me-- what is my incentive
for not shooting you
or killing you right now?
I'm clever.
You just said it.
Joe underestimated you.
I will not.
I've proven my loyalty to you.
Not yet,
but soon you will.
Oh shit.
What the fuck is going on here?
Hup! Take it easy.
What is this?
It's a test.
- Who's the girl?
- I know that your friend is a liability
that Joe tolerates just
to keep you close to him.
I really don't know why.
I don't deal with liabilities.
Unfortunately,
the girl was with your friend
when we picked him up.
She's an innocent bystander.
Now you're dealing with me,
Mr. Maldonado.
You're gonna shoot one of them
or I'll kill them both.
You choose, Mr. Maldonado.
- Hey.
- All right, let's start it. Let's go.
- Everybody in line.
- Nice.
Here we go.
Come on, you little sissies.
Let's go. Move it!
What-- what's up, man?
Guys, come on!
Let's move move!
It's good what you're doing, man.
Hut hut! Hey hey, hold on.
You know, my TO was right.
I've learned a lot about myself.
You could too.
32, grip the ball. Set. Hut hut!
There you go. There you go.
I gotta go back to the kids, man.
You be good.
You look like shit.
Sarcone is in the car.
Look sharp. This is it, folks.
Still no word from Lureu?
Yeah.
You know why I trust you, kid?
- 'Cause you know I won't fuck you over?
- Yeah.
When's the last time you seen Baez?
Not long enough.
I gotta see that prick tonight.
As long as that money
come through nice
- twice a month, right?
- It takes a certain type of individual
to do what we do, to have the balls
to be the type of men we are.
You gotta want it-- all of it.
Good guys, bad guys--
that's all bullshit
when it comes down to it.
It's about money, fear and respect.
Like you, I always wanted all three.
Iike your father did when--
when we started out.
Do not let them out of your sight.
Copy that.
Tell me the story
about that plane heist.
- I love that story.
- What, how me and your dad started?
- Attaboy.
- Me and your father used to pick up
Baez's mules at JFK cargo
and escort 'em through the city.
We'd babysit through
distribution, collection
around the city,
then we'd escort 'em back to JFK.
Easy-peasy, 1 0 Gs easy.
- Nice.
- Yeah, 1 0 Gs
before skimming off the top of cargo.
That's how I built my empire,
stealing dope from that--
you know, dope.
- So when did it go bad?
- Between me and Baez?
No, between you and my father.
I told you everything
you need to know, kid.
Tell me what you think I don't know.
You know...
when it came down to it,
your father was afraid
to make the tough decisions,
so he made the wrong ones.
Shake the tree, Malo.
Come on.
I've always done right by you, kid.
- Like a father to me.
- Like a father.
And I wouldn't offer you my hand
if I thought you were gonna bite it.
I just wanna know the truth.
Attaboy.
I never ever,
not for one instant, thought your father
would or could rat us out,
but the facts are what they are.
He made a deal with an ADA.
We're talking serious jail time
for everybody, including me.
Everybody was gonna be shamed
and disgraced in the papers,
the whole nine yards.
And the word came down
on Monday morning. It had to get done.
Why you?
Because l-- I was his partner.
It was a test of my loyalty.
Was it them or was it him?
What would you do?
It was a Wednesday.
We followed him
to Roosevelt lsland and--
All units, stand ready.
And he was pulled over
by a patrol car, of all things.
We waited for them to leave
and then we went over.
I made him get out. I...
Your father was a--
your father was a...
he was a rat.
Take him
when he exits the car.
Would you do it again?
Your father was afraid
to make the tough decisions.
Men like us are built to make
those kinds of decisions.
That's who we are.
Can you do that?
Can you make those tough decisions?
I already have.
Take him. Go. Go go!
I'm gonna go.
Get your fucking hands off me.
Man down.
Where'd that shot come from?
Check the rooftops now!
It's gotta be Baez! God damn it!
Everybody out there right now!
Get up on those rooftops, all units!
Shut down everything!
I don't want anybody
getting out of this area,
not in a five-block radius!
- I want everybody to move now!
- Fall back. I'm going in.
What the hell happened?
I need a car on that end.
I need a car on this end.
Thanks for not
giving up on me, Cyn.
- You always get what you want?
- I did my part.
Oh, I know what you did
and I know what you're planning.
With my help, you got Baez
to clear Sarcone out of the picture
and now you get to take
Sarcone's place at Baez's table.
That's very clever.
Why don't you try
working for the good guys for a change?
I know you got it in you.
You think you know me.
I'm not a good guy.
All right, part-time then.
Part-time good guy, like a--
a freelancer.
Freelancer, huh?
If you're gonna wear the badge,
take the responsibility
that goes with it, huh?
Who knows? You might even find
a little self-respect too.
Agent Jude,
this is an old friend of mine.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Agent Jude works for the DEA.
He's my new boss.
- Nice to have met you.
- Likewise.
I'll be going undercover.
What does that mean for us?
Look...
this is our time, Cyn.
Trust me.
Jonas.
I love you, Cyn.
Yeah!
- Decoy.
- Unh, shotgun flow
Hit 'em with the sawed-off,
killing all these haters
Make 'em all get hauled off
Bitch, look at me,
act like you don't see a king
Make you kneel down and kiss
the motherfucking ring
I ain't gonna hide,
you ain't gotta look for me
Taking back every single thing
that was took from me
So fly, burn into the sky
Screaming "Fuck the whole flow scene"
E, tell 'em why
I got the money and the power
I'm ready for the rain,
it's a shower
I'm running this city
I'm running this town, yeah
I'm Mr. Bad Guy, but it's all good
Yes, you tough,
but it's all good
This city,
I'm running this town, hey
Whoa, now I'm on top
I'm on--
whoa, now I'm on top
Whoa whoa, whoa whoa
Whoa, now I'm on top,
I'm on
Baby, I'm a bass,
ain't nobody fucking with me
- Come on
- Why can't you see
It's you and the world
against me?
Baby, I'm a rapper
I don't even care, so don't tell me
what you think and feel
- Hold on
- Remember, I won't stop
Surprised when
you see me on top
I got the money and the power
I'm ready for the rain,
it's a shower
I'm running this city
I'm running this town, yeah
I'm Mr. Bad Guy, but it's all good
Yes, you tough,
but it's all good
This city,
I'm running this town, hey
- Ho ho, ho ho
- Yeah, yeah
- Ho ho
- Yeah
- Ho ho, ho ho
- Yeah, yeah
- Ho ho
- Yeah
- Ho ho, ho ho
- Yeah, yeah
Yeah
Ho ho
Ho ho, ho ho
- Ho ho
- Whoa, now I'm on top, I'm on
Whoa, now I'm on top, I'm on
Whoa whoa
Whoa, now I'm on top,
I'm on
Whoa, now I'm on top, I'm on
Whoa, now I'm on top
Whoa whoa
Whoa, now I'm on top, I'm on
Yeah
Yeah...
Decoy.
Ho ho
Ho ho, ho ho
Ho ho.