Hey, Erika, how is your
new boyfriend next door?
He's not next door, he's behind me,
I ain't never even seen him.
Who are your neighbors then,
Gomer Pyle and his brother Goober?
Eat shit...
What was that?
Hey, come back here, faggot!
I said come back here!
Who's there?
Are you asking me?
Are you spying me?
No, I'm working on my mud fort,
what are you doing?
I'm planting vegetables...
Thanks for moving in here,
now the kids in school call me faggot
and walk on the other side of the hall...
I have to live somewhere...
Why don't you go inside, until
I get done working on my garden.
Why?
So I don't have to worry
about catching something,
and dying!
It can't be transmitted through the air.
Just to be on the safe side,
I think you should go inside.
But I'm working on my mud fort...
Hey, what would you do if I come over
there and whooped your ass?
How long would that take?
About ten seconds...
I would wait until you were finished
and then I'd continue working on my mud fort.
You mean you'd just let me beat you up?
I'd try to stop you,
but I probably won't be able to...
I'm not very big.
In that case it would only take 5 seconds...
So is that what you're gonna do?
Maybe later...
Hello...
are you still there?
Shit!
Son of a bitch!
I warned you what would happen
if you got all dirty again...
One, two, three, the winner!
There's some boys outside playing baseball.
If you can go make the effort
to get to know them,
it'll be very nice...
I'm gonna go out with some
girls from the office tonight,
so cook yourself a dinner in microwave.
Have you thought anymore about Colorado?
I'm not going to camp!
Yeah but if you just give it a chance,
you'd meet some extra friends...
Why can't I go see Dad?
We'll call him,
if he says yes,
I'll put you on the next plane...
You know, you and his little friend Cindy,
can go to the movies
and get in for half price!
She's 23, mom!
Amazing, old enough to drink!
Yeah, but she doesn't...
Man! I was on World Eight!
You know it's not good to spend too
much times with these games.
What a bullshit! It's boring.
I have nothing against going fishing,
but I'm not touching the worms.
- I'll take care the worms.
- I will.
- Yeah, we'll see about that...
Good night.
Got ya first!
They ended up giving me two pints of blood.
I guess it's a lot for baby.
My grandmother said
you're going to hell,
she says you'll suffer eternal torture
of a billion flames,
hotter than the center of the Sun.
Then she must be some kind of genius...
What?
My doctor's really smart,
he says he has no idea what happens
to people after they die...
If your grandmother knows,
she must be a genius.
She's a clerk at K-Mart.
Maybe she's just an underachiever.
No, she's an idiot.
So maybe I won't go to hell after all.
Are you sure those germs of yours
don't travel through the air?
Yeah, Why?
How old are you?
Eleven.
Jesus, you're a midget!
Well, if you look at the lower limit
of what's considered normal for my age,
I'm only 4 inches shorter.
Oh...
So...
do you know how to play Battleship?
G9...
Miss.
Damn!
Are you sure?
Yup...
D7...
Miss.
I have to eat my lunch now.
Why don't you just eat
whenever you're hungry?
Cause if I only eat whenever
I was hungry, I wouldn't be here.
Do you wanna go to Peterson's?
- What is that?
- It's a supermarket.
Food...
You got any money?
In my bedroom.
What should we do with him?
You wanna burn him?
Where did you get it all?
Allowance...
and fines.
Fines?
It's a little hard to explain.
This is great, since I know
where the store is,
I'll be a the navigator
and you be treasurer.
What's a treasurer will do?
He carries all the money
and pays for things...
I'm to supposed to pay for both of us?
I'm navigating for both of us,
you want to be fair don't you?
How far is Peterson's?
Why?
If I walk too far I get kinda tired.
it'seems to me the depth of
the water would be the key...
Obviously in the middle of the
ocean the shark would win.
And on dry land the lion would win.
So how much water are we talking about?
2 and a half feet.
And how big is the shark?
Eleven feet.
I'd still sayin' the lion would win...
Wrong!
How can you be sure?
Cause they did research on
Stanford University,
the shark won easily.
They just let two animals killed
each other at the college?
No you idiot, they just had a fight
long enough to see who was gonna win,
and then the trainers pulled them apart.
How?
Haven't you ever heard of a leash?
Never heard a shark on a leash...
Or there's a lot of things
you've never heard of.
I guess that's true...
Hold on.
My mom says that every drop
of water that lands in the water here,
eventually end up in Mississippi.
That means it goes to my dad,
he still in New Orleans.
What does he do?
You've ever heard a rock
group called Led Zeppelin?
No...
They really famous,
you know who the guitar player is?
Your dad?
No, the guy named Jimmy Page,
my daddy,
sold him his car insurance.
for a Pontiac TransAm...
Know what you're gonna get?
I don't know, it's been a
long time since I've any candy.
My mom has me eats a lot of vegetables.
Come here...
We allowed to do this?
Of course! How else are you supposed
to know what you're gonna get!
- Wow!
- Not bad, huh...
Well you got your money...
Get out of the road!
Go on now!
Asshole!
3 degrees to the right,
aim fire!
You missed!
Hey, how much did you pay for that faggot?
You guys took a wrong turn,
this is a no homo zone.
I ain't a homo!
And neither is he!
He got from a blood transfusion...
What tell what's that awful smell?
Well, you see we were walking across the grass
and we accidentally stepped in your mother.
What did you say?
You can't hit it us all with that!
I only be aiming it at you...
Come on then...
And what about your little brother, huh?
What about him?
When he fell of the Jungle Jim at school,
they'd to take him to the hospital,
he could've caught something in...
Yeah, but he didn't...
But he could've!
Then everybody be calling him
faggot and queer,
and he'd get sick and die!
And you got homo on his headstone,
and when your mother went
to bring him flowers,
she would see her little Eddie Horner homo,
You know the worst part of that would be?
probably he before he died,
a bunch of assholes like you,
who ain't sick and thought
it might be fun just
to beat the shit out of him!
Come on man, let's beat!
Sorry you're sick...
Thanks!
What'd you do that for?
Get 'em!
So long faggots!
Don't you think we should slow down?
- How?
- Anyway would be fine!
Ma'am get out of the way!
- Move it!
- Move your ass!
Oh God!
Hold on! Go!
Go!
So they really think I'm a faggot.
Now all of a sudden I'm yelling
the same stuff at them.
But they know I'm not a faggot,
cause a faggot won't yell
a faggot back,
Now that's why you should yell faggot too...
Well, just wouldn't be right saying that...
Why the hell not!
They were nice to me at the hospital,
they played games with me...
You played games with homos?
Just talk about something else...
Sometimes I don't know about you.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing...
Do you wanna play Nintendo?
No... I'm getting kinda tired.
I think I should go take a nap.
We should work on the mud fort tomorrow,
you want to?
Okay.
Leave it...
Why can I eat in living room?
I don't get home for dinner that often
when I do, I want us to be together.
It's part being a family, isn't it?
You know some woman saw that little AIDS boy
down at the Peterson's yesterday..
It's in the newspaper?
No... Jan told me...
I've seen him in the backyard,
I didn't know he left the house.
The other day I heard him coughing.
I said I heard him coughing.
Oh, I don't think
you have to worry about anything,
with that fence there,
you're not going to catch anything...
What if wants to come over and play?
Oh Erik, think of some excuse,
you're so good at that...
What if I bump into him out in the street?
Well it's common sense,
you just keep a safe distance.
What's a safe distance?
7 feet,
guess that rules out sleepovers.
My mom wants you to come to dinner.
Well,
mom's working late, so... cool.
Well there's something
I have to warn you about...
What?
She likes to call me Sweetie.
Sweetie?
You gotta promise not to laugh.
You want some more carrots Sweetie?
No, thanks.
Are we ready for dessert then?
- I'll try a little.
- Yeah I bet.
You didn't even finish
your meatloaf, Love Muffin!
Would you shut up!
She's not gonna hear me sweetheart!
Be quiet.
You don't worry about it sweetie,
she's not gonna hear me!
Here we go!
Dexter tells me you have a girlfriend.
Yeah, well I did, but I have to dump her.
Spin, spin, spin...
His father has a girlfriend, named Cindy.
Yes, as soon as they get settled in
their new apartment,
I maybe goin' down there.
And how's your mom feel about this.
Actually we haven't really talk it out much
yet...
Well, I'd love to meet her.
She works quite a bit...
20, 22 hours a day...
What she do?
A real estate
and at night she works at a minimart.
The one downtown...
25 cents!
I got you!
Whenever I catch her twirling her hair,
she has to pay me a quarter.
25 cents and this!
Are you gonna finish that?
Well doctor says
"it's completely safe",
but when it comes to
other people's children,
we've decided not
to take any chances.
Forgot...
I've got plan...
Just as soon as they find the cure,
we're headin' out to Baskin Robbins,
and ordering one of those monster sundaes
where everybody just digs right in...
It's a good plan...
What is it?
She's afraid they might
not find the cure in time...
Banzai!
Oh my God!
He's afraid of heights...
Hey, what if they don't find the cure?
I'm sure they will eventually...
But what if they're looking
in the wrong place?
What do you mean?
Have you ever seen
that movie "Medicine Man"?
We found a cure for cancer,
and all you can say is: "I know"?
What is it?
Vermilliad. A flower.
You want me start eating flowers?
We're not going to worry about what
flowers, leaves maybe even pine cones.
It can't hurt to try!
My mom has me eating lots of vegetables,
especially broccoli.
All I ever eat is candy and I never get sick.
Hey, that's it!
Somebody gets sick and
all they eat is fruits and vegetables,
it's the one thing they stop eating!
This is stupid.
About fifty years ago, a doctor knows
some mold was growing on his bread,
he started feeding it to people...
and everybody said "this is stupid",
you know what it out turned to be? Aspirin!
It's still a hundred-point-two.
- How are ya feeling?
- Okay.
Let's start "Butterfinger"
combine with "Bubbelicious".
I am not sure I understand
why you have to try this all stuff too.
Don't you know anything
about scientific method?
Little.
You have to have a control group,
so you'll see if the results are uniform...
You're in control group?
Yup.
Hallo...
Is Dexter here?
Yes, he is, but he's grounded.
Why?
Because he used up all his money,
buying candy.
How long is he grounded for?
Till tomorrow...
Why's that?
We're gonna play submarine.
Grounded is grounded, so
you're gonna have to wait till tomorrow...
I understand.
Just a minute, okay?
Dexter, get your ass down here!
Why?
Coz I'm changing your punishment,
you have to play with Erik!
- Thanks mom!
- Here's your paddle.
Watch the flowers!
How are you feeling?
Terrible.
Told you candy was a stupid idea...
Hey, what'd ya think of this one?
I'm wondering about something...
Where do bugs go to bathroom?
It's not on leaves.
How can you be sure?
Because bugs eat leaves,
not even bugs are stupid
enough to shit on their own food...
Now, what do you say?
Go ahead...
Oh, tastes like crap!
No shit, don't you know
where bugs go to bathroom?
Sweetened crap.
It looks too weird...
You can't be afraid to try...
I'm afraid to touch it.
How do you feel?
Okay.
She's here!
Dexter?
You got me!
Is your friend Erik staying
for dinner again?
Wakkah!
That means yes, white woman!
Okay, hey, Allie.
Settle down! Go get some yogurt.
Wakkah!
You guys really very well nuts today!
Did Dexter take his nap?
"Oekoo"
Sorry.
Good night.
I need to take Dexter
to his doctor tomorrow,
we should back at one...
- Good night
- Good night.
Shit! The notebook!
Where have you been?
- I thought you won't...
- I asked you a question!
Gordy Johnson asked me
if I wanna go to the mall with him,
and I didn't think you'd won't mind.
Is that that doctor's boy?
Yeah...
You really should've left a note for me...
Maybe Gordy would like to go
with us to see the fireworks.
Maybe...
These are pennies?
There's one, two...
three... that's a dime,
isn't it? Oh, dear.
There!
Thank you very much, so neat of you!
Oh, my God!
The mysterious Dr. Fishburn
derives the extract from a plant,
found deep in the Louisiana bayou.
At a backwater location he refuses to reveal...
I knew it, it was a plant...
The government's trying
to suppress its findings...
Bastard!
Why would they do that?
Because they're embarrassed.
I'm mean, think about the money
they spend each year,
and this Dr. Fishburn got goes out in his
backyard in his underwear one morning,
and picks up the cure for AIDS!
Maybe your mom could drive us down there!
It's right here!
I don't want you boys thinking that
something like this cannot happen,
but if it does and Dr. Jensen's gonna
know about it before the National...
"Examiner"
Examiner!
Why don't we call him?
No!
Why don't we wait till your next appointment
and you can ask the man!
It's for after lunch.
Like I didn't see that?
You say your dad lives
in New Orleans, right?
Yeah...
Maybe he can get that some
of that secret extracts
mail it to us...
Maybe it's already here...
That one again?
Yup...
I just don't like it...
Look at that thing,
he's got all the look like a plant from the bayou,
then I don't know bayous.
This is the worse yet!
My grandma says, that the
worst it tastes, the better it works.
Your K-Mart clerk grandma?
Drink!
I need to talk to Erik,
some kind of leaf that he took in...
Erik has something to do with this?
Erik, Erik...
I need to know what you gave Dexter...
I need to know what kind
of leaves you gave him,
it's poisonous and he told me that
you have written it down in a notebook.
Here's one it this,
it's down by the river...
Where? Where the bridge crosses...
Back inside...
What were you thinking?
What!
Tell me!
Not measles, not chicken pox, aids!
What're you trying to do?
What are you trying to do!
Fucking kill us both?
There's gonna be some big changes around here!
Big changes!
I don't really care what do you think,
I don't want him over here,
I don't want my son over there!
I don't care that they're friends,
I don't want them
associating with each other.
Period!
He's gonna be fine. Thank god!
His mother is officially on notice,
she allows him to see you
I'm gonna have her ass
thrown in jail.
And for you,
on Monday morning your
ass are going to summer camp!
Hey Dad?
Sorry, we missed you. Cindy and I are in Lake Charleston
until Tuesday. Call you as soon as we get back...
When we're get down there,
where we're gonna sleep,
where we gonna eat...
We're not worry about that,
I already talked to my dad,
he said we could stay with him...
I might even be able to
talk him to take us fishing.
I can't.
You have to Dex!
Tomorrow morning I'm out of here.
And this time she would be
really really worried.
She's already worried because you're sick.
And you and I both know that the
only thing that's gonna make her happy,
is when we're going to New Orleans
and Dr. Fishburn has the cure...
Dear mom... I'm fine with Erik...
but I brought along the medicines
so there's no reason to worry.
We're planning to be careful
and sensible.
Whatever you do make sure you
remember to tape Star Wars
8 PM channel 5.
I love you very much, sincerely Dexter...
The biggest fish in the world,
he weights over 2000 pounds...
That's why they calling him
the General Steur.
What if he decides to take us over?
He wouldn't know that...
One time this kid,
he went swimming after eating,
and he got a stomach cramp,
and he started to dry on
but the General Steur grabbed him by shirt
and put him on the shore.
How fast do you think we're going?
3 miles an hour.
How far is this New Orleans?
About 12 hundred miles.
How long will it takes us to get there?
Hey, where you headed?
Hampton
Minneapolis
Memphis
Centralia
Peoria
How much you got?
What?
Wanna ride you gotta
pay for the gas, you know...
Where you headed?
New Orleans...
I can give you 20 dollars.
20 bugs?
You wanna go to New Orleans for 20 bugs?
I don't know, I think you're gonna
have to do better than that.
Forty, it's all I got.
Hey Pony, we ready to float, man!
What are you saying, we locked and loaded?
Alright.
162 dollars,
check my pockets.