- Come on, come on, come on.
- All right, here we go.
Take a seat, buddy!
Come on. It was a good play.
Are you gonna be like this all day?
I don't know. Is it gonna be like this all day?
- I don't know.
- It's up to you.
- I have no room to sit.
- I got no room to sit.
I'm sitting next to a guy who's sitting
like he's at home on the toilet
with his legs spread.
Please don't crowd people.
Relax, please. Look at me.
- I am relaxed.
- Look how I'm sitting.
- Why are you sitting like that?
- Because... What do you think?
Why'd you wake me up for this shit?
Because I'm trying to relax
and have a nice day.
Sweating in the sun like a Tijuana whore.
Ice-cold soda!
Get your soda here!
On the right. Coming down there.
Pass that on down there.
Hey, hot dog guy, can I get six hot dogs
down here, please?
Right away.
And make it right, please.
You know, with the mustard
and the ketchup and the relish.
Don't make me hit you up for more.
I thought we were going
to Wiener Circle after this.
- We will.
- Then why are you getting hot dogs?
Pass this down, please.
You can keep the change.
Do you want one of the hot dogs?
You can have a hot...
You want a hot dog?
Do you want a hot dog, miss?
- No. Thank you.
- You can have one.
- That's okay.
- Go ahead. You can have a hot dog.
- No, I don't want one.
- Excuse me, sir?
Would you mind passing the lady
one of the hot dogs?
- I'm good, thanks.
- You don't have to share.
- You can have your own.
- Thanks. That's really nice of you.
- Just have one, please.
- Okay, give me a hot dog.
Somebody give her a hot dog. I got...
The big guy can't eat all of them. Have one.
- Have you ever had one before?
- A hot dog?
- At the ballpark?
- I have. I believe I have.
- Okay, good.
- Thank you.
- Well, enjoy this one.
- Thanks.
- Do you like mustard?
- No, I'm okay.
It's much better with a topping. Here.
I'm just kidding, I'll give you two.
- Cheers!
- Thanks.
We'll share it.
It's a good dog. I like the hot dog. I know.
That's nice.
You have a problem
with me eating a hot dog, guy?
I'm trying to watch the game
and have a hot dog.
- I'll smack him in his head.
- No, just leave him alone.
- Hey, you want to go get a drink?
- No.
I'm with somebody, sorry.
Who? The guy with
the tucked-in shirt and the visor?
What, is that like a brother?
The guy was not your brother, then.
- Who is this guy?
- He's not my brother.
Who's this... I'm getting mad now.
I'm jealous. Who is this guy?
- Who are you?
- I don't know. I'm kidding with you.
Who's the guy with the tucked-in stuff?
Is that a boyfriend?
Uh, it's...
- I'm going.
- Do you think you'll marry him?
- What?
- 'Cause I know you've thought about it.
The first time you laid eyes on him,
you probably thought,
"I wonder if I could marry this guy in
plaid shorts who tucks his shirt in. No way. "
Then when you kissed him,
you said, "I can't believe it.
"I had a lot to drink tonight.
I'm kissing the tucked-in guy. "
- My point is, if you're not gonna marry him...
- Yeah.
...and if it's not forever,
then you really don't have anything to lose
in taking me up on my offer.
- Uh-huh. Well, I'm gonna go.
- Okay. Me, too.
- Okay.
- To where? On an ice-breaking first date?
- Well, no, I don't think...
- Listen.
If you want to stay off the market
while you're with
I'm-not-the-one-but-I'm-comfortable,
then you can do that.
But for all you know, I just offered you
a get-out-of-bored-love-for-free card
with no strings attached.
- God, you're crazy.
- No, I'm not crazy.
And a lot of times people go,
"Oh, that's crazy,"
and then they go, "It's genius. "
That's what happened
when the person invented fire.
They burned that witch. And guess what,
then they got warm and they ate good stuff.
Now, where are we headed to?
Let's not make this weird,
- 'cause I'm not good on dates.
- No. You know what?
I'm better just to kind of hang out and,
if we don't have fun,
- I might go my separate way.
- Okay.
I'm not committing to anything.
I'll go hang out with you for a little bit.
- That's not gonna happen.
- But I can't say for sure.
All right, all right, everybody.
Welcome to Three Brothers Bus Tours.
I'm brother number two.
It's good to have you here.
That's right, there's plenty
of seats here up front.
I promise I won't bite. I'm not a biter.
I'm psyched to have you here.
Okay, a couple quick ground rules.
Please don't jump off the bus.
Weird. Not fun for anybody.
Also, no throwing objects at pedestrians,
unless, of course, they deserve it. Okay?
We are not at work today.
We are on vacation today.
And if you can't blow it
out here on the big funny bus,
where the hell can you?
I do split the tips
with my driver, Shondra.
We don't want her back out turning tricks.
That was a weird time for everyone.
Seriously. Honest to God.
And I was a customer. Long time ago.
Come on, everybody, let's get loose!
I'm gonna ask you once.
Show me that you mean it.
Don't make me ask you twice.
Are you ready to see Chicago?
That's what I'm talking about.
Shondra, put this baby in the air.
Let's get the blood flowing.
Let's get everyone up and let's loosen it up.
Coming up here, you're gonna notice
one of the only buildings
to survive the fire of 1871.
That is the original Chicago Water Tower
and Pumping Station.
Happy Holidays.
Marilyn Dean Gallery.
The artist was inspired
by the neoclassical movement.
No, she doesn't.
But wanted to reflect it
with an abstract bent.
Okay, bye-bye.
- And how much is it?
- $35,000.
Happy Holidays. Marilyn Dean Gallery.
Hold, please.
- Will you excuse me for a moment?
- Sure. Go ahead.
- Christopher?
- Yes, sweetie.
- Hi, honey.
- Hi.
- Christmas was months ago.
- Don't remind me. I miss it so much.
Yeah, I know. But today is not a holiday.
I know for a fact that people like
my spirit on the phone
and they dig the energy that I give them.
Okay. I'm just saying, I don't think
Marilyn Dean will "dig" the energy.
Oh, no. She's the one that told me
to be creative. So...
I know. It's just... Okay.
What is the next holiday coming?
The Fourth of July, is that what's next?
Well, if you want to get technical,
there's Memorial Day,
there's Flag Day.
Some people recognise Father's Day
as a holiday. I don't.
I get it. I get it. Well, on those days
you can say, "Happy Holidays. "
Every other day,
"Good morning, good afternoon,
"good evening, Marilyn Dean Gallery. " Okay?
Okay.
- I'm so sorry about that.
- Oh, no.
So, now this is a new piece by Zakrzewska.
What do you think of this?
- Can I be honest with you?
- Please.
Other than taking
an art history class in college,
which I pretty much slept through,
I don't have the first clue about art
or how to go about buying it.
I mean, like that painting.
I mean, I don't see the point in buying
something that I could have done myself.
Yeah. I completely agree with you.
You know, an art teacher of mine once said,
"Never buy a piece of art
that you don't have to have. "
You know, don't worry about who
the artist is or how much it's worth.
I mean, you have to live with it every day.
You have to walk by it every day.
You know, you have to really love it.
You have to really appreciate it.
It's kind of like picking a mate.
- Hey, honey!
- Hi.
- How's it going?
- It's good.
- Oh, wow. You got a lot happening.
- I know.
- Very exciting.
- I am starving.
- Oh, careful. That's really... That's very hot.
- Oh, that's hot, hot, hot.
- Yep.
- Jesus.
Hey, honey, you've got to really...
You should get ready, okay?
- Oh, you look great.
- Thank you.
Got a lot of nice stuff. Got a pizza.
- All kinds of stuff.
- Terrific.
I just need you to decide what to...
You know, I did everything.
- Gary?
- Yeah?
- Oh, come on! Really?
- You got three lemons.
What my baby wants, my baby gets.
You know that.
Yeah, but I wanted 12. Baby wanted 12.
Why would you want 12 lemons?
Because I'm making a 12-lemon centrepiece.
So, no one's actually even eating them?
They're just show lemons?
Yeah. They're just show lemons.
Shown in the centre of the table.
I'm glad you find that amusing,
but I cannot fill a vase
with only three lemons.
Well, can't you just use, like,
maybe a drinking glass?
I'm not gonna use a drinking...
We could have a smaller version
of a centrepiece.
I'm not gonna use a drinking glass
for our centrepiece.
You know what? I've got an idea.
Why don't we go ahead and scratch
the centrepiece idea altogether,
because the chicken that burnt my mouth
could maybe use
a little bit of lemon on top of it.
Guess what? Now we've made a better meal
versus something visually nice to look at.
What are you do... What's happening here?
What are you doing?
Oh, I had such a long day on the bus.
I need a little bit of down time.
My feet are killing me.
- Gary, come on, my feet are killing me, too.
- I'm exhausted.
I worked all day. Went to the market.
I cleaned this entire condo and then
I've been cooking for the last three hours.
Come on. Help set the table.
- Sweetheart.
- What?
You've done such a great job already.
Don't you want to finish it yourself
and have that personal power
of that accomplishment?
- Set the table.
- Listen to me.
Do you think that when Michelangelo, right,
was painting the Sixteenth Chapel,
that he said,
"Hey, guys, you know, I did pretty good
on the first 15 chapels,
"but why don't you help me
design this one?
"And maybe you could help me...
Give me a brush
"and you guys can grab brushes,
and we can all make a great chapel. " Uh-uh.
No, he didn't.
And you wanna know what the results were?
A masterpiece.
Okay.
It's the Sistine Chapel, not the Sixteenth,
and I bet when Michelangelo asked
for 12 brushes, they didn't bring him three.
Yeah. Okay, all the talking
is really starting to drain me,
and now I'm gonna have to watch the
highlights later to see what I missed here.
- Honey, look, Gary, just...
- Down time's important.
- Gary, please just take a shower, okay?
'Cause this is what
I don't want to have happen.
I don't want the doorbell to ring.
I'm then forced to answer the door,
entertain people,
and I'm still cooking dinner.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
You're absolutely right. Let's do that.
The second that this inning's over...
- Gary.
- There's one out all ready.
They're gonna be here in 20 minutes.
Baby, have you ever seen a shower of mine
take more than four minutes?
Yes, I have. Come on.
Oh, great!
They're here. Okay.
Table's not set. Dinner's not ready.
Would you please just let my parents in?
- I gotta jump in the shower.
- What?
I gotta go.
Gary. Gary.
Well, seeing how our families
haven't had many opportunities
to get to know one another, we figured,
what better way than to break some bread?
So, everyone, thank you for coming
and enjoy the meal.
- Cheers.
- Cheers, honey.
- Mrs Grobowski. Nice to meet you.
- Thank you.
Cheer with the sons.
Sweetheart, cheers to you.
Darling, I see that you put
those Feng Shui books
that I sent to you to good use.
- This place is so well balanced.
- Thanks, Mom.
Yeah, the energy in this place
is just amazing.
Yes.
Well, the energy in the condo
might be a little more amazing
if we had a pool table.
Gary, we've already discussed that.
We're gonna get a pool table
when we get a bigger place.
The place is plenty big now,
if you wanted a pool table because...
- Gary.
- Yeah. You could take the dining room table,
go ahead and move her in the living room.
Really?
Plenty of room.
And put a dining room table
in the living room? Okay.
How do you... I mean, what do you do
with a dining room table?
- Eat on it.
- We'd have no furniture in the living...
- Where's the furniture go?
- All I'm saying is,
it would be nice
to be able to shoot some pool.
- Well, this isn't a dorm.
- Look, baby, I completely understand.
There's halls and stuff. I mean, you can go...
We will wait and get a pool table
when we have a bigger place.
Thank you.
- The food is outstanding.
- It is delicious food.
It's outstanding.
Yeah, it really is nice.
- Okay, everybody.
- Time for the joke of the day. Knock, knock.
- Dad. Dad, come on.
- Who's there?
- Norma Lee.
Norma Lee, who?
Normally, I don't go around
knocking on doors,
but would you like to buy
an encyclopaedia?
I got a joke. I got a joke.
How's it going? I got a joke for you.
What do you get when you cross
a gay Eskimo and a black guy?
All right, look, I think we've had enough
with the jokes for tonight.
Thank you, though.
Let's just talk with each other.
All right.
I saw that Three Brothers
article in the Trib this week.
Sounds like you guys are up
to some pretty exciting stuff.
Basically, our big goal is to try to
take Chicago tourism by air, land and sea.
We're still in the ground
phase with the buses.
But as soon as we get
our infantry established,
- then we'll take it to the squids.
- Yeah.
- Boats. Boats.
- Oh, boats.
As soon as we control the waterway,
then we'll bring in air supports
and then we'll pretty much
control everything.
You know, Dennis,
the way your face lights up
when you describe your ambitions,
it's really inspiring.
- Oh, thanks.
- Because I understand
how you feel that passion.
And sharing it with other people,
I think that's what life's about.
I don't feel that about boats and squibs...
Squids?
- Squids.
- Sorry.
- Yeah.
- But I do feel it about singing.
With my a cappella group,
The Tone Rangers.
Although it's not
as aggressive as your dream,
it's really more of a brotherhood.
It's like a musical team.
It's like a symphony of guys.
Guy symphony.
And it's very hard to describe the true magic
of a group of guys
singing in perfect harmony.
It's transcendent.
But it's still very real.
I guess the best way
to put it in words is just...
Even that doesn't do it.
That doesn't do it
because that's just one person.
And what I'm talking about is
the pulse of the collective.
Oh, heck.
Let me just show you how it's done.
Dad, how about a little percussion?
- Tap-tap-tappy.
And, Mom, high-hat.
Good, Mom.
Excellent. And Gary!
On the kick drum!
Come, come! On the kick drum! Come, come!
That's Gary! Come,
come with the kick drum. Come!
Come, come with the kick drum.
Gary, on the kick drum. Come, come.
That's Gary on the kick drum.
Go! And Gary. In the house.
- Come, come.
- I'm not with you.
Come, come. With the kick drum.
Come, come.
I'm just not really
the kick drum kind of guy.
I'd rather be just a listener and enjoy
all the banging that he's doing and the...
You know, Gary, that's your prerogative.
That's your right, to listen.
Meantime, I've gotta talk
to Brooke about something.
- It's called the bass line. Excuse me.
- Okay.
Good, Carol.
Good, Brooke.
Yes, Dennis.
- Be nice.
Totally awesome.
Move yourself
You always live your life
Never thinking of the future
Prove yourself
You are the move you make
Take your chances
win or loser
See yourself
You're every step you take
You and you
and that's the only way
Shake
Shake!
Shake yourself
You're every move you make
So the story goes
Thank you so much.
Okay, bye.
- It was great to see you.
- Okay. Come on.
- Have a good night.
- It was really nice, Gary.
- Nice to see you. You, too.
- Good to see you guys.
- Thanks, Brookie.
- Oh, honey. Thank you, sweetie.
- You're still my favourite singer.
- Stop it.
Love you, sis. And I'd love for you
to come to a live performance
of The Tone Rangers singing live.
That's something you'd really enjoy.
- It was good seeing you.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- Bye, darling. Thank you for such a...
- Okay. Okay, Mom.
- We'll see you soon.
- Bye, dear. Thanks, darling.
- See you later.
- Okay, buddy.
Oh, now, are you sure
that we can't help you clean up?
- No, no. I think we're gonna be great. We'll...
- Yes?
So nice of you to offer, but we got it.
Thank you.
- Oh, it was such fun.
- Great.
- I love you.
- Great to see you.
- Good night, sweetie.
- Thank you so much.
I appreciate it. Thank you so much.
- All right, guys.
- Bye-bye.
- Thanks for coming.
Love you, too.
Are you blind?
Oh, no, no! My demos!
- Well, I'm gonna go do the dishes.
- Cool.
- It'd be nice if you helped me.
- Damn it.
Way to go!
No problem. I'll get them a little bit later.
I'm just gonna hit the streets here
for a little bit.
Gary, come on, I don't want to do them later.
Let's just do them now. It'll take 15 minutes.
Honey, I am so exhausted.
I just honestly want to relax for a little bit.
If I could just sit here,
let my food digest,
and just try to enjoy the quiet for a little bit.
Get some! Get some! Get some!
That's what happens.
And we will... You know,
we can clean the dishes tomorrow.
Gary, you know I don't like
waking up to a dirty kitchen.
- Who cares?
- I care! All right? I care!
I busted my ass all day cleaning this house
and then cooking that meal.
And I worked today.
It would be nice if you said thank you
and helped me with the dishes.
- Fine. I'll help you do the damn dishes.
- Oh, come on. You know what?
No. See? That's not what I want.
You just said that you want me
to help you do the dishes.
- I want you to want to do the dishes.
- Why would I want to do dishes?
- Why?
- See, that's my whole point.
Let me see if I'm following this, okay?
Are you telling me that you're upset
because I don't have
a strong desire to clean dishes?
No. I'm upset because you don't have
a strong desire to offer to do the dishes.
- I just did.
- After I asked you!
- Jesus, Brooke, you're acting crazy again.
- Don't you call me crazy. I am not crazy.
- I didn't call you crazy.
- You just did.
I didn't call you... No, I didn't.
- I said you're acting crazy.
- You know what, Gary?
I asked you to do one thing today,
one very simple thing,
to bring me 12 lemons
and you brought me three.
God damn it. If I knew that
it was gonna be this much trouble,
I would have brought home 24 lemons.
Even 100 lemons.
You know what I wish? I wish everyone
that was at that goddamn table
had their own little private bag of lemons.
- Honest to God!
- Gary, it's not about the lemons.
Well, that's all you're talking about.
I'm just saying it'd be nice if you did
things that I asked.
It would be even nicer if you did things
without me having to ask you!
Well, I do seem to remember
doing something for you this morning
without you asking.
- Gary, come on.
- What? I'm serious. Come here.
- You know what? I'm serious. I really am.
- I am, too.
Come on. You knew I was working today
and I made that meal.
And you could have thought to yourself,
you know, you could have said,
"Yeah, I think I'm gonna
get Brooke some flowers. "
You said on our very first date
that you don't like flowers,
that they're a waste of money.
Every girl likes flowers, Gary.
You said that you don't like flowers.
I'm supposed to take that to mean
that you do like flowers?
No. This is not about... You're not...
God, you're not getting it.
You're not getting this, Gary, okay?
It's not about the lemons.
It's not about the flowers.
It's not about the dishes.
It's just about... How many times
do I have to drop hints about the ballet?
You know I can't stand... Brooke, come here.
We've talked about the damn ballet.
I hate the goddamn ballet!
You got a bunch of dudes
in tights flopping around for three hours.
It's like a medieval techno show.
It's a nightmare.
I sit there in a sweat. The whole thing, I do,
wondering when the hell's the
goddamn nightmare gonna end.
- Go to a damn ballet.
- It's not about you loving the ballet, Gary.
It's about the person that you love
loves the ballet
and you wanting to spend time
with that person.
Not when they're at the ballet.
- Okay. Forget the ballet! Forget the ballet!
- I will.
We don't go anywhere together.
- We just went to Ann Arbor together.
- To Ann Arbor.
To the Michigan-Notre Dame game.
You think screaming, drunk kids
and leprechauns doing backflips, that's fun.
That's fun for me. Come on, man.
I did that for you.
What do you... How do you show up for me?
I'm up on the bus
every goddamn day for you!
- Come on. You...
- I'm busting my ass
to be the best tour guide in the damn city,
so I can make enough money
to support both of us
and hopefully you won't
have to work one day.
- I want to work.
- All I ask, Brooke,
is that you show a little bit of appreciation.
That I just get 20 minutes
to relax when I come home,
instead of being attacked with questions
and nagged the whole damn time.
- You think that I nag you?
- That's all you do!
All you do is nag me!
"The bathroom's a mess. "
"Your belt doesn't match. "
"Hey, Gary, you should
probably go work out. "
Nothing I ever do is ever good enough!
I just want to be left the hell alone!
Really? Is that what you want, Gary?
- Is that what you want?
- Yeah.
- That's what you want?
Fine. Great. Do whatever the hell you want.
You leave your socks all over this house,
dress like a pig,
play your stupid-ass video game.
I don't care, I'm done.
- What?
- I'm done! I don't deserve this.
I really do not deserve this.
I deserve somebody who gives a shit.
I'm not spending one more second
of this life with some inconsiderate prick!
You're a prick!
Addie, it just became so clear tonight
how much he takes me for granted.
- What happened?
Just the same old shit.
I asked him to do one thing
and he didn't do it.
Then he complained
that he had to do anything,
and I just felt like I had no choice.
No, sweetie, you did have a choice, okay?
And it sounds like you made the right one.
You respected yourself.
But it's just not what I want.
I don't want to break up with him.
I don't. I just want him to say thank you.
I want him to want to do the dishes.
I just want him to want
to take me to the ballet.
I want him to get me 12 lemons! You know...
I just want him to care enough
about this relationship to want to work on it.
Okay, you know what?
I'm putting on my shoes
- and I'm gonna be there in 15 minutes.
- No, Ad. Don't.
Please, I really don't want to see anybody.
I really don't.
But, look, I'm worried about you, okay?
And I can hear you in there
banging around your dishes.
And I don't want you getting out your Clorox
and your rubber gloves,
- and taking this out on the kitchen.
- Look, look, look.
Okay. Tonight just...
It just got a little out of hand,
and hopefully he's just gonna realise
that he's got some changes
to make and he's gonna...
He's gonna come home and apologise.
Okay? That's what's gonna happen.
I feel like, I don't... You know, like,
you dress however you want to dress.
You know, do whatever you want to do.
- I'm done with the relationship.
- Whatever.
So, it's just kind of,
"You're done with the relationship?"
Well, you're obviously hurt about it.
- She got to you. You're hurt.
- I'm not.
It's nothing to be ashamed of. She hurt you.
Will you look at me? I'm not heartbroken.
I'm a little shocked. I'm a little surprised.
Gary, you're devastated. Now, what's
the name of the guy she's doing?
I'm gonna solve your problem.
What's his name?
- What are you talking about?
- Have you checked her e-mail?
I don't check e-mails. I don't...
You can get a programme
that records keystrokes.
It costs, like, 20 bucks.
Very easy to use. Okay?
You get a password, you check her e-mail.
You find out everything about her.
That's how I found out
about the Puerto Rican
- that Stacy was running around with.
- Okay.
You are reading a little too much
into this situation.
There is no one she's
running around with, okay?
We had a fight over the groceries
I brought home.
You're probably right.
She's probably not sleeping with anybody.
- No. Not what it's about.
- Okay.
- Maybe she's with another guy, maybe not.
- She's not.
I don't know. I'm not Columbo. Okay?
But what we do know is that
she doesn't want to be with you anymore.
I mean, I hate to be shitty about it,
and so cut and dry, but let's face it.
She says she doesn't want to be with you,
and I believe her.
Now, we gotta figure it out.
And you're gonna need a place to go
and lick your wounds while
you get your head right over this thing.
I don't need a place to go
and lick my wounds.
You're gonna stay with me.
- I'm not gonna hear it.
- Look it...
- I'm not moving out of the place.
- Oh, you're not moving out.
No. I put money in the place.
I put half my money in the place.
You're obviously not
the one calling the shots in this case.
Yeah, but I own the place.
- With her.
- Yeah.
But it's not up to her who gets to keep
the goddamn place.
If you find out who she's sleeping with,
maybe we could leverage it.
- I want you to listen to me.
- You listen to me.
- I'm gonna leave you a key.
- I don't need a key.
- Why?
- 'Cause she's gonna put...
She's gonna move out of the place, Johnny.
- Did she say she was moving out?
- She will. She's gonna move out.
Oh, she's... I'm gonna keep the place.
I'm not moving out of the place.
I'll leave you a key.
- Hey, how's it going?
I almost got it.
- Yeah.
- You know, I was thinking.
You know what you should do,
is you should find somebody
who looks like Brooke,
but even hotter and, you know,
bang the shit out of her.
- What the hell's wrong with you?
- What?
- Logs.
- Just fix the damn engine.
- I am fixing the goddamn engine.
- I need your tour logs.
I'm off the clock, okay?
Well, I cannot file the quarterlies
until I have your log.
I'm going through a little bit of a
life change here, Dennis.
I would really appreciate
a little bit of sensitivity, please.
I know they're both French,
but that has nothing to do with it.
Because Manet was earlier and... No. Monet
and Manet are very different things.
I'm sorry, I beg to differ.
Excuse me, sir, can I have her
call you back personally?
Yes. Okay, thank you. Sorry. Brooke?
- I am so sorry.
- What?
Come here.
Oh, honey, your mom called
and told me everything.
Oh, Jesus.
Good morning, Marilyn.
Morning. I'll go water the plants.
I understand you had a long night.
Tell me everything.
"Everything. "
I couldn't possibly...
Then don't. My time is pressing.
What I want is for you
to take the rest of the day off.
Oh, no. No, that's not necessary.
Who am I?
- Marilyn Dean.
- And where are we?
- The Marilyn Dean Gallery.
- And of whom is that portrait?
- That is Marilyn Dean.
- Yeah.
You know, your personal life
is your personal life.
But you look like shit.
And when you look like shit,
Marilyn Dean looks like shit,
and now it is my business.
And when it comes to my business,
I don't like anything that's distracting.
So, I want you to take
the rest of the day off to be sad
and then come back to work tomorrow
ready to take care of business.
Got it?
Oh, hey, Brooke. How are you?
What the hell are you doing?
Well, my whole life, I always wanted
my own place with my own pool table.
I finally got my own place,
but you would not allow me
to have a pool table.
I just kind of figured I'd rectify that today.
And it does feel good.
I'm gonna go ahead and put the four ball
in the corner pocket.
Nice.
I'm sorry, can I...
A little room for the shooter, please?
It's hard to shoot with someone standing...
Thank you.
Wow.
Well, I guess he feels threatened that
you broke up with him and he's acting out.
Okay, look, Brooke, men are like children.
You know? And they...
Sweetie, it's a figure of
speech. It's Brooke. And I love you so much.
And you're my man and you know that.
You're amazing. I love you.
Listen, and they're gonna test boundaries
to see what they can get away with.
I think there's three things
that Gary needs to know.
One, this type of behaviour is not unnoticed.
Two, it's not acceptable.
And three, you know,
you're definitely not gonna tolerate it. Right?
Yes.
And Brooke, remember, we're always
owning our actions, right?
And we're always healthy with it, yes?
Yes.
I don't wanna finish the game.
I got showings, okay?
I gotta buy the cookie spray.
I gotta clean up the dog.
And now I'm really leaving
'cause I don't want to hear that. Okay?
Thank you for the pool.
Thank you for the snacks.
- I'm going to get a cab.
- I'll split it with you.
What are you, 12?
Brooke, that is not healthy.
- I'm trying to make a point.
- And what is that point?
My point's your point. Your three points.
That it's not unnoticed,
that it was not acceptable,
and that it would definitely not be tolerated.
Not exactly what I meant.
Unbelievable.
- I knew it!
- Hey, gang.
Found my shirt on the floor.
Thanks for laying it out.
- Gary, are you here for couples bowling?
- Yeah.
Well, don't you think
you and I should discuss something first?
Like what?
How your 47 average is killing us?
Okay. Great. No.
Gary, this is couples bowling.
And since you and I are no longer a couple,
because you have chosen
not to participate constructively
in our relationship,
we're now singles.
So, there's not room
for two singles on the team.
Why do you look confused?
I don't have any idea what's happening.
I've come to play on the team.
Look, Gary, I just don't think
it's a good idea
for you and I to be around each other
any more than we have to right now.
I completely agree.
Maybe you should go play some pinball.
- No, I think you should leave.
- Okay.
Brooke, when a man makes a commitment
to a team, he honours that commitment.
He doesn't let emotions or personal issues
get in the way of victory.
And I've made a commitment to this team.
- They don't want you here either, Gary.
- Yeah. Sure, they don't.
They don't. They're my friends.
- But you're not a strong bowler.
- That's not the point.
You know what? Let's just...
Why don't we let them decide?
Gary, don't. No. Don't involve them, okay?
That's unnecessary.
- What's wrong, Castro?
- Castro?
Well, Castro doesn't
let people vote as a team.
- Okay. Ask them.
- Thank you.
Okay, everyone. Team vote here.
By a show of hands,
just put it up when you make a decision,
who here agrees with Brooke
and thinks I should leave the bowling team?
Shocker.
Band of Brothers.
You should rent it sometime.
Good luck, everyone.
Riding Miss Gutter Ball to the finals.
- Hey, Gary.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna need your shirt back.
- What?
Well, we're gonna have to replace you,
and you know we get docked 10 pins
if everyone's not in matching
Pin Shakers uniforms.
- My shirt says "Gary" on it.
- Granted.
But actually, we know a guy named Gary.
And he's not as tall as you,
but he's a pretty good bowler.
I'm gonna have to request
that I have my wrist guard back then.
I'm sorry. That's mine.
Just give me the goddamn wrist guard,
please. Thank you.
I hope your wrist snaps.
Wow. Okay? You see that?
You know what I mean?
Yeah. That was awesome.
You just had your ex-boyfriend,
who you wish you were still dating,
voted off the bowling team.
Well, I had to do that to get him
right where I want him.
Where's that? Shirtless in the parking lot?
Addie, you're not getting this.
Gary loves this bowling team.
He's hurt right now.
He's feeling pretty bad.
He's gonna go out there
and he's gonna get drunk.
He's gonna make a complete fool of himself.
And he will be sitting there
feeling pretty lonely
and pretty pathetic,
and then it's just gonna hit him.
What's gonna hit him?
That not only is he out a girlfriend,
but his life is just falling apart piece by piece
and maybe that life was pretty great.
And maybe I was the glue
that was holding it all together.
And if he wants that life back,
he's gonna have no choice but to change.
- How about this, huh?
- I feel like we just found hell.
When did you start coming
to knobby joints like this?
I might be the greatest you've ever seen, pal.
I'm conquering new frontiers. Hello, babe.
Yeah, you've got to put up
with the bad music and the $15 drinks,
but this place is stacked
with top-shelf, young, dumb ass.
All you gotta do is just
separate the weaker ones from the herd.
Come on, I'll get you into the VIP.
- Can I get a couple drinks from you?
- Okay, L.G.
Lupus, I got to be totally...
I got to be honest with you.
I'm not feeling it here.
You're gonna like it in here.
You're gonna love it.
- I don't like it out here.
- Look, listen to me, will you, please?
How you doing, Buzz?
While you were on the inside
locked up for the past two years,
the game has changed.
Do you remember
when you were an outdoor cat
and you used to have to hunt
and kill for your food?
Well, you've become an indoor cat.
You've been getting your milk brought to you
in a silver bowl, and guess what?
Now, you've been tossed back outside
and the alley has changed.
For example, your MTV generation,
your technology, your text message,
your TiVo. You name it.
People want their information faster.
People e-mail each other because
they want to exchange information, Gar.
They don't want to connect,
they want results.
- Okay.
- You gotta get to the message quicker.
Now, I want you to watch.
It's real simple. Okay?
How you doing, ladies?
Now, here's what I'd like to do to you.
First, I'd like to get you naked.
And then I'm gonna take some Saran Wrap
and I'm gonna wrap you up in it, head to toe.
Then I'm gonna cut out two holes.
One for your mouth,
so you can breathe, obviously.
- And the other one...
- Asshole.
It could be a gorgeous evening for us, babe.
The pink is gorgeous. Jesus, God.
Come here. Lupus, listen to me.
I want you to listen to me.
There are our drinks. You want your drink?
- No, I'm fine.
- Thank you. The L.G. Thanks you.
Will you listen to me, please?
You're my brother and I love you very much,
and maybe you do get laid tonight,
but maybe you get arrested.
Arrested for what, babe? Being awesome?
Come on, babe, listen.
You want to tell your jokes, tell your jokes.
But sooner or later you're gonna get hungry
and you're gonna wanna eat.
And jokes might make you feel better,
but they don't get you fed.
I'm gonna go take a lap.
- What are you doing?
- I'm sketching.
And where are you sketching?
- In the living room.
- No, in my bedroom.
And I didn't say anything to you, Brooke,
when you so arrogantly
claimed the bed without asking me,
but you can't just waltz into my room
and turn it into a damn art fair.
Gary, I've only taken up
a little bit of space, so...
I don't care if you only took an inch.
There might not be a door here,
but this is my domain. Okay?
I don't go into your bedroom
and set up a goddamn sawhorse.
Well, then what the hell
is that pool table doing in the dining room?
Because that's a common area.
And that's where this belongs.
- Not in my room.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- It belongs in another common area.
- Gary.
People want to come home
and they want to relax in their room.
Gary, it is 2:00 in the morning!
- Don't you drop my things.
- I don't know what to tell you, kid.
This is how I am when I'm single.
My hours start to get pretty strange.
Might be time for you
to think about moving out.
Why would I... No, I'm not moving anywhere.
Gary, just please turn the volume down.
Yeah, but I don't tell you
what the hell to do in your room.
You can doodle. You can dance.
You can bake
a goddamn gingerbread house.
I don't give a shit.
But in my room, I want to relax
and watch my highlights
in complete surround-sound experience.
- What the hell are you doing?
- You're not even gonna watch it!
Don't tell me what I am or aren't not doing.
Oh, what you are not, not doing?
- Go learn some English.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't have a grandfather
on the board of some fancy college.
Key word being "was. "
Did he touch the Filipino exchange student?
Did he not touch the exchange student?
- I don't know, Brooke. I wasn't there.
- Okay.
No, don't start with the family stuff.
Like your family's so perfect?
Your brother's a pervert!
Don't talk to me about
the sexual habits of family members.
What about your sister?
- My sister's been through a lot.
- Of dick.
There are some problems, Gary,
but can we please just leave it...
Problems? She slept with
the entire Arizona Cardinals offensive line.
That's not problems.
That's she's the problem!
- She was on vacation!
- She was on vacation.
Don't even get me started,
by the way, on your brother.
If I have to hear
that guy sing just one more time,
I'd hang myself with wax dental floss.
Could the guy just
come out of the closet, please?
Richard is not gay.
Okay, lassie, I want you to listen to me
and listen good.
I'm not saying he won't get married.
I'm not saying he won't even have kids.
But then one day his wife will come home,
and then she'll find him
with a guy named Majulio,
wearing leather helmets and
clubbing each other to Yanni's greatest hits.
Yeah. Right. Whatever. You're an infant.
Yeah, I'm an infant.
Go enjoy your room, Brooke,
'cause I'm gonna enjoy mine!
- Okay.
- You know what?
I might enjoy some pay-per-view
options tonight.
It's gonna be a long one, sweetheart,
and I got nothing to do maana but sleep in.
Boogie nights
Ain't no doubt we are here to party
What are you doing?
Boogie nights
Come on now, got to get it started
Ricky, you and the Get Along Gang leave
or I'm gonna throw you out of here
personally, you understand?
Actually, Gary, this is Brooke's bedroom.
So, technically,
you don't have jurisdiction here,
but I think it'd be really fun
if you sang with us.
Come on, Gary. I think you'll like it.
You got 10 seconds to get out of here
or I'm gonna break
your damn magic whistle.
You understand what I'm saying to you?
Move this group out of my house, now!
Gary, you can't take
a pitch pipe out of a guy's hand
when he's in the middle
of a very funky groove.
You can get hurt doing something like that.
I'm tapping out, I'm tapping out!
Here we go. From the bridge.
Party night
Get on down with the sound of the music
Boogie nights Do it, do it
What kind of bullshit move was that?
- I'm sorry. What? What happened?
- Oh, don't be coy with me.
You sent that animal over here
to attack me when I was hung over and weak.
Oh, no. Look, all I know
is The Tone Rangers,
they needed someplace to rehearse,
so I very clearly told Richard,
"Stay in my room,"
which you explained to me
was my space to do with what I want.
Is that how you want to play it?
'Cause I'll play it like that.
I'll play it like Lionel Richie.
All night long, lady. Oh, yeah.
I'll call some guys
from my neck of the woods.
And we're not talking, Brooke,
about a couple of queens
who know a few grapples.
We're talking about Polacks
that don't have a goddamn future.
- Right.
- That's right!
We can make shit real uncomfortable
around here,
and that's what we're gonna do.
Please. Come on. You know what?
You're just embarrassed
because Richard kicked your ass.
Richard did not kick my ass.
What Richard did was attack me
when I was half asleep.
Really? Is that how you see it?
There's a really big gap
between getting your ass kicked
and having a dancing, singing sprite
fool you with trickery
and then strike your throat
before you know that you're even in a fight.
And I wouldn't expect
someone like you to understand that,
because all you ever do
is make moves from up in your ivy tower.
Wow. You have officially
gone off the reservation.
I'm an adult. I talk through shit.
He ran out of ideas.
God. Listen, by the way,
there's messages on the voice mail
regarding game night,
which is obviously not gonna happen,
so you might want to
call people and tell them that it's cancelled.
- Why would I cancel game night?
- Well, I mean...
If it's our turn to host game,
I'm gonna host goddamn game night.
- You want to host game night?
- I'm fine, Brooke.
I don't have any strangeness
over what happened here today.
Okay.
If there's anyone that should feel weird
about seeing people,
that's you, Tonya Harding.
Me? I'm gonna honour my commitments.
- Great.
- Fine.
- Let's do that.
Let's honour the commitment.
- Hey, there's no food in there!
So?
Well, people are gonna be here in an hour.
What are they supposed to eat?
You're a big boy. Figure it out.
Oh, great. Well, that's what we got.
We have only tap water
because, you know, Gary didn't shop.
And we don't have
any ice either 'cause he didn't fill the trays.
- That's trash. It's your shot.
- What is your name again?
- Diane.
Did you call?
I called the five.
Well, yeah,
but you didn't call the second ball,
so that's trash, so it's your shot.
You got to play by the rules.
It's your shot.
- Hi.
- Andrew.
Oh, hi.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hey, hey, hey!
These two Benedict Arnolds
aren't welcome in my condo.
- Who sent an invite to them?
- I'm sorry.
These are very loyal friends
and they are always welcome in my condo.
Oh, really? Why don't we take it to a vote
and see who has the numbers this time?
All right.
Show of hands here.
Who thinks that these two traitors should
leave and not be a part of game night?
And maybe take their shirts
off when they leave.
Raise your hand.
I know I feel that way. Who else?
Come on, Johnny O,
put your hand up, please.
Come on. Thank you. You, Miss? New girl.
Who's the girl? What's her name?
What's her name?
- The girl you're with. What's her name?
- Her name's Diane.
Oh, I'm sorry. You might want to go ahead
and touch some sky.
- Thank you. Come on, Riggleman, please?
- What are you doing?
No. We need the eight
to count towards a running tally.
You know that. Come on.
Show her whose side that you're on.
Put your hand in the air.
You know whose side I'm on.
You know we need eight, though. Come on.
Put your hand down.
Please don't touch my Ruffles.
Put that one back.
Those are my Ruffles.
Don't eat them, please. Thank you.
- Oh, Gary.
- They're mine.
- Come on.
- Here we go. All right.
Eyes front. Ready?
- Hold on. Get the timer going, please.
- Ready?
Now I gotta do it. Go.
Okay.
- It's a brick.
Square. Square.
- Box. Box.
Corner. Corner. A dot in the corner.
- A house.
- Home plate!
Football! Baseball! Sports. A house.
A triangle. It's algebra.
- Okay, it's a house.
It's a house.
Two words.
Banana?
Chimney, chimney, chimney!
A fruit. House. Fruit.
Oh, restaurant. Or...
No, chimney, chimney.
Smoke...
Oh, a house call.
- House call!
Oh! House call!
Yeah, well, I thought it was a house call.
- Like a hotel, then it hit me it was a house.
Yeah!
You're terrific. Absolutely terrific.
All right, beat that.
Okay, guys, listen.
The next one wins, okay?
So let's stay focused. Let's stay calm.
We can do this. High fives.
Let's go. Come on. Let's go.
Let's get a mind-meld.
Let's try and get a mind-meld, okay?
Here we go. Let's go. Mind-meld.
- I heard you!
- Don't over-think it. Mind meld.
Ready?
- I heard you!
- Well, just keep it simple.
Shush.
- Ready? Wait. Go!
- Here we go! We're mind-melding.
Draw faster. It doesn't have to be beautiful,
- just has to be something we can get.
- Shoe, shoe...
Shoe! Shoe, shoe, shoe.
Shoeless Joe Jackson. Draw something
different. No one's getting it.
- Shoe. What, is that a smaller shoe?
Baby shoe.
- Smaller shoe. Baby shoes.
Shoes.
Baby shoes. Smaller shoe. Gumshoe.
Smaller shoes.
Gumshoe? Gumshoe?
- Running Olympics.
Inside the shoe.
- Inside a shoe. A bubble...
Lining.
Stop pointing at the shoe.
We're not... No one's guessing shoe.
Stop pointing at the shoe
and draw something different.
Draw something different. You...
Goddamn it! No one's guessing shoe!
You drew a big shoe,
then a small shoe, and no one got it.
You gotta draw something different.
Everyone said "shoe" seven times.
It's a sock, asshole.
- You call yourself an artist?
- Yes!
A three-year-old with a box of crayons
could do a better job than this.
I'm sorry, I don't have the great talent
of standing on top of a big red bus
and pointing out architecture
that other great men have built!
I'm the one who should be sorry, Brooke.
- I shouldn't sit here and pick on your art.
- No.
Because you got
the nuts part down, Picasso.
All you have
to do is cut off your frigging ear.
That's Van Gogh, you idiot!
And your insults are much more effective
when they're accurate.
Don't talk to me about
being goddamn accurate!
I can talk to you about anything that I want.
'Cause you couldn't even draw a sock.
You don't do anything right! You're a lazy...
Everyone said, "Shoe, shoe, shoe!"
At first, I figured that the split
was just something temporary,
something that you two
would work out and get past,
but after tonight I think it's pretty clear
that you two genuinely
do not want to get back together.
- There's not a shot in hell.
- Gary.
- I'm just...
- I got you.
As your friend and as your realtor,
I'm not gonna leave here tonight
until we decide what to do about this condo,
because this living situation
is obviously not working out.
Gary?
Well, the only logical thing that I can think of
is for her to move out of the condo,
and then to pay me some
sort of a penalty as compensation for
- the labour that I did all around the condo.
- What? What?
What? Pay you compensation
for your labour?
- We fixed this place up together.
- Are you nuts?
- Stop calling me nuts, I swear to God.
- I fixed the...
You went around with a sponge,
and you went in the bathroom
and you dotted foofy shit.
- That's what you're saying that I did?
There's no...
That was...
That's called aesthetics.
It warmed this place up so it didn't look like
an army barracks, which it was about to.
I'll tell you what it's called in his language,
depreciated.
- That's what it's called.
- You don't even know what that means.
Unless the next buyer happens to have
your same Zulu-voodoo-land taste.
- All right.
- Let me tell you something else.
It's gonna cost money
to cover up the holes in the wall.
The holes that you drilled in the wall there
to hang up whatever that thing is called.
Oh, please. Gary.
You're gonna have
to cost money to fix that.
What I did, Brooke,
has concrete value to the condo.
I added concrete...
Well, let's just go on record.
We're dealing with facts here.
I did the tiling in the bathroom.
- Have you seen...
- I did the new track lighting.
- That tile is the shittiest tile job.
I did the plumbing!
- The plumbing!
- That's realty terms.
Okay. Let's talk about your plumbing.
This is his plumbing.
We have two temperatures in our bathroom.
We get either scalding hot
or we get frostbite.
- That's it. That's all we get.
- It's my problem
that she doesn't know how
to pace a shower?
Now all of a sudden
that's my fault.
I get one minute to take a shower.
- One minute?
One minute of warmth?
- Oh, Jesus. One minute.
- That's it. That's correct.
Thank God you're not in charge of keeping
all the clocks in Chicago on time.
- This is basic logic.
- You are out of your mind. You have lost it.
Let me explain this to you
in plain chapter and verse.
Cheese and rice, you guys are gonna
kill each other. Now, let's just...
Realistically speaking, neither one of you
can afford this mortgage on your own, okay?
And that's a shame, because this building
will continue to increase in value.
I get nothing but phone calls about it,
all right?
Waiting for a unit to open up.
So, as your realtor,
the last thing I would suggest is selling.
But as your friend,
I just, I don't see any other solution.
You take your halves,
you go your separate ways,
and you get on with your lives.
I know that selling is not the easiest thing,
but I do think that it's the best.
And to be honest, this is a situation
where I would just as soon
not take a commission.
- That's great. Thank you.
- That's great. Thank you for that.
I wish I didn't have to, you know,
but company policy says I cannot waive that.
But I was just...
You know, I'm saying in theory, you know.
In this situation, 'cause we're friends,
I wish I could waive it.
No can do, though.
As soon as you can, I would love to get
a set of keys from you guys.
You just drop them off.
Okay. Great. There they are.
I'll be bringing by people all week.
You won't even know I'm here.
The good news is, should move quickly.
All right.
Okay to leave you two alone now?
Got to get back to Jen.
Very excited about the win tonight.
Okay.
Addie, if the condo sells,
I think I'm gonna lose him.
Yeah, but game night
was so light and fun,
I'm really surprised to be hearing this.
Okay. You know what?
That's not constructive. Really.
I just... Yeah,
I need a new plan, Addie. I don't...
I'm just kidding. It's me.
I'm gonna have to call you back.
Whenever one of my friends is down,
we all go on, like, happy patrol.
I was actually having
a very serious conversation.
Christopher, do not sing.
If you're happy
and you know it clap your hands
If you're happy and you know it
Clap your hands
You're going to smile to...
Pack up your shit and go home.
Okay. You know what? This is not his fault.
He was just really trying
to cheer me up and it...
Did I or did I not give you
the day off to be sad?
- Yes. But I...
- Well, today's not that day,
and unfortunately for you,
I can't afford to look weak.
No, please.
You have warned me so many times
and you have yet to fire me.
I think you and I both know
that to find and train somebody new,
it's gonna cost you time,
and it's gonna cost you money,
and I don't think you want
to spend either one of those.
Now, look, I'm just gonna
take a wild guess here,
but you don't become Marilyn Dean
without knowing how to handle men.
Okay? Now, just listen to my problem,
tell me how to fix it,
and then we'll all go back to work.
Okay. What is this problem so severe
that has caused you to blaspheme
in the synagogue of Marilyn Dean?
Well, it's Gary. I broke up with him
in hopes that losing me
would make him want to change,
and that's, you know...
And I've just ended up pushing him,
you know, farther and farther away.
- That's it?
- Yeah.
Honey, this is not surrealism or cubism,
it's paint-by-numbers.
Go see Mischa,
my personal waxer at the spa.
Ask her for the Telly Savalas.
The Telly Savalas.
Compliments of M. Dean.
Then go show Gary your immaculate canvas
and let him see another man
eager to paint it. Got it?
- Got it?
- Uh-huh.
Ow!
Who loves you, baby?
Wow, impressive. Three sharp hands landed.
What an amazing display
of punching technique.
The crowd jumps. That punch rocked him.
They sense he's on the verge
of hitting the canvas.
The roaring for anticipation of a knockout.
We are witnessing a great fight.
He's displaying incredible
rhythm with his hands.
Bulldog terrorising his opponent.
Down he goes!
Hard punch slams him to the canvas.
One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten.
It's over.
Is... Did... Is Brooke here?
I don't know.
- Brooke?
I'll be right there.
Cool, baby, cool.
So, how do you and Brooke
know each other?
Well, how don't we know each other,
you know what I mean?
Hi, Paul.
- Oh, hey. Wow, you look great.
Thank you.
Are you ready to go?
- Yeah. All set.
- So, it was great meeting you.
- Apple martinis.
- All right, come on.
- That normally does the trick.
- Just ignore him.
- But just two. Three, she'll get sloppy.
You'll become a babysitter.
Oh, and fantasy role playing.
She's got a real thing for lifeguards.
Put some zinc oxide
on your nose and she'll lose her mind.
It'll all be over with.
Y'all want me to stop running?
I mean, the most challenging part
of what I do
is between February and April 15th.
That's what we in the biz
like to call crunch time.
That sounds fascinating.
- Good evening.
- Hi.
Can I start you two off
with something to drink?
Yeah, you know, we're gonna
start with a couple of apple martinis, please.
No, you know what?
I'm gonna... I'm just gonna start with a water.
Well, you can just bring those, just in case.
What was I saying?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, you know,
it's not like it's all work and no play.
You know, I mean,
after April 15th, that's what we in the biz
like to call party time.
Excuse me.
Oh, I have to get this. I'm so sorry.
Hello.
Okay, is this when
I'm supposed to call?
What?
What do you mean? What?
Where? What happened?
- Okay, that's great.
- Wait. What? Oh, all right.
Listen, where... Just don't move.
Where are you?
- I'm sitting in my kitchen.
- Sitting? Okay.
Don't move.
Don't... I'm gonna be right there, honey.
I'm gonna be right there, okay?
- Is everything okay?
- Oh, my gosh.
That was my best friend.
She just had an accident and she...
She has this knee thing
- and she's just very fragile, and I have to go.
- What?
- I can give you a ride.
- No. No. That's okay.
I'm gonna grab a cab, so... I'm so sorry.
I like your dress.
I think he's fascinating.
He's obviously read a lot of books.
Yeah. Yeah, I bet he has.
He reads a lot of books
because nobody wants to talk to him.
He's a friend of Andrew's
who's always been polite.
It's the best I could do
on such short notice, okay?
Well, you know what?
Polite is not gonna do it.
We've got to find somebody
who is really gonna make Gary jealous.
Can I just say something?
You sound a little jealous, Gary.
Why would I be jealous
of some guy with computer skills?
Let's say he doesn't have computer skills,
but he's got a big old elephant hog on him?
Would that bother you
or would you be okay with that?
Not nearly as much as the way
that your mind works.
My mind works great.
So, what's this bullshit
I hear about you selling the condo?
Selling that condo is ludicrous.
I was waiting for when I was gonna get
the how-Gary-always-screws-his-life-up
speech again.
- This must be the right time.
- Look, you tell me,
- you just tell me, tell me.
- Is it happening now? Yeah. Okay.
Tell me how losing that asset
is gonna get us on the river?
Go ahead, just tell me. Tell me.
Somebody tell me. What is this?
- What is this? What is it? What is it? Hey!
- Don't patronise me.
- Helicopters.
- Helicopters. Exactly!
How does losing the asset
give us helicopters?
Dennis, I'm being totally serious with you.
I don't need this shit right now.
Hey, you want to cry, cry to Mom.
Nobody's crying. I'm not crying.
- I just don't feel like hearing it.
- There's no feelings here.
This is about money and business.
Fine, you broke up.
You broke up. Fine.
You know, sad.
Sad is, instead of putting $1,000
into your mortgage every month,
you waste it on rent. That's what sad is.
Oh, you're broke up.
You're confused, brokenhearted.
Heartbreak is not having that money
as part of your net worth
and then not saving the money,
so that after taxes you can invest!
You know, you're confused.
- Are you finished?
- Look, I need the damn tour logs.
Yeah.
Well, I really, really appreciate
the heart to heart.
It was a great talk, Dennis. Thank you.
Oh, well, you're behind three months.
You're still behind three months.
And those logs are imperative
to insuring that our books are straight!
I'll tell you what those logs are.
Those logs are bullshit is what they are!
You got the receipts.
Tally the goddamn things yourself!
I do, I do!
And I don't appreciate it,
because it cuts into my time with my family.
I could be spending that time
with my family instead of doing your books.
I already do the taxes. I do the billing.
I do the hiring, the firing.
I do the maintenance.
Come on, what do you do?
What is it that you do?
- You do the tours!
- I am the talent, Dennis!
They sign up a month in advance to see me.
They'll wait in line for the next bus
to see me! All right?
So don't drain me with all this bullshit
about the goddamn tour logs!
How big's your TV?
Oh, shut up!
How big's your TV, 'cause I wanna know
if you can see what's happening.
Oh, wow. You beat a 12-year-old.
I don't care if you're 12 years old.
You have more time in the day to play.
I live in the real worid, my man,
With bills and responsibilities.
That's right.
You can't have a handle called
Mad Dog Killer if you complain every time...
- Brooke?
- Hi, Mike.
- Hi.
- Come on in.
Hold on, Mom. I'm coming.
Is your mom in the room with you?
'Cause I hope she can't see
what's happening.
I hope she can't see what's happening.
I'm gonna be just a few more seconds.
So, just sit down and relax.
Oh, yeah, no problem.
I'm sorry?
Yeah, why'd you do that?
You take the fun out of beating you,
because you have an excuse to lose.
Get a life, dude.
Do you think it's possible that your mom
won't love you anymore
if she sees how bad
you're losing in the game.
Shut up!
Okay.
All right.
That's great. You're gonna
stay man-to-man with me.
What happens when I make a play?
Making plays, making plays! Making plays!
Well, you know, that's how my people
like to handle their business.
While your guys are out partying,
mine are running routes.
Try to make a difference.
Mike? I'm ready to go.
Oh, hey,
do you mind if we finish the game?
We got a real nail-biter going here.
Yeah, sure. Of course. Great.
Awesome, all right?
- Touchdown.
- Oh, God, is that pretty.
God, is that pretty. Yeah, I'm a gentleman.
I like to be humble.
I'm old school. I don't like to talk a lot.
But at the same time, am I talented?
Tell me how you felt about
what just happened there.
That's him going deep. That's him going...
Work ethic. Work ethic.
I could play this game forever.
- Oh, I could, too. I love it, yeah.
- I love it, don't you?
I mean, it's the kind of thing where literally
I play the game and it's like,
four hours go by.
Fate has me highly skilled
and loaded with talent.
Oh...
'Cause I think I'm good enough
to figure out how to beat myself.
You push yourself.
You push yourself trying to achieve
the impossible,
because you know
that when that moment comes
that everything you've done up to
that moment has prepared you for victory!
I can't take credit for it, Mike.
I got to thank these little digital guys
with the big hearts.
Does it feel good to be a champion? Yeah.
- Yeah, it feels good to be a champion.
- Good game.
Hey, Brooke, are you ready to go now?
- Oh, yeah, yeah. Sure.
Great.
Hey, Gary, thanks a lot, man.
It was great to meet you.
Absolutely, man.
Come on, Mike.
I know a great little martini bar.
Yo.
Hey, man, saddle up.
It's time to rope in some talent.
What's up? What do you got?
My place. Tonight. Poker.
Call some giris up.
Your roommate is awesome.
Mmm.
Yeah, he's something.
- So, where did you go to law school?
- Oh, Northwestern.
God, Gary's hilarious.
Yeah, he's okay.
Okay? I mean, the guy's all time.
But he's gonna take Chicago tourism
by air, land and sea.
And he asked me to join
his new bowling team.
I mean, how cool is that?
Mmm-hmm.
You know what? I can't do this. I'm so sorry.
Excuse me, would you please pull over?
Can you pull over, please?
Hey, wait.
Tell Gary to call me.
Welcome, everyone,
to the first annual Texas Hold'em No-Limit
Strip Poker Tournament.
Now, per the e-mail that Lupus sent,
we each have eight articles of clothing.
Now, if you want to bet,
you take off an article of clothing,
you put it in the centre.
If you win, you take back the clothes,
you put back on what you bet.
The extras that other people bet
will stay in front of you,
much the same as chips would.
You can go all in at any point,
but as I outlined, you must take off
all your clothes to do so.
The game shall last an hour, maybe two,
at which point we will begin
the dance portion of the evening.
Let's get going here.
I need to see the blinds.
Small blind. Big blind.
The blinds are one and one.
Come on, ladies.
All right.
- Oh, yeah.
- Let's get going here.
- Shuffle up and deal.
- All right.
I mean, just because
they were playing video games,
that doesn't mean
it didn't bother him, right?
Honestly, Brooke,
I wish I could tell you, but I wasn't there.
All right, Sally,
get the soap out of your mouth.
We're gonna save that for when you're 12.
Mike was really, really good-looking.
I mean, he's a little bit of a goof,
but Gary doesn't know that.
I mean, for all he knows, a sophisticated,
really good-looking guy
took me out on a date tonight.
I could be in bed
with this guy right now for all he knows.
You know?
I'm telling you, if you saw the look
on his face,
Mike got to him.
Hello.
Hey, it's Riggleman. Great news.
So, how does this work?
I'll bring the car around front
and you wrap them up to go?
Oh, no, no. We take care of everything.
We deliver it. We hang it.
We check the light and the sun exposure.
- Oh. Perfect.
- Yeah.
Listen, I don't want to be too forward,
but would you like to have
some dinner with me sometime?
I'm sorry. I have a boyfriend.
- Of course.
- So...
- Well, he's a lucky man.
Oh, thank you.
I guess I will just have to keep it to
home deliveries and gallery purchases.
Thank you, though. See you.
- Have a good day, Brooke.
- You, too.
Okay, are you out of your mind?
Gary's throwing Greek orgies
in your living room
and you're telling hot rich guys
you have a boyfriend?
- Are you nuts?
- Hey, look. I'm not exactly innocent here.
Brooke, as an outsider
with some perspective, I really think you...
Christopher, stop. Stop it.
I don't want to hear it.
This has already gotten way out of hand.
I know what I have to do now, all right?
I know what I have to do.
Hi.
- Did you get my note?
- Yeah.
Two weeks.
Yep.
I brought some boxes from work,
so, you know, if you need any
just help yourself.
Great. Thanks.
Oh.
Listen, a while ago I got these tickets
for the Old 97's tonight,
and I completely forgot about it, so I...
You know, if you want to go.
Well, how many tickets did you get?
I got two.
How much do you want for them?
Oh, no, I'm going. I'm going.
So, then it would just be the two of us?
Well, yes, and 2,000 other people.
I mean, it's not a big deal,
but, you know, look, you know,
I was going to invite Addie,
but I just figured I'd gotten them for you,
so...
Sure. Why not?
Are you sure?
I mean, if you don't want them,
- I can definitely give them to somebody.
- No. No, I'll be there.
That sounds... It sounds great.
Okay. All right. It's at the Riv.
So, I'll just leave your ticket at Will Call.
- Good?
- Okay.
Okay.
- Yeah, so, there. I'll just leave that for him.
- Okay, great.
- Okay, so.
- Gary Grobowski?
Grobowski, yeah.
He should be here in a minute.
- He's really... He's oddly tall, so.
- Oh, okay. Great.
- You won't miss him. Thanks.
- All right, have a good night.
- Hi. Can I get a beer, please?
- Sure.
Actually, make that two beers.
It's gonna be $8.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Hello, everybody!
Good evening, Chicago. We're the Old 97's.
Brooke?
- Are you up?
- Yeah.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
- What's up? What do you want?
I just want to say
I'm sorry that I missed the concert,
and let me know what that ticket cost,
I'll pay you back for it.
Just leave me alone, Gary.
I planned on going to the concert.
It's just, I stopped by Johnny O's and we...
It doesn't fucking matter, okay?
Would you just leave my room
and shut the door?
- Jesus.
- Please.
I didn't really know that the concert
mattered all that much to you.
Exactly.
Hold on a second here.
Let me talk for a second.
Gary...
Brooke. You broke up with me.
Then you have guys
coming over here for dates,
and all of a sudden
you ask me to go to some concert.
I mean, I just figured that, you know.
Gary.
I just... I don't know how we got here.
Our entire relationship
I've gone above and beyond for you, for us.
And I mean, I've cooked.
I've picked your shit up off the floor.
I've laid your clothes out for you
like you were a four-year-old.
I support you. I supported you, your work.
If we ever had dinner or anything,
I make the plans.
I take care of everything and
I just don't feel like you appreciate any of it.
I don't feel you appreciate me.
And all I want is to...
Is for you to just show me that you care.
Why didn't you just say that to me?
Gary, I've tried. I've tried.
Yeah, but never like that.
You might've said some things
that you meant to imply that, Brooke,
but I'm not a mind reader.
I doubt it would matter.
You are who you are.
Just leave me alone, okay?
Right now. Just shut my door.
Listen.
All right, Gary, just, please.
Just leave the room.
- Listen to me.
- Gary, just...
- I don't want to be near you right now.
- Listen to me. I just want to...
Please, just shut the door. Please.
I know. Look, I know you feel
bad, but, you know, what are you gonna do?
I mean, what does she expect, for me to
want to go with the girl who dumped me?
I don't know. She probably just wanted you,
you know, to show her the respect
of not standing her up
or some shit, who knows?
Well, damn it.
I should have just said no in the first place.
I don't know why I called...
You know what? It's her fault she got hurt.
You shouldn't even feel bad about it.
She should have expected it from you.
You're a fun guy, okay?
Everybody likes you.
You're the quickest guy I know.
Anytime we go out, I have a blast.
All right? But, you know,
everybody who knows you knows
you're gonna do what you want to do.
And if it's not what the other person
wants to do, well, that's their problem.
- That's bullshit.
- It's not bullshit.
There's plenty of times
I do shit that I don't want to do.
- That's ridiculous. No.
- Like when?
That's bullshit to say about me.
When have we ever
done something you didn't want to do?
You know, I don't know,
off the top of my head. I don't keep score...
When's the last time we went to a Sox game?
The Sox.
Not when they're playing the Cubs, either.
We always do what you want to do
and she always did what you want to do.
It's who you are.
Everybody thinks
that you're their friend, okay?
But the fact of the matter is
that there's not one person
that I know that you trust enough
to let close enough
that they could hurt you.
And her big problem
is that you really liked her.
I mean, she is the one girl you really liked.
And no matter what she did
and how hard she tried,
you were never gonna let your guard down.
That poor girl never stood a chance.
Marilyn?
- Marilyn?
Yeah.
I'm sorry. I just...
Oh, just get in here.
Oh, okay. I'm sorry, excuse me.
Marilyn, I just...
I just wanted to let you know
that today is gonna be my last day.
I'm gonna be travelling for a bit.
Here's a blank cheque.
Write down a number, I don't want to know
what it is, and go back to work.
No, no. It's not about that.
I can't accept that.
Brooke.
Travis, get your gorgeous
tuckus out of here.
If you make it to Rome,
search out an establishment
called the Padre Negro.
Ask for a strapping young
fellow named Alberto.
Compliments of M. Dean.
Well, thank you. I appreciate that.
Yeah. And, honey,
take as long as you want,
because when you're done,
your job will be right here waiting for you.
And if you discover a path
that doesn't lead back here...
Well, I hope you'll text.
I will.
And, like I said, the apartment's a mess,
but I'm moving, so...
It's okay. Relax about the place. I don't care.
- Okay. This'll just take a second.
- Okay.
Hello?
Hey. I'm in here.
Don't say anything. I...
How're you doing?
Could I talk to you in private for a second?
You know what?
This is really not a good time,
and obviously you have
something happening here,
- so we'll just be in...
- No, no, I don't have anything going on.
This is actually for you.
- I'm just gonna wait outside.
- No, no. Wait.
No, no. Really. It's okay.
I really can't do this right now.
Brooke, this whole thing
has been really tough on me
and I've tried to act like it
hasn't been that tough on me,
but the first Sunday
after me and you broke up,
it all kind of really hit me.
And I think it partially hit me
because Sunday was sort of always our day
that we would do stuff together.
But I didn't have any idea
you still cared so much.
And, you know,
when I saw you crying the other night,
that was honestly
the worst moment of my life.
Gary.
Let me just try to say
some of these things here. It's just...
Look,
I know that I've caused you a lot of pain.
And the funny thing is,
all I really want to do is make you happy.
I just want to make you smile.
Now, I've had a lot of time
to think about some of the things
that went on, and I know, Brooke,
that I don't always do the right thing
or always say the right things,
but I am willing to try
to do things differently.
And I'd be happy to go take a dance class.
Well, I would. Honestly.
I would like to go do that. Or go travel.
I mean, I'd even be willing to go to the ballet.
Although I would much rather
do the dance class or take a trip somewhere.
But I realise that's not the point.
I realise that the point isn't that at all,
because it's not really about doing things
that you love to do always,
but it is about doing things
with the person that you love.
And I love you.
- Gary.
- Just give me one second here.
I've missed you so much.
I promise you, Brooke,
I will do whatever it is that I have to do
to never hurt you again.
I love you and I'm sorry.
Okay, that's it. That's all I...
- Oh, God.
- That's all I wanted to say,
so you can go ahead now
with anything that you're feeling to say.
I don't know what to say.
Just say whatever you feel inside.
I don't feel the same way.
I don't. I just... I don't know.
Oh, God.
I just, I think... I don't know,
but I don't think I have
anything left to give.
I'm sorry.
I was hoping for...
It doesn't matter.
Oh, this is now beyond awkward.
There's some new guy
standing out in the hallway
and I think I'm gonna go.
Okay.
Thank you.
I made a dinner,
and I don't know if it's any good or not,
but you're welcome to have it.
Okay.
Gary, that's really...
That's not what you think that it is.
It's okay.
I'm gonna go take a walk.
- I'm sorry about that.
- No.
- I'm sorry I imposed.
- No, that's fine. Please.
- So, what do you think?
- I think you're right.
- I think it's great.
- Good.
- Okay.
So,
I will have that wrapped up.
Packed up, sorry, and delivered.
Thank you for taking the time
to show it to me, okay?
Sure.
- Yeah. I'm gonna run.
- Okay, I'll walk you out.
No, no, no. I can... It's okay.
So, the thing that
I was most afraid of happening happened
and I don't regret it at all,
because now she knows how I feel.
- Do you know what I mean?
- Yeah.
I think, what you got to do now
is really think hard,
because you have to find somebody
that can't be traced back to either of us
to visit this guy.
What are you talking about? I don't...
The guy who came with her.
I don't need anything to happen to the guy.
But if they could trace him
back to either one of us...
- It's not about him. I don't care about that.
... it's a problem.
- The guy, he's not a...
- They're not dumb. Cops are smart, trust me.
- Okay, but he's not a problem to me.
- Right.
Listen to me.
Promise me that you're
not gonna do anything.
I got you.
It's better if nobody...
You don't know anything.
- What are you talking about?
- I'll take care of it.
I don't want you to take care of anything.
John, do me a favour.
- I'm being serious with you.
- I know, I know. Smart. You're smart.
No, I'm not. I'm being honest with you.
- I don't want anything to happen to him.
- Me, either.
Promise me you're not gonna have
anyone do anything to this guy.
But you've gotta tell me exactly
what you're gonna tell them,
if the cops come to you.
Because if we tell a different story...
- Nothing. Promise me one thing.
- We don't care...
John, I'm gonna go home.
I can't do this. I'm exhausted.
Right, go home. Just make sure
your neighbours know you're going home.
Do me a favour. They got phone records.
Make a couple phone calls tonight.
Especially around 10:00.
- Okay. Please don't do anything.
- All right.
I don't mean it like... I mean, honestly.
No, no, I got it.
For all you know, nothing's happening.
- I don't want anything to happen.
- Right.
Say it louder.
What are you doing here so early?
Hey.
- Everything okay with you and...
- Yeah, everything's gonna be great.
I just wanna get my day started,
but I just wanted to say that
I'm sorry it took so long for me to...
I love you, Dennis.
It's all right. It's okay.
I'm sorry. I'm gonna go do the stuff.
So, that's it for all my stuff.
If you want, you could give me
your key and I'll drop it off at Riggleman's.
All right.
Thanks.
Gary.
You know, there's a thousand things I...
I would have done differently.
Me, too.
Sort of, actually, when I see this space,
I realise that if we didn't have
such a big coffee table
and that oversized couch
a pool table would have fit nicely.
Yeah.
Although the oversized couch did come in
very useful the last couple of weeks, so...
Yes, it... I guess.
Have a good trip.
Thanks.
Chicago is called the Second City
because after the Great Chicago Fire of 1871,
Chicago was rebuilt on its ruins.
The city came back even bigger and stronger
than it originally was.
So it's not really an insult,
it's more of a badge of honour to be called...
The Second City!
Okay. People, you might be able to get away
with that reaction at work,
but you are on vacation here.
If you can't blow it out here,
then where the hell can you blow it out?
Ladies and gentlemen,
show me that you mean it.
Do not make me ask you twice.
- Are you ready to see Chicago?
Yes!
- I said, are you ready to see Chicago?
Are you ready to see Chicago?
Shondra, put this babe in the air.
Let's go!
There is a bar downstairs.
Please enjoy yourself.
I know it's early in the morning,
but it is Chicago in the summer.
Who are we kidding? It's fine.
Go get hopped up,
make some bad decisions.
My jokes get better.
The buildings look bigger.
It's not so important
that everything is finished.
It's important that everything is right.
Well, what time's the presentation?
All right, I'll pick up the rest of the stuff
and I'll see you at 6:45.
Great. Bye.
Brooke!
- Hi.
Wow.
- It's good to see you.
I'd give you a hug, but my hands
are kind of full with all the bags here.
- How've you been?
- I've been really good.
- How have you been?
- I've been good.
Yeah.
- You look great.
- Thank you.
- The hair's a little different. Looks nice.
- Yeah? Oh, yeah.
- You've lost some weight.
- Well, it's very deceiving, actually.
I've managed to become thin without having
any real muscle on me whatsoever.
Very tough thing to accomplish, by the way.
I'm proud of myself.
- Well, you look terrific.
- Thanks.
- I heard your trip went really well.
- It did. It went really well.
- Oh, good.
- It was fun. It was amazing.
I saw so many amazing places. It was just...
But, you know, you do realise
how much you love home.
- It's good to have you back.
- Yeah. It's good to be back.
- And the boat. Congratulations on the boat.
- Thanks.
I'm waiting for it to get warm,
and I'm gonna come by and take a ride.
Well, anytime you want.
It'll be on the house. Come on by.
Well, I will, then.
I hope you do.
Definitely.
Well, I got to... I'm going to a meeting, so...
I got to drop these bags off anyway,
but it's really good to see you, Brooke.
- Really good to see you.
- Shouldn't...
- Sorry.
- I'm sorry.
I'm just saying we shouldn't
wait so long the next time before we...
- Yeah.
- ...catch up.
- We have a lot more to talk about.
- Yeah.
So.
- Be good.
- Okay.
- Bye.