(HORSE TROTTING)
(BELL RINGING)
Mr. Blackwood?
Sir?
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
Mr...
Mr. Blackwood, I'm
sorry. You did ring, sir?
BLACKWOOD: Come down.
(SCREAMS)
(WHEN YOU AND I WERE YOUNG,
MAGGIE PLAYING)
# I wandered today
to the hill, Maggie
(GROANING)
# The creek and the creaking
old mill, Maggie
I'm so...
So very sorry.
I didn't see the steps.
They made me do it.
I didn't...
(GRUNTS)
If I want to see
my child again,
I must comply.
Mr. Blackwood.
Please understand.
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERS)
(SCREAMING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
# ...are gone, Maggie
When you and I...
BLACKWOOD: Precious
teeth. Beautiful teeth.
Ransom for my boy.
Yes.
# They say I'm feeble
with age, Maggie
BO Y: (FAINTLY) Daddy.
# My face is
a well written page, Maggie #
(FAINT WHISPERING)
(SNARLING)
I... I brought you
something more to eat.
Not children's
teeth like you wanted,
but please accept them
in exchange for him.
CREATURES: Children's teeth.
(CREATURES HISSING)
Oh, no, that's the best I could do.
And they're my own.
You see?
My own.
(SOBBING) Please.
Give me back my son!
CREATURES: Yes, your son
is down here. Reach for him.
Son? Son!
(BO Y FAINTLY CALLING)
Son!
Grab my hand!
(CREATURES SHRIEKING)
(SCREAMING)
(INTERCOM BEEPS)
FEMALE FLIGHT ATTENDANT: We've now begun
our descent into T.F. Green Airport.
Please return to your seat,
make sure it is in...
(CART BEEPING)
She's landed.
What do you think?
Too much?
No, it's perfect.
Just like you.
(CART HONKS)
There's my girl.
Sally?
Wow! Look
how tall you are!
What are you,
17 now?
Dad, you know
how old I am.
I know.
I'm being silly.
- Hey.
- Good morning, sir.
Thank you.
ALEX: Come on.
Sally, this is Kim.
Kim, Sally.
Hi, Sally.
It's nice to meet you.
TO Y BEAR: I love you.
I love you.
Thanks.
What about a picture?
You got your camera?
It's good
to see you.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
MAN ON RADIO: Good morning,
Rhode Island!
KIM: Everything okay?
ALEX: Yeah.
We've got fog this morning
and a slight chance of a shower later on.
Smell that fresh air,
kiddo?
- Sure beats the smog of LA, huh?
- (WATCH ALARM RINGS)
(DIALING PHONE)
I have to call
Mom now.
Just press one
and the green.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hi, you've called Joanne
and the magical Sally! Leave us a message.
L.C. delivered
the flooring.
If it rains, I'm afraid
it's going to warp.
Well, just put it
in the garage.
Sally, say hello
to Mr. Harris.
Nice to meet you.
ALEX: Come take
a look at the house.
MRS. UNDERHILL: Mr. Harris. Mr.
Harris, would you give me a hand...
KIM: How's it going?
- Good.
- When do you think you'll be finished?
- No problem.
Good, huh?
- It smells funny.
- Oh, you should have smelled it before.
They had moldy
newspapers everywhere,
and dead pigeons all
over the floor and poop.
(PHONE RINGING)
- Lots of it.
- It's Jacoby's office.
Mr. Jacoby.
Oh, hey, Michelle.
Sorry.
Uh, I don't know.
Hold on. I'll check.
You got
the photographs?
I like to draw, too.
You work here?
No, Sally,
I live here.
I'm the interior designer.
Do you know what that is?
Of course you do.
You see all the animal
paintings and friezes?
They're by Emerson Blackwood,
a man who once lived here.
He was a very
famous wildlife painter.
Hey, Sally, look.
You want to try?
What do you
have there?
- I found it.
- That's mine.
It was my grandmother's. When I
was little, my mother gave it to me.
My mom gave me
to my dad.
ALEX: Sally?
You want to see
your room?
What do you think?
Kim and I worked really
hard to get it ready.
Check this out.
(LULLAB Y PLAYING)
It's pretty great, huh?
It looks better
at night.
How long am
I staying here?
What did your
mother tell you?
She told me I was
coming to visit.
But then she packed
all my clothes.
She didn't explain
anything to you?
- No.
- Sally.
Your mother and I
are worried about you.
She thinks that maybe
you're feeling sad
and she thought that... Well,
we thought that perhaps a change
might be good for you
and that you could come
and live here
with Kim and me
until we finish the work
on the house and sell it.
Then we could move
somewhere else and...
Sally? Come on.
Open the door.
Come on.
Let me in.
(SOBBING) Are you going to marry her?
(CHUCKLES)
Uh, that's between
Kim and me.
Mom said you only liked
her because she was young.
But she isn't.
She's old.
Sally.
Open the door.
Come on, sweetheart.
Sally, please,
let's talk about this.
Look, I know...
I know it must
be tough.
You've had a long flight, and
it's strange being in a new house.
I want to go
to bed now.
Okay.
Don't forget to
brush your teeth.
You'd be a terrible
poker player.
You've been ironing that
shirt for half-an-hour.
She sure didn't
take to me.
I wouldn't take
it personally.
She's like that
with everybody.
Those pills she takes,
what are they?
Adderall, I think.
Jesus.
That's her mother
for you.
That woman medicated
our dogs.
(SOFT JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING
ON STEREO)
So, what about Jacoby?
His assistant said he still hasn't
looked at the new photographs yet.
- He's had them for a week.
- I know.
We're still in the running, and
he's still coming to the dinner.
- He should just give us the cover.
- Yes, he should.
He gave it to the Spencer
restoration two years ago
and you have
done miracles here.
We have done miracles here.
It's not all about me.
Thank you.
These are new?
- Yeah.
- Great.
If we get the cover of
Architectural Digest,
we won't need to take out
another bank loan, will we?
You know what your
daughter told me today?
What?
She said your
wife gave her to you.
Kids say all kinds of
things they don't mean.
It couldn't have
gone any worse today.
(SIGHS)
I feel like
the evil stepmother.
The evil and
very old stepmother.
- Let's not forget the old part.
- (LAUGHING)
Because I was kind of thinking
you were looking a little ancient.
KIM: Oh, yeah?
- Oh, yeah.
The stuffed bear?
What was I thinking?
Oh, come on. It's great. She
likes it. I saw it in her room.
KIM: On her bed?
- Well, above the bed. Hanging by a noose.
- (KIM CHUCKLES)
That's okay. Nice sign
of affection, I think.
(KIM'S LAUGH ECHOING)
(LULLAB Y PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
CREATURES: (WHISPERING) Sally.
Her name is Sally.
(HUMMING)
Sally!
(GASPS)
KIM: What do you think?
Yeah. Looks great.
Have you seen Sally?
Yeah, she's
on the bench.
ALEX: Sally!
(SCREAMING)
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
It is not safe
for you back here.
Hey. What's going on?
Everything okay?
Keep her out from
the back of the house.
She could fall in. We'd
be in a hell of a mess.
I didn't do anything.
There's pits.
Old wells.
It's dangerous
for a child.
Mr. Harris is right,
Sally. He knows.
His grandfather
worked at the house.
- You shouldn't be back here.
- But I found a basement.
There is no basement.
Easy, Harris. I'll take her. It's okay.
It's there!
It's right there!
There's a reason this
house is called Fallen Mill.
The English had
a mill here,
and it fell
into a sinkhole.
That's why most of the houses
around here don't have basements.
This one does.
ALEX: You may want
to check this out.
HARRIS: It's unsafe
for a child.
Pull on that.
(ALEX LAUGHS)
SALLY: Look! I told you it was here!
ALEX: Can you believe this?
(KNOCKING)
This is
definitely hollow.
I'm going to
get some tools.
You sure you want
to do this now?
Of course!
You kidding?
We can fix this
easy if we have to.
You may want
to step back.
(HAMMERING)
HARRIS: Mr. Hurst, I...
(ALEX GRUNTING)
There's a door in here.
Where did you put
the old house keys?
They're in your junk
drawer in the office.
Okay.
Have a look.
ALEX: Oh, wow.
- You be careful, Sally. Okay?
- Okay.
How the hell did
we miss this?
KIM: That must be
the garden window.
KIM: It's all of his paints and old
colored pencils. This is amazing.
Wow. Alex,
look at this.
Harris, did you know
about this?
This place isn't safe.
(STAMMERS)
Especially for kids.
It's okay. I'll keep
an eye on her.
This must be where
Blackwood worked.
SALLY: I found
another door.
KIM: Look at
these sketches.
It's an ash pit,
I think.
Yeah. It's bolted shut.
KIM: These are incredible.
(GASPS)
ALEX: Okay.
Let's go, Sally.
Come on, Sally.
Let's go.
ALEX: Sally, come on.
This must be like
King Tut's tomb for you.
KIM: Which is why we
shouldn't be touching anything.
This stuff must
be valuable.
CREATURES: (HISSING)
She's gone.
No, no, she will come back.
They always do.
Yes, they always do.
ALEX: I don't think
that's important, Alan.
No, I just need
to make sure I get
the paintings and furniture
back in time for the dinner.
You told me
you could.
Come on. How long
have we known each other?
I'll write you
a post-dated check.
Hold on.
It's either walnut or
mahogany, I think. Yeah.
There you are. I thought
maybe we could bake scones.
I promised Mrs. Underhill we
wouldn't make too much of a mess.
No. That's all right.
What have you got there?
My doll.
And my drawing stuff.
KIM: Looks like it's just
you and I baking scones today.
MRS. UNDERHILL: I made
sandwiches for everyone.
(GRUNTING)
CREATURES: (WHISPERING)
Sally.
Open the grates!
Yes, yes,
open the grates.
Set us free!
Who are you?
What do you look like?
We've been locked
up for so long.
Set us free!
(GASPS)
Come down. You'll see
what it's like down here.
Wait a minute,
will ya?
There's other children down
here. They're just like you.
ALEX: Sally?
Sally.
What are you
doing down here?
- I heard something.
- Rats, probably. It's time for dinner.
It was a voice.
Really smart rats, then.
No! Listen.
Nothing. Come on.
Let's go, kiddo.
I forgot my bag.
Hurry it up, then.
(CLANKING)
(GASPS)
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
ALEX: Sally, now!
We can get this tomorrow. We can't
get the rest of these for two weeks.
What about
the burnt umber?
It's much warmer, and we can
get it for half the price.
You not hungry?
Sally?
Don't you like rice?
Mrs. Underhill made
apple pie for dessert.
Apple pie has gluten,
and Mommy says gluten is
bad for my concentration.
Oh, come on.
You love apple pie.
We can worry about your
concentration tomorrow.
Mommy says
no gluten.
What's your mother
filling your head with?
- How about some chocolate milk?
- No.
- I'll make something else.
- Hold on.
Sally, you need
to eat this,
or you can go to your room. Okay?
Good night, Dad.
What?
- Did that work on you when you were a kid?
- She's testing us, Kim.
That's what kids do.
Who's the parent here?
Certainly not me.
I didn't mean that.
No. You're right.
I'm not a parent.
- We talked about this, remember?
- No, you told me about this, Alex.
I'm not sure I'm ready
to be anybody's mother.
I had a hard enough time
getting over my own childhood
to have to deal
with somebody else's.
Listen, will you help
me with this, please?
I realize this is terrible
timing, but I don't have a choice.
I can't just
send her back.
That's not what
I'm asking you to do.
Apple pie.
Thanks.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
- Hello?
- Hi, Alex. It's Joanne.
- Hi, Joanne.
- Can I speak to Sally?
- No, you can't.
- Why not?
Because she's asleep. We're
three hours ahead, remember?
What were you thinking
not telling her
she was going to
be living here?
You and I had a conversation. I asked
you if you wanted me to tell her.
Don't do this
every time I have...
You're the one
who wanted her here.
(GASPS)
(LULLABY PLAYING)
TOY BEAR: I love you. I love you.
- (GASPS)
Did you just
speak to me?
I love you.
(SCREAMS)
(CREATURES SHRIEKING)
CREATURES: The light,
it hurts us.
Yeah. Turn out the light.
I love you.
(CREATURES WHISPERING)
Turn out the light.
We want to be friends.
Where's my doll?
CREATURES: (WHISPERING) With
us. Sally's doll is with us.
Who are you?
We're your friends.
Friends?
Where?
CREATURES: (WHISPERING) Come down
to the basement and play with us.
Where are you?
What are you?
CREATURES: Hungry.
Hungry.
Very hungry.
(WHISPERS)
I have food.
Let me see you.
I won't hurt you,
I promise.
ALEX: Sally?
- What are you doing under there?
- I'm looking for my doll.
Looking for what?
I'm looking
for my doll.
ALEX: Oh.
How about
Teddy instead?
No. That's all right.
- Did you lose a tooth?
- That's not mine.
- I found it.
- You found it? Here in the house?
Yeah.
Can I call Mommy now?
No, it's too late.
She's probably asleep.
I don't think you should keep
this. It's not very sanitary.
What about this light?
Should I...
Leave it on, please.
All right, well,
sleep well.
Oh, Sally, would you do me a favor?
Would you try to, maybe,
be friends with Kim?
- Yes.
- Thanks, kiddo.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING
ON STEREO)
Kim, have you
seen my razor?
We have to leave
in five minutes.
- Yeah. Have you seen my razor?
- Here, take mine.
Five minutes.
My dress.
(HUMMING)
Sally. I want to talk to
you downstairs right now.
ALEX: I cannot believe you
cut up Kim's clothes.
SALLY: (CRYING)
I didn't do it.
- I didn't do anything. I swear.
- Stop lying.
It was a horrible thing to
do. And it was dangerous.
You could have
cut yourself.
What did you use,
my razor?
Let me see
your hands.
- It's mine.
- What is this?
Where did you get this?
- Let me go home.
- You can't go home.
Just let me
go home.
I'm sorry
about this.
She's never done
anything like this before.
She's obviously very
angry about something.
Alex, that is not anger.
That is fear.
We need to go.
Mrs. Underhill,
Kim and I have an appointment
at the historical society.
We'll be back
this afternoon.
Sally, we're going out.
Listen to Mrs. Underhill
and do what she says.
And you think about what
you need to say to Kim, okay?
(FAINT WHISPERING)
Are you there?
Did you cut
Kim's clothes?
Do you have
my dad's razor?
You have to tell
me the truth.
If you want
to be friends.
I won't be angry.
CREATURE 1: (WHISPERING)
Sally's not angry.
CREATURE 1: They're angry.
CREATURE 2:
No, I'm not angry.
CREATURE 1: They don't
want to...
CREATURES: But we do.
CREATURES: Come
down here, Sally.
Come down and play.
(CREATURES SCREECHING)
(HISSING)
You said you
were hungry.
Do you like raisins?
CREATURES: We said
we liked them.
See? Delicious.
Delicious. Yeah.
So delicious.
Did you do
something bad?
You have to answer if
you want to be friends.
CREATURES:
Yes, friend.
Sally?
What are you doing
down here in the dark?
Were you talking
to someone?
Is there someone
here with you?
No. I'm all alone.
There's nobody here.
Why don't you go help
Mrs. Underhill make lunch?
Go on.
Off you go now.
That's right. Up those
steps! Quick as you can, now!
(GRUNTS)
CREATURES: (WHISPERING)
Harris. You old fool.
(CREATURES WHISPERING)
HARRIS: I swear. I
didn't tell them anything!
(SCREAMING)
(HISSING)
(GROANING)
No.
(YELLING)
No, please!
(CREATURES SHRIEKING)
(GROANING)
(SCREECHING)
Get away!
I had an accident!
Call for help!
(COUGHING)
(MOANING)
(GRUNTING)
Oh.
Don't look.
(SOBBING)
MRS. UNDERHILL: I could
hear screams down there.
- Noises.
COP: Did you see anything?
MRS. UNDERHILL: He asked
me to leave the cellar.
It was so dark in there,
he must have stumbled.
- Oh, Mr. Hurst, thank God!
- What happened?
- Are you William Harris' employer?
- Yeah.
There's been
an accident.
Are you okay?
Where's Sally?
I'm sorry.
She saw him.
I tried to cover her eyes,
and I was too late.
- Where is she?
- She's in the garden.
(CRYING)
Oh, I am sorry!
Sally?
Hi.
Are you scared?
Do you want
to talk about it?
Is Mr. Harris
going to die?
No, Sally.
He is going
to be okay.
Can I show you something?
This is my favorite
part of the house.
Blackwood loved nature.
He imported these fish
from Japan. And so did we.
They're called Koi.
They're considered magical.
Badgers can spot them
against the mud at the bottom
because of
their bright colors.
So what makes
them special
is also what makes
them vulnerable.
They have to be tough.
And you, too, Sally.
(CRYING) I didn't
touch your clothes.
I swear to God,
I never touched them!
- I didn't touch them.
- Sally.
I didn't! Didn't cut them, I promise.
I don't care
about my clothes.
ALEX: I can't really tell.
1804, I think.
It's hard to see. The
coin is pretty worn down.
She probably found it
in Blackwood's studio.
ALEX: I don't want her
going down there anymore.
I'm worried about her,
Kim. It's not safe.
(PHONE DIALING)
- Hey. This is Joanne.
- Mommy?
Oh, sweetie, it's you!
How are you?
Can I come home?
You want to come...
The sashimi. Stuart, the sashimi.
- I don't like it here.
- You what?
Honey, don't fret.
It's so beautiful there.
You just need to
get used to it.
But it's cold.
- Honey, what?
- My bed is too big.
- Sweetheart.
- And I think I'm getting sick.
You're not
getting sick.
It will take a little tiny bit
of getting used to,
but you are going
to be so happy there.
Okay? I promise.
You'll get used to it.
I got to go, honey.
Mommy's got to go.
I'll see you soon. Bye!
(LULLAB Y PLAYING)
Kim?
- Don't leave.
- What's wrong?
Even when I'm asleep.
And don't turn
off the lights.
I'll be right here.
Come on.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(CREATURES WHISPERING)
(SCREECHING)
Kim?
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
TOY BEAR: I love you.
I love you.
(SHRIEKS)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
(CREATURES SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING)
Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy, please!
Daddy!
Sally,
what's the matter?
(SALLY SOBBING)
I don't want them
to come anymore.
Who, Sally?
The little things.
They live in the basement.
They gave me the silver dollar.
They said they
wanted to be my friend.
But they're
horrible and mean.
Oh, Sally.
You just had
a nightmare.
Don't say that!
It's okay.
(LULLAB Y PLAYING)
My bear.
Look what they
did to my bear.
Your dad tells me art is your
favorite subject. I wish I could draw.
Drawing is easy.
The other kids can't
do feet and hands.
When you say "the other kids," do
you feel they're different from you?
My doctor back
home asked me that.
What was your answer?
Okay. Let's start
with something easier.
What's your
favorite color?
What is that? Purple?
Black.
How about these little things you
saw? What do you think they are?
Fairies.
Or gnomes.
But scary ones?
And you say they
know your name?
They talk to you?
Yes.
What do they say?
They want to play
with me.
Is that all?
They say my parents
don't love me.
Can I go now?
PSYCHIATRIST: Just a few
more questions, okay?
There is a lot of anxiety in
that little girl
and a deep belief
that she's not wanted.
I believe that's what's triggering
these fantastic episodes.
She told me she
found a little tray
filled with teeth right
inside that fireplace.
Yeah. She found a tooth, but that
doesn't mean anything, does it?
She's constructing
this elaborate fantasy
about wrinkles,
claws, fangs.
She's individuated
each one of those things,
her imaginary world,
its inhabitants.
It's as detailed as any
I've ever encountered.
What do we do?
I'd like to try her on a
stronger medication, for a start.
I'll ask her doctor in LA to
send me a copy of her charts.
You call my office,
make another appointment.
Okay, great.
Meanwhile, I'll give you
something to help her sleep.
(HORNS BLARING)
I'm going to be late.
I can't believe it.
If we don't get the
extension on this loan,
we're not going to get the
paintings or the furniture
back on time.
(GROANS)
We forgot the invitations
for the historical society.
Maybe we should just
postpone the dinner.
Kim,
it's Architectural Digest.
We have to get
the house on the cover.
- I know.
- If we don't,
I'm never going to
get my career back,
and we're not going
to sell the place.
How often have we
talked about this?
What about
what's been happening?
Harris?
That was an accident.
I'm talking
about Sally.
It's all in her head!
It's real to her. It
doesn't matter if we see it.
(HONKING)
- Come on!
- Calm down!
I'm going to walk. It'll be
faster. I'll see you back at home.
I'm not sure how
lucid he'll be.
He's pretty
heavily sedated.
(MONITOR BEEPING)
Mr. Harris, I know this is difficult,
but I need to
understand something.
I need to know what Sally
saw so that I can help her.
Is she out
of the house?
No.
Out.
She needs to be
out of there.
Why?
Why was that
room sealed up?
Grandfather.
Your grandfather
closed it up?
- Yes.
- Why?
After...
After what?
Blackwood.
What about Blackwood?
Lot 1134.
Public library.
HARRIS: Get her out
of the house.
(SKITTERING)
WOMAN ON PA: The library
will be closing in 15 minutes.
The library will be closing in 15 minutes.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
I'm looking
for the librarian.
Lot 1134.
Emerson Blackwood, Special
Collections. One sec.
Right this way.
Can't remember the last time anyone
requested these. They're beautiful.
I'm a designer. I've been
working at Fallen Mill.
Wow. Now,
that's a privilege.
Personally, I think Emerson
Blackwood rivaled Audubon.
Come across
his mural?
A mural? Where?
There in the house,
supposedly.
If you do,
I'd love to see it.
(SALLY HUMMING)
Hello?
Now, it's pretty
ironic, really.
For a committed realist,
someone who insisted on
drawing only from nature,
to do these at
the end of his life.
I've looked at everything by Blackwood,
and I've never
seen any of these.
You wouldn't. The family
made it a restricted donation.
These may never
be published.
Is it possible
to get copies?
I'll see what I can do.
"Wrinkles, claws,
teeth?"
Have you ever
read Machen?
Arthur Machen. Welsh.
He believed
in fairy folk,
these ancient entities from the
netherworld, predating mankind.
Blackwood quotes
him extensively.
Here, that line. There.
"One life must
be taken."
These creatures had
to take one human life
every time they emerged
to replenish their ranks.
Many of these creatures
fed on the bones,
the teeth of
young children.
And then there's a truce,
a pact of sorts,
between Pope Sylvester II
and these ancient beings
in the year 999.
In exchange
for human teeth,
they start leaving silver
pieces under the pillow.
Now, this is the last known
drawing by Emerson Blackwood,
made shortly before his disappearance
and the loss of his child.
His child?
Blackwood's only
son vanished, lost.
Not long after, Blackwood himself
disappeared without a trace.
No!
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
- (SALLY SCREAMS)
- (CREATURE SHRIEKS)
(HISSING)
(SALLY SCREAMING)
(SNARLING)
(GASPING)
(SCREECHING)
(SNARLING)
No!
No! Please!
(SCREAMING)
(SNARLING)
SALLY: No!
(SALLY SCREAMING)
Sally!
Sally, what's wrong?
Sally, open the door!
(GROWLING)
(CRYING)
(SNARLS)
(SCREECHING)
Oh, my God!
Oh, oh.
- (PANICKED BREATHING)
- Shh.
(BREATHING RAPIDLY) Dear,
thank goodness you're home.
- Where is she?
- I put her to bed.
She wouldn't
stop screaming.
Sally?
(GRUNTS)
(CHILD FAINTLY CRYING)
ALEX: Kim!
She's not down here.
I think she's run away.
She's done it before.
ALEX: Once she tried to
walk all the way back to LA
from our family home
in Boston.
I wouldn't be surprised
if that's what she's doing.
(SIGHS)
I went and visited
Harris today.
Blackwood had a son.
Did you know that?
And when he was eight,
he disappeared.
And Blackwood vanished
a few days later.
Why are you
telling me this?
A lot of what Blackwood wrote
at the end of his life,
it's awfully close
to Sally's story,
gnomes, creatures,
all of it.
Kim, don't tell me
you believe this.
Something terrible happened
in that basement.
- We need to leave.
- What are you talking about?
Put a million miles
between us and that house.
Every cent I have
is in that house.
And you're saying
that we just walk away?
I accept that my daughter
has problems, okay?
Thank you.
We all know that.
But they do not involve
monsters in the basement.
There she is.
Come on, Sally.
Get in the car.
Sally, please,
just tonight,
and after the party
we'll talk, okay?
Four, three,
two and one.
There.
After the party, I will
get you out of here.
No matter what.
I promise.
- Sally!
- No.
I took it from them.
- You can't have this.
- They stole it. You don't understand.
- I need it to fight back.
- Absolutely not.
Please!
SALLY: Nobody believes me.
Sally, I trust you,
and you can tell
me anything at all.
They don't like
bright lights.
Those things.
They don't?
Then I have
a good idea.
Mr. Jacoby, I am so
glad you could make it.
- Alex, call me Charles.
- Charles.
- My wife, Evelyn.
- Hello, Alex.
It's a pleasure.
Come on in.
The house looks
absolutely fantastic.
You've done
a remarkable job.
Well, thank you.
We'd love
the nickel tour.
Of course.
That's the whole point.
The foyer, obviously.
The mahogany, we shipped
from the very same vendor
that Blackwood
used in London.
It's been in
business since 1865.
You know Bill from
the heritage board.
Easy, Sally. Not everybody wants
to have their photograph taken.
So, Alex,
where's Kim?
I think she's
still upstairs.
Why don't you step into
the library, grab a drink,
and I'll join you
in a moment.
(ALL CHATTING)
(CREATURES WHISPERING)
(SHRIEKS)
Kim, hey,
what's going on?
Her drawings. They're
exactly Blackwood's sketches.
Yeah, I'm sure
she probably saw
your photographs
and copied them.
No, she didn't.
Kim, please,
Jacoby's here.
- Alex, this is your daughter!
- I know.
This is serious!
Just because you keep
denying it does not mean
...it's not happening.
- Kim, I can't do...
Excuse me,
Mr. Hurst.
When should
we serve dinner?
Ten minutes, please.
Kim, everybody is waiting.
Will you come downstairs?
- We can talk about this later.
- No.
- I have proof, Dad. Look!
- Not now, honey.
- Please!
- Not now. Come on!
Welcome, everybody.
Please, have a seat.
Uh, If I could just
say a few words
to all of you friends
of Fallen Mill,
both big and small.
Thank you for joining
us this evening.
It means a great
deal to us.
Every aspect of this restoration
has followed the exact specifications
and materials used in the
original construction of the house,
including the wood assembling
techniques, the layout in the kitchen,
even the lacquering process
for all the timber.
It's something Kim and I are very
proud of, and I'm sure all of you,
with your vast
array of expertise,
will appreciate
the attention to detail.
The art you see on
the walls, the friezes,
even the furniture
that you're sitting on,
has all been meticulously
chosen, reassembled or restored,
depending on
its condition,
to, I think, truly represent the
essence of the Blackwood collection.
So, thank you to
the heritage board
for their assistance, and
to the historical society,
and, of course, to our guest
of honor, Charles Jacoby.
Your interest
in our projects
is nothing short of
inspirationa! So, thank you.
And finally,
to the house itself.
May its newly restored
life be long and happy.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
I guess not everybody is
a fan of tonight's menu.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(GASPS)
(SHRIEKS)
CREATURES: Poor Sally.
No one believes you.
(CREATURES LAUGHING)
CREATURES: Sally.
(SHRIEKS)
(SNARLING)
(CREATURES WHISPERING)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(CREATURES CHUCKLING)
(CREATURES SHRIEK)
(CHATTERING)
(ALL SNARLING)
(SCREAMS)
What do you want?
Please just tell
me what you want!
We want you! (SHRIEKS)
(SCREAMING)
SALLY: Daddy!
Daddy, please!
Daddy!
ALEX: Sally?
- Daddy!
- Sally?
Daddy!
(CREATURES SNARLING)
Daddy, they're in here!
- Open the door!
- Sally!
(SCREAMS)
Charles.
KIM: What's going
on in there?
- (SCREECHING)
- (SCREAMING)
No! Get off of me!
Stop it!
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
(SHRIEKING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
KIM: Sally!
(ALL MURMURING)
Sally. Sally.
Look at me. Sally,
look at me. Look at me.
Picture,
I took a picture.
(SOBBING)
I think we better
call it a night.
I think we should.
It's okay.
Alex, can I talk to you?
I feel like I have
no idea what to do.
I love my daughter, Kim,
and I love you.
I love you, too.
We should go, right?
- I'll get Sally ready.
- I'll get the car.
- Will you put this in the car?
- Yeah.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(ENGINE STARTING)
SALLY: Kim?
Hi.
Where are we going?
We're going to go
to a hotel downtown.
We're going to get
you out of here.
(GRUNTING)
Alex?
It's okay, it's okay.
(GASPS)
(GROANS IN PAIN)
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
CREATURES: (WHISPERING)
A life will be taken.
One life must be taken.
Sally.
(STAMMERS)
Sally!
Child's teeth!
Kim?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Daddy?
(CREATURES WHISPERING)
Kim?
- (CREATURES WHISPER)
- (GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
Kim!
Kim! Please.
Kim.
- Wake up, please!
- (CREATURES CHATTERING)
CREATURES: (CHANTING)
Wake up, Kim. Wake up, Kim.
Wake up Kim.
Wake up, Kim.
(SCREECHES)
(ALL SNARLING)
(SCREAMING)
(WHISPERING)
The key. The key.
(GROWLS)
(COUGHS)
(MURMURING)
(CRYING)
(CREATURES SHRIEKING)
Kim, please!
Daddy! No!
Kim!
(SCREAMING)
(ALEX GRUNTING)
- (MOANS)
SALLY: Kim, please!
(COUGHING)
(SALLY SCREAMING)
Sally?
Ah.
Ah!
Sally? Sally!
SALLY: Kim!
SALLY: Let go of me!
Don't make me
go in there!
Kim! Please!
(CREATURES SCREECHING)
Kim?
- Please, Kim!
- I'm here, Sally!
SALLY: No, please!
(SHRIEKS)
(CREATURES SHRIEKING)
(SALLY SCREAMING)
Sally!
Kim?
No! Go away!
KIM: Hold on!
Hold on! I got you.
Keep them away, Sally. Use
the light. Use the light.
Kim!
Get him.
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
No! Please!
Get away from me!
Get off of me!
(SCREECHING)
(SHRIEKING)
(GRUNTING)
When I cut this rope,
Sally, you run!
Please!
You run!
You got that?
No, what about you?
No! Please!
KIM: Be strong.
(GRUNTING)
(SHRIEKING)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
(YELLS)
Kim!
(SCREAMING)
No!
(SHRIEKS)
(SCREAMS)
(SOBBING)
Sally?
Sally, are you okay?
Sally.
KIM: Alex?
(KIM SCREAMING)
Kim! (GASPING)
Kim!
Dad?
Daddy?
(SOBBING)
Daddy.
Please!
(CRYING)
That's far enough, Sally.
I love you, Kim.
CREATURES: They will find us. They
will find us and hurt us. We must fight.
KIM: (WHISPERING)
No, we will go deeper,
and we will wait.
They will forget,
and others will come.
CREATURES: (WHISPERING) When will
they come? When will we get them?
KIM: Soon, soon.
KIM: We have all the time in the world.
- Yes.
KIM: All the time
in the world.
CREATURES: All the time in the world.