Long ago in another galaxy far, far away...
Let us rock and roll with the Fat Man.
Here Fats...
Miss Givens drives me crazy.
If she holds my pipe I'm 35
the high school as I did.
I do not care,
as I sit by Marilyn Mc Cauly.
Forget it, Jonathan.
You sat her down last year,
all you did was drool.
You're funny Harry.
I've never had the chance.
The word, if we are to unif.
Here's your chance loverboy,
there is Marilyn and Rosalie.
Come on Jonathan, not ruining it.
You're with your dad his car...
Say something.
I can not.
- No guts, huh?
Look at those Jugs,
They defy gravity.
We're dead.
I had no idea it was
going to be so much fun.
Rosalie, come inside.
The water feels so good.
It does not matter so much.
I see you, Jonathan.
1001, 1002.
2000.
Do not do that.
Turn that thing off.
Where did he come from?
Oh, my God.
Okay, dude?
You came all of a sudden.
- Yes, I did.
Are you ok?
Yes.
I'm okay.
Kenny do something, he's ok.
He's hurt.
- Get in the car, he has nothing.
Everything cool, no problem.
Take care.
It was his mistake.
He came from behind the truck.
He also drove across the grass.
- He has more pieces.
I'm Jonathan Bellah I live next door.
From where are you?
- Chicago.
Are you serious?
Give me the hex again.
I said 'hex'.
Got something on wheels?
What?
Need a car?
No, not yet.
- How do you decorate?
Dad lends me his car sometimes.
What does he have?
- Studebaker.
Girls do not in a Studebaker.
Not?
- Chevy's, Ford are the best.
But a Studebaker?
Is worse than a Desoto.
What about the girls?
Are there?
All at the fair.
So it is.
I would not find them.
I understand what you mean.
I do not think you do.
I have to stay out of trouble.
Why?
I may not enjoy school anymore.
Have you put out at school?
Hoedat?
I fucked two.
Come on.
- The moms were complaining.
I was out.
Unbelievable.
You've never been binned?
What?
- You've never had any contact?
I am not a freak or anything.
Not freak, weird though.
I had the chance yet.
Is there someone you like?
- Yes.
Maybe.
- What's her name?
Marilyn Mc Cauley.
And?
She does not know I exist.
Good throw.
The fair, where is him?
- Tonight.
I'll take you.
.
What a small village.
Your dad sure the flag every morning heist
and your mom make pie every Sunday.
My mom does not bake, yours?
I have no mother.
Sorry.
Okay kid, come get it.
I want a real kiss for one euro.
Marilyn Mc Cauley is here.
With my brother.
Watch out for that tongue.
Brunette?
- The blonde.
You have competitors.
Go home.
- Jonathan Day.
Rosalie Day.
Hey Marilyn.
You got me.
Thanks Jonathan,
this was for a good cause.
I am very happy.
My turn now.
Turn it.
You have Marilyn.
Are you ready?
Thank you for your donation.
It was my pleasure.
Do you have money?
You have quite a nerve.
That kiss lasted three times
longer than normal.
I can put her feelings do not hurt?
I have 50 cents.
I took 6.
Who do you get back.
- Hey.
You have Bunny.
We met al
- I know.
I heard ringing.
It is over there.
No, from here.
I see you.
Now I've had enough.
Who is he?
I do not know.
Day.
Village idiot?
Oh, yeah.
He is also good at it too.
His dad has Brubaker.
- What is that?
The biggest clothes store in Nelsonville.
And he goes with Bunny?
What a waste.
So, you never loved one?
I bet you score within the month.
With marilyn.
Why are you so docile with my sex life?
To combat boredom.
So I stay out of trouble.
It is a challenge you know, a good thing.
Thanks, but no.
Find it for yourself.
Do you have money?
Good morning.
- Good morning.
I've been thinking about your bet.
- Yes?
What are my chances?
- You have quite confident in yourself.
Jump to it.
Rule number 1:
make eye contact every chance you have.
What if they look away?
- Keep staring, your eyelids down.
Then it seems you smarter.
Oh yeah?
- Like James Dean in 'East Of Eden'.
Like this?
This never works.
I can practice.
Where did you get the jeans from?
You have exactly one
luggage in your pants.
My mom, she has achieved.
- Shrink.
Why?
- So your balls bulge.
You have to look hot.
Girls have no balls.
So they are curious.
Is it so?
Occasionally they look to check.
Do you have a handkerchief?
- Yes.
Put it in your pants.
Here is Marilyn.
Do not stand there like a sissy.
Lean against the wall.
Everything OK, Jonathan?
Just a cramp.
This becomes harder than I thought.
Why the rush?
No hurry, Kenny.
I was just the first.
Slow down, live longer.
Here's a little bit for you.
Let the bastard if not tease you.
Easy for you to say.
Let now the title bar
discussion of our government.
Eg. If President Eisenhower died in August.
We all know who follow him.
Is not it?
- Nixon.
Exactly.
What happens if they both die?
The Communists.
Not true, Kenny.
Not even the Democrats.
- Is there a difference?
It maybe funny to you, now.
But our constitution provides for a line...
That's a difference to the
democracy and dictatorship.
When a dictator dies is
that the people hard.
Very difficult.
Now, the question is.
- I die.
I have a hard that does not break.
and if both presidents die?
Who follows?
Yes, Rosalie.
The spokesman of the
White House, Joe Martin.
And as Joe Martin dies?
Who follows?
No Rosalie,
someone else.
Jonathan?
What haunts you from?
Nothing, ma'am.
I just took my pencil.
Certainly, Jonathan.
Explain to the class once from
what we just explained...
...about the title line of our government.
Well... if Eisenhower would die...
- Get up, Jonathan.
Eh... I can not.
Why not?
- My leg is asleep.
Stand up and put your weight on it.
I can not.
- Why not?
My other leg also sleep.
Stand up and massage 'm.
Put down the books, Jonathan.
Here she comes,
just in time.
I can not.
- Where's your sense of adventure?
Hiding behind my fear of shame.
You have nothing to lose but your virginity.
I'm used to it after 17 years.
Is everything okay?
Your blood, I have no handkerchief.
I do.
Why did you do that?
I'm sorry. I did not see what I was doing.
My first chest.
Thank you said
- That's nothing.
You go the whole ride.
Have they no Elvis?
Sir Hugh will not.
What are you doing?
- I know a better version of the song.
Do you love rock and roll?
- And some classical.
My father played for The Chicago band.
It swings.
Where's your boyfriend?
Kenny?
We're not serious.
Really? He thinks so.
I think I'll go back to my friends.
- See you.
Two hamburgers...
...And two frits.
Thank you, Rosalie.
It's okay.
- Do you...
...The reading list of all Ohio?
I think so.
Need 'In The Cathur Reye' already read?
- No.
I do not like baseball stories.
Rosalie, pick up.
So there you are. hey.
You feeling better?
- Oh, yeah. Thank you.
Nelsonville be annoying
are compared with Chicago?
Yes, a little bit.
Have you 'Rebel Without a Cause seen?
- Twice.
Do you want him again?
He plays on the drive-in.
I want to go with you.
Yes, good idea.
- Here's my number.
So Saturday night.
I understood that correctly?
I had no idea.
She asked you out?
I could not say no
- She asked you out.
You bastard.
- Jonathan, come outside.
She was for me.
I have to tell you anyway
I was planning on her.
Stay calm, Jonathan.
If I say no?
We now have at least control of it.
We know where she is,
what she does.
I want nothing to do with you.
- I do not touch her.
I want bunny, remember?
Swear.
Swear that your hair does not touch.
Listen to me, I have a plan.
Bunny you ask for the drive-in.
Yes, and I'm Elvis Presley.
Are you sure that Kenny is not here?
Kenny owns me.
- You're pretty brave.
Shut up if he hears you I'm embarrassed.
Hey Gene, where we exchange?
- Stay calm, later.
It is so sad about James Dean.
Live fast and die young.
And good-looking corpse.
Gene, you are so absurd.
Why I love you so.
Lights on.
Damn.
I'm so sorry Gene.
Oh Jonathan,
it's just a movie.
It's break time.
So hurry, hurry you.
I'm thirsty.
Jonathan, do you want a Coke?
Yes.
- Get me one.
For me a shake.
- Me too.
You come along.
What a piece.
He is ok.
How's Jonathan?
Very good.
Can not we go bowling or something?
- Why?
Because the waiver is yours to see her kiss.
Do you think I am happy
Bunny behind you?
They in no danger.
Going somewhere?
What do you think you are?
- It's about me and puistenkop.
Keep your outside.
Oh no, it's Kenny.
Do not be so Kenny.
- Shut up bunny.
Did you score?
- Walk to the pump Kenny.
Let him asshole.
Shut up.
He took them not.
I was.
You took her out?
Want something out of it maybe?
Yes.
Do you know where the old mill?
- I like it.
See you in 15 minutes there.
- Ok.
Bunny Come, come with me.
I said, come on.
I better go.
But do not get lost, Eugene.
I wait for you.
Exciting.
As the movie.
I thought you had no guts.
- Let's begin.
Have you heard of the coward-Race?
I've heard.
100 meters you turn back
left tire on the white stripe.
The first that comes off is a coward.
Do you play a lot?
Always.
- Liar, you never play.
Listen, I do not.
- A little bit of fun.
Eugene wants his luck a little force.
Go fuck.
Oh shit.
Are you okay?
- Gene, are you okay?
Kenny, you okay?
Asshole.
Come to the car.
Come on, Bunny.
I kill you.
That car was my income.
How do I work?
Go inside.
Does he go to school today?
- I do not know.
I have knocked on the door but no answer.
Move around, Jonathan.
Want to talk?
Get out.
Listen damn.
I had an appointment with 'r.
- Forget it now.
I do not forget.
If you do not open I break my neck.
Thank you.
Very funny.
House arrest.
Except school.
Want some?
This is good stuff.
You must be accustomed to.
You need to simmer down.
He had no right me store for everyone.
For bunny.
Let's go.
Do you know how to run?
- Shit, yes.
What did I do?
Do sober and go to the side.
Which one of you drove?
- Ikke.
Great. Stand up.
Marc Bellah is not your father?
- Yes, sir.
You know that your dad on the street, now?
- No, sir.
Shame on you.
Normally I throw you in jail.
Only that I did not love klikspanen.
You know what guys?
Take your motorcycle.
And walk home.
Can you do that?
- Yes, sir.
Can you run?
- Shit, yes.
That was nice.
Do not you feel bad when you
before someone does something?
Kenny do you mean?
No idiot.
My dad.
He's hard and stuff.
But it's not my fault.
Have you already agree
with him talking about it?
Yes.
No.
When my mom died crept him in a shell.
He could not stomach.
When I got into trouble.
Truancy.
Autos borrow. Stupidities.
He then began to rattle me.
Next time I knock back.
It was not your fault.
He has stopped playing to me to watch.
That was the final straw.
Do not worry.
Next year you are on the unif.
Then you worry.
- Are you mold?
I'm not made for unif.
Why not?
What would you be?
Dentist as your father?
I take his practice time, Gene.
Exactly.
- What's wrong with it?
Nothing.
You're not the world's largest
seducer, Jonathan...
You need at least one family.
You can have my brother.
Thanks friend.
This is Kenny's shop his family?
The largest store in Nelsonville.
What will you do now?
Just wait.
I love this store.
What a collection.
See you at school.
You okay?
- Sure.
I was worried.
I wanted to call you.
No problem.
I wanted to let you know what I felt.
I want to see.
Tonight?
I'll be better for you.
- Yes.
Marilyn Day.
What does this mean?
- I want to save for my dad's car.
Great.
House arrest is over?
- If I did I must go home.
I saw you with Bunny in the hall.
Now you have no fear of Kenny?
- I have no fear of that idiot.
Gene, keep your eye on the matter here?
Jonathan Day.
What you gonna do with Marilyn?
Forget it.
We tried, eh?
As for the bet?
Admit it.
They need me.
I am the dreamer type.
Would you like an idiot all your life?
I'm not an idiot, Eugene.
Really?
See this?
I put him on the phone Marilyn and I'll call.
I ask her for an appointment.
They will of course refuse.
They humiliated me that snow white again.
But maybe, maybe...
...Leave me alone.
Marilyn Day, will you Saturday
with me to the movies?
Oh, Mrs. Mc Cauley?
Would you possibly take me to the movie?
No no, it was just a joke.
Marilyn Can I speak?
She said...
Yes.
I play so bad.
She said yes?
Remember boy.
You have to progress.
What does that mean again?
You have to hit.
Them?
Honey, can you bring me some coffee?
We go to church tomorrow.
I need an early start.
Good night.
Not so early.
We would rather keep for another time.
Say good night your friend Marilyn.
Good night.
Hi, honey.
Kenny came along and you missed him.
Where were you?
- I was studying French with Rosalie.
We have a key.
Just go to sleep.
Sleep well.
Not so fast.
What?
come here.
what?
You're crazy.
Where are we?
Come 'ns flat pants here.
Unbelievable.
That's not fair.
Wait a minute.
You see that horse?
This is a Quatermain.
Ready to jump.
How do you know?
Strong hind legs, long stride.
How do you know so much about horses?
My mom drove.
In the stables...
...I want to help.
It depends how you ask me.
Where are Jonathan and Marilyn?
Jonathan.
- Yes?
Not here, we should stop.
- Okay, okay.
I mean stop.
- I'm stopping.
Jonathan, pull back.
- No, not yet.
Jonathan the horn.
- Sorry.
There are people.
- They do not look.
I must not let...
- You must, you should.
It's enough now Jonathan.
Do not remember.
But it feels so good.
Jonathan, where are your hands?
- They fell off.
Do not weak.
- I admit that I am weak.
You put your hand in my pants.
- Do not worry.
They come back anytime.
- It's alright.
We can not continue.
Please Marilyn, it is already 17 years ago.
Let me go.
I said, let me go.
You need to make that door.
Somebody might fail.
What do you want?
It is a Studebaker.
What you did was indecent.
I know.
Here.
Jonathan?
- Yes?
You do not look dangerous.
While you're well.
My parents are away this weekend.
Jonathan day.
I have a headache, find mind if I afzeg?
Cancel?
Just kidding.
Come here.
Hurry.
I dribble towards the goal and go score.
I got everything from Elisabeth
Taylor his publications.
Then you have lots of books.
Remember the scene in Montgomery Cliff
Elizabeth Taylor and 'Place In The Sun?'.
Are you sure your parents are gone?
Far away.
Jonathan?
- Yes?
Do you not like?
Of course.
Do you do anything?
I had to just take off.
I mean a contraceptive.
Do not you?
- No.
I thought you was useless.
- What do you think?
Ok then, we can.
But not the whole way.
I'm a bit of it stabbing
and get out before something happens.
Promise?
- I promise.
Swear you?
- I swear.
You are incorrect.
- Sorry, I'm aiming.
Better?
Remember your promise.
- Yes, certainly.
Do not forget.
- Not at all.
Go away.
Herbie, get out.
You came, right?
You did not removed.
I was planning.
- The whole time in it?
We have never talked about.
I thought you would think I
a freak when I was a rubber omdeed.
Montgomery cliff would certainly not to do.
What are you so naive.
I'm sorry.
I did not spoil the first time.
Nobody has ever said
that this is my first time.
Something happened.
They're back.
They're back?
The back.
- I'm not.
Quick quick.
Hurry.
Marilyn, are you home?
- Yeah, Dad, is there anything happening?
Your mom forgot the wedding gift.
Can you imagine?
Maybe.
Under the bed.
- No.
The cabinet.
Out the window.
I think it is up.
Go, go.
Hi, honey.
- Daddy Day.
Get bored?
- A little.
I see you.
Mrs. Mc Cauley day.
Goodbye Mrs. Mc Cauley.
Harold.
Darn.
Ok Eugene.
It does not hurt.
Next.
What is it?
- Does nothing.
See you tonight?
- Can not.
Tomorrow. Absolutely.
I need the toilet.
How nice to see you,
my boy.
Come in and make yourself at home.
Look who's here.
Hi Kenny.
Bunny is at the top of it to do.
She'll be right down.
I put these in water.
Sit down.
Gene, what's up?
How was the dinner with
your parents last night?
It was my parents idea.
I knew nothing.
You think I do?
- Yes. I do.
You think I lie to you?
No, sorry.
- I hated all the sneaking too tired.
I know.
It will be okay.
If I got one million, then I pass
the front door like a bastard from Kenny.
Why now an issue of it.
We just hurt their feelings.
Ocharme, Mom and Dad.
- Stay reasonable Gene.
I'm unreasonable? Great.
I gotta go.
Jonathan?
You can tell a user with days.
I thought you were mad at me?
- No, my parents.
I called you but never got answer.
We can make it right.
The gala is about 6 weeks.
How fortunate I am free.
Oh yeah?
Day.
$ 1.
Can a little faster?
We have not got all day.
You've missed a spot.
Good boy.
This is one U.S. dollar.
Turn on the account.
Check the tires every post.
Thank you.
Guess.
I go to the gala with Merilyn.
She asked me.
- Fantastic.
You should go get her for me.
Her parents think I'm oversexed.
Have you already asked Bunny?
- I want to talk about it.
What do you get?
What is the service?
The usual.
Check it out.
Dinner for two.
Kenny Say, are not you going to Bunny?
- Again? Were you not there yesterday?
I've been a part of the family.
That's 95 cents.
Keep the rest.
Thank you.
Apropos Eugene. Her parents
want you to stay away there.
You're scum.
Check it out.
Stay away from her, asshole.
You miserable dog.
Look, a fight.
Remain outside.
Let him fight.
Come on motherfucker,
Come on.
Come on Kenny, get up.
Stop.
I said, stop it.
I mean, stop.
It's over.
Go home.
You okay?
- Yes.
You have him beaten.
Everything ok?
- I think my arm is broken.
Come, I'll take you to the hospital.
Wait a minute.
I know who you are.
You started it...
And you will pay for it all.
You were great.
- And my best friend is finished.
It was worth it.
- My dad thinks it is not.
Out.
Pack your bags and off the ball.
You had something to do about that boy.
You are nothing than a beggar.
You're lucky you now are not in jail.
Who pays all this?
Pack and Go.
Where should I go?
Not my problem.
That is your problem.
You're gone when I get back.
Have you heard anything?
- No.
When I hear, I tell you.
I promise.
You do the same for me?
- Yes.
I keep thinking that this is my fault.
I had to ignore my parents and him to talk.
I think that more going on.
See you.
Buy your Gala tickets now.
Is not it lonely without: what's him again?
Would he have the guts to
Kenny to come back?
He's not coming back.
I have my bracket anymore.
You look good, Rosalie.
Going to a funeral?
I wish Gene was back.
Maybe it is'm ashamed in order to be seen.
Maybe there were reasons Marilyn.
He'll be back.
Where should he go?
It's not a good time.
But Jerry Jeager here at the gala ball.
Jerry who?
- Jeager. Soccer star last year.
He called me an appointment or
had the gala ball.
What did you do that?
- I said I needed to talk to someone first.
With someone?
You mean me?
Jerry is only a few times a year...
I thought you would understand.
Sure.
Marilyn...
What?
First...
We had a bad football team last year.
Second...
You do but with a gala ball.
And third...
You and Jerry-celebrity-Jeager,
walking together to hell.
You have quite a taste for music.
Darn.
- Dancing shoes at home?
And my sweater too.
I'll leave you alone and you end it?
I thought I would never look back.
I also thought not.
I had no one to talk.
Where were you?
- I'll tell you later.
Do you know where Bunny is?
Yes, come.
You're not a student anymore.
You and Jonathan have to leave.
Right now.
Wait a minute. I'll be back.
Exuseer me.
Well, is not Eugene?
Back for more?
You're not worth it.
Let go, Kenny.
I had not run away.
My dad has put me out.
So I'm to Kentucky gone and I now work.
As a groomsman.
I love it.
I came back for Bunny.
Maybe they leave with me.
What a joke, right?
They love you very much.
- Tomorrow I'm very far from here.
Why leave?
- There is nothing left for me here.
Except you.
You still get your dentist after college.
Then I come back and you make my teeth.
Very funny, Eugene.
I want you so many questions.
I was so wrong about Marilyn
I was so busy for her...
Fucking.
I do not even know her.
I do not understand women.
I watch while I live never to housewifes.
Gene?
Jonathan?
Where's Gene?
I looked everywhere.
Come with me, come on.
Are you sure?
- Yes.
Gene?
How did you get here?
Jonathan.
Well done, wretch.
Shall we walk?
Yes.
You know I can be found.
I sit at home all alone.
And if you can not get.
Please Call me.
Do not be cruel. Your heart is pure.
Maybe I made you mad.
To something I said.
Please forget the past.
The future looks bright to us.
Do not be cruel. Your heart is pure.
I want no other love.
It's you that I think.
Do not stop thinking of me.
Let me not feeling so feel.
Come here and love me.
You know what I want you to say.
Do not be cruel. Your heart is pure.
Why should we break up?
I really love you baby I swear.
Let's go to a priest.
Let us say 'I want'.
Then you know you need me.
And I know it.
Do not be cruel. Your heart is pure.
I want no other love.
It's you that I think.
We leave together.
- Darn.
Jonathan, I do not want my parents
I do worry about.
You tell them?
- Sure.
Thank you.
I drive back.
- No.
But departure from here.
No problem.
- I need the walk.
Besides, you need an edge.
Thank you.
- Ok.
See you friend.
Thank you.
Mr. Miller?
- Jonathan Day.
I have a message from Bunny.
She has started walking
with Gene Harbrough...
...and she said you had to not worry...
Everything will be fine.
Hey, strontkop.
See you later.
Tell your friend Eugene I'm looking for.
When I'm like, I'll break 'm.
Tell him that, strontkop.
Look what that bastard did with my car.
Come on.
Damn.
Look what you my car did.
That was Gene.
Strontkop.
Jonathan, what have you done?
Rosalie...
Do you want me to cinema, Saturday?
Why do you think I
with you would go to the cinema?
Just kidding.
- Very much, Jonathan.
Great.
Maybe we better with your car.
- Yes.
Translated and SUBT by: >.