Excuse me, but aren't you Sarah Morton?
It is you. I recognize you.
Look, I'm reading your latest novel.
I love it.
I'm a big fan of Inspector
Dorwell. I've read all your books-
You must have mistaken
me with someone else.
I'm not the person you
think I am. Excuse me.
Excuse me. Good morning.
What would you like?
Whiskey, please. Ice?
Yes.
Yeah! And after that
in all the directories.
And we will renew, most definitely,
that shouldn't be a problem.
Just a minute. Hello,
Sarah. How are you?
Could be better. Is John in?
Yes, but he's in a meeting.
Who with?
Terry Long. Who?
Yeah. I'm in the process of drawing up the
contract now and it should be with you shortly.
Yeah, I'm absolutely sure.
Now, you're on what's called "a roll. "
You must keep the momentum good, take
a short holiday, but nothing to long...
Sarah!
Um, let me introduce you. Sarah Morton,
Terry Long. Terry Long, Sarah Morton.
I'm so pleased to meet you. My mother adores
you. She's read all your Dorwell books.
Right. Well, Terry, always a pleasure.
We'll speak very soon. And
congratulations again on that award.
I'm sure it's the first
of many. Oh, geez, John.
Very nice to have met you.
And do hurry. My mother's impatiently awaiting
the arrival of the newest Inspector Dorwell book.
So what award did that little shit get?
The Manchester Book Critics.
Hardly the Booker Prize, I know,
but it's not bad for a first novel.
The "little shit," as
you call him, has talent.
I just hope he sells.
I trust you taught him your favorite
motto. And what motto's that?
You know damn well. You
drilled it into me 20 years ago.
"Awards are like hemorrhoids. sooner
or later every asshole gets one. "
Did I say that?
My God, you're jealous, aren't you?
You don't look after me anymore.
Just because I give a little
fled things, some encouragement,
does not mean that
I am neglecting you...
Besides, you've never had any problems
finding inspiration for the Dorwell-Series...
You write with such remarkable
ease I wonder you need me at all.
Okay, Sarah, what's the matter?
Can't be money. You're rolling in it.
It's incredible. The only thing you
can find to talk about to me is money.
I don't give a damn about money...
or success!
- I just want to find
- - An inspiring plot.
No. You don't understand.
It's
- It's got nothing to do with inspiration.
I'm
- I'm fed up with murders...
and investigations.
Why don't you confound your critics and
write something completely different?
Put Dorwell on the shelf, as it were.
You didn't like the last one, did you? I knew
it! And you haven't had the balls to tell me.
That's simply not true. You know very well I've
loved the Dorwell series right from the beginning.
As well you might... considering
the money they make you.
Do you like France?
I like frogs' legs.
So what?
My house.
Why don't you go there for a
while, hmm? Breathe some fresh air.
It's free, it's out of season, the
weather's glorious. There's a swimming pool.
Would you come and visit me?
Well. I have got my daughter.
But maybe I'll come for a weekend.
- Are you Marcel?
- Yes.
Hello, I'm Sarah Morton.
[French:] - How was
your trip? - Very nice.
- May I carry this?
- It's on wheels.
- I'll take the small one.
- Thank you.
My car is just outside.
Okay.
The bedrooms and bath are upstairs,
the kitchen's on the left.
[French:] I'll let
you take a look around.
I turned on the hot water and gas.
If you need anything,
you've got my number?
- Yes, John gave it to me.
- Good.
To go to the village,
you can take the
footpath I showed you...
or use the moped in the garage.
The keys are in the ignition.
Thank you, Marcel. Good-bye.
Good-bye, Madame. Enjoy your rest.
Bonjour. Bonjour.
What can I get for you?
- Um - -
An aperitif?
No.
[French:] Uh, maybe something lighter?
How about a panache?
No. Just a cup of tea.
Very well.
[ Woman On TV Speaking French: ] In
Marseilles bus service is drastically reduced.
but the Metro is running at 75%.
It's the second strike in two weeks...
and passengers are growing weary -
Hello? Hello, Father. It's me.
Are you all right? Yes,
I've arrived safely.
How is the house? The house is lovely.
The weather? The weather's gorgeous.
How is the weather in
London? Doesn't stop raining.
Are you all right? Yes, I'm okay.
Have you met anyone? No,
I haven't seen anyone.
You shouldn't stay by
yourself. Try to get out.
Father. Yeah -
Look, Father, if there's a problem
of any kind, ask Mrs. smith for help.
All right? I don't need anyone's help.
Yes. You take care now.
You too. All right. Bye-bye.
Good-bye.
Hello? Sarah!
John, how are you? I'm very well.
I should be asking you that question.
So, tell me, how's everything going,
darling? Did Marcel come and fetch you?
Yes, but listen. I have just one thing
to say to you, and that's thank you.
You were right, as usual. Your
house is a little piece of paradise.
And I've already begun
working. Hmm? So soon?
Yes. The idea kept running through
my mind while I was on the train.
You know, one of those stupid things that
just latch on and won't let go. Really?
I don't know where it's heading, but
- so, what's Dorwell up to now?
Well, I'm not ready to talk
about it right now. All right.
But I think it might be quite funny.
Anyway, I'm going to wait until I'm sure.
Well, that's marvelous.
Well, I'm glad you're happy.
Have you been out and about yet?
No. I'm just enjoying the
peace and quiet here. Good.
Yeah. so, when are
you thinking of coming?
Um, I don't know.
I'm not sure. It
- It depends on the work, you know.
Um, look, I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I've got another call coming through.
Now, you take care, and call me when you're
ready to read me something, all right?
Right. Fine.
Good-bye, John.
[French:] You scared me!
Who are you? What are
you doing in my house?
Your house? This is my house!
I should be asking you.
Are you English? That's correct.
I'm Sarah Morton. I'm a writer. And my
publisher, John Bosload, is letting me this house.
Ah. so you're Daddy's latest conquest.
You're his daughter?
So what? Didn't he warn you?
No, he didn't tell me you'd be coming.
I'm not surprised. Is he here?
No. I'm here on my own.
and I'm here to work.
Maybe he'll come and visit.
I'm glad he's not here.
Are you going to be staying long?
I don't know. I don't
have much work these days.
So, which bedroom did you take?
The one upstairs overlooking
the pool. Of course.
That's the best one.
Well, I'm gonna unpack.
Sorry.
Hello. Leave your name, number
and any message you might have...
and I'll get right back to you.
Bastard! You could have told me your
daughter was coming to your bloody house.
How do you expect me to work now?
It's Sarah. Good-bye.
I couldn't get through to
London. Is there anything to eat?
Yes. Go and look for it in the kitchen.
Personally, I'm gonna go back to bed.
I have to work early in the morning.
Fine. Good night. Sarah, right?
Right.
I'm Julie.
You're not too hot
Sorry. I woke you up.
No. I was just dozing.
You must be working too hard.
You should have a swim in the pool.
The water's cold. It'll wake you up.
Well, thank you for your advice, but
I absolutely loathe swimming pools.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
I prefer the sea too.
The ocean. The crashing waves.
The feeling of danger. That you could
lose footing at any time and be swept away.
Pools are boring.
There's no excitement, no -
no feeling of infinity.
It's just a big bathtub.
It's more like a cesspool
of living bacteria.
Oh, that? No, it's just
a bit of dirt and leaves.
So. what are you
writing? A romance novel?
God, no. I write crime fiction.
Oh, yeah! That's how he makes his money.
And that's how he can afford to buy a beautiful
house in France for his daughter to enjoy.
What about you? Are
your books selling well?
- I can't complain.
- What is this one about?
Murders and a police investigation.
In the Luberon with
rich English tourists.
Listen, if you don't
mind, I do have work to do.
Okay. I leave you alone, Miss Marple.
I need to make some phone calls anyway.
[Julie speaking French
] He was at the macumba?
No way!
With Jean-Pierre?
Yeah, right.
What a pervert!
You're gross!
He came back?
I don't know.
Going shopping? No, I'm going
to have lunch in the village.
Ah, good idea.
By the way, I spoke to Marcel.
He's coming very soon for the pool.
[Julie speaking French:] His English
bitch has a broomstick up her butt.
[French:] - May I have
the bill? Please. - Yes.
Hello? Don't worry about it.
I'm not going to bother her.
Anyway, it's a big house.
Did you ring mom?
I'm telling you, she's
still waiting, so hurry up.
Yes, C’est ca. Ciao.
It's your publisher.
John? Hello? John?
He hung up.
Hello? Hello, this is Sarah Morton.
Could I speak to John, please?
He's gone out. Oh. Really?
Well, could you ask him to call
me back in France? Okay then.
Yes, thank you. Good-bye.
He scolded me. He told
me not to bother you.
He said I should leave you
alone so you could work.
Listen, Julie. I'm going
to be frank with you.
I need peace and quiet to concentrate.
And since we share
the same living space,
I must ask you just to go about your business
without getting in the way of mine, hmm?
I mean, this house is certainly big enough
for the two of us. so, please make an effort.
I was only trying to be
polite and make friends.
But if you prefer I don't
- I don't prefer anything!
I just want to work on my book in peace.
Fine. That's too bad, though, because
I just bought loads of nice food.
I guess I have to eat
my foie gras all alone.
Ca va?
[French:] - We're almost
there. - I'm wasted.
Are you okay?
- Where are we?
- my house.
You live here?
Yeah, I swear!
[French:] Can't you turn the music up?
No, the old bag's sleeping upstairs.
Oh.
Good morning.
Bonjour.
[French:] I made some
coffee, if you like.
Oui.
I hope we weren't too loud?
I don't speak French. I
can't understand a word.
Pardon.
[French Continues:] Get up!
I've got to get to work.
Just a quickie.
I'd love to, but I've really got to go.
And there's that woman.
- You saw her?
- Yeah, she's outside.
- She's a foreigner?
- Yes.
- English.
- Not bad looking.
So fuck her, if you like old maids!
I was just kidding.
[Julie, French Continues:]
Want me to drive you?
It's not far. see you later.
Thanks. It was nice.
- Call me sometime.
- No problem.
Ciao!
[French:] - Is everything
all right? - Yes.
Are you from around here?
Yes, Lacoste. Have you been there?
- No.
- The Marquis de Sade's castle is there.
Oh, right.
I've heard about it.
It's practically in ruins now, isn't it?
You can say that again.
But there's a nice panoramic
view of the Luberon.
It's beautiful.
I'll let you finish.
[French:] Oh, it's you.
Your bedroom's not big enough for you?
Yes, it is, but he snores like
a pig. I couldn't get to sleep.
Expecting another one?
Bonjour.
[French:] I've come for
the pool. Julie called.
- Hi, Marcel.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- Not bad.
- You're back already?
- I was sick of work.
I felt like a rest.
This is Sarah, a friend of my father's.
Yes, we've met.
Are you cleaning the pool today?
Isn't that what you wanted,Julie?
Sarah wants to swim, but
it's too dirty for her.
Bonjour.
[French Continues:] -
Where's the girl? - What girl?
I forget her name. The little blonde.
Julie, maybe?
That's it. Julie, right.
Check out in the backyard by the pool.
I believe she's getting some air.
Thanks, Madame.
[French:] Bernard, this is Marcel.
- He's my dad.
- Stop joking.
Come on, Marcel!
Going out? Yes. Do I have
to ask for your permission?
Well, it would be nice if you didn't
make any noise when you came home.
Yes, mother. I pity your mother.
You pity her? Why?
Well, I imagine having a daughter who comes home with a
different man every night must be difficult for a mother.
Well, you imagine wrong. You know what?
You're just a frustrated
English woman...
who writes about dirty
things but never does them.
You can shove your
uptight morals up your ass.