What the hell was that?
Hello, hello.
How are you?
Nice weather
we are having today.
Nice weather?
You think
we're having nice weather?
I guess you didn't lose
the only one...
that meant anything
in your life.
I guess you don't feel
burned out...
by the human misery
and despair...
perpetrated
by the criminal vermin...
that infest every pore
of this decaying city...
forcing you to guzzle cheap wine
and cheaper whiskey...
to dull the pain
that shatters your heart...
rips at your soul,
keeps your days forever gray.
What flavor Icee you got today?
Kiwi cherry.
Oh, baby.
Namaste.
Excuse me.
Do you have any of these
in taupe?
No taupe.
Beef jerky.
And you call this
a convenience store?
Open up the cash register,
or I'll splatter your brains.
Excuse me.
You scuzzballs mind
if I join in?
I know what you're thinking,
punk.
You're thinking...
"Did he fire 173 times...
"or 174?"
Well, do you feel lucky...
punk?
You guys got to get
that thing fixed.
I know. Don't thank me.
I'm just a cop doing his job.
You have reached the desk
of Sergeant Wes Luger.
Please leave a message
after the beep.
Yeah, Wes. It's me, Billy.
Hey! I said, "after the beep."
Well, excuse me.
Listen, it's nine thirty...
Oh, nine thirty-seven.
Look, it's just getting
too dangerous to wait here.
I got to get out.
Meet me at the Squealer's Hotel
in forty-five minutes.
I have a contact there.
Who is it?
Wilderness Girls.
A little late
to be selling cookies.
Troop leader says
we are not meeting our quota.
I'll take a couple of boxes.
That won't be necessary,
Miss York.
I got to be honest.
You look better in the wig.
My hairstyle is the least
of your worries.
Wilderness Girls, eh?
So that's how you're
moving the drugs.
Brilliant, Miss York.
Now...
Where is the meecrofilm?
The what?
The meecrofilm.
I don't know anything
about any meecrofilm.
Don't play coy with me.
This is too important.
And this is the plot.
Important enough so that anyone
within earshot...
should listen to each
and every detail?
That important.
And you're talking
about the microfilm...
which holds the recipe
for turning cocaine...
into innocent-looking cookies?
I don't know anything about it.
In a little while, Miss York,
you will be begging for mercy.
No, no. I'll beg now.
Save yourself unnecessary pain.
Tell me!
McCracken.
Thank you, Miss York.
Is that Dan McCracken
or Mike McCracken?
Mike.
Is he on Alpine or Oak?
Alpine.
Hey, psst!
Park on Third.
You'll never find a spot
on Alpine.
Thank you.
You have been most cooperative.
Don't mention it.
And, you, remember,
you saw nothing.
What you got, Irv?
Oh. Beats me, Sarge.
Dandruff, seborrhea,
maybe just dry, itchy scalp.
Have you tried this, Irv?
I use it.
Head & Shoulders?
Sarge, you don't have dandruff.
I know.
Are you ready to limbo?
What'll it be?
Matte finish or glossy?
Matte.
Good choice.
Be ready in about a week.
So what are we looking at
here, Doc?
The worst-dressed stiff
I've ever seen.
This stiff and I pounded a beat
together for five years...
so show some respect.
I'm sorry, Wes.
I see so much
of this senseless mayhem...
that sometimes I get
a little insensitive.
All right, this loser has taken
the chickenshit way out...
and punched her own ticket.
Suicide, huh?
She must have caught
herself by surprise.
Found these
on the floor near her.
Wilderness Girl cookies.
Give me a hand, Doc.
Sure.
You knew her, Sarge?
Yeah, I knew her.
She was my partner.
I'm sorry, Sarge.
Hey... hey, Sarge.
It's tingling.
Good, Irv.
That means it's working.
Here's to getting through
another lousy day.
Claire.
I miss you so much.
I'm trying, Claire.
God knows I'm trying.
But it's too damn hard
without you.
I'll get the bastards
that took you.
Well, Herb,
back to the salt mines.
Mind if I drive this time?
This is supposed to be
an express line!
No, he had fuller lips.
Pouting lips.
Wide eyes.
Yes, that's him.
Dooley, give it a break.
What's going on?
Dooley's bet us he can escape
in fifteen minutes.
- How long has he been at it?
- Three days.
Better step on it, Dooley.
You think crime's
taking a holiday?
Well, think again!
- What the hell you want, Luger?
- I want the York case.
There is no York case!
It was a suicide! Coffee?
No, thanks.
Cappuccino? Espresso?
Hey, Scotty, can you get
this machine to work?
I'm giving it
all she's got, Captain!
If I push it any harder,
the whole thing'll blow!
Give me my plate!
I don't think York
was a suicide.
She was onto something.
On something is more like it.
Those Wilderness Girls cookies
was laced with cocaine!
No wonder
I couldn't eat just one.
York left me a message.
She'd uncovered
a drug-running operation.
I think that's
what got her killed.
You don't think
it was the bullets?
Give me the case.
You're days from retirement.
Let it go.
York was a partner, a friend.
I owe her.
I owe it to every cop
who's walked a beat...
every cop who's made a bust...
who's ever laid
his life on the line!
Wait a minute!
I'm the captain here!
I do all the yelling!
If it's that important to you,
take the damn case!
Thank... thank you, Captain.
Don't be so fast to thank me!
Because you're going
to be naked on this one.
People are going to be watching!
You screw up,
you'll be hung out to dry!
You drop the ball, you'll be
left twisting in the wind!
If you embarrass
this department...
your pants
will be dancing with figs!
Is that clear?
Everything
but the pants-fig thing.
And one other thing...
Narco's sending over one
of their burned-out psychos...
to look into
the Wilderness Girl cookies.
I'm teaming him with you.
Captain, you know I work alone.
You get the case,
you get Jack Colt!
Cigarette!
Hit the floor!
Hey, back off!
Easy.
That's Luger's new partner.
Captain, you can't seriously
be thinking of using this man.
He's dangerous, a menace.
A loose cannon.
A walking time bomb.
Most of all, he is gun-happy.
Where do you get off
saying that?
I give up.
There's someone
you better talk to...
if this case involves cookies.
Not him.
Yeah. Him.
You know the rules.
Do not touch the glass.
Do not hand him
any sharp instruments...
power tools, sewing materials,
or condiments.
Make sure you stay to the left
when you walk down the hall.
He's in the last cell.
The right!
I meant stay to the right!
What?
Un papa?
Is it a code?
An obscure foreign language?
So, this is Mr. "Screw
With Your Brain...
"Eat Your Spleen...
"Wear Your Flesh As A Hair Net"
Leacher, huh?
Well, look who's
Mr. Scaredy Pants now.
Identification, please.
Closer.
Please sit.
Dr. Leacher,
we need to ask you...
There's someone out there
again, isn't there?
A bad boy with pastries.
Hai Karate. You wear that
sometimes, don't you?
But not today.
Today it's...
mentholated deep-heat rub.
You order chef's salad
with dressing on the side.
You have an attractive wife
with perky breasts...
a nine-year-old son,
and a sixteen-year-old daughter.
Who told you that?
I saw their picture
in your wallet.
We came to talk about cookies.
Quid pro quo, Mr. Colt.
What's that mean?
It means I'm pretentious.
Tell me about the worst meal
you've ever eaten, Mr. Colt.
Quick!
Uh, it was a fish sandwich at...
Don't tell him anything.
Can you help us?
You hold the key, Mr. Colt.
Look into yourself for an answer
to the cookie concern.
Look to a man with whom
you were involved.
No, no. Not him.
It was in Vietnam.
You disappoint me, Mr. Colt.
It was Mortars.
General Mortars.
W-wait a minute.
L... I never...
I didn't mean
that kind of involvement.
You were under his command.
Mortars was once my patient.
I taught him
to express his anger.
You taught him well.
Quite.
After our last session,
he started the Vietnamese war.
Seek him out...
and... when you find him,
please...
I would love
to eat his cookies...
with some fava beans
and a nice chilled Fresca.
I just got to ask.
What does human flesh
taste like?
Chicken.
Are we going to see Mortars?
Follow the lead of some
psychotic, mind-twisting...
jumpsuit-wearing sociopath?
Forget it.
I've only got forty-eight hours.
Wrong, Sarge.
Forty-seven hours,
twenty-nine minutes.
I'm looking for the man
that killed my ex-partner.
Come on, spud.
She was going to meet some
stoolie at Squealer's Hotel.
I don't need some
hotshot cowboy from...
Don't fry me!
- Not validated.
- What?
Val-i-dat-ed.
I don't need some hotshot
from Narco in my way.
You're not the only one
who's lost a partner.
You got anything smaller?
Keep it.
Anything larger?
Claire and I rode together
for seven years.
York and I
were in academy together.
Then we partnered
for five years.
Before that,
we dodged the draft together.
Before that, we played
high school football together.
Before that, we were
in grade school together...
and before that,
we breast-fed together.
What happened to your partner?
The hell of it is I don't know.
I came home one night,
and she was gone.
You two were living together?
She used to sleep at my feet
and lick my toes...
though sometimes
she'd forget about me...
and just lick herself for hours.
Personally, I don't think
it's a good idea...
to get that involved
with your partner.
You try not getting
involved with a partner...
who saves your life
one minute...
then nuzzles your crotch
the next.
Billy and I weren't like that.
She left the force
five years ago.
We didn't see each other
much after that.
When we did, she was always
excited to see me.
When Claire was excited,
she'd pee on my leg.
What do you think
happened to her?
Maybe she just took off.
I hadn't been paying
enough attention to her.
I realized
how neglected she felt...
the night she shit in my shoes.
My gut tells me we were getting
too close to someone.
When she disappeared...
I had a feeling
we were being followed.
I think we're being
followed now.
Don't look.
Just play it cool.
So, did you catch that Stallone
retrospective at the Omni?
No.
Sounds fascinating, though.
I'm going to try and lose them.
Nice driving.
Thanks.
You really got me going
You got me so I don't know
what I'm doing
You
Really got me now
You got me
so I can't sleep at night
Oh, yeah
You, you've really got me now
You got me so I don't know
what I'm doing
Oh, yeah
You really got me now
You got me
so I can't sleep at night
You really got me
Don't ever set me free...
What the hell?
General.
How's your health, Mike?
Fine.
Sea Monkeys?
Piranha.
Their lives exude
a beautiful simplicity...
savage, ruthless...
existing only to devour
and destroy...
to taste blood, to rend flesh.
Sounds like me, right?
In its own environment...
the piranha
is a ferocious killer.
In mine,
just a helpless little fish.
There's a lesson to be learned
from that, don't you think?
I have a concern
that you might alleviate.
It seems certain information
was shared...
with an individual
who might have jeopardized...
the cookie operation.
While that individual
has been eliminated...
we have yet to recover
a very important item.
Where's the microfilm, Mike?
I don't know.
I gave it to York.
I thought
she was one of your men.
Act in haste, repent in leisure.
But he who hesitates is lost.
Never judge a book by its cover.
What you see is what you get.
Loose lips sink ships.
Life is very short...
and there's no time for fussing
and fighting, my friend.
Sorry, Mike.
No good.
You've been careless, sloppy.
We just can't have that.
Where's the microfilm, Mike?
Does this have anything to do
with the Billy York killing?
Nah.
Domestic dispute.
OK, I'm going to try
and talk them out.
Hold your fire
until I give the order.
Can I have one that's made
in America, please?
You up there.
I order you
to throw your hands down...
and come out
with your weapons up.
Who fired that shot?
Sergeant...
That... that was me that...
- Give me the gun.
- I was just...
Give me the gun.
When you learn to follow orders,
you can have it back.
Oh, so we think that's funny,
do we, Officer Davis?
Maybe we'd all like to know
what's so funny.
Maybe Officer Davis
can make us all laugh.
Nice to see all those
smiling faces out there.
What do you call 2,000 lawyers
at the bottom of the sea?
A good start.
Say, why'd the guy give a name
to his penis?
He didn't want a stranger
making most of his decisions.
Thanks a lot.
You've been great.
Make sure he doesn't
get any doughnuts.
You could have gone
a little lighter on the guys.
That's how it starts, Colt.
You lighten up,
next thing you know...
all the rules
are out the window.
Tight ass.
You say something?
Pencilneck.
Butthead.
What is it with you guys?
I run a respectable place.
What are you rousting me for?
I got friends downtown.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
We haven't said anything yet.
I got nothing to say.
Park the tongue, buddy.
I'm Sergeant Colt.
This is Sergeant Luger.
You know a woman
by the name of Billy York?
You got a picture?
Oh. Ahem. Here we go.
That her?
No. That's her picture.
Nope. Don't know her.
Well, maybe this
will refresh your memory.
I don't know.
She's a little out of focus.
Is this the Billy York
informant shootout?
I don't know.
I just got here.
Wait a second.
Hey, Larry.
Is this the Billy York
informant shootout?
No.
Check out the third floor.
Thanks.
Beat it.
This is an FBI case.
All right, bring him on out.
Is he the Billy York informant?
Get your shit together.
That's Becker, four-oh-three.
Hey, you!
Not so fast.
That's better.
Nope.
I'll handle this.
All right, Becker, open up!
Police!
Now that we've tried it
your way, let's try mine.
Who is it?
Room service.
What?
I don't know nothin'.
I didn't see nothin'.
I ain't sayin' nothin'.
Nothing, the word is nothing,
not nothin'.
There's an i-n-g
on the end of it. Nothing.
OK. Nothing.
OK, you happy?
That's better.
That's not what you told York.
L... I don't know no York,
and where's my food?
We ate it, and please,
no double negatives.
Sorry.
I don't know any York.
You don't know any York?
These matches say you're lying.
Oh... York.
She was supposed to meet you
here the night she died. Why?
It's where I live.
Yeah, but why you?
The other guy couldn't come up
with the security deposit.
What do you know about a piece
of microfilm?
It's small and brittle...
and it's used
in a lot of Bond films.
All right,
I did some money laundering...
for your standard
ex-military psycho types.
Give me a name.
Weren't your parents
supposed to do that?
Who are you working with?
There's been three attempts
on my life.
Come with us. There won't be
any successful ones.
This thing is big.
It's really big.
It's bigger than Watergate.
It's bigger than Oprah.
There's nothing you can do.
They're too strong
and powerful...
and they're too...
je ne sais quoi.
We can protect you.
Le commedia est finie.
Guess that's the last time
he'll trust a cop.
Give it to me straight.
Is this it, the big checkout?
Level with me.
How bad is it?
It's not bad.
You'll be fine.
You'll be back
on your feet in no time.
Your ticket.
Don't bury me.
I'll only be a minute.
Yes, sir.
Closer together.
OK, big smile.
Beautiful.
They bought it right away.
Those two tried
to make a getaway.
They gave me a new partner, too.
This is Sport.
She likes you.
I've done worse.
What are we looking at?
A mixed breed...
Rottweiler and Chihuahua.
They must have used a lubricant.
I'm talking about the case.
Seeing Sport makes me think
I could love again.
What do you have, Irv?
I'm not sure, Sarge.
It's a nagging, itching,
burning sensation.
What the hell do you expect?
Your foot's on fire.
Hey, what you got, Sarge?
I don't know.
Nothing solid.
You got any theories?
Uh, E equals MC squared.
Anything of your own?
But I'll tell you, Sarge.
Something just doesn't add up.
What?
My wife and I haven't had sex
for two years.
I have a six-month-old daughter.
You're getting too suspicious.
This job will do that to you.
You're right, Sarge.
Thanks.
Hey, buddy, come give me a hand?
I don't know.
This may look like a suicide,
but my gut tells me...
there's something else
going on here.
Hey, weren't there five stiffs?
Damn!
McCracken's missing.
Hey! Hey, has anyone seen
McCracken's body?
I need a little help here.
He didn't just get up
and walk away!
I got something important
to show you.
So, what's the big news?
You see this?
This ring was given out
to a CIA front in 'Nam...
run by General Mortars.
When the VC tried financing
the war with cocaine...
they went in and burned it.
Twelve years later,
after sobering up...
General Mortars
went into the drug business.
I just could never prove it.
Are you telling me
you took evidence...
from the scene
of a criminal investigation?
You want to crack
this case or not?
Not by making up
the rules as I go.
Sometimes, pal, those are
the only rules that work!
Good thing
we used valet parking.
Taxi!
I guess we're making
somebody nervous.
It's going to take a lot more
than a couple of car bombs...
to get us off this case.
Not a hell of a lot more.
Luger, don't worry about
all this bomb stuff.
Happens to me all the time.
I'm not worried about bombs.
I'm trying to figure out what
to tell my wife about her car.