In other parts of the world,
young men leave home
and travel far and wide...
in search of a promising future.
Theirjourneys are often fueled
by dreams of triumphing over evil,
finding a great love...
or the hope of fortunes
easily made.
Here in St. Cloud's, not even
the decision to get off
the train is easily made,
for it requires an earlier,
more difficult decision...
add a child to your life
or leave one behind.
The only reason people journey here
is for the orphanage.
- Good morning.
- We have an appointment.
Yes. Come in.
Welcome to St. Cloud's.
We're going right upstairs
to see Dr. Larch.
I came as a physician
to the abandoned children...
and unhappily pregnant women.
I had hoped to become a hero.
But in St. Cloud's,
there was no such position.
In the lonely, sordid world
of lost children,
there were no heroes
to be found.
And so I became the caretaker
of many,
father of none.
Well, in a way,
there was one.
Here he is.
His name
was Homer Wells.
I named him after
the Greek writer.
You know, Homer, of course?
And I made his name Wells
because I could tell he was...
very deep.
In truth,
Nurse Angela named him.
Her father drilled wells, and she once
owned a cat named Homer.
Bye-bye, Homer.
- Good night,
you Princes of Maine,
- Can we see the doctor?
You Kings of New England.
- Good night.
- Doctor?
Doctor?
There's something wrong with him.
- He never makes a sound.
- He didn't cry.
Orphan babies learn
there's no point in it.
Do you think we could have a look
at someone a little different?
Thus was Homer Wells returned.
He was too happy a baby.
Bye, Homer.
The second
family to adopt him had a gift
for getting sounds out of Homer.
They beat him.
He couldn't stop crying.
Shh, shh.
Shh, shh, shh.
It's okay now.
Nobody's gonna hurt you
anymore.
Here in St.
Cloud's, I try to consider with
each rule I make or break...
that my first priority
is an orphan's future.
Twice adopted,
twice returned.
It didn't bode well.
And yet it was always clear to
me that he was a special boy.
Near the angle of the rib. And...
- It was with
Homer's future in mind...
- Homer?
- That I began his tutorials.
- Lf you're going to stay at St. Cloud's,
I expect you to be of use.
I admit
that our lessons were, in part,
- the simple expression
of a father's love.
- Homer.
But in failing to
withhold love...
and making the orphanage
his home,
had I created a true
and everlasting orphan?
- No!
- Keep breathing. You're gonna be okay.
And so my
excellent pupil learned to look
after abandoned children...
- and to deliver unwanted babies.
- Relax!
Long ago, I had decided
that sometimes...
it was the women
who needed to be delivered.
I chose my own path.
No one would ever choose
for Homer Wells.
# I saw the splendor of the moonlight #
# On Honolulu Bay #
#There's something tender
in the moonlight #
# On Honolulu Bay #
#And all the beaches
are full of peaches #
#Who bring their youth along #
#And in the glimmer
of the moonlight #
# They love to sing
this song #
#If you like
the Ukulele Lady #
- # Ukulele Lady like you ##
- Dr. Larch!
Dr. Larch!
Dr. Larch?
We have two new patients.
- One to deliver.
- Coming.
- First pregnancy?
- Yes, for both.
I presume you'd prefer
handling the delivery?
All I said was,
I don't wanna perform abortions.
I have no argument
with you performing them.
You know how to help these women.
How can you not feel obligated...
to help them when they can't
get help anywhere else?
One: It's illegal. Two: I didn't ask
how to do it. You just showed me.
What else could I have shown
you, Homer? The only thing
I can teach you is what I know.
In any life,
you have to be of use.
Of use? Of use.
That was good, Carla. That was perfect.
Everything's gonna be fine.
- I don't wanna see it.
- You don't have to see it, dear.
Don't worry.
I don't even wanna know
what sex it is, so don't tell me!
- We won't tell you.
You're gonna be okay.
- Your baby's gonna be okay too.
- I don't wanna know!
- That's a big boy.
Let me see him.
I wanna see him.
- Would you mind joining me
in the nursery?
- Okay.
Wilbur, the adopting couple
is waiting in your office.
Life is waiting.
Let 'em wait.
Where's the name sheet?
Uh, nobody's named
this one yet.
Oh, it's my turn. Henceforth,
you shall be Little Dorrit.
Oh.
No, you don't like that,
do you?
He's a boy, that's why.
Can't a boy be a Dorrit?
- I don't think so.
- You do it.
Okay.
Henceforth,
you shall be Little Wilbur.
I'm not crazy about
the "Little."
Okay, just Wilbur then.
We haven't had a Wilbur in a year or so,
have we? We used to have dozens.
He sniffs that ether.
I've seen him do it.
It's because he's too tired
to sleep. He has to.
He smells like he could
put you to sleep.
He's a doctor, Buster.
Doctors smell like ether.
- You're a doctor, Homer.
You don't smell like ether.
- I'm not a doctor.
I haven't been to medical school.
I haven't even been to high school.
- But you've studied
with the old man for years.
- I'm not a doctor.
I'm sorry, Homer.
#I saw the splendor
of the moonlight #
# On Honolulu Bay ##
Fuzzy is not uncommon.
There's something about the premature
babies of alcoholic mothers.
They seem to be susceptible to every
damn thing that comes along.
I haven't read that.
I haven't either,
but you will.
Those morons who write the books
ought to do some research here.
Isn't Fuzzy just
underdeveloped?
When doesn't
he have bronchitis?
I wouldn't call his bronchial
infection underdeveloped, would you?
Come on, Fuzz.
Here we go. Feet up.
There you are.
- What's going on here?
- Sit up straight.
- Wilbur? Wilbur, can you
come out here, please?
There you go.
- Hi, Homer.
- Hey. What is it, Mary Agnes?
Now calm down.
- What is it?
- Look.
Oh. Uh, did you bite it?
- Did you bite your tongue?
- I don't remember.
Uh, yeah. That looks like you bit it.
You'll be fine.
Well, maybe I was kissing
someone and he bit me.
Oh, I think you bit it. Maybe
in your sleep. Story time, Fuzzy.
O Lord, support us
all the day long...
until the shadows lengthen
and the evening comes...
and the busy world is hushed
and the fever of life is over...
and our work is done.
Then in Thy mercy,
- grant us a safe lodging
and a holy rest...
And peace at the last.
- Amen.
"A dog, which had lain
concealed till now...
"ran backwards and forwards
on the parapet...
"with a dismal howl.
"And collecting himself
for a spring,
"jumped for
the dead man's shoulders.
"Missing his aim,
he fell into a ditch...
"turning completely over
as he went...
"and striking his head
against the stone,
dashed out his brains."
And that...
Is the end of the chapter.
That's it till tomorrow.
Good night,
you Princes of Maine,
you Kings of New England.
Good night,
Princes of Maine, Kings of New England.
Whoa.
John, you all right?
Why does Dr. Larch
say that every night?
- Maybe to scare us.
- No, you jerk.
Dr. Larch loves us.
But why does he do that?
- Does it because we like it.
- Do you like it, Curly?
Yeah.
I like it too.
Watch the door.
You two get Copperfield
and Curly. Buster's mine.
- And remember, nobody touches Fuzzy.
- Attack!
Hey!
- Ow!
- Ouch.
What do you think
you're doing?
Children, stop it. No fighting.
Share the snowballs.
Fuzzy. Fuzzy.
Listen to you.
You've been running.
Hey, over here!
Look! Pick me!
I know the type.
They'll take one of the babies.
Mary Agnes.
Come here.
Don't run.
Fuzzy.
Curly.
John.
Hazel.
Andy.
They wanted a girl,
Curly.
Nobody ever wants me.
Oh, hey.
Hey, come on.
Come here.
You know, you're one
of the best, Curly.
And we wouldn't let
just anyone take you.
Dr. Larch wouldn't let
just anyone take any of us.
Well, that's true.
- Nobody's asked for me, have they?
- Nobody special enough, Curly.
You mean somebody has?
Only the right people
can have you.
Now what do you say
we go unpack your suitcase?
- It's movie night tonight, Curly.
- Okay.
Look. Kong thinks
she's his mother.
- His mother?
- He thinks she's his mother.
- He doesn't think
she's his mother, Fuzzy.
- He does so. He loves her.
- That's why he holds her.
- Shh, Fuzzy.
Fuzzy, how can she
be his mother?
He just thinks she is.
They want to replace me.
The board of trustees
wants to replace me.
They just want you
to hire some new help.
We don't need any more help.
Some new things would be useful.
Yuck!
Aw, come on.
- Homer, I need you.
- Happens every time.
Kong, Kong, Kong,
Kong, Kong, Kong!
Thought you'd taken care of this.
Always breaks in the same place.
- It's your splice, isn't it?
- No, it is your splice.
You blame me for everything.
Angela, we need a new movie,
a new projector, a new typewriter.
That's what needs replacing
around here.
- Wilbur, we have a delivery.
- Homer, would you get this one?
She's a patient, right?
She should see a doctor.
Homer, you are a skilled
and gifted surgeon...
with near perfect obstetrical
and gynecological procedure.
I just mean that I'd rather
fix the movie tonight.
Okay, sure.
You splice,
I'll deliver.
Come on, Fuzz.
Let's go. Let go. Come on.
Homer, doesn't King Kong
think the woman is his mother?
- That's right, Fuzz.
That's what Kong thinks.
- That's why Kong loves her.
It's your turn.
I'll get this.
Okay.
Story time!
The Personal History
of David Copperfield.
Chapter one.
"I am born."
"Whether I shall turn out to be
the hero of my own life...
"or whether that station will be held
by anybody else, these pages must show.
"I was a posthumous child.
- "My father's eyes had closed
upon the light of this world...
Six months
when mine opened on it."
His father's dead, right?
That's right, Fuzz.
Is your father dead?
Cirrhosis.
It's a disease of the liver.
What, a liver killed him?
No, alcohol killed him.
He drank himself to death.
- But did you know him?
- Barely.
But it hardly mattered
that I knew him.
- Did you know your mother better?
- Mm-hmm.
She's dead now too.
She was a nanny.
What's a nanny do?
She looks after
other people's children.
- Did she grow up around here?
- No.
- She was an immigrant.
- What's an immigrant?
Someone not from Maine.
Let us be happy for Hazel.
Hazel has found a family.
Good night, Hazel.
I was dreaming about you.
How beautiful you were.
- Ah, you weren't.
- I was.
- And I was beautiful?
- You were.
You are.
It was fantastic.
It was just the ether,
Wilbur.
- Hi.
- Hey, Eddie, look at this.
- Homer, do you ever think about
trying to find your parents?
- Not really.
Why not?
Well, they never did the things
parents are supposed to do.
Dr. Larch did those things
and Nurse Edna and Nurse Angela.
Well, I wish I could
meet mine anyway, sometimes.
What for?
Well, I'd like to show 'em
that I could cook a little.
- Mm-hmm.
- And...
that I could drive a truck.
Mm-hmm.
Sometimes I wanna meet them so I can
kill them. Just sort of kill them.
You know I'd never
kill anyone, right?
- Mm-hmm. I know.
- Get away!
Get the hell off of me!
I think Mary Agnes
could kill someone.
- What the hell do you
think you're doing?
- I don't think so.
No, she's... she's just
an emotional girl.
What's she so emotional about?
She got left here
like the rest of us, didn't she?
Throw it to Copperfield.
I go first.
I'll be on Buster's team.
Look!
Her temperature is 104.
Scoot down.
Come on. Good girl.
That's a girl. Little more.
Dear child, it won't hurt when I look.
I'm just gonna look.
All right.
Dear child, did you, uh,
do something to yourself?
It wasn't me.
- Did you go to someone else?
- He said he was a doctor.
- I would never have stuck that
inside of me. It wasn't me.
- Listen, you've been very brave.
- I'm going to put you to sleep.
- It wasn't me.
Homer, I want you
to see this.
You won't feel it any more.
You've been very brave.
We'll make it deep.
- You sure?
- You bet.
The fetus is unexpelled.
Her uterus is punctured.
She has acute peritonitis,
and there's a foreign object.
I think it's a crochet hook.
Take this.
If she had come to you four months ago
and asked for a simple D&C,
what would you have done?
Nothing!
This is what doing nothing gets you.
It means that somebody else
is gonna do the job, some moron
who doesn't know how.
I wish you'd have
come to me, dear child.
What did she die of?
She died of secrecy.
- She died of ignorance.
- Oh.
Homer, if you expect people to be
responsible for their children,
you have to give them the right to
decide whether or not to have children.
- Wouldn't you agree?
- How about expecting people
to be responsible enough...
to control themselves
to begin with?
How about this child?
You expect her to be responsible?
I'm not talking about her.
I'm talking about adults.
You know who I mean.
- What?
- It's just... It's just a marvel to me...
that you still have such
high expectations of people.
- I'm happy I amuse you.
- Look at it this way.
What choice does Buster have?
What are his options?
- Nobody will ever adopt him.
- Look at it this way.
Buster and I are sitting here
right beside you. We could have
ended up in the incinerator.
Happy to be alive under any
circumstances. Is that your point?
Happy to be alive?
Yeah, I guess so.
- You're it.
- Pass it over here.
- So many children.
Are they all orphans?
- Well, it is an orphanage.
- Who wants chocolate?
- I want some chocolate.
Hi. Okay.
They're getting in the car.
Watch your fingers.
Hi.
- Hi.
- I'm the best.
- You are?
Wow! The best?
The best at what?
- I'm the best one.
- The best one, huh?
- I'm the best one of all the kids.
- You are?
He seems like
the best one.
Well, let's see if we can take care
of that. Can you blow?
I really am the best.
I just have a cold.
Sorry. They're not used
to seeing a car like this.
Ah, it's okay.
I don't mind.
Come on.
Come on. Let's get out.
Come on now.
- Oh, sure you can. Come on.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- Dr. Larch.
- Candy.
- Hi, I'm Wally. I brought
some chocolates for the kids.
Chocolates? How thoughtful.
Come on, Curly.
- So, Mrs...
- Candy.
Candy Kendall.
Wally. Wally Worthington.
How many months are you?
- Uh, two.
- Two.
Um...
Are you... Are you the...
Are you doing the...
Oh, no. Dr. Larch will be
performing the procedure.
- Oh, good.
- Okay.
I was...
I was just curious.
Excuse me.
The woman you delivered last night,
she's complaining of pain.
Okay. I'll take a look.
Couple of minutes. Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I think
it was the ether.
Oh, the... That smell
must've got to me.
Oh, God,
this is all my fault.
Homer, Steerforth got into the pantry.
He's eaten all the pie dough.
- He wasn't sharing it either.
- He's down the hall throwing up.
- He's such a pig.
- Don't call him a pig. It's
not nice to call people names.
But he is a pig.
What kind of planes
do you fly in?
A B- 24 Liberator.
Oh. Liberator.
You enlisted?
They wouldn't take me. I'm Class 4.
I have a heart defect.
- Yeah? Is it serious?
- No.
No, it's not serious.
I'm just not supposed to get excited.
You know, no strain, no stress.
I try to keep calm all the time.
I can't imagine there's
any strain or stress around here.
Yeah.
- How she's doing?
- Just fine.
Good.
Boy or a girl?
- It's all over, dear.
- Yeah, it's all over, honey.
I would really like
to have a baby one day.
- I really would.
- Why, of course.
You can have as
many children as you want.
- I'm sure you'll have
very beautiful children.
- Oh, yes, I'm sure. I'm sure.
You'll have Princes of Maine.
You'll have Kings of New England.
Lieutenant, I think you should
find yourself some fresh air.
- I still don't feel so good.
- Cut it out, children.
Homer, what's a runt?
Copperfield called me a runt.
He was just kidding, Fuzz.
- Here.
- Orange is my favorite color.
Should I keep
the teeth orange?
Homer, look.
Homer, look, look.
Homer, when is Halloween?
- It's at the end of October.
- Is that soon?
That's a few months away, Fuzz.
Oh, it's the best time.
Homer?
- What is Honolulu?
- Honolulu?
Hmm. It's a city.
Oh. What's the moonlight like?
Well, I've never been there,
- but I think that it would
probably be very bright.
- Oh.
Why do we get pumpkins
only once a year?
Don't get too excited,
Fuzzy.
Eeew, that's disgusting!
He does this all the time.
Stop it right now.
- Hey.
- Hey. How's she doin'?
- Oh, she's fine.
- Good.
Fine.
L... I was wondering
if you could give me a ride?
Sure.
I'd be glad to.
Uh, a ride where?
Where you goin'?
We're headin' back
to Cape Kenneth.
Cape Kenneth?
That sounds fine.
Okay.
Doubtless you will let me know
what immensely worthwhile...
or at least useful thing
that it is you find to do.
I wasn't intending to leave here
to be entirely useless.
I expect I'll find some
other way to be of use.
- In other parts of the world,
I suppose there are other ways.
- Of course.
Are you so stupid you imagine you're
going to find a more gratifying life?
What you will find is people
like the poor people who get left here.
Only nobody takes care of them
half as well. You won't be able
to take care of them either.
There's no taking care
of anybody, not out there.
You know I'm grateful for everything
that you've done for me.
- I don't need your gratitude.
- I don't need this.
I know all about my condition.
It's your heart.
You ought to take it with you.
Going where?
Does he have a plan of some kind?
- Will he be back soon?
- I don't know. He's just leaving.
You were the one who says
he needs to see the world.
- That's what he'll do, is see the world.
- He's leaving.
- He'll need clothes.
He'll need some money.
- Let him try to make some money.
That's part of seeing
the world, isn't it?
Oh, Wilbur, stop it. You knew this was
going to happen. He's a young man.
He's still a boy.
Out in the world,
he's still a boy.
Just find him some clothes,
Wilbur.
He could use some clothes.
Homer.
Copperfield.
It'll be all right.
Children,
up on the porch. Up, up.
Say goodbye.
Wave from here.
- Bye. Bye.
- Bye, Homer.
Bye, Homer.
Come on.
- I can walk. Put me down.
- Nope. I wanna carry you.
- No, it's okay.
- Here, let me get this.
Wally, put me down.
Okay. Okay.
Hey.
Coming with us?
That's good.
You never know when
you're gonna need a doctor.
- Do you want me to put the top up?
- No.
- You might get cold.
- I want some fresh air.
She'll be just fine.
Is he gonna come out?
- Bye, Homer.
- Bye, Curly.
Sorry I have to go.
It's not fair.
You're too old.
I couldn't find Buster.
Maybe you could tell him that l...
- Bye, Homer!
- Don't go too far!
Homer, bye!
Hey, Homer!
Let us be happy
for Homer Wells.
Homer has found a family.
Aren't we all happy
for Homer?
- Yes.
- Good night, Homer.
Good night, Homer.
Actually, the army's
given me leave twice.
First, when my father died.
And now I'm on leave to help
my mom with the harvest.
She's no farmer.
Apples were my dad's business,
but with the war on
she's short of pickers.
- Wally thinks apples are boring.
- I never said they were boring.
Yes, you did. You said apples
weren't exactly flying.
- They aren't.
- I think I would like
the apple business.
- You're a little overqualified,
aren't you?
- No.
- No, not really. I need a job.
- Where are you headed?
- I don't know.
- What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
Is your family in
the apple business too, Candy?
No. But I work there.
I like it.
My dad's a lobster man.
- Oh, wow.
- Mm-hmm.
I've never actually seen
a lobster.
Are you serious?
I've never seen
the ocean either.
You... You've never
seen the ocean?
That's not funny.
That's serious.
It's beautiful.
Yeah.
Do you have cramps?
They'll ease up soon.
As long as the bleeding
isn't heavy, it's normal,
it should taper
off tomorrow.
Catch!
All right.
- Throw it back.
- Okay.
All right!
Put your fingers on the laces.
Here's China.
Here's India.
- Mm-hmm.
- Seven-hour round trip flight.
It's called the "Burma run."
And this part's called " Flying over
the hump." These are the Himalayas.
How high do you fly there?
Well, I have to fly 15,000 feet
within the first 35 minutes.
Otherwise we won't make it
over the first mountain.
- They got the worst
air currents in the world.
- Dangerous, huh?
Yeah. Actually,
I volunteered.
Did you really?
Hey, look. If you're serious
about wanting a job, picking
apples isn't that boring.
Yeah? Oh, I would
love that, Wally.
- See you around, Homer.
- Oh, yeah.
- Thank you, for everything.
- Mm-hmm.
Hi, Sam.
Hi, Dad!
Come on.
You're gonna meet my mom.
By the way, I've been
at a wedding, all right?
If it comes up, that's where
I met you, at the wedding.
Wally?
Wally, is that you?
Mom, this is Homer Wells.
- How do you do, Homer?
- Oh, good. How do you do?
He's the most overqualified
apple picker you'll ever meet,
but he's dying to learn.
Really? Were you a friend
of the groom's, Homer?
Homer's a friend of the groom's,
the bride's, everyone. Come on.
In that case, maybe you'd
like to stay to dinner, Homer?
- Another time, Mom.
You gotta meet Mr. Rose.
You used up
all the hot water!
- You're usin' my soap, ain't you?
- I ain't usin' no soap.
They're migrants.
They pick the fruit.
All kinds.
They travel up and down
the coast with the seasons.
The trick to Mr. Rose
is you have to let him be boss.
Oh, excuse me.
- The sink's backed up again, Wally.
- Not again.
- Thought you said you was
gonna get us a plumber.
- Rose, this is Homer.
- Homer, this is
Mr. Rose's daughter, Rose.
- You a plumber?
Homer's the new picker.
He's gonna stay here with you.
- He's stayin' here?
- Yeah.
Uh-oh.
This daughter of mine, she's just Miss
Hospitality, ain't she, Wally?
New picker?
You got lots of experience, I expect.
Homer's got no experience,
Arthur,
but he's smarter than I am
and he's a fast learner.
Mr. Rose is gonna teach you
the apple business.
Well, I believe
this is history.
We're makin' history,
Wally, ain't we?
We're makin' history
havin' this young man stay with us.
- Why don't you
show him around?
Your name is Rose Rose?
- Pretty, ain't it?
- Very.
- You like to read?
- I really can't read that good.
Homer, what does
this say? Here.
"I looked at the stars
and considered...
"how awful it would be for a man
to turn his face to them...
"and he froze to death
and see no help or pity...
in all
the glittering multitude."
More.
Since you the one...
who's smart enough to read,
what's this here?
- It's a list of rules it seems.
- Whose rules?
I imagine they're for us,
I suppose.
Go on then.
Read 'em, Homer.
"One: Please don't smoke in bed.
It's too late for that one.
Keep reading, Homer.
Two: Please don't operate the grinder
or press if you've been drinking."
You know, they ain't
our rules, Homer.
We didn't write 'em.
I don't see no need to read 'em.
Okay.
Good night,
you Princes of Maine,
you Kings of New England.
Hoo! Remember this.
In the morning when the grass
is wet, you can make it slide.
- Feel it?
- Yeah.
It's almost like flying.
Watch out for the trees.
Trees are flak,
antiaircraft fire...
from the geeks
on the ground.
- Hey, Homer.
- Hi.
I was just showin' Homer
the orchard.
- Kind of a geography lesson.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- What's that?
- What?
- This, here. Looks like you've
been giving him flying lessons.
Ah, he loved it.
Didn't you?
Wally here thinks people
like being whacked by branches.
- Oh, I liked it.
- Really?
Yeah!
- You're unbelievable.
- Well, thank you very much.
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Sorry.
That's Vernon. You better stay away from
him till he gets to know you better.
- Then you best stay away
from him even more.
- Homer.
Lieutenant's calling you.
You better watch your ass, Homer.
Hey, Wally.
- You gettin' along okay?
- Yeah.
- Guess what.
- What?
I'm shippin' out today.
It's a little sooner
than I expected, but...
I wanted to make sure that you're
settled and happy enough considering...
Are you bored stiff or do you think
you can stick it out a bit?
Yeah, of course.
I'm grateful for the job, Wally.
I'm grateful too. It gives me
peace of mind knowin' you're
here keepin' an eye on things.
- Well, that's good.
- You about ready, Homer?
Yeah.
- Uh, look, Wally, thanks.
I'm lucky I met you.
- I'm the lucky one.
- No, really, I'm lucky.
- Do you wanna fight about it?
- Kidding.
- Oh, okay.
- Take care of yourself.
- Okay.
Bye.
Okay, Mr. Rose.
Turn. That's right.
Turn and pull.
Just like that. Good. Good.
Okay, that's good. Right now
you're pickin'mostly cider apples.
All these drops here,
they good only for cider.
And you're picking apples with
the stem only half the time.
Golden rule, Homer. You wanna
pick the apple with the stem.
Now, see that there?
The spur right above the stem?
That's the bud for next year's apple.
That's called the "spur."
Pick the spur,
you're pickin' two years in one.
You're pickin' next year's apple
before it have a chance to grow.
So you wanna leave that.
- Okay.
- All right, let me see you work.
Yeah. That's good.
Yeah, that's much better.
That's better.
I can see you got yourself
some education.
Them good hands you got.
Them hands you got, they know
what they're doin'. Ain't that right?
- I guess so.
- All right.
- You keep on workin', Homer.
I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Wilbur? Wilbur?
Wilbur?
You should read this.
It's from the board.
Another letter.
"Merely suggesting that some new blood
might benefit you all.
Someone with new ideas in
the obstetrical and pediatric fields."
I think they're just testing some ideas
for our next meeting.
Dr. Holtz seems nice.
I think he only wants to help.
He's a goddamn psychiatrist!
Of course he wants to help.
He'd be happy to help
to commit me.
It's this Mrs. Goodhall
you have to be careful of, Wilbur.
We have to be more
than careful of Mrs. Goodhall.
She has enough Christian zeal
to start her own country.
I'd like to give her
a little ether.
- So, what are you going to do?
- Take this.
Homer Wells, born
Portland, Maine, March 2, 1915.
But Homer
was born here.
- In what was it? 1922?
- Mm-hmm.
Graduated Bowdoin College,
1935.
Harvard School of Medicine,
1939.
- That's you, Wilbur. You went there.
- An internship,
and two years of training at
the Boston Lying-In, South End Branch,
he was judged an accomplished
gynecological...
- and obstetrical surgeon...
- That's not him.
With experience
in pediatric care.
Wilbur, you're making
this up.
Angela, the board
is going to replace me.
That is what
the new blood is for.
You mean they're going to
replace you with someone
who doesn't perform abortions.
Well, we can only guess at that.
They are against the law.
These credentials
are against the law.
We all know I trained Homer, so his
credentials are as good as mine.
And don't be holy to me
about the law.
What has the law ever done
for anyone here?
So, what do you think
about my candidate?
What about school records?
Homer doesn't have any diplomas.
Come here, Edna, please.
Come here.
He will have them.
Wilbur!
I don't know...
All of these on there, okay.
- Gotta pack 'em tight now, y'all.
- I got it.
What do you think we do?
- All aboard, Mrs. Worthington.
- Thank you, Arthur.
How's this crew this year?
Got any rotten apples?
- It's a good crew, ma'am.
- Hey, Rose Rose.
- You tryin' to break my finger? Damn!
- Just an accident.
Excuse me.
Well, maybe we got one bad apple,
but it's nothing we can't handle.
I see.
How's young Homer
working out?
- Good. He's a smart young man.
- Hey, Homer.
- Wally was right about him.
Real hard worker.
- Good.
Mornin', Miss Worthington.
Why don't you come up and visit
me at the house? I know I've
got clothes that will fit you.
- Okay.
- I'm sure I can find
a ton of things to fit you.
- Rose don't really need
any more pickin' clothes, ma'am.
- Uh-huh.
- Now don't be a party-pooper, Arthur.
I have
a beautiful blouse...
- Hey, Rose Rose.
- Homer.
- Hey.
- Hi.
How you feelin'?
When I'm not thinking
of Wally, I'm fine.
I'm not really good
at being alone.
Oh.
Feeling much better.
Thanks.
Hey, listen.
Maybe if you're free, you'd like to come
and have dinner at my dad's place?
- Okay.
- You haven't seen
a lobster yet, have you?
- No.
- Oh, good.
You're hungry, right?
- What is that?
- It's a drive-in
movie theatre.
- It's a movie outside?
- Yeah.
- Oh, can we see it?
- Okay.
- It's closed now
because of the blackouts.
- Oh.
It's so big.
You smoke?
You want a cigarette?
Okay.
Wally would kill me
if he saw me doin' this.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
So, you like movies?
Yes. Seen only one, though.
You've seen only one?
Which one?
Uh, King Kong.
It's really good.
Mmm. Oh.
Wilbur, it's a pie apple. Here, look.
See? Try one of those.
So he's an apple expert now,
is he?
Oh, my, yes.
That's a far superior taste.
And crisp too.
So many apples
are disappointingly mealy.
Wilbur, he picked these
for us himself.
You don't find it depressing
that Homer Wells is picking apples?
Or that he can't be bothered
to write us a proper letter?
Wilbur, it's a gift.
I'll show him a gift.
I'll send him a gift
he can use.
One of the most popular
stars on the screen.
Today he's Lieutenant Stewart,
U.S.A.
Crossing the equator, there's a lighter
side, as novices are introduced...
- to the traditional realm
of King Neptune.
Boxing matches, helping relieve
the monotony of long, weary days at sea.
Well, it looked
like you liked it.
I did like it. All I said was,
it's no King Kong.
I mean, first she loved him,
then she didn't. Then no one
else could have him.
No, but she did love him.
How many women have you known?
And what did she
die of exactly?
She was torn apart.
She died of a broken heart.
Oh. Well, I just...
I need a better
medical explanation.
Torn apart. At least King Kong,
he knew what he wanted.
Hey, what you doin'
with that Candy, Homer?
Makin' history, I suppose.
- You ain't gettin'
in no trouble, I hope.
- No trouble.
That Candy, she's
the nicest girl I know.
She's about the most beautiful
girl I've ever seen, but I
don't know if she's the nicest.
She's the nicest and most beautiful
girl I've ever known.
See, that sounds like
you in trouble already, Homer.
Sounds like big trouble
to me, Homer.
- I'm not in trouble.
- Yeah, you is.
I know when people
are in trouble.