Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I haven't got time
for this Mickey Mouse bullshit!
You want cooperation?
Come up in my office, room 4602.
Kids should be at school.
Come on, that's my ball!
Give that back.
Where you goir?
Damn! Where you goir, man?
That's my ball!
Follow the blue car.
You want me to blast the music
and go through the lights?
No, drive slowly.
Take the hundred bucks,
and shut the fuck up.
I do not want to fight you,
but you leave me no choice.
Boy, you just gave me
a great idea!
- I mean a big one!
- Welcome back to E! News Daily...
our 30-minute look at the latest
in entertainment news.
I'm Bianca Ferrar.
It's for you.
A present.
Do you want me to open it?
I'll open it.
How do you like it?
Nice, eh?
Mr. McGuffin?
Can I have a word with you?
Here. It's for a contract.
Twenty grand, right?
His name is Norman Stansfield,
and he's in room 4602...
in the D.E.A. Building,
26 Federal Plaza.
- I'm not taking it.
- Why not?
- It's too heavy.
- Well.
Will you rent me your gear
for the day?
I never lend out my gear.
But...
you still have your gun.
Use it.
Just do me a favor.
Don't shoot out the window.
Why are you so mean to me?
Wildly killing people
you don't give a shit about...
but you won't get the bastards
that killed my whole family?
Revenge is not good
once you're done. Believe.
- It's better to forget.
- Forget?
After I've seen the outline
of my brother's body on the floor...
you expect me to forget?
I want to kill
those sons of bitches.
Blow their fucking heads off.
Nothing's the same
after you've killed someone.
Your life is changed forever.
You have to sleep with one eye open
for the rest of your life.
I don't give a shit
about sleeping, Leon.
I want love...
or death.
That's it.
I want death.
Get off my case, Mathilda.
I'm tired of your games.
There's this really great game, Leon.
Makes people nicer.
Starts them thinking.
The kind of game you love.
If I win...
you keep me with you...
for life.
And if you lose?
Go shopping alone, like before.
You're gonna lose, Mathilda.
There's a round in the chamber.
I heard it.
So what?
What's it to you if I end up
with a bullet in the head?
Nothing.
I hope you're not lying, Leon.
I really hope that deep down inside
there's no love in you.
Because if there is...
just a little bit of love in there
for me...
I think that in a few minutes
you'll regret you never said anything.
I love you, Leon.
I win.
I took a hit.
I need a hand now.
I know she's young,
but she learns fast.
Kids need to be shaped
into something, right?
I know. I taught you that.
But ain't there an age limit?
She's 18.
Really?
How about something to drink, Tony?
Sure. Manolo, glass of milk
for Leon.
Nice tattoo.
Manolo, make that two.
- What's that for?
- Can't afford to catch cold.
First you find out
where the chain is.
You can't see it,
but you can feel it. Here.
- I'll ring, you start talking.
- What do I say?
Whatever you want.
- Yes?
- Hi.
It's Susan.
I'm sorry. You must have
the wrong door, little girl.
I don't know any Susan.
Move back a little.
I can't see anything.
The light's out.
It's all dark out here.
- Mister, I'm scared.
- Okay.
What the fuck are you doing?
Open up.
If it leaves your mouth,
I'll pull the trigger, capisce?
Here's okay.
Let it go.
I said, "Let it go."
Move. Move over.
Easy. Easy.
Easy. Careful.
You want me...
Go ahead. Your turn.
Help me.
Please don't beat me.
Sir?
Sir, it's not my dope.
Sir, look l...
A little left, please.
Before... Ple...
Now, the security shot.
No, the second goes
higher on the chest.
Aim for the heart and lungs.
There. Right there.
You see?
The first shot takes him
out of order.
- The second finishes him off.
- What are you fucking doing?
Never in the face.
If they can't recognize the client,
you don't get paid.
You could take out anybody
and said you did the job.
- Got it?
- Got it. Never in the face.
- Now you can put the tools away.
- What are you fucking doing?
What the fuck is going on?
Hey, mister!
What are you fuckin...
You see, when you use
the silencer a lot...
you have to put
a piece of cloth here...
because it gets very hot
and could burn it inside.
A damp, black cloth is the best.
What you doing?
We said no women, no kids.
Who do you think this is gonna kill,
junkies and monkeys?
Now it's clean.
Let's get out of here.
I thought we don't have
the right to drink.
I know, but we're making
an exception for your first time.
Well, if we're making exceptions
for a job well-done...
how about a kiss,
like in the movies?
Yes.
What you doing?
- I'm going to kiss you.
- I want you to stop, please.
Come on. Just a kiss.
Stop. Everyone is watching us.
Go sit down.
Enjoy.
- You don't believe me, do you?
- How's that?
- When I say I'm in love with you.
- Mathilda, please drop it.
- Just change the subject, okay?
- Okay. Sorry.
So, how old were you
when you made your first hit?
Nineteen.
Beat you.
- What you doing?
- Can't afford to catch a cold.
- There's no doorbell.
- So knock on the door.
- Yes?
- Hi.
I'm looking
for Mr. Reubers apartment...
but it's all dark out here
in the hall, and I'm lost.
Just a second.
You want more? Come on.
Show your fucking face.
You think you're going to
get me that easily?
When it's tough like this,
you know it's gonna be ugly.
Better make it quick or else
we'll be all day listening to his crap.
Asshole! Come on, show me
your fucking face, faggot!
- Come on, gum trick.
- Hey.
What about the ring trick?
You know that one?
Ring trick? Come on, asshole.
I'm waiting.
Show it to me, motherfucker.
That's the ring trick.
Mario, go back to the barbershop.
We'll finish later.
Leon, what's up?
All done already?
Nicer than people, eh?
I told you that.
You got a problem?
Get the chair. Sit down.
I was thinking.
If something happens
to me someday...
Hey, Leon,
nothing's gonna happen to you.
You're indestructible. Bullets
slide off you. You play with 'em.
Tony, I thought about my money.
You remember the girl
who came here the other day?
Her name is Mathilda.
If anything happens to me...
I'd like you...
to give her...
my money.
You can count on me, Leon.
Thank you, Tony.
I won't be long.
- Did I do something wrong?
- No.
This one is too big.
Yeah, and I only get the leftovers,
is that it?
Mathilda, since I met you...
everything's been different.
So I just need some time alone.
You need some time
to grow up a little.
I finished growing up, Leon.
I just get older.
For me it's the opposite.
I'm old enough.
I need time to grow up.
Shit.
Come on! Hustle!
- Good shot.
- Come on.
You're new, aren't you?
Fifth floor, right?
- You can't sit here like that.
- Really, why not?
Nothing's free.
Like a parking meter.
When you stop, you pay.
It's the law.
- Only on T.V.
- What'd you say?
- Forget it. How much is your meter?
- Ten dollars...
a month.
Got change?
Don't worry about it.
We'll do ten for twelve.
I'll pay now for
the rest of the year.
Okay, a year.
Does paying rent here mean
I have to put up with you guys?
So go play somewhere else.
I need to think.
Stand up.
Don't you like your job?
Food.
- Where you going?
- Special delivery, room 4602.
Sign here.
Come here.
- Have a nice weekend, girls.
- Thanks.
I'm gonna go
to the restroom.
Special delivery?
Let me guess.
Chinese?
Thai, maybe?
I've got it.
Italian food.
What's your name, angel?
I want you to put the sack
on the floor.
Good.
Now I want you to tell me everything
you know about Italian food.
Don't forget the name of the chef
who fixed it for me.
Nobody sent me.
I do business for myself.
So this is something...
personal, is it?
What filthy piece of shit...
did I do now?
You killed my brother.
I'm sorry.
And you wanna join him?
It's always the same thing.
It's when you start to become
really afraid of death...
that you learn
to appreciate life.
Do you like life,
sweetheart?
That's good.
Because I take no pleasure...
in taking a life...
if it's from a person
who doesn't care about it.
Stan, I've been looking
all over for you.
- I checked upstairs...
- What? I'm busy.
It's Malky, man.
He's dead.
Malky was makir a buy for us
from the Chinaman.
But they got nothir
to do with it.
They told me this guy came
from the outside. He was a pro.
He was fast.
He fuckircame out of nowhere.
Boom, shoots the Chinaman dead
in two seconds.
Easy, man.
I'm a cop.
Then turns around,
says something to Malky like...
No women, no kids.
I think
it was somethir personal.
Death is whimsical today.
Blood, do you hear me?
Yeah, I hear you, Stan.
Just chill out, man.
Would you take her
up to my office?
All right.
Jesus fucking Christ.
"Leon, my love.
I know where to find the guys
who killed my brother.
Their boss is Norman Stansfield.
He's in the D.E.A. Building, room 4602.
I'm gonna do them myself.
If something goes wrong,
I left you 20 grand on the table.
It's for a contract.
Five grand a head, right?
I know I'll feel better
after I do this.
I love you. "
Wait. I won't be long.
I can't park in front like this.
It's a federal building!
He's gonna do the same exact thing
that I said.
A nine "millie."
Bullets.
Another nine "millie."
What'd you plan to do
with all these guns?
Maybe she was planning on
taking out the whole building.
Holy shit!
What's this? Lunch.
Careful, Blood,
might be poisoned.
There's no anchovies on this.
Is that what you call "I won't be long"?
I been here for ten minutes.
I did my best.
Do you like it?
Yes.
So say it.
I like it.
Not thirsty?
You know, a girl's first time
is very important.
It determines the rest
of her life sexually.
I read that once in one
of my sister's magazines.
My girlfriends told me
they hated their first experience.
That's because
they didn't love the guys.
They just did it to show off.
Afterwards, they started liking it,
like cigarettes.
Will I like it the first time?
Mathilda, no.
Why not?
I just can't.
- You love someone else?
- No.
I mean...
There was someone a long time ago.
Before I came to the States.
Her father didn't want her
to see me.
She was from
a very respectable family.
Mine was...
you know...
not so respectable.
Her dad went nuts every time
she'd take off to see me.
She still snuck off
to see you, right?
Right.
See, nothing can stop love, Leon.
He killed her.
One shot through the head.
They kept him in jail for two days,
and they let him go free.
They said it was an accident.
So...
one night I...
waited for him.
Five hundred feet with a lens.
He also had an accident.
The same night I took a boat
and came here...
to meet up with my father
who was working for Tony.
I was 19.
Since then I've never left
the city, and...
I've never had another girlfriend.
You see, Mathilda...
I wouldn't be a good lover.
Okay.
Would you do me one favor?
What?
I'm sick of watching you
sleep on your chair.
We're gonna share the bed.
I don't think it's a good idea.
It's okay.
Put your legs up on the bed.
Yeah. That's nice.
Put your head down.
It's okay. Relax.
Good night, Leon.
Good night.
I want a piece of cake first!
Manolo, take the kids
in the kitchen.
I have a lot of respect
for your business, Tony.
When you've killed for us
in the past...
we've always been satisfied.
That's exactly why today
is going to be very hard for me.
I hope you'll excuse my mood.
My man was killed
right here on your turf.
The Chinks tell me
that the hit man...
was kind of the Italian type.
So we figured that Tony
might know something.
Wait. There's more.
You're gonna love this.
A few hours later, a little 12-year-old
girl comes into my office...
armed to the teeth, with the firm
intention of sending me to the morgue.
Do you know who came and got her
right there in my building?
The very same...
Italian hit man.
I'm dying to meet him.
Relax. Everything's fine.
Sleep well?
I never really sleep.
Got one eye open always.
Yeah, I forgot.
I never saw someone with one eye open
snore so much.
- I snore?
- Like a baby.
I'm gonna get some milk for breakfast.
I won't be long.
Don't forget the code
when you come back.
Two knocks, then one,
and two knocks again. Right?
Right.
Ring these up.
I'm gonna go get some milk.
From here on out,
you don't make a sound.
You answer my questions
by nodding yes or shaking your head no.
Is he alone?
Does he expect you?
Do you have keys
to the apartment?
Is there a code, a way of knocking,
so he knows it's you?
Alpha team.
- Final position. We're ready to go.
- Be careful.
What up? Move! Fuck.
Shit.
Alpha team. Man down.
I told you.
- Bring me everyone.
- What do you mean, "everyone"?
Everyone!
Take this.
Go take a look.
- Don't move.
- Do you see anything?
It's the guy. He's here.
He's got a gun to my head.
Nobody moves.
- Let the girl go.
- Take it easy, man!
Okay, the girl's comir out.
Let the girl go.
Grab the axe off the wall.
Over there. Go!
You're coming with us.
Christ, he shot him!
Bastard!
Move!
- Shut
- Shut the fucking water off!
- Got it.
Come!
We're in a bad way here.
Send the cats.
I don't know what happened.
I didn't see 'em coming, I swear!
I just went shopping and I came back,
and they were everywhere.
Stay away from the window.
Come here.
Snipers.
Okay, now, get this fucking asshole
out of there.
- How are we gonna get outta here now?
- Leave it to me. We're checking out.
But it's not big enough for you.
It's barely big enough for me.
- We said no discussion.
- No, I'm not letting...
- I'm not going! I won't go!
- Listen to me.
We have no chance together.
But if I'm alone, I can do it.
Trust me.
I'm in good shape.
I know I've got a lot
of money with Tony.
We'll take it and leave together,
just the two of us.
Go.
You're saying that
so I won't worry.
- I don't wanna lose you.
- You're not gonna lose me.
You've given me
a taste for life.
I wanna be happy,
sleep in a bed, have roots.
You'll never be alone again.
Please, go now, baby. Go.
Calm down.
Go now. Go.
See you at Tony's. I'm gonna
clean them all. Tony's in an hour.
I love you, Mathilda.
I love you, too, Leon.
Hey, what is going on up there?
Take the guy out, not the building.
We've got one breathing here!
Get a medic on the horn!
Clear the hall!
Let him through!
- We've got a wounded man. Make way!
- Down those stairs.
Let's go! Move!
Get that guy off the stairs!
- Get your team back out there!
- I got him!
We've got two men comir
down the stairs. Let's hurry!
You okay?
Hey, I need a medic over here!
Move your fuckir asses.
Squad Number One,
what's the status on the apartment?
Can't see shit. Too much smoke.
Give us five minutes.
You got it.
What? Two hundred men can't find
one man and a girl?
Did you find the girl?
How are you doing?
Take your mask off, quick.
Let me see you. That's deep.
Right. And this one here...
You're from the 3rd Precinct?
Let's open up
his sleeve a little bit.
All right, fine. Put it down.
This one.
You stay there for two minutes.
I'll be right back.
Let me put the mask back on.
I breathe better with it.
You're all right.
Sit tight.
Come on, everybody out!
Let's go! Out!
Clear the way, men.
What are you doing here?
Get out. Come on.
At your service.
This is from...
Mathilda.
Shit.
Get out of here!
Leon asked me
to help you out...
if somethir happened,
and I think somethir happened.
He put aside
a little cash for you.
So what I'm suggesting
is that...
seeir as how
you're still so young...
I should hold the money for you
until you're older.
Like a bank, you know, except...
it's better than a bank
'cause banks always get knocked off.
No one knocks off old Tony.
But it's your money.
In the meantime...
all you gotta do is come here
every once in awhile...
and I'll dish it out
so you can have a little fun.
Here.
- Here's a hundred bucks to start.
- Can't I get a job instead?
Ajob?
What the hell can you do?
I can clean.
I ain't got no work
for a 12-year-old kid...
so get it out
of your goddamn head!
It's over!
The game's over!
Leors dead!
You hear me?
Come on. You think
I ain't hurtir too?
But he's dead.
You're gonna forget all this craziness
and get your little ass back to school.
Now take this money
and get the hell outta here.
Don't let me see your face
till next month...
'cause something tells me
I'm about to lose my famous kind streak.
My parents...
died...
in a car accident
four weeks ago.
It was terrible.
We didn't have the time to get to know
one another when you first came here...
but I want you to know I'm not the kind
of woman who'd let down a child...
whatever her situation,
whatever her mistake.
So I'm going to help you and do my best
to welcome you here again.
But on one condition:
You have to stop lying to me,
Mathilda.
I want you to take a chance...
and trust me.
Tell me what happened to you.
My family got shot down
by D.E.A. Officers...
because of a drug problem.
I left with the greatest guy on Earth.
He was a hit man, the best in town,
but he died this morning.
If you don't help me,
I'll be dead by tonight.
- You know her?
- I've never seen her.
I think we'll be okay here.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org