Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Next, please.
Next in line, please.
Next, please. Next.
How you doing?
Can I see your documents?
What's the purpose of your visit
to the United States today?
Two weeks holiday.
Do you have
a return-trip ticket?
Excuse me. No photography
in the F.I.S. area.
Is he traveling with you?
Are you two together?
Sir, why don't you come on up?
Join us.
Is there a problem?
No, but if you're together,
I want to talk to you together.
-Can I see your documents?
-Sure.
Passport, please.
Are you related?
Yes. He's my friend.
You're a Czech national.
You're a Russian national.
-How do you know one another?
-We know each other from Prague.
How long are you
planning to stay?
Two weeks.
I'd like him
to answer for himself.
He doesn't speak English.
No, sir.
I speak very good English.
I'm here for movies.
For movies?
I don't understand.
When I was a boy...
I've seen at my school movie
called "It's Wonderful Life"...
directed by Frank Capra.
Ever since, I want to come
to United States...
Iand of the free,
home of the brave...
country where anyone
can be anything.
Bullshit!
"Abandoned Baby
in Times Square."
Come on,
it's too fucking soft.
It won't work,
and it won't get the numbers.
What are you suggesting, Robert,
we manufacture bad news?
It's what they tune us in for.
We're a tabloid show.
They tune in for rough stuff.
The network's up my pretty
little ass to make a change.
Every lobbyist, mom,
and politician...
is screaming about violence
in prime time.
We've got to broaden the format.
You broaden the format.
In the end, they'll run
the story with the juice.
They want ratings
as much as I do.
If it bleeds, it leads.
-What do you got for me?
-Ride-along with Eddie Flemming.
Fuck, again?!
On the cover of "People"
this week.
He is not new.
I love Eddie,
he's a dear friend...
but we've done him to death.
No, this is very good.
The psychiatrist
is going to trial tomorrow.
The ratings'll
be through the roof.
What's Eddie working on?
Staking out
a Jamaican serial killer.
That sounds good.
I don't want
just blood and guts!
I want to broaden the format!
I know they brought you in here
to raise our standards...
to be the journalism cop--
-Excuse me!
-You're killing my show!
Don't forget,
Eddie's always good TV.
Not when he's drunk.
He's got a new cure for that.
When?
Tomorrow at lunch.
Ready, set.
Let's go.
Thrill of the hunt.
Girls, girls, girls!
I am the resurrection
and the light!
Check it out.
Taxi!
"Fuji color.
"Adjustable shutter speed.
"Night vision. Infrared.
"Black and white.
"Make your own movies."
Damn !
Watch where you're going!
Where'd that big guy go
with the video?
He stole my camera!
Stop that guy!
-Go!
-Stop that guy in the cab!
Bryan, we're pulling up now.
This is important.
I need fresh footage
for the piece on Eddie.
You come in fast on my signal
with the camera rolling.
So, what's unique?
Not what, who.
From Jamaica.
His girlfriend took too long
putting her makeup on.
They were late for a party.
-He stabbed her with a bottle.
-Jesus Christ.
That's unique, all right.
Shit.
He still went to the party.
Top floor, back room.
Eddie, autograph, mon.
Phone number.
Why your picture not on this?
-Bounce.
-All right.
Yo, Unique.
Five-O's on the way, bro.
Cops? Yeah, mon.
-Let's go.
-Love you, too, man.
-Who does he think Leon was?
-It won't matter.
He'll hear the cops are coming
and just get out of there.
Come on. Be quiet.
Right. Stand by.
Standing by.
You going to be home tonight?
We're running the Geller piece.
You're on it.
You ran that thing
a thousand times already.
So what?
He's going to court tomorrow.
The psychiatrist's trial
is starting.
Ratings will be
through the roof.
Get out. Get out. Get out.
Do me a favor.
Cut my interview out.
What for? Jesus Christ.
You getting shit from downtown?
Fuck 'em.
You're the only one
making big cases in this town.
I bring the big cases,
that brings the big news.
That stuff hurts
as much as it helps.
Get real jealous downtown.
Stay behind me.
Hope this fuck don't run.
My knees are killing me.
Be quiet. Get back.
You're worried about my safety?
I'm touched.
Go! Get away!
-Just keep them out of my way.
-Right.
-You ready?
-Yes, Robert, we're ready.
-I'm ready.
OK. Let's go.
Just get out!
Come on, you fucking guys!
Come in rolling!
What's your rush?
Going to a party?
What you chase me for?
You always leave your house
like that?
This not my bloody house!
-You live here, or you don't?
-Me don't live here!
That sounds like burglary
to me, pal.
Any chance
we could get that again?
I didn't want to do it
in the first place.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Turn that fucking thing off!
Are you out of your mind?!
Jesus Christ,
where the hell were you?
You two are a waste
of my goddamn life! Fuck!
No, Emil, get the position.
What?
First scene of my new movie.
Collecting our share
from the bank job.
And action.
Just a moment!
It's Emil.
Kalinka
Kalinka, hey!
Kalinka, Kalinka
Hey
How are you?
Beautiful necklace.
Emil, it wasn't my fault
you two got caught.
I know.
Please, it's his fault.
It's really his fault.
Trying to get the bank clerk's
phone number.
How could I wait?
Let's forget all this shit!
Hang on. Calm down.
Calm down.
You know what?
Give me my money.
Emil, we spent it.
What?
Emil, look at the way we live.
I'm a plumber.
-You think...
-Nice watch.
...l'd be working
if I had money?
What's going on?
Just give me my money.
-I'll help you.
-You'll help me?
Yes. I get you ajob.
A job?
Yeah. The money is good.
A job as a plumber?
Yes. It's easy. It's good.
You think I came to America
to work?
No way.
Emil, we started over.
You can, too.
Emil, please. I'm your friend.
-Sorry.
-It's my fault.
Emil. Please.
Emil, put down the knife!
You spent all my money
while I was in prison?
You're telling me to get ajob?
As a plumber
fixing fucking toilets?!
Put down the knife!
-You're my friend!
-Yes, I am your friend.
You're my best friend!
Please, put down the knife.
Emil, please.
Shut up!
She saw.
-What are you looking for?
-Her wallet, you idiot.
Daphne Handlova.
Six-month visa.
Still here after two years.
She'll call the police.
She will!
She is illegal!
Turn that fucking
sick thing off!
Do as I say!
What are you looking for?
Bohemian barbecue.
What you got for me?
I don't have time for this.
Where you think you're going?
Get the hell out of here.
You'll make me bust your ass?
I'm not telling you again.
This ain't a smart move.
Give me your fucking money--
Yo, man--
Happy?
Now you're under arrest.
-What are you, the cops?
-Fire department.
Firemen don't carry guns.
Guess again.
I'm an arson investigator.
We do everything cops do.
Come on !
You got to un-ass me, man.
We're getting up on three.
One, two, three.
Why don't you let a brother off?
No harm, no foul.
My bad, dawg.
What's up, man? Come on !
-Put your hand up there.
-What you going to do?
-Where you going?
-I'm going to a fire.
-Hell, no!
-I'll send a cop right back!
Oh, hell, motherfucker!
You can't leave me handcuffed
to no goddamn tree!
Some freak'll come stab me, man !
Make sure EMS is standing by.
We'll have to take
the bodies out pretty soon.
Let's get the fourth winches
to the front of the building.
Chief, you first due?
Yeah. I got two roasts
on the top floor...
but you don't have
to investigate...
because Homicide's here.
Homicide? Who let them up there?
I didn't make this
a crime scene yet.
It's Eddie Flemming.
Fuck Eddie Flemming.
Jordy, where you been?
We got a celebrity.
I heard.
Who the hell let him up there?
Don't know. Think Eddie'll
give me his autograph?
Maybe he'll give you
a kiss, too.
Whoa, shit.
-Hey, Cap.
-Bobby.
Stairs are soggy.
-Hey, Eddie.
-What?
Looks to me,
from the sixty-nine position...
that they were doing each other.
They must've been
smoking something...
and they were so wacked
out of their heads...
that they got careless,
lit up the mattress...
and set themselves on fire.
I don't know.
We got the experts here.
Show 'em what you found.
Hope you don't mind, guys.
We thought you needed help.
Not at all.
Detective Flemming?
Bobby Korfin.
How you doing, Bobby?
My uncle Tony
used to work with you...
Mind putting that cigar out?
Trying to pick up a scent.
Sorry.
I'm glad you guys
got it all figured out...
but you mind if we go
through our routine?
Give us something to do.
We don't mind.
No, no, no. Certainly.
-Appreciate it.
-Be our guest.
Thanks.
Talk about smoking after sex.
We got a fast-burning fire.
We got some good
low patterns down here.
Mouth's clean.
Clean?
You think a couple of crackheads
burned themselves up?
That's what it looks like.
They're burning, they're still
going down on one another?
Got to hand it to them.
I guess some people have
their priorities straight.
I guess they do.
Flammable.
Thank you.
What's that?
Evidence of a homicide.
-You know what that is, right?
-No. What?
Punch a hole in the corner.
I want to look at the floor.
You got it.
No soot in their mouths...
means they weren't breathing
before the fire.
This cloth means they were
doused in a flammable liquid...
and then positioned on the bed.
To the untrained eye,
it looks like an accident.
No offense.
What's he looking for?
He's looking for a timer.
Here you go.
Big double homicide.
Good.
Take some deep breaths.
You see the look on Eddie's face
when you handed him that timer?
Damn,
I wish I had a picture of it.
-He knew all along, though.
-What?
Why do you think
he was so quiet?
He was testing us.
You think so?
Detective,
does it look like a murder?
We haven't determined
the exact cause of death yet.
There's a lot of answers to get.
-How many victims?
-We got two bodies.
Have you identified
those bodies?
No, not positively.
Is it drug-related?
We don't know the cause
of the fire or the deaths.
We get them all,
we'll let you know.
What's in your hand? Evidence?
Something we found on the scene.
Whether it's evidence or not
has yet to be determined.
-Thank you, Detective.
-You're welcome.
Look over here, Eddie!
Come on, big shot!
See you.
-Do you see her?
-Who?
There was a woman in the crowd.
She looked scared.
Looked like she wanted
to talk to us or something.
Aw, shit.
Get a blanket.
Now here you come.
It's about fucking time.
What the hell happened to you?
She stripped me, man.
A bag lady.
Stripped all my clothes off.
Grabbing my nuts.
It was disgusting.
Consider yourself lucky
because I won't lock you up.
You're free to go.
A dog pissed on me, man !
You violated my civil rights!
We got you for robbery one.
Take a walk.
So, before you slept with her...
with your own son's wife...
did you take even a second
to think about the consequences?
I take full responsibility...
for sleeping
with my daughter-in-law.
I had very low self-esteem.
I felt like I had
to compete with somebody.
It just happened to be my son.
So you're blaming this all
on having low self-esteem?
I had a lot of
behavioral disorders.
A behavioral disorder
and low self-esteem...
makes you have sex
with your son's wife?
It's not all his fault, though.
It isn't all his fault.
What about your wife?
He's ignored me for months.
I had no one around.
I didn't think that he loved me.
How could somebody
who loved somebody do that?
That's the lowest thing
you could possibly do to me.
"Self-esteem."
"Low self-esteem."
Don't speak to me in Russian.
You got it?
Just erase it!
Why don't you look at him
and tell him you're sorry?
Daphne Handlova.
What's this?
"Worldly Escorts."
"Worldly." What is it?
What is it?
-Really, I'm serious.
-Get on your knees.
Get on your knees.
Look me in the eyes, apologize,
and let me see if I believe you.
I'm sorry for what I've done.
I'll never do it again.
How come we don't believe you?
Are you looking
for companionship?
Yes. I'm homesick.
I can set you up
with a real fine date.
Do you have Eastern European
girl, Czech girl?
Of course.
Ask her for her passport.
Whatever you want.
As a matter of fact, I have
a lovely Czech girl right here.
Send her. I take her.
What's your address?
-Can you forgive him?
-Give me a hug.
Wait a minute. Hold on.
That's a start.
That's a good start there.
Maybe Eddie will put you
in his next movie.
-Yeah, you think so?
-Yeah. You can play his wife.
What's up, Chief?
What the hell is that?
What's in your hand? Evidence?
Something we found on the scene.
Whether it's evidence or not,
we're not sure yet.
You gave Eddie Flemming
the evidence?
Who did cause and origin?
Who do you think did? We did.
Then why didn't you
talk to the reporter?
We got more important things
to do...
Iike finding out who did it.
Oh, really?
Don't you guys understand?
It is all about image.
The better we look, the more
money I get to pay overtime.
Good evening.
I'm Robert Hawkins,
and this is "Top Story."
Tonight, an exclusive interview
with Stephen Geller...
who horrified the nation
two years ago...
when he went berserk
and murdered three clerks...
in a Manhattan shoe store.
But now,
Mr. Geller's claim...
spoken softly
and articulately...
is that he is the victim.
Hard to believe.
Watch.
These people died...
because of the criminal actions
of my psychiatrist.
He didn't insist
I stay on my medication.
So you feel no responsibility
for killing these people?
My finger pulled the trigger...
but morally,
I'm not responsible.
My psychiatrist knew
what I was capable of.
How can I know?
I'm not a doctor.
That seems very savvy
for a man that's been found...
mentally incompetent
to stand trial.
I'm a victim here, too.
My life has been
permanently disrupted.
Permanently disrupted?
Hasn't this incident,
as you call it...
jump-started your career
as an artist?
Isn't there a movie
in the works about you?
We're in negotiations.
That's correct.
But doesn't the "Son of Sam" Iaw
prohibit convicted criminals...
from profiting
from their crimes?
Doesn't apply to me.
I'm not a criminal.
I wasn't convicted.
I was found to be
temporarily insane.
I love America.
No one is responsible
for what they do.
-Get in the bathroom.
-We'll fuck her first.
-Fuck her first, right?
Stay there! Shut up!
Right?
I'm Honey from Worldly Escorts.
You called us?
And how are you tonight?
Where's the Czech girl?
Baby,
I'm whatever you want me to be.
I'm a little schoolgirl,
I'm Mommy, I'm a Czech girl.
I like to do business
before we get to pleasure.
Can you put the money
on the dresser?
Yeah, but I need the Czech girl.
Daphne--you know her?
It's an outcall service
run from a loft.
I don't know the other girls.
-You going to get undressed?
-Where's the escort service?
That's confidential.
Can you put the money
on the dresser, please?
Yes. Sure.
Thank you.
I'd like to talk with the person
who runs the service.
Can you give me her address?
Do we have a problem?
Good, because there's no reason
for us to have a problem.
I'm going to make you feel
real good.
Sorry, no smoking.
When I'm through with you...
you won't even remember
the Czech girl.
Listen to me.
I don't want sex.
Just give me the address,
please.
I don't give a shit
if you want sex or not...
but you're paying me
for my time.
Just listen to me.
Just give me the address,
and then you can go.
OK, just--No--
What are you doing?
Listen to me.
You got to help me!
Calm down and listen to me.
Give me the fucking address,
and then you go!
Please, you got to help me.
I need your help!
All right! OK! OK!
It's in my purse. No!
Shit! God!
What?!
Help me!
No! Help me!
No! God! Someone!
Please help!
No! Help!
The thing that stood out
about this girl were her eyes.
She had the most amazing
huge blue eyes you've ever seen.
I mean,
just absolutely beautiful.
How long they been living
in your building? Four years.
Yes, I'll hold.
I'll call as soon
as we know something more.
-What do you got?
-Milos and Tamina Karlova.
They were quiet,
kept to themselves.
Landlord don't know
who your girl is.
OK if I smoke?
It's your crime scene now.
You can do whatever you want.
Did you watch the news?
No, I must have missed it.
Well, just so you know...
I gave you guys all the credit.
Just so you know...
I don't really care
about that stuff.
Why should you?
I don't even watch TV.
Good. That's commendable.
-You get a report from the M.E.?
-Sure did.
I want to ask you something.
You got a problem with me?
If you found me
stepping on your crime scene--
and it was my crime scene
yesterday--
it might piss you off, too.
What about the report?
You were right.
They were dead before the fire.
The man was stabbed so hard...
the tip of the knife
broke off in his spine.
That usually indicates
something pretty personal.
Super said he's seen her before,
but she didn't live here.
Prettiest suspect
I've had in a while.
I don't know if she has anything
to do with this.
I saw her after the fire.
I thought it was a lead.
Thought maybe she saw something.
Why would they
have taken the trouble...
to position the bodies
like that?
Maybe they're trying
to send somebody a message.
Burial rites are taken seriously
in Eastern Europe.
-Could be to humiliate them.
-How do you know?
My folks were from Poland.
Where?
Sure it was a knife?
Really? OK.
There was another murder
on 8th Avenue in a hotel.
A stabbing.
Clerk said a Russian
rented the room.
Mind if I go along with you?
This isn't a fire.
There's nothing for you to do.
I'll watch you.
Maybe I'll learn something.
This isn't homicide school, kid.
But if you want to help,
take that.
What's this?
The matching set
for the murder weapon.
This is our second day
in America.
First day was very exciting,
full of thrills and chills.
Over here is the costar
of my new movie.
My partner Emil.
Who's this?
That is New York's finest.
Yeah, that's his case.
Is that all you want?
Do you know how much killer gets
for movie rights?
It says he wants a million.
A million?
You're kidding.
The killer gets a million
for television interview?
It pays to be a killer
in this country.
Taking a bath.
Any l.D.?
-P.D. only.
-No, he's OK.
We still got to run some prints.
This kid here from midtown
caught the case.
-How you doing? Tommy Cullen.
-Hiya, son.
A pleasure to finally meet you.
This is what we got.
Figure she's a prostitute.
Judging from the defense wounds
on her arms and hands...
she was really fighting
for her life.
The room was registered
to a Frank Capra.
Capra?
Who said this guy's Russian?
The clerk.
Check with the switchboard.
See what calls came from here.
I'm on it.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
We're waiting on the M.E.
to find out if she was raped.
We got a shitload of prints,
but they could be anybody's.
Anybody take a piss lately?
Check the toilet seat.
Only one guy checked in?
You want to go
to homicide school?
Let me show you something.
The killer was standing there,
slashing her.
At death, the heart stops,
so you don't bleed anymore.
See these two marks?
Somebody else was standing here
while the killer stabbed her.
Murph.
What kind of knife
we talking about?
If you look at the marks
on the wall over here...
they're wide but not very deep.
This was not your everyday
kitchen or pocketknife.
What if the tip was broken off?
Could be. Then we'd
probably find it somewhere.
I think we already found it.
There was only one phone call
made from this room last night.
I dialed it,
and it was an escort service.
-Did you identify yourself?
-I'm new, not stupid.
Call communications. Let's get
an address on that number.
Good work.
Thanks.
-Going to the escort service?
-I'll let you know what happens.
Eddie, you the man, bro!
Eddie, this is ridiculous.
If I ride with you,
we can talk over the case.
I'll tell you what.
I'll bounce this coin.
You win, you come.
If you don't win,
you don't come. Fair enough?
All right, but I call it.
You call it.
One, two, three...
-Tails.
-Heads. You lose.
That's bullshit.
I didn't get to see.
Go ahead. I'll call it.
Heads.
See? You lost twice.
See you around.
Come on.
All right.
I can't say that.
I don't know.
That supposed to be funny?
Yeah, come on.
I'm just joking.
Thanks for letting me come.
No problem. Souvenir.
Two heads.
-Who's there?
-Better than one.
Police. We want to ask you
some questions.
-You have a warrant?
-We're not busting you.
It's Detective Eddie Flemming
from Homicide.
Just open the door.
We want to talk.
Oh, my God, what an honor.
Rose Hearn. Please come in.
I just saw you on television.
-You look better in real life.
-Thank you.
Just give me one second.
What can I help you with,
Detective?
I think one of your girls
got murdered last night...
at the King Edward Hotel.
What?
Did you send anybody over there?
Yeah. Honey.
Yeah, she's one of my girls.
-She's dead?
-I'm afraid so.
Oh, my God.
You all right?
-You want some water?
-Please.
Some water, please.
What was she doing there?
She was on a date with a guy.
He called
for a Czechoslovakian girl.
I sent him Honey...
because once they get there,
it doesn't really matter.
Do you have Czech girls
working for you?
No, but he insisted on one.
Does this girl look familiar?
Linda?
What were you saying?
I think I know this girl.
Daphne. She's a Czech girl.
I tried to recruit her.
I gave her my card.
I never heard back.
She's very popular
all of a sudden.
-You have a last name?
-I don't know.
I just had two guys come in here
a second ago asking about her.
Who were they?
One guy said he was her cousin
trying to find her.
They had a video camera.
He was taping.
I just wanted them to get out,
so I told them where she worked.
Where's that?
It's a salon
on 63rd and Madison.
63rd and Madison?
What's the name?
Ludwig's. She works there.
She washes hair.
Leon, Ludwig's Hair Salon.
Something might be there.
We think the suspects
will be there.
Want a sip?
-I'm on duty.
-So am l.
Hunting for Daphne.
I'll go inside.
You cover the exit.
Of course.
I always wanted to be a cop
when I was a kid.
Dreamt about pulling out my gun,
kicking in the door...
yelling "freeze" at the bad guy.
What did you dream about?
Running up
to a burning building...
kicking down the door...
rushing through the smoke,
and saving a kid.
I guess we're doing it
the right way.
If we pulled up to a burning
building, I'd let you go first.
Watch out.
Fuck.
The thrill of the hunt.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
I'm looking for Daphne.
I don't know where...
Maybe in front.
Thanks.
I've got a temper.
When I lose it, I lose control.
Get out of here!
I didn't intend to kill Milos.
When I went to prison,
they beat me.
I still didn't tell
he was my partner.
I loved Milos like a brother.
Daphne,
will you be coming back to work?
-Yes, in a minute, Ludwig.
-Yeah, come.
Thank you.
I don't want to kill you.
But if you talk...
I will.
I thought...
you'd want this.
This was Tamina's necklace.
Keep it.
Let's get out of here.
Good-bye, my love.
Your name's Daphne, right?
Remember at the fire,
you saw me?
You were trying
to tell me something.
I got it.
I smell smoke across the street.
We just want to talk to you.
We're here to protect you.
You speak English?
You speak English, don't you?
OK, let's go this way.
Did two guys visit you today?
What's that? Who gave you this?
Across the street,
two guys with a video camera.
Don't look! It's OK.
Let's just box them in.
You stay here with her.
Come on, let's go.
Shit! Go!
Goddamn !
Split up!
Fuck! Go!
Son of a bitch !
Get the fuck out of the road!
Move! Damn !
On the bus!
-Look out!
-Be careful!
Oh, my God!
Excuse me! Move!
I'm a cop!
Hey, look, look!
Watch out!
Perfect! Cut! Print!
Don't shoot!
-Bobby, you OK?
-I'm all right.
They went towards the park,
towards the park!
You hit?
Got my piece.
-Let's get out of here!
-I don't believe this.
Did you get him?
Think so.
I'm here, Leon.
-I'm having a bad day, man.
-You'll be OK.
...armed and dangerous.
We've surrounded the park.
They've disappeared.
...to parts unknown
within Central Park.
-Can you tell us what happened?
-I can't talk right now.
What's the fire marshal
doing here?
I can't give any statements now.
I'm sorry.
Your partner, Leon Jackson,
is injured. Correct?
He was hurt, but not seriously.
-You have a suspect in custody?
-Now's not a good time.
Detective Jackson was not hurt
seriously. That's all.
All right.
Eddie, are you all right?
Not a good time. All right?
All right.
-If you'd cooperate...
-Let me tell you something.
I want to know who these guys
are and how you're involved.
I don't know them.
I've never seen them before.
I was showering.
Tamina is a friend of mine.
My shower was broken,
so she let me use theirs.
-Go on.
-That's it.
I saw the killings.
I don't know why.
-Why are you protecting them?
-I'm not. I'm protecting myself.
From what?
Are you here illegally?
Don't worry.
We'll talk to lmmigration.
-Don't talk to lmmigration.
-Why not?
You better tell us.
We'll find out.
Better it comes from you.
You understand?
Let's make some room.
Bring him in.
You want to sit down?
Why don't you sit down?
You want a glass of water?
My little sister and I
shared a flat.
I came home one night,
and a man was raping her.
His gun was on the chair,
I grabbed it...
and when he came at me,
I shot him.
That's ajustifiable homicide.
Yes, but he was a cop.
So you shot him,
and you killed a cop?
I was living in a small town
in Slovakia.
We don't want to hear
your life story.
I got an officer shot.
Where can we find these guys?
You're a cop.
You won't help me.
I won't help you
unless you help us.
Eddie, can I talk to you alone
for a second?
For a second.
Even if she is telling
the truth, she's fucked.
Would you mind
letting me talk to her?
Any leads I get,
they're yours...
but let me
get first crack at her.
You want to talk to her alone?
This girl is scared,
you're intimidating her.
Big hotshot celebrity.
I'm a nobody.
Maybe she'll open up with me.
Maybe she looks at me different.
What is this?
You'll be her savior?
This the girl you'll save
from the burning building?
I'm being serious.
OK, I'll give you a head start.
Get her to the station house.
Don't let her out of your sight.
She's the only warm body
we got left.
Come on, I'm a professional.
Women like that have a way...
of turning professionals
into amateurs.
What are you doing?
I've got to light
this scene better.
Make it more dramatic.
Just like in the movie,
"Silence of the Sheeps."
Shut up.
Hurts?
Big enough?
Just kidding.
Want to get married?
I love you.
You want to get married?
Sweetheart.
Come on.
She's here.
She's here?
What does that mean?
"Good luck" in Greek.
Good luck in English.
Are you married?
Do you live alone?
I haven't showered
since the killings.
We could stop at your place.
I could take a shower
before we go back to custody.
Look, l...
I can't take you
back to my place.
Then somewhere else?
How's it going, Eddie?
-Eddie, how are you?
-Not too good.
You have a funny way
of showing it.
Yeah, me, too.
Why'd you snap at me?
-I didn't snap.
-You did.
Just wanted a statement.
I can't answer you
every time you want me to.
You didn't have to embarrass me.
Sorry. I didn't mean
to embarrass you.
-You know that.
-It's all right.
You OK?
Blood is all over your watch.
Is it Leon's?
Yeah. Probably. Has to be.
Is he going to be all right?
He'll be OK.
You had that schoolteacher's
blood on your shoes.
I don't know how you do it.
Speaking of shoes,
you know what I was thinking?
I would like to have...
some shoes next to my shoes.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Forget the phone.
What are you--
-Go ahead. Answer the phone.
-Shit.
Nicky, it's me.
-Can I call you back?
-No. We can't find Katie.
We want you to anchor right now.
Get in a cab
and be here in an hour.
Wait a minute. Now? Right now?
You want your shot?
Come now.
They want me to anchor.
-Great.
-Tonight.
-Great, great.
-Oh, my God.
Forget that for a second.
What...
No, when you come back.
You promise?
We'll talk tonight?
Of course I promise.
I'll see you when you come back.
Go ahead.
You'll be great.
I love you, Eddie.
I love you, sweetheart.
-See you tonight.
Good luck.
Don't be late.
The video of Milos
and Tamina...
I told you to erase it.
I erased everything.
It's all gone.
Don't lie. I won't be angry.
Why not?
What is it?
What does it look like?
It's an address book.
I took it from the black cop.
What's this?
What is it?
"Eddie Flemming."
Why won't you be angry at me
for keeping my movie?
You'll see.
Come. Bring the camera.
My name is Frank Capra.
I'm a famous Hollywood director.
There she is!
Warsaw.
Chief, what are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
I came to see how
the investigation is going.
I called,
and you're not here.
I waited by the station house,
you never show up.
I beep you,
you don't return my call.
Where the hell have you been?
Ladder 21 was at training.
We stopped there
so she could get cleaned up.
What do you mean, cleaned up?
-I let her take a shower.
-A shower?
Did you take one, too?
She's been through a lot.
I'm trying to help her.
That's really nice of you.
You take a homicide witness
to take a shower...
after your partner's been shot.
Are you
out of your fucking mind?
You having trouble
getting dates?
I told him to take her there.
Tommy, get her out of here.
The press was all over.
I didn't want her in the news.
I told him to take her someplace
quiet till things calmed down.
-Really?
-It was my decision. Not his.
I am
the Deputy Chief Fire Marshal...
and I like to be
included in decisions.
I understand.
Once he briefs me...
take over the press conference
and the lead in the case.
All right.
I'm ready to be briefed.
-Excuse us.
-Sure.
Are you ready to brief me?
Good.
Wait.
Can you just give us
a few minutes, please?
Thanks.
Shut that door when you go out.
Thanks, guys.
Just so you know,
I didn't touch her.
Maybe you should've. Nobody
will believe you, including me.
It wasn't the smartest thing
to do...
but I swear to you,
nothing happened.
It wasn't
the smartest thing to do.
You ought to know better.
She's got the potential
to hang you.
If she even suggests you made
a pass at her, it's over.
You can deny it.
It won't matter.
-You never went out on a limb?
-Know how you go out on a limb?
You say, "Here's the name
of an immigration lawyer."
-You'd believe her, too.
-You'll jeopardize your career.
You'll jeopardize your life
and my case.
Another piece of advice.
You don't watch TV,
but I'll tell you a secret...
The whole fucking world
watches television.
When you go out there,
they know your face.
And the little bit of fame that
I have in this fucking city...
makes my job a lot easier...
and I get a lot more done
because of it.
So why'd you stand up for me
with the chief?
I don't know.
You remind me of a puppy I had.
Pissed all over the carpet,
but I still kept him.
-Let's go.
-Captain !
One at a time, please!
We're looking for 2 male, white
suspects in their thirties.
We believe them to be of
an Eastern European nationality.
That's another lesson.
You got nothing to say,
don't waste their time or yours.
Let somebody else do that.
What's the plan now?
You're on the team, so I'll
call you when something happens.
Now I've got to propose
to my girlfriend.
Really? Congratulations.
Don't congratulate me.
She hasn't said yes yet.
I still think
there's something...
I could be doing
to help find these guys.
Go home and get some rest.
Sometimes you can try too hard.
Sometimes you have to go away
to come back.
Like you did
with that shot today?
That's right.
All right. I get it.
Good, 'cause you don't
look like you get it.
I get it.
-Sure you get it?
-I get it.
-You get it?
-No, I get it.
Trust me. I get it.
Why don't you keep it? Don't say
I never gave you anything.
Coming.
Nick?
I'm looking for Gayle Cassiopi.
-Cassiopi?
-Cassiopi.
I think it's one flight up.
Thanks.
Action.
So.
Who's she?
None of your fucking business.
Who's Nicky?
Beautiful.
It's OK.
You know what I need?
I need your opinion.
You do? About what?
You see...
they're going to make a movie
about me, too, Eddie...
and write books.
Write books.
And write books?
What's your fucking
accomplishment?
I kill someone famous.
And I saw you...
on the page
of "People" magazine.
Eddie, look at me.
Good.
Good. Be tough to the end.
Actor who plays you will
want you to die like a hero.
Tabloids don't have
to do reenactments.
They're going to have
a real movie this time.
You film killing me,
you'll get away with that?
You're stupider than I thought.
You're both
out of your fucking minds.
Turn it off.
Turn it off!
No. We are insane.
Who else but crazy men
would film their crimes?
So I kill you...
and if we are caught, we are
sent to mental hospital...
but once I'm in the hospital,
I say I'm not crazy...
just pretended
so I would be acquitted.
We see psychiatrists.
They must certify we are sane...
and because of
your double jeopardy law...
we can't be tried
for the same crime twice.
We come out free,
rich, and famous.
This is a great idea.
This is a fucking great idea.
You think ajury'll
buy that bullshit?
You sick fucks.
I'm smarter than Americans.
You watch crybaby talk shows
all day long.
Not only will
Americans believe me...
they'll cry for me.
So...
Detective Eddie Flemming...
would you like to say good-bye
to your Nicky?
Maybe you can
propose to her now.
He has nothing to say.
Give me a pillow.
Give me a fucking pillow!
Come here. Start the camera.
Cut! This is my project.
I'm the director,
and I say action !
Shut the fuck up!
Detective Flemming
was one of the most decorated...
NYPD detectives
in the history of New York.
Among the several thousand
arrests he made...
during his career,
the famed Stephen Geller case.
He was widely loved
by the community he served.
His partner eulogized him.
Eddie was my mentor...
my partner...
Tragedy.
Every great film must have one.
...the word "friend."
I will miss him.
I said no. No! No means no.
Do you want me to get ugly?
Gentlemen, I'm sorry.
It's a private affair.
-Sorry, no.
-Let me get a drink.
Please hold. Just stay on.
Hold on.
-You've got a call.
-What are you doing here?
Hold on. I'm here.
Just stay there.
-Don't be ridiculous.
-Trust me. Take this call.
Hang up the phone
and get a drink.
Take the call. Take it.
Give it to me.
I'm sorry.
Hello? Who is this?
I made a movie
of Eddie Flemming's murder.
How do I know this is you?
You'll know when you meet me.
-Where?
-35th and Broadway.
Don't bring the police,
or you'll be in next film.
Listen, asshole. I've been
threatened by better than you.
No. I'm the best
that's ever threatened you.
They'll get you.
We'll talk about that.
About surrendering?
Four o'clock.
It gives you time to go to bank.
One million dollars.
Hey, "Top Story."
Are you still there?
Yeah. I'm here.
It doesn't work that way.
If you don't want my film,
I'll call another show...
and they will show it.
I'll meet you.
I need two things from you--
I want exclusivity,
and you will surrender to me.
Bring cash.
Let's go.
Truck 21 spotted
north of the building...
put the aerial ladder
up to the roof.
Engine Company 54
and Engine 9...
took hand lines
up to the second level.
Truckies cut a hole in the roof
over the fire.
So how was the funeral?
Not good.
Did the D.A.
videotape her deposition?
He finished a little while ago.
Swing by her apartment,
pick up her clothes...
and take her to INS.
She's their problem now.
OK, Chief.
Hard to believe. Watch.
-What's this?
-I don't know.
"Good luck
with all your troubles.
"I'm here if you need me.
Ludwig."
Who's he?
My boss.
Why, are you jealous?
Why don't we get your stuff?
Look...
you're a witness
to a double homicide.
I can't get involved with you.
All right?
Why don't you go get your bags,
and I'll wait here?
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Get back!
No! That's not mine!
No! Don't do it!
Come on !
Hurry! Hurry!
-It's locked.
-Where's the key?
-It's not mine.
-Get in the bathroom.
10-75! 47th and 8th !
We're trapped!
Two alarms on arrival!
Oh, my God.
He's nailed it down.
Don't open the window.
It'll suck the fire towards us.
They were here.
Jesus Christ. That's Eddie's.
They were here!
Calm down, Daphne.
Just get in the tub.
-There's gasoline.
-What?
-What are you doing?
-I'm pouring it out.
-It's not going down.
-Oh, my God.
Give it to me.
Jesus Christ, it's clogged!
Please do something.
We're going to die.
Forget it. They're all clogged.
-Just stay low and stay calm.
-Do something!
Just stay low!
Ninety percent people who die
in a fire die from eating smoke.
Let me introduce you
to my partner...
and the man
who started the fire.
Emil.
Emil, say something
for your fans, huh?
Stand back and get down !
Stay low.
Stay low!
This'll buy us some time!
Get back!
This is a great film.
We can see fire right now,
and Daphne's in the fire.
Tell him it's OK.
Got to go!
Come on, guys. Let's go.
Take care of the boy.
And get her some oxygen !
-You all right?
-What happened up there?
It was a setup. Somebody
booby-trapped the apartment.
-Who?
-Got to be the same guys.
Speak louder. I can't hear you.
-Jordy, are you hurt?
-I'm all right.
What? You have to speak up.
What the hell
are you talking about?
What is it?
-Where's Hawkins?
-He's not on the premises.
Bring that tape here right now!
Any request for that tape
has to go to our attorney!
I am begging you !
You can't let this happen !
You want that tape,
contact the attorney.
You think we're joking?
Back off, man !
You can't do this!
Don't do this to Eddie.
Don't do it to the people
of this city.
You can't show
the man's murder on TV!
You want the tape, there it is.
Stay tuned for a special edition
of "Top Story."
Detective Eddie Flemming's
brutal murder was videotaped...
and we will broadcast it
after these messages.
Hard to believe. Watch.
Who says you can't be success
in America?
I came here with nothing,
knowing nobody.
And now, look.
I am success story.
Emil, why did you say "I"?
It should be "we."
Don't be paranoid.
I gave you half.
I'm Robert Hawkins,
and this is "Top Story."
Here we are.
Tonight I present material of
a graphic and violent nature...
never before
seen on television.
I do so with a heavy heart.
It would only be normal
to ask...
why are we showing something
so disturbing?
My answer is,
as ajournalist...
I am obligated to show it.
I air this tape in loving memory
of my friend Eddie Flemming.
Hard to believe.
Watch.
You film killing me,
you'll get away with that?
Turn it off. Just turn it off.
Cut! This is my project.
I'm the director,
and I say action.
Shut the--up!
Why did you leave that in
about being a director?
-Because I am the director.
-What?
Don't you fucking realize that
if it wasn't for my idea...
no fucking way
we'd be sitting here right now?
-Your idea?
-My idea.
Is that the guy?
Don't you understand?
This is a great American movie,
and who made it?
I made it all.
I was the director.
-Who are you?
-I am everything.
This is what America wants--
violence and sex.
Before we hand in the next
video, I'll put titles on it.
And my credit will read,
"Directed by Oleg Razgul."
But there is only one problem.
One credit,
but I don't share credit.
You got it?
You think you're a director?
You're just a little, small,
Russian piece of shit.
This is Robert Hawkins
for "Top Story."
We'll be back after this.
All right, I'm here. Jesus.
This is the man
I told you about.
This is Bruce Cutler.
Bryan, come get this from here.
I am Emil. I'm insane.
-Are you my lawyer?
-Not just yet.
I got your money.
Where is it?
Shit, where is it?
He's got the camera!
He's got the movie!
Let's sit down
and talk a minute.
Don't move!
Get your hands up
and drop the gun !
Drop the goddamn gun !
What did you hit him for?
He surrendered!
Go tight on them.
He's unarmed and hurt!
Emil, I'm going with you.
Come on !
I'm coming down there with you.
I'm his lawyer.
-Turn the camera off!
-Keep rolling!
Keep filming! Keep filming!
-I'm invoking his rights!
-What's going on?
I'm going with you, Emil.
Fuck!
Emil, I'm going down there
with you.
-What's going on?!
-They'll take you downtown.
-I'll take him.
-No! He's mine!
Don't argue with me.
-He's my collar!
-He killed my partner!
After he's booked, he's yours,
but I'm walking him in !
All right, have your 15 minutes.
Tommy, ride with him.
Get in the fucking car.
Don't speak to him!
Put your head in !
Get him in the car!
Put your head in, you fool!
You ought to be
ashamed of yourself.
Bullshit, Leon !
I got him off the streets!
-Bravo, Mr. Hawkins!
-Back off.
You are sick!
I'm fed up with
your fucking bullshit!
That is crap, and you know it!
Get out of here!
Jordy, where are you going?
You're going to lose everybody!
What are you doing?
This is not the way
to the station !
Talk to me! You're losing them!
Answer me, man !
-Answer me!
-Where am l?
-What the hell--
-What's going on?
Hold on. Jordy, wait!
Come on !
-Where's my lawyer?
-God damn it!
What's wrong with you? Shit!
Fuck you ! What's going on?
Wait a minute!
Jordy, you can't do this!
-Listen !
-Get out of the way!
Jordy, listen, man, please!
How'd you know how
to rig that apartment?
My father was a fireman.
He taught me about fire.
Now it's my friend.
-Take a walk.
-You're not thinking straight.
He knew he'd get caught.
That's why
you taped Eddie's murder!
I want this son
of a bitch dead, too.
You can't kill him
in cold blood!
Get the hell out of here!
Get in the car!
Listen to me!
I won't let you do this!
Tommy, get in the car and go!
Now go!
Fuck it, man ! Shit!
Something fucking funny?
Refreshing.
You think this is funny?
Turn around!
You want to be famous?
You want headlines?
All right, now's your chance.
Put your hands up.
Get your goddamn hands up!
Turn around.
You want to be
a real American, right?
Want to be a tough guy?
Here's Eddie's gun.
Remember him?
You want to be famous? Shoot me.
Want headlines? Money?
Celebrity? Shoot me!
You can't kill me.
You're not a cop.
You're just a fireman
with a gun.
I'll make it easy.
You Americans are pussies
without your missiles and money.
You won't kill me.
You don't have the balls.
Don't do it, brother!
Kill me.
Get up!
You're mine now, sucker!
You are out of control,
you know that?
Here's Eddie's gun.
Where you going?
I lost my shoe.
I want my shoe.
Get him out of here!
Emil Slovak is a victim here.
He is not a culprit.
We all appreciate the tragedy
of Detective Flemming's death.
I represent Mr. Slovak.
He was operating under
the influence of his partner.
This will all come out
at the trial...
and Emil will be vindicated.
I will see to that.
-Good job.
-Thanks.
How you feeling?
I brought letters.
Fan mail from women.
One wants to buy you a suit...
another sent money,
and another one wants money.
-Did you bring cigarettes?
-I did.
The perception out there
is very bad right now.
And perception is reality.
You may not be crazy...
but I want to get
that message out now.
That's our only defense
in this case.
You have to focus
on three things...
paranoia, fear, and delusions.
I was all of those.
But you never appreciated
the severity of it until now.
Of course not. How could l?
I was paranoid, fearful,
and deluded.
Now, what about Oleg?
They're looking
all over for him.
Haven't found him.
Maybe he went back to Russia.
No, he's here.
Let's forget about him
and focus on you.
You're what's most important.
What about my movie rights?
Book rights?
For you?
I have not thought about that.
How much do you want?
What's your cut?
I think we could be partners.
Fifty-fifty.
No. No way.
Thirty percent, no more.
We're in it together.
I thought forty percent
might be all right.
Oh, my God! No.
Thirty,
or I call another lawyer.
This is the biggest case
of your life.
Don't try to negotiate.
Say yes or no.
I can live with thirty percent.
It's important you understand
this is not all about money.
What else do you need?
I need to know about you,
what makes you tick.
I need to know your background.
Your mother, father, brother,
sister, everything.
That's what I need to know.
My father always degraded me.
He killed my self-esteem.
He hated me from the day
when I was born.
Emil Slovak will appear
in court today.
His lawyer--
Stay focused. Start again.
Emil Slovak
will appear in court today.
His lawyer will argue that
his client is mentally unfit...
This is such bullshit.
In a related matter...
Mr. Slovak's attorney,
Bruce Cutler...
famous for handling
sensational cases...
claims his client is unfit
to stand trial.
Bobby, give me a break.
Hello? No, not you, hon.
Hello?
No, we have no comment.
...his partner Oleg Razgul,
who threatened to kill him...
if he didn't follow his orders.
I got to go!
I'm going back to
the Czech Republic...
to face the charges against me.
I'm innocent.
If she shot a cop
who raped her sister...
in this country,
she'd be a hero.
I approached him and asked
for some spare change.
Politely, right?
Whereupon he pulls out
his big gun...
pushed me up in the tree,
handcuffs me like this...
and then he takes my money.
Left me here
exposed to all the elements.
Un-fucking-believable.
Look at this fucking guy.
Kids, if you out there...
don't hate your firemen.
Not all fire marshals like this.
It's not like this,
so keep the love.
Hard to believe.
You're watching "Top Story."
How could you forget handcuffing
a civilian to a tree...
in Central Park
in the middle of the night?
Chief, I know I screwed up...
but this guy is not
some innocent civilian.
He'll end your career
and probably mine!
End my career?
The press will be all over us!
Get the fuck back to your desks!
Chief, look at my file.
I've never had a complaint.
I crack big cases.
-Your record doesn't matter!
-It should!
Past history! Don't you get it?
I'm sorry. It's unfortunate
I have to make decisions...
based on your press coverage,
but I do.
You're suspended without pay...
pending a department trial.
Not to mention
your criminal charges.
That's not right.
Just get yourself
a damn good lawyer.
...over a million dollars
for the disputed video.
In related news, Emil Slovak
is back in court tomorrow...
where we'll learn if
he is competent to stand trial.
Meanwhile, the massive manhunt
continues for Oleg Razgul...
the alleged mastermind behind
the murder of Eddie Flemming.
"Action News" has learned that
Slovak won't have to worry...
about how
to pay for his defense.
He has received movie offers...
and has been in conversations
with publishers...
concerning the rights
to his story.
Further developments
are expected today...
in the bizarre Eddie Flemming
murder case.
Judge Stanley Stern
will issue his ruling...
on alleged killer
Emil Slovak's insanity plea.
If the court rules
in his favor today...
Mr. Slovak will be transferred
to the psych ward...
at Rikers lsland before
being remanded to the custody...
of a permanent institution
for the mentally ill.
Slovak's attorney
Bruce Cutler has maintained...
an abusive childhood is to blame
for his client's actions.
The Czech national
apparently has a history...
of physical and emotional trauma
from an alcoholic father.
What's ever left over, keep it.
Thanks, buddy.
Keep the Statue of Liberty
in the background.
-How do I look?
-Beautiful.
Thanks. Fuck you. Roll.
What are you looking at?
Forget about him. Let's go.
All right. Just roll.
All right. Let's go.
Bruce Cutler,
do you have a statement for us?
It's been a difficult
and long day for us.
Emil has been found
incompetent to stand trial.
In times of extreme stress,
as a result of delusions...
he could not appreciate
the wrongfulness of his acts...
and therefore
he's not liable for his acts.
This is a victory
for the mentally ill...
and before Emil
is taken on the boat...
to the psychiatric ward
at Rikers lsland...
it should be noted
that what he did...
he was forced to do
by Oleg Razgul...
a dangerous and demented
individual at liberty now...
in the streets of New York,
and both Emil and l...
Iook forward to when
he is brought to justice.
What are you looking at,
you piece of shit?
Officers, watch him.
He assaulted my client.
That's it? This scumbag
kills Eddie Flemming...
and spends the rest of his life
in a country club nuthouse?
What about the victims?
What about the families?
Marshal,
I understand you don't agree...
but this is
the system and the law.
Let's go.
I can kill you. I'm insane.
We need this area cleared.
Move back.
Two-shot of Cutler and Slovak.
All right.
Give me the boat
in the background.
Emil knew exactly
what he was doing.
Watch this.
All right.
Turn it off.
This tape I kept for myself.
In hospital
I say I'm not crazy...
and because of
your double jeopardy law...
we can't be tried
for the same crime twice.
We come out
free, rich, and famous.
Can we deal for this?
It's free.
Bruce! What would you
say to evidence...
that proves your client
is not insane?
"Top Story" has the truth
from Oleg Razgul himself.
You knew what you were doing.
It's all in my movie.
Officers, do your duty
and arrest this man.
I'm not the killer.
I'm the director. Action !
-Back off!
-Let her go!
Everyone, back away from me!
Tell him to put his gun down !
Do not fire your weapons!
-Stay back!
-Nobody's going to fire.
-Hold that line!
-Let her go!
Tell him to put his gun down.
Stay back!
-Get that shotgun out of here!
-Stay back!
Nobody's firing.
Everybody, get back!
Do not fire, anyone!
Lower those weapons!
Now! Lower!
Tell him to put his gun down !
Let her go!
If he doesn't lower his gun,
I'll fucking kill her!
Officer, lower that weapon !
-Remember Eddie!
-Shut up!
Do not fire that weapon !
I'll surrender
if he lowers his gun !
Don't you let
this piece of shit surrender!
If you don't let me surrender,
I kill her now.
I don't care!
-Do not fire that weapon !
-Shut up!
Jordy, God damn it!
You take that fucking shot!
Officer, for the last time,
lower your weapon !
He's lowered the weapon.
Don't shoot her.
You take that shot, Jordy.
He lowered his weapon.
Don't shoot her.
No! Jordy! No.
He lowered the weapon,
all right?
You're OK. Don't look back.
Don't look at him.
Fuck! Did you get that? Fuck!
Come on,
let's get you out of here.
Come on, let's go.
Boss, he's still alive.
Come on. Let's go.
A film by Oleg Razgul.
How was that?
That was great.
Thanks.
I thought you might want that.
Alan, here. Take this camera.
Marshal, you feel up
to making a statement?
Forget it. No statement.
Cut the camera.
Listen, I can help you.
Take a lesson from Eddie.
The media
can be a powerful ally.
Eddie was my friend.
I'd like to be yours, too.
Good job.
-You OK?
-I'm fine. Fuck him.
Follow him walking away,
then whip back to me.
We've been talking with
Fire Marshal Jordan Warsaw.
He's understandably overwhelmed
with what's just occurred--
the tragic end
of two vicious psychopaths...
who attempted to manipulate
the news media...
for their own greed and egos.
We at "Top Story" will never
be used in this way.
Our goal is to bring you
the news in all its complexity.
The truth was
the real hero here today...
and we're proud to bring it
to you on "Top Story."
This is Robert Hawkins.
Good night.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org