THIS IS NOT
A TALE OF FEES.
Hello!
I am your ancient chorus.
The incarnation
body,
your sherpa of suspense.
Take my hand and if you dare,
declad your sword.
Ready Etes you?
MEGAVIXENS
September 19 9h47
You manias better the whip!
My old friend Roehm
would have been impressed.
Limehouse!
We draw.
Let us go by car in Salmon Creek
to swim and treat to good time.
You will return by bus.
You did not forget
something?
Your task is not finished.
I am washed.
Which is this name...
Cursed English...
Ah yes! A no-claims bonus!
Exact, ducon.
Bring or keep silent yourself.
How much?
I will be generous.
Approach...
bridal layer.
Didn't you forget anything?
In my wallet...
a ticket of 100 marks.
Thank you for the no-claims bonus.
Come here!
I said "come here"! Schnell!
And for the 2nd ticket of 100 DM?
Quickly. I am in a hurry.
In Thursday, Adolf!
Even hour!
Eh, Gwendolyn...
Soft Alice, I will climb you.
As I said...
Wait a little.
Let us speak initially.
Idles a little...
Good God, wait!
I charge you
to unearth a super trick.
This gode, it is pure poetry!
Begin again to me with the return.
I will have innovations.
With in 15 days!
Hello, headstock!
You do not have anything to make
in my bathroom.
You did not include/understand?
A fish???
A piranha?
In Paraguay,
I saw some devouring a cow.
Poor Schwartz died...
one day terrible and beautiful.
Harry, the tool of the massacre.
Who unchained
its wild appetite?
Such is the question.
Headsperson, hired killer,
service returns at low prices.
The Ethiopian cooker,
hammering joyeusement
the scrotum of the colonizer.
Limehouse, girl of the Raising Sun,
kamikaze of the cunnilingus.
Paul,
father founder, husband,
torturer...
and lover, ready with all the engagements,
everywhere, always,
choosing, comparing
one with the other...
Alice...
beauty queen,
phantom of passion,
vautrée in the lust.
Gwendolyn with the impetuous kidneys,
nave of cathedral...
And the intruder,
penetrating at Schwartz,
like Sparte in Athens,
y leaving devouring it tool of death.
You know all.
But before the Court withdraws itself,
you must all examine.
I can help you, Miss?
Broken down?
Not, I keep the form.
I never saw you.
I have just arrived at Miranda.
Dancer? Stripper?
Interpret.
You go up?
It is not casher.
No importance.
I am the only cop of the corner.
Go up. You are already in form.
I need exercise.
Your name?
Margo Winchester. And yours?
Homer Johnson.
My word!
An appearance!
Be deaf for you or what?
OK, I repeat...
Where do you go?
Miranda.
Music?
As you will like it.
- You remainders with Miranda?
- Of passage.
I can make you change opinion.
Ca would astonish me.
- It is a short cut.
- I suspect it.
Bitch!
It was super!
It morflé...
It ceased suffering.
Regain the road!
Advance!
Why devil have killed it?
You had removed his combativeness to him
right before removing the life to him.
This karate is frightening.
What I see,
you can defend yourself.
Ca is not any doubt.
Go up in it.
Magne.
Get into the car!
It took on board you...
You had to cause it.
If I believe about it
my experiment of cop,
the girls create problems...
especially with half-naked.
In addition, an exception
is possible with Léonard Box,
it is the name of the type,
it was a foutor of shit.
Nobody will regret it,
except his/her father.
He hardly liked it,
but it belonged to him,
like the mill of Belcher' S Flat.
It is full with the aces.
It would give large
so that you stagnate in clink.
And then?
Let us see the things differently...
You avoided many paperworks
in the State.
It was to finish thus,
considering its control...
In the Kneader, with a large P.
You can arrange your weapon...
I did not attend the scene.
I was going to see Charlie Sumner
In Lucas Meadows.
This stubborn person refuses the telephone.
One did not see it in Miranda
since a lease,
it is perhaps sick.
I saw 2 people
to fight at the edge of the ravine,
just as I passed.
You fell both.
I believed you foutus.
A whore of fall!
To break the back.
I ran and I saw Box
spread out at the bottom of the ravine.
Then, hung to you with a root.
You have escaped it beautiful.
A cord... I went up you,
setting on the back seat.
You were hysterical.
Ca is included/understood.
I called the coroner Lou Dougal.
It had evil to recover the type.
Fortunately that it had two assistances.
It examined the body.
Cause death: broken back.
Reason: fall mortal.
I forgot anything?
Your commission.
One will speak about it at home.
You are a villain.
I saw it immediately.
What does one say on the desire?
With each one it his.
One will not continue thus!
Why not?
- tempo should be changed.
- Already inaccurate...
You will not know anything of it. And then...
I should not speak while sleeping.
You either, Homer.
You broke my glasses!
Afflicted,
I do not know my force.
A trick in plan was left.
Instead of the equality in front of the law,
Margo finds the equality under Homer.
The nest of the vulture where all is played.
The most macabre murder
ever made.
The Paul, most suspect,
inspired by 3 Muses,
jealousy, avarice and ambition.
Margo, machine with pleasure
that any man dreams to impale.
Headsperson,
white pink of death,
provider of pain.
The Ethiopian One,
hurricane of passion and trick.
Limehouse,
disconcerting
like a speech of Mao,
its body: a gold zither.
Alice, girl, lesbian,
protective princess of the sanctuary.
Gwendolyn,
have fornication, pseudo-husband.
Soft Alice...
Homer,
threatened by the axe and the cord,
in its dreams,
the gleam crimson saw,
heard the voice. was crucifié.
Leonard Box,
victim of its lust.
Dead end in truth
if he is the killer of the Nazi.
One of these creatures made
a horrible crime. Who?
Mister?
A sandwich with tuna and chips!
Of nothing, Ken.
Homer will fill
its monthly quota...
Then, that comes?
It is ready, treasure.
Bring back your bottom here...
Touch my centres...
Attempt at corruption?
- What do you look at?
- I admire.
I suck well...
I badly was never sucked.
This will rectify it.
Homer is made lubricate
early.
Look at the head of the chick!
Less than 30 seconds...
It was a warning.
Slip by, salts bitchy girl!
Bar yourself before...
that I remember
that I am the Law and the Order.
The warning...
Shit!
What does it believe, this whore?
Thus say, Homer,
what does it occur here?
Two murders! Bones of Adolf
scoured by a quite fatty fish!
Box broken into two!
With the girl, it acts of an accident.
I want the facts, Homer.
This which been able history.
Rafe, as usual?
With French bread.
I do not believe in it.
Darling, of the ration of oats for Rafe.
With the job!
Négrière!
It was said to me that the girl of the accident
was superb,
with an impressing name.
That is said?
Why not?
I do not have anything of to better do...
Speak to me
of this Margo Winchester.
I like the large milks,
but it converted me.
She has a époustouflant bottom.
You will not gourez.
Its milks are enormous.
With nipples
as large as of the centres.
But this bottom! Last night,
it sucked me with knees,
it returned nut to me!
Would have you need for assistance...
And how!
Saw you the panel?
ONE ENGAGES
It has been there for 15 days.
Nobody.
I know somebody...
I see you coming...
You refuse
what your Jules sees this vamp?
After me, it has right to the remainders.
One is made a remainder?
The job initially.
I will reserve to you
one moment this afternoon.
Not so quickly!
The stones hurt me!
There are not time.
A step beyond
abyssals zone of the extase.
The face of Teuton
is it binding to the lovers?
The mystery it is buried
or it is shamelessly
in front of our eyes...?
A vicious, but real murder.
Return quickly!
Ham sandwich,
fried, salad, 2 sandwiches hot!
Let us dispatch!
I bet that they are
like honey drops.
From which come do all these people?
I pigé.
Appointment after the job.
A double Chile-mustard
without onion.
It left.
Chile without onion.
I know. Double Chile,
much mustard,
no the onion.
I was right.
You attract the customers.
It is my personality...
Then! This hot dog?
I have shame to pay it if little.
The tip must compensate.
What a bottom!
Ouais, not badly.
One is succeeding,
treasure,
to really succeed.
Darling,
the purchases should be doubled
sausages and of bread.
Another thing, darling?
Avoid raising weight.
Thank you for your assistance, Margo.
Ca occupies me.
Homer is taken.
Ca says to you to go in Garberville
to make races?
I want to go to swim
In Salmon Creek,
close from Homer.
Deep splits,
superb surroundings... I go there.
I would like to attach you...
Good joke!
Will make your purchases.
How is water?
Useless to press itself,
there are all our time.
Hurry, décampe!
In the reserve, Pocahontas!
It is red!
Kissed you with a squaw!
The murder claims revenge.
The murderer rôde among us.
It will be betrayed
by its glance, its emotion?
Its efforts
to choke its culpability?
Paul, with the émacié face,
with the various dashes,
leave its mark
on the belly of its prey,
alleviating only its devouring thirst.
_ its eye himself embuent in front of the gold
piled up by the new barbarians.
Margo,
soft myrrh with the pointed centres.
Why is it there? Plundering
and draining the men.
Lust and the desire
mixed in a figure
of Superwoman.
Alice, diligent wife,
sharing the daily problems
with its Master,
faithful... even if
its variations lesbians
profane the marital extase,
the palate of the gourmet excites.
Angel... or demon?
Alas! A whore!
Homer, ex-champion of the law,
has a devouring appetite
for sexual excesses.
A bull
who takes part in the decathlon...
10 tests
pornographic figures.
Gwendolyn, black horse
in the race with the murder.
The duet became a double duet.
The quartet became a trio.
It is not between Paul and Alice,
but with them,
each one being conscious
relations of the other.
Inaccurate Gwendolyn has it...
opened the Pandora's box,
releasing the manes
of Desdémone and Othello?
Here is the difficulty.
Let us see the observers. Their innocence
does it hiding place the evil?
Rafe, a ram
drawn up like Gibraltar.
The Ethiopian cooker,
the black sheep does not carry out
always the herd.
The Young Mamelue Thing,
pulverizing the seed
Gendarmerie.
Léonard Box...
deaths are dumb.
Limehouse,
it tightens its satin skin.
1/2 H later,
would it kill again?
Headsperson, the gloutonne,
able to milk the flow of the life.
The only language
included/understood by the savage,
it is the fire of the gun.
You all studied them.
But which?
When illegitimate couples
link themselves,
the face of dying Teuton
impose yourself it
with the lover without law,
and the memory of the crime to the extase?
Higher, Fred.
Like that?
Hang it.
It is the great evening!
You succeeded well,
you two....
To open a new bar...
Motus! It is for Margo!
It prepares for this evening,
wait to see its behaviour!
I will miss the spectacle,
I must go to Eureka
this afternoon...
Box, that which violated Margo,
would have known Adolf Schwartz.
One never knows...
To burst a tire one evening similar!
Where is Alice?
Part to get dressed...
Will seek others of them.
On the rack.
My uncle broke a leg.
Motor bikes of shit!
What a foot, this evening!
Beer is missed.
Everyone is burst!
George, the beer!
Is Rafe, where thus your axe?
Give him.
Beer!
What a weak!
With hair! With hair!
Thank you, the guy,
for this ovation.
The speeches, it is not my style.
Aim its tits!
The juke-box...
Send the other!
Two for Rafe.
Cool, Raoul...
Rafe wants a recall.
Call Smokey!
Homer...
It is the only one with being able to calm
this soak of Rafe.
Let us go, it takes good time.
Slip by to telephone!
I will try to contain it.
I hate this secrete way.
Not touches!
Remove your hands from there!
Does not touch it, Rafe!
What do you make?
Release me!
Known as In Homer Johnson
to come illico!
Poor jerk!
Go ahead, Rafe!
Here is Cavalry!
We draw!
Withdraw your whore of tail!
The Help |!
Release me!
Child of bastard!
The axe!
Do not cry any more. It is finished.
Dumb! You wounded Paul.
Rosebud!
It is best.
Meeting again
and treasons continue,
the actors enlisent themselves in the extase,
taken in a hurricane
of fire and passion.
Where ground the killer?
Unsuspected, anxious and dissimulated.
Gather the indices,
there will not be more.
Heard. I hang up again.
Yes, me. Soft the small Alice!
The least suspect!
You are cop,
you are not a waitress...
It was obvious. you and Homer...
Error, loophole!
Our relation is fortuitous.
I have evil to believe it.
Your death will not be fortuitous!
Why you? Your mobile?
I will be the best!
You and your muscular bottom!
With what it will be used to you
in this combat with death?
When did I reveal my identity?
Your identity? Ah!
You are only one whore!
Then why to attack me?
What do you believe?
To have violated...
raped my Paul!
To have tripoté your guy?
A weakling
and a poor fucker!
Perhaps.
Paul has innocence
and the stupidity of a child.
He deserves forgiveness.
As for its sexual value,
28 cm, it are not to scorn.
Last night
in full orgasm,
it murmured your name,
whereas it was still hidden
in the splendour of my body.
Who is a true woman?
Pretty centres!
Well drawn Pelvis! But Paul
is a victim of the flesh,
a man what!
Here it is!
Retain that well,
nobody will play
with the feelings of Paul.
I always protected it,
even against this fag of Adolf.
Which importance
if it were made put by Schwartz?
It was my father.
Then your maiden name
is Schwartz?
My bottom!
My true name
is Eva Braun Jr,
bastard girl of Adolf Hitler
and of its mistress fair oakum.
But corpses
found in the Bunker?
My mother sacrificed herself,
she aged,
dad preferred the jeunettes...
Both
worried for me...
I waste my time.
Where is this dagger?
But the holocaust...
the hooligans Nazis
fleeing the ship in perdition?
The paddle of 3rd Reich?
Wait one minute!
The provided evidence
by the Russians?
Concoctées twaddles
to like Stalin.
Nobody likes to lose.
With the devil History!
I killed my father
to save my marriage.
- To save your marriage?
- Exact.
Dad and me, one did not get along.
It had been put to the boys
and 28 cm of Paul...
I was tolerant.
But the night, it did not ensure any more.
Exhausted by these meetings.
It kissed for corn,
this rotted corn
that my father extorted
with poor guy.
This corn which it gave to Paul
to be made glitter
by humiliating its virility.
Its money financed the bar,
not alleged success
"Coffee of Alice".
This male chauvinist pig deserved to burst.
All is recut.
This business is complex.
The secrecy of Eva Braun Jr
will die with you,
woodcock!
- Is wary,
hedgehopping!
- Bitch!
You have appointment
with eternity,
prepare
to undergo my revenge!
Murder and revenge combine
with the obscenity of Adolph.
The law requires an equitable lawsuit
and me, I will make you put at knees.
Balivernes!
I like that better.
It was a question of time.
Rosebud... I will go until the end.
One crescendo
of removed from rim extravagance
be a prelude to with the events to come.
A camionneuse friend,
expert in godemichés,
brought back for me of Frisco 2 tricks
that I die of desire for testing.
According to it, they offer
"the best of the 2 worlds",
if you see what it wants to say.
Here a bed in charge of history.
It belonged to a girl
named Vixen.
Paul, why?
You killed Mr. Schwartz!
Poor Adolf...
if misunderstood, condemned
to have wanted to save the world...
You hurt me, Paul!
The ideal wife.
My needs, its requirements.
Soft Alice,
if pretty... if egoïist.
Always after my prick,
but for it only.
Punish it, Paul.
You resemble to him.
A simple whore.
A egoïist
who wishes my body of sylphid
for it only.
You also, you must perish.
You hurt him!
Do not move or parks with your bottom.
Only one gesture and bye bye!
I love you and I hate you!
Be reasonable... The Company
you will save.
You with your large centres
and your large bottom!
Sergeant,
your direction of the duty,
your contempt of the danger,
deserve my admiration
and my gratitude.
It was with joy.
Can I tighten you the hand?
Alas, your mission is ungrateful
and infinite. I ask you
of replonger in the brawl
and to destroy
another kind of vermin
who pollutes our people.
These naïives hearts
of which the force
resist less than ours.
I know that your prowesses,
your direction of the duty,
your pride to be useful
you will be useful.
God blesses you...
and keeps you.
Another thing, chief?
With The De luxe hotel Bar With 8h15,
precise.
The fly took the spider.
I will reveal you
intimacy and sensuality
merry.
You came by far.
Think of those
that my accounts effleurés.
Rafe, the coléreux giant,
victim of the silly thing and alcohol.
Homer Johnson,
the man behind the badge,
obliging but unsubdued.
Its emblem shines again.
Soft small Alice...
... in other words Eva Braun Jr...
It is good...
Kindness does not have anything to see in it.
The which gallops filly
and left, very wet.
Paul Reynart,
how it is good!
A fox running after its tail.
That it is done
Margo Winchester!
No too high summits,
too broad rivers
of too hard furrow with biner!
I enjoyed!
Winchester... über Alles!
Moron! I had defended you
to give this disc.
In your orders, Martin!