Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
You know that first amount
of money you offered me...
you understand why
I had to turn you down?
I made good money
when I worked.
Yeah, I know,
where I live...
it doesn't look
I'm that well off because...
well, that's because
I was gambling.
I was fucking sick and blew every dime
I made because I had a gambling habit.
But now I'm trying to do
the right thing.
Even though we never
worked together...
I value this
in a relationship.
But I won't work for nothing.
Sure, I can use the money...
but I gotta be paid my quota.
You understand that, don't you?
How long since
you've worked, Dosmo?
Hey, you go through a little
dry spell, what's it make?
It makes you stronger.
I'm okay. I always knew
I'd be back.
What is it?
Sounds like she's having
a bad dream.
Roy.
I'm on my knees,
where you always wanted me to be.
I never wanted you
on your knees, Roy.
What do I do next,
beg or bark?
All right. Come on the bed.
Go to sleep on this side.
- My little worm.
- Don't call me that.
But you were
my little worm, right?
God!
Why did you come over?
Because it's our anniversary.
I kept thinking of all the good times.
So, you seeing someone?
No. No one special.
How many girls are you seeing?
No one.
- Are you gonna try for '98?
- No.
- What's so funny?
- He is.
What's going on?
He's trying to screw her.
He's in her bed?
When I saw you before I skated,
that's why I fell.
Tell me what the fuck's happening.
Please!
Come on, Becky. I miss you.
That's why I came over here.
Why are you doing this?
What are you doing here? You left me!
I think I made a mistake.
Who's the Norwegian bimbo you brought
to watch me race in Lillehammer?
Helga? Did she distract you?
No. No, not at all.
Out of the corner of my eye I saw
this giant, Viking blonde...
with blue eyes
crawling all over you.
Didn't distract me at all. Blocked it
out and came in fourth fucking again!
At least you came in fourth.
Let's just go to sleep.
This is a destructive relationship.
I'm not starting it again!
Why am I getting turned on then?
- I know you want it.
- Go call your Viking...
Come on.
Becky, I think I'm still
in love with you. I do.
Roy, stop it. I mean it.
Stop it.
I'll throw you out.
Good night.
Oh, God.
They're going back to sleep.
Let's go.
What the fuck happened?
Does every other word have to be "fuck"?
Is that the extent of your vocabulary?
It fucking bothers you?
I didn't fucking know.
Very quietly.
This ain't my first barbecue.
You sure she don't have
a fucking dog?
Tough guy like you
is afraid of dogs?
I ain't afraid of them.
They just don't like me.
I don't know what it is.
They always growl at me.
Teddy?
You don't have the rent?
What would you do
if you were me...
and I hadn't paid the rent
for four months?
I would evict me.
I don't wanna be
an asshole, Teddy.
You're not an asshole, Evelyn.
I'll be gone tomorrow.
Where will you go?
Listen, there's one thing
you could do.
I may be moving around
for a while, and...
would you look after Bogey?
You're not giving him away?
What about that agent you ate with once
a week? Couldn't he advance you money?
He doesn't return my calls.
Okay, little man,
one last walk to the park.
Bang.
When I do it,
I'll load it first.
Is she out?
Yeah.
Okay, buddy, lay back.
I'm gonna take the gun out of your
mouth, and you're gonna be quiet, right?
Otherwise I'm going to
have to pull the trigger.
Open up.
So I don't hurt the teeth.
You mind if I smoke?
You have one minute to decide
the rest of your life.
I'm gonna ask you
three questions.
If you lie, you die.
Let him sit up.
Get comfortable.
All right.
Forty-seven seconds.
First question.
You met her in Lillehammer.
Who'd she say she was?
Helga.
Helga Svelgen.
Did Becky know about
your other business in Norway?
Did she know what you did there
besides fall down ice-skating?
I don't know what you're talking...
No use protecting Helga.
She's dead.
Twenty-six seconds.
Helga's dead?
Oh, God!
- Can I see that picture?
- Shut your mouth and let me finish.
This is the one
not to get wrong.
Was Helga the one
who approached you...
on behalf of the North Koreans?
You have 16 seconds left.
I don't know what you're talk...
Just a moment. Was it Helga?
If you don't admit that
she was your contact...
in the next ten seconds...
nine...
eight...
seven...
six...
five, four...
three...
two...
Okay.
She was my contact.
This thing isn't about
a gambling debt?
Shit! I just got a flat!
Can you believe it?
I'm on my way to a $300,000 commission,
and I just got a fucking flat!
Call Triple-A right away.
Send them to Ventura and Woodman.
Tell them to hurry.
There'll be a big tip waiting.
Do you have enough cash?
Tell Mr. Connelly I'll be there soon.
Apologize. You know what to say.
Go to my house and feed the dog.
Wait there till you hear from me.
The thing is
I had plans tonight.
I just assumed you never
have plans, Susan.
Shit!
Hey, what the fuck are you doing?
Get out of the street!
Please, help me.
Hold it.
Bitch.
Stop. Stop!
That's my car!
He just stole my car!
Teddy!
Teddy Peppers?
Is that you?
It's Ralph.
It's Ralph Crupi.
I did three days work on that feature
of yours called Lights Out.
Oh, yeah, I remember.
Boy, what a bomb that was.
Have you worked since?
Just kidding. Just kidding.
That was one of two or three
in a row for you. I mean flops, bombs.
So what happens now?
You go back to TV?
You must be thinking
you're losing touch with your audience.
God, those critics were cruel.
I don't think I've ever
read reviews that terrible.
What happened? I read the script.
I thought it was a drama.
What was all that stuff
with the elephant in the middle?
I know, it's a long story.
The studio fucked you over.
Hey, you still have the same dog,
the terrier.
This is another one.
That one was hit by a car.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I remember your wife...
used to bring that other one around
the set when he was still a puppy.
How is your wife?
She's an actress, right?
We're divorced.
Oh, God, I'm sorry,
'cause she is so pretty.
I hope you get
another chance soon.
Otherwise, I'll see you down
on the unemployment line.
Just kidding.
Feel good?
Oh, yeah, it feels great.
You live in California?
Chicago.
- Here for vacation?
- Mm-hmm.
- Where are you from?
- Vietnam.
Vietnam?
I thought this was
a Japanese place.
My mother's Vietnamese.
My father's Japanese.
I'm, how you say...
a mutt.
No, you are not a mutt.
You're a very beautiful girl.
Thank you.
Turn over, please.
- Feel okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I do softer this side.
You like?
That feels very nice.
Oh, you strong.
Nice body.
Oh, look at you, so big!
Finished.
You're done?
You want something else?
Like what?
Well, what you want?
What could I get?
You been here before?
I've been to
massage parlors before.
Just not this one.
Didn't this place just open?
You have nice eyes.
Yeah, it just open.
What you want I do?
I'd like...
What's the matter?
I take too much time.
Next customer waiting.
What you want I do?
I should go.
I gotta go.
I didn't realize the time.
I gotta meet somebody.
You want nothing else?
No, thank you.
What happened?
Nothing. She didn't do anything.
Just a straight massage.
- What?
- Maybe she made me as a cop.
Are you trying to tell me that's
a legitimate Japanese therapy studio?
No. I'm trying to tell you
that nothing happened.
That place is definitely a hand job
house, and we're gonna raid it.
Every one of them slanty-eyed whores I
am gonna personally throw in the can...
and make sure
they're deported.
Hey, Alvin,
can I ask you a question?
I hate it when people ask me if
they can ask a question. Just ask it.
Why do you hate Asians so much?
I don't hate Asians.
I don't like whores.
- Hey, Alvin?
- Just ask it.
Okay. There are about a hundred
massage parlors in L.A.
For years, Vice hasn't bothered
any of them. Why start now?
Because this one's
in the Valley.
All the others are downtown...
or in Culver City or Santa Monica,
but this one's right in the Valley...
and there are gonna be
no massage parlors in the Valley!
I was born two miles from here.
I own a house in Studio City.
This is a nice place to live.
I would like to keep it that way.
That fuckin' place
opened four weeks ago...
and it ain't gonna operate
a day after today.
Does that answer your question?
Good.
I thought this was a thing
out of New York.
I thought this was a bad guy
who welched on a bet.
What was all this shit
about Koreans and spies?
You know,
curiosity killed the cat.
You're a real pisser,
aren't you?
You like fucking with people's heads?
How did you find me?
In the phone book
under "Washout."
You know about that.
Look, I'm grateful
for a chance at a...
at a comeback.
To tell you the truth, you know
what I was doing when you called?
Flipping pizzas at Polly's.
Who the fuck are you?
How come you know so much about me?
I know more about you than
you know about yourself, "Dumbo."
My name is Dosmo.
Dosmo Pizzo.
What do you know about me
that I don't know?
This is where you get out.
Have a little coke.
All done, honey?
- What a buffoon.
- Roy?
Dumbo, the pizza man.
Roy's dead, right?
You killed him?
- Why, you gonna miss him?
- Of course not.
You didn't enjoy yourself
with him?
We have to get out of here.
You definitely didn't sleep
with Roy?
We're not going
through this again.
What exactly did you do?
We kissed, necked. That's all.
- He didn't touch your breasts?
- No.
I'm just telling you, if I found out
you were lying, I'd go crazy.
Don't go crazy, okay?
Now let's just go.
I can walk by myself!
- Let me help.
- I don't need it, all right?
I'm not a cripple.
I'm just sore.
Hot and sore.
It must be 110 fucking degrees!
What happened up there?
A car fire. Some kids
blew up a car up there, I think.
Oh, shit.
A fucking dog!
A dog! Fuck!
Do you have to follow
a special diet now too?
Yep.
No more dairy products,
no red meat...
no milk, no nuts,
no coffee, no tea...
no chocolate.
- No sex.
- Are you kidding?
I've got to drink three gallons
of water a day.
I never want to be without
a glass of water in my hand.
I have to be constantly
pouring water down my throat.
Where's the only joy
of my life?
He was by the pool
when I left.
You fed him last night?
Flavored his food with bacon?
Yes.
- Good girl.
- Me or the dog?
The dog is a boy.
Oh, shit!
Sorry.
Open the door
and let the air in.
And let Mark in.
Call the hospital. Find the name of
the fag who gave his credit card for me.
I want to send him,
maybe, a Chagall lithograph.
That's very generous.
Thanks.
I owe this guy.
He might have saved my life.
You must still be sedated.
You never gave me a Chagall print,
and I've worked for you for eight years.
Susan, if you wanted,
I could give you something better.
What?
With a little surgery,
you don't have to be that homely.
I'd pay for implants and liposuction,
but don't take it as an insult.
You know how much I like you.
I'll let your dog in.
If you fixed yourself up,
you might meet a man.
Hello, Audrey, it's me.
Your kidney stone-less
half-brother.
That's right.
I had them last night.
Did Mom have kidney stones?
The urologist wanted to know.
If you're checking your machine
before you leave work, just come on by.
I need a nurse.
Susan?
Susan, don't be so sensitive.
Christ!
For God sakes, Susan.
Come back inside.
Call him off!
Who are you?
Call your fucking dog off!
Mark!
Come here!
Mark! Heel!
Call him off!
He's not vicious. He wants to fetch.
He's waiting for you to throw the gun.
You better get over here...
and drag him away,
or I'll shoot him.
And then I'll shoot
the both of you too.
Do you have something to do with
that car that blew up on Mulholland?
I was supposed to be
in the car.
There's a man that's gonna come looking
for me to finish the job he botched.
- I'd like to borrow your car keys.
- Give him the keys.
I'm going to pull him away.
Good idea. Prick fuck.
Fuck prick. Fuck you.
God, are you ugly.
Do I know you?
- Me?
- You look familiar.
- Susan, let him go.
- Susan what?
Parish,
but I changed it from Pollutzo.
Pollutzo is a beautiful name.
You shouldn't have changed it.
- You got a smoke?
- No, I don't smoke.
Look, I'm not a thief,
but I need money.
I lost my wallet.
No, not yours. His.
All I is have is about $40.
It's crooked.
Pollutzo?
Shit! Shit!
Leave the dog outside.
You two come in.
Shut the door!
You got anything to eat here?
I'm fucking starving.
Got any pasta, marinara sauce?
Any garlic?
Why don't you just go?
Take the car and leave.
You want us to cook for you?
No, no, I'll cook.
You know, people don't realize
how important a minute is.
So much life revolves
around a single minute.
You have a minute egg,
minute waltz, Minute Rice.
People are always demanding
you give them a minute.
Nobody realizes how valuable it is
until they only have one left.
Wait.
Just stand there a minute.
I just wanna look at you.
God definitely broke the mold
after you, baby.
Tell that to my modeling agency.
Tell them yourself.
You're not too tall.
It's the world
that's too short.
God, you are beautiful.
You know,
when I asked Roy...
if you approached him
on behalf of the North Koreans...
and he had 16 seconds
to answer...
I think he wet his bed.
Why did you go through
that ridiculous story?
Just to torture him?
Sometimes I think you should've been
born during the Spanish Inquisition.
Your minute is up.
Lay back.
Don't put your hand
around my throat.
I think you like it a little.
No, I don't.
It makes me not trust you.
You can trust me.
You can always trust me.
Just like I trusted you
with Roy.
Which breast did he touch?
This one?
He didn't have to touch either
the way it turned out.
Why did you change your mind?
I thought the idea of the affair was
to lure him to the desert to kill him.
But I know why you did it
at Becky's house.
Why?
You got jealous.
You let it get to you personally.
You've never done that before.
I guess I must really
be in love with you.
You got any rapini?
What is that?
An Italian vegetable,
like broccoli.
He doesn't have any.
I do the shopping.
Keep it in the house.
It's good for you.
It's got a ton of vitamins
and minerals. Prevents cancer.
I eat it on a daily basis.
What are your pants
stained with?
Oh, yeah.
I gotta borrow
a change of clothes.
Why was that car
you were in blown up?
Why does that man
want to kill you?
What were you two
involved in?
You think I'm gonna tell you?
He doesn't know. You don't know
why that man tried to kill you, do you?
You're a pretty smart cookie,
aren't you?
Anybody in your family connected?
No, I'm not from New York.
I grew up in Reseda.
We got people out here.
We got people everywhere.
You guys are hungry, right?
Well, I could eat.
Well, sit down.
It's almost ready.
Don't do that!
You sit in the chair.
He's sitting on the floor.
He's a rude little shit,
and that's his punishment.
I heard the comment you made before
while I was by the pool.
If you weren't injured,
you'd catch a beating.
And don't listen to that plastic surgery
bullshit. You're very attractive.
Don't change a thing.
You don't think
I need a nose job?
Fuck no,
you don't need a nose job!
Good, because she already had one.
- Please!
- Oh, shit!
Sit down on the floor.
By your window.
By your dog!
He doesn't mean anything by it. He's
naturally cruel. Don't take offense.
While I'm here, you don't make no more
apologies for him. New rule, okay?
Okay.
As a matter of fact, you don't make
no apologies for nobody in your life...
including yourself.
You mind serving?
My God!
Remember, you gotta have her
on tape propositioning you.
Keep that earring toward her.
You gotta negotiate a price.
Be specific.
How much for a hand job,
blow job.
If you don't get it on tape,
the DA won't prosecute.
This goddamn fucking
air conditioner!
Hottest day in the fucking Valley
and it breaks!
What's the matter?
Nothing.
You don't look like
you're into this.
I'm supposed to be excited
about busting a massage parlor?
You really think closing this place
down is gonna have a major impact...
on your precious Valley?
These people spread disease.
Oh, geez. Why am I justifying
your job to you?
What the hell did you think you were
gonna do when you transferred to Vice?
Wanna know what I think?
I was in that massage parlor,
and I liked that girl. Yeah.
Sweet kid. Woman who runs
the place...
probably gave her a ticket, brought
her over, working to pay her debt...
She is a dick-head. We should bust her.
Absolutely, but not this kid.
She's just...
a victim of circumstance.
You're a fucking bleeding-heart liberal.
No, I'm not. I'm just fed up.
I joined the force
to get into Homicide...
to bust people who commit murder.
I want to be a detective,
but I can't seem to make it happen.
I can't get promoted into Homicide,
so I transfer around...
from Robbery to Bunko
to Forgery to Vice.
I spent ten years
banging around.
I'm not doing
what I want to do.
You ain't going in there.
You ain't gonna make this bust happen.
You're gonna fuck it up.
You're right.
I'm not going in there.
24-10...
this is AC-6.
We got a problem.
- We are not going forward.
- Help, help.
He's dead.
Somebody killed him.
Do you have a car phone?
I need to call the police.
Lady, we are the police.
Bogey...
come here.
Shut up.
Shut up!
Somebody will find you
and take you.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
You're a good boy.
You're the best boy.
You'll have a nice house
and everything.
Give papa a kiss.
Hi, Jaime.
How you doing?
Shh.
I'll miss you...
like always.
Bogey, come on.
Excuse me? Miss?
I was wondering if perhaps
you might want a dog?
I have to move, and they don't
allow pets where I'm going.
Then don't move.
It's more complicated than that.
I have to leave the country.
Oh, boy, it's hot today,
isn't it?
I just came here from the Valley.
It's hell over there.
The reason I stopped you, you being
a nurse, I thought, perhaps...
one of the patients
at the hospital you work at...
might be interested
in a companion.
What do you do?
I'm a writer-director.
Do you make war movies?
War movies?
You like war movies?
Yeah, they're my favorites.
No, I never made a war movie,
though there's probably a lot of...
great stories in this cemetery.
My mother was a nurse
in World War Two.
Did you lose a family member
to war?
I lost a friend.
Would I have seen something you've done?
I don't just see war movies.
Arthur's Last Hope.
It was a TV movie.
Did you see that?
No, I didn't,
but I think I heard of it.
What else have you done?
Something called Lights Out.
Lights Out? You did that?
- You saw it?
- Yes, I did.
It was very funny.
I was the only one laughing, but yeah.
Were you the only one
in the theater?
I still liked it. Especially
the part with the elephant.
That was so unexpected.
I'm very impressed.
- Ah, what's his name?
- Bogey.
I know it's trite.
No, no, Humphrey Bogart made
two great war movies.
- Across the Pacific and...
- Tokyo Joe.
All right, I'll take him.
You will?
Are you sure you can't
postpone this trip?
Here, take him.
Thanks.
Take it easy.
Bye, Bogey.
- Come here!
- Huh?
I'm gonna introduce you.
Come on!
Introduce me to who?
To the fella I'm gonna
give the dog to.
That way you'll feel better.
It's my brother.
All right, okay.
Bogey, come on.
We're gonna go for a ride
with the lady.
He's got a puppy
that swims.
- What's your name?
- Teddy. Teddy Peppers.
- Audrey.
- Hi, Audrey, and thanks.
Ain't you gonna eat?
Not unless Mr. Hopper does, and he
won't eat unless he sits at the table.
What's the matter with these forks?
What kind are these?
You're the loyal type?
I'm Italian.
All right, get up.
Bring a plate.
Get up, up, up.
Sit down.
You expecting somebody?
- It's my half-sister.
- Get rid of her!
She won't leave. She's coming by
to see if I'm okay.
She's a nurse.
She's got a man with her.
He's holdin' a dog.
Another fuckin' dog?
I can't go in there.
Okay. You're all right.
Just wait here.
We're gonna take a quick look inside.
What's the matter?
I'm really sore right here.
Oh, my God! Look at that!
I'm bruised!
- What is that?
- Looks like a little prick...
from an injection.
What kind of injection?
I don't know.
Miss Foxx, you're all right.
Wait here. We'll be right out.
We'll take you to the station
and have a doctor look at that.
Try and remain calm.
Breathe.
Jesus Christ!
Shot him point blank
in the head.
- Don't touch anything!
- I wasn't going to, all right?
- Let's go.
- Hold up.
- We're not wasting our time here.
- I'd like to look around.
We're gonna let Homicide do it.
Fuck anything up
in this crime scene...
Defense will use it against Prosecution
when they catch the fuck that did this.
Come on, Wes.
- Let's go.
- Don't put your hand on me.
- Get downstairs.
- Get your fucking hand off me!
- Keep pushing me.
- What?
- What are you guys fighting about?
Oh, God!
Miss Foxx, where exactly were you
when this happened?
I was lying right next to him.
I mean, I think I was.
- You think?
- I don't remember anything.
We were sleeping last night and...
He's my ex-husband.
We fell asleep,
and when I woke up he was...
Roy was lying...
Oh, God!
I'm a little confused here.
You say you slept next to him,
but you didn't hear a shot?
Maybe that's what the injection was.
Stuck it in her, then used a silencer.
Who would do this?
- Do you know anyone...
- Let's go downstairs.
- Miss Foxx?
- Come on.
- Do you smoke?
- No.
- Did your ex-husband?
- No. Why?
- Do you have friends who smoke?
- I don't allow it in my house.
- Why are you asking me?
- Because I found this in your bedroom.
- Where was it?
- On the floor behind a hamper.
It must be the killers.
It must belong to them.
Put it back where you found it,
you idiot!
What?
That evidence might be part of
the crime, and you're moving it around.
Put it back!
All right, it's back.
- Could we get out of here?
- Yes.
Did you hear that?
She said it belonged to "them."
- What?
- She said it belonged to "them."
- What are you talking about?
- I held up the smokes...
and she said, "It must be the killers.
It must belong to them."
- Why would she say "them"?
- It's a figure of speech.
Like when you find your car stolen,
you say, "They stole it."
Or someone breaks into your house,
you say, "They robbed me."
It's just a figure of speech.
Your wanna-be detective brain
is working overtime.
Can you wait?
He'll be right down.
- I'll go up.
- No, no. He wanted you to wait.
- Susan, why are you acting so strange?
- I'm not acting strange.
I don't think Allan's
going to want another dog.
Where's the swimming puppy?
Can we let him in?
Let's just wait until
Allan comes down.
Why don't you guys come over here
and sit on the couch?
Just over here.
Do you want something to drink?
Oh, I would love a scotch.
Sure. I think we've got some.
Is Glenlivet all right?
- Perfect.
- Audrey?
I'm fine. Susan,
I'm wondering about you.
- That won't fit.
- Why? Because it's expensive.
It won't fit you!
Fuckin' liar! Lie to me again,
and I'll knock your teeth out.
- It's a 44.
- Some in there are 40 regulars.
Oh, yeah?
Show me one!
Ow, Jesus!
They're at the cleaners.
But that suit's not gonna fit you.
Oh, shit! Look what
you've done to my door!
I only... Ouch!
I had them fitted last month!
That suit's not going to fit you!
I had the waist custom-tailored.
I have a 32-inch waist.
I'll fit into them.
How do you get kidney stones?
- Too much calcium oxalate.
- Oh, yeah.
One of the nurses thinks
it's caused by stress.
Fuck, then I probably got them.
What do you got to be
stressed-out about?
Big house, all this money,
all this art.
It's all relative.
Oh, you're lonely.
It's tough being rich.
You can't find someone to love you
for who you are and not for your money.
I wasn't born with a silver spoon
in my mouth.
I spent a large part of my childhood
being brought up in a trailer park.
My father abandoned us.
My mother couldn't afford
to send me to college!
I might be an asshole...
but I've worked hard
to become one.
Well, you definitely
achieved your goal.
How much do they pay you
for a hit?
Two thousand? Five thousand?
Five thousand dollars?
What do I look like,
an amateur?
You look very professional.
So you'll be at this number, Miss Foxx,
if we need to get in touch?
Yeah, I'll be at my girlfriend's,
the one who's picking me up.
If you wanna go anywhere else,
let us know.
And don't worry.
When will they have, you know,
my urine analyzed?
- We should have the results...
- Could you help me out here?
What'd I tell you?
As the doctor said, we're almost
certain it was a sedative of some kind.
We're gonna find out who did this,
I promise you.
It's just all so weird.
There she is.
There's my girlfriend.
Miss Foxx, do you have to go back
to your place for any reason?
No. I never want
to go back there again.
And call me Becky.
If you think of anything, Becky...
anything at all that you think might
help us, I want you to give me a call.
I'm putting my home number on the back.
Call me anytime.
Day or night.
Even if it's just to talk.
Thanks.
You guys have been great.
You weren't coming on to her now,
were you, Doug?
Now what do you think?
She's one hell of an athlete.
I watched her compete on TV.
Did she ever medal?
I don't follow skiing.
No, she just missed.
Came in fourth
in the last two Olympics.
How did it go?
"How did it go?"
How could you kill Roy,
in my house...
in my bed,
with me sleeping next to him?
You were supposed to shoot him
at his place.
We didn't tell you
where we were gonna do it.
Lee didn't want you to know
when or where it was gonna happen.
That way you're out of it.
You can't be connected.
Can't be connected?
- I was three inches away from him!
- That's why they can't put it together.
- Did Lee drop a pack of cigarettes?
- Why?
Because they kept asking me
about them.
Yes, they were planted.
I'm not gonna tell you anything more.
The less you know, the better.
They asked; you answered honestly. You
don't know anybody who smokes them.
That's the way
it's supposed to go.
Lee knows what he's doing.
He's protecting you.
Were you there too?
Where's the money?
Lee wants you to bring the money.
Well, we have
a little problem there.
- What problem?
- It's in my house.
- In your house?
- In a safe in the closet of my house!
- Our 30,000 is in your closet?
- That's right.
- How can you leave it lying around?
- Don't yell at me!
You know, I'm just curious.
This friend of yours who's buried
in the veterans' cemetery...
I don't want to talk about him.
I don't mean to be nosy.
I just know what it takes
to get in there.
There's a lot of heroes buried
in that place. Was your friend a hero?
He wouldn't have
considered himself one.
- You lose him in Vietnam?
- Yes.
Now I don't really want
to talk about it anymore.
Okay. Next subject.
What are you gonna do?
I'm going to get our money. It's time
for us to say good-bye to California.
We'd like to take
our money with us.
But those detectives
are up at the house.
- No problem.
- What are you gonna do?
I'm going to get our money.
Then Helga and I...
will say good-bye until you get
the check from his insurance company.
Then you'll contact us,
and we'll divide it in half.
- Get packed. Have everything in the car.
- Okay, baby.
I wish I knew you were
gonna kill Roy in my house.
I would have wanted to discuss it.
I've already been
through this with her.
Look, darlin', it's over.
There's no turnin' back.
Stay calm.
Follow the plan and everything
will happen as it should.
Is there someone else in on this,
somebody I should know about?
Why don't you tell me the truth?
Why do you keep torturing me?
Just tell her, Lee.
What's the difference?
Since you've been such a good sport,
I'm gonna put your mind at ease...
so you can sleep at night.
Yes, there is
another person involved.
He'll take the fall, but don't worry
about him talking because he's dead.
Everything will lead back to him,
and it will appear as if...
he was hired to kill your ex-husband
because of a drug deal gone bad.
Now, you know almost everything.
What else is there to know?
Becky.
We have to keep
some secrets from you, don't we?
In case you forget to call us
when you get that insurance check.
Exactly.
He's coming.
Everybody, sit down.
What's going on?
This guy's holding us hostage.
Who is he?
He won't tell us his name,
but I know him from somewhere.
Everybody shut up.
Didn't I tell you to sit down?
Be smart.
Here's the situation.
When it gets dark,
we're all gonna take a ride.
- Not me! I have to lay down!
- Then you'll lay down in the trunk!
- Goin' where?
- You'll see when we get there.
I don't wanna shoot nobody...
but I will if it becomes
a necessity.
If everybody behaves,
nobody's gonna get hurt.
Miss Pollutzo,
you're gonna drive.
- Who's Pollutzo?
- That's my real last name.
- How does he know?
- She told him.
She's been with me for eight years.
I never knew she had another last name.
He meets her, and five seconds later,
they're bosom buddies!
- What are you doin'?
- I'm just taking some notes.
- He's a television writer.
- Put the fuckin' pen down!
Could you talk slower?
- Don't!
- He's think I'm fuckin' around.
You better tell him
I'm not fuckin' around, Susan.
He's not fuckin' around.
"He's not"...
- Gimme back the pen.
- Sit the fuck down!
- Gimme that back.
- Shut up!
Sit the fuck down!
Shut those fuckin' dogs up!
Fore!
Goddamn it!
I've had it with you assholes.
That is the third time
you've broken my fuckin' window!
Whoa!
Get out from behind that tree.
Come out with your hands up!
I'm a police officer!
It wasn't me. It was him.
- Walk out!
- Where you going?
- Okay, I'm comin'.
Don't shoot.
Fuckin' hack.
Son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch!
Aren't you and Lee engaged?
Yeah.
Why?
It doesn't bother him
that you slept with Roy?
I didn't sleep with Roy.
And Lee believes that...
that you just fooled around?
That really bothers you,
doesn't it?
No, I'll tell you what bothers me.
That he's gonna murder those detectives.
- What do you care about them?
- Roy was one thing.
He was a shit.
He treated me like shit. He was a rat.
He cheated on me our whole marriage,
and then he sued me for alimony.
I was paying him alimony.
Did you know that? No.
I don't give a shit about Roy.
But those detectives?
They were nice to me. I don't want to be
a part of them being killed.
Then you shouldn't have left
our money in your closet.
How was I supposed to know
you were gonna shoot Roy in my house?
- Don't raise your voice at me!
- Can't you call it off?
Now lower your voice,
you little bitch.
What did you call me?
A bitch?
Roy put up with a lot of shit too.
You were never supportive of his career.
Yours always came first.
You made your husband feel like shit.
That's why he cheated on you.
He deserved alimony.
You liked him.
You really liked him.
Of course I liked him.
Roy was a likable guy.
He knew how to treat a woman.
How would you know?
You were never there.
You were always too busy
training for your next event.
That's why your husband
went to other women.
His little "worm"...
couldn't even satisfy him in bed.
What the hell
are they doin' up there?
Maybe that's how they make love
in Tarzana.
You want walls?
You bitch!
Maybe she'll give you
skiing lessons.
This girl is in great shape.
She ought to be.
Look at all this equipment.
In her bedroom.
Think she's a little obsessed?
Hey, that's what it takes to win.
You gotta be obsessed.
I admire her. She never won,
but she keeps on trying.
You know what bothers me
about all this?
This job is so clean,
so professional...
but he leaves
an empty cigarette pack.
I know we're Valley detectives,
but how stupid does he think we are?
Unless he doesn't care.
- You hear something?
- What?
I'm gonna check downstairs.
Carla?
Hello?
Hello.
You guys up there?
- Can I help you?
- Hi.
I'm Van Nuys vice.
My partner and I discovered
this crime scene this morning.
Right.
I thought I'd drop by
and see how things were going.
- We're kind of busy right now.
- Right. Listen.
I was curious.
You know that cigarette pack?
- Did you find that?
- Yes, I did.
- Good work.
- Well, thank you.
Thanks.
It's interesting, actually.
When I asked Miss Foxx about it,
her response was...
"It must be the killers.
It must belong to them."
What's your point?
I think that Becky Foxx
might be in on this.
- Really.
- Yes.
Maybe she hired the hit men.
I know.
It sounds farfetched, but she
and the victim were recently divorced.
Maybe that's something to check into.
Maybe the divorce was a messy thing.
But the fact that she said "them,"
it bothers me.
- What do you think?
- Interesting.
It's reaching,
but worth consideration.
Listen, would you be willing to do
a little legwork for us?
Absolutely. You name it.
Anything. What do you need?
I have to drive down
to the station...
see if the lab has an I.D. Print
of the cigarette pack.
Maybe you wanna ride along.
We could talk on the way.
Maybe you could find out
who that divorce lawyer was.
And I should check into
the insurance policies.
A lot of times these couples
get divorced...
and don't change the beneficiaries
on their policies right away.
Good idea. Come on.
Lee.
Becky shot me.
That bitch shot me.
Help!
Let's go. Come on.
I don't think so.
Are you kiddin'?
You think I'm gonna shoot you?
Go ahead. Shoot me.
- Shoot me.
- Are you fucking crazy?
I think he's suicidal.
We all have our flaws.
I had a bad feeling about you
right from the beginning.
- What if I shoot her?
- You harm her, and I'll kill you...
and I'm not fuckin' around!
Point that gun somewhere else,
or you'll be sorry.
You'll come with me?
If you give me your word,
once we're safely out of the Valley...
you'll let everybody go.
You'd take this loser's word?
You can't believe him!
I'll take his word over yours.
It's been my experience,
more often than not...
that a loser has more honor
than a winner.
- I give you my word.
- Your word of honor?
You got it.
Come on, Bogey.
I'm telling you, there's not
enough room in the car.
Don't you start with me,
you little selfish prick...
because you
I don't give a shit about!
I can't go.
I'm in a lot of pain!
Doctors compare the pain
of passing a kidney stone...
to a woman
giving birth to a baby!
Bouncing in the car will hurt.
I've got to take painkillers
and lay down!
Tell him, Audrey. You're a nurse.
Make him understand!
He's out of pain now.
Let's go.
Audrey, come on.
As soon as I'm out of the Valley,
I'll let you all go.
I really didn't
want to have to hit him.
You lost your temper.
Sometimes that happens.
When I was a kid,
once I got so mad at my father...
'cause he didn't come to my...
What didn't he come to?
To my piano recital.
I got so mad I...
I set fire
to his favorite chair.
Did you really?
Good for you.
What's your name?
Dosmo.
- You still play the piano?
- Nah, I gave it up.
Well, it's never too late
to start again.
Let's get the hell outta here.
You, in the back.
In the front.
- Am I dying?
- Is Becky dead?
She ran. I shot at her.
I don't know if I hit her.
It hurts.
Please take me to a hospital.
What are you doing?
This is a tough decision for me.
"Decision"?
What decision?
Honey, I love you. There's no other way.
I can't take you to a hospital.
Understand?
Give me a minute.
You give everybody else a minute.
Baby, the wound,
it's not as bad as it looks.
No, you've lost too much blood.
You're definitely dying.
I'm doing you a favor
by finishing you off.
Honey, just tell me the truth.
I gotta know.
Did you sleep with Roy?
How can you ask me that?
How can you ask me that now?
You're right. I'm sorry.
I gotta get outta here.
Just for the record,
I think you did sleep with him.
Goddamn automatics!
Always jam!
Hold on a second.
You don't mind
if I borrow this, do you?
Hey, baby.
Help!
- Where we going?
- I'm gonna drop everybody in Pasadena.
Then you're gonna go
back to Brooklyn?
What's this?
- Stop the car!
- Shut up!
- Keep goin'!
I'm a nurse.
I have to get out of the car!
- Shut up and just...
- Let her out.
- What happened?
- She came out of the bushes.
All right. It's okay.
Try to relax.
Just try to relax. That's it.
You can hold onto my hand.
That's it.
Everything's gonna be okay.
- What kind of language is that?
- Sounds Swedish.
Try to relax.
Everything's gonna be okay.
She's not gonna make it...
- Get out.
- What's going on?
- I need the car.
- I'm driving you.
Thank you, Teddy.
There you go.
Everything's gonna be okay.
All right. That's it.
Try to breathe.
That's a girl. Just relax.
Get the fuck down!
Down!
Get behind the car.
Stay the fuck down!
Go on.
Save him, 'cause the next shot's
gonna blow his brains out.
- Who is he?
- I'm a police officer.
Stay where you are.
Do not jeopardize
your safety for me.
Shoot a guy when he's down?
Where's your guts?
You can save him.
Go get him.
Fuck him.
I'm comin' to get you.
Come get me, Dumbo.
Stay where you are.
That's an order.
You motherfuckin' cowardly prick!
Come get me, Dumbo.
Dosmo, don't!
He'll kill you!
Boo!
Time's up.
You're a tricky son of a bitch.
You almost got away with it...
but that's your life,
isn't it, Dosmo?
Almost, but not quite.
Come on, Dosmo.
Dosmo, hurry!
Go.
Thank you.
You want this?
Nah.
You know, you do know me.
From Polly's Pizza
in Studio City.
You knew?
I realized it when you were cooking,
but I didn't want to say anything.
I didn't want to embarrass you.
You know...
this could be seed money
to open up a pizzeria in Brooklyn.
- Dosmo?
- What?
There's just one thing
that bothers me.
It's been bothering me
since we met.
Can I do something?
Don't get mad. Just try it.
What?
- Give me that!
- You really look better without it.
Don't ever do that again.