Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Uh.
Dito.
Oh, my goodness.
I can't believe
to hear your voice
on this machine.
It's your mother.
Dito, I called
your friend Nerf to call you.
He's a good kid.
Uh--
I don't know
what else to do.
Your father's sick.
He's real sick,
and he won't go
to the hospital.
You know how he is,
and I'm sorry.
I don't know
what else to do.
Your friend Nerf, uh,
he's a good kid, you know.
He said he'd pick you up
at the airport if you came.
I know that it's far.
I'm sorry.
I, uh--
I'm gonna hang up
now, Dito.
Okay.
I love you.
No matter what you do,
Tonight we have the author
of a wonderful,
wonderful book.
A Guide to Recognizing
Your Saints.
Dito Montiel.
Thanks.
By the end
of all this, Giuseppe,
his brother Antonio
used to call him "Little Sister"
'cause he slept with Noxzema
on his face every night.
It never even made sense,
being everything else
about him was a mess.
Well, he loved
the face cream, you know?
Anyway, Giuseppe,
he's gonna be dead.
Yeah, I know.
It sucks.
There'll be another guy
you'll meet too,
same with him.
And then another little boy.
He's gonna die, too.
What a mess, huh?
And I don't even know why
I feel I gotta tell you this
up front but I do.
And don't worry, like,
I'm not giving away
any big ending, you know,
with this.
A whole lot of other shit's
gotta happen first.
But I just, uh,
I wanna remember
who these people are
and what they meant to me.
What they mean to me.
And they are real.
My name's Dito.
I'm gonna leave everybody
in this film.
I see Laurie's and Diane's
walkin' down 31st Street.
Hot pink leg warmers.
Red, white and blue
roach clip feathered earrings.
"The Song Remains the Same"
painted on the back
of their jackets.
And they wanna know,
"Yo, Dito, you Rock or Disco?"
What the fuck?
You fuckin' idiot!
I see innocent Giuseppe's
walking down the streets
where Puerto Ricans
still listen to Journey.
Dito, what's up, man?
Really, It's true.
Puerto Ricans
listen to Journey.
Yo, Steve Perry's
the shit, bro!
Antonio!
When this place
isn't covered in violence,
That's where the fuckin' shit
from the toilet goes.
And even sometimes
when it is,
You're drinking it
like an idiot.
You taking a bath
and shit, man.
this place is heaven.
Get the fuck off him!
Whoa, whoa.
Stop, stop, stop!
What's wrong with you?
What the fuck?
What the fuck is that?
Motherfucker sounds
like he's prayin' and shit.
Yes.
Praying and shit, huh?
Oh, ladies.
Uh, which one of you
wanna suck,
suck me off first?
You?
You ain't got shit!
What about that?
It's cute.
I like it.
You got it.
Hey, clean this shit up, too.
Hey yo, check it out.
I wrote "Bruce Lee" up there.
Nerf, you climbed
all the way up there?
What are you,
a fuckin' stupid, man?
What the fuck
is the matter with you?
Yo, that's fucked up.
Somebody wrote some shit
on your house, man.
Reaper, he's from Queensbridge.
They wrote Satan and shit
all over the church, too.
Hey, Dito.
It's so hot outside.
You got out, yet?
Tell him it's hot
because it's summer, you know.
Antonio, come in.
Look at you guys.
You're filthy.
You want juice?
Yeah, give me a juice.
Hey, look who's here.
Antonio, what's going on?
Are you fixin'--
What are you doing?
Could you keep it down
down there?
Hello!
Could you please--
Do you want me
to say somethin' to 'em?
No, it's okay.
No. It's alright.
Come on in.
Giuseppe, sit down.
Good to see you.
Antonio, where you been lately?
What do you mean?
I've been around.
I haven't seen you
at the handball courts.
You guys getting tired
of getting beat, huh?
Dito didn't tell you
we been at the Boys club,
boxing?
They got the Golden Gloves
coming up.
The only thing
you'll ever box
is oranges.
Dad, this is serious.
They got bags and everything.
It's cheap.
$10.
$10. Where you guys
gonna get $10 from?
It's just $10.
You guys wanna be
Golden Gloves?
You learn from the best.
Up from the waist,
down from the chin.
That's Golden Gloves.
Okay.
Stop it already.
Seriously.
You're serious?
Come here.
Shake my hand.
I'm glad to meet you.
Serious.
That's a funny joke
if I was five years old.
Stop it.
The joke is five years old.
Antonio, how old
is this guy?
He's serious.
I don't know
how old he is.
What happened to your nose?
It's bleeding.
It's my father.
He's stupid.
Whatever.
Don't say that
about your father.
Hand him a dish rag.
Wipe his nose there.
What's the matter with him?
Are you alright?
Are you getting a job?
What are you doing
with your life?
Yeah, for sure.
I'm doing--
Yeah, you're not doing anything.
You wanna be boxers.
Forget about
these Golden Gloves.
You wanna learn?
You come to me,
'cause I'm the king.
And the king
sits right here.
Monty's throne, right?
Monty's throne.
I'm the king.
I'm gonna get up.
I'm gonna show you--
Are gonna get up?
What?
I'm gonna show him.
I'm going to show you
the left hook.
I'm gonna show you
that left hook.
Bye, Mom.
Antonio, come on.
Antonio!
Alright, man.
Come on.
Antonio, come on!
Where you going?
What's the matter with him?
What's the matter?
Where you going?
He wants to go.
Giuseppe, come on, man.
Say good bye.
Thank you very much.
I appreciate it very much.
It was a pleasure
talking to you.
Thank you very much.
That kid doesn't say
two words.
It scares me that kid.
Antonio?
Tonight I want you
to come back.
I want you to have dinner
with Dito and the family,
alright?
You take care
of that nose kid.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
They're alright.
Good dancing.
Look who we got here.
Oh, shit!
Friggin' pistachio dick.
Look at these girls.
It curves like a banana, right?
No, like a pistachio.
Do you want some?
You.
It's as hot
as a fuckin' oven in here.
Get the fuck off me!
It's like 250 degrees.
Get off me.
I feel like a piece
of roast beef.
But look at me.
I'm fuckin' sticky.
Look at me.
So?
Fuckin' landlord's
got the fuckin' radiators on
in the summer.
You better not fuckin'
cum in me.
No!
Don't fuck.
You better not fuckin'
cum in me.
Fuck!
What the fuck?
Fuckin' radiator burned me
and shit!
Fuck me.
Come here.
You want me to come over there
and give you a hug
or some shit?
I don't want you
to fuckin' hug me.
Look what we got here.
You guys are two
naughty fuckers.
Who the fuck is this guy?
My little retarded sister.
You're the bitch
who works at the pool
with Diane.
I just got done
fuckin' her.
Get the fuck
out of here.
I'm virile and I'm virile
and I'm virile,
and I'm ready to do that shit.
I just stole this dildo
from Mrs. Duran's,
and I was wondering
you go into that shit, baby?
Two on one action?
All I'm saying,
if I was an ugly bitch
and two hot studs like this
wanted to fuck me,
I'd be into it.
I'm taking a shit
and I'm out.
What are you thinking about?
I don't know.
You're really beautiful,
you know.
Thank you.
Are you pushing?
Do you wanna kiss me?
For sure.
Kiss you.
Fuck you.
I'm sorry.
I just, just wanna fuck you,
you know.
Alright.
Alright?
No.
You're bugging, man.
I don't know
why I said that.
I wanna fuck you, you know.
I wanna fuck you, too.
I do.
I really do.
For real?
For real.
Class, this is Michael O'Shea.
He's a new student.
He just moved here
this winter from Ireland.
And besides making music,
Michael wants to be a writer
just like his father.
On his first day here,
he wants to read a poem
about America.
Here you go.
My name's Michael O'Shea,
and I'm from Scotland.
Uh. My father says
poems don't always
have to rhyme.
This one doesn't.
My New friend.
I know he likes me,
but I think he needs me.
I definitely need him, too.
This is a scary place
sometimes.
But my new friend,
he needs me
because together
we're not like everybody else.
That was very nice, Michael.
Thank you.
Okay, class, let's turn
to page 64, please.
Thank you.
It's hot as shit out here.
What the fuck
you looking at?
Don't even fuckin' try
that shit.
Want some gum?
Yo, did you really take
a shit in there?
What is wrong with you?
You smell
like open ass, man.
Hey!
Hey, old bitch.
Hey, hey.
Hey, put your ass here.
Go ahead.
Nice dress.
Fuckin' looking
like a cheetah.
Clean that shit up!
What?
Fucker!
What the fuck
is wrong with you, man?
Clean your shit up
and tell him to fuck off!
Police'll be here
in five minutes.
Antonio, come on.
No, no, no, no.
Wait, wait.
Open the door, man.
Hey, come on,
open the fuckin' door!
Yo, meet me
at the park, alright?
Meet me at the park.
You fucker.
You better fuckin' flinch.
You're the new kid
from my class, right?
From Ireland.
Scotland.
We came and lived
in Manhattan for a bit
but now, yeah.
Fucking crazy there, right?
I'm Dito.
I'm, uh, I'm Dito.
Mick.
Uhm, Mike.
And then Giuseppe was the kid
climbing on the window.
The church, the roof.
My friend, he was running naked
on the-- you remember that?
On the roof?
He was funny.
Where you going?
Just got bored,
you know?
Kind of ride
the subway around.
Back and forth,
and back and forth.
And back and forth.
Back and forth.
Stupid thing.
Just back and forth?
Yeah.
I was gonna ride it
to Coney Island or something.
Go there
and I don't know,
ride back.
I was thinking about going
to Coney Island, you know.
Yeah, 'cause I've never been.
You've never been?
No. I went to the zoo once
but that was like
in the Bronx or something.
It's not really--
That's not traveling.
It sucks, too.
There's nothing really there.
What are you looking at?
That dot.
Close one eye like this.
Fly right over it.
Oh, shit.
I got it.
You want China?
That's what they got
Chinatown for.
You want Italy?
You go to Georgie.
Where's the Italians they go?
Mulberry Street.
Little Italy.
Wanna go to Puerto Rico?
Go uptown. There's
Puerto Ricans everywhere.
You know what Antonio
just told me?
That there's wild dogs
in Italy, right?
Who needs that?
Not me.
I don't wanna be there.
How are you?
Nice seeing you.
Uncle George,
how you doing?
I'm just boiling.
It's summertime.
That's why you're boiling.
You want some juice?
Where you been?
I was in Coney Island.
What were you doing there?
I was on the train.
I meet up with this guy
from school.
This Mike kid.
He's from Ireland.
Like from the country Ireland.
He was telling me about
how he wants to do some music,
like a band or something.
You just went
to Coney Island.
Is it just me
or it's 100 degrees
in this house?
It's summer.
That's why it's hot.
Right, Antonio?
Yeah.
It's summer.
It's, summer, baby.
It's hot.
What can I tell you?
Will you just stop teasing?
The heat's unbearable.
We gotta get a fan, Monty.
We gotta get a fan.
Maria, you still there?
I have to attach
this machine.
She's gonna set
this place on fire!
Can I see
what's going on?
I brought the tape.
I brought the machine
to show you, Monty.
I don't care
about that machine.
You can play things
from the television.
So it's that machine.
Rewind that.
Let's see that again.
Dito, where you going?
It's show time over here.
Are you expecting a date
with that girl?
That swimmer?
We heard from your friend
you have a girlfriend now, huh?
She's a swimmer?
A Swimmer?
Who, Laurie?
She sells food at the pool.
Yeah, she sells food
at the pool.
That swimmer girl?
right, Antonio?
The swimmer girl.
Uncle George,
she's not a swimmer.
She sells food at the pool.
That's what she does.
What does she do?
Like races or marathons?
Maybe it was the guy
from Coney Island.
The Irish guy.
The guy who wants the band.
Right, Monty?
She's a swimmer.
What's she doing at the pool
if she don't swim?
You have seven
new messages.
Uh, Dito,
this is Nerf.
Your old friend Nerf.
Monty's not,
not doing too good, man.
I know Antonio called you
and, uh,
you-- you're father's
real sick, man.
Your mom called me
and... she really wants you
to come home, you know.
So you should.
Hey, come back.
Fuck you!
I hate those fucks!
What are you doing?
Pay, thank.
Oh, my God.
Chinese motherfucker
always staring me down!
You pay.
Why does your dad
calls us swimmers?
'Cause you work
at a pool.
But I'm not a swimmer.
You better tell Antonio
and his fucking brother
not to come around my house.
I don't like that asshole.
Diane, don't worry
about it.
He's a controlling little fuck!
I could tell
just by looking at him.
You're making it bigger.
Stop being crazy, alright?
Is it just me
or does that nigger
seem retarded?
What the fuck are you doing?
That's my friend's
mother's store.
That's the shit they wrote
on your housel
What the fuck
are you doing?
You got a problem?
Get off him right now.
I'm not playing.
What the fuck?
Are you crazy?
Fucking bitch!
That's right, asshole.
I don't have a problem.
Laurie, go get Antonio.
You need a bitch
to go get your man?
I should fuckin' kill you!
I should fuckin' kill you.
I'm gonna get you.
I got you, baby.
You stupid fuckin' bitch!
You nappy motherfucker.
I got you!
Explain this to me.
You and this swimmer
got into some trouble?
Mr. Montiel,
I don't even swim.
You don't swim.
Look at that eye.
We collect tickets
where the food is
at the swimming pool.
I'm thinking of quitting.
Maybe working
at the supermarket.
It's just like
too many kids.
Yeah, we care.
Fuck you, okay?
Put this on your eye, alright?
I'm not putting meat
on my eye.
Get out of here.
I'm not putting that
on my face.
People used to do that
100 years ago.
I just want to know
what's going on.
Tell me what happened.
Nothing's going on.
It's very simple.
What happened to your eye?
I'm telling you,
nothing happened, okay?
Some jerk was acting
like a wise guy.
Daddy, some jerk was acting
That's it.
That's it, okay?
You got cut a little bit.
He grabbed him
by the face
and cut him.
Who grabbed him
by the face?
A Puerto Rican?
The one that spray painted
all the graffiti outside.
A Puerto Rican did this?
Was it the Reaper guy?
Please, stop it.
Don't ask me to stop it.
This guy better worry now.
And I know where he is.
Nerf told me where they stay
down by Queensbridge.
Remember what I said.
Two shots.
Six inches, they go right down.
Two shots?
Shit.
Shut the fuck up.
I'm sorry, Monty.
I don't mean to be cursing.
That's enough, okay?
Hey!
God gave me this mouth
so I can use it
and that's what I'm doing.
Am I gonna have
to smack this girl?
She's just talking.
Get the fuck
out of my way!
Yo, Yo,
get the fuck out!
Hey, fuckin',
Nerf, where the fuck
did you get a car?
My mother let me
take it out to practice
for my license.
How'd your mother
get a car?
I gotta practice
for my license.
Hey, get off the car!
Get the fuck off my car!
What the fuck?
Get in, get in.
Let's go.
No, don't get in.
I'm coming back.
You're gonna leave me, then?
This thing is huge!
I'm coming back.
We're gonna go
around the block.
What happened
to your face?
They hit him in the face
with a bottle.
Your graffiti friends
hit him with a bottle.
They fucked up your mom's store.
Dito.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Take us down
to Queensbridge.
I gotta take
the car back.
Take me down
to Queensbridge right now.
No, I can't.
Fuck it.
I'll drive.
Alright.
Shut up!
Are you gonna call me?
I'm gonna be on this corner.
You better call me, Dito.
Your graffiti friends
hit him in the face
with a bottle.
What, are you fuckin' stupid?
What did you say?
He's my brother.
You know the guy
that writes graffiti around here?
No hablo inglés.
No habla fuckin' Inglés.
What the fuck
you doing out
so late, man?
So you know the kids
that write graffiti
and shit, right?
How you know them?
Because one of,
one of the members
are my brother.
Is your brother?
Your bro-- brother?
Reaper.
Reaper?
You see my friend
right there?
He's cut, right?
Your brother did that.
Yeah, he cut Dito.
Can you say that?
Can you say his name?
He cut Dito.
You can tell him
Antonio came by?
Yeah?
He's a little kid, man.
You can remember
to tell him that for me?
He cut Dito.
I like this kid.
I like him.
This kid's good.
Alright, I like this kid.
Are you fuckin' stupid?
What's wrong with you?
Let's get out of here!
Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
I sent a little
fuckin' message.
Your father's not stupid.
I swear your father's
a good guy, man.
If anybody ever
fucked with him,
forget it.
Antonio's not a well kid.
He shouldn't be
hanging out with him.
He's a good kid.
No!
I was any different?
Come on, stop it.
You were so much different.
You are a great father.
Not this guy's dad.
He beats him to a pulp.
He's a good guy, you know?
He's a good guy.
That's right, motherfucker!
That's the song?
Man, I'm telling you,
your band's gonna be
fuckin' hardcore, man.
Yo, Radioman,
what's up, my man?
Who the fuck
is that guy?
He's cool.
Your band has to be cool.
We need to be like Black Flag,
Bad Brains, Urban Waste,
Major Conflict, all of them.
Those bands rule.
That's fuckin' music.
Our band needs to be cool.
We need a good name.
For what?
The band.
This is it.
Right here?
This is Frank?
What's the deal with this Frank?
We can do the job together.
Definitely.
He's going to go
on about Job.
You know,
the guy from the Bible.
Just say you know.
Which one's the job?
He's got like
everything going on, man.
He's cool.
I told him
you don't have to be a fag
to talk like a fag.
Therefore you don't
have to be a fag to have
your dogs walked by a fag.
Watch the little one.
I gotta go, Raul.
I gotta call this pain in the ass
before it gets too late.
Yeah.
Oh, unbelievable.
Frank, this is Dito.
Hi.
Okay.
Mikey, there's $10
I owe you in dimes.
It's on the floor.
Take it for train fares, okay?
Yes?
Miss Levitt,
I was just gonna call you.
I would never take little Bobo
onto the subway.
Please!
George, come here.
Come here!
No, I'm serious.
You gotta tell me
who would say things
like that about me.
No.
Wha--
I got somebody here.
Let me ask.
Listen, Hey!
You know the video
of, uh, Lionel Richie
with the blind lady?
Hello.
Yes.
She heard you.
I love that song, too.
Yes.
Yes, 9:00
Thank you!
Oh!
Nightmare!
Okay.
Let's go.
Come on.
I got Shakespeare.
Let's go, guys.
Come one.
Let's go.
Come on, come on!
Come on.
Did you take the dimes
for the train fare?
Okay, let's go.
Come on.
And close the door.
You see, they're insects.
Fuckin' horseflies
like animals in this place.
I don't want them
getting out.
Get George.
Let's go.
That's it, come on.
Let's go, come on.
My good friend here says
your name is Titi
or Chiti or Rodito.
Dito.
And you guys
are gonna do a band?
Dito's gonna sing.
Oh, how gay.
I mean, great.
Is this gonna be
like Lionel Richie
or you guys rock out?
No, Frank.
We're gonna be hardcore
like Black Flag.
One of my clients, Bobby,
he has the Pomeranian.
He's an entertainment manager,
like music or something.
I'll have you guys
walk his dog.
You never know, right?
Hello there, Abigail.
Taking the dog out
for a drag again,
I see.
She's too cheap
to pay the six bucks
for me to walk that thing.
I mean, come on,
they're older than dirt.
Frank, what's the job about?
Miss Abigail needs
some hot young action,
right lovely?
Come here.
George.
She can't hear worth shit.
You walk dogs
for half an hour
or until they crap.
I charge them $6.
I give you $4.
I thought we get $3.
This is one honest
young man, this boy.
Like Job from the Bible.
You know
who Job is, Condito?
Yeah.
I already told him, Frank.
You just got a raise then,
for the band.
'Cause we walk dogs, you know?
You walk dogs.
Whole wide world
walks fuckin' dogs.
Always carry paper.
Pretend you pick up the crap.
Ay!
How loud
is this freaking city.
Nerf.
Oh, my God.
It's good to see you, man.
Really.
Thanks for picking me up.
Hey, no problem, man.
I couldn't believe it
when you called, dude.
I still can't fucking' believe it,
but you're here, man.
It's fucked up, right?
It's been a long time,
and it's great to see you.
You bugged out
when Antonio called, huh?
I still can't believe it, you know.
That's all.
Guess who I saw
the other day?
Fuckin' Laurie.
Your old fuckin' girl, right?
Still up on Ditmars.
She's got a kid now.
Kid's a fuckin' rat.
She's got a kid?
Who with?
I don't fuckin' know.
Not that Guido
who used to hit on her?
Guido Tony!
No, no.
Fuckin' no.
That motherfucker
went to the army
or some shit.
Maybe he invented something.
I don't really know.
Hey, remember this place?
Greek Pancyprian Club.
Yo!
Uh, this place rock or disco?
I hate that shit.
Fuckers.
Uh, it's a full-on
Yuppie club now, man.
Unbelievable.
Better that way, though.
People always dress up
and shit.
It looks a little bit better
around here, you know.
Your mom's still here, huh?
Yeah.
But she's sleeping.
I mean, everybody says
I should get
my own place, but--
I ain't got to pay rent.
You get free food.
For now, you know.
Thanks for letting me stay.
I can get a hotel
if you want.
Hotel?
Hell, man.
My mom's got the room
all cleaned out.
She's all excited.
She thinks you know all
the movie stars in California.
Wait a minute.
Let's just, uh--
Let's just hang here
a minute, okay?
I mean, damn.
I didn't think I was ever
gonna see you again,
you know.
Upstairs we can't really talk.
You want some?
Uh, no, no.
That's cool.
I just take a little.
Yeah, sure.
We just--
We should go to Monty's
right now.
Nah, it's late.
It's late.
What time is it?
We'll go in the morning, then.
I hate to--
I hate seeing him
like he is, man.
He's fucked up.
And your mom,
she--
She didn't think
you'd come back.
She told me that, uh--
She tells everybody
about your book.
It's like your friend, remember?
That, that kid, fuckin' Irish.
How are you?
How am I?
Are you alright?
I'm alright.
Ah!
I don't know
how to answer that, man.
Just like my fuckin' mom.
Like I told you.
I told you how she's so excited
to see you, and then with me,
you know, it's like--
When I--
She sees me
on the street,
she hides.
And she's so fat, you know.
And she tries to hide behind
these skinny little poles.
Poles like that
right there.
Even she hides from me
and she's my fuckin' mom.
They're not supposed
to do that.
I know.
Things will--
Things will pick up
and get better.
No, man.
Things don't get better here.
You tell me
that they fuckin' do, but--
It's really,
it's fuckin' good
to see you, man.
That's the truth.
Is that true?
Shit!
Oh, shit.
They got this thing
over the Empire State Building
which is like Ripley's
Believe it or Not.
Mike was telling me
about this guy he saw.
He's humongous.
It's a 10-foot tall statue
of this real guy
and a bunch of other shit.
That's where the niggers
stay at, right?
No.
That's 42nd Street.
Oh, Yeah.
Needledick was saying they got
triple X movie over there.
Like fuckin' people
fuckin' pigs and shit.
People fuckin' pigs?
Get the fuck out of here!
This guy is like 10 feet tall.
He's fuckin' huge, man.
There's loads
of cool shit there.
Check this guy out.
What do you wanna see,
some fuckin' titties
or a giant?
Yeah, I wanna see a pig
get fucked.
Exactly.
Mike, huh?
Dito says that you guys work
for some faggot, right?
Think he can give me
a job?
I'll see.
Yeah?
Yeah, man.
I'll check out.
Yo, this weed is bogus.
I know a guy from school.
He's got great weed.
That shit will fuck you up.
He's cool as well.
Guy is cool.
Wow!
You can get weed, huh?
This guy's pretty fuckin' cool.
He can get fuckin' pot.
That's pretty fuckin'--yeah.
This guy's pretty cool.
You can understand
what he says?
'Cause I can't fuckin'
understand him.
Yo, Dito,
I'm going to take off, man.
Where you going?
What's your problem, man?
Antonio, I don't want
any trouble.
I just wanna hang out.
If you got a problem
with me, I'll go.
No, man.
I ain't got no problem.
You can hang out
as much as you want.
You can show us
where the giants are
and all that.
I like this guy.
He's, he's fun.
He's a good guy.
We're getting something
to eat,
and she wants to go
go White Castle.
Why don't you shut up?
Why you got to do this?
What'd you say?
Why you got to do
that shit?
Don't you fuckin' move, Diane.
Cut the fuckin' shit, alright?
Do what?
You know what.
It's just played out.
What's played out?
She moved.
What the fuck.
I'm fucking serious.
That shit is not funny!
Giuseppe, that's enough.
I'm getting the fuck
out of here.
Yeah?
Go ahead.
Bye.
Could you do something
about your fucking
crazy brother?
Fuck you, Giuseppe, alright?
You fuckin' piece of shit!
Fuck you.
Laurie!
She wants to go
to White Castle, alright?
This bitch loves going
to White Castle.
To White Castle.
Laurie?
Come on.
Where you going?
Fuck them.
It's played out here.
Laurie.
Laurie, can you stop for a sec?
Laurie, come on!
Did you really see
what that fucker did?
I know.
You think that's funny?
I know it's not funny.
I don't think it's funny.
Hold on a second!
I'm sorry.
I don't fuckin'
like that, either.
Yeah, right.
You do.
I'm coming.
I'll be right there, alright?
I am sorry.
Whatever.
Hey, my name is Diane.
I like to fuck.
My name is Jenny.
And everybody in this place
is a fuckin' joke.
My name is Nerf.
And this shit sucks.
I'm Giuseppe,
Antonio's brother.
I'm Laurie.
And everybody's
gonna leave me.
I know they are.
I'm a fuckin' piece of shit.
And that's who I am.
Hey, listen, Antonio.
I'm sorry about this
played out shit.
Don't worry about it.
No, that's fucked up!
Now, that's fucked up.
I'm going to go in.
Do you want me to come?
No.
Don't worry.
I'm good.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Monty said he wanted to play
some handball tomorrow.
So I'm gonna come by.
That's fucked up.
He's my Goddamned son, too.
They run around
like a pack of wolves!
Do you even have
any concern?
Do you?
No!
What's wrong?
You okay, mom?
I'm okay.
It's okay.
It's nothing.
Dito.
She, you know,
she got excited, you know.
I was just, uh--
Your mother, she-- you know,
went for a walk.
She gets excited.
You okay?
Fine.
I'm good.
What happened with you
and Antonio?
He was here.
He said you were mad at him.
You had a fight or something?
It's alright.
How'd get that?
What's this on your face?
You okay?
Yeah.
What happened to you?
What is this?
It's nothing.
Hey, come on.
You know me.
Rock of Gibraltar, right?
Yeah.
You been taking
your Dilantin?
What, are you writing
a book, huh?
No, it's just--
I'm fine, okay?
You were on one
of your journeys
with that kid Mike
in Manhattan.
Antonio was telling me.
I wasn't with Mike.
What if I did go?
What if I went to Manhattan
or I went somewhere else
like, uh, I don't know?
Come on.
You're not
going anywhere, Dito.
Come here.
How are you, Dito, huh?
Since when are you here
at this time?
Put on the TV.
Give your old man
a break, huh?
Forget it.
Are you scared?
I would be.
If a guy wrote on my house
"I was dead",
he's already fucked you up.
I'd be having
a fuckin' heart attack.
They just write shit.
Locker room
disinfectant stuff, right?
Check this shit out.
"Do not inhale, breathe.
Avoid skin-eye contact.
Irritant.
Skin irritant.
Unsafe.
Eye irritant.
Skin irritant.
Unsafe.
Keep away
from all body parts."
Wanna try it?
What, do you drink it?
Sniff it.
Mike, I'm sorry
Antonio's a fuckin'
asshole, man.
He's not always like that.
It's just when he gets
around people and shit.
Fuck him.
You're always
fuckin' afraid of him.
Give me that shit, man.
No, I'm not afraid.
He's a dick.
Fuck him.
I'm scared, Mike.
It's just--
I'm sorry.
I don't even fuckin' know
what I'm saying when smoking.
What the fuck
are you sorry for, Mike?
If some guys were after me
like that, I would be
shitting myself.
California's probably
the best, right?
I always think
about that place.
Well, let's go, then.
What do you mean?
Let's just fucking go.
I saw this, uh,
TV commercial, right?
You can take like a,
a bus, right?
It's $39.
$39?
That's crazy.
Hey, is your fuckin' head
going like boom, boom, boom?
Like hard.
Laurie.
Laurie?
You're so stupid.
Uh?
Hey, stupid,
I'm not talking to you.
I'm still not gonna
talk to you.
Come on.
I'm not talking.
Why are you here?
Why are you even here?
'Cause I wanna be here.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Why are you still mad?
You forgot, right?
You let Giuseppe throw knives
at me and Diane.
You still mad
about that?
Like, I'm not even mad.
I just feel like the whole shit
was stupid, you know?
Hello?
Shit.
You're drunk.
No.
Oh, shit.
You're stoned.
Yeah, you are.
No, I'm not.
You are.
You know what I'm gonna do
if you let me in?
No.
What you gonna do?
I'm not even
gonna fuck you.
Wow! You're not
gonna even fuck me!
Not even if I let you in?
I'm just gonna lick
your pussy.
Oh, my God.
My mother's like right there.
She can hear you right now.
You know why?
No, why?
Why what?
What are you talking about?
I don't know--
I don't know why
you're gonna lick my pussy.
That's what you wanted me
to say.
Because, uhm,
I'm gonna lick your pussy
because me and Mike
we're going to California
with our band and shit.
I want you to come, you know,
because I love you.
Because the fuckin' Mets won.
What?
What did you say?
You said you love me.
What?
You said you love me, right?
I'm serious.
That shit means
a lot to me, you know.
I love you.
I don't why.
'Cause I love you.
'Cause--
I can't.
Stupid.
Hey, yo.
Hey, yo,
I stole us a Spalding
from Fishbein's.
I swear that fuckin' Charlie
his getting blind as he can be.
I can't wait to get
that motherfucker.
I would play.
I just gotta go back.
I gotta go
to the city right now.
What do you wanna go
to Manhattan for?
Monty wanted to play handball.
You okay?
What happened?
It was my fuckin' father.
You wanna go first
to the park?
No, I gotta fu--
I gotta go fuckin'
with the dogs.
Mike with the dogs?
Come on.
Hey!
Maybe you could see
if I can get a job there, man.
Tell your friend
I ain't gonna fuck
with him, right?
Maybe we can hang out later.
Look who's here.
Sorry.
I got lost
changing trains.
Take little Geronimo here.
You got to go
through the teeth over here.
Look at Young Geronimo.
Careful, motherfucker.
The teeth are lethal.
Take Bobo and Lulu too,
because Miss Levitt will have
a fuckin' heart attack.
You gotta go through here.
Merry-go-round.
Could they make it
a little more heat
in this city or what?
Sorry, he's blind.
Poor kid.
So this guy
has a Pomeranian.
Marilyn.
You gotta walk the thing
sometimes for like an hour
before it craps.
On 2nd Avenue.
Bobby, the owner, he can be
a real pain in the ass.
He'll check the dog's ass.
Make sure it just does it.
Okay?
Thank you, ma'am.
They're okay.
Those things always end up
with you going to hell.
So, remember he's like
an entertainment manager,
or like he owns a store
or something.
Fish and lizards.
But music, too.
Whatever.
I told him about you guys
and the music,
and that maybe
he should do something.
You never know, okay?
I gotta head downtown.
Mikey, you have the address.
You can walk from here.
And break the leg.
That's what they say
in the big time.
Cheerio, Frank.
Your mothers must be
really proud of you.
I could jump from one side
to the other like this.
Jesse Owens would've.
You're not a track star, man.
I'm sorry.
I hate to tell you this.
You're not making it.
What you think,
you cute Giuseppe?
I'm not cute.
I'm handsome.
Who the fuck
told you that?
Girls.
Go get my ball, man.
Go get my--
Go get my ball.
Hey, Bobby.
This is Dito.
Hey, there.
I'll bring him right back.
Thanks.
Let's go.
No, don't fuck with that.
Come on, man.
Touch it
with your finger.
With your finger.
What the fuck
are you doing, man?
I heard if you put both feet
on it at the same time,
nothing happens.
You like conduct
electricity and shit.
What are you Einstein?
You sound like an idiot.
You're worried about me,
Antonio, aren't you?
Am I fuckin' worried
about you?
The fuckin' train is coming.
I don't give a fuck about you.
Get my ball, man.
You don't give a shit?
Now how about
giving a shit?
The fuckin' train is coming.
You don't see it?
Tell me you're worried
about me.
I don't give a fuck about you.
If you wanna die, go ahead.
Go ahead.
You're not gonna tell me
you're worried about me?
What the fuck?
Come on, man.
Get the fuck up here.
What the fuck are you doing?
The train's coming
right at you.
You're my brother.
The fuckin' train.
It's right there.
You're gonna be retarded
and just sit down?
I don't give a fuck.
Get the fuck out already.
Get the fuck out!
Go!
I was calling.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
When I call you,
you always call me back.
I got worried.
This is messed up, huh?
It's fucked up.
It's just fucked up.
I'm getting out of here.
Me and Mike we're leaving.
We're going to California.
I know.
Remember you told me?
You wanted me to go with you.
Yeah.
What?
You don't want me
to go with you?
Is that what you're saying?
I want to talk
to Antonio.
I'm just going to talk.
Why can't you even look
at me right now?
You're not looking at me.
How do you mean?
How else can I look at you?
You said that
you loved me, right?
Did you mean that?
Laurie, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna talk to Antonio.
You better not.
You better talk to me right now.
You okay?
Don't worry about it.
What are you going to do?
It's fucked up.
He's, he's fucking--
He's stupid.
It's just fuckin'--
Now he's dead
and he's stupid.
You know Giuseppe.
He's fuckin',
he's an idiot.
I found out
where the fuckin'
Reaper guy is.
I found him for sure this time.
I know where they hang out.
Don't worry about that, either.
I'm gonna kill his ass.
I'm here for Giuseppe.
Antonio, you're here
for your brother.
That's your brother
in a box.
That's your brother.
Is that all you think about,
the Reaper guy?
It's your brother's funeral.
What the fuck do you mean,
"Is that all I ever
fuckin' think about?
What do you mean?
What do you mean by that?
What'd I say?
All I ever think about is you?
Is that what you're saying?
I think about you?
I'm asking you
a fuckin' question.
What did you mean by that?
I didn't mean
anything by it.
Get the fuck out!
I don't even fuckin' care
about you!
I don't fuckin' even care.
Do you hear me?
I don't give a fuck.
Antonio!
I'm sorry, Monty.
Fuck!
You alright?
Hey.
Do you know this used to be
a candy store here?
Can you believe it?
What does the Stop mean?
Do you see the hand?
Stop!
It means you don't cross
the street.
You stop.
Go.
Yo! Don't be making
no transactions
on my corner here, alright?
Yo.
Fuckin' Hector.
Little kids here, man.
I'm serious.
I'm serious, Hector.
Fuckin' television.
Yo, that works?
Hey, is that's flat screen?
Yo, I'm serious.
That works?
You used to be a swimmer?
Oh, you used to be
a swimmer, right?
Hey.
Who's that?
Shit.
This is Joey.
Look.
Joseph.
Mr. Joey.
Joey, like Giuseppe?
Like Joseph.
It's his father's name.
Joseph.
Mommy, who's that man?
He's gone now.
He wants to know
who you are.
I've known your mother
since she was, like,
she was this big.
She can't be this big,
you know.
Your mom said
you were coming into town.
Yeah, I'm gonna see
my father.
Yeah, Nerf told me,
you know, you'd be here
in your corner.
My corner.
Nerf.
Wow.
Laurie, you look beautiful.
You know, I'm in my bests.
I'm looking really good.
My best slippers.
You should see them actually.
Manolo's.
You're staying
at your mother's, right?
Nerf's.
Nerf's mother's.
Alright.
Yeah.
I'll be around, you know.
Maybe later I'll come back
or you wanna come down.
You wanna come down
and play.
It was really nice to see you.
I gotta make dinner now.
It's good to see you.
Alright.
See you, Mr. Joey.
Antonio.
Yo!
Yo, Antonio.
Yo, Dito,
what's up, man?
Come on.
I'm sorry.
What's up, Dito?
Where the fuck you been?
I know where he's been,
since he's all I have
to think about.
He's all I have
I'm fuckin' working.
What are you always
fuckin' pissed off for?
I'm not pissed off.
You know your father
had a seizure?
This guy don't even know
his fuckin' father
had a seizure.
He's acting like
there's nothing wrong.
You're in fuckin' Niggerville.
Nerf's dad is black.
What happened to my father?
My father's Dominican.
Nerf's fuckin' Nerf, man.
You're never around anymore.
Where the fuck were you?
Where the fuck are you?
Nowhere!
This fuckin' guy.
Come on, let's go.
I don't fuckin' know you
anymore!
Yo, tell me who the fuck--
Look, yo,
you don't think
I'd fuck you up?
Chill out, Antonio.
You have no idea
how fuckin' close you are.
Nerf, let's just fuckin' go.
Antonio!
Nerf.
Nerf!
What's up, motherfucker?
Think you can hide from me?
Think you can fuck
with my family?
with my family, nigger?
Don't fuck with me
'cause I know your family.
I know your father.
I know where you live.
Don't fuck with TSS!
Next time I'll kill you.
That's my word.
I know your family.
I know you live right here.
Don't ever fuck with me!
Hurry up.
You're scared.
Yo!
What the fuck, man?
Yo, yo, yo yo.
Just-- just fuckin' lay there
for a second.
Yo, come here.
Come here.
Look at me.
Oh, fuck.
He fucked up.
Don't be mad, okay?
No, no.
Nerf, get your mother's car.
Go get your mother's car
right now.
You're fucked up.
That fuckin'.
It's--
Oh, fuck!
Every day something's different
with you guys.
I don't know what it is.
Every day is something, huh?
Right, Antonio?
Every day is something.
Yeah.
So what happened this time?
A dog bite you?
Huh?
I told you I fell off
a park fence.
Oh, you fell off a fence?
Never mind about that, okay?
Just tell me what happened.
Hi.
It's 2:00 in the morning.
I just wanted to see
what happened.
Sorry.
What happened?
There, now you see.
Now go.
I said I just want to know
what happened.
The freaking graffiti guys.
You know, the Reaper.
Your fuckin' race.
They whacked him
with a bat.
It's not my race.
Monty?
What are you doing out there?
Uh, don't worry, Flori.
I'm talking to Dito
and Antonio, okay?
It's so late!
These guys, they knew
who you were, too.
The Reaper guy.
The bat man.
But don't worry about it.
We'll take care of it.
Just trust me.
Why do they care
who I am?
They care who you are.
These guys
are crazy, Mr. Montiel.
Daddy, me and Mike are planning
a trip to go to California
for a month.
Listen to Antonio, okay?
What do you mean
you wanna go somewhere?
You wanna go to China,
go to China Town.
You don't even listen
to anything.
I'm sorry.
I just feel you're not listening
to what he's saying.
Sorry, daddy.
I'm serious.
You said to me that
if I were to leave,
that you wouldn't talk
to me anymore.
And if I were to go,
would you not talk to me?
That's what you said
you were gonna do.
But you're not going
anywhere, Dito.
You're not going anywhere.
You stay right here at home
with us, okay?
Daddy, can you be
my fuckin' father
for a second?
I wanna go somewhere.
I wanna do something for once.
I can't be here anymore.
It's a nightmare here.
What's going on out there?
Flori, wait a minute.
Everything's gonna be alright.
Who do you think you are
talking to me like that?
He's your son.
Just mind your business.
I told you to mind
your business.
Alright.
You wanna go,
then go!
Is that what you wanna hear?
Then go.
Don't you ever talk to me
like that again.
Antonio is gonna make
everything right.
Right, Antonio?
He's gonna make it right. Yes!
He's gonna make it right!
He's gonna take care, okay?
Why don't you shut the fuck up?
Listen to him.
Why don't you leave my fuckin house?
Listen to me.
Antonio, you are going
to make it right?
You're gonna make it
right, right?
He's not going nowhere.
Get the fuck out of my house!
Get the fuck out of my house.
Hey, hey.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Get the fuck out.
I hate you!
What the hell
are you saying to me?
You hate your father?
Hey, fuck, relax!
Monty?
Hold his head!
Dito, where are you going?
What is happening?
You'll be alright.
Dito.
Hi.
Come here.
Look at you.
You're beautiful.
Momma, you do.
Monty?
Monty.
Look who's here.
Hey.
Look at you.
Long time no see.
Daddy.
Antonio and Nerf called.
Said you were sick.
Me?
Rock of Gibraltar, man.
You don't look so good.
He came all this way to tell me
I don't look so good, Flori?
No.
He's here to take you
to the hospital
because you're sick, right?
Well... thanks for coming.
You take care, okay?
Take care?
When I came
all the way here
to see you?
Dito, it's nice
to see you again.
You came and everything.
Now you take care.
I see what he's doing.
Nice.
I see what you're doing.
That's because
you're a very smart guy.
Well, I'm your son.
You know that, right?
You're my son?
Yeah, I'm your son.
Remember?
You're my son?
You're not my son.
I'm not gonna fight.
You want me to leave?
Big shot comes here.
Comes 15,
comes 3,000 miles.
From co--
Comes 3,000 miles
in 15 years.
You go back to California
like the rat you are.
You leave me,
your mother.
You don't see
your friend Antonio.
Monty.
Not once!
Once!
You can go.
You take care.
Used to be Antonio's house.
House of horrors.
The poor kid.
Look how nice
it is now.
It's nice, huh?
I wasn't upset
when he went to prison.
Not a bit.
That's where me
and you father are different.
You know, if you hooked
your father up
to a lie detector test
and asked if he was
the best father
whoever lived ever,
he'd pass with flying colors.
That's because he loved you
with everything he had.
Every last bit.
He loved you.
He loved coming up here
with you.
You know, people used to think
he was your grandfather.
He thought that was funny.
You know, one generation
can be funny, I guess.
But two?
We were too old
to have such a young boy.
We needed you probably more
than you needed us.
Or, you know.
Your father was so crazy
about you.
I never saw nothing like it.
You were more his buddy
than a son.
He couldn't wait for you
to come out and play.
I'm sorry, Ma.
You can't come back
with hatred for your father.
You can't.
How could you love him so much
in that book and not see him
for so long?
I know you have your reasons.
We all missed you here.
You're my son, too.
Look at you.
You're a man now.
It's good to see you again.
To say your name
to you.
I thought of this every day,
and now it's here.
Every day.
You asked your dad, right?
How can we afford California?
Frank.
Remember the commercial
you told me about?
You told me about that.
I saw it.
The $39-buses.
We get the money from Frank
and we can go.
Hey, Ronnie,
give her her shirt back.
I just wanna get
the fuck out of here.
I'm not gonna go without you.
And we're going, right?
Yeah.
I want my fuckin' shirt back.
Can you give her back
her frigging shirt?
I'm serious, Ronnie.
I'm serious.
Ronnie!
Give her the fuckin'
shirt back.
Why you do this every time?
Fuckin' little pervert.
Here.
I gave you your shirt.
Tell your friend
to talk to me.
Your friend has a mind
of her own.
Tell your mind
to talk to me.
My mind is not
gonna talk to you.
I don't wanna talk to you.
You don't think
I'm not gonna get
in there now?
You're not gonna get in.
You didn't think
I was gonna get in?
Huh?
I'm sorry, Laurie.
At my fuckin' house
I didn't mean to--
I didn't mean to.
You were so mean to me.
You were really mean to me.
I was pissed off.
I lost it, you know.
I fuckin'--
What is that?
Is that a bruise?
I did that to you?
Yeah.
Don't worry.
I bruise easily.
It's fine.
When I grabbed you?
Yo, Dito.
The Reaper's over there.
Let's go.
Get up out of the pool.
Antonio found the dude
that hit you with the bat.
He's waiting for you.
Come on!
You going over there
is so fuckin' stupid.
Let's go!
Dito, come on, man.
You don't need
that fuckin' asshole.
He is the fuckin' worst!
Where are you going?
You're so full of shit, man.
You wanna get out of here,
but you're running
after Antonio.
The guy's a fuckin' dick, Dito.
It's because of him
you're fucked up.
Fuckin' go then!
Go!
I'll be right back.
You're not coming back!
What's up, Dito?
The fuckin' spic
is right there, man.
Nerf told you, right?
Yeah.
That's our motherfucker
right there.
He's in there playing Asteroids.
Yo, get down.
Get down.
Yeah, let him go.
Let him go.
He'll be there
all alone.
I'm gonna show this fucker
what's up.
Frank?
Oh, shit.
What's up?
Is it Saturday?
It ain't Saturday, Frank.
Sit down.
Frank, we need our money.
Remember I was telling you--
You guys know
this shit's no good.
Huh?
You like this song?
You can hear it, right?
Listen, listen, listen.
Oh, fuck!
Did you hear that?
It's like--
Oh, I love it.
Right?
And these things
like fuckin' ultrasonic.
They're like
walkie talkie shit.
But in your head.
Like, it sounds there
but it's in here, too.
You know what I mean?
It sounds there
but it's in here, too.
You know what I mean?
Walkie talkie shit,
I'm telling ya.
Out there, in here.
It's amazing.
Frank, you ain't paid us
for three weeks.
Damn.
This shit is impossible!
You hear that?
Come on, Frank.
We know the fuckin' money's
in the fridge.
Fucking great song.
I love this song.
Frank, enough shit already.
The fuckin' money's
in the fridge.
Either you get it for us
or we're gonna take it.
What are you gonna do?
Wait.
Mikey, you came here
to rob me?
Frank, we're friends, man.
I didn't come
to rob you.
Frank, we didn't come here
We just want
to get paid, you know.
You haven't paid us
for three fuckin' weeks.
Three weeks?
I haven't paid you
in three weeks?
Okay.
I mean, it's cool.
It's cool.
I owe you money.
I mean, you know,
I got a gun in here too,
you know.
And if you rob me,
you know,
I would've had
to have used it.
But I wouldn't.
I would never.
I'm sorry.
How much do I owe you?
Three hundred for both.
Three hundred.
You know what?
Take it all, Mike.
Take it all.
It's only $300, Frank.
All we want is what we're owed.
We're not asking--
Like Job.
Remember from the Bible?
Like him.
You're so good, Mikey.
You're so good.
But here is no good anymore.
Here is no good.
You're always talking
about the music,
or California.
Here's no good anymore, okay?
Here's no good anymore.
Take it!
Just take the money, please.
Take the money.
It's time to go.
Listen to Dito!
He knows when it's time to go!
It's time to go.
Mikey... it's time to go.
Take it.
Take it all.
It's time to go.
Yeah, yeah.
That's me.
Yeah.
No conscience.
These motherfuckers.
Do what they want.
Do exactly what they want.
No conscience.
These motherfuckers.
You show them what's up.
What's right.
You go, boy.
You go.
Pow!
I was afraid maybe
you drowned in here
or something.
Listen, Dito.
Uhm, you know,
this thing with Antonio,
you know,
you know, don't worry.
You're kids.
I spoke to the guy,
the guy with the suit.
He said everything
is gonna be okay.
It's gonna be good.
He's gonna take care of it.
I'm not worried
about it.
Okay?
I'm sorry I ran away
when you had the seizure, dad.
Don't worry.
Monday, instead
of going to school,
you take your ID card.
You go to Riker's Island,
you see Antonio.
Take your friend Mike.
He's a good kid.
Daddy, I wanted
to tell you that--
I know.
I just want you
to understand everything.
I like Antonio.
Yeah.
Why don't you ever listen
to anything I ever say?
I'm listening to you.
Listen to me.
It's gonna be okay.
Alright?
Don't fuckin' touch me.
Listen to me.
Get the fuck off me!
Don't touch me.
Don't fuckin' touch me.
Don't you talk
to me like that!
Don't you raise
your voice to me!
Your my son.
Come on.
Dito.
Get the fuck off me!
What's the matter with you?
It's gonna be alright.
Do you hear what I'm saying?
It's gonna be okay.
It will be okay.
My friend Mike just died, dad.
He just got fuckin' shot.
You don't know what's happening.
What are you talking about?
What happened?
My friend Mike is dead.
Come here.
Don't fuckin' touch me!
Please, get the fuck off me!
What is the matter
with you?
You don't raise your hands
to your father!
to your father.
I love you.
I'm asking you
not to fuckin' touch me!
It's okay.
Don't you fuckin' do it!
Don't you raise your hands
to me again!
I'm your father.
You're not supposed
to hate your father.
When are you my father?
You know, I, uh,
I waited around for a year
at my window when you left.
I bought California maps.
Any time I heard
anything about it,
I would think of you.
Embarrassing.
Dumb little girl.
Listen, I'm not heartbroken
about it, alright?
I'm over that shit.
I was just a dumb girl.
We were fuckin' kids.
Whatever.
But you need to take
your father to the hospital.
I mean, your mother--
I'm serious.
I got a little boy.
He's a good kid.
And he's gonna look after me
when we're older.
So you look after your mother.
You take care of your father.
You take care of your mother.
It's real simple.
'Cause she's a good woman.
It's not a fuckin' stretch.
I know what you're saying.
Alright?
Thanks for coming.
I should go.
Wow.
Monty's son.
You know what?
You're Flori's son as well.
And that's why
you're all fucked up.
Yeah, I'm all fucked up.
You think you're going?
You're gonna fuckin' leave?
Go ahead, fuckin' go.
You're not gonna go.
You didn't fuckin' come
all the way over
so you could leave again.
You don't know.
You don't know
what it was like
in the house, okay?
Listen.
You want it straight?
'Cause I'm the only one
who's gonna tell you
for some fuckin' reason.
You killed him.
You killed your father
when you left.
Are you hearing me?
You fuckin' killed him.
You left a trail of blood
when you left.
So forget me.
Forget all this shit.
Forget it, alright?
You killed your mother
and you killed your father.
And for the past
fuckin' 20 years
he's been dying,
just waiting for you
to come home.
Say daddy, you're fucked up.
I hate your guts.
Whatever you need to get out
of your angsty little
fuckin' head.
Touch my head
one more fuckin' time
and I'm gonna go nuts.
Go ahead.
Go fuckin' nuts.
Let it out!
Stop fuckin' running away.
You think you're a man?
That's just a fuckin' tail
between your legs.
Go home
and take care
of your mother.
Go home
and take care
of your father.
That's gonna make you
a fuckin' man.
That's all you've got left.
'Cause if you don't do
that shit, it's too fuckin' late.
Okay, bye.
Yeah.
You're going
to hospital.
Where's Ma?
Ma?
Where is she?
Why don't you get out?
Get out of the house.
Did you love me?
Ever?
I said go.
Dad, did you love me
or not?
Daddy, I gotta know.
Lie to me and tell me you did.
Let me feel like
the piece of shit I am.
Did you love me
or not?
Answer me!
A father always--
Not a father!
You!
Of course I did.
I told you I loved you
the last time I saw you.
I love you, Dito.
Alright?
You're my son.
I'm very proud of you.
Now, Antonio,
he doesn't have anybody
to tell him something
like this.
Listen, Monday
you don't have
to go to school.
Monday you take your ID.
You go to Riker's.
You see Antonio.
Take your friend Mike with you.
I like that kid.
You take the bus there
with your friend.
You go see Antonio.
Yeah, man.
Have fun.
You're just kids, Dito.
Just kids.
But your friend Antonio,
he needs you now.
'Cause he don't have anybody
to tell him what I just told you.
Come here.
Okay, enough.
Thank you for coming.
I know I'm in the middle
of no place, right?
No, no.
I-- I should've come,
you know, a long time go.
It's alright.
Damn, Dito.
I got so much
I wanna say to you.
I just don't know
what to say.
I don't know what I was
expecting to happen.
Antonio exists.
Crazy, huh?
In the end,
just like I said,
I left everything
and everyone,
but no one.
No one
has ever left me.
Poor Antonio.
He's in for life.
Maybe he'll get out.
Yeah, but he's got
a bad temper.
With a bad temper
you can't be out of here.
He's a good guy, though.
Oh, yeah.
I like him.
But good guys
don't get out of here.
They won't change.
Not to worry, you know.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org