Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Hank: when i
was still just a kid,
I remember
my father telling me
What he thought that it took
for a man to be happy.
Tommy, finally.
Come on, man.
New year's
is tonight.
I'm sorry
i'm late.
Don't worry.
I covered for you.
Thanks,
hank.
What, did you
stay out
Till they hung
the last dog?
Yeah. Ha!
Hank: simple things,
really...
A wife he loves,
A decent job,
Friends and neighbors
who like and respect him.
And for a while there,
Without hardly
even realizing it,
I had all that.
I was a happy man.
Hey, tom.
Remember we talked about
me getting off early today?
Man: hey, hank!
Hey, happy new year,
schmitt!
Hey, linda,
happy new year.
Happy new year.
Hey, where you
guys going?
Sledding! Sledding!
Hey, can i come?
No! No!
Ohh...please!
Ohh!
Hey, carl.
Hey, happy
new year, hank.
You gotta start charging
people for that.
Ha ha ha!
Yeah, it'd pay better
than the county does.
[Whistling
o tannenbaum]
Honey, it's me.
How you feelin'
today?
Hey. Good.
Oh, my gosh.
He was sure kickin'
a lot today.
[Car horn honking
insistently]
Uh-Oh...
[honking]
Looks like it's gonna be
a long afternoon for you.
He brought lou along.
Oh, great.
Yeah. I'll just be
lyin' here, relaxing.
Oh...
ha ha ha!
[Spirit in the sky
playing on radio]
Hey, jacob!
Ha ha ha!
What's he
doing here?
He needed
a ride home.
Little out of
the way, isn't it?
We can drop him off
when we're done.
You know? It's
no big deal, hank.
What's the big deal,
hank?
Hey, you know, you need
to shovel this shit
Off of your, uh...
whatchacallit deal there.
I'll pay you
a quarter to do it.
Huh!
I could use it.
Ha ha!
Look at lou.
Here, hold this,
will you?
Wanna put it
back there?
No, no,
it's gonna wilt.
Hank,
say hi to--
You didn't say hi
to mary beth.
Oh, yeah.
Hi, mary beth.
He said hi,
mary beth.
Hank said hi.
Hi, lou.
Come here.
Somebody else
was here.
Oh, i brought those.
When?
Well...what the hell
do you think, hank?
This is the only day
we can come here?
What the hell's
wrong with you?
Hey, jacob!
Look!
I'm writing
my name!
Hang on a second!
Let me get mrs. Johnson
out here!
I'll help you out.
[Chuckling]
[Panicked clucking]
Lou: you know what
the guy says?
Jacob: says it's
the crock pot--
Or, uh, crock box?
No, no.
Pay attention now--
Oh, no, that's
the preacher, see?
This is the cowboy.
Yeah.
He says "moo."
No, no. It's the guy
standing by the road.
He says, "why, officer,
it's just a pine  apple."
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha!
You get it?
Yeah.
Well, mr. Accountant
doesn't get it.
Ha ha ha ha...
Look out!
Shit!
You ok, baby?
Go on, get out!
[Arf arf]
Look at that,
man!
My truck.
Come on, get out.
Mary beth!
She's gonna
come back.
Hey, what
are you doing?
It's a nature preserve.
You know that.
So what?
So you can't
hunt here.
Come on, put
the gun back.
But it--But it
messed up my truck.
So what?
Come on.
Hey, hey, hank...
It's not like
we're huntin' here.
Uh-Uh. We're
collectin' the dead.
That's right.
We're collecting
the dead.
[Indistinct talking]
[Laughter]
Just look
at him...
He runs like
my wife.
Hey, come on,
wait up!
Come on, i'm not dressed
for this shit!
[Indistinct talking
and laughter]
Mary beth!
Jesus! Look at
all them birds.
Those things are always
waitin' on something to die
So they can eat it,
right?
What a weird job.
Wish we had
something to drink.
Always
be prepared.
Oh, that's
a good idea.
Let's all start
drinking now.
See there?
See how he is?
Wonk! Dit-Dit...
like that guy, huh?
Remember?
Wonk! Dit-Dit.
Uh-Huh.
You want some?
I'm not thirsty.
What, you
don't drink
Till after 5:00?
After 5:00,
heh heh.
Or maybe you just
don't wanna share.
You're afraid you'll
catch something
From us, huh?
[Sotto]
yeah.
Hey, hank.
Hey! Come on,
what are you doing?
Quit jackin' around.
Now, you see...
That's what
you might call
An insinuating
throw. Remember?
You said that to me
last time i saw you.
Coulda just said
"hint," but no.
You had
to put on airs,
Show us all them
fancy words you know.
What, do you sit around,
you think about this stuff?
When was that,
2 months ago?
Kiss my ass.
[Clunk]
What the hell
is it?
Jesus christ.
Shit,
that's a airplane.
Jacob:
you know what,
It's probably one of
those drunk doctors.
They're always crashing
their plane, you know?
Lou: yeah, it must've
come down right there.
See all them
broken trees, jake?
It's too dark.
I can't see.
Scrape some of that snow
off the windshield.
Lou:...can't see
a damn thing.
Door's stuck.
Jacob: probably
a singer or something.
Lou: still can't see
nothin' here.
Still can't see
anything.
Can't see
a damn thing.
I see the pilot!
What's he
talking about?
Said somebody's
in there.
Are you ok?
Hey. Hey, buddy...
Aah! Whoaaa...
Ah! Aah! Aah!
Hey, get--Get off!
[Crows squawking]
Lou: what the hell
is going on..?
Aah! Ohh!
Oh, god!
Shit!
Hey, lemme
outta here.
Good grief, hank.
Let me get this
off of him. Here...
Hank, did you--
Did you--
Did you see--Did you
see all them birds?
Did i see the birds?
Come on, help me
get outta here.
Hank, put that
on your eye.
Thanks.
You tore your coat,
you know.
Oh, my god...
Oh, my god!
Look at this!
Shit!
Oh, my god!
How much you think
is in here?
God almighty!
These are $100 bills!
The whole bag's
full of 'em!
Is this--Is it
ha ha! Real money, lou?
Oh, hell, yes,
it's real.
Don't be stupid.
Why would somebody
be flying around
With this kind
of cash?
You know what? I bet
it's drug money.
That's probably
i bet you're what it is. Right.
This guy's
a dope dealer
Because that's
what they do.
They fly around in
these little planes.
I guaran-Damn- Tee you.
This is dirty money.
That's right.
I saw it
on 20/20.
"Dirty money"?
What do you mean?
Are you telling me
it's counterfeit?
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
No, this
is real.
Whatever it is,
it's a police matter now.
What do you think
we should do?
Somebody should
stay here,
Somebody should go
after the cops?
How you wanna
what? Work it?
Let's think
this through.
What?
Hold on!
What if we didn't
turn it in?
You wanna keep it?
Ha ha ha!
He wants to keep it.
Well,
that's a hot one.
Why wouldn't we?
Yeah.
Because we'd go
to prison.  Why?
Why? Because
it's stealing.
Stealing.
Stealing from who?
From him? Hell,
he won't mind.
Heh heh...
Oh, 'cause he's
dead, right? Ha ha ha!
Ha ha! That's
pretty funny--
He's dead.
He won't mind.
I say we take this bag
back to the truck,
And we pretend like
we were never here.
Fuck yeah.
Why not?
Why not? Because
we'd get caught.
Aw, hell! I'll
tell you what.
Stay the hell
out of it then.
You know, we
don't need you.
It'd just be more
money for us.
Hey, i don't wanna stump you
another fancy word, lou,
But does the term "accomplice"
mean anything to you?
Come on. That's stupid.
But, hank, why
would we get caught?
Because it's a lot
of money.
Somebody's bound
to be looking for it.
When they find
that plane
And the money's
not in it,
They'll come
bullshit! Looking for us. Bullshit!
This is
dirty money!
And as far as that
guy's concerned,
The cops don't even
know he exists.
Nobody knows
about this...
But us.
See there?
Nobody knows
but us.
It's like we came
out here on a hike,
And found lost treasure.
Right?
It's the american dream
in a goddamn gym bag.
He--He just wants
to walk away from it.
You work for
the american dream.
You don't steal it.
Then this is
even better.
If this guy's
a dope dealer,
Then--Like we're
talkin' about--
Then that means we're
like robin hood.
Oh, yeah, and i'll
tell you what.
You got a beautiful
wife at home.
You're about
to have a baby.
I know you ain't
pullin' down that much
At the feed mill.
Wouldn't you love to
have a piece of this?
Hell, yes, i would,
but we can't just take it.
Hey, what if
there's a reward?
Maybe there's a reward,
and they'll give--
Maybe there's not!
How about this.
I tell you what.
I'll bet you
$10,000--
Just one of
these packets--
That when they
find this plane,
There's no mention
of this money.
Hank, why--
Why turn it in
Until we know
whether or not
Somebody's
lookin' for it?
That's right.
If you scratch,
then don't--Don't itch.
If you--If it's--
If it's broken,
don't fix it. Right?
Or if you--If--If--
If the--If--If--If--
And i know
what you mean.
[Caw caw]
Suppose i was
the one to keep it?
For how long?
Just till spring,
till they find the plane.
Then what?
Then, if you're right and
nobody mentions the money,
We split it up,
and we all leave town.
Why should you
get to hold it?
That's the only way
i'll do it.
Otherwise we can just
turn it in right now.
So, what, you mean--
You--You--
You don't trust us?
Is that what you mean?
That's a lot of money.
I guess i don't.
Look, no--No promises.
If somebody comes searching
For the money,
i'll burn it.
I'll burn it,
listen, and that's it. Hank...
No. That's the only way
i'll do this!
Look, we gotta be
agreed on this.
That's the deal.
I hold onto it, we wait
till they find the plane.
If nobody mentions it,
We split it up,
and we move away.
Ok?
I'm in.
We count it
first.
That's probably
a good idea.
I mean, you know...
Heh heh heh...
Heh heh...
heh heh...
This is nuts.
Oh, my god...
Hey, what you gonna
buy, jakey boy?
I'm gonna buy me
a truck.
No. Fuck that.
Get something
classy.
Trans-Am.
Oh, yeah, in my wildest
fuckin' dreams, a trans-Am.
You could buy a fleet
of trans-Ams.
Mary beth!
Where the hell
have you been?
Where you
been, huh?
There's shoes
for baby, ha ha!
Lou:...4,350,000,
4,360,000...
4,370,000...
4,380,000...
4,390,000...
$4,400,000!
Isn't that great?
Listen to that.
Look at that shit, man.
Look how square it is.
That is cool, huh?
How much is that
apiece?
About a million
and a...
A million
and what? Shh!
A million and
a half? What?
Shh! You
hear that?
Uh-Uh.
Oh, shit.
Get in the truck.
I'll handle this.
Shit.
Go on!
Hank: let's go!
Come on, cover up
the money!
Jake, get
in the truck!
Dummy up.
Let's go!
Come on!
Hey, carl.
Engine trouble,
hank?
Oh, i wish.
Dog trouble.
Jacob's mutt chased
a fox into the woods.
She tree it?
We thought so, but just
when we went after it,
She came running back.
Ah.
What'd you do
to your head there?
Oh. God, uh...
Heh. Ran into
a tree branch.
Your brother
still out of work?
Yeah.
Lou?
Yeah, him, too.
That's a shame,
ain't it?
Well, we probably better
be heading back--
Hey, hello, jacob!
Hey, carl,
how you doin'?
Good, good.
I was beginning
to think
You were trying
to avoid me.
I'm sorry?
Well, you sittin'
over there in that truck.
I thought you was
trying to avoid me.
No. Just sittin'
in the truck.
It's a little cold
out here, you know.
Just keepin' warm.
Well, we probably
better be--
Did you tell him
about the plane?
It sou-Sounded
like a plane.
What plane?
What, you heard
a plane?
Uh...i don't know
what he heard.
You know he's always
hearing shit.
Maybe you better
tell me, jacob.
No, that's ok.
We're gonna
get on home.
All right.
Come on, man.
It's new year's!
Let's get outta here.
Jacob:
call me, carl.
Happy new year.
Sure you don't
need any help?
No, we're all set.
Thanks.
All right.
Goddamn it!
I've seen you do some
pretty stupid things, jacob,
But that pretty much
takes the cake!
It was my idea.
Oh, well, that's
brilliant, lou.
Now when they find
the plane,
And they realize
the money's gone,
They'll know right off
who took it.
Well, that's--
That's what's cool
about it, though.
I mean, we wouldn't
tell somebody
If we were the ones
that did it.
It's not like he said
That you actually saw
a plane going down.
Just you thought you
might've heard one
With engine trouble.
You want me to
burn the money?!
I am not going
to prison over this!
If it looks like there's
even the slightest chance
Of us getting caught,
I swear to god,
it's all gonna vanish!
You understand?
"It was a pine apple."
Hee hee hee hee hee...
[Groaning] oh, god...
this is gonna be fun.
Woman: where the hell
have you been?!
You come when
i'm always finished.
I'm finished,
you asshole!
Hey, nancy!
Don't--
Don't hit--
Don't hit
mary beth.
[Low] remember,
nobody knows about this.
That includes nancy.
She'll have to find out
about it sooner or later.
She'll wonder where all
the money's coming from.
2 hours late!
Ow! Stop it!
Tell her when we decide
it's safe to keep it,
But not before then.
Then the same goes
for sarah.
Of course.
[Thunk]
Damn it!
Nancy: come on!
You promised to
shovel the walk,
You lazy son
of a bitch!
Calm down, baby.
I got a good reason
for being late. What?
See you, lou!
[Indistinct arguing]
You know, i bet
he's telling her.
That guy can't
keep a secret.
Hey, honey.
Hey.
Where you been?
I was starting to get
worried about you.
Sorry i'm late.
Oh, that's all right.
Hey.
What happened to your head?
It's ok. It's
just a scratch.
It's all bloody.
Can i ask you something?
Yeah, sure.
What if you were
walking in the woods--
It's not deep.
And you found
a bag full of money,
Let's say $4 million...
Would you keep it?
Of course not.
Here, hold that.
How come?
Well, for starters,
it'd be stealing.
We were talking about
lost money here,
Nobody's looking for it.
$4 million
of lost money...
Yeah.
That nobody's
yeah. Looking for?
Well, so then
whose money is it?
Yours.
Oh.
Ooh.
It's my money?
But whose money
was it before?
A bank robber's.
So then it's
the bank's money.
All right, it's, uh,
A drug dealer's.
It was--
Hank.
I mean, this is
really silly.
Obviously you want me to say
something in particular.
I don't know what it is,
But you want me
to agree with you
Or say that you're right
or something.
But i wouldn't take it.
That's just me. I wouldn't.
It's real.
If we keep it,
we never have to worry
About money again.
But we don't have to worry
about money now, hank.
You've got a good job.
We don't need it.
Yeah, but nobody gets
hurt by us keeping it.
I mean, that's
what makes it a crime,
Doesn't it?
Somebody getting hurt?
What makes it
a crime
Is that it's
against the law.
It doesn't matter if
somebody gets hurt
Or if they don't.
If you get caught,
you go to jail.
Nobody's
gonna get caught.
The money's the only evidence
That we've done anything wrong.
We sit on it,
we see what happens.
If somebody comes
searching for it,
Then we just burn it
and that will be that.
There's no risk.
We'll always be
in control.
What about
jacob and lou?
As long as we're
handling the money
They have to let us
call the shots.
It seems...crazy
Just to give it up.
I mean, before we know if
anybody's searching for it.
Tv: 10, 9, 8, 7, 6,
This is it.
It ain't champagne,
But happy new year.
You have to go back and
return some of the money.
What?
A lot. Like 500,000.
You see, that way
when they find the plane
They'll assume nobody's
been there yet.
It'll put us beyond
suspicion.
No one would walk away
from that much money--
Wait a second.
We're gonna keep
the rest?
You'll have to go
in the morning
So when it storms later
it'll cover your tracks.
You can't tell jacob
though.
What, do you think he'd
go back and take it?
It's--It's just
being careful.
That's what we have
to be from now on.
We have to be careful.
We have to be thinking ahead
all the time.
Ok. Ok.
Ok.
[Knocking]
Jacob.
[Knocking on door]
Jacob, come on,
open up.
Oh.
Hey, i screwed up,
i moved the pilot.
Come on, we gotta go put
him back like he was.
Come on,
i need a lookout.
If somebody comes by,
You pretend you're
changing the tire.
You know,
that's not gonna work.
What do you mean
it's not gonna work?
Nobody's gonna believe
that. It's not flat.
You're kinda crafty.
I observe things.
Observe and learn,
my friend.
Observe and learn.
[Air hisses]
That's cool.
[Caw]
Jacob, what happened,
she die on you?
No, we had a flat.
We had a flat tire.
I fixed it. See? The
new one's on there now.
I took the other one,
the bad one,
And put it in the trunk.
It's back there now,
flat as a pancake.
But it's cool now.
Everything's all right.
You see that god damned fox
come by here about 5 minutes ago
Heading right on down
to the woods?
No, i didn't see a fox.
I didn't see any fox.
Well, if you'd been
standing where i'm sitting
He'd have bit you
on the ass.
[Men arguing]
Jacob: why don't
you stay here?
Hey, hank.
Don't do anything
stupid.
Don't do it.
No. Don't do it.
Jacob!
Oh.
Oh, god...
jesus, jacob,
What the fuck?!
I--I--I--I hit--
I hit the farmer.
He was tracking
a fox. I--I-- Dwight.
He was gonna go right
by the plane.
I had to do something.
I was just trying to
help us out.
Just listen--Listen
to his--To his heart
Or something like that.
Come on, man, listen.
You gotta do it--You--
He's--He's gonna be ok.
Oh, god, jacob,
i think you killed him.
I'm pretty sure
he's gonna be ok.
What else was i gonna do?
Oh, god. He's dead.
Oh, hank,
that's not right.
No, we could probably--
We could probably do--
We can probably do
that cpr deal.
And you know,
you could do that, uh,
Cardiac arrest thing,
couldn't you?
We could do something.
God damn it!
Jacob, what
the hell you doing?
God damn it!
Stop!
Stop it!
Come on!
I'm working cpr.
God damn it,
stop it!
Come on! Come on!
Be still.
Let me think.
Ok, we can't panic.
Have any cars gone by?
Uh, cars?
Cars, cars,
come on, think.
While i was in the woods,
you see any cars go by?
Why, hank?
[Breathing heavily]
Oh, god. Oh.
All right.
We gotta make this look
like it was an accident.
Come on.
Come on. An accident?
Grab his legs.
Wait, wait, wait.
We can't--
Why?
We can't do that.
Come on.
What do you mean
we can't do it?
Because we're gonna
make tracks
And they're gonna see
them and follow 'em. Ok.
It's gonna be like
a crime scene or something.
We're gonna drive the
car back to the bridge.
I'll put him
on the snowmobile
And take him
through the park.
You gotta get there
ahead of me.
So whatever you do, i
don't want you to stop.
I want you to just drive
on by then circle back.
I don't want people to
see you sitting there.
Circle back?
That's right.
Come on,
come on now.
They're not gonna
take me away, are they?
You gotta promise me--
Nobody's gonna take
you away, i promise.
But we gotta hurry.
It's gonna be ok,
right, hank?
Come on. We gotta go.
You gonna be there,
right?
I'm gonna be there.
Now just go.
Go.
[Engine starts]
[Moaning]
Dwight?
Dwight.
Your brother.
He hit me.
You call the police.
Get the police.
Jacob, what
are you doing?
Come on before
anybody sees.
I'm not gonna
what? Do this.
Well, it's
just stupid.
I mean, if--
See, if we cover it up
It's just gonna be
worse anyhow.
So, you know,
i'm--I'm just--
Get in the car.
I'm just gonna go and
pull him out, you know?
We're just gonna tell
everybody the truth.
Just gonna tell 'em
about the money
And everything and just
say that i--That i--
You're gonna
leave tracks.
Wait a minute.
This is
my decision.
Mine.
Not yours.
You didn't kill him.
We both did.
What are you
talking about, hank?
He was alive when you left.
I smothered him.
I guess that makes it
my decision.
It's gonna be ok.
I mean, it looked real.
And even if--I mean,
let's say it didn't
Look like an accident.
Whatever. I mean...
Why would anyone
think of us?
Your tracks lead
right to the plane.
But it's gonna snow.
Any minute now, it's
gonna start snowing.
Was there any blood?
Blood?
Jacob hit him. Was
there blood anywhere?
Did he get blood
on anything?
Was there blood
on the road or--Or--
I don't remember.
Did you look?
I looked,
But i--I just don't--
It was all hap--
Honey, it's gonna snow.
It's gonna snow
And everything's gonna
be covered up.
All the tracks--
Shh.
Tv:  he was apparently
trying to cross
Along this bank of snow
When his snowmobile
slipped over the edge
Throwing him into the icy
waters of anders creek.
Wright county deputies
recovered the body
Shortly before
4:00 this afternoon.
A tragic beginning
to this new year
For one local family.
Back to you, paul.
Thanks, tracy.
I wish you hadn't
told jacob.
I wish he still thought
that he did it.
Does it scare you?
Yeah, it scares me.
What if he tells somebody?
I mean, what i did.
What you did?
Well, i know that
you only did it
Because you felt trapped.
That you couldn't
find any other way.
Would you have done
the same thing?
I mean, if you'd been
there instead of me?
I--I--I just need to
know if it's possible.
Oh, honey.
You listening to me,
hank?
Every monday i come down
here, buy 2 bags of feed
Regular as clock work.
2 bags of wheat
4 times a month.
That's 8 bags i'm supposed
to be billed for.
I don't know how else
to get through to you.
December started
on a monday, mr. Schmitt.
So there were 5 mondays
in the month.
So you came in here 5--
Are you telling me there
were 5 weeks last month?
No, sir, i'm telling you
there were 5 mondays.
[Telephone ringing]
Excuse me.
I got it.
Yeah.
Jacob: hey, hank,
it's me.
Hang on a second.
Listen, check that
calendar over there
If you don't believe me,
sir.
I need to talk to you.
Well, i'm a little busy
right now, jacob.
What is it?
Ok, listen, can you
meet me at the farm?
What farm?
Our farm.
Look, uh,
what is it?
On your lunch break.
12:30, ok?
Hey, are we straight
on this, mr. Schmitt?
Thanks for coming in.
Look, i can't drive
out there right--
Jacob?
Hey, what are you
doing here?
Look out!
Ha ha ha ha ha.
What the hell'd you
drag me out here for?
Listen to this.
I'm gonna buy it back.
I'm gonna fix it up.
I'm gonna rebuild it
Just like it was
before mom and dad died.
Whoa, whoa. Come on, wait, wait.
We've been through all this.
We've been over this.
Once we split up the money,
we've gotta leave.
We have to go.
What do you--What do
you want me to do,
Just like that, just
drive off by myself?
Well, i mean,
suppose you stay.
Where are you gonna tell
people you got the money?
Oh, that's easy.
We just tell people
that sarah
Inherited some money.
It's easy.
Nobody around here knows
anything about her family.
You guys coulda just
bought the farm, you know,
And then left me to run it.
It's not gonna work.
I thought this was
gonna make you happy.
Jacob...
Farming? Come on.
You don't just buy a farm.
You gotta--You gotta work it.
You gotta know
about machinery and seed.
I know that.
No, you don't.
Fertilizers, pesticides,
herbicides,
Drainage, irrigation,
the weather?
Come on, you don't know
about any of that stuff.
You're gonna end up
just like dad.
Why do you think he
ended up like that?
I'll tell you how he
ended up like that.
He had 2 mortgages riding
on the place.
He couldn't make the payments.
Where do you think
the money went?
He was a bad businessman.
Where do you think
the money went?
No, you think he spent
it all on the farm?
I'll tell you exactly
where the money went.
4 years of college, bud.
Yeah, didn't you ever think
about how he paid for that?
Didn't that ever
occur to you?
No, my tuition was--
Listen, i'm supposed
to get the farm!
What do i get?!
I'm supposed
to get the farm.
You got--You got
the whole world. You can...
I don't wanna hear that.
You can go anywhere
you want.
This is what i want.
This is--This is where
i wanna be.
It's my home, hank.
Shit.
Hey, honey.
What?
I wanna show you
something.
What is it?
I got this.
I had it sent over
from the other branch.
Look. Here it is.
"Heiress's body
id'd by feds."
$4.4 million ransom.
You see? This person
nobody knows
Has just disappeared
right into thin air.
Do you recognize one
of them from the plane?
I can't tell.
His face was...
What?
This changes it.
Why is that?
We can't say it isn't
stealing anymore.
Well, hank, it's
always been stealing.
We just didn't know who
we were stealing from.
We thought it was drug money.
We thought it was money
that we could find--
No, you thought that.
This is good.
I'm glad--
It's good?
Yes, it's good we know
where it's from,
Because i was starting
to get worried.
I thought that it might
be counterfeit or marked.
It might still be marked.
No, it says right here.
Look. Denomination
in unmarked bills.
Unmarked.
You see?
You're just being
paranoid, hank.
It's over. It's good.
Man: sarah?
Would you
come here, please?
Sure. Ok. Just a second.
I'll see you tonight.
[Banging]
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Jesus.
Hey, come on, hank.
Open up.
What the hell
are you doing?
Hey, mr. Accountant.
Well, i've come to make
a tiny withdrawal.
Go home. Turn around
and go home right now.
Oh, come on, it's
freezing out here, hank.
Shh! Keep it down.
Invite me in.
All right,
just for a second.
I don't have time
for this shit.
I gotta get up
and go to work.
I want my share.
What?
I do. I want my share.
I don't have the money here,
And even if i did,
i wouldn't give you any.
Oh, come on, now.
Look, just because
you have it
Doesn't mean it's yours.
Part of that is my money.
Part of it might be
your money...
If we decide to keep it.
The plan was to sit
on the money
Till we decide that
it's safe to keep it.
Why are you coming over here
with this shit?
All right, look.
I'll tell you what.
Just give me
one packet, ok?
Just one packet.
And i'll come back
later for the rest.
Ask me again, and i'll go
burn it tomorrow morning.
Is that clear?
Bluff.
What?
It's a bluff.
B-L-U-F-F.
Oh, then why don't you
call it then
And just see what happens?
Yeah.
All right. Ok.
See, jacob told me
A little secret,
mister accountant.
I know what happened
to dwight stephanson.
You drank too much.
I want one
of those packets.
Well, i told you,
i don't have the money here,
And i hid it away
from the house.
Mm-Hmm. Well,
you know what?
It'd be a shame
if somebody
Was to drop a note
to carl jenkins
Saying there
might just be
A little something
suspicious about
Dwight stephanson's
accident.
He just drove off
that bridge?
Do you believe that?
Do you?!
Come on. Jesus, lou.
Remember, you're a thief, too.
We're all in this together.
If one of us goes to jail,
we all do.
Oh, god.
I need my share, hank.
I do.
I'm broke...
And i owe people money.
Christ, lou,
i mean wh-Wh...
I need some
help here, man.
Ok, just wait here.
Here, here.
$40?
That's all i got.
Maybe i can go to the bank
And get you a loan out
of our savings.
Look, look, look.
The money's a day's drive
from here.
Even if i wanted go get it,
i can't go get it,
Not till sarah
has the baby.
A day's drive?!
Yeah, that's right.
I put it in a storage locker
above the interstate.
What the hell is it
doing in a storage--
Shh! It's safe.
Don't worry, all right?
I didn't want it near us
In case we come under
any suspicion.
How the hell's
that gonna happen?
How's that gonna happen?
How about carl knowing
about the plane, huh?
Who's idea was that?
Yeah.
All right.
But we go get it as
soon as she's done,
Split it up
right there...right?
Yeah.
Hank...
[Baby crying]
[Humming]
Hey. I said whoa.
I'm looking
for hank and sarah.
I'm sorry.
Oh, god,
look at this.
Jacob: hello.
Do you have a car seat
In the car you'll be
traveling home in?
Yes.
Is it currently
installed?
Hello, look who's here
Bearing tidings and gifts
and great joy.
Would you sign here?
Sure.
What do you mean
"gambling"? Where?
At the casino.
He lost some money.
How much?
I don't know
how much.
Shh. Hey,
congratulations.
Woman: thank you.
Congratulations.
Did you see that
little baby?
It looked like
a little tomato.
How could you have
told him that, huh?
I put myself out for you.
What do you do,
you betray me?
What are you
talking about?
What am i talking about?
It's like
there's 2 sides now.
Why are you both always
talking about sides?
There's no sides.
Who's talking about sides?
I'm on both of your sides.
We're all in this
together, man.
If you had to pick right now,
who'd it be?
No, i don't--Why would
i wanna pick?
No, i wanna know--
Me or lou?
Good grief, man. I...
I'd pick you.
You're my brother.
I bou--I bought
a present for the baby.
Ok--Ok, i--I brought it
from the house.
I didn't buy it, but, look,
it's--It's kinda cool.
Just trust me on this one.
You're gonna
like it, i think,
When you see what it is.
Thanks.
God, it's used.
Let me see that.
Oh, my gosh, this was his
when we were kids.
Oh, i guess it's sweet
of him then, isn't it?
Buddy the bear.
Here's your little girl.
Oh, good,
good, good.
Got her?
She's just about ready
for her feeding.
Would you grab
that thing?
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Hello, little girl.
Hello.
She's hungry.
I want you to buy
One of those little
tape recorders,
You know, the little
dictating kind,
The kind you can
hide in your pocket?
Why do you want
a tape recorder?
You're gonna tape
lou confessing
To stephanson's murder.
What? What are you
talking about?
[Curtain being drawn]
You and jacob invite
him out for drinks.
Get him drunk.
You take him back
to his place,
Then you start
joking around,
Kidding about confessing
to the police.
Each of you take a turn
pretending how you'd do it.
You go first, jacob
second, and lou last,
And when lou goes,
you tape him.
Come on,
that's not gonna work.
Jacob helps you.
That's the key.
If jacob eggs him on,
he'll do it.
Yeah, but even
if he, you know,
Even if he talks on the tape,
it won't mean anything.
I mean, who's ever
gonna believe it?
Well, it doesn't matter
as long as lou believes it,
As long as he sees that
jacob's taking your side.
That's all you want.
We should at least try,
shouldn't we?
We can't lose anything
by trying...right?
Hank: come on,
it's not like
I'm asking you
to do that much.
Here, just pick up the phone
and give him a call
And say, "hey,
lou, hank suggested
We go out drinking
tomorrow night."
Hank suggested
we go out drinking?
What are talking about?
Will you let me finish?
We suggest we
go out drinking.
You don't ever suggest
we go out drinking.
I'm getting to that.
Let me finish.
I'm saying, tell him i've
agreed to split up the money.
I thought it'd be
a good idea for us
To--To go out and
celebrate first.
So you want me
to trick him?
You want me
to trick lou?
You want me to
trick my friend?
Ok.
Do you get what's
happening here?
Do you understand
the seriousness
Of the situation
we're in?
He can put us both
in jail, jacob.
He's not gonna
send us to jail.
Well, i can't take
that chance,
Not now,
not with the baby.
I can't afford to
go to prison, jacob.
I mean, wh-What
about sarah, huh?
Wh-What are
they gonna do?
I'm gonna
have to get rid
Of that christmas tree
out of here.
It's too dry. It's
gonna start a fire--
Would you--Would you
pay attention here?
Pay attention.
I'll think about it.
What would dad do?
Don't do that,
please, hank.
Don't you think he'd
want us to stick together?
Don't--Don't say that.
I mean,
you don't know
What the hell
dad would do.
That's fucked up.
Don't bring him up.
Well...
What if i was to say
I'd help you get
the farm back, huh?
All right,
I'll help you
buy back the farm.
But you got
to help me first.
You know, all i meant by
that about the tree is
It's just dried out,
And it could start
a fucking fire.
You know how
that stuff goes.
It wasn't like i was
trying to ignore you
Or something like that.
I was just, you know,
I was talking about
practical shit to you
Is all it was.
Hank: yeah, we got
that white carpet.
Honey?
Oh. Oh, hey.
Hey, sarah.
Hey, jacob.
I take my shoes off
for you there, see?
Thank you.
Oh, uh...
It's a nice shirt.
Ta-Da! Ha ha.
Here, let me do that.
[Whispering]
hey, i gotta pee.
Yeah, go ahead.
Hi, baby.
Hey. You brought
him here?
Well, yeah. I invited
him for dinner.
Oh. Oh! Oh, good.
Good, good.
Ok.
So he's gonna do it?
I had to promise him
the farm.
You what? Wait,
i thought you said--
We agreed that you
were gonna say something.
Where's he supposed
to go, sarah, huh?
I mean, what's
he gonna do,
Drive away?
I don't know, honey.
I don't know,
But if he stays,
we get caught.
I know, i know.
It's just--
It's just a matter of
time before he screws up.
I know. That's
not what i'm saying.
I just...
I just wish he could,
that's all.
[Laughter]
[laughter]
No, no, you remember
what she did?
She was so freaked out
that she called
The volunteer
fire department,
And then, remember,
they came out...
Oh, yeah, there was
all of dad's buddies--
All his drinkin'
buddies.
Yeah, yeah.
That's--That's all the volunteer
fire department was,
Was guys he knew,
you know?
So they show up--
And he's sitting
there in the kitchen
With that ice pack
on his face.
That's ridiculous.
He felt like an idiot,
'Cause they're
all gathered in there
Like there's some huge
murder going down, you know?
[Baby cries]
Shh, shh.
Ok.
[Baby cries]
Well, back on call.
Hey, how about
some more wine?
You got a full
glass here.
What's it like,
a walkie-Talkie, sarah,
Kind of like a baby
walkie-Talkie?
Yeah, yeah.
It's kinda cool.
Remember, we had
that thing we did
With them little
walkie-Talkies?
Oh, yeah.
You got that kit
for christmas.
Remember that?
Yeah.
You know, it's weird.
I think--I think
about that stuff.
I think it's kinda weird--
You remember everything,
too, don't you?
Well, yeah.
I was always--
I was always
talking to dad.
I know you were.
I was always figuring out
what's going on, you know?
I was always nervous about
shit, you know, i guess.
But i tell you what,
he's a...
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org