(Dramatic music plays over dialogue)
O Mighty Khan, the city is ours.
And the Caliph?
We have searched all Baghdad.
The Caliph has escaped.
Find him!
Every day until he dies,
a hundred of his subjects
shall be tortured.
(Fires crackle)
(Squawks)
O Mighty Caliph,
O Defender of the Faithful,
praise be to Allah
that you have come safely
through the Mongol lines.
My defeat is heavy upon me, Cassim.
The very stones of Baghdad
cry out for vengeance.
Tell me,
where have you taken my son?
Ali is safely hidden in my own house.
Then let us go quickly.
With him I journey to Basra
to raise another army.
You go up against the Mongols
a second time?
They are powerful enemies, My Lord.
Well, do I know their power,
but I swear to you, Cassim,
by the power that Allah
has invested in me,
I will avenge my men
who have died this day.
My Lord, perhaps...
Perhaps it will not be necessary
to fight these Mongols again.
Other ways might be found.
Other ways?
Your meaning is not clear, Cassim.
If you will say the word, O Caliph,
I will arrange a meeting
between you and the Khan.
You and your nobles may be permitted
to live on in luxury.
To avoid further bloodshed,
we might arrange terms.
Terms? There will be no terms,
except death to the Mongols.
Blood runs in the streets
of Baghdad, My Lord.
Aye, the blood of brave men
who died for freedom.
Yours is the counsel of a coward,
Prince Cassim.
Forgive me.
Come, take me to my son.
My Lord, it were best
I stay here with men
to guard the road
against a surprise attack.
Mahmoud knows the way.
You'll find dhows at my landing.
Everything is ready.
You have served me well,
Prince Cassim.
With the help of Allah,
we shall meet again in Baghdad.
Then you shall have your reward.
(Girl gasps)
Shh!
(Woman) Lady Amara!
Lady Amara!
Quick!
Out of your beds at this hour!
In a moment we will come, Nilah.
If Prince Cassim knew
that his daughter were up at this hour!
In a moment, I said.
In a moment! In a moment!
Now, before she changes
her mind again.
There. It is done.
Your blood has flowed into my arm
and mine into yours.
- But I'm afraid...
- You cannot be afraid now.
The blood of a Caliph
flows in your arm.
I'm afraid I'm going to be sick.
Is that not like a girl!
Sick at the sight of a little blood!
I...
I'm all right now, Ali.
We are pledged now, Amara.
It will go on forever,
like the ripples in the water.
Now we shall never be apart.
Father!
My son!
Ali, we sail to Basra tonight.
(Amara) Ali!
Father!
Ali, you said
we would never part!
I'm sorry to take your playmate away,
little Amara.
- But you said...
- I said that we would never be apart.
And that is true,
for now, wherever I am,
some of my blood is with you,
and some of yours is with me.
That's all right for you to say,
but you are going to Basra.
So, my little son
grows into a man.
(Man) My Lord, the dhows are ready.
We await your coming.
Ali.
Yes, Father?
My son, the future of Baghdad
depends upon this journey.
If we fail, our people will die
under the heel of the Khan.
But if we succeed, they will live
as a free people once more.
Yes, Father.
About your neck I place
the Royal Seal of Baghdad.
And if some evil should befall me,
you, my son, will rule in my place.
Remember this always,
while one of us lives, Baghdad lives.
I will never fail you
or Baghdad, Father.
My Lord!
Come ashore!
Come ashore at once!
Something has happened
Turn back, Mahmoud.
Turn back?
It may be a trick, My Lord.
Prince Cassim is our friend.
He may be in trouble.
Turn back!
Quickly! Over the side.
(Groans)
The Caliph of Baghdad.
You did not lie.
The Mighty Khan will reward you greatly.
And the boy? Where is the boy?
He must have drowned.
(Mahmoud) Fire the boats!
Close, oh Sesame!
(Echoes repeat)
Sesame...
Sesame?
(Shouts) Sesame!
(Echoes repeat)
Sesame.
Close, Sesame.
(Shouts) Open, oh Sesame!
(Echoes)
(Man 2) Baba!
We've caught a mouse.
Allah, defend us.
(Laughs) Your mouse has teeth.
Another move and you'll die!
Oh! O, spare me, little master!
Oh, here I lay
in the dust before you.
Oh, pity!
Let me go free, and I'll spare him.
The lad has spirit.
Now that you've got him,
what are you going to do with him?
I'll split his ears!
Cut him up in little pieces.
Tie him up by the thumbs!
That'll take the spirit out of him!
Put him down, I say!
This is no time forjesting.
The boy knows the secret of our cave.
- Then kill him!
- No...
It is best we keep him with us.
I'd join no band of thieves.
But I'll lead you against the Mongols.
The little mouse shall lead us!
The boy speaks like a king.
I wear the Seal of Baghdad.
By Allah! The boy speaks the truth!
You were right, Old Baba,
he does belong with us.
Anyone that could steal
that amulet is a thief indeed.
You are the cleverest thief among us.
I am no thief!
The Seal belongs to me.
My father, the Caliph,
gave it to me before he...
Before he died at the hands
of the Mongols.
The Caliph is dead?
Aye, he was betrayed
by Prince Cassim.
Now do you believe me?
Now will you follow me?
We have no love for the Mongols.
If they have stripped Baghdad
of everything worth stealing,
we will soon rob them.
- Eh, my men?
- (All) Aye!
We will ride together,
and you, Abdullah,
shall be his guard and protector.
Me, Abdullah?
The terror of Baghdad
nurse to a whimpering infant?
This boy will never whimper.
And should he go hungry,
you will starve.
Should he suffer,
you will be disembowelled.
Abdullah, the fastest rider,
the greatest swordsman,
the fiercest fighter!
And now I'm the nursemaid.
(Laughter)
If Allah had granted me a son,
I would have wished him
in your image.
I am known as Old Baba,
and we will call you Young Baba.
No, my name is Ali.
You are welcome, Ali Baba.
Ali Baba!
(Cheering)
(Music drowns speech)
♪ Ride high
♪ Ride high, ride
♪ Ride
♪Wrong or right, plundering sons
♪Thundering sons, forty and one
for all
♪All for one
♪ Bedouins call, Bedouins all
♪Side by side, saddle and ride
♪Saddle and ride,
following sons of yore
♪Swift and sure
♪ Robbing the rich
♪ Feeding the poor
♪ Ride high
♪ Ride high, ride
♪ Ride
♪Guide me right to a caravan
♪Caravan
♪ Ride again, Ali Baba men
♪ Ride high, ride high, ride
♪ Ride of delight
♪ Following one, son of Hassan
♪ Forty and one for all
♪ Forty and one for all! ♪
Open, oh Sesame!
(Echoes)
(Man shouts) Baba! Baba!
Baba, a rich Mongol caravan,
camels by the score,
laden with wealth!
Where did you see such a caravan?
Camped beside the Pool of Midnight.
They bring wedding gifts from Basra.
There is a woman in the caravan.
She is betrothed to Hulagu Khan.
The betrothed of the Mighty Khan!
By Allah! That is
a prize worth taking.
And it is all ours for the asking.
Treasure like that is well guarded.
A few soldiers scattered about,
some aged camel drivers
and the slave girls
who attend the bride.
- There is your guards.
- To the Pool of Midnight!
No, wait! We must not rush
headlong into danger.
Does the little mouse fear
aged camel drivers and slave girls?
Surely Ali does not object
without a reason.
My son, let's hear your counsel.
Remember, there is a price
on our heads.
Aye, 10,000 pieces of gold.
Think you the Khan
would bring his own betrothed,
under the very shadow of our swords,
without his butchers guarding her?
You speak wisdom, my son.
Then let us move with caution.
The wealth of kings collected for us,
and all in one caravan!
Now we let it go
for fear of shadows.
We will take the caravan,
but, first, I will make certain
it is not a golden snare.
We will wait for your signal.
Abdullah, go with him.
Ten years! Still the nursemaid.
(Amara) Why am I forced to bear
the heat of the day inside my tent?
I am a prisoner in my own caravan.
Such was the order
of Hulagu Khan, My Lady.
But why?
Already the great Khan
guards you jealously, Lady Amara.
The beauty of his Queen
is not for the eyes of all men.
You forget, I am not yet
Queen of Baghdad.
Besides, who is there
to see me here?
A few old camel drivers
and a handful of guards.
It is not ours to question, My Lady.
Nalu!
Yes, My Lady.
You have lived
in the court of Baghdad.
Tell me, what is the Khan really like?
He is magnificent, My Lady.
He rules the world.
He is the greatest warrior
in all the land.
Ali Baba is greater.
Slave, you would be flogged
if your words reached
the ears of the great Khan.
We are camped beside
the Pool of Midnight, My Lady.
The water is clear
and blue and very cool.
Then I need not bear
this terrible heat any longer.
My Lady, you may not leave your tent.
The guard would not permit it.
Attract the attention
of the guards, Jamiel.
Give me your clothes.
But the order of the Khan!
Hulagu Khan is not yet my master.
Your clothes.
Wait here. I will signal.
Let me go! I haven't killed
a single Mongol all day!
(Water splashes)
(Ali Baba) Hello.
Where are you?
I'm curious to see you.
I feed on the curiosity
of foolish men.
An evil genie in the pool.
I distract the thoughts of men
and lead them in
the ways of mischief.
I know the ways of mischief.
Come out and let me see you.
A confection of the gods!
Are you among the men in the caravan?
I haven't seen you before.
I'm a weary traveller
who also takes the road to Baghdad.
And your caravan rests
beside the Pool of Midnight?
Nay, I am alone.
I hope to join your caravan,
and so find protection
against the thieves.
Oh, that's not possible.
We carry the betrothed
of Hulagu Khan.
Now go away and let me dress.
What manner of woman is she
who marries the Khan?
Very much like any other woman.
Some find her beautiful.
If I had a thousand pieces of gold,
I would give them all for you.
A thousand pieces of gold?
That's not enough. My price is high.
My mistress awaits my coming.
Who may your mistress be
that you grudge me
a few minutes of your company?
She's the betrothed of Hulagu Khan.
Return to your mistress, then.
But know I shall come to you
under the stars.
And someday I will buy you
for my very own.
It is the duty of a slave
to please her master,
and if that master
be young and handsome,
so much the better.
Wait!
Tell me.
Would I be safe in your caravan?
- Is it well guarded?
- It is not guarded at all!
Who would dare rob
the betrothed of Hulagu Khan?
Who indeed?
(Tree branch breaks)
What are you...?
Abdullah!
It's a trap!
Ride for your life!
(Nalu) My Lady!
(Jamiel) You are not harmed?
- Are you all right?
- I'm safe.
Woman of the Mongols! Traitor!
- Well?
- We lost him. He was too far ahead.
One poor thief is a small catch!
But we'll take him back to Baghdad.
The people shall see what happens
to those who defy the Khan.
Jamiel.
Yes, My Lady?
What will they do to the thief?
They will make an example
for all Baghdad to see.
The whip and the rack,
mangled on the wheel perhaps.
He is one of the thieves, My Lady.
It is hard telling what they will do.
Can we not find
some way to help him?
Help an enemy of Hulagu Khan?
We must take care, My Lady.
Jamiel, somehow see to it
that he does not thirst.
Is one permitted to curse
that mangy thief?
Dog of a thief!
Ignominious son of a camel!
- Filthy scum!
- Why, you...
The ride across the desert
will be very hot.
Here is water
for your parched lips.
There are many in Baghdad who love
the followers of your leader, Ali Baba.
Allah be with you.
May Allah send you warts
and give you bedbugs for company!
O Mighty Khan,
Ruler of the World,
Master of the Universe,
my daughter, Lady Amara.
Know, O Mighty Khan,
that peace and happiness
will come once more to Baghdad
when the blood of my noble family
blends with that of the Mongols.
Because she's your daughter,
Prince Cassim,
there will be
a royal marriage ceremony.
Nalu, you may go.
As the bride of Hulagu Khan,
you will one day rule the world,
my daughter.
And if I do not choose
to rule the world, Father?
We must face facts, Amara.
Once you are married to Hulagu,
my position in this court
will be made safe.
Must I be sacrificed for your position
in the court of this tyrant?
Amara!
For years I have planned
and worked for this.
I have suffered contempt
and humiliation at his hands.
That is why I have kept you in Basra.
Now that my dream
is about to be realised,
I will not see it shattered.
And if I refuse to marry the Khan?
Why not accept conditions
as they are, Amara?
This marriage brings wealth
and power and luxury.
Would you rather starve
and die for a lost cause?
That choice is easy.
When you look on the tortured bodies
of those who stood against the Khan,
you will know what it means to rebel.
When you know the agony
of a thousand deaths,
you will be glad
to accept my counsel.
Amara...
For your sake I have been
a slave to the whims of the Khan.
For you I have sacrificed
my dignity that...
That you may one day
reign in Baghdad.
Does all this mean nothing to you?
It is written that a daughter
must obey her father.
The wealth of the world
shall be yours, Amara.
Your slightest whims
shall be commands.
You will never regret
what you have done for me this day.
The Khan calls for you,
Prince Cassim.
See how the thongs
cut his flesh, Cassim.
A thief bleeds as any other man.
And the hatred in his eyes, Cassim.
His gall bladder is like to burst
with the venom that is in him.
I have given the order for
your execution at noon tomorrow.
But if you tell me the hiding place
of the thieves of Ali Baba,
a way to freedom might be found.
Shall I trust the enemy
of my people?
Or the murderer of the Caliph?
Who are you?
I'm the sword hanging over your head.
By moonrise tomorrow,
you will be carrion for the vultures.
(Cassim) I know how to deal
with these men of Baghdad.
I will wring the secret from him.
Splendid!
The Royal Seal of Baghdad!
On your knees before it, you traitor!
I begin to see now.
You were not drowned.
You are Ali. Ali Baba the thief!
Ali, the son of Hassan!
Aye, Cassim, the son of Hassan,
the friend whom you betrayed
to the Mongols!
Hassan is dead. Speak no more of him.
His memory lives,
and I will avenge his death.
By noon tomorrow you will be dead.
Nay.
Tomorrow I will see the moon rise,
and yet another moonrise.
And in the end, I will point the way
for the vultures to find your body!
Jamiel, your eyes
will be burned from your head,
if you are discovered here.
I thought you'd like to know,
the thief is tied in the marketplace.
He dies tomorrow.
What is that to me?
You would not let him die
cursing your name.
He thinks you led him into this trap.
What would you have me do?
You could have a word
with the prisoner.
Are you mad?
I cannot go to the marketplace
to speak to a thief.
This thief is a follower of Ali Baba.
He dies because he dared
to defy the Mongol tyrants.
Is he not worthy of your comfort?
He's a fool to die for a lost cause.
Should he then live a slave?
Is it better to live taxed
and trampled upon than to die a man?
I have known the tortures of chains,
as I know the value of freedom.
These thieves...
They will be remembered
long after the Mongols are driven out.
Oh, you will come, My Lady. Please.
Now you come to torment me,
beloved of the butcher.
Beloved of the...!
I came to tell you that I did not know
of the trap that was laid for you.
What does that matter?
The Mongols were hiding at the pool
and they took me.
I cannot let you die thinking
that I have delivered you
to the soldiers.
Hundreds die in Baghdad every day.
Why should one more matter?
And that one a thief?
Because hundreds die
and I can do nothing about it.
I want you to know
that I would never betray you,
or any follower of... of anyone.
Must you torture me with your lies?
Why would the future Queen of Baghdad
risk discovery to torture you?
Why should I come
to the marketplace to lie to a thief?
Why, indeed?
Except to trick me into telling you
the hiding place of Ali Baba.
Return to your butcher
and tell him that neither you
nor Cassim will ever
wring the secret from me!
(Horn blares an alarm signal)
(Trumpeting continues)
(Shouting)
Again you come before me
with evil tidings.
Again you tell me
these robbers have escaped.
I send troops there!
I send an expedition here!
I set traps for them.
And what happens?
My entire army is not capable
of dealing with forty thieves!
We outnumber them,
we ride them down,
we surround them, we charge,
only to face each other.
They disappear into thin air,
O Mighty One!
Craven liar! The truth is not in you.
And now they come within
the walls of Baghdad itself.
Under the nose of my own guards
they will ride into Baghdad
to rescue the only member
of their band we've ever captured!
And to steal the betrothed
of Hulagu Khan.
By the thousand one-eyed kings,
I will have their heads for it.
Their heads, or yours!
We must take him back
into the cave, Ali.
Nay, let me die as I have lived,
here in the open desert
under the stars.
A little wine, Old Baba.
It will strengthen you.
My strength is spent.
You will live to ride
with us again, Old Baba.
Many times.
You will ride again, my son.
Again and again until the Mongols
are driven from Baghdad.
Without you to lead us,
we will never triumph.
For ten years you have led this band.
When he came to us we were thieves,
despised and feared by the people.
Now we are loved and honoured.
Shh. You tire yourself, Old Baba.
There are things I must say
before I leave you.
Return to Baghdad, my son.
You cannot escape your destiny.
Avenge your father
and free your people.
They must throw off the tyrant.
Remember, Abdullah,
you are still his nursemaid.
Forty and one for all.
Allah be with you, my son.
We found a spy at the outpost
near the Great Rock.
- What was he doing there?
- Following our trail.
I am no spy!
Release him.
I know not who you are,
but once you were very kind to me.
You brought me water
when I was a prisoner.
And it was your knife that
saved my life in the marketplace.
Why? Why did you do these things?
When I brought the water
to your cage in the caravan,
I did not know who you were,
but I would have died
for any follower of Ali Baba.
She whom you serve
will soon be Queen in Baghdad.
Why should you be willing
to die for Ali Baba?
Because I have seen
what the Mongols do to our people,
and have heard the songs
that are sung in secret,
songs of praise for Ali Baba.
Let me join your band.
Are we a wandering tribe of nomads?
Do we collect lazy desert rats
as we go?
Desert rats did you say, Abdullah?
By the prophet,
I'll slice him to little pieces.
Your choice.
(Coughs and clears throat)
Sharp, aren't they?
I'll let you go this time.
Abdullah! The terror of Baghdad!
(Laughter)
You're very clever with your knives.
But how do I know
you've not come from the Khan?
Set me a task that I may prove it.
(Abdullah)
Think you can trust him, Ali?
You can trust me
as you can trust your own eyes.
I will not fail you, Ali Baba.
Are you well known in Baghdad?
Aye. I can move freely
within the gates.
No one will question me.
Good. Then you shall deliver
my message to the Mighty Khan.
- The Khan?
- Aye.
I have written that if he delivers
Cassim to me by noon tomorrow,
I shall return him his bride.
Now we buy traitors
in the open market!
A female beauty
for the grand vizier!
The Khan must deliver Cassim
to his own riverbank estate.
We will await them there.
They'll set a trap for us, Ali.
Then we shall post sentries
to warn us.
Go, and Allah be with you.
We must move quickly
before they have time to set a trap.
Abdullah, bring the girl.
Men, on to the house
of the traitor Cassim!
Close, oh Sesame!
(Echoes)
Why have you brought me here?
If all goes well, you'll be returned
to your beloved by noon tomorrow.
And if all doesn't go well...
Why don't you kill me
and be done with it?
While we hold you alive,
the Khan must listen to our demands.
What have your demands
to do with me?
That is not yours to question, My Lady.
Where are you going?
Is one permitted to go
into one's own garden?
Yes.
Why do you give her all this freedom?
If you were her prisoner,
she would serve you
baked, sliced and on a platter.
Strange are the fortunes of war
which place the thief
beside the Khan's beloved.
I'm curious to know
why one so beautiful, so young,
should marry the ruthless Khan.
I shall be Queen in Baghdad.
Does that mean more to you than love,
more than happiness?
Why are you suddenly
so kind and gentle?
My memory is long.
I can recall a country
when the Mongol scourge
was nothing
but a fantastic nightmare.
When the people lived
to dream and love.
Not to torment and destroy.
Strange that Ali Baba
should speak of dreams.
A man without his dreams
withers and grows old.
In the midst of terror,
the memory of other days is sweet.
Aye.
There was a beautiful garden
where two children played.
The moonlight was reflected
on the water.
As it is reflected
in your eyes now.
For a moment you made me forget
that you are Ali Baba, the thief.
If these are to be my last moments,
let me live them in peace.
(Ali Baba) There. It is done.
Your blood has flowed into my arm,
and mine into yours.
Call the guards!
Surround the palace!
What does it say?
- "To the...
- Read it!
"To the Mongol Dog.
We will bargain with you.
"Your betrothed is our prisoner.
In exchange..."
Read it. Read it, I say!
"In exchange we want Cassim.
"Cassim, who betrayed the Caliph.
"Let him be brought to his own estate
before noon tomorrow,
"then the woman will be
returned to you unharmed.
"Otherwise she dies."
It is signed with
the mark of Ali Baba.
Can we not send soldiers
to the estate?
This may be our chance
to capture the thieves!
He is no fool!
He will watch for every trick!
I leave the decision to you.
She is your own daughter.
Shall it be your life, or hers?
Cassim does not come.
He does not come.
Why do we wait?
- Vengeance for Old Baba!
- Remember our pledge!
Listen.
(Shouting)
Why do you want to kill me?
To avenge the death
of our Old Baba.
What is the death
of your Old Baba to me?
(Jeering)
He was our leader. He died
of wounds inflicted by the soldiers
of Hulagu Khan, your beloved.
A life for a life, that is our law!
(Jeering)
If you kill me, the great Khan
will send soldiers to take you.
For years the great Khan
has sent soldiers,
and he hasn't taken us yet.
(Jeering)
Silence! Have I given you nothing
in the past years?
Fighting and snarling
like a pack of curs!
The men are tired of waiting.
You gave them your pledge.
The traitor has not come.
I have made my decision.
Then let me be the one
to carry it out for you.
No. Jamiel shall do it.
I, Ali Baba?
You begged to follow me, Jamiel.
Ask anything else of me,
anything but this.
You will do as I say.
There's no better way to serve me.
Coward! You would force
my own slave to...
Take her back to the Khan. Alive.
Alive? But our message to the Khan.
Our pledge.
(Jeering)
All night I lay awake,
telling myself she must die.
Now, I break my pledge.
Why must you weaken now?
Whatever my reason,
she goes free.
- But the Mongols will laugh at you.
- Let them laugh!
You have heard my decision.
If you want me
to leave the band, I will go.
Then I will fight you for her life.
Send her away if you must.
We cannot quarrel with you
over a woman.
Now take her back to Baghdad.
Now will you tell us
why you spared her?
Your blood has flowed into my arm,
and mine into yours.
It will go on forever.
Your horses are waiting,
Prince Cassim.
By hard riding,
you can still arrive before noon.
Great Khan, for years
I have served you.
I sacrificed my honour,
I betrayed my friend,
and helped to deliver Baghdad
into your hands.
Would you sacrifice your daughter
to save your own miserable skin?
How do we know
he will keep his word?
Thieves do not keep their bargains.
Ali Baba will slay Amara
and then kill me.
Have mercy, Mighty Khan!
Have mercy!
The road of a conqueror
is never an easy one,
but I find the hardest part of it
is trying to deal with you traitors.
You are a breed apart.
Take him away!
See to it that he reaches
his estate before noon.
Mighty One.
Father!
Amara!
- Father.
- Come here!
Tell me, by what wiles did you secure
your release from the thieves?
I cannot explain it.
This morning Ali Baba
defied his men and set me free.
But he bargained
for the life of your father.
For the life of my father...
You were to die at noon,
if he were not there
to take your place.
What manner of woman are you
that thieves and cut-throats
release you?
Why should he seek to kill you?
I saw how he hated you there
in the marketplace.
What is it between you
and this Ali Baba?
Speak!
Father.
This... This Ali Baba is Ali,
the son of the Caliph.
Ali!
You told me he was drowned.
We never found him.
How do you know
he's the son of Hassan?
He wore the Royal Seal
of Baghdad about his neck.
Why didn't you tell me then?
I thought he would die there,
and thus the threat to us
would be removed.
But he lives!
And he will rally the scum
of Baghdad under his banner.
Why did you not tell me?
You knew we were pledged.
So... he would have double reason
for his revenge upon you.
They pledged themselves as children.
Pledge?
But the pledge
still burns in his heart.
And it is stronger
than his hate of me.
Our marriage will go on as planned.
You do us great honour.
No! It will not go on!
I cannot marry him now!
And you shan't force me to.
Now, now, Amara,
I think only of your happiness.
Were you thinking of my happiness
when you did not tell me
that Ali is alive?
You know how much
that pledge meant to me.
- We will talk of this later, Amara.
- No!
O Mighty Khan!
You have power and wealth.
You have only to command it,
and the most beautiful girls
in Baghdad
will be yours for the asking.
Surely you wouldn't want me,
knowing that I love Ali Baba.
What is love compared
to what I have to offer you?
I can make you a queen.
I can give you silks, jewels,
wealth and power!
The blood of Baghdad
would be on any gift you offered me.
'Tis a pity one so lovely
should be confused by politics.
Once I was confused.
I see clearly now.
Too clearly!
Nothing you say or do will ever
induce me to marry
this Mongol tyrant!
Be gentle with her.
She's wild and headstrong.
This has been a great shock.
But I can make her realise
the future lies in your hands.
Hurry! Take only what is necessary.
We have no time to lose.
- Did you find Jamiel?
- Yes, My Lady.
- Everything is ready for you.
- Then let's go quickly.
My Lady, come!
Look!
(Cassim groans)
Your men torture my father.
What is the meaning of this?
Cut him down from the rack and...
And I'll marry you.
Because he has served me well,
I will grant your wish.
Only release him
and I'll do anything you ask.
We shall be wed
on the festival of Ramadan.
It will be a great holiday.
Princes and merchants will come
from every corner of the world.
They shall bring rich gifts
in token of their servitude.
You are a master of trickery,
Prince Cassim.
There are times when trickery
is more powerful than force.
(Man chuckles)
Leave me.
The horses are ready, My Lady.
I cannot go, Jamiel.
But now that you know
who Ali Baba really is...
I have given my word.
Hulagu Khan would've killed
my father if I had not promised.
I will marry him
at the feast of Ramadan.
It will be a great holiday.
But, My Lady, what of Ali Baba?
Go to him, Jamiel.
Tell him I, too, remember
the pledge we sealed with our blood.
If he had only told me who he was,
I would have stayed with him.
He will come to your rescue, My Lady.
No, he must not.
It may mean disaster for him,
and failure to the cause
for which he fights.
And you, Jamiel,
you must stay with him.
Your heart is there. Go quickly.
And the slave, Jamiel,
leaves the palace, My Lord.
But he has not had time
to reach the outer gates.
You see, O Mighty Khan,
I'm still useful to you.
Your little spy
has done well, Cassim.
Return to your mistress.
I will send soldiers, great Khan,
to bring the treacherous slave
before you.
Make no move to stop him.
Let him go to Ali Baba.
The thieves will come to the rescue,
but this time
they will fall into our trap.
Jamiel!
Tell me of your lady.
She learned from Prince Cassim
who you are.
She said to tell you that she, too,
remembers your pledge.
Then why does she marry the Khan?
She thought you were dead.
- But she does not love the Mongol.
- No. She refused to marry him.
But when he tortured her father,
she gave her consent.
I will go to her.
Why all this fuss about one woman?
For a thousand pieces of gold,
you can buy the best in the market.
A thousand pieces of gold?
I bid my life for Lady Amara.
For a man's country or his stomach,
he might bid his life,
even for his horse.
Never, never for a woman.
I do not ask the life
of a single thief to save her.
But if I choose to give my own,
it is between me and Allah.
(Jamiel) I will go with you.
What, you two would storm
the walls of Baghdad
and attack the Mongol armies
single-handed?
You would break into the palace
and carry off the wench?
What do you possess? A magic carpet?
- When will the wedding be held?
- At the feast of Ramadan.
And for entertainment,
they'll chop the two of you
into little bits.
There will be many guests
at the wedding.
One more will pass unnoticed.
Then there'll be forty more
than they bargained for.
Good.
This is the hour
for which we have waited.
This shall be our day
of reckoning with the Mongols.
You're right. This is our hour.
With a single cast of the dice,
we will free Baghdad
or we will die together.
We must disguise ourselves
if we are to enter the palace.
Children of camels,
offspring of donkeys,
paint your foolish faces!
Dress your ugly bodies
to deceive the Mongols!
This time we enter the palace!
(Cheering)
You must return
to Baghdad ahead of us.
As sentry within their gates,
you'll be able to warn us
should the Mongols become suspicious.
As Caliph of all Baghdad,
I bow to you.
I kept that a secret
until it was time to strike.
Now all of Baghdad shall know.
Abdullah, you'd be a favourite
in any harem!
Who do you see, you ill-mannered,
insignificant little ape?
Why, Abdullah, of course.
Now whom do you see?
- Who am I supposed to see?
- I'm disguised.
Who are you?
You are a stranger among us.
Truly I have never
laid eyes on you before.
It's a wonderful disguise, isn't it?
It is black magic.
He has changed
from Abdullah the thief
to Abdullah the thief in a turban!
Wait!
We must find some other way.
We will fool no one
with our disguises.
Even a blind Mongol would know us.
If a rich merchant from Basra
were to attend the wedding,
it would be fitting he bring
a rich gift for the invader.
By the stars in heaven,
this is what we shall do.
We will assemble forty huge jars,
large enough to carry
forty weights of fragrant oil,
and large enough
to carry forty thieves.
My Lady!
(Gasping)
Jamiel! You cannot come in here.
I must talk to Lady Amara. Quickly!
Go, please.
Why have you returned
against my orders?
Because of Ali Baba.
He bids you have courage.
He will come.
No, no, he must not!
He must not try to save me.
They will kill him.
The Mongols would welcome an attack.
Ali Baba is not such a fool
as to attack the city openly.
There will be wonderful wedding gifts
brought to Baghdad.
Among them will be forty jars of oil
from a rich merchant.
She was spying on you, My Lady.
No, no! I came only
to bring My Lady's dress.
We can trust her.
If she heard our words,
she will lock them in her heart.
I have heard nothing,
but I would die
before I would betray you.
It grows late.
- (Whispers) Today Ali Baba comes.
- Ali Baba?
Today.
- Ali Baba comes today.
- Ali Baba!
Great Khan,
many guests enter the city
bringing rich gifts
to win your favour.
You must challenge everyone.
Each caravan that enters
the city must be carefully watched.
Take no chances.
The thieves are certain to try
some trick to gain admittance.
I have spies everywhere, Mighty One.
We will know the plans of Ali Baba
almost as soon as he does himself.
Good.
This time he will receive
a welcome he did not bargain for.
Gifts for the Mighty Khan.
Pass on!
If you love Baghdad,
wait for the signal,
and strike down
the Mongols for Ali Baba.
Whose caravan is this?
It is mine.
I am Abu Radi, merchant of Basra.
What is inside the jars?
Oil. Oil for the Khan.
If he uncovers the jar, he dies.
It is a gift to celebrate the wedding.
Pass on!
(Fanfare)
O Mighty Khan,
Haidar, Prince of El Samrah!
Precious sapphires and topaz.
Garnets and bloodstone.
Vases from the ancient
temple of Isis
for Your Highness.
(Fanfare)
Abu Radi, merchant of Basra!
I, a lowly merchant,
do plead with the Mighty Khan
for the privilege of adding
my humble offerings
to those of his noble guests.
In all the land,
there is no finer oil.
Oil for your lamps,
oil to cook your feasts.
Fragrant oils
to please your senses.
I have waited for this moment.
My spies told me that the thieves
entered the city in forty large jars.
This merchant from Basra is Ali Baba.
No, wait, O Mighty Khan.
I have prepared entertainment.
It will amuse you to see
the fate that is awaiting them.
Excellent, Cassim. Excellent!
(Fanfare)
Sada Gen, Chief of the Tartars!
Come here.
(Khan) Rubies, blood red,
for the people of Baghdad
who stood in my way.
And now, for your pleasure,
a most unusual bit of entertainment.
(Fanfare)
What is the meaning of this grim jest?
Seize him.
Sand!
Your spies discovered our plans,
and we discovered your spies.
You have failed me.
(Screams)
You are my honoured guest.
Now there will be entertainment
befitting your rank.
You shall not die as a humble thief,
but with all the honour
to which you are entitled.
You will live through a thousand tortures.
And you will pray
for the release of death!
(Screaming)
(Horn blares)
On to the palace!
Quickly! Come with me!
(Shouting)
(Banging)
Open the gates, Amara,
for your people.
Still the nursemaid.