Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Do it.
Hey, I think we ought to wait.
Don't go pussy on me all of a sudden.
I'm not, man. I mean, l--
Don't!
This is the stupidest goddamn
thing I've ever done.
Go right, Cody, go right.
Watch for traps.
Hey, moron! You almost harpooned me.
Suck it up, piss pants.
Idiot.
Guys?
Shit!
Duke!
It's over here!
Shit.
Fuck. Fuck.
God damn it!
Shit.
Fuck you!
Fellas!
I can't believe we actually caught one.
It's uglier than I remembered.
It's about to get uglier.
Those sons of bitches following us.
I don't think so.
You don't think so?
Rush took off right after
we seen the first one.
God damn right they ran. Little bitches.
I need more chains.
More chains.
I ain't got no more.
He ain't got no more.
Son of a bitch!
Cody!
Stop that shit!
God damn it, Duke,
You're bleeding all over the van.
I try holding it.
It looks dead.
It's not dead.
I don't think it's breathing.
Would you just shut the fuck up, please?
I need to think.
Cody!
Don't look that thing in the eyes.
What do you think, I'm retarded?
That's some dangerous shit back there.
Oh, thanks for the news flash, brainiac.
Duke?
What the hell is that?
It's a star.
It's a moving star.
It's an airplane, then.
Ain't no fuckin' airplane.
It's a fucking airplane, Otis! Chill.
Oh, God!
What the fuck!
For protection. Against the eyes.
Gimme that shit.
Left! Turn left!
What the fuck's that?
That's not the turn.
Only thing up here is boonies, man.
Oh, man, Duke.
We gotta get off the road.
Fuck no, Duke.
Fuck no!
You got a better idea?
All these years we pissed away
at Nixon's farm...
... waiting for this...
And this is the best you've got?
I never thought
we'd catch the damned thing.
We can't trust 'em, Duke.
Wyatt's the only one who
knows about these things.
We all know about these fuckin' things.
Not like Wyatt.
Fuckin' bullshit!
Fuck this shit.
Wyatt?
You better go back to sleep.
There's nothing out there, baby.
It never ends.
This is fucked, Duke.
They're gonna come looking.
We can't just stand out here
in the open.
Get back in the van.
The thing's in the van.
Wyatt.
Fuck this.
Wyatt, I know you're in there, Wyatt.
Look,
I know you don't want to see us.
I understand. But me and
the boys. We got no choice.
We've been out to Nixon's farm, Wyatt.
And...
They're after us.
You know that better than I do.
And I bet my ass you know
what we got out here in this van.
Get it!
Go get it!
Dadgommit, Wyatt,
we need a place to hide.
You don't let us in here,
... we're all gonna die out here.
I know you, Wyatt.
You won't let that happen.
You can't let that happen, Wyatt.
Not this time.
What's up, Wyatt?
That's far enough.
What is this?
It's a chance to make things right.
What's in the tarp?
You know damn well what's
in the goddamned tarp.
What the fuck did you boys do?
We took some action.
But you wouldn't know shit about that.
Come on, Otis.
The mask was my idea.
The chains.
Did you kill it?
It wouldn't come without a fight.
It's lost a lot of goop, though.
Is it breathing?
Is it supposed to?
Is... god damn it.
Shit.
This thing dies,
we're all in a world of shit.
Kick this one's ass.
Kick some more.
You ignorant shit.
You kill it and the rest are
gonna come and put us down.
And I don't just mean us
in this fucking garage.
Get out of the way, Otis.
What the fuck is this?
Hope.
It's one thirty in the morning.
Yeah, it's just business.
Christ, Wyatt.
What the fuck kind of business.
They have guns.
One of them's bleeding.
Hey, Wyatt.
You need me to put
your woman in her place?
Excuse me?
Well, he don't mean nothing, ma'am.
He's just an asshole.
At this point I'm gonna ask you all
to get the fuck out of my house.
Please, baby....
Let it go.
It's okay.
Wyatt, you in some kind of trouble?
Nothing I can't handle.
What the hell is that?
Please.
Just give me a minute.
That's all I need.
What is that, Wyatt?
I'll explain everything.
Do I want to know?
Please, baby.
You all need to get that thing
back where you found it
But we think they're coming after us.
It ain't my goddamn problem.
Wyatt.
It ain't my goddamn problem!
Now, you listen to me.
The longer you keep that thing,
the more dangerous things get.
I told you, he ain't changed.
Wyatt, just hear us out.
I'm not getting mixed up
in your shit, Duke.
I left this shit in the
rear view a long time ago.
It's been 1 5 years, guys.
So let this shit go.
Fuck this pussy!
We'll take it back to Otis'
and carve it like a turkey.
The hell we will. My mom would shit.
Pissing on these things
ain't gonna bring back Timmy.
I ain't gonna hide like a pantywaist...
... from the sons of bitches
that murdered my brother.
Fuck it. You do what you want.
But don't do it in here.
God damn right I'm gonna do what I want.
You sack of fucking shit.
Cody...
What.
We're all friends here, Duke.
You gotta trust me on this one, Cody.
Trust you?
Last time we did that,
you made us look like apeshit.
The whole town thought
we gone retard, you asshole!
My own fuckin' father thought...
... I killed my brother and
buried him out in the woods.
I thought it would be better.
Better?
Fucking over your friends was better?
Telling the whole world we were lying?
Telling everybody we made everything up?
Guys?
I thought if people knew the truth--
Cody!
Cody. God, that's enough, Cody.
What'd you think about that, dipshit?
Cody.
Guys. 205a. Huh?
You're worse than any fuckin'
cocksuckin' piece of shit!...
You got your money's worth,
now get the fuck out of my garage.
It's awake.
That's good, right?
Wyatt, I think it knows you, man.
No. No. No.
What's it doing?
Fuck if I know.
Wyatt, what's it doing?
Wyatt!
They're coming back.
This fucknut wants to take care of us.
We should make it to the van.
I mean, if they're coming,
we probably should--
Shut up! Shut up!
Nobody talk. Nobody talk.
What? Oh, fuck that shit.
Shut up!
What the fuck?
The man says shut up, you shut up, Cody.
They're gone, right, Wyatt?
It's sending a signal.
Hold it down.
Hold it down! Hold it down!
Hold it down!
Hold it.
Good.
God fuck!
Fuckin' God!
Hold it down!
Aw, fuck.
Fuck you, goddamn it.
Fuck.
Hold it still, damn it.
The fucker's trying to send a code.
Cut it.
What?
Cut it! Cut the fucking...
Get something to cut the fucking thing.
Come on, Duke. Cut it. Cut it.
That's it. Cut it.
Come on. Cut it. Cut it.
Cut it, Duke!
It was trying to call the others.
If it's calling its buds,
why aren't we knee deep
in these sons of bitches?
It must be damaged.
Probably because of that
goddamn ass whooping
... we put on this motherfucker
out in them woods.
Probably.
Best not to take no chances.
How'd you know, Wyatt?
About the implant?
Call it a hunch.
Keep the lights out and stay quiet...
... and they might not find us.
Take it back to Nixon's farm
in the morning.
Safer to travel in the daytime.
Hey, do you think
we all got one of those
... GPS clicker thingies in us?
Wyatt would know if we did.
Hey, that clicker went off
the second it saw you.
What the fuck is going on, man?
Wyatt?
You think you can check me
for one them clickers?
Not usually... but have them deliveries...
... and they're willing to...
Who you calling?
Wyatt, baby,
this is a dangerous situation.
Who did you call? Just tell me!
She's calling the cops, wasn't she!
I'm outta here. Give me the keys.
The hell you are, you fucking bitch!
Shut the fuck up.
Give me the keys, Wyatt.
Listen to me. I can't let you go.
Not until morning.
Hope, I'm trying to protect you.
By holding me hostage.
First thing in the morning,
I'll take you anywhere you want to go.
I'm on fucking parole.
Fuck off, Cody.
You fuck off, Wyatt.
I ain't going back to prison
... 'cause this crazy
ass bitch is losing it.
You understand that?
This bitch called the cops,
I swear to God I'll cut her up.
Hey, baby.
What's the play now?
You always got the answers.
Put the gun down, Cody.
You always thought you were the leader.
Some leader.
Look at us.
We're all fucked up now.
I guess Timmy was the lucky one, huh?
Lucky my ass.
You got no idea what happened to Timmy.
That's right, I have no idea.
But you do.
Look, we're all friends here, okay?
Let's not do anything stupid.
Let's take a deep breath and calm down.
Hope!
What are you doing, baby?
Give me that knife, Hope.
She looked it in the eyes, didn't she?
Ah, fuck. Easy.
This ain't gonna fly, Wyatt.
The thing's got her.
Don't matter.
She ain't got nothing to do with this!
If that thing gets loose...
We're all dead.
I know she's your girl and all...
But I don't give a shit.
No.
It's playing with us.
Look what she's doing!
I'm shooting.
No. No. No.
Cody.
Hope...
Hope. Please, baby...
This man will kill you.
She's fucking cutting it.
Please, baby... Concentrate on my voice.
What do you want?
He's talking to it.
You let her go!
The gun.
Put down the gun, Cody.
No fuckin' way.
Calm down, Cody.
Put down the fucking gun!
Fuck this bullshit!
Jesus Christ!
Put down the gun!
No fuckin' way.
Stop!
Let go of her!
Let go!
God damn it! Let go!
Red line's out of bounds.
Nobody crosses it. No matter what.
Oh, damn, that looks infected.
Might need a tetanus shot.
Had one when I was seven, remember?
Fuck itps deep.
Oh, jees... Wyatt.
That works?
Hell if I know.
You shouldnpt be out trying to pull
some cockamamie stunt, Duke.
You got a wife and kid.
Pam left me four years ago.
That ain't shit.
I've seen worse.
How many nights have you boys been
out trying to catch one of those things?
Nights?
Try years.
Probably seven by now.
Damn, Duke.
That's some shit.
It was either that or go out drinking.
Well, there was some drinking
out there too.
Actually after a while it was
pretty much all about the drinking.
Got easier
when Otis started hanging out.
We could watch in shifts.
Then numbnuts got out of prison.
Fucking bear traps was his idea.
Yeah, I could have guessed that.
Going out to Nixon's farm was...
... our way of coping.
You been coping, Wyatt?
What do you think, Duke?
Ah, shit!
Motherfucker!
Fuck!
Fuck it. God damn it.
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
I'm supposed to...
... put this duct tape over your mouth...
... because of the...
Wyatt thought it'd be better.
You tell Wyatt to go fuck himself.
We all know how it feels.
Having one of those things...
... inside you like that.
Controlling you?
It's the worst fucking thing ever.
It's hell.
It's worse when it's longer.
They did it to us for days.
Oh, well.
Let's hold off on tape for now...
God damn it.
What the fuck?
Oh, fuck me.
God damn it. What the fuck?
What the fuck are those...
God damn it.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, God damn it.
Oh, fuck.
Please no.
What the fuck.
Fuck. God damn it
Fuck!
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
Come on, man. I gotta drop a deuce.
Quit playing.
Is this why you gave me so much
shit when I wanted to move in?
Yeah.
Good call.
Honey...
I never wanted to get you
mixed up in all of this.
You understand that, right?
You're gonna have to give me a little
more time on the understandin' part.
Get the hell out of my way!
Get the fuck out of my way!
Come on, Cody. Calm down, man.
This was your fucking plan.
No, my plan was to catch it.
And now what? You want out?
Oh, you sad fucking sack.
There's more at stake now than just us.
You're damned right.
They killed my brother.
Now get the fuck out of my way, Duke.
Cody!
Cody, put that thing down.
You're not calling
the fucking shots, Wyatt.
Now I'm not playing around here.
I've got business with this thing.
And I plan on taking care of
it right fucking now.
Get out of my fucking way, Duke!
Cody!
Get the fuck out of my way, Duke!
Fucking savages.
Calm down, Cody.
I want answers, motherfuckers. Now!
Cody, this is some dangerous shit.
Dangerous?
You want to see dangerous?
You boys still think
I'm screwing around?
It bit me.
Look at that. It is spreading.
We can help you.
Duke. Not too close.
What?
Listen, Cody, why don't you
turn off the torch and lay down man.
You seen it before.
It's bad, ain't it.
Ain't it!
It's just a rash, right, Wyatt?
It's just a rash, Cody.
Oh, shit!
Get out of the fucking way!
This is between me and it.
Put the torch down, okay?
We can fix this.
We can get you to a hospital.
Yeah. Yeah. I could be some
college boy's thesis project.
I'm not being a lab rat.
Not again.
That ain't gonna happen, Cody.
Now just put the torch down.
Now see, Wyatt? That's your problem.
You always think you
got a say in the matter.
You see what happens when
you try to fuck with me?
Come on. You see what
happens, motherfuckers?
I dare you. Come on.
Try that shit again, you motherfuckers.
You little pussies.
Duke!
Don't touch him.
What about you, man?
Don't worry about me.
He's not dead, is he?
I mean, I didn't hit him that hard.
No, he ain't dead. Don't worry.
We just gonna let him rot away in there?
He needs help, Wyatt.
Nobody can help him, all right?
Stay away from him.
That shit's contagious.
But you touched him.
It won't do nothing.
None of this shit ever does.
That's what Timmy had, isn't it?
When they took us.
That's what killed Timmy.
It won't take long.
They'll start eating him inside and out.
He'll watch his flesh peel
away layer by layer.
It'll hurt so bad,
it'll make him insane.
Dangerous.
A few hours from now,
he'll be begging us to
put a bullet in his head...
... 'cause his fingers are hurt so bad...
he won't be able to pull the trigger.
Sweet Jesus Christ on the cross.
Wyatt.
Can I talk with you for a minute alone?
Hey, what about me?
You stay in there and watch the girl.
Shit, Duke,
I don't want to be alone with
that chick. She freaks me out.
Sorry, Wyatt.
Just get your ass in there,
Otis, please.
Please.
They let us catch it, didn't they?
What the fuck you talking about, Duke?
I'm saying there's no way in Hades...
... we could have caught
that thing the way that we did.
They just dropped that
fucker off and sent him right to us.
You're crazy.
I'm sorry, Wyatt.
I'm sorry.
I'm such a fucking idiot.
They knew our dumb
asses would bring it to you.
What the fuck would they want with me?
I don't know.
Maybe they ain't
done fucking with you yet.
Have you ever wondered why you
were up there the longest and
... came back with
that clicker shit inside you?
I try not to think about that.
I think it's about time you
started giving that some thought.
Fuck me.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
What's going on?
Nothing, buddy.
I wish you weren't lying.
Otis, you keep this door locked,
... and don't let anything through.
It's loose, ain't it.
Just do as he says and secure the door.
Maybe it's gone.
Oh, fuck. God damn it, Duke.
It was over here.
There's fucking blood
all over the place.
Where the hell is it?
Help!
Wyatt, it's Sheriff Henderson.
Open up or I'm breaking in.
Get the fuck away from me.
Just a minute.
Hands up.
Easy, Sheriff.
What's with the lights?
The power went out.
Happens out here all the time.
Oh, yeah? Well, I heard voices.
It's the radio.
I was hoping they'd say when
the electricity would be back.
What's this all about, Sheriff?
91 1 call.
Said you were holding a hostage.
Is that right?
Yeah.
An extraterrestrial one.
What is it?
The third time this winter?
The fourth, I think.
What, are you locking me in here?
No, it's wild dogs, man.
... snooping around lately.
I guess I could take care of
some wild dogs.
I guess you're getting used to
this prankster shit.
Yeah.
Anyways, we gotta check it all out.
You know, the routine.
Especially since the call
came from your phone.
My phone.
Yeah.
You been drinking?
Yeah, I had a couple.
You mind if I have one?
I guess not.
Good.
What's back there?
Uh, nothing.
You got a key?
Yeah, I got it right here.
Shit. I stepped in something.
What is this?
A radiator leak?
Yeah, I guess so.
Listen, Sheriff, there's
something I need to tell you.
I got a girl in there.
You got an alien groupie, huh?
No, she's just a friend.
I'd like to meet this friend.
What the fuck!
What--
Go away. Wyatt! Wyatt! Help me! Shit!
Hold it.
On the ground.
I gotta ram it.
I said hold it!
You're gonna have to shoot me, Sheriff.
Wyatt, help! Wyatt!
Fuck!
On the ground!
Come on, Sheriff!
God damn it! Please, Sheriff!
The next one's gonna
be between your ears.
Otis?
Don't move!
Don't move! Please, Wyatt, don't move.
It's come here, Wyatt.
I want my mommy. I want
my mommy. I want my mommy.
What the fuck.
Don't move.
No. No. Don't point the gun at it.
Point it away, god damn it.
Point it away!
Everybody stay calm. Stay calm.
Stay calm.
Get the tape, Duke!
Make it stop!
Hold on, Duke.
You fucker! Take it!
Make it stop.
You're all right.
I don't think the duct tape's
gonna work this time. Wyatt?
You're gonna be fine.
Just hold it together, all right?
It's all over.
Sheriff?
Shit.....There's a pulse. All right.
I'm gonna get you some help.
Okay, Sheriff?
Fuck that.
Go get me a beer.
All right.
Easy.
How's your friend?
About as good as you.
All that shit about you
and aliens was true, huh.
Yeah.
Shit. That's fucked up.
Got anything harder?
Yeah. Yeah.
It's not safe out here.
It's safe in there?
I'm not going back in here, Wyatt.
Not until it's dead.
We're taking it back
where they found it.
Otis needs help. We're
gonna take him to County.
Kill it, Wyatt.
You can't kill it, Hope.
I 'll do it, then.
Hope.
Hope?
Please don't tell me
it'll be okay, Wyatt.
If you tell me it's gonna be okay,
I swear to God, I'll fuckin' hurt you.
Killing this thing will
only make it worse.
Worse? Fucking worse?
Did you fucking see what it did?
Why can't you be a man?
Why don't you care? I hate you!
I care. I care.
Oh fuck.
You had the keys.
You should have just gotten
the hell out of here.
I've never been
so good with "should've".
Me either.
We're losing him.
Cody.
Cody. Otis is...
Otis is bad off.
We're gonna go for help, man.
Always thought one day we'd find Timmy.
Take him back to town and have
a fucking parade or some shit.
That ain't gonna happen, huh, Wyatt.
I'm gonna die...
... with everyone thinking
I killed my brother.
Nobody thinks you killed Timmy, man.
The hell they don't!
My own pop...
If I had my way...
I'd take that fucking monster and...
... drive it back to my
pop's little peach house,
... walk right past that
motherfuckin white picket fence,
... and drop that piece of shit alien...
... right on that cocksucker's doorstep.
Ding dong.
Oh, that will be good.
I'm sorry, Cody.
My mom...
she thinks I 'm working overtime.
She's gonna be all alone, now.
Oh shit.
Watch your fingers.
Yep.
Ready?
All right.
It's a heavy little fucker, isn't it.
I doubled the chains.
Let's hope it stays unconscious.
Yeah.
It ain't safe out here, Duke.
I can't leave Cody.
The boy's my responsibility.
Take care of yourself.
Bye, buddy.
What happens if we kill it, Wyatt?
You know what happens when
an animal kills a human?
We kill that thing and they put us down.
They put us all down.
We kill one...
They declare
war on the human race?
Wouldn't be no war.
They want us gone from
this planet, we are gone.
The show is over, end of the human race.
It'd be a goddamned massacre.
Wyatt, when this is over,
I think I'll move back to
my mama's house.
Cody?
I'm real sorry, Cody.
I'm gonna make things right.
Why'd they come back, Wyatt?
They let the others go after
the second night.
They tested us all, you know.
But Timmy and l...
I guess we made it past the first round.
Timmy got sick real fast...
Like his brother.
But it didn't take with me.
So they kept doing more and more.
They kept fucking with me.
They altered me.
Till one morning I woke up,
... naked...
... couple of counties away.
They'd sent me back with some
sort of tracking device in my body.
But I knew it was there because I could...
... hear it clicking away.
So I cut it out and went into hiding.
I guess they want me back.
They're scared of you, Wyatt.
When that thing was fucking
around inside my head, I felt it.
That's why they came back for you.
They're scared shitless of you.
Yeah, well the feeling's mutual.
What?
What the fuck, Wyatt?
Shut up! Shut up!
They'll hear.
How do you even know--
I can feel them.
Where are they?
Everywhere.
Lots of them.
We can't just sit here.
It's not safe out there!
I'm real sorry, sweetie...
Sure as fuck ain't safer sitting
in the middle of the road in this van...
... with that thing in the back.
Wyatt?
Wyatt!
Hope.
Hope. This ain't cool, Hope.
Hope, this ain't cool.
That van'll be our coffin.
Otis is back there.
Otis died ten minutes ago.
That is not true!
Yeah? Then check on him yourself.
Hope, we should get back in the van.
I'm not hiding for
the rest of my life, Wyatt.
That's your thing.
Hope.
Hope!
Otis?
Come on, buddy. Otis?
Come on, Otis!
Come on, Otis.
Come on, boss. Come on.
Come on. Stick with me. Come on, man.
Son of a bitch!
God damn you motherfucker.
Why'd you pick us? Why?
Motherfucker!
You like that? You like that shit, huh?
Fifteen years ago,
we were out on a hunting trip.
You know all about hunting trips,
don't ya.
Don't you!
It was me, Wyatt...
Otis and Cody...
And Timmy.
Yeah, you fucking remember
You fucking remember.
You fucking remember that shit!
We were just kids
But Timmy...
You remember Timmy.
You killed our friend.
Now you're gonna pay for it.
You're gonna fucking die.
See what it feels like.
Feel what it feels like.
Duke!
Duke.
Oh, shit. Fuck.
Cody. Cody.
Holy shit.
What the fuck, Duke.
Shit, Duke.
You're not supposed to be
holding me like this. Shit.
It's okay.
We could get help.
You get help. I'm going back.
Take this, okay?
Won't you need that?
No.
Okay. I'll drive you back.
No. You stay on the road
and keep driving.
All right?
You don't turn back for nothing.
I won't leave you.
I need you to do this for me, Hope.
No, I won't leave you.
Duke?
Duke. Duke. Duke.
Duke.
Wyatt.
Duke. Where is it?
Where'd it go?
It's calling the others, Wyatt.
Duke.
You run, Wyatt.
Go.
Duke.
Damn.
Get off him, you fuck.
Duke!
Nooooo!
You motherfucker!
You fucking bastard!
Why'd you have to do that,
you son of a bitch!
You goddamned motherfuck--
How'd that feel?
You ugly motherfucker.
Cody!
How does it feel to be probed,
motherfucker?
Cody?
Oh, shit, Cody.
I ain't got time for this, man.
We've got some serious company coming.
Cody. God damn it, Cody.
You hear me, Cody? Please.
God damn it. Shit.
Oh, God, Cody. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, man.
God damn it, Cody. Listen to me!
Cody!
Oh, shit!
Oh, shit, Cody.
Shit, Cody.
Cody.
Oh, Jesus.
He's had enough!
God damn it. He's had enough!
I said that's enough!
I know what they want.
Call them off.
I'll go with you.
Call them off!
Just leave Cody alone.
And don't hurt anybody else.
And I'll go with you.
They'll give you a ribbon or
something, you piece of shit!
No! This is between you and me!
Nobody else!
I said call it off and I'll go with you!
I'll go with you! I'll go with you!
You're not going anywhere with them.
Van's down the road. Let's go.
Wyatt.
Cody?
Cody.
Timmy was never really
good with pain, was he?
He was a real pussy, wasn't he?
I need you to do what you did to Timmy.
I didn't... I didn't do...
Please, Wyatt.
You were his best friend.
Come on.
Come on. Come on. Hurry.
Come on, Hope. Get in.
Hope, get in.
Come here.
Cover your ears.
What the fuck.
Where now?
Somewhere else.
We're all right now, aren't we, Wyatt?
We'll see.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org