Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I'll be honest.
Before I came down from the room...
...I took about a pound of Vicodin.
I'll be comfortable till late March.
You're funny.
How do you live with him?
She doesn't.
She lives with someone else.
Must've been exciting working with
Hal Weidmann. Were you apprehensive?
Oh, no. No, Hal's brilliant.
He's so easy to work with.
He loves actors.
Just loves actors.
You had a nervous breakdown
recently, didn't you?
What?
Can audiences watch you without
recalling your attack on Ms. Harrison?
That's five minutes. Thank you.
It was so great meeting you guys.
I'm a huge fan.
Lunch?
Why does he get a neck-rub?
- I want one.
- He's so tense.
Hello? I have a neck too.
This thing holding up my head.
And we're back.
- Everybody ready?
- Of course.
Of course.
Hello again, Syracuse.
Mort Josephson, your Movie Maven.
Ann Arbor, I'm Laura Messinger,
the Cinemaniac.
- Popcorn's buttered.
- Lights dim.
- It's Bob...
- And Ken.
At the Multiplex.
We're great friends.
We talk every day.
We're better friends than ever.
We talk two, three times a day.
We're just cosmically, spiritually
bound. Eddie's really good...
...and he's my pillar of strength.
It's like Sodom and Gomorrah.
So strong, you know?
And that's five.
In spite of all
the emotion and hurt...
...we leaned on each other for
support.
That's when I realized how strong
our friendship really was.
- We're in constant contact.
- Right.
I mean, not only
are we great friends...
...and not only are we
in constant contact...
You should see our phone bills.
We've also done...
I don't know, how should I put this?
Hell, I'll just say it.
We've done a few three-ways.
This guy she's with now...
I can't say I'm happy. She's my wife.
But after spending time in the sack
with him, I see the attraction.
But for a fairly big guy, he's not
packing much south of the border.
And that's five minutes.
Thank you so much.
Say hi to everybody in Salt Lake.
Good to see you.
Next.
- Hi, guys!
- Hi, guys.
- That wasn't funny.
- It was a joke.
- I do that after 400 interviews.
- Hector won't find it funny.
Guess what? I don't give
a shit what he thinks.
Take a picture with my baby?
Just smile and shut up.
- You have given me 110%/% today.
- Who has?
You. It's been a great day.
- What do you want?
- A small favor.
45 minutes, an hour.
I need you to have dinner with Gwen.
- It'll be great.
- I won't do it.
- You should do this.
- I'm gonna be alone with the minibar.
We're in deep shit.
Hal's holding the film hostage.
We have nothing! Understand?
But I do have you. You and Gwen.
When you're together,
the press forgets that.
It's roses blooming,
flags flying, pudding...
- Are you on something?
- A panic high.
Just order an entree,
chew a little bit, smile and go.
They have delightful pork tenderloin.
8:00. Thank you so much!
- It's Gwen's idea.
- Really?
Absolutely.
I can't believe you said
I'd have dinner.
They serve a very nice
pork tenderloin.
I'm not going. Here.
I was with him enough today
for the rest of my life.
- I gotta give him the divorce papers.
- When?
Just before we leave.
What, toss them at him
as your limo pulls away?
You don't understand.
It's very complicated.
Being nice makes giving him the papers
easier, but then he gets hopeful.
- Is that your foot?
- Sorry.
Pedicure. Hello?
- So when you're nice, he thinks...
- I can't talk about it right now.
It's so hard being someone
people just don't get over.
- Tell him I have a headache.
- I won't lie for you.
- You lie for me all the time.
- Not to him.
This is high school all over again.
When you wanted to break up
with a boyfriend, I had to do it.
- You did not.
- Oh, please.
Let's refresh your memory.
Robert Mancuta? Kyle Hassler?
Half the lacrosse team?
I was the most hated girl in school.
That's untrue.
My quote in the yearbook was,
"Hey, we have to talk." I was hated.
Fine.
Don't go.
Eddie will sit there like an idiot,
and it'll be all your fault.
Whatever.
- How are you?
- Lee.
- Where's the film?
- What?
In its canister, waiting to be shown,
to go into history.
There is no film.
What have I seen five times that
gave me the best feeling ever?
You'll have a great time.
See you later.
We're dead, we're doomed. Thank you.
Look at you. You clean up good.
- Thanks.
- What's going on?
Gwen isn't feeling well,
so she won't make it to dinner.
- She isn't sick.
- Not physically.
- I didn't want you to sit, wondering.
- Thanks. Really.
Wanna join me?
Haven't you read the papers?
I'm unstable. Don't let me be alone.
Come on.
- A few minutes.
- Yeah.
We have an understudy.
They never make it easy, do they?
The house phone, please.
Thank you.
- Holly Golightly's cottage, please.
- Who's that?
Gwen's code name.
From Breakfast at Tiffany's.
- What's that?
- It's a movie, a great movie.
- Hepburn?
- Right. Katharine.
Listen to me.
Don't tell anyone you're in the
movie business, okay? Thank you.
Hello? Hey, Gwen, it's Lee.
I'm at the restaurant,
and guess what? You're not.
Are you okay? Oh, that's too bad.
Eddie's with Kiki.
She looks unbelievable.
It's a bit "Hello, Young Lovers."
I may have some fires to put out,
but that's my problem.
Have a nice night.
Feel better. Okay. Bye.
Five minutes.
- You're amazing.
- Take notes.
"This is Larry Flange.
I'm sitting with the lovely
and talented Kiki Harrison.
You play a lesbian firefighter
on an oil rig.
One word comes to mind: Typecasting.
Your thoughts?"
You really want my thoughts?
- Larry.
"Okay, Larry...
...the truth is...
...after playing Madame Curie...
...and discovering radium...
...I just thought it would be a hoot
to strap on those big rubber boots...
...kiss my favorite gal goodbye
and go fight some fire."
- A very personal role for you.
- Very close to my heart.
- That's funny. You're funny.
- I am. Yeah.
Do you remember Silent Run?
We rented that go-cart?
You attacked the director...
- There was no attacking.
- You rammed him repeatedly.
- You rammed me.
- Ramming you was a different thing.
And you rammed Gwen.
She was not laughing, and we were.
- She wasn't happy.
- She was pissed.
- That memory kept popping in my head.
- Those were good times.
- I'm sorry I didn't call you.
- She's your sister. I understand.
But you're my friend.
I let myself get kind of...
- It's good to see you now.
That's a nice necklace.
- It's not really mine.
- I know.
- It's Gwen's.
- She gave it to me.
- And I gave it to her.
I know.
- It looks good on you, though.
- Thank you.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking something
I shouldn't be thinking about.
- Me too. What were you thinking about?
- How much I want that breadstick.
You want to eat this?
No, I don't eat bread.
I just dream about bread.
I've been doing a lot of
dream analysis since I cracked up...
- At the center.
- At the center. And I believe...
...bread represents something you want
but can't have. What do you think?
Well, I think that
when I dream about bread...
...that would represent...
...bread.
Pretty much.
What are you thinking about?
Gwen...
...is here.
Sorry I'm late.
- Thought you were ill.
- All better. Just like that.
- Thanks. You can go.
- She doesn't have to go.
- Stay.
- Good to see you.
- I need mouthwash.
- Right away.
So...
I hear they have
great pork tenderloin.
- She didn't have to go.
- Thank you. You look great too.
- Excuse me. Is Holly Golightly here?
- What's the name?
- What's he doing here?
- I'll get rid of him.
Get a camera.
Film, tape, anything. Go!
It's Gwen Harrison.
- Lee. We met the other day.
- Where is Gwen?
- I want to see her.
- I won't get involved.
How do we stop people in love?
What are you talking about?
I want to see her now.
I can't cover for them anymore.
They're in the restaurant.
They're right over there.
She's in the red dress.
- Hi.
- Hector!
Jesus.
- That's all right.
- Hi, Gene.
- Don't wave at him like that.
- I promote my movies.
- I know.
- It's part of the biz.
I apologize.
- I'm sorry.
- Hector.
- I apologize for him too.
- He's here.
For why are you sitting with him?
Get in. Would you get out of the way?
Good. Get that side. Let's go.
- What are you doing?
- Protecting the woman I love.
- I'll let you two catch up.
- Why don't you be quiet!
- I'll get to you soon.
- Don't point.
Don't tell me what to do.
- Don't you trust me?
- I trust you implicitly.
It's this asshole I don't trust!
What? What did you say?
I hope he's not
making fun of my accent.
Okay, enough! You guys enjoy
your little public display!
I'm leaving.
Okay, pussy boy's leaving.
What's wrong? You don't like that?
Maybe you want to take a swing at me?
Tall boy. Come on.
What are you...?
- What is that?
- Let's go. Please, make my day.
You're a genius,
beyond my wildest expectations.
Tracking's up.
Spielberg's moved off our date.
This is good! Hit him! Hit him!
- Who?
- Anybody.
- I won't fight!
- You're a pussy boy.
- I'm trying to find some peace.
- You want peace? Okay, he wants peace.
- Pussy boy's leaving.
- Don't do that.
- Hector, don't.
- Don't tell me "don't."
Maybe you want a piece of me.
You see?
Huh, pussy?
I really don't think there should be
a problem here. After all...
...you took my wife and I tried
to kill you. We're even.
You crumpled duck!
Oh! Dear me!
Go away!
Punk! You hungry?
Eat this, punk! Eat it!
Are you hungry?!
I love your work.
You forgot something.
- Did you see him go down?
- Shut up.
- Why'd you have to do that?
- I didn't have to. I wanted to.
- Just deal with it. In there.
- It was my pleasure.
Did you see that?
- Are you okay?
- Everybody back, please.
Eddie! Are you okay?
I can feel my nose in the back
of my throat. Is that bad?
Can you hear me?
- Let's all just step back.
- Some ice, please.
I swear to God,
Gwen can be just horrible.
How can you love someone and not like
them at the same time? Seems strange.
- You need to lie down.
- I thought I was.
Why don't we try sitting down?
There we go.
Let me have a look.
- It doesn't look good.
- No?
Cold.
- What happened?
- I needed another humiliating photo op.
I tried to walk away,
but he kept pushing.
So I hit him in the tray with my face.
I should've walked away.
For some reason, these days,
I do the stupid thing.
This doesn't look good.
- What was that?
- Another stupid thing.
Stupid and maybe verging
on crazy or...?
It's a fine...
There he is. The master!
I'll have what he's having.
I have to say, you have
completely outdone yourself.
In 24 hours, we've had
a walk in the woods...
...a romantic dinner and a fistfight.
I can't wait to see what happens next.
Maybe I can get him to commit suicide.
You like that?
Let me think about it.
It won't help initial release
but video will go like crazy.
- We could do a box like a coffin.
- Yeah. That's good. No, wait.
Imagine if he killed himself
at the premiere.
I'm joking.
I'm thinking out loud or whatever.
- Good night, Dave.
- Good night, Lee.
Good work!
Good morning.
How do you feel?
I feel... I feel...
I feel good. I mean,
I feel weird, but I feel good.
- You?
- I feel something along those lines.
Good, weird. Weird, good.
Here's what I was thinking.
What about breakfast?
We'll take it from there.
Why don't you order some breakfast?
I'll brush my teeth first.
- Can I use your toothbrush?
- Yeah, it's in there.
Can I get some juice?
Keek? Hello?
Where are you?
Want some toast?
You buttered my toast.
No one's done that before.
I don't eat toast with butter...
I don't eat toast.
I'll stop talking now
and make an exception.
Want some tea?
It's hot.
- Here. Okay.
- Thank you.
No, I'm fine. I look like
half a raccoon. What's up?
Now's not a good time.
Can we do it later?
No, don't come here. I'll come there.
Bye.
That was Gwen.
- She wants to talk.
- About what?
I don't know, she didn't say.
But I better...
...go over there.
- Why didn't you say you'd talk later?
She said she'd come here,
and I thought...
...that's not a good idea so I better
go over there, given the situation.
- Will you tell her about last night?
- I don't know. I'll just let her talk.
Know what I mean?
Sounds like it's important
so I'll let her say it.
Then I'll go do these dumb interviews.
I'll come back and we'll lunch
together. Does that sound good?
You look terrible.
- Does it hurt?
- Only when I'm awake.
- He's not here.
- Who?
- Hector.
- That doesn't matter. Is Kiki here?
I doubt it.
- I don't know where that girl is.
- That girl is here.
Nice of you to join us.
Where have you been?
Got up early. Things to do.
Nothing important.
Would you make scrambled eggs?
She makes great scrambled eggs.
- I remember.
- Would you like some?
- Two orders. Make mine runny.
- Let's get room service.
It would be my pleasure.
What did you want to talk about?
I think you're doing pretty well, huh?
- Are you feeling okay?
- Yeah, I'm better.
I'm shocking myself.
"I forgot how charming you were."
"You, Miss Julep, are a warm breeze
on a cool afternoon."
What was that?
"What was that?"
- What movie was that?
- I don't know.
What was that movie called?
I don't give a shit!
- No, that wasn't it.
- You look like you're in a good place.
When I saw you and Hector,
I was so conflicted.
Conflicted is the word du jour.
There's no question about that.
You know what that is? She's tired.
- You seeing anybody?
- Excuse me?
- Are you seeing anybody?
- Let me think about it.
Not...
You know...
- Not technically, no.
- What?
Not technically!
That's fascinating. "Not technically."
That's sad. Really, that's a shame.
Your eggs, darling sister.
I hope they're runny enough.
And you! Son of a bitch!
Here are your eggs! There you go!
- What's wrong?
- A lot, actually.
I can't believe it's taken
so long to figure out.
I'm going for a long walk
to simmer down.
First, I'd like to cut
through the shit.
He's not technically dating because
he's technically hung up on you.
And you! You moron!
She's only here to salvage
her precious career...
...and serve you with divorce papers.
I've done all I can do.
I'm going for a walk.
Leaving is just something
I've really perfected, so...
...once more, with feeling.
- She was more fun when she was fat.
- Is that true?
- What?
- About the papers.
Yes, but now I don't know.
Seeing you, being in front of the
press with you... We have something.
Maybe I've made a horrible,
horrible mistake.
Maybe I should give you the papers.
I don't know.
You're the devil.
- I want to talk. Hold on a minute.
- Let go of me.
- I want to talk.
- I don't!
- Why not?
- You're an idiot. I'm an idiot too!
In that respect, we belong together.
- It's a complicated situation.
- I'll un-complicate it!
Forget about what happened between us.
It's not gonna work, all right?
Last night? Last night was great.
But she calls you,
and you can't wait to get to her!
What is that? It won't work.
You'll probably always think of her...
...and I'll probably always wonder
if you're thinking of her.
I just...
- I need you to know one thing.
- What?
That woman that you saw by the pool...
That woman you just have to spend
the rest of your life with...
That was me.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
So here's the buffet.
What's going on?
Nothing. I'm great.
Just great. Ma'am, can I get
some more butter?
When you hit Formica, stop.
You know the expression
"falling off the wagon"?
But you got 30 pounds of food
to break your fall.
- What the hell happened?
- Bad morning. Preceded by 33 bad years.
- Does this have to do with Gwen?
- Of course not.
I love my sister.
I love everything about her.
"Kiki? Kiki-kins?
Who's smoking? I smell smoke.
Is someone smoking within a six-mile
radius of me? Stop them, Kiki."
Oh, ma'am, the butter? There's
no butter? How can you run out?
- I have one theory.
- I need an assistant.
If I had one, she'd be outside
milking a cow...
...and I'd never run out of butter.
"My butter has touched another food.
I need new butter."
"Anything you want."
That's how it goes.
You know. Anything they want, right?
She's got a green dress.
Looks like crap on her.
Brings out the bags under her eyes.
She gave it to me. It looks nice.
Then she said she wanted it back.
She doesn't want me to have it.
So you're in love with Eddie?
- Wouldn't that be stupid?
- I've done every one of their movies.
He never looks at her
the way he looks at you.
If you're in love, just go for it.
The way you went for this breakfast.
Not the way you went
for the breakfast. That's...
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Can you just...
I'll take all of this to go.
I'll need 30 bags and a forklift.
No laugh, no tip.
I want to play someone
like the Terminator.
I think the Hispanic people
are crying out to see...
...a deadly, destructive
killing machine they can embrace.
- That they can relate to.
- Nice to see you.
How are you? Hal here yet?
He's a dead man. No, I'm serious.
I know a guy. I'll make a call,
and he's dead, because...
How are you?
Hope you're having a good time.
- What time is it?
- 12:50.
We're doomed.
May I suggest that you follow my lead
and get completely shitfaced?
- Hi, how are you? You look gorgeous.
- Hi, Mr. K. Thank you.
How long must I stay with the people?
They're drunk and touching me.
Wait. If Hal doesn't bring the film,
they'll be busy building a gallows.
I don't think that's funny.
Is that pussy boy?
- He's gonna jump.
- He's not.
- I said I'd give him divorce papers.
- Shit, he's gonna jump!
- Excuse me.
- Please.
- I'll do something.
- Get him!
Let's take advantage of this.
Get some shots.
- Shut up.
- All right, yeah. Okay.
- Jump, jump.
- Jump, pussy, jump.
- I can't believe this.
- He'll be a pussy pancake.
- I'm coming!
Why's he doing this to me?
- I'm sorry! You okay?
- What are you doing?
- I was stopping you from jumping!
- By killing me?!
- Stay right there!
- Where am I gonna go?
Right!
Oh, shit. Hang in there, Eddie!
I'm coming!
- Okay.
- You're hosing me down?
I'll throw it, and you catch it.
One, two, three.
Pull yourself up. I got you.
Come on.
Got it? Good.
Oh, my God!
Pussy boy'll go splat.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
That's it. One foot at a time.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna kill you.
Take a bow. It'll look better.
Jesus Christ.
Next time, take
a hair dryer into the tub.
- I wasn't killing myself.
- Then what?
I came here to think. Is that a crime?
Do that in your room!
I blew it.
I lost her.
Guy goes to his rabbi.
He says, "Rabbi, my wife
is trying to poison me."
Rabbi says, "I'll talk to her."
He comes back and says,
"I spoke to your wife for three hours.
Take the poison."
- You get it? You and Gwen are over.
- I don't care about Gwen!
- I'm talking about Kiki.
- Kiki?
She's the only one worth spending
any time with in this hellhole.
No offense.
You have some nice qualities.
But for a review,
you'd sell me for medicine.
- Don't let her get away.
- Too late.
No, it's not. Trust me.
I'm telling you...
- That's Hal!
- It is?
He's here with the film! We're saved!
- We're beyond saving.
- You wanna see the film?
- I don't care.
- This could put you back on top.
- You think? On top?
- "May I have the envelope, please?"
Hal! It's Hal. Hal!
- He's got the film. Go, go.
- He's the director.
- He looks good.
- He looks great.
Let's get started. I'm Lee Phillips.
Welcome to Time Over Time.
Thank you.
I'll go out on a ledge here
and say...
I couldn't help myself.
Welcome the man responsible
for this junket, Dave Kingman.
Thank you very much.
They say that good things come
to those who wait.
I waited 20 years to work
with the great Hal Weidmann.
- Hal's cinematic influence has been...
- That's good. Thank you.
Thank you.
My name is Hal Weidmann. Hello.
Ladies and gentlemen...
...this is the most honest movie
I have ever made.
I wasn't looking for it. It came
to me like a bus in the street.
Or the woman who changes
the flowers at our desert house.
I can't talk about this film
without weeping. Roll it.
Thank you, Hal.
Have a great time, everybody!
Sarah. I'm Ben. We must speak.
- Who are you?
- That's unimportant.
What's important now is yoursafety.
You're in danger.
This is hard to say,
so I'lljust say it.
- I'm from the future.
- Oh, my God!
- You look beautiful.
- Thank you.
Come with me now. Now, Sarah, please.
Love is a bridge
built between two people.
We want what exists
between them to be real.
My name is Hal Weidmann.
The film you're about to see
is Time Over Time, oris it?
The details are unimportant.
Simplyput...
...the script was shit. I tossed it.
- I let my camera capture real life.
- Just watch.
I filmed my actors
without theirknowledge.
I let the camera run after takes.
I placed hidden cameras around.
And the end result is a story...
...farmore involving than anything
manufactured by actors and writers.
This is real life.
Thejuice.
The stink.
The glory.
Often, you wonder
where the budget goes.
Shut up!
It's gonna be good.
I don't mean to pressure you,
but we're 15 days over.
- Oh, no.
- What are we gonna do?
I'm in the middle ofshooting.
It's a sensitive time. Do me a favor.
Go away. Please.
Never visit my set again.
Watch him take it...
...up the gazoo.
You're an idiot. I told you
we nevershould've hired him.
You're so good in this.
Cut.
- Hal, can I get like three minutes?
- Three minutes.
- Gwen, can I talk to you?
- I'm working.
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
- His hands are all overyourass.
- My character would've done that.
- You look like a prostitute!
- Oh, please.
- Don't make a fool ofme.
- Cut it out.
I'm watching you every minute.
You hearme?
- Cut it out.
- Do you hearme?!
- I think Eddie knows.
- Knows what?
About me and Hector.
- You said nothing was happening.
- Well, something happened.
You see thatzit?
- What the hell is this?
- You think I know?
You bastard!
- You see it?
- I'll get something.
- I slept with him.
- Hector?
- Are you in love?
- Come on.
It's not always about love.
Sometimes youjust need a lay.
I tell you, he's hot.
Handsome. He can go forhours.
Just wish he had a bigger,
you know, thingy.
I love this movie.
What do you mean?
It's like a roll of quarters.
It's like this.
- Well, maybe like this.
- Okay. I know too much.
I'm gonna scream.
- I think it's very entertaining.
- Lee, get over here!
You stop this right now.
I'll sue the studio.
- Lower your voice.
- Shut up.
- Cut the film.
- Excuse me. Was that deserved?
I think so. You've ruined me.
You've ruined my career.
Look at the screen.
Don't you realize what that is?
That's reinvention. That's birth.
That's life itself.
Can't you smell the life?
Pretty soon you'll smell
Ira Stern, my attorney!
- Thank you, Hal.
- Wacko.
The film's new direction caught
some of us a little bit off-guard.
- I am shocked. I'm outraged.
- There are textures!
Can I say something, please?
What was said about my penis
is completely false.
I'm extremely well-hung.
I'll submit to an inspection.
I knew this film
would be misunderstood.
Kubrick was misunderstood. Godard.
I'll kick your ass! Understand that!
- Who are you?
- Who am I?
- I'm your ass-kicker!
- Can I defend my dad?
No. Who's her dad?
- Hal.
- No, you cannot!
Let me defend Hector. We had sex.
His penis is bigger
than a roll of quarters.
- You slept with her?
- No.
- I swear she's lying.
The part about my penis is true.
It's bigger than coins.
There will be a lawsuit. Invasion
of privacy, damage to my career!
Yes, yes, I know.
Congratulations.
It's my most honest work.
- I'll work with you.
- I got a script.
- You're great.
- I'll send it.
I have an announcement to make.
I'd like to thank you all.
I'm so happy you're here
and all our friends in the press...
...who've been so supportive
this last year. I'm so happy to say...
...that Eddie and I are getting
back together.
So thank you all so much.
- What is this bullshit now?
- Be quiet.
This is bullshit. Bullshit!
Today, Eddie came to the cottage.
We had breakfast and a heartfelt talk,
didn't we, honey?
I've wanted to get back
together with Gwen...
...ever since we weren't together
anymore. I've obsessed about it.
- How sweet.
- Now that it's happened, I must say...
...l'm amazed and grateful. And I
agree with Hector that it's bullshit.
Thank you very much!
- We talked about this.
- No.
- We did. Don't you love me?
- We did not.
I love the bright,
sexy woman up on-screen.
- He loves me.
- The movie girl.
That's not you. You're good
at pretending to be real.
I think I'm with
the real you, but I'm not.
I'm with the real you,
not the movie you. I don't want that.
- Why?
- I just explained it.
- You did?
- I don't want to talk.
- Not in front of these...
- Why not?
What could I have to say to you
that I don't have to say...
...in front of 300
international press members.
I'll tell you why.
I'm in love with your sister.
Is this some kind ofjoke?
Kiki, could you get over here?
- Why her?
- Oh, why not?
Is it so unbelievable
that a man could love me?
- Not now.
- Now is the time.
- You just wait for me!
- Can I say something?
- Yes.
- No!
Listen. Okay, one nut at a time.
You're my sister. I love you.
You should know nothing happened
between me and Eddie until last night.
I feel much better
about you stealing my husband.
Ex-husband. I didn't steal anything.
You're the one shacked up for
the past year with Ricky Ricardo.
Look, I am just tired
of making excuses.
I am done picking up dirty clothes.
I am done pretending...
...that your life is my whole life.
I'm just... I'm done.
So what you're really
worried about is you, right?
Well, I guess you're fired.
Honey.
You know all I care about
is your happiness.
That's sweet...
So don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.
- You're unbelievable.
- Shut up.
Next? What can I do for you?
I shouldn't have said that
in front of everybody, but...
I've been searching for clarity.
All of a sudden I am so clear,
it's ridiculous.
- I want to be with you.
- When did you decide this?
The moment I thought I'd lost you.
- Damn it.
- What?
That was... That was good.
No. No, this is crazy.
Eddie, this isn't gonna work.
Listen to me.
I'm grateful for you.
In all the world, the thing
I'm most grateful for is you.
- Lf that's a line from your movie...
- That one's mine.
- What do we do now?
- Traditionally...
...we kiss.
Give her some room.
Thank you. Step back, please.
Easy, easy.
I'm on pain medication...
...that makes me say things
I'd never say otherwise.
To set the record
perfectly straight...
...Eddie and I never
had any plans to reconcile.
And?
And Hector is very well-endowed.
Almost too well-endowed.
I've had complaints. Literally.
- What are you doing?
- Packing.
- Let me help you with that.
- That's okay.
That's... No, really...
Folding!
Let somebody help you for once.
There you are.
That was unbelievable.
Like a movie with a stage show.
If you'd tour with the film,
we'd be rich.
And your sister is unbelievable.
The entire country has voted her
off the island but, no! She's back!
I've never seen anything like it.
They like the film!
They call it The BlairBitch Project!
But the best news is you two.
Want a drink?
- We're on our way out.
- Where?
We don't know.
Once in a while, good things happen.
I'll see you.
There's a car,
so you can dodge the press.
But I'll need you! We got work to do!
This one will work!
Hi. Can I explain why I didn't call?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org