Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
What the hell happened to you?
Vitti threw me off a roof.
Vitti? You talked to Vitti?
Yeah, I talked to Vitti.
- What did you say to him?
- Nothing.
- You sure you didn't tell him anything?
- I didn't say anything, Mr. Rigazzi.
Can I go now? I think my leg's broken.
That must hurt, huh?
Wait a minute.
I have something for that.
I hate to see people in pain.
Get him out of here.
What about Vitti?
He's a hard man to kill.
But he's not immortal.
Our time will come.
- Okay, roll film.
- Background.
Hey, I like my sausage burnt.
I don't know how you like your sausage?
I been doing this 20 fucking years.
- You got the money?
- I almost got it.
I'm still light 15 large.
But don't worry about it, I got it covered.
All I gotta...
Cut! Cut! Can you do something
about the goddamn smoke?
Cut!
Can you do something
about the damn smoke?
This is the trouble
with shooting on location...
...although it's worth it
for the authenticity.
Well, it looks authentic.
Hey, Tony!
Tony.
Anthony Bella, Nicky Caesar.
- This is Paul Vitti.
- You don't have to tell me who he is.
- It's a pleasure to meet you, mate.
- Hey, mate.
I don't believe this. An English guy.
- You ain't even Italian.
- Australian-ltalian.
- There's a lot of paisans down under.
- Down under what?
- You like to laugh, don't you?
- It's a nervous defense mechanism.
I don't have to do it if it bothers you.
So I'll just...
So, Paul, are you gonna join us?
I'm thinking I might.
I like the whole setup here.
Sensational, mate. I can't wait to work
with you. I got a lot of questions for you.
- All right, mate.
- All right.
- Can we get this fucking shot?
- Yes, yes.
Paul, thank you. And welcome.
Welcome aboard.
Couple of things.
I don't know who makes these decisions...
...but there are things that
l see that don't look right.
Yes, I sensed this myself.
Which elements strike you as wrong?
Well, the people, mainly. I mean,
you got a boss who speaks Australian.
- What the fuck is that about?
- Not my first choice.
- And your background is what?
- Theater, mostly.
That figures. I got some people
l could bring around...
...that will add a certain authenticity
to the whole thing.
I would be eternally grateful
to you if you could.
Is there anything else that you would need?
I'd like one of those trailers
like the stars got.
Done! Done! I am gonna go
put that in the works right now.
Right.
Brian!
- Hey, Paul. You really gonna do this?
- Yeah, I'm really gonna do this.
Are you out of your fucking mind?
I'm going nuts already with this job thing.
In a week, I'll fucking kill
this Raoul or I'll kill myself.
This is just a good cover till I figure out
what I'm gonna do. But call the guys.
- You know, there's a line here.
- Yeah, it's in back of me.
Take the chicken and the two pastas.
You must be a teamster.
Youse don't stop eating.
"Tell me why I'd give a shit
about your wife's cousin?"
- No, no good.
- It's not good?
What about this line? "Stevie Wonder
sees more shit than you do!"
- No. Never.
- It's not good?
Never.
"How much does the chosen snitch
want for this?"
- No?
- No.
- It's no good.
- No good.
Jesus.
That's it. That's...
That's the end of the scene.
- There's no dialogue in the scene.
- You're better off.
Get in the car.
- We going to the prom?
- Shut up and get in the car.
I know.
Sit down.
Careful. The eggs are on the bottom.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
You the shrink taking care of Paul Vitti?
- Yes, I am.
- So is he nuts, or what?
I'm sorry, I don't discuss
my patients' cases with anyone.
Discuss it.
He's suffering from a chronic anxiety,
and...
And what?
Antisocial personality disorder.
Sociopathy.
I'm getting a fucking headache here.
What are you trying to say?
He has a criminal temperament.
He's a criminal?
This is news?
And for that you need a doctor degree?
What do you do for him?
I try to get him to see
the possibility of change.
Wrong.
You do not want him to change.
That's Mrs. LoPresti.
Patti.
Patti, I'm Ben Sobel.
Paul Vitti is very important to this family.
We don't want to see you
turning him into a stromboni.
Stromboni? The thing they clean
the ice with at the hockey games?
That's a Zamboni, asshole. Stromboni.
It's a bull with his balls cut off.
- No, we don't want to see that happen.
- Not unless you want to be one too.
No, I'm very attached to my balls.
As you can probably tell.
Then do the right thing. Understand?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Goodbye.
No hard feelings.
No, and probably never again.
We're gonna need a grapple or a crane.
Fifty-foot boom, at least.
I seen one in Bayonne, but I'll call around.
All right, see what you can do.
And we're gonna need a city bus.
Anybody got ideas about that?
I got a guy in the Transit Authority.
He owes me big.
- Let me know when you want me to call.
- Hello, Paul.
- Hey. How you doing?
- Hi, guys. How are you?
- Patti, how you doing?
- Good. I guess everyone's gone Hollywood.
Excuse me. This is a closed set.
We're about to start shooting.
Yeah? So am I. Let's walk. Come on.
- I heard you had some more trouble.
- Yeah, Lou the Wrench took a shot at me.
I don't have to tell you, Paul. Alone on
the streets, you don't stand a chance.
That's what the family is all about.
Since the old days when
the grandfathers first came over.
It's not something you walk away from.
When you're a Jet,
you're a Jet all the way.
- What?
- Nothing.
So you wanna tell me what's going on?
I see you have your whole crew
back together.
Nothing's going on. They're actors now.
Don't bullshit me, Paul.
I know you're planning something,
and I'm feeling left out.
All right. All right, I'll tell you.
Something's going down.
You'll get your end.
Just let us do what we gotta do.
It'll be fine.
Okay?
You're a good friend. I would never
insist on something like this...
...but I'd feel better if you'd bring Eddie
and a couple of my guys in...
...you know, to help you with the job.
Eddie "Yeah, what?"
- He's a good man.
- He's a fucking jerk-off.
He's young. He's got a lot to learn.
What is this, crime school?
This is a serious thing we're doing here.
Check him out. Talk to Frankie Brush.
Talk to Jackie the Jew.
He's worked jobs with them before.
They'll vouch for him.
Paul, please. For me.
He does what I tell him, stays out of the
way, and he keeps his fucking mouth shut.
All right. Fine. Thanks, Paul.
I really appreciate this.
Oh, God. Dear God.
Look, sweetheart...
Sweetheart, first of all...
...we're not shooting the hooker scene
until tomorrow.
And the hair, please, what is it?
Something from the cliche store?
Raoul. This is a friend of mine.
Patti. This is Patti Lo. This is Raoul.
Patti Lo...?
Patti LoPresti?
I am so very, very sorry.
How dare you not inform me
that Mrs. LoPresti is on the set today!
You are fired! Get out!
That is why I'm...
Please, enjoy your visit with us.
And if there is anything at all
that I can do...
Go fuck yourself.
Immediately. Immediately.
He's from the theater.
- Should I wait here, Mr. Rigazzi?
- No, pull the car up your ass and wait there.
Get over your hurt feelings, okay?
Tell me. Was she angry?
Am I in danger?
Don't worry about it. I just wouldn't start
my car for a couple of weeks if I were you.
I'll have Brian do it. He's new.
Hey, Paul.
Hey, Lou.
This is Lou Rigazzi, Lou the Wrench.
The Wrench?
Brian? Sorry.
Start my car!
Now!
Come on, I wanna talk to you.
The guy who shot at you,
he was acting on his own.
- I never gave the order.
- Yeah?
He's been taken care of.
There won't be another incident.
Unless you're thinking
of working for Patti Lo.
Me? No.
Good. Then I got no beef with you.
Good, I can sleep better.
Let me tell you,
because that's not the way to go.
You wanna back a winner,
which is gonna be me, okay?
It only makes sense.
So you come work for me.
I'll treat you right.
No, thanks.
So much for sleeping better.
You be careful.
Listen, Jelly, you just pick numbers.
- You know why? It's an open race.
- Jelly.
- Hey, doc! How you doing?
- How you doing?
How are you?
How are you, Yo-Yo?
Mo-Mo.
Mo-Mo, right. I was thinking of the cellist.
Jelly, where's Paul?
He's in his camper.
Yeah.
Doc, what are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
What are you doing here?
I came to tell you that you had a meeting
with your parole officer, and who do I see?
Patti LoPresti!
Patti who?
Stop lying to me. Your whole gang is here.
Who says I'm lying? I finally get a straight
job, I start getting my life together...
...and you start accusing me?
That's how much you trust me?
Paul, it's not that I don't trust you.
It's just that I don't trust you.
This is what's so hard
about being an ex-con.
You make one mistake
and nobody lets you forget it.
So now you're the victim?
Paul, I want the truth.
Wait a second.
- Say that again.
- Say what?
- What you just said. "I want the truth."
- I want the truth.
- No, strong, like before.
- Paul, I want the truth!
That's it. That's good.
- What?
- I'm serious, that had power.
- I believed you. You could be an actor.
- Paul, I am not an actor.
You're better than the bums here.
- There's this part you could do.
- I can't. We have this meeting.
We're shooting now. There's this part,
you could do it. I'm telling you, it's you.
I did do Music Man in high school.
People thought I was quite good.
Jelly, what are you...?
Help! Help!
Hey, help me!
I don't wanna do this!
- Does that screaming sound real to you?
- Yeah, that sounds pretty real to me.
That was not funny at all. There was
no harness. They could've dropped me.
If you didn't wanna do it,
you should've said.
You said a scene on the roof.
I didn't know they would throw me off.
They didn't throw you off.
They hung you over the side. That's it.
I know what you're doing.
You're upset that I have custody of you...
...so you passive-aggressively
make me look like a fool.
Come on. You were great.
You were great.
Second take, I thought,
was better than the first.
Jelly wasn't giving me much, honestly.
So I...
Screw you, Paul.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy. That's it. Okay.
- What are you doing, self-medicating again?
- No.
Don't give me that decongestant,
multivitamin shit.
- Come on, what are you doing?
- Ginkgo biloba. Helps my memory...
...and I forget what else.
But don't worry about me.
Worry about what you're gonna say
to this parole officer.
I mean, what are you gonna tell him?
That you left my house?
That you got your gang back together?
And for what? A high-school dropout reunion?
- You recognize that car?
- Which car?
The one that's been following us
for the last few miles.
That? Oh, yeah. I know that car. That's a
Mercedes S500. That is one sweet machine.
It's an eight bore.
It comes in a 12, which is a beast.
- Lose them.
- What?
- Lose them!
- Lose that car? You can't...
I'm gonna stop, Paul.
This could be the FBI.
The FBl is two cars back.
You gotta be more observant. Left.
I'm pulling over.
They won't shoot us. It's daylight.
Broad daylight is the best time.
They can see better. Right!
We gotta stop. This is a lease.
Hey, it's a goddamn lease!
- Move over. I'll drive.
- Move over where?
- Get in the back seat. Back seat!
- Damn seat belt.
Get over!
- Buckle up, doc.
- It's gonna get worse?
It ain't gonna get better.
Stop it!
Oh, my God.
You think they'll get out?
Yeah, that's James Bond and that
Sea Hunt guy, so they got a good shot.
- I feel bad. Where are you going?
- I gotta take care of this.
- Paul, your parole officer...
- Send him my regards.
- Paul, I'm warning you. If you leave now...
- So long, doc.
That's it. You're on your own now, pal.
That's it. I'm done.
I'm...
...screwed.
So where is he, doctor?
I wish I knew.
Considering I released him into your custody,
that's not quite the answer I was looking for.
He's got something in the works.
Care to tell me what you know?
I don't know anything.
I really feel he's making
an effort to go straight.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yes.
That's why we got two corpses
in the bottom of the river?
Here.
Vitti with Sal Masiello.
Vitti with Patti LoPresti.
Vitti with Eddie DeVol.
Let me know.
I can order you some wallet-size.
I am giving you 24 hours
to find him and deliver him to me.
Otherwise, you're looking at obstruction
of justice and accessory to manslaughter.
- Can I go?
- Sure, but you can't take your car.
We're impounding it as evidence.
- Can I get a ride?
- Have a nice day.
I don't got a lot of time.
They're probably gonna come looking for me,
so we'll go over everything at the club.
Paul, not that I'm questioning or anything,
but what do we need with this Eddie DeVol?
The guy is like a petty larceny scumbag.
Hey, I ain't happy about it either.
But if he keeps Patti off my back, so be it.
- Yeah?
- Mr. Vitti?
- Mr. Bella asked to meet you in makeup.
- Can't. Gotta go.
- It's important.
- I'll talk to him tomorrow.
Here, here.
Tell him you never saw me, okay?
- Paul, excellent, mate. Come here, please.
- I can't talk right now, mate.
I've gotta ask you a question.
Two seconds? Come on.
- I gotta...
- Come on.
- Can we do it later?
- Please. It's important.
Paul, I'm looking for something to do when
my character finds out he's being indicted.
And I was thinking of punching the wall.
But I did that when they killed Uncle Lenny,
and I punched a car...
...actually, it was a van, when Peezee
screwed up the big drug-deal.
So I'm looking
for something different this time.
Something that doesn't involve,
you know, punching anything.
Kick something. Let me know
how it works out. I gotta go.
Paul, wait.
That's really interesting.
- Kick what?
- I don't know. Like, kick a guy in the face.
- Who?
- Anybody, just some guy.
Knock him down, give him a
couple shots in the head and walk away.
- Why?
- Why not?
You're pissed, he's there.
I got friends waiting for me.
My character wouldn't do that.
What else you got?
- I don't know. You could yell real loud.
- Yell real loud?
That's really original.
Shut your fucking mouth.
I don't care what you do. I gotta go.
- What'd you say?
- Wait. What are you doing?
- You can cut that shit out right now.
That was bloody great!
My character could do that.
Thank you.
Jelly? Where's Paul?
Michael. What are you doing?
I'm working for Mr. Vitti.
Yeah, I'm his driver now.
Oh, no. No. No. No, Michael,
you are not doing that. Sorry.
- You keep telling me to get a job.
- Making sandwiches at the Subway...
...not driving a getaway car.
Dad.
No "Dad" about this. He should have
spoken to me before he spoke to you.
All right. Where is he?
I cannot give you that information.
You cannot give me that information?
Look, I promised not to repeat anything
l heard in the car, okay? I took an oath.
You took an oath?
Was there blood involved?
Ben?
What...? What happened? Where were you?
I'll tell you the truth. I was involved
in a high-speed car chase.
- What?
- My car was totally shot out...
...and the men who were
chasing us probably drowned.
- Oh, my God!
- It's not as bad as it sounds.
- When is this all gonna end?
- Tonight. I just have to find him.
Why? A few days ago you weren't even
sure you wanted to be a therapist.
Honey, I have to finish this.
I have to. Understand?
Go.
- Go. Just don't get shot.
- Okay.
- Please.
- All right.
- Hey, Clemenza. Where is he?
- I can't.
You are gonna tell your father...
...or so help me God, I'll kick
the ever-loving shit out of you.
Little Darlings, okay? It's a club in Queens.
- Give me the keys to the car.
- I'm responsible for the Town Car.
- Give me the fucking keys!
- Take my car.
- Okay.
- Here.
Thank you. Bye.
Hi.
Excuse me.
Jelly.
- Hey, doc, what are you doing here?
- Where's Paul?
- I think she likes you.
- I have to talk to Paul.
Man, give her a few dollars.
Hi. I only have a 20,
so could I get change?
Ten, five, singles would be great.
Thank you.
Okay.
Thank you very much for giving me this.
Thank you.
Listen, this is my meter money,
l don't have any more bills, so...
Where's Jelly?
What are you doing?
What do you mean? Blowing off
a little steam. What's the big deal?
Here he is.
- How's it going, Paulie?
- It's going all right.
You know my guys?
Enormous Bobby and Al Pacino?
Al Pacino? That's your real name?
No. They call me that
because I look like Al Pacino.
- The actor.
- Anybody ever call you Carol Burnett?
Why?
Because you look as much like
Carol Burnett as you do Al Pacino.
- What are you looking at?
- I actually see it.
It's, like, right through here,
it's just very much Pacino.
So we're all here?
- We're all here.
- Then let's do this, all right?
- Let's do what?
- Let's go.
You're not telling me something.
I want to know what's going on.
- I'm not leaving till you tell me...
- Get out of here. You're gonna get hurt.
Okay, this is big.
We only got one shot, and there's a million
ways this fucking thing can go wrong...
...so everybody listen carefully.
The Federal Gold Depository
in downtown Manhattan.
Three times a year, a shipment of Gold bars
Goes in a heavily Guarded armored truck...
...from the depository to a vault
in the Federal Reserve...
...to hold for foreiGn Governments
that trade in Gold bullion.
Three o'clock in the morninG,
about eiGht hours from now...
...we're gonna hijack that truck.
All right, everybody look at the map.
This is where we're gonna be.
- What the fuck is this?
- He was listening by the door.
- Hi, guys.
- Get rid of him.
- Hi, Carol.
- You're a dead man, asshole.
Put the gun down.
Put the fucking gun down!
Put the fucking gun down, okay?
- What are you doing?
- What do you think?
- He can make every guy in this room.
- Keep your hands off him. He's with me.
Yeah? What, on the job?
- Gonna start that "yeah, what?" shit again?
- Either he's in or he's dead. Which is it?
I think in is better.
If I had a vote, I would vote in.
- He's in. He's my responsibility.
- Okay.
No more surprises. And from this
moment on, no one leaves my sight.
Got it?
Here, try this on.
- Is this bulletproof?
- You better hope so.
See if it fits under your shirt.
I could fit you under my shirt.
Got anything smaller?
What are we, a Bloomingdale's?
Hey, nobody knew you were coming down.
You're lucky to be alive, you know.
We're all gonna be lucky to be alive.
This plan is crazy. It's stupid.
Hey, hey, watch it.
Crazy, but not stupid.
You wanna stay alive?
You do everything I tell you, keep your
mouth shut, and try not to pee your pants.
- Can you handle an M-16?
- You mean shoot it?
No, twirl it like a fucking baton.
- AK?
- No.
- Kalashnikov?
- Jelly.
- Stop me when something hits your fancy.
- Well, can't I just use that?
Yeah. This brings back fond memories.
- Use it in good health.
- Thanks.
Great.
Cold. Cold.
- Check everything in there.
- Talk to the doc, I think he's caving in.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm great.
I'll try to get you out before
the shit goes down.
- Just don't flip out on me, okay?
- Right.
Here they come.
Big, big mistake.
- They're here.
- Go. Go! Go! Go!
Are you fucking kidding me?
Move the truck!
Where you going?
It's a setup!
Everybody get down, watch the walls!
Watch the walls and the gates!
On my command,
get the drivers back in the trucks.
You're gonna take the rear.
I'm gonna take the point.
We're gonna back
these fuckers out of here.
- What the fuck?
- They're lifting the truck!
They're lifting the fucking truck!
Son of a bitch!
Hold on!
Hold on, Harold! Hold on!
Going over.
You have got to be fucking kidding me!
Hang on!
- It's not too late. You don't have to do this.
- Let's go. Let's go.
What a day for my balls.
Open the fucking door.
- Where's the keys?
- We don't have the keys.
They've got the keys at the bank.
Keep your fucking head down.
Get over here!
Move. Get the fuck in there.
Here we go.
Take the gate. You guys take the gate.
Get the wall. Climb the wall.
On the wall, guys. Get up on the wall!
Get the gate! Move. Move. Move.
Break through the gate.
Get the ramp.
You know, this might just fucking work.
Go! Go! Go! Get over the wall.
Come on.
10-13, shots fired.
Need some backup.
10-13, shots fired. Shots fired.
Move! Move! Move! Over the wall!
- Get over the goddamn wall!
- You get over the fucking wall!
Fifty bars. Fifty bars is all we need.
Fifty bars.
- Let's go.
- How much is that?
350 an ounce, 16 ounces to a pound,
90 pounds to a bar. Do the math.
- 22,995,000.
- What?
Give or take.
Hit it again!
They're breaking down the door.
Bobby, move up the Payloaders.
Move them up.
So much for not peeing in my pants.
- That's 50.
- All right, pack it up.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Let's get out of here.
We're moving out.
Paul, remember what you said
about not flipping out?
- Yeah.
- Sorry. What have I done?
I had a perfect life,
and I threw it away!
I'm going to prison. That'll be bad.
I have delicate features.
- I'm small. I'm gonna be popular.
- You gotta calm down!
- I can't calm down. I'm gonna die.
- Calm down!
- I can't breathe! I'm suffocating!
- Listen. Relax.
- Get a hold of yourself!
- I can't! We're gonna die!
- We're not gonna die.
- We are! We're all gonna die!
- You feel better now?
- This is all my fault.
I wanted to be there for you.
I really wanted to help you.
I want... But I couldn't
because I'm not good enough.
Ever since my father died, I lost my way.
I didn't think this would hit me this hard.
But, Paul, now I know how you felt
when your father was killed.
We don't have time for this.
- But it's...
- I'm telling you.
- Don't do this.
- It was 10 times worse for you.
- He was killed right in front of you.
- You were just a little kid.
- Don't go there.
- But it's so sad.
- Don't go there. I'm telling you...
- All of his dreams for you died with him.
- There I go. You happy now?
- He loved you, Paul. He really loved you.
- I know he did, and I loved him too.
- Loved him too.
- I know. I know.
Oh, boy, this is bad.
How's the heist going?
Did you really think
you were gonna live through this?
- Yeah. I had my hopes.
- Well, nice work.
- Mr. Rigazzi will be very grateful.
- I thought he worked for Patti LoPresti.
Patti thought so too, but he played
both sides against the middle.
There's only one side
as far as I'm concerned: mine.
What did you think?
I was gonna stand by...
...and let some fucking broken-down valise
like you move back in?
So long, Mr. Vitti.
I can't take it anymore!
That's what I hate
about you fucking sociopaths!
You keep changing the rules
to suit yourselves!
Well, not this time, you antisocial,
misfit piece of shit!
This time
you fucked with the wrong shrink!
You want a fresh one?
This session is over.
Son of a bitch. Ram it!
Take them up and leave them there.
- Nice going. Good plan.
- Shut up.
- Bye.
- Yeah, what?
What's a sociopath?
I don't know.
- Somebody!
- Come on, help us out here.
Come on! This way! Come on!
- They're getting away! Come on.
- Let's go!
Drop your guns!
Drop your fucking guns!
Drop your weapons, now!
- Who the hell is this?
- Cut. Cut. Cut! What the hell is going on?
Drop your fucking guns. Nobody move!
Raoul! Look, if you're gonna
change the script, you have to tell us.
Who are these people?
What are they doing in my shot?
- What are you doing on my street?
- I have a permit!
- Take your permit and stick it up your ass!
- Oh, my friend.
Release traffic, please. Release traffic.
This is like a bloody Chinese fire drill...
Jesus!
- You are in trouble. You are in trouble!
- You are gonna be in federal prison!
Prison? You think I'm powerless?
- Enough. I'm going back to my trailer.
- No, you've gotta stay.
- Move these cars, goddamn you!
- You, please be quiet. I'm trying to think.
- Is there a problem, officer?
- Keep your hands where I can see them.
That's it, we're screwed.
We are so screwed.
You.
Me?
- You're one tough shrink.
- All right.
- Feeling pretty good, huh?
- Yeah, I'm feeling pretty good.
What are you thinking?
I mean, what's next?
Do you go on the run
for the rest of your life?
Do you just go back to Sing Sing?
Or maybe they find you dead in an alley?
- How does this work now?
- Those are my choices?
Hey, doc. Can't you let me enjoy this
for five fucking minutes?
- Must you always be a fucking killjoy?
- Five minutes?
- Five minutes.
- Okay. Five minutes.
- And then what?
- And then you'll see what.
- I'll see.
WWEN news time, 8:06.
Seventy-two deGrees.
A quick resolution to last niGht's
spectacular armored-car hijackinG.
FBl aGents,
actinG on a tip from an unnamed source...
...raided the RiGazzi PlumbinG Company
early this morninG...
...and recovered the 50 Gold bars
stolen in the darinG robbery.
Arrested in the raid were reputed crime
family boss Louis "the Wrench" RiGazzi...
...and 11 other hiGh-rankinG
RiGazzi family associates.
The rest of the stolen bullion
was recovered at the crime scene...
...alonG with three hiGh-flyinG hijackers
apparently stranded...
OrGanized crime
has been dealt a serious blow...
...and I'm happy to report to the people
of New York and to the entire nation...
...that this Great city is today
a safer place to live and work.
Questions?
Hey, doc.
- Did you see Patti?
- Yeah. I saw her.
- You gonna be okay?
- Yeah. It's okay.
- She's glad the Wrench is out of the way.
- Good. Good. I spoke to the U.S. attorney.
- What did he say?
- He's happy about the gold...
...and he said he won't come after you.
But you gotta stay out of trouble.
Fuck him.
So one big happy ending, right?
- You gotta admit you feel better.
- Yeah. I feel better. Sure.
Twenty million down the drain.
Why shouldn't I feel better?
- You're grieving, Paul. It's a process.
- It's a process, I know.
It's not easy. But you gotta know
you did the right thing.
You too, doc.
- You hung in there. It took a lot of balls.
- I did what I had to.
You were a monster.
I seen the beast in you.
- A lot of misplaced aggression, that's all.
- Listen.
I'm gonna send you after people
that I don't like.
Give them a little psychology,
then beat them up.
I wanna thank you, doc.
- You don't have to thank me, Paul.
- You helped me out a lot.
You.
- You're good, you.
- No, I'm okay.
No, no, no. You're very, very good.
You got a gift, my friend.
I'm telling you, you got a gift.
All right, I have a gift.
All right.
- Okay. Okay, doc.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
- Take it easy.
- I'll see you.
- All right.
Hey, doc.
When I was a resident, we used to
actually play with the catatonics.
Just to have a little fun,
it's just so dreary.
Okay, let's just... Okay.
When I was a resident at Downstate...
...we used to play with the catatonics,
just for a few laughs.
Okay.
I'm not hurting you.
- Sorry.
- Marker.
You told her at the drop of a hat.
She's with the FBI.
She needs this information.
I see. And I don't need this information.
Okay.
No. No. Why? Why tell Paula?
She couldn't possibly handle a phone call.
But your name's not Paula.
- Who am I?
- Laura.
Okay.
- Hey, you.
- Coffee?
- What?
- Somebody said something about coffee.
Yeah. That was you.
You said you wanted some.
Yeah.
- "So, what's the holdup?"
- I know.
I'm taking a long time.
I'm taking my moment.
You also took mine.
Here you go. Thank you very much.
Hey, Michael.
Jelly.
Michael!
If I could only get out of this car!
Come on. Who would you...?
Who are we kidding?
- You hated your father.
- I didn't hate my father.
- No, I loved him.
- You hated your father.
You hated him. You fucking hated him.
What the fuck we talking about?
- All right. I got it. I'll stop.
- Good, that was good.
- "Yeah. I can see how touched you are."
- Yeah, I can see how touched...
- That's my line.
- That's your line.
What am I doing here?
What are you doing here?
I came here to tell you
that you have a preliminary...
- Come back and try again.
- I will.
Preliminary meeting. Preliminary meeting.
You have a preliminary meeting
with your parole officer.
Fuck you. Fuck you. It's "preliminary."
I'm from the Bronx,
and it's 4:00 in the morning.
Come in.
Hey, doc, what are you doing here?
- Preliminary.
- Yeah, preliminary.
Come in.
- No.
- All right.
A marker.
You know who was always
a favorite of mine?
The late, great Groucho Marx.
Because he would put stuff on his,
on his...
He would draw them in on his eyebrows
and then...
"That's the most ridiculous thing
I've heard." He would do stuff like that.
Hey, look.
I'm the sheriff of the undersea club.
Salute me, I'm Captain Midnight.
Ultimately, it's just sad.
That's what I've been jerking off to
the last 850 nights, a home-cooked meal.
Yeah, like a nice fucking lamb chop.
A nice home-cooked meal. Like...
- Let me think of a good one.
- A tuna casserole?
Help me.
I just wanted to see it again.
- We still going?
- We're good? Okay. We'll beat it to death.
All right. That was great.
I think we can move on.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org