Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
You know, l ain't a churchgoing person...
...but, l swear,
that's gonna be a thing of a past.
Let him be all right.
l didn't hit him hard,
he should still have one good one left.
Sweetie.
Thank you, Lord.
That's it.
Excuse me, Officer. Can you tell me
where the Pink Cloud Motel is?
Yeah.
Just hang a right out here.
Go down a little bit a ways. Can't miss it.
How would you and your girlfriend, there,
like to race me over?
Come on, guys.
Philo!
All right, wise guy.
-Which station?
-Fourth Street. Why?
Fourth Street Station!
What is it, snookums?
Somebody's bashed into our car,
honeybunch.
We can always get another car.
Come back to bed, sweetheart.
What's that for?
Just in case.
Take her home. Hurry on back.
You wait here.
Over this way.
That's enough.
Thanks, old buddy.
That took guts. l owe you one.
Don't even think about it.
-How long has she been like this?
-All morning. Ain't said a word.
l suppose you'll have to fight, now.
Yeah.
l don't think they're going to hurt her.
l think they just wanted you to fight.
l know.
-Piece of crap, though.
-Yeah.
She's getting on.
l think maybe her brains are, you know,
turning soft.
Jelly, sonny. Jelly.
''Jelly roll killed my mama
''Drove my daddy stone blind''
You're going to church next Sunday.
You, too.
Philo. lt's him.
Yeah?
Jackson, Wyoming. Saturday, noon.
Not until l talk to her.
You are in no position to set conditions.
You heard me.
Nino.
-Philo?
-You okay?
l'm fine.
Don't fight, they don't dare hurt me.
l trust you're not so foolish
as to believe that, Mr. Beddoe.
No, l'm not.
Lynn, the fight's not your concern.
l'll have you out of there on Saturday.
Philo, listen--
We have a deal, Mr. Beddoe?
You'll produce her Saturday noon,
before the fight, right?
Deal.
All right, boys. Belly up to the table.
Get yourself some hair there.
Here. Paint on some eyebrows.
You look like a bunch of freaks.
-You promised me a moustache.
-Cholla. You promised l could be a blond.
l want to be a redhead.
-Give me that brown one.
-l like brown.
Cholla, why don't you tell him
to give me what l asked for?
l love it.
Nobody knows nothing.
l checked everybody l know,
even the sleazies.
They're probably holding her somewhere
near Jackson.
We'll just do little scouting.
Jesus.
Why don't you just shut up
and start passing out them tickets, there.
l ain't got the heart.
You've got enough trouble.
Wait a minute.
You have to give us them tickets.
You have to.
l mean, didn't you see us?
We're lawbreakers.
l mean, we are totally despicable.
We have earned them tickets.
Son, you are a walking violation
of the laws of nature.
But we don't enforce them laws.
Lord.
You have given me these crosses to bear.
l will carry them...
...all the way from Jerusalem to Jackson,
whichever is closer.
But hear me, Lord.
''Though l walk through the valley
of the shadow of death''
l will chew on Philo Beddoe's ass
for my last supper.
l lose.
Excuse me, sir, there's a call for you.
Mr. Beekman.
Hello, Beeky, it's your dime.
Zack? l got a sporting event laid out
for this Saturday.
A fire-eater named Philo Beddoe.
Against Jack Wilson.
Philo Beddoe? Never heard of him.
Melvin, can Beddoe whup Jack Wilson?
Beddoe's good, real good,
but l'd have to give Wilson the edge.
How big an edge?
lf it was my money, 7-to-5,
but 6-to-5 is a fair bet.
l might be interested in 4-to-1 .
Even money, Zack.
Well, l might go 3-to-1 .
l've reserved your suite for you.
l'll be there.
You all saddle up. We're going on a trip.
Jim Martin and his crew are coming in
from Kansas City.
We got contingents coming in
from Seattle, LA, Frisco.
Any takers at 6-to-5?
We got about $30,000.
You know, Jim...
...we may have to go 2-to-1
to pick up the action a bit.
We'll get enough action at 8-to-5.
All right.
-l'll call up Boston and set up a lay off.
-No.
No. There's not going to be a lay off.
Jim.
We could get a couple million dollars
on this fight.
Wilson's not going to lose.
lf we try any funny stuff,
they'll retire us to the Jersey Flats.
No funny stuff. l'm telling you,
Wilson's going to take him.
All we've got to do....
We set up a little lay off.
We take a nice 6, 7out
We walk away with $200,000. No risk.
l'd rather walk away with $2 million.
Yeah.
All right, l'll go along.
But if Wilson loses,
you better have snowshoes.
Because north of the Arctic Circle
is the only place we'll be safe.
Welcome to Jackson, Mr. Wilson.
lt's a great honor to serve you.
l'll take you up to your suite myself.
Here, let me take this.
There are three parties in progress,
one of which started yesterday afternoon.
lf there's anything you need, anything.
The hotel does allows pets in the room.
lf you understand my meaning.
l don't keep pets.
No pets, no booze.
-l can read.
-And no parties.
That's Aunt Hortense.
The last party she was at
was Teddy Roosevelt's inauguration.
-ls she your aunt by blood or marriage?
-Blood.
l'd be careful about having any children
if l were you.
Always am.
That's the fifteenth private jet
this morning. What's going on?
Bare-knuckle fight.
California boy named Philo Beddoe's taking
on some monster from the East Coast.
-l ain't seen anything in the papers.
-Strictly illegal.
No referee, and the fight won't end
until one or the other's half dead.
Oh, my God.
-l think l'm doing something wrong.
-You're doing just fine, hon.
But we've been flying upside down
for 15 minutes, Zack.
lt takes a little time to get the hang of it.
Don't be so hard on yourself, hon.
Like the ride at the fair
where everything falls out.
-l hope so.
-You're terrible.
-You can't drink upside down.
-Sure, you can.
-Here, try it.
-All right.
lt worked.
You'd be surprised
what you can do upside down.
Surprise me.
l'll take the south side of town.
You take the north.
-What are we looking for?
-l don't know.
Keep your eyes out for anything peculiar.
And keep Aunt Hortense out of sight.
Why, you're Philo Beddoe.
-Yes, ma'am.
-lt's him!
-He's looking too good.
-Too good by half.
Excuse me, ma'am.
We can't get decent odds on you
looking that good.
We're trying to find some fool
who will give us 2-to-1 .
Try to look a little more peaky, would you?
Excuse me.
-Sorry.
-You damn fool!
-Let me see that hand.
-What?
Wiggle your fingers.
You could have broken that hand
and made paupers out of all of us.
Sorry.
What are you standing here gabbing for?
Get on back to jogging.
-l think l might do that.
-Wait.
No booze, no parties. ln bed by 8:00 p.m.
You can count on that.
l do.
Did you all see that?
The way he grabbed me with one hand
like l was a feather?
Son of a gun, boys, we're going to be rich.
We're already rich, Zack.
Mind if l jog with you?
You work for some pretty strange folks.
Who l work for is my business.
They got my girl.
They're running together.
Talk about beef on a hook.
-l got $40 on Beddoe.
-You're on.
l didn't know.
l didn't say you did. l just said
you worked for some strange folks.
Well, their business isn't mine.
l never said it was.
We're even, remember?
Jim.
Tony Paoli's on the way up.
-Poor little Tony, he never learns.
-Not junior, senior.
-Big Tony?
-Big Tony.
What is he coming here for?
Mr. Paoli. What a pleasure to see you.
l hear you ain't laying off any of the action.
Not so far, no, sir.
You got guts. l admire a man with guts.
So l says, ''Big Tony,
maybe now's the time you go out...
''...and make a little bet with this
high-roller Beekman with guts.''
$100,000?
Mr. Beekman.
You and l are not men
who deal in five zeroes.
-He means six zeroes, Jim.
-''He means six zeroes, Jim.''
Of course, l have to cover it.
Of course.
Give us a look, sweetie.
Come on, honeybunch.
Show us those big blue eyes.
He's a menace.
Goes around peeking in windows.
Ogled at me last night while l was
getting it on with two young beauties.
Clyde has no interest in human sex.
What were you doing,
getting it on with a couple of apes?
Get out. Out.
Let's go.
-The fight ain't on till noon.
-l know that.
l found where they're holding Lynn.
Best to hit them when they move her.
-What's going on?
-He found out where Lynn is.
Let's go.
l know they're packing heat
and they might use it.
l'm his friend and Clyde's his friend.
We go.
Hop in there, kid.
Right turn, Clyde.
-You all right?
-l'm fine.
Why don't you get the cops
and the ambulance?
-The cops ain't part of the bargain.
-All right, just the ambulance, then.
That bullet was mine.
l like being a hero, too,
sometimes, you know.
Well, you're doing a good job with it.
Look, l just saved you guys' asses
from the slammer.
So now they belong to me.
But if l ever see you again,
l'll come and collect them.
You just get in this car and
keep driving west, until you see the surf.
Got it? Move.
-l owe you one.
-No, we're even.
Your hairy friend back there
saved my skin for me.
-We're even, then.
-You're not going to fight, are you?
Well, if l don't, it's a forfeit.
A lot of people bet money on me.
Not all of them are rich.
lf neither one of us showed up,
then there wouldn't be any fight.
Then all the bets would be off.
That's something to think about.
Wilson! He hung up.
Well, that's it.
Neither of them are going to show.
-All the bets are off, then.
-Damn it.
l spent a lot of time,
a lot of money setting this thing up.
Well, you better let
the sporting folks know.
-Are you going to fight?
-l don't know. That depends on Wilson.
You want to stay with Orville?
On your way out, could you kind of
tell the nurses what a hero l am?
-Why didn't l think of that?
-ls that the hero?
That's him lying right there.
You're a good man, Philo Beddoe.
That hurts right here.
-Young man's got a real healthy appetite.
-That he does.
l don't think we can end it even.
l don't think.
But then, on the other hand...
...l don't have any great desire
to make Beekman rich.
Did you figure you would?
l figure.
But then, l guess we'll just have to find out
if l would have or not.
l guess.
Real shame.
-lt would've been the fight of the century.
-Sure as hell would have.
l blew a $100,000 deal to get out here
for this fight.
Hell, it would have been worth it.
Wilson would have taken him.
-The hell he would have.
-Who cares?
Get up there.
Look at this.
What?
Let me see.
All right, you kids,
what are you doing here?
l said, what are you kids doing here?
Come on. Move back.
lt's on.
The fight.
Jackson Base, this is Car 2.
The fight is on. Here.
Breaker, 1-9.
This is your good news channel.
lt's on! The fight is on!
Did you hear that?
What are you waiting for, dummy?
Aren't you going to have any? Come on.
Yeah?
-Jim, the fight is on. They're fighting!
-What time is it?
-1 1 :50.
-All bets don't cancel until noon.
That means all bets are still on.
Come on, lets go!
lt's on!
-What?
-The fight.
lt's on. The fight's on!
Hey, Cholla. What are we doing on foot?
-l told you. The cops pinched the bikes.
-Yeah, but what for?
Who's head of this outfit anyway,
you or me?
Fighting?
Come on.
lt's right around the corner,
and we'll be ringside, boys.
Come on!
Kill him. You heard me. Right now.
Listen up.
That's Beekman's hoods up there.
They're gonna kill Beddoe.
Cholla, that's great.
Let's give them a hand.
You twit!
l sold all our bikes and put
everything we had on Beddoe to win!
Cholla, how could you?
We been at war with Beddoe
for over a year.
War is war, but business is business.
lf Beddoe losses, we are flat busted.
Hell, yeah, business is business.
Don't you stand there, you freaks,
go get them!
We could end it here, you know.
Even?
No, you owe me one.
-Hey, is it over?
-l don't know.
Think l'd buy that while l'm still standing?
No.
lt's broke.
That's it.
-No, it ain't.
-That's it.
-His arm's broke.
-Philo broke his arm.
Stop this. lt doesn't matter.
-lt matters to me.
-Beddoe.
We're even.
l owe you.
Come on. Put that spaghetti down.
l knew he would do it.
You get your money's worth.
-Was l out?
-Yeah.
-How long?
-Long enough.
That's it, then.
That's it.
-That was one hell of a fight.
-Better get that arm fixed.
-l think we better get out of here.
-You're right.
He's paying off 30 cents on the dollar.
But he offered us 40 cents
if we promised not to touch him.
-Did you promise?
-Of course.
Good.
Now go back there and kill him.
Hell, Zack, 30 cents on the dollar
isn't gonna pay for the cost of that plane.
lt don't matter.
lt's worth it to pay for the privilege
of seeing a fight like that.
Sure as hell is.
l should say.
l'm gonna have to call you
on your bloomers, ma'am.
Oh, damn it. Chivalry ain't dead in Texas.
Thank you, ma'am.
-What's the matter, who is it?
-Tony's boys.
What are they coming here for?
-What the hell do you think for?
-Yeah, but they promised.
Come on.
Hurry up. Grab the case. Come on.
Hey, Beekman, l believe you owe us
another 70 cents on the dollar.
Come on, get out of the way, you punks.
You really don't know who we are, do you?
Tell him who we are.
We are the Black Widows.
We are feared throughout the land.
-Jim.
-Let's get the hell out of here!
You see how they lit out of here
when they found out who we were?
Didn't l tell you l'd make you great?
-But we sure got screwed, man.
-Right, Dallas, we got screwed.
Not quite.
And l'd check that case if l were you.
l got a telegram from Ma in Bakersfield.
She's at another revival meeting.
What are you going to do,
you going to head back East?
Yeah, l guess so.
California ain't such a bad place.
Well, l'm not all that wild about it.
But l do like the people.
And the music is great.
Thank you.
What about Beekman?
You going to have any problems with him?
Beekman's the one with a problem.
He can't cover the bets.
-Orville, what do you say?
-l'm staying here in Jackson. Medical care.
l love the place and l love the people.
Right, Clyde?
Right, Clyde.
Hey, Beddoe!
Are you talking to me?
Yeah, l'm talking to you.
We got a little debt to settle.
We do?
$40.
Now, l believe that makes us even.
l believe so.
You know, that was one hell of a fight
you put up over there.
l mean, one hell of a fight.
l understand you boys
had a little scuffle yourself.
Yeah, wasn't half bad.
These things don't look bad
when you get them on straight.
No, they look real good.
You take care, Beddoe.
You do the same.
Let's go.
-Are we rich, Widows?
-We are rich!
What do we have here?
New girlfriend, Clyde?
Very nice, but we may have trouble
getting you this one.
We'll do what we can, boy.
l thought l recognized you
and your hairy friend.
Because of you,
l'm stuck out here in this steam bath.
l'm citing you for speeding
and reckless driving.
What? We were only doing 50.
-l'm impounding this truck for evidence.
-lmpounded for what?
Evidence for transporting an animal
without certificates of ownership...
...and certificates of inoculation.
Nobody owns Clyde. He's a free person.
The animal goes to the kennel.
The truck goes to the police yard.
l'll be roasting out in this desert
for three years because of you, Beddoe.
You're going to pay.
Right turn, Clyde.
Onward.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org