Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Far Far to the North lies an unforgiving land
where the nights last several
moons and the winters are cruel
This is the land of the vikings
Here fierce chieftains lead their warriors
to battle
Charge
Hello?
Anybody Home?
By Thor
It's always the same.we raid and nobody
is there
Are the gods angry with us?
Here the words of the gods
Half a loaf of bread is better than none
-The early bird gets the worm
Kryptograf,make yourself useful for once
-Odin sa....Ah
How do our enemys vanish without a trace
Odin says that
fear lends them wings
What did you just say, Kryptograf?
This thing called "fear" gives
them the power to fly?
No,it was just a figure of speech, th..
-Imagine if we could fly
Excuse me, i thing you have misinterpreted what i ..
we need to find the champion of fear,
who will teach us this magic art
with fear giving us wings nothing
will stand in our way
Soon we can boast to the world ,
Vikings doall about fear
We are the most chicken hearted,
jelly belly cowards of all
Cowards,cowards ...
Cowards, cowards ...
I will give anything to whoever
brings me that champion.
Anything?
Kryptograf,can you do it?
Odin says that the champion of fear is..
located right..
right ..
Right there
ASTERIX AND THE VIKINGS
But where has the finger of fate pointed?
A village of sted fast Gauls ,
the last hold-out against the Roman Empire
sharing mutual respect ,
harmony and understanding
-Hey Obelix.
-So.. Asterix..
..anything exciting happening today?
-No not really
-Hey ,any trouble from the Romans?
-No , i'm afraid not
-You say my fishes roten?
-It;s more than roten, it's a health hazard
-I feel like something is missing around here
-I don't know what
-Maybe a good fish fight
-Actually i think there is a fish
fight going on right now
There is?
-Want to join in?
-I suppose so..
-But Obelix no stones ok?
-Well at least they are fresh
Stop the fight
-stop i say.
Stop it
I hold in my hand a letter from
my brother Doublehelix
the renouned warrior, the famous
hero of the battle of Gagovia
who fought side by side with
the great Vercingetorix.
But what's the news?
A..Oh yes. He is sending his
son Justforkix here from Parisium
Now ..you are my two finest warriors
I'm giving you the job of
training Justforkix to be a man
We will make him the greatest
warrior Gaul has ever seen
We must prepare a grand feast in his honor
Allright people you know what to do
Hey dudes
So..are you? ..
of course you are
Justforkix
This is Justforkix ,son of my
brother Doublehelix
the renouned warrior, the famous
hero of the battle..of Gre
Yeah Yeah big deal..
These are my finest warriors
Asterix and Obelix
They will be in charge of your training
Hello
Hey look over there,is that your bird?
Yeah,that's SMS:
Short message Servicix
I send SMS to all my babes
i guess you are not in the new
technology out here in the sticks
Hey ,what's for dinner?
We have prepared an exquisite dinner..
-This fishes aren't very fresh
I told you so..
-Not fresh? why you..
I think its great about Parisium
24 hour time
well you know whoping all
night..that's pretty cool
Well you want some wild boar?
Oh yeah ..no .i don't eat meat,just vegetables
Vegetables?
You will understang i bang the boar myself
come on..
Try a peeny weeny bite
When i was your age i ate
nothing but boar
Boar pudding ,Boar pud-pie,
boar cake with marmalade
Don't force him, he will turn them off
Asterix look at him
you see how skinny he is?
If we want to make a warrior out of
him we've got to get him to eat
Ah..man this really is the sticks
Kakofonix,αν συνεχισεις να τραγουδας
θα τραγουδας στις τουαλετες ανδρων
Barbarian
you wanna dance?
-To this? no way..
Keltic music is like ancient history
So what's like..groovyright  now?
Let me show you how
we get down and dirty
He he are you in the flow bro?
Oh yeah i am down and dirty pal
Are you sure you pied everything Olaf?
your mace a change of under armor?
Dad please this is my ..34 or 35.. raid
Honey come here a sec
-Yes dear
While you are out pilleaging the barbarians
don't forget to drop by their temples
and pick up a pair of sandaliers
Yes dear.
-And here  is the list of furniture i want..
I want a full selection of economical but
stylish tables ,desks ,bookcases
and cabinets in oak,pine and tik ,
they are easily assembled
You've got that?
Yes Vikea
Oh and we can use a new
pair of matching skulls
I'll look out for twins
Ok.is it time to go? i am all ready..
Abba, i have told you 100 times
thios is not a pleasure cruise , it's a business trip
Daddy please...pretty please..
Let me come with you just this once,
and then i'll never bother you again,i promise
Well you...
Wai..Absolutely not
No women and no children abroad
Why?
-Don't argue, i have spoken
By Thor and Odin put together
And don't you dare the bazooka
onto me young lady
I'll make you another list
No women ,no children on board
Being a girl sucks
Κωπηλατήστε
Κωπηλατήστε παιδια
Justforkix
It's time to start training to
become a mighty warrior
It's not even noon yet .
leave me a bit ..
-Obelix.
-May I?
Pi..Pi.. Pirates..
Ga..Ga..Gauls
Being a man sucks..
Gentlemen how is my nephew doing?
Fantastic ..he is doing great
Well..great may not be the word exactly..
Oh yeah,he is doing really great.
Let's just say we are doing our best
Mina bring him in..
-Go on..
No.No not them.
Please. Please do
not leave me alone with them
Is that what you call fantastic??
Great progress?
I gave you a mission to make
a man of him
Nobody asked me if i wanted to be
a man
That's enough..you'll carry on
And you two had better find
something he likes to do
Ah..it's ready
Are we getting ready for a party or something?
-Sort of..
But first you need a little pick me up
WOA..thanks sonny
I'm not drinking that!
it's not organic
Hey wait..wait..it's good for you
-Wow..look at him go
It will make you manly.
It will pull hair out of your chest
You don't have hair on your chest..
Come to think of it..Neither do I
Obelix
Take..
Salmon or Boar?
Salmon,Boar?
-Salmon
Salmon ,Boar?
Salmon
You know.. i don't know you
-Yeah
Abba,what are you doing here?
I said you can't come
I am not staying at home any more..
Do you think its right to treat
women like slaves?
Yeah..
One day we are going to be equal to men..
-Yeah..
Are you finished?
No i am not finished..
Women want to fly too.
We want to learn fear..
We can be just as scared as men
Who is this new guy.
-That's my daughter cod-brain
Your daughter is a man?
Land ahead
Al right men.Everybody back at their seats
and fasting your seat belts
We are getting ready for landing
Guys..I am really not sure about this..
Just relax.It will be fan.
You know..everybody is going..
Is this where the party is?
-You can say that..
Long live Pax Romana
What is that?
Caesar for ever
That's Oliaginus.He is new around here..
Can i take this one?
No..leave him to the kid..
Yes asterix leave him to the kid..
All right all right take it easy
Would your highness care to
do the honours?
On three..
-Are you crazy?
One..
-I am a pacifist
Two..
-I am not going to fight anyone
Three
Yeah..you did it first
one down
They are animals
Let me out of here.
-Second door on the right past the tent
Thank you
Hey the kid is getting into it
-I knew he would like it
Crazy..they are all crazy
Vikings..Aahh
At last my fist raid, i can't wait
Don't even think about it,you
are staying on board until we are back home
What?You can't do that..
Yes i can
I want stay, you can't make me
Yeah..
-Oh Yeah?
Yeah
All right men.You know why we are here
but there is going to be no killing and
plundering this time
Rather than slaughter them we
must observe them and get what we came for
Find the champion.
Then we can slaughter them.
Olaf.Over here..
You are sure you got the plan
-Yeah..
No..I am sorry dad,but it's a very
complicated plan
Sit down and i'll try again
Here..this is you.
-I am a rock
Just pretend this is you
-OK
Now..here is the champion of fear
see how he is shaking and trembling
Now if you capture the champion
of fear like this
then you can ask chiftain
Olaf for anything you want
Ah..
What do i want?
-Ah..the chiefs daughter..Abba
Looks like a rock
There..it's a girl.
What am i supposed to do with her?
Marry her.
-Why?she took my hair
Because the chief doesn't have a son
whick means his son in law
is next in line to be chief
Do you understand the plan now?
Yeah..
I am a rock
Well i think that went rather well
Yeah ..i thinkit was good for the kid
anyway .He was really enjoying himself
Obelix,Asterix  Help,they are coming..
Ah,there is our boy
-Yeah look at him run
They are landing.The Vikings
are landing on the beach
We have to tell the others
because it's too late
Take it easy.One invader at a time
That's right ,they have to take their time,
we were fas..
We have to go..what are you waiting for?
What?you wanna go now?
Aren't you listening to me?
Don't you know who the Vikings are?
Sure,the ruthless savage warriors
who destroy everything in their path.
Just because we are provential doesn't
mean we aren't with it..
Maybe we should talk to him.
-Yeah.You know what i think he is hungry.
I'll go get a boar.        -No i think
it would be better if you talk to him
All right listen,you mustn't get scared
we are here for you
Remember we are Gauls,we don't
know the meaning of fear right?
Well..i do.I am an expert.
I am afraid of everything
I am like ..the champion of fear
There there, look at you a big tough warrior
you aren't frightened now, are you?
I guess not.It's not so bad now,
as long you are here
Spoil sports.
We've better get going
We don't want to miss launch
Yeah,we will continue the training tomorrow
You will see.You can easily
become a warrior.No problem
No.It's hopeless
What?You saw the champion?
and he knows the meaning of fear?
Yeah he does.I observed him
But when he is with those stupid Gauls
he starts to forget it
He is not too bright. You idiot..
You looked at the right man and didn't grab him?
You think  you had to
take notes?
Rescue the champion before these
Barbarians drain the fear out of him
Justforkix i have been trying out some
of those dance steps
You know..the one's you showed me
And i am not sure i got it right..
Well you are right about one thing..
you don't got it right, look..
Your left foot goes behind your right,
like this
Oh yeah,yeah it's better
-Yeah,much better
Repeat that a few times after i am gone,
and you'll rule the dance floor in no time
Gone?Justforkix are you leaving us?
Yeah
Hey Justforkix ,hold on a second
Here kid,i've got something for you,
this is my finest stone
I was planning to give it to you as
a graduation present
You know,when you became a warrior
But you can have it now. You can keep on
training with it back home if you want
If you try to lift it every day, i am sure
you will make it
I don't think so..it's impossible
How can you know it's impossible if
you don't try?
What are you doing? You are
encouraging him to leave
It's his own decision to make.
No it isn't,No it isn't
What about our promise to Majestix?
What about the honor of our village?
We can't force him.It isn't right.
-Well it's not right to..
Yeah..faster..
Oh look at that..the axle is shot
Stupid stone
This is great, it just keeps
getting better and better
Who is there?
Hello?
Obelix?Asterix?
Is that you?
Hello?
Oh,it's just the wind
The wind and some squirrels,
tiny winny harmless squirrels
and a Viking
Well he doesn't want to be here,
and we don't want him here
I guess it's better this way
Ah..I feel pretty good about it.
Don't you Obelix?
I guess so..
Oh boy ,i am getting hungry
Oh..I sure could use a couple of boars,
what do you say?
I am not hungry.
You are not?Come on..
A couple of nice juicy boars..
You know,he never even got
to taste that wild boar
I guess we didn't make him feel all that
welcome if you think about it
He was really improving too,with just
a little bit more training
I could have made a real warrior out of him
It's going to be really quiet around
here now
SMS?wha..what?wait..
what's happening?
Justforkix had an accident
Ah this foreign charrioted junk.
You are putting
a tiny little stone and they bust
Strange though that he went of into the
forest on his own
Even stranger ,he left my present behind
Obelix,look
Justforkix's sword
He's been kidnapped by the Vikings
Oh no..
We have to tell the chief
Asterix,Obelix ,guess who has dropped by
my brother Doublehelix
the renouned warrior,the famous hero
of the battle of Gregovia
Don;t forget the battle of
Parisium. HAHAHA
Well i only have a few minutes before i
have to go of to Parisium
so i'll just drop by and say hello to
Justforkix and..
No..you can't see him
It's impossible.
-He is far far away
On a field trip. It's a training program.
lot of training in the programm
Are we talking about the same kid?
That's a good one
I'll return at the next full moon
He'll be back from his field trip by then.
I suppose..
See you men later..
The Vikings?
I make a sallom vow
I shall go to the land of the Vikings
and bring back Justforkix before
the next full moon
Me too.
-That's good
My nephew's life and the honor
of the village are in your hands
Don't worry, we'll get him
back in time
Asterix,take this potion with you
for the dangers ahead
Go North, until you hit the
first intersection of land
Turn left
-Left
Then to the right, and go straight into
the next shore
Then turn left. - Left
and go right after that..
Then you want to..
Hey..what was that?
Just follow the North Star
Right.Got you.North star.Ok
Wait..wait ,before going on
your epic journey
you can't leave without a farewell ballad
No..No..
-But i insist
Farewell..
-Lok be with you
What's all that?
Ahm..survival rations
He doesn't look too smashed up
Mercy!
-Mercy?what's that?
Must be another one of their
strange inventions
He is good
Tie him up.
I don't want him flying away
NOOO...
I'm hungryy..
Yeah..well ,maybe you shouldn't have eaten
all the survival rations on the first day
I can't help it,
when i am worried i eat
How much further is it?
-I don't know Obelix
The fog is hiding the sky,
i don't know where the North Star is
Anything else for that matter
SMS
I thought i have lost you.
We'll get out of this right?
Hey..cool bird,
It's yours right?
Yeap,sure it's mine allright.
-Are you the champion?
My name is Justforkix. Who are you?
Oh,yes.I am sorry.
I am Abba
Would..would you help me?
Yeah if i can..
-Ok
Yeah..thanks..that's nice
You are cold?
-No not cold..
Afraid..
You are so lucky..
-Lucky?
To be able to fly..
-Fly?
I'd love to glide over the sea like a bird
and rise higher and higher
right up to the sun
Will you teach me?Please teach me..
Tell me your secret
Well..if you help me get
back home i'll give it a try..
What are you doing?I told you 100
times not to talk to strangers
Sorry..
-Not you!!
Dad..thanks for embarrasing me
in front of the hostage
I'm still hungry!!
-No kidding!
Asterix?Do you really think the North Star
is still up there?
Above the fog i mean..
-Ha ha..unless you ate it yes..
Obelix,you just gave me an Idea
Did you see it?
-No try again
That way Obelix..
So when are you going to talk to
your father about setting me free
As soon as you teach me to fly..
Oh yeah..That..
I was just wondering..
What's your attitude about people
who promise something..and..and..
..then..
can't deliver all it..
Oh..You mean a liar?look up there..
What is that?
-The last guy who lied to me..
Daddy took care of him..
Let's raise our skulls to
the champion of fear..
Long live the champ..
I think i'll be drinking out of my head soon
-No silly..
This is how  Vikings welcome guests
So i am assuming this is organic
vegetable juice?
It is vegetable juice allright..
That's organic allright..
Look..
That way..
-Yeah..that way..
Wait..i have an idea
Telegraf..Statograf..Kryptograf
Rifraf..Hafenaf
What's so funny?
You hear that Asterix?All their names end in "af"
Asteraf actually,my name is Asteraf
,Obelaf..
Obelaf..Hahaha
-I don't have you on the invitation list..
Here..right here..
Ok ..are have officially sneaked in
Not now!We have to find Justforkix..
Hey you..come here!
-Wow!He is back up already?
Hey..they are tougher that the Romans,
don't you think?I'll handle him this time..
Ok ..but whatever you do don't get
yourself..
Noticed..
-What's going on here?
Can't i have a moment of piece and quiet
to eat my Wallace ala Crem
Horw do you make Wallace ala Crem?
Oh i t sounds marvellous
It is..
It's just like putting on the creme
Only instead of strawberries,you use..
Wait a minute!who are you?And what
are you doing here?
Well i am Asteraf and this is Obelaf..
-Shut up..
and we are looking for Justforkix
-Ah..the champion
The..champion of what?
-Well..fear of course..
Take a look
Why aren't you dancing with your fiance?
-I am busy
Look..He is in trouble
Hey..leave them alone,they are my friends
-Friends?
Long live the champ..
Well that's great champ,
but now it's time to say goodbye
We are going home, come on..
Say bye bye..Bye bye everyone
Hey i just got here.
Well your father is expecting you at the
village by the next full moon
Oh no..Not dad.
-Oh no.. not dad..
I'm staying here
-He's staying here
Enough already.You are coming with us..
Don't talk to him like that.
You are going to get him mad..
Hey..you are just like my dad.
Don't do this.Don't do that.
Well if your dad says that, it's for your
own good,it's because he cares about you.
My father doesn't care about me.
All he ever wanted was to get rid of me.
If he cared about me so much ,
he wouldn't have sent me to stay with
a bunch of country pumpkins.
Pumpkins?
-Oh..Pumpkins?
You put me through a nightmare.
They treat me the way i deserve.
So just go away ,allright?
I never want to see you again..
Obelix wait..
Don't forget the tip..
Obelix! Wait for me..
Hey..Obelix..
Justforkix.. wait..who are
those two strangers?
Ah.. nobody.
What's the matter? You were having a
great time until they showed up.
It was just a message from my father.
I've got .. problems
You don't understand..
Maybe i understand better than you think.
Don't worry about it.
Come on.. lighten up!
It's past your bed time, go home now.
Beat it!   - Sorry
We should get back to the party..
Yeah..let's go back in
Friends..
I propose a toast ,to the man who brilliantly
accomplished his mission
by capturing the champion of fear..
None other.. than my son Olaf.
Yeah! Long live Olaf..Long live Olaf.
So what does that
big lad of yours want?
Oh.. what?
My son Olaf ,has the honor to
request the hand of your daughter,Abba.
My daughter's hand?
-My daughter's hand?
I could use her skull, but her hand.. i don't know..
What's this all about?
Did you promise my hand to
this Fishface??
It's none of your business.
Are you saying choosing a husband
is none of a women's business?
That's the viking way.
You pick out a girl and drag her
by the hair back to your house.
That's how i met your mother!Nothing wrong
with the good old ways,is there Vagia?
Oh.. well ..you know..beside the near sculping
and a nasty case of road rush from the dragon
It was the happiest day of my life!
Yeah..if i can jump in here for a second.
-I am not marrying that hanaprene
You are marrying that hanaprene,
and that's that!
There is not going to be any wedding!
Yes there is!
Stop her!
Justforkix!    Abba!
-No!
Don't worry Abba i'll take care of this!
As the champion i'm warning you, that I..
Tomorrow would be a
good day for the wedding!
Allright!
But first the champion is going
to show us how he flies!
Obelix! Obelix where are you going?
Are you planning to walk back home?
Yes!
I know how you feel , but just because
Justforkix
Don't mention that name!
I've already forgotten it!
That's my doggy.
That's a good doggy who loves his daddy.
Unlike some others,i won't name!
Obelix ,you can't just walk off!
-Why not?
Obelix. Justforkix needs us!
He just doesn't know it!
Now come back and help me!
I can't after what he said! It's impossible!
That's what Justforkix said about lifting a stone
Allright! Go ahead and frighten us!
Why? So we can fly of course!
Is he stupid or what?
-They are completely crazy!
I said scare us!
Sure.. here we go..
What's that?
-Είναι μια τρομακτική γκριμάτσα!
Όχι ,αυτή ειναι μια τρομακτική γκριμάτσα!!
There has been misunderstanding.
You are frightening me!
Enough! It's time for the champion
to demonstrate his flying skills.
Take him to the cliff.
Justforkix?
Where is everybody?
There is somebody!
Where is Justforkix? Where did they
take him?
I don't know! Tell me.. where he is
or I'll really lose my temper!
It worked!
Showed how to interogate
the enemy into telling us nothing!
Are you ready for take - off?
Roger!
Oh..we have an organical problem, i'll fix it!
It's my teeth! My teeth is shattering!
False alarm.He is in perfect flying condition!
Request permission
for take-off.
-Roger. Launch the champion!
Stopp!! Wait one moment!
What now?
-Look! Thor is giving us a sign!
Oh too late.. it's gone
Enough stall!
I'm beginning to think that he can't fly!
And if he can't fly there will
be no wedding!
He can fly!
-No, i can't!
He is ready now!
-No please!
please don't drop me,i am begging you!
Please!
Drop him!
Amazing! He is flying!
Allright you lilly livered cowards
let's fly off the cliff!
Off the cliff..Off the cliff!
Stop! You.. first of all
you are not scared enough!
and even more important we have
a wedding to attend!
Oh.. right!
Wait!what about me?
Olaf.Olaf!
you have to come too!
This is your WE.D.DI.N.G
O..ok if i have to..
What about the champion?
I believe, it want be long now, to his flying
way back home.
Kryptograf! You are coming or what?
Coming.. chief!
Well, this is really strange!
Maybe fear can make you fly!
You are pretty strong!
Asterix.Obelix!
I am so glad to see you.
I didn't think you'd ever
want to do anything with me again..
after.. you know after
what i said to you!
Was i really flying?
Let's get back to the boat!
-No ! We can't go!
The Vikings think, that i..i..i can fly
so the chief has to keep his promise
to Kryptograf.
And his son will marry Abba
so that i can teach them how to fly,
except that i can't
and.. we have to stop the wedding!
These Vikings are crazy!
-No no.. we are going home!
Sorry.
-Forget everything i just said!
I hate you.
My little girl.
Stop! Turn around. We
have to take Abba with us!
No sir.we don't have time!
Besides we can't kidnap the
chief's daughter!
But she wants to be kidnapped!
Let's give the kid his Viking.
It would make him so happy!
Out of the question!
And don't make any more trouble!
-Hey don't get mad at me
I didn't do anything!
-No?
Not in front of the kid!
If we'd taken Justforkix straight from
the feast
We wouldn't be in this risk!
And why didn't we take him?
Because mr Obelix,had to be a big
baby and run off soaking!
And what about you?
If you'd been nicer to him at the feast,
he would have agreed to come with us!
I am tired of all your if this is..
and if that..
Oh i get it!
Only mr Asterix has any brains!
But mr Asterix doesn't know how to talk to kids!
You think i don't know how to talk to kids?
What do you think Justforkix?
You think i don't know how to talk to you?
Justforkix?
No..Ahh..
Can't make me marry !
No!.
-It reminds me of my wedding day!
You nearly bit my finger off before
we ganged you!
Good times!
You are going to be in big trouble,
when Justforkix gets back!
But he is not coming back!
He flew away!
And i don't think he's ever coming back!
Nobody move! Stop the wedding!
Hooray the champ!
-Justforkix!
What are you doing here?
You were fallin..Ah?
I mean flying away..
Liar! you know i can't...
Possible let this wedding go on.
Justforkix what happened to you?
Get him boys!
Hey! Hands off our kid!
Right now buster!
That's our chance!
Let's go out of here!
Follow them! Kill the champion!
Do you understand?
Kill the champion.
That i understand!
We have to make it to the harbour!
Why do we need a boat?
You can just fly away and take me with you!
Right..sorry..listen..
I'm not scared enough!
Look!
If you touch her , i'll break you in
two.. like this!
Potion is not working any more!
I have to visualize to break!
Like this?
Great!you are afraid!
Fly away! you can carry me with you!
You are still not scared enough?
I'm plenty scared! But..
I... can't fly!
What?
Woah..
Abba! Are you allright?
You lied to me?
You are as bad as all the others!
Abba wait!
I'm sorry! I never meant to lie to you!
It just sort of happened!
Go find Asterix and Obelix!
Now that's what i call the real fight!
Much more fun than the Romans!
You know.. we should invite them down
to invade our village sometime
Oh no! where is Justforkix?
What's that?
Dogmatix. What he say?
What's the message?
It's something about Justforkix being
in trouble
She is too kind to say more!
Nice technique.
That bird has talent!
We better follow her!
Abba , we have to get away!
This is going to be fun!
Don't kill him!
Who is the champ now, ha?
Ha.. Over there!
Our boy is coming along isn't he?
Abba?
Abba..
Olaf! They are coming!
Kill him now!
Where are you?
Hi dad!
The champion.
He is flying away with your daughter!
Hold it right there!
You again!
Stop him, before he flies away!
He is not going to fly away!
He is a liar ,and a cheat and a phoney!
But we saw him fly.
-That's right. We did!We did
It was all a trick!
-See?
That was me! I was holding him up
with a rope. Am i right dad?
You idiot.
That was supposed to be a secret!
He can't fly?
So you were trying to trick me!
You're shaking! Are you afraid?
No.. no chief! Well..maybe a snitch!
Tiny fear..
You are in the right condition to fly!
Odin lied to me!
Fear can't make you fly..
Abba!
Justforkix!
Abba. Hold On
Stay where you are! We're coming!
Flying is the only way out of this..
but that's impossible!
You know a very good friend once told me
how can you know something is impossible
if you don't try?
No! Justforkix..
No...No
Obelix! look....
He did it!
He can fly?
You saved my life!
You see? Did you see that?
DO you see  what he is doing now?
Oh yes.. He is doing good..
he is doing really good!
You see Obelix.It's not fear that
gives you wings!
It's love!
Hello? Vikings?
I have congestion! Very weak!
Needing help now.Please!
A little more boar?
Oh yeah..allow me to pour you
another mug of beer!
No..No..we aren't
going to make it in time! Faster!Faster!
Where is my son?
I told you! He's gone fishing!
No! You said he had gone hunding!
That's right!
Hunding for bears!
Coming from Parisium ,i'm sure you will
appreciate my newest composition.
I want to see my son..NOW!
Hi dad!
I get it! I know my boy allright.
Always after the girls..
And Justforkix fought Olaf with just a
boom from a sail boat!
He was like an one man army!
Vitalstatistix i want to thank
you for what you did for my son!
You should thank Asterix and Obelix.
They did it all!
It wasn't us! It was all your son..
Justforkix..
No i'm not going to shake your hand!
Son.. i'm proud of you!
A little gift for the hostess.
Modern Viking design
Skull muds, lambs, furniture, we make
some really lovely stuff, you know..
And this is fully Automatix,Unhygienix
Geriatrix, and our resident musician Kakofonix.
You hear that? All their names end in "IX". HAHA
Perhaps you gentleman from the North ,
would like to enjoy an original Gaul ballad!
Sure.. Sure.. I'd love to..
Ok.. This is the moment!
No more.. no more..
I feel crazy
My legs are jelly!
What's wrong with me?
Now..that's fear!
If this is fear, ...we can fly!
I was wondering Kalifix,
what's the use of fear?
Kalifix!
What?
i said what is the use of fear?
Fear is what makes us brave
- Untranslated subtitle -
And so for the vikings a new adventure begins
because you have to admit their scientific expedition succeedeed
beyond their wildest dreams
Is that fog?
i hate fog,i cant stand.
I want my mommy. I don't want any fog
Mommy Mommy
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org