Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Sorry. Are you alright?
l'm getting my radar fiixed Monday.
-You live in New York?
-l do.
-There you are! l didn't see you there.
-You are shameless.
-That woman was 6 months pregnant.
-Which is the reason l flirted with her.
lt made her day.
lt made her feel really good.
-So, it was out ofcompassion, right?
-l'm working on it.
-Good, good. What about the other woman?
-Blind.
-Blind... like love.
Let's go for a ride. Why, you're afraid
you're gonna pull a muscle?
No? Come, lets ride the lake.
lt'll be fun.
-l can't. l'm breaking up with you.
-So, do it in the boat.
No.
What's the matter?
My God, you're serious.
lt's got nothing to do with you.
-Really?
-Really.
l can only offer you what we've got...
right now... just this.
Until it's over. And it will be over.
l could've put offtelling you
but it wouldn't be fair...
l don't understand this.
How can you be so sure?
lt's only been a few weeks!
Feelings change. Situations evolve.
You don't even really know me.
Maybe not. But l know me.
l'm sorry.
l'm looking to see a Chilean Sea Bass.
-lt's not on the sideboard?
-No. l see no Bass.
l'm gonna kill that son-of-a-bitch!
Fakir! Did you move my fiish?
l'm talking to you.
Did you move my fiish?
Could it be this one lying here
disguised as an Artic Char?
Artic Char! The other son-of-a-bitch,
Gluckman, who calls himselfthe fiish man.
-Boss, l'm getting pissed.
-l validate that emotion. Netto? Problem!
-Yes, boss.
-Bouillabaisse?
-ln there 20 minutes.
-This pot is empty.
-This pot is bouillabaisse-less.
-Fakir! What did l tell you?
-You got a minute, boss?
-Yeah. Where'd it go?
-Taste it.
-Tumeric.
-No tumeric!
-How much? Three or four?
-Four.
-You're right. Perfect. Congratulations!
Excuse me? l'm here to meet Will.
Ofcourse.
l know, l got it, l got it.
What happened to Lynn?
l believe l baked that cake.
Light up the oven. There's
a fresh bowl of batter at the door.
l'm an easy-going guy, right?
l'm good to my staff. l treat them well.
ls that a mistake?
Because, an occasion, one ofthem has
stepped over the line and said very...
-familiar things about my private life.
-lf l didn'tfeel like...
l was leading these poor
women to the slaughter...
-So, warning you has no effect?
-No. lt's like a Greek tragedy, isn't it?
Guys, l've got bad news.
l'm kicking you out...
so other people may eat.
Here are your checks.
The good news is the bar drinks
are on me. Tommy?
-You got it.
-Thanks.
Lady, what am l gonna do with you?
You're killing me.
-Us? Come on!
-How about l set you up out on the patio?
-Out on the patio?
-Before my bartender leaves his wife.
-l was divorcing her anyway.
-Restrain yourself, Tommy.
Eriko...
-Are you too busy?
-lt's frantic tonight, a madhouse.
-Can you bear with me 2 minutes?
-Sure.
Alright, l'll be back.
We got the heat going now. Billy? The
heat's gonna be up all the way around?
l got this and the champagne
is coming in any second.
Happy Birthday toyou...
Happy Birthday to dear Charlote...
Everything okay?
l'll come back later.
-Finally. l'm sorry. You alright?
-ls that Will Keane? lt sure is.
He hasn't changed a bit. What did you
do, make a deal with the devil?
-l'm sorry, do...
-Come on. lt's Dolores Talridge.
-Dolly? l can't believe it...
-Be careful ofthe cocktail.
-Oh my God...
-l know.
-Time has kicked my ass a little.
-No, don't be silly. You look wonderful.
Will... spare me the bullshit.
Honey, are you feeling alright?
You look sort ofseafoam green.
l'm fiine.
lt's him.
-He's how old?
-Who cares?
lf he's rich as well, you might
have a fiight on your hands.
l want you all to meet an old
chum of mine. He's irresistible.
He's Will Keane. And he owns
this overpriced establishment.
Overpriced? l can't believe you'd say...
Where else are you gonna fiind a...
-beet salad for under 35 bucks?
-l loved the Chilean Sea Bass. Shannon.
-Shannon. Thank you.
-l'm Simon.
-Hi Simon.
-Nice to meet you.
You too.
May l ask whose birthday this is?
The birthday girl happens to be
my granddaughter, Charlotte.
lt's not Katie's daughter?
You bet. She's got Katie's eyes,
hasn't she?
And talent! Forget about it.
Do you know that this kid made
from scratch all these crazy hats?
-They're great.
-Then she got serious with mine.
-Pretty sassy, isn't it?
-Very elegant.
-lsn't it divine?
-You're not kidding about this?
Have l ever lied to you?
No, it's wonderful.
Really wonderful work.
Do you speak?
-Thank you.
-So, you're Katie's daughter.
-You about...
-Twenty-tow and never been kissed.
No, l don't buy that.
Happy Birthday, Charlotte.
-Thank you.
-Great to see you again, Dolly.
-Great to see you, Will.
-Go right in there. There you go.
-Great seeing you. Bye.
-Be still my beating heart.
-Or, is that yours?
-l think it's mine.
He's cute but
he's a little old for Charlotte.
-He's simply fabulous.
-How do you know him?
>From Newport. He's an
old friend ofyour Mom's.
Thanks, Melissa. Good night.
When Will Keane comps Crystal to an
underage girl, l know what'll happen.
She's not underage. She's 22.
-l know her grandmother.
-Tell me you're not gonna date her.
The grandmother? l promise
l'm never touching that woman.
You know what's wrong with people like
you? Too much sex. lt melts the brain.
-Here we go.
-No worry about that around our house.
l'm on your side. l'm the good guy.
l'm sorry. l melt
at least 3 times a week.
-ls he lucky l'm offthe market or what?
-They wouldn't even look at him.
-You hear? They wouldn't look at you.
-You're going to do this, aren't you?
What is it with you two?
l smile at this girl, she bushes from
head to toe. Why would l do this?
Knock it off. You'd kill
to be in his place.
-Okay bitch, l'm ready.
-Not me!
-Can we start with "good-morning"?
-My God, l'm so sorry. Who is this?
Guess.
-You?
-lguess.
-Who'd you think it was?
-My friend, Simon.
He always callme the morning
after to... dish.
-Do you want to talk to my grandmother?
-No, l was calling you.
-You were?
-lgot this littleproblem.
l thought you could help me out. l got a
Benefiit coming up. One ofthose...
black tie worthy cause,
lousy foodkindofthing.
l'd like you to make a hat... for me.
Actually, not me, it's for my date.
l don't wear hats,
except to Yankee games.
The problem is that l don't know her hat
size and l don't want to ask her...
-because it's a surprise.
-Was it the woman you're with last night?
No.
Cause she had an
abnormally small head.
lt might accountfor
the limited conversation.
l could always put in
an adjustable band.
-That'sperfect. Wonderful.
-lt is risky doing it this way.
You can do it. Life rewards the
courageous few. You can do this.
Can you give me
a point of inspiration?
-Like what?
-Like an image. This hat is like...
Like the line ofa woman's hip.
-Okay.
-When can lhave it?
-Let's say... two weeks.
-Great!
-l'llgiveyou till Thursday, 4 o'clock.
-Okay. Wow.
One other thing...
-you say "wow" an awful lot.
-l know.
You're a grown-up now.
-When is thatgoing to stop?
-Soon.
-l'll see you Thursday.
-Okay. Bye.
Wow.
-Mikey, howyou doing?
-lcan'tcomplain.
You're early, aren't you?
ln this soup, you're
better safe than sorry.
-Will Keane?
-Visitor.
He's going to a fancy party tonight.
He's up on twenty-four.
l'll key the elevator for you.
Tony, this was notan ace
Parmesan from Froman's...
Tony, this was more like
a pepperino from Scarsdale...
lknow the difference!
lt's difference price.
-You're late.
-l know.
l'm so sorry. l tried to get a cab and
couldn't. l took the subway and...
Yeah, yeah, it's alright.
What's the point of being beautiful
if it isn't to keep men waiting.
ln fact...
l'm disappointed. l was looking forward
to at least half-hour ofsuspense.
-l could leave and come back.
-Too late.
So, whaddya got?
-Try it on.
-l'm soaked.
lt's alright.
Go ahead. Try it on.
You have to imagine it on your friend.
ls it the line ofwoman's hip?
-ls it?
-Yes.
-What a shame.
-Why?
-She stood me up.
-Who?
My date. She called an hour ago;
said she had a cold.
lt sounded more like
the hiccups to me.
-So, you mean you're not going to go?
-Alone? No, no...
Unless...
What?
No... no...
-Wait, no... wait...
-No. Forget it.
No wait, what were you
going to say?
l don't know. l don't know.
You wouldn't want to go, would you?
Great. Forget it. Thanks.
Thank you very much.
lt'sjust...
-You've got the hiccups!
-Are you kidding? l'd go in a heartbeat.
-You're fabulous!
-Yeah?
Oh dear...
-lt must be me.
-Must be.
-Do you think l'm too old for you?
-No, l collect antiques.
Or l aspire to.
We appreciate it.
l would love to go,
but l'm a disaster.
l think with a little plaster and a
little paint, you're as good as new.
Do you wanna see the dress?
There's a dress?
l'm curious. What made you choose
my restaurantfor your party?
l had to pick a place for my party.
l read that article about you.
-The magazine!
-The magazine.
-lt's so embarrassing.
-No. l liked it.
You don't dance. You float.
That's from my dad.
l used to stand on his feet.
My mom was a great dancer too.
But, you knew what. Maybe.
We danced a couple oftimes.
Now you're dancing with me.
How weird is that?
She was very special.
l had great parents.
l was lucky.
Shall we do this?
Here you go!
-Do you want something to drink?
-Yes, champagne please.
l'll get you one. Sit at the table
and l'll be over in a second.
l had to come. l work at the museum.
What's your excuse?
-A date... sort of.
-With Will Keane, right?
-Yeah, do you know him?
-Only by reputation.
-l'm Lisa Biloy.
-l'm Charlotte.
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you too.
What's he like?
Damn it, l see a huge donor
disappearing. l gotta go.
-Enjoy yourself.
-Yes, you too.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Who was that?
-Lisa somebody.
-Here's to...
-Us!
Some people star to fall
into recognizable patterns.
The next step is that... immediately...
you know people...
inside. And if it's a woman...
it's a romance, forget it. lt'sjust...
this majorly chilling effect'cause
you know exactly in the beginning...
what's going to happen in the end.
What l like about you is l fiind you...
completely unprecedented...
and therefore, utterly unpredictable.
God! That must be a relief.
What?
To fiinally deliver that speech to a
woman and have it apply to there.
Because, coincidentally,
l am all those things you just said.
-Yes.
-And so much more.
My yoga teacher calls me a "unique".
-Come again?
-A unique.
A unique. He's a very wise man.
Are you sure he's not hitting on you?
lt's a woman! You are what
she would call a "typical".
-Really?
-Yes! Really.
l can prove it too.
You want me to?
-Okay, try.
-Alright...
Come here.
l'm serious.
Closer.
Closer...
Close enough?
Yes. l was hoping
gravity would do the rest.
Maybe l am a "typical".
We should go.
l can smell the rain.
When did l learn how to do that?
What should we do, Will...
with this moment that we're in?
Do you look guilty.
l'm thinking.
-You hungry?
-Yep.
Didn't anyone ever tell you
it was bad manners...
to stare at a girl
while she's eating like a pig?
This isn't right.
You... you are...
Young.
Yes, and l am...
Old.
-Older.
-Much older.
Alright, much older.
The point is... l could put this off,
but l genuinely like you.
l want to be clear from the start, so
there's no confusion later on, okay?
What l want to say to you is that...
all l'm able to offer you...
is this... what we have right now.
Nothing more.
Until it ends.
What l mean is..
we have no future.
l know.
l'm sick.
What do you mean?
lt's my heart.
Nobody even thought l'd last this long.
l could've put offtelling you but...
l genuinely like you.
l wanted to be clear
rightfrom the start...
so there was no chance
for any confusion later.
She's the perfect woman. Young,
beautiful and on her way out.
-Notfunny, John.
-l know it's not. lt's sad.
-She's so young.
-No, l mean you're sad.
Even this, as far as it's gone.
You shouldn't be doing this.
-Why not?
-'Cause it's out ofwhack.
lt doesn'tfeel totally out ofwhack.
lt doesn'tfeel totally out ofwhack
to you because you're looking at her.
l'm looking at you and it's fucked.
There ain't a right angle in it.
Alright... l end it.
l don't know.
Make up your mind!
What do you want me to do?
l don't know. Maybe it's a good thing.
Maybe it makes a sad girl happy and
a desperate guy think. Anyway you look
at it, one thing... treat her nice.
What do you mean, "desperate"?
Treat her nice.
-Well, well...
She'll be right down.
She's upstairs, gilding the lily,
so to speak.
-He's here!
-l'm coming!
Now, come on. Do come in.
These are for you, Dolly.
Thank you very much.
They are "Loverly".
Aren't they... lovely?
Care for a "cock-i-tail"?
-Yeah, sure.
-Scotch?
-Neat, please.
-My kind ofguy.
Sorry about the mess.
My maid died 14 years ago...
and l have found it absolutely
impossible to replace her.
What can l say, Will?
Time is a thief.
One day, you're rich as an Arab.
Next day, you're lucky
ifyou can afford pistachio nuts.
lt's funny. Most of us are young for
what? About a minute and a half?.
Not Katie.
Katie will be young forever.
So will the guy she married.
l console myself
with that idea sometimes.
Who'd have thought
what time had in store for her.
l'm sorry. l should have
called after the accident.
Then, on the other hand...
time is in love with some people.
Like you, for instance.
You look exactly the same!
-Please...
-Handsome as ever.
And up to your old tricks...
looks like to me.
-Look, Dolly...
-Leave her alone!
She's sick.
Will, she's really sick.
-What are you guys talking about?
-Nothing.
Just how much you look
like your mom, is all.
Yes... Yes, you do.
Are you ready?
Yes. Bye Dolly.
Don't listen to her.
Have fun!
You gotta look on the bright side.
lf l wasn't sick...
this would not work. There is no way
that we would be sitting here.
We're totally wrong for each other.
l know. l could be your father.
l prefer, Uncle.
Do you think we should break this off?.
Afraid you mightfeel something?
Well, look at it this way.
We can have it real,
which we both know is way better.
You wouldn't have
to pay full price...
because, in a year or so...
l'd bejust a sob story
you could use to bag more chicks.
That is a pathetic characterization.
l don't know. l don't accept that.
The stench oftruth.
"O world, l cannot hold
thee close enough!
Thy winds, they wide grey skies!
Thy mists, that roll and rise!"
lt does feel like rain. You wanna get a
cup ofcoffee, and go to the West side?
No, no. You'd abandon the universe...
and me for a cafe late? No, let's not do
it. Let's not do no thoughtless thing.
We can't talk about
he fact that you're sick?
l'm right here, right now.
Let's talk about you.
-Come on, 49 years...
-48!
All right, 48 years. Come on,
tell me about it. Give it. Share it.
You look at me in a way
that l haven't quite earned.
Then earn it.
Earn it, please.
What do you want me to do?
l'm yours. What is it?
What are you doing?
l'm keeping it.
-This is my watch.
-Yep.
-When do l get it back?
-When you forget that l have it.
Mix this up a little bit...
Sorry...
What?
Your mother used to do that.
-Really?
-Yep.
That's how we met. l was a waiter...
at the Beach Club. Whenever l'd pass
with a tray, she's steal the garnish.
What else did she do?
What do you mean?
l don't know. Little things.
She'd eat her ice cream with a fork.
-Really?
-Really. Yeah.
She wrote great letters...
But she couldn't spell.
She was a McGovern Democrat
but incredibly snobbish.
She hummed all the time.
And Stephen Stills was
her favorite singer.
Who?
Never mind.
What's else?
Considering the times...
she was actually...
pretty straight. l think
she only tried drugs once.
There was a lifeguard
who gave her a hash brownie.
She threw it up all over him.
She laughed just like that.
Words and poetry is what she loved.
She was a "unique".
Okay, you guys.
How about a toast?
Welcome to Charlotte.
Welcome.
Cheers! Thanks, you guys.
You know, call me crazy... but l could
swear your friends like me more...
-than they like you.
-That's altogether possible.
-My friends defiinitely like me more.
-What's your point?
That l'm way outfront
in the love race.
-What? Love is not a race.
-Our love is.
-Our love?
-Yes, we're going for it, aren't we?
Why not?
-Alright, l have to tell you something.
-What?
l never had a date for the benefiit.
-Really?
-Yeah.
l was kind ofwondering about that.
-l made that hatfor myself?.
-Yes.
-You bought that dress for me?
-Yeah.
You did all that so you could
get a hold of me and muss me up?
Yes.
First ofall, you have great taste
because that dress was amazing.
-Thank you.
-And second, you didn't have to lie.
lfyou wanted to seduce me,
all you had to do was ask.
That's not seducing,
that is asking.
Besides - l don't know why - but women
seem to love it when you lie to them.
There isn't a lie in the world
l'd rather hear than the truth.
There she goes again, stepping out
on me and breaking my heart.
Even he likes me more.
You're fiired.
-Come on, it'sjust...
-No! Ouch! Ouch!
l can't believe this!
Breathe, breathe.
Breathe... are you alright?
That's not accurate. Neuroblastoma is a
soft-tissue malignancy, but not a cancer.
Most common in children.
Very rare in young adults.
ln Charlotte's case...
the tumor is in her chest cavity.
lt's growing rapidly, it's proved
resistant to both the radiation...
-and the chemotherapy.
-What about alternative therapies?
Eastern medicine...?
You don't hum this away.
Charlotte is the expert in that area.
Eventually, she'll be treated for pain.
l suppose, as a fiinal effort...
surgery could become on option.
But it's risky. So risky that
Charlotte has signed a directive...
forbidding it,
or any other form...
of heroic intervention.
All right.
Doyou have any idea...
about time?
Ayear. Maybe ayear, atbest.
Real charmer, isn't she?
How are you on
Cambodian money units?
-Are you okay there?
-Yes, thank you.
That's incredible.
Doesn't it look exactly like
something she would have worn?
Who?
"Hope is a thing with feathers
That perches in the soul."
Woody Allen?
Emily Dickinson! Only the greatest
poet ever! Uncultured swine.
We all have our areas. l'm a food guy.
Why don't you ask me aboutfood.
Why are you the food guy?
What is it about the food?
Food... food is the only...
beautiful thing that truly nourishes.
ls that a quote?
That's me.
-Excuse me? Excuse me?
-Yes.
The woman whojust passed
by here and went in the door...?
-Yes?
-lt's not Lisa, is it?
-Yes.
-Lisa Tyler?
Yes.
Could you...?
No. Thanks.
-Hello. Come in.
-Oh, you look so great.
-Where are the girls?
-They're upstairs.
l'm going to run up and say hi.
You're a dog. Oh, man!
There's stuff... in the kitchen.
You want to give the can out to the
trick-or-treaters... when they come?
One, two, three, go! Go!
Ricky, don't laugh, or you're
going to get snot in the water.
-Snot? Where is this snot in the water?
-Can l get you a bone or something?
Don't bite anything
that's not an apple.
Guess who?
-lt's Wonder Woman.
-No.
-Get your hands out ofthere.
-l got it!
-We got the champ!
-Let me give you a hint.
l was the best thing
that ever happened to you.
-lt couldn't be Lynn McHale.
-God! You are really bad!
Lynn! l can't believe it!
-Where are the kids?
-Upstairs in their room.
Keep bobbing for apples in there.
-Just one more.
-Please...?
But then you're going to have to promise
you're going to get in yourjammies.
-Yes.
-You promise?
Which one?
l know, "Butterflies".
"Two butterflies... went out at noon..."
"And waltzed above a stream..."
"Then stepped straight through the
fiirmament... and rested on a beam."
"And then together bore away...
upon a shining...sea."
"Though never yet, in any port...
their coming mentioned me..."
ln my day, you bobbed for the apple...
may there's a nickel in it but...
you eat the apple! Your little animals,
grab the coin and run for the door.
-They're offto by crack.
-Defiinitely.
-Where's my little puppy dog?
-l think he's upstairs.
-There you are.
-Hi.
We werejust up on
the roofchecking out...
-The kids are sleeping.
-John's got this amazing set-up there.
Lynn, l want you to meet Charlotte.
-Nice to meet you.
Something tells me
you're upset with me.
What is it?
l wasjust wondering if...
ifyou had sex with that woman?
With Lynn?
Ever?
-The answer to that is kind ofobvious.
-She's an old girlfriend.
-You knew that.
-l meant... tonight.
-On the roof.
-You're not serious?
You are serious. no!
No, ofcourse not.
First off, it's... it's not
exactly my style. Second...
You have a girlfriend.
lsn't thatfor me to say?
As far as Lynn goes, why would l do
that? lt doesn't make any sense.
l know. l mean,
that's what l was thinking...
we're... so happy...
What would be his reason?
l thought, God, if he did do it,
then you'd at least look... guilty.
And you don't.
You look totally relaxed.
You look more relaxed...
than before the party started.
Well... there you go.
But, you're a womanizer.
You were a womanizer.
-What is that exactly?
-Here we go.
That's a guy who has sex with a lot of
women and is good at lying about it.
Yes. But in this case l don't have
anything to lie about. Nothing happened!
There's something about being sick...
in my heart.
lt's like l can feel every beat.
l'll know ifyou're lying.
Oh, God!
Oh, my God!
-Can you pull over, please?
-Don't do this.
-Charlotte! Charlotte!
-What?!
Look, l never pretended to be...
what l'm not.
-Why?!
All right, fiine, why? Why?
Because l felt like it.
Because nothing stopped me!
What about love?
Why do you have to be sojuvenile?!
lt was nothing.
lt was nothing! lt meant nothing!
lf l could be different... l would.
What about love?
You know what?
This was all wrong. This was a mistake,
rightfrom the beginning.
You're a kid... l'm a creep.
You've got better things to do with
your last... with your time...
then spend it with a man like me.
Look who's here.
The Belle ofAmherst.
l've seen thatface before.
-You have?
-On several... occasions.
All for the same reason.
You said Mom and Will
werejustfriends.
They were friends.
But she wasjust nuts about him.
She never slept with him.
Maybe because she was
an old-fachioned girl.
But she was smart.
She made the big mistake.
She told him how she really felt.
lt was up in Newport at the club.
Labor Day weekend.
Big clam bake.
Well, what happened?
Next thing you knew, he was knocking
up Millie What's-her-name in a cabana.
-Millie?
-Your mother's doubles partner.
Why didn't you tell me any ofthis?
-You know, you could have warned me.
-l could have. But l didn't.
You never talk to me.
You never tell me what to do.
Charlotte, take a good look at me.
You want me to tell you what to do?
Yes! You're my family!
You're my family.
You're supposed to take care of me.
-Where you been?
-Home.
-l called you ten times.
-l had the ringer off.
-l don't get it.
-What's to get? l was hanging out.
-Something happen at my party?
-You were there. We had a good time.
-Come on! What's going on?
-Nothing!
What is it, something with Charlotte?
-We called it quits.
-You're shittin'me!
lt's not exactly we called it quits,
it was a more of, she called it quits.
-What did you do?
-What do you mean...?
-What did l...?
Don't bullshit me. What did you do?
l had sex with Lynn McHale
up on your roof.
You're kidding me.
No, l'm not kidding you.
Charlotte found out.
Now she's gone. Totally.
l'm really sorry you did that.
l blew it.
You can't get her back?
-l blew it.
-So?
So, l just go back to the way l was.
How are you going to do that?
lt wasjust going to get worse.
The more attachment on both sides,
leading to what?
lt's now or later, right?
l leave her a few months
from now, she...
No, this is better.
This is much better.
l wish the fuck l'd never met her.
l hate to tell you, but there's
only two kinds of love stories.
Boy loses girl.
Girl loses boy.
That's it. Somebody
always gets left behind.
Try and avoid that, you'll end up an
old man toasting yourselfat Christmas.
-Listen to me...
-l don't care!
-you're going to die in your own arms!
-l don't care! l want it over with now!
-Mr. Keane.
-Good night, Michael.
You've got a visitor.
She's been waiting almost an hour.
Lisa!
-Sorry to disappoint you.
-No... you surprised me, that's all.
Did you get my letter?
What did you do with it, burn it?
l read it.
-Do you want to come upstairs?
-No, thank you. l'm sorry.
l didn't plan this.
l didn't plan to come.
Peter, my husband
thought it was pointless.
But, as it turns out,
l'm pregnant... just a few months.
-Lisa! Congratulations! That's great.
-Thank you.
Anyway, that made me want to meet you.
l've been a little sentimental
about parenthood lately.
-Do you consider me your parent?
-ln a lousy absentee sort ofway, yeah.
-So, how... how is Millie? Your mother?
-She's great. She's good.
Well, she's a nut. She went to Costa
Rica last summer with some guy.
He owns a charter airline
and wears sunglasses indoors.
l think he's a gun runner, but...
-Do you really care?
-No. No.
l guess not.
What about you? How long
have you lived in the city?
Just a few months.
We moved from Austin.
lfyou hadn't been on that magazine...
l might not have recognized you. l only
have one photograph and it's ancient.
l have one picture ofyou, too.
Just one. Your mother sent me one...
a long time ago.
You must have been about twelve.
You had a horse.
Summer camp. My teeth are
bigger than the horse's.
-l hated that picture. l hate it.
-l don't. You were very beautiful.
And you... haven't changed a bit.
-l should go.
-Why?
l reallyjust wanted to meet you.
And maybe...
-l don't know.
-What? Tell me.
lt's not big deal. l've always had a
fantasy that you were looking for me.
And all you really wanted was
to say that you were sorry.
Lisa, l am.
Hey, can l... Can l call you?
How did you get in here?
Dolly.
Would you mind leaving now, please?
l need to talk to you.
l think you've wasted
enough of my time.
What l did was... very wrong.
And stupid.
l have no excuses...
l did what l did because...
-l was scared.
-You were a coward!
Can you forgive me?
You betrayed me! For what?
Because you got the shakes?
-l was scared.
-You don't think l'm scared?!
You don't think l'm hanging onto
my courage by my fiingernails!
Don't touch me! Get away from me!
Get out of here!
Just go!
You're not good enough.
l know... l know l'm not.
l just...
Can you let me love you?
Please.
Please. Please...
Please let me try again.
l'm so tired.
"The stars are as soft
as flowers and as near."
"The hills are webs ofshadow..."
"...slowly spun."
"No separate leafor single blade...
All blend into one."
l love you.
We did it... that was great.
-Bye!
Are you jealous?
-You think...? l am notjealous!
-Yes you are!
Do l look jealous? l am notjealous.
l'm a littlejealous.
-Wait, check me out.
-Excellent! Go! Go! Go!
Judges give it a ten!
A perfect ten!
Charlotte!
Doctor!
-Mr. Keane...
-Tell me.
The repeat MRl and CAT scan
show interval progression.
-The tumor's grown.
-Yes.
Considerably. lt's begun to obstruct
the outflow from her heart.
l'm sorry, l wish there was...
There's very little we can do.
We may be talking about weeks.
-Weeks?
-l'm sorry.
-You said she had a year!
-No, l said a year at best.
That's not good enough!
You said a year!
-l want to have a year!
-This is inappropriate.
Alright, sorry, sorry.
You said there would be
a point when surgery...
-might be an option.
-lf Charlotte agrees to it.
Let's assume that she did. When
would this operation take place?
When it's clear we're losing her.
-Would you perform it?
-l am not a surgeon.
The point is notfiinding someone
who's qualifiied.
lt's fiinding someone who's qualifiied
who is willing to do the operation.
-Hey!
-Hey.
-How are you? You okay?
-Yes.
-How do you feel?
-Stoned.
You're killing my hand.
Charlotte, there's something l would
like to talk to you about.
Don't. Heavy. No heavy.
Sibley and l have been talking...
about surgery.
About the paper you signed.
No violins. Come on.
l'm fiine.
Woody, you're the head ofsurgery...
ifyou can't help me, who can?
Are you trying to tell me that in all
of Mt. Sinai, there is not one single...
Yeah, Sibley told me that.
The 30th. Yeah, fiine... blank.
Right. Got it. Thanks. When will
the doctor be out ofsurgery?
This is urgent. l have a friend
who says she's one ofthe few doc...
l'm sorry. Thank you.
Please, l don't... speak German.
Please, l'd like to speak to a doctor.
Where's the doctor?
He can't be in surgery for a week
and a half. No! You do not hang up!...
She doesn't have long.
-Weeks. Maybe less.
-And they can't do anything for her?
No, her doctor says when
it's hopeless at the end...
...surgery could be an option.
Heroic surgery, she calls it.
That's why l'm out looking for someone
to make sure that when the times...
comes, it's a hero that performs it.
l haven'tfound anybody yet though.
l can'tfiind anybody who's even
willing to attempt it. l will!
l'm going to fiind someone
because l can't lose her.
lt won't happen.
She's too young.
l'm sorry. l'm here,
but l have no right to be here.
There's no excuse for
what l did to you, Lisa.
You were my child.
You needed me.
l'm sorry.
l want to help you... fiind a surgeon.
l'm a researcher. l can fiind anyone.
Even you.
What do you wantfor Christmas?
You can be really selfiish
about this... anything you want.
Or we can go somewhere... anywhere.
l'll take you to Bali...
Timbuktu... Buffalo.
Don't you have a restaurant to run?
What's more important,
is what do you wantfor Christmas?
No, you already gave me my present.
l forgot. Did you like it?
What was it again?
Misery, heartbreak, pain...
...happiness, love...
-life.
-l remember now.
What can l give you?
More ofthis.
-Yeah?
-l'vegothim.
Oh Lisa, hold on, hold on.
-Yeah, go ahead.
-His name is Tom Grandy.
Harvard undergrad. He's at
the Cleveland Heart lnstitute.
-Ohio?!
-lt's one ofthe bestin the world.
He didhis residencyatBrigham,
cardiac surgery training at Cleveland.
He takes the cases no one else will
touch. Theysay he's a miracle worker.
He spends a lotoftime traveling,
a lotoftime lecturing.
lgotyou an appointment todayat 12:30.
Do notbe late. He only has 15minutes.
The surgeon thatrecommendedhim said
ifyou can gethim to take the case...
...you know Charlotte'sgota chance.
He hates the fail.
-Mr. Keane?
-Yeah, hi.
Thanks for a seeing me. l've got
everything that you asked for.
Just once l'd like
to get sent something simple.
That never happens anymore.
The downside of being good at myjob.
Good? My daughter was told
you were the best.
Like most people,
l do the best can.
Last time she passed out she regained
consciousness almost immediately.
Next time, or the time after, she won't.
When that happens, call me.
Room 1 7 is ready, Dr.Grandy.
They'll reach me wherever l am.
l'll coordinate with Sibley.
-l can't thank you enough. Thank you.
-l haven't done anything yet.
l'm home.
Hello.
There you are.
-Where were you today?
-What do you mean?
When you called,
l thought you were at work...
then when l called you back, John
said you hadn't been in all day.
l was in Montclair, New Jersey.
-Why?
-An opportunity.
Do you mean sexual or professional?
Sexual.
l mean, professional!
You get it in there without breaking
it, l'll give you another 5 bucks.
Six dollars... six ofyou.
lt's way too crowded.
l'm way too claustrophobic.
-l'll take the next one.
-You sure? Okay... bye. Help.
-You're going away for the holidays?
-l doubt it.
-Did Mr. Keane enjoy his trip?
-What trip?
-Just yesterday.
-l wouldn't call that a trip.
l've never been to Ohio. lt's amazing
how little l've seen ofthis country.
Cool... l'm gonna
get me some hot chocolate...
-ls it straight?
-Not straight.
What were you doing in Ohio?
l had a meeting with heart specialist.
He's willing to operate.
That's exactly what
l didn't want you to do.
You went behind my back.
You lied to me.
-This what we talked about...
-Cut it out! Stop!
No, we talked about that!
You do not want to die!
You want to live!
You think l haven't
been through this? So many times!
l don't want to give people hope
when there isn't any.
Why not? Maybe, we need hope.
Maybe, l need to know that l've
done everything that l could do.
lf l'm gonna...
What would l do, Will
ifyou weren't here?
Where would l be? Seriously?
You'll never have
to worry about that.
l'll do whatever l have to do.
l'll tear up the papers. l'll tell
the doctors. Whatever you want.
Cause l really want...
l don't to leave you.
You know?
No. No,no,no.
-This is really good.
-What?
-This is much better than mine.
-No, you didn't!
-Yeah, l did.
-Oh, God!
-Forgeries!
-Yeah, a lot ofthem.
Mine...yours...
Will?
-What are you doing in there?
-Nothing.
Hey, no, no! Go back!
Give me another minute, alright?
-No, you're going to tire yourselfout.
-This l've got to see!
-Go back! Back!
-l can't believe it.
Oh, my God!
Alright. Almost.
Hold on, hold on.
Finishing up. Hold on now.
Just a second.
Here we are. Okay! Alright.
Surprise!
lt's New York.
This is Grandy.
-You won't have long.
-All right.
"Time cannot break...
the bird's wing from the bird."
"The bird and wing together...
go down, one feather."
"No thing that ever flew..."
"...not the lark, not you..."
"Can die as others do."
What have l done to you?
You ruined me for other women.
l saved you for them.
ls she type`n' cross 6 for units?
What're we waiting for?
-Just you, Doctor.
-Let's move!
-l don't believe it.
-What?
l'm here with my father and my son.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org