Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
If you'll just
give me a minute...
I'm sure I could find us
a couple of bathing suits.
But why bother?
I don't want you to think
that I'm stuffy or uptight.
I'm considered
a pretty groovy catch.
You know, tuned in.
Like when I'm on business
in Los Angeles...
I always have lunch
at a topless... place.
Just because I don't have
the long sideburns...
that doesn't mean that...
Did you ever hear
of "Old Calcutta"?
I've seen it twice,
and "Carnal Knowledge," too.
Yeah, the permissive society...
age of Aquarius,
sexual revolution...
I'm into all of that.
Take the secretaries
in our home office...
always wearing
those hot pants.
There's nothing
wrong with that...
just as long as they're worn
by consenting adults.
Please keep in mind
that it's Sunday...
and this is
a Catholic country...
and they may think
it's in very poor taste.
Can you hear me?
Oh, my God.
Are you all right?
I'm fantastic.
I'll give you one minute
to catch your breath.
Then we're gonna swim back.
What's the rush?
No rush. Just a little cold
in here in the water.
Nice and warm here,
just lying in the sun...
with your eyes closed.
Yeah? Are your eyes closed?
Why?
Nothing. Just asking.
Here we are...
basking like two baby seals.
Wonder what they talked
about... Willie and Kate.
I'm sure they didn't
talk at all.
They would just listen.
To the wind and the waves...
and the beat, beat, beat
of their foolish hearts.
Why not?
When you're in love,
you don't need words.
A look, a touch, a sigh...
you've said it all.
That's not bad.
I should try that on my wife.
Every time I come home
from work completely pooped...
she always wants to know
why I don't talk to her.
Do you and Bertram...
Do you communicate much?
We haven't talked
for six months.
Beautiful.
You must really dig each other.
The fact of the matter is...
we haven't seen each other
for six months.
The bastard walked out on me...
stole my telly,
two Picasso posters...
and my hairdryer.
There's an apostle for you.
Moved in with some
skinny girl in Kensington.
When I found out,
would you believe...
I tried to commit suicide?
- No.
- Yes.
I took my week's salary...
bought myself a suitcase
full of fish and chips...
and a dozen bottles
of Guinness stout...
and tried to
eat myself to death.
Took them hours
to pump my stomach out.
Was it worth it
for a guy like that?
It was stupid,
but I've learned my lesson.
Good.
No more fish and chips.
I guess there is something...
to what it says
in the tourist guide.
What does it say?
It says,
"ltaly is not a country.
"It's an emotion."
It's certainly been
an experience.
I'm afraid we have
some sightseers.
Please. Where's
your British reserve?
Here.
Maybe you can use these.
That was quite
the loveliest night of my life.
Thank you.
You're entirely welcome.
See you around.
What's up?
It's an emergency.
The Baron Forshmetelli's suite.
I hope it's not a heart attack.
That old crock,
I wouldn't be surprised.
No, it's not the baron.
It's one of the nurses.
Good night, Willie.
Good night, Kate.
Good morning, sir.
Are you all right?
What?
Because they told me,
at seven this morning...
you asked for
two bottles of aspirin.
Oh, that.
I just needed the cotton.
Damn bells. You talk
about noise pollution.
There are 68 churches in Ischia.
They all want the business.
How's that nurse?
She all right?
Yes. Just a slipped disk.
The three of them,
they were playing frogleap.
The word is leapfrog.
I would rather not know.
I have come to give
a progress report.
- How we doing?
- We are making progress.
I have met with
the Trotta brothers.
I gave them German marks.
The bodies are back
in the morgue.
Good.
The doctor from Capri
has examined them.
I have the health
certificates right here.
What about the coffins?
They arrived this morning,
all three of them.
Three?
The two from Bologna
and that first one...
that I ordered
from Amalfi, remember?
There is no refund,
no exchange.
No big deal.
Make a lamp out of it.
About my nephew.
He got to Naples,
and his friend...
let him into
the license bureau...
even though
it's closed on Sunday...
and he got
the export license.
Then we're all set.
Yes and no,
because this nephew...
he gets tickets
for speeding all the time...
and while he was
in that empty building...
he got to the file...
and he removed ten
of his traffic citations...
and now he's in jail.
What about the export license?
They're holding that
as evidence.
But not to worry.
When the court opens
in the morning...
I have a cousin
who is a lawyer.
I will get to him straightaway.
He is the worst lawyer
in Naples...
but fortunately,
he and the judge...
they have the same mistress.
Is that what you call
Italian justice?
What about Sacco and Vanzetti?
When are you people
going to learn...
how to make
a decent cup of coffee?
You know what I had
for breakfast?
Hot Pepsi-Cola.
- What's that?
- Your shorts.
They washed up on the beach.
My shorts? What makes you think
they're my shorts?
Maybe I am wrong.
Maybe they belong
to the young lady.
Just put them down, will you?
About those photographs
I mentioned...
your father and his friend.
I have searched and searched
and searched...
- And?
- I found them.
Of all places,
they were inside my mattress.
Is this the complete set?
Absolutely.
That's the beauty of Polaroid...
no negatives and just one print.
Fair enough. What was our deal?
I owe you a hundred bucks?
No, please...
You want Swiss francs
or German marks?
I told you, it's not
a question of money.
I don't need money.
What I need is...
A visa.
A visa?
Yes. I want to go
back to America...
and you can help me.
How?
You know all the big shots...
senators,
the State Department...
Dr. Kissinger.
You can pull strings.
Not a chance.
Not once you've been
deported as a criminal.
A criminal?
I'm not a criminal.
I'm a patriot.
You know why they deported me?
There were
all these hippies...
demonstrating
in Washington Square...
calling our President
filthy names...
and burning the American flag...
on July 4th, with police
all around doing nothing.
So I got pissed off...
and pulled my gun
out of my holster...
and what do you think happened?
The cops arrested me.
It was a bum rap.
Give me all the details,
and then when I get back...
This can't wait.
You know that maid Anna...
with the mustache?
- What about her?
- She wants me to marry her.
Congratulations.
God forbid.
If there is one thing worse
than a Sicilian woman...
it's a Sicilian woman
who's pregnant.
I must get out of here fast.
I sympathize with you,
and I'll do all I can...
but I can't make you
any promises.
I am counting on you.
Because, you see...
I have other photographs...
taken this morning.
Same rock, same sunrise...
different bodies.
So you better try very hard.
Wait a minute.
Where are those pictures?
They are not in my mattress.
You miserable little crook, I'll
beat the bejesus out of you!
What a day.
Do you believe it?
And how about all those bells?
Smashing, aren't they?
Smashing is right.
If you need me, just ring.
Is it all right
if I go into your bathroom?
Yeah, by all means.
Don't let me interrupt. Go ahead
and finish your breakfast.
Isn't the coffee here fabulous?
What happened?
What's the matter?
Did you burn yourself?
Guess what.
I weighed myself
on my own scales...
but I didn't believe it,
so I came here to check.
- I've lost three pounds.
- Really?
After that enormous meal
last night...
and strawberries
and cream this morning...
and bacon and eggs
and croissant and butter.
Wait till I see Dr. Shaftsbury.
They should defrock him
or disbar him...
or whatever they do.
- Who's Dr. Shaftsbury?
- My psychiatrist.
Him, yeah.
He kept telling me I was unhappy
because I was overweight.
Rubbish! Obviously
I was overweight...
because I was unhappy.
See what I mean?
Yes, I do.
I think I do.
How long will it take you?
Because I can be ready
in no time.
Why?
You know those carts
with the horses...
with the feathers
on their heads?
I thought maybe we could
take a ride around the island...
and stop for
a late lunch somewhere.
I'm starved again.
I'd like to,
but there's so many things...
I have to take care of
here at the hotel.
- It's our last day.
- There's still tonight.
Same program?
Dinner downstairs
and sunrise and...
Last night,
that was their thing.
I thought maybe tonight
we'd do something different...
an our thing.
Surprise me.
You can do my room now.
Here you are.
You call this
a first-class hotel?
If it is about the bed
not being made, I can explain.
Who cares about the bed?
It's about the valet
on this floor... Bruno.
You know about it?
I know he's
a goddamn blackmailer.
I ought to kill
that dirty little fink.
- It has all been taken care of.
- What has?
- The dirty little fink is dead.
- Dead?
Murdered.
He's lying in room 126...
with three bullets
in his chest.
Miss Piggott's room?
She had nothing to do with it.
It was the maid Anna.
She killed him,
and then she ran away.
That is why your bed
has not been made.
Terrible.
It's a tragedy.
If you lose a guest,
you can always replace him.
But to lose a valet and a maid
in the middle of the season...
Listen, that character Bruno,
he took some photographs.
Perfectly innocent, mind you...
but if they fell
into the wrong hands...
Don't worry. They fell
into the right hands.
I'm sorry. I had to look
just for a second...
but I had to make sure
who they belonged to.
Thanks.
There is just one thing
that puzzled me.
The black socks...
Is it because
you are in mourning?
- What's this?
- Miss Piggott's things.
We are moving them in here
temporarily, as a precaution.
- What precaution?
- The police will arrive...
and we do not
want her involved.
They will start asking
all kinds of questions.
And who knows
what may come out.
What would I do without you?
I have often wondered
about that.
I'm sorry,
but you have been moved.
Moved? Why?
I just follow orders.
You are now in 121-122.
But I was perfectly happy...
121-122?
Mr. Armbruster's suite.
I'm sorry
for the inconvenience.
Don't be.
It's me... Pamela.
Hi!
I'm in the tub.
Make yourself at home.
I must say,
you do have some cheek.
I do?
Aren't you taking
rather a lot for granted?
Just what made you think
that I would have...
the slightest interest
in this arrangement?
Did you say something?
Not that I expected
any subtlety from you.
After all, you're American.
You're accustomed to having
everything your own way.
You see something you want,
and you just grab it.
Come again?
London Bridge, for instance.
You simply took it apart
stone by stone...
and shipped it off
to someplace in the wild west.
Or the Queen Mary,
with all that tradition...
sitting there off
the coast of California...
reduced to
a floating cafeteria.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Such conceit, such arrogance.
You act as though
you own the world.
Playing golf on the moon.
Now, really.
Me, I play golf
at the country club.
Twelve handicap.
And then you wonder
why people don't like you.
Because you're like
spoiled children...
no manners,
no consideration.
You don't just pick up
the phone and say...
"Move that bird
in here from 126."
If I'm to have
an affair with someone...
I'd like to know it first...
and not hear about it
from the concierge.
Oh, my god. The bags.
Wait a minute!
A girl likes to be asked.
She should be given
a chance to say no.
Miss Piggott...
She wants to be talked into it.
What we have here is
a failure of communication.
It's not that I'm
women's lib or anything.
I don't mind being treated
as a sex object...
but it's like any other game.
You have to play
according to the rules...
or it takes
all the fun out of it.
Hang on a minute
before things get out of hand!
Hello? Hello?
Baltimore?
Yes, this is
Mr. Armbruster's suite.
Could you speak up
a bit, please?
I'm sorry. Wendell can't
come to the phone right now.
He's in the bathroom.
Can I help you?
This is Miss Piggott.
Am I the what?
The interpreter?
Whatever gave you that idea?
Hello? Hello?
- This...
- You're dripping.
Whatever you may think
of Americans...
I do not consider you
"a bird."
- I do not take you for granted...
- Thank you.
About your things being here...
there was no time
to ask you.
You were out of the hotel,
and under the circumstances...
it seemed the most
practical thing to do.
- I understand.
- No, you don't.
You were moved
out of your room...
for your own protection,
for our protection.
We do have to be very careful.
I said surprise me,
and you certainly did.
You're taller than I thought.
What... The bed.
Have you noticed
it's not been made up?
I'll do it later.
That's because
of Anna, the maid.
It seems that she was pregnant
by Bruno, the valet.
The things that go on
on this floor.
She wanted to get married,
but he didn't.
He wanted to go back
to America...
but there was a problem
because he'd been deported.
So he wanted me to help him,
and she found out about it...
Is this going to be
a long story?
Anyway, the maid...
she's Sicilian, you know...
she got a gun, and she
shot him just like that.
Three bullets right
through the photographs.
And that's why your bags...
All clear. The body
has been removed.
The police have left the hotel.
So we can now take
Miss Piggott's luggage...
back to her room.
I'll take care of that.
As I was trying to tell you...
The murder... She shot him
in your room.
We had to move you
out of there fast...
before the police got there.
Then this was not
exactly an... invitation?
Not really.
As a matter of fact,
it was Carlucci's idea.
How stupid.
No, it wasn't.
Because the Italian police...
once they start
asking questions...
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
It's just one of those things.
It's nobody's fault.
Fortunately,
I'm only half unpacked.
These things happen.
I remember I was invited...
to a New Year's Eve party
in New York.
3 East 72nd Street.
I had a ball!
It wasn't until
the next morning...
I found out I was
at the wrong party.
It was 3 West 72nd Street.
Don't you think that's funny?
Put it through. Baltimore.
They called you before.
Hello.
Hello, Emily. How are you?
Is something wrong?
What was that?
Wait a minute.
Miss Piggott?
I told you before,
she's the interpreter.
Who says she isn't?
She did?
I can explain that.
She's English,
and we're in Italy.
She can't get a labor permit...
and naturally,
she's not going to admit...
What do you mean,
she's in my room all the time?
I don't mind you getting
a little jealous now and then...
but isn't this ridiculous?
Do you think that I,
at a time like this...
What music?
OK, all right!
Go ahead! Have it your way!
I've got a gypsy band
up here...
incense is burning,
the booze is flowing!
Miss Piggott and I
are playing frogleap bare-assed!
Is that any better?
Just to put
your mind at rest...
you needn't be worried
one bit...
because if you saw me,
I'm short, I'm fat...
and I'm not
very attractive. OK?
All right, Emily,
you satisfied now?
Let's just forget
the whole incident.
Yes, I should be out
of here by tomorrow.
Everything's all wrapped up.
One small snag in Naples...
the export license.
Blodgett? Jo Jo Blodgett?
Yes, I know he's with
the State Department.
A friggin' bore.
He's stationed in Paris?
There is no reason to contact...
all right, if worse
comes to worst.
Yeah, I'll tell her.
Kiss-kiss.
Mrs. Armbruster said
to apologize to you.
No need.
Personally, I thought
you overdid it a little.
I was just telling the truth.
Come on. Stop
putting yourself down.
I'm sure there's
any number of men...
who'd find you very attractive.
Oh, yes.
No-good bastard Bertram...
and some sex-starved
sardine fishermen...
and the local coroner, who took
me for a ride on his scooter...
and then pinched my behind.
If it's of
any interest to you...
you know who finds you
attractive? Me.
I find you attractive.
Don't bother. I'll survive.
This isn't the first time
I've made a fool of myself.
Excuse me.
Would you consider it
impertinent...
if I asked you
to step on the scales?
- Yes, I would.
- Please?
I really don't care anymore.
It's not the weight,
it's the height.
Why don't you
just make a contribution...
to your favorite charity?
Are you guys sure
this is Ischia?
Reasonably sure, sir.
Because I don't want
to land in Africa.
That would be bigger, sir.
Maybe it's one
of those Greek islands.
No, sir. Greece is
way to the left.
Not as long as I'm
with the State Department.
Go away! Go away!
What the hell is
the name of this place?
Ischia, but you cannot land.
What do you mean, we can't land?
It is lunchtime.
Come back later.
My good man, do you know
to whom you're talking?
I do not talk to anybody.
Lunchtime!
Let me make one thing
perfectly clear.
I am Joseph J. Blodgett...
United States Government,
State Department...
and I'm here
on an emergency mission...
concerning an American citizen.
OK, boys, stand by.
And you better start clearing
some of these seats out...
so we have room
for the coffin.
Roger.
Tell me, how far
is this hotel?
Grand Hotel Excelsior,
five kilometers.
OK, OK. What do we do
about transportation?
No transportation.
Lunchtime!
What the hell is going on
in this country?
This wouldn't have happened
in the old days.
You remember Mussolini?
Christ.
What's the matter?
Just thinking about
going back home.
I hate the whole idea.
- Thank you.
- Right after the funeral...
there's going to be
a board of directors meeting...
and probably a proxy fight...
and I'll have to spend
a week in Washington...
because they're investigating
the Armbruster Foundation.
And there's that strike...
at our electronics plant
in Wisconsin.
And we'll probably
have to recall...
250,000 square feet
of artificial turf...
because they said...
there's too much lead
in the green paint.
Goddamn Ralph Nader.
Who asked him?
Guess we all have our problems.
I have to pick up my cat
from the vet's in Bayswater.
Hope the garage will have
my Mini Morris fixed by now.
And I really should
repaint my kitchen.
Can I have your croissant?
Of course. You can have
anything you want.
About your flat in London...
Won't you need a new
television and hairdryer...
all that stuff that
your apostle ran off with?
Don't bother.
I dry my hair in the oven...
and I really
don't watch the telly.
It's always the same...
northern Ireland
and Princess Anne...
and the Common Market.
Pamela... my father
and your mother...
Now, during all those years,
didn't he ever give her any...
He must have helped her out
from time to time.
Financially.
You want to know whether
my mother was a kept woman?
After all, a man likes
to show his gratitude.
Maybe an occasional present?
Every Christmas,
he would send her...
a dozen long-stemmed roses
to the Savoy hotel.
Your mother was well-to-do?
No. She was making
£15 a week and tips.
On £15 a week,
she was living at the Savoy?
She wasn't living there.
She was working there...
as a manicurist.
Did my father know that?
She didn't want him to know.
Why not?
I told you the first day.
She loved him.
She didn't want any tips.
That'll be Carlucci.
"I have good news.
"The arrangements,
they have all been made."
I guess it's checking-out time.
Yes.
Did Miss Piggott
enjoy her kippers?
No, that's not why I called.
I called to tell you
that Anna the maid...
she has been arrested
by the police...
in a rowboat trying
to escape to Sicily.
And the bodies,
they are in the coffins...
and all ready for shipment.
Let me see...
there was something else.
The judge in Naples,
he has had a slight stroke.
Wait a minute. What judge?
I don't know
any judge in Naples.
Yes, you do.
The one with the same mistress
as my cousin the lawyer...
who was going to get
my nephew out of jail.
She was going to help him,
but she helped him too hard...
and the judge, he always had
high blood pressure.
What are you trying to tell me?
We have no export license,
is that it?
More or less.
Now they will have to
appoint a new judge.
That may take a day or two.
We sure are running
in bad luck.
It's not your fault.
It's the way it goes.
Don't worry about it.
I still like you.
Problems?
We may be stuck here
for another couple of days.
That's terrible.
Yeah.
What about the funeral?
Oh, boy!
All those people...
the closed-circuit TV,
glee club...
I'll just have to call
Baltimore.
If it has to be postponed,
it has to be postponed.
- I'm so sorry.
- What can I do?
You've certainly done
everything you could.
How about you and your plans?
We're not that busy
in the shop.
I'm sure mother won't mind.
She's in no hurry...
to get back to the rain
and the cold.
I guess dad
wouldn't mind, either.
They deserve another
couple of days together...
don't you think?
Thank you.
My pleasure!
What room is he in?
Just a moment.
Your name, please?
Here. I'll talk to him.
Wendell, boy?
Jo Jo Blodgett,
State Department.
How are you, kid?
Emily called me last night...
told me about
your little problem.
Damn it. I told her
not to bother you.
I'm sorry, Jo Jo.
I realize you've got...
more important things
to do in Paris.
Sure do.
That's why I grabbed...
the first plane to Rome
this morning.
Borrowed a helicopter
from the sixth fleet.
You're on Ischia?
Where? At the airport?
Better than that, kiddo.
I'm right here in the lobby.
You're in the lobby!
That's great.
That's what I
really call service.
Why don't you
just check in, wash up...
and we'll have a drink
later in the afternoon.
What drink? What later?
I got to get
back to Paris tonight.
I'm taking Julie
and David Eisenhower...
to dinner at Maxim's.
So we got to get cracking.
We haven't got a minute to lose.
Be right with you.
What's that room number?
What are we going
to do with this?
to do with you?
I am Carlo Carlucci,
director of the hotel.
Such a pleasure
to have you here.
Thank you.
It may interest you to know
we once had...
another famous American diplomat
staying here once...
Mr. Benjamin Franklin.
Franklin? Yes, Ben Franklin.
A good man for his time.
Of course,
today I'm not sure...
he could pass
the security check.
Would you like to see his room?
It is in the old part
of the building.
Not now!
Excuse me. I would like
your advice about something...
straight from the horse's mouth.
Do you think there will be
a war in the Middle East?
We don't give out
that kind of information.
I have been offered a job...
with a chain of American
hotels... the Sheraton.
There are a couple of openings,
and one of them is in Damascus.
Don't quote me on this,
but with the Russian presence...
escalating
in the Mediterranean...
and the military posture
of the Arabs stiffening...
and the first-strike capability
of the Israelis at its peak...
the whole place is a powder keg.
Could blow up
in your face any second.
My advice is forget Damascus.
Thank you. In that case,
I had better take the other job.
- What's that?
- The Sheraton in New York.
Take the one in Damascus.
- One more question.
- No more questions!
Come in.
Jo Jo Blodgett,
if I ever saw one.
Hi there.
How are you? Been a long time.
I haven't been back
to the States since '67.
That's it.
Halloween of '67.
Party at the country club.
You came dressed as Batman.
I'm sorry about
what happened to your father.
Look, it's 2:00
in the afternoon.
At 11:00 tomorrow morning...
you have a funeral
4,000 miles away...
and you're sitting here
getting a manicure?
This is Miss Tromboncino.
She works in the barber shop.
Could you possibly
speed it up a little?
She doesn't speak any English.
I get that all over the world.
Mind you, I don't object...
to foreigners speaking
a foreign language.
I just wish they'd all speak
the same foreign language.
- Odd.
- What's odd?
If I didn't know
how straight-laced you were...
and if I didn't know
that you were in mourning...
and if that dame
were about 20 pounds lighter...
- I would sort of suspect...
- Suspect what?
Mr. Blodgett, please.
That dame, she is my niece.
She was brought up
by the Carmelite sisters.
I was only kidding.
It is forgotten.
How many more fingers
has she got to go?
Relax, will you?
Relax nothing.
You're screwing up my timetable.
I've got that helicopter
standing by.
- Can I use your can?
- What for?
To wash my hands.
I mean, what's
the helicopter for?
To pick up the old boy.
We're going to fly him to Rome.
Then I'm going to put you
on the night plane to Baltimore.
- Tonight?
- Sure.
That's what you think.
This is Italy.
Nothing's that simple.
We're still hassling over
the export license.
Emily told me all about that.
It looks like we can't get
out of here before Wednesday.
I was about to phone home, tell
them to postpone the ceremony.
Postpone nothing.
Batman is here.
We don't need an export license.
We're gonna bypass
all that bull.
Bypass?
How can you do it?
No sweat. We're
appointing your father...
commercial attaché
to the embassy in Rome.
And that entitles him
to all the rights...
and immunities of a diplomat.
Wait a minute.
You're going to appoint him...
- Why not?
- A dead man?
Just proves that we don't
discriminate against anybody...
for reasons of race, creed,
color, or state of health.
You mean we handle him
just like a diplomatic pouch?
You bet. He goes
right through customs...
sealed coffin, no inspection,
no formalities at either end.
- That's kind of cute.
- That's nothing.
Someday I'll tell you
how we got Batista out of Cuba.
First on the agenda...
First, you wanted to go
to the can.
Can. That's right.
I'm sorry.
Mother would never forgive me.
Look at the wretched job
I did on your nails.
Tell me something.
Bruno's body.
What did they do with it?
It is lying in the morgue,
unclaimed. No family.
- Interesting.
- In what way?
We may have a use
for that third coffin.
That is very generous of you.
Your family plot,
does that offer still stand?
You're not suggesting
we bury Bruno there!
The Carluccis, they would
turn over in their graves.
I wasn't thinking of Bruno.
No?
You were thinking
of somebody else?
Maybe... two somebody elses?
My ancestors,
they will be honored.
We're not there yet.
There's a time element.
And we'll need
some transportation.
Transportation?
No sweat.
I will call the Trotta brothers.
You know you got...
a plate of scrambled eggs
in the bathtub?
- I do?
- And half a herring.
Now you understand why
I want that job with Sheraton.
OK, kid, here is the game plan.
You get dressed and packed.
Next, we collect your father.
Sure thing. As soon
as they open the morgue.
And I want some officials
at that airport.
I want the mayor
and what-have-you.
Of course.
Right after lunch.
- That will be 4:00.
- 4:00?
That's when they open
the mortuary.
That goddamn lunchtime again.
We pour in millions
of dollars of foreign aid...
just so they can sit
on their butts and...
What the hell is there to do
around here for two hours?
Tell him about the mud baths.
Mud baths?
World-famous.
For rheumatism, arthritis,
neuritis, phlebitis...
urinary complaints,
hyperacidity, male potency.
Is that so?
Come to think of it, I do have
a slight acid condition.
Maybe I'll give that
a little whirl.
By all means.
It is downstairs.
I will show you.
Be right back.
Where do we meet?
Let me put it all together,
and we'll meet at the airport.
Right-o.
That mud business...
does it really help?
I assure you, after one bath...
you will have the acidity
of a man of twenty.
Thank you.
It was your idea.
What's the name
of that orchestra here?
Sergio... something. Why?
We might as well go all the way.
I'm sure he'd enjoy it more...
than that glee club
in Baltimore...
the son of a bitch.
The marble, do you
want it white or pink?
Pink.
Very good. And the inscription?
I guess..."Willie and Kate."
"Willie and Kate."
That is all?
We don't want any weeping angels
or hearts intertwined.
Or do we?
How about
"Willie and Kate Carlucci"?
I'll go for that.
You make me very happy.
And there will be
tromboncini every Sunday.
After all, we are now
one big family.
Hold it, boys.
My father goes
on the other side.
Very important.
It's his good ear.
Damn!
What the hell took you so long?
Signore, in Italy,
when a coffin passes by...
people cross themselves.
They kneel down sometimes
in the middle of the road.
You just cannot...
All right, all right.
Over here, boys!
Let's get this thing down!
Poor Bruno.
If he knew what was
happening to him...
What do you mean, "poor Bruno"?
This is what he always wanted...
to go back to America.
Come on, boys.
Snap it up, will you?
Come on. It's getting late.
Will the witnesses
please step forward?
Raise your right hand
and repeat after me.
I, Wendell Armbruster Sr.,
do solemnly swear...
that I will uphold
and defend...
the Constitution
of the United States...
against all enemies
foreign and domestic...
and that I will perform
the duties of my office...
to the best of my ability,
so help me God.
Congratulations, sir.
And salute!
Ready, hup!
Thank you, gentlemen.
That concludes the ceremonies.
All right, load her up.
Here. You'll need this.
It's your father's
diplomatic passport.
You don't miss a trick, do you?
The C.I.A. Ran it off
for me last night.
The C.I.A.?
Never heard of them.
Let's go.
Good-bye, Pamela Piggott.
Have a good flight.
Don't work too hard.
Suppose I do?
The worst that can happen...
is I'll wind up
with a bad back.
The suite, it will be ready.
July 15th to August 15th.
If we should run into
each other again...
in the lobby
or the souvenir shop...
I promise you I'll be so thin.
You lose one pound,
just one pound...
and it's all over between us.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org