Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
She said,
"Do you think it'd be fun
if we got married?"
And what did you say?
I took her up on it.
I never wanted to be
away from her.
She had the spark of life.
Careful.
When did we last
wash that sweater?
Right after the war.
Christmas.
In the '50s sometime or the '60s.
Shut up.
I'll go make the fire.
"You climbed the bank and said,
"'This is how you touch
other women,
"the grass cutter's wife,
the lime burner's daughter.
"And you searched your arms
for the missing perfume
and knew..."
Don't worry, darling.
I expect I'm just losing my mind.
"What good is it to be
the lime burner's daughter,
"left with no trace
"as if not spoken to in the act of love,
"as if wounded without
the pleasure of a scar.
"You touched your belly
to my hands in the dry air
"and said, 'I am
the cinnamon peeler's wife.
Smell me."'
When I look away,
I forget what yellow means.
But I can look again.
Sometimes there's something
delicious in oblivion.
I think you're supposed to be able
to put your fingers
inside the curled petal
and feel the heat.
Well?
I can't be sure.
I can't be sure if what I can feel
is the heat or my imagination.
The heat attracts the bugs.
Nature never fools around
just being decorative.
Yes?
I don't quite know
how to introduce myself.
I used to see your husband
at Meadowlake.
I'm a regular visitor there myself.
Those are lovely flowers.
I've never seen
those purple ones before.
The earth there must
really appeal to them.
What?
You could just open the drawers.
Remind yourself.
What?
Maybe all the labels and lists
are defeating the purpose.
If you stopped thinking about things
the moment you write them down,
maybe that's the end
of your need to recall.
I heard a story at a dinner party
about the German soldiers
on border patrol
in Czechoslovakia during the war.
I heard it from that
Czech student of yours.
Veronica.
We spoke once at a dinner party.
Don't be nervous.
It's a good story.
She told me that each
of the German patrol dogs
wore a sign saying "hund."
"Why?" said the Czechs.
And the Germans replied,
"Because that is a hund."
It was one of those craft shows
where you look around and wonder
that the laws of supply and demand
can allow for the production
of so many macramé ducks.
Oh, God, those things are everywhere.
- What do you do with them?
- Come on, Phoebe, you've got one of those.
You use it as a... what do you call it...
a light fixture holder or som...
- I do not.
- Phoebe, in the...
Oh, yes. Wait a second, I do.
Fiona gave it to me.
Yes, I did.
Would anybody like some more?
Ween...
Wai... Wain...
No, but I'll have a touch of wine.
Yeah, Fiona, that would be lovely.
Some more wain.
The thing is...
half the time I wander around
looking for something
which I know is very pertinent.
I can't remember what it is.
Once the idea is gone,
everything is gone.
I just wander around
trying to figure out what it was
that was so important earlier.
I think I may be
beginning to disappear.
And what year is it?
2003.
Fiona, if you found a letter on the street,
addressed, with a stamp on it,
what would you do with it?
I'd mail it.
And where would you put it to mail it?
And if there was a fire
in a movie theater,
and you were the first person
to spot that fire,
what would you do?
Well, we don't go
to the movies much anymore,
do we, Grant?
All those multiplexes showing
the same American garbage.
Have you seen my coat?
There it is, dear.
It's on your chair.
Oh, yes.
Fiona, would you mind
if I asked you a few more questions?
Would you mind taking a seat?
I was just feeling
a little cold, that's all.
What an ugly baby.
When did we move into this cottage?
Was it last year
or the year before?
No. It was longer than that.
It was when I left the university,
20 years ago.
Well, that's shocking.
Let's just see how it goes, shall we?
How is your husband doing?
Okay.
He and my wife struck up
quite a close friendship.
I heard about that.
So, uh,
I'd like to speak to you
about something.
If you have a minute.
My husband did not try
to start anything with your wife,
if that's what you're getting at.
He did not try to molest her.
He's incapable of it.
And anyway, he wouldn't.
From what I hear, it was the other way around.
No, uh, that isn't it at all.
I didn't come here with any complaints.
Oh.
Oh, well, I'm sorry.
I thought you did.
Maybe you should come in.
It's not as warm a day as it looks.
"Never let a person make you feel guilty
for your anger with God."
Hmm. Random.
I can't even see what the point is.
We can't be certain this is what...
You're far too young.
"Should the patient
afflicted with the disease
"remain at home...
the caregiver will very often be the spouse."
"The caregiver must preside
over the degeneration
"of someone he or she
loves very much,
"must do this for years and years
"with the news always
getting worse, not better,
"must put up sometimes
with deranged
"but at the same time
very personal insults,
"and must somehow learn
to smile through it all.
"Caregivers must be able to diagnose
"a wide variety of ordinary ailments
"under extraordinary circumstances.
"Imagine the person
you love the most
"suddenly upset about something,
"but completely unable
to communicate the problem
or even to understand it himself."
Sounds like a regular marriage.
Hello, there!
Oh!
Hello, there.
We are at that stage, Grant.
We are at that stage.
Well...
if we do think of it...
if we do...
then it must be as something
that isn't permanent.
A kind of experimental treatment or...
a rest cure of sorts.
All right.
We can think of it that way.
We have to sit in the kitchen,
where I can hear Aubrey.
Well, you might as well
have a cup of coffee.
Thank you.
My son put him on the Sports Channel
a year ago Christmas.
I don't know what we'd do without it.
Must be a struggle.
Well, you know.
You know what
struggle is by now.
- You're sure?
- I'm sure.
You don't want to just get
a sense of the place?
I don't want to make
this decision alone.
What place?
Just kidding!
Fuck off.
You're not making
this decision alone, Grant.
I've already made up my mind.
Okay.
It's time to go home now.
- No, no.
- Mrs. Taylor...
- Hi. Is this your son?
- Yeah. I'm her son.
Hi. I'm Betty. It's time for your bath.
- Bath.
- Yeah.
You have to have a bath now.
Mama.
Mr. Andersson?
Madeleine Montpelier.
- I'm the supervisor here at Meadowlake.
- Hi, there.
I'm just going to take you
on the quick tour of the facility,
and then we can sit down
and discuss Mrs. Andersson's condition
and the appropriate time
for admitting her.
As you can see,
we get a lot of natural light.
Yes, I can see that.
This is my favorite room.
Look, over there, as you can see,
they have a puzzle on the go.
They always have
a puzzle on the go.
- This works.
- You know, it's real important to us here
that our residents
maintain social function,
so a lot of our activities
and our whole layout
is really geared toward...
Hello, there, Miss Madeleine.
Hello, Michael.
Now, as you can see,
we're coming into our common room,
and again, we're really emphasizing
everybody being social.
So you can bring the family.
Everybody can come and visit.
We have a state-of-the-art
entertainment system
so the residents can gather
and watch together.
- Hi, Madeleine.
- Hello, ladies.
- Hello, Madeleine.
- I got a Christmas sweater.
Aren't you festive!
And this is our quiet corner
for crafts and reading and reflection.
We have a lot of activities
for physical activity.
Balloon badminton and sit and fit.
And here we have our
lovely new dining room.
We can accommodate
any dietary preferences or restrictions.
We're just serving up a little Christmas dinner
early for the families.
The old Meadowlake is just next door,
and that's a day center
now, but, um...
this for the permanent residents.
This is brand-spanking new.
So let's go upstairs, shall we?
Just taking my tea for a ride.
Oh, look at this one, Flo.
He's a real charmer, isn't he?
Would you say,
are you a charmer?
I think you could say
I was kind of a charmer.
You're a rascal.
Mr. Andersson is here about his wife, Eliza.
Behave yourself.
I should have known it.
At this age, it's...
What do the kids call it, Flo? It's...
It's a real clusterfuck.
All the charmers are taken.
Or dead. Mostly dead.
You're kind of charming
yourself, sweetheart.
Shall we?
This is our second floor,
the extended care wing.
The elevators, of course,
have the lockdown system,
and this is where
the patients can move to
once they become more progressed.
Interesting choice of words.
Why don't I show you some of the rooms here,
while we're at it?
Then we can go back down
and see the regular rooms
where Mrs. Andersson will be living.
No, that will not be necessary.
My wife will not be
progressing to this floor.
All right.
Who chooses the music?
I'm sorry?
I'm assuming it's not the residents.
I don't see any of them
singing along.
Yeah, well. You know the rooms on the regular
floors all have their own stereo systems
so the patients can listen
to whatever they like.
How kind.
Now, we don't admit anyone
during the month of December,
so Mrs. Andersson will
have to wait till January
to make the big move.
Just December, Christmas, you know, too
many emotional pitfalls.
- Right.
- Sorry to interrupt, Madeleine.
I'm looking for those documents
on Aubrey Burke.
Sure. Go ahead.
Mr. Andersson, this is Kristy,
our new managing nurse.
Against some people's
better judgment.
Now, now.
Mr. Andersson is here about his wife,
Mrs. Andersson,
who will be joining us in January.
- Hi, there.
- Hi.
We also have a policy,
which I'm sure you saw
in the brochure,
that our new residents
are not allowed visitors
or receiving phone calls
during the first 30 days,
just to give them a chance to settle in.
What sort of visitors?
Everyone. Even close relatives.
I couldn't just leave her here.
We understand,
it is very difficult
to leave a loved one
in a new environment for so long,
but most people need
that time to settle in.
Before we had this rule in place,
residents would forget
again and again
why they were being left here.
Whereas we find,
you give them the month
to settle in,
and they're happy as clams.
And after that, a little visit home
every now and then, perfectly fine.
We'll take good care
of her, I promise.
- Knock-knock.
- Oh, no! Not again.
Knock-knock. Boo.
- She's bringing two babies.
- Two babies?
She's got a new baby,
four months old.
Smells good.
I was going to go for a ski,
but I thought I shouldn't chance it,
what with the Alzheimer's and all.
Why didn't you wake me?
What are these, Grant?
Those are the documents
you're supposed to sign
if you decide to go to Meadowlake.
That is exactly
what I have decided.
You were to go and sign these
and leave them there.
I wouldn't be allowed
to visit you for 30 days.
30 days isn't such a long time
after 44 years.
I don't think I like the place.
I don't think we should be looking
for something we like, Grant.
I don't think we'll ever find that.
I think all we can aspire
to in this situation
is a little bit of grace.
I suppose I'll be
dressed up all the time.
It will be sort of like... in a hotel.
How do I look?
Just like always.
Just as you've always looked.
And how does that look?
Direct and vague...
sweet and ironic.
Is that how I look?
Oh. Remember?
Surprised, Grant?
No, I'm not surprised.
I'm just grateful
you can remember that.
I'm not all gone, Grant. Just...
going...
There are things
I wish would go away.
But won't. You know.
Things we don't talk about.
You never left me.
You still made love to me,
despite disturbing demands elsewhere.
But all those sandals, Grant.
All those bare female toes.
What could you do but be a part of the time
you were a part of?
All those pretty girls.
Didn't seem like anyone
was willing to be left out.
I think you did all right,
compared to some
of your colleagues.
Those who left their wives.
And the women who
wouldn't put up with it.
I think people are too demanding.
People want to be in love
every single day.
What a liability. And then that silly girl.
That silly girl Veronica.
Girls that age
are always going around
saying they're going
to kill themselves.
But that was that.
Promised me a new life.
We moved out here,
that is exactly what you gave me.
How long ago was that?
20 years.
God, that's shocking.
So you see, I'm going...
but I'm not gone.
- Fiona.
- Grant.
Don't go.
That's what is happening, Grant.
It's happening... right now.
Fiona.
Hello. I'm checking in today.
My name is Fiona Andersson.
Yes, Mrs. Andersson.
We have your room
all ready for you.
- Perfect.
- We'll have our supervisor,
Mrs. Montpelier, show you.
I'll go fetch her. She's expecting you.
Thank you.
Fiona.
Grant.
I can't go away from you like this.
We had nothing
to tie us down, Grant.
You could have just driven away
and forsaken me.
But you didn't.
I thank you for that.
- Mrs. Andersson.
- Oh, hello.
- How do you do? I'm Madeleine.
- Hello.
Should I give you two a moment?
- No, thank you.
- Yes, please.
All right, then, well,
we'll get you settled in your room,
and then I'd like to give you
a tour of the facility.
- That'd be lovely. Thank you.
- Right this way.
So, as you can see,
we get a lot of natural light.
Here we go.
Yes. This'll do just fine.
Good. I'm so glad
you like it. Now, is...
is this all you brought
with you today?
- For now.
- We'll see how it goes.
Well, if you need any help arranging things,
you just let me know.
Thank you, Mrs. Montpelier.
Now, if you wouldn't mind, I'd like to say
good-bye to my husband.
We haven't been apart for a month
for the last 44 years.
It could be quite something.
Okay.
Please, Fiona.
Grant.
Fiona...
You know what I'd like?
I'd like to make love,
and then I'd like you to go.
Because I need to stay here,
and if you make it hard for me,
I might cry so hard
I'll never stop.
Go now.
"All of the officers
"were from outside
the local area,
"and it probably had not
entered their minds
"that almost all of us
were named McDonald.
"Nobody moved except for
the shuffling of feet.
The red roo"...Hey.
- Hello, there.
- Kristy. We met on your tour.
How's Mrs. Andersson?
Has she settled in?
I'm wondering if I could have
a moment of your time
to ask your advice?
Oh, sure. I was just
reading to Mr. Burke here.
Maybe when we finish this chapter,
I can come find you
in the dining room?
Sure. That's fine.
"The red roof lights
revolved in the afternoon sun,
and even the dogs were
temporarily quiet."
Hi, there, Mr. Andersson.
Now, how can I help you?
Going down the center
of the dining room...
That's Frank. He used to be the play-by-play
guy for the Winnipeg Jets.
- Really?
- Yeah.
He loved his job too much to retire.
Frank's on the second floor.
I just... My wife has always been
sort of a different sort of person.
I've been told that Alzheimer's can't be
confirmed until after...
And on our way here today,
we passed this conservation area
where we went
for a walk last spring.
And there were these gorgeous flowers.
The skunk lilies.
Oh, those are
beautiful, aren't they?
Yes, they really made
an impression, see?
And even though the whole
place was covered in snow,
she said, "Oh, remember?"
Now, that was...
that was... quite recently.
And isn't the short-term memory
the thing that goes first?
Well, yeah, but not all at once.
And what's comforting
is the long-term memory sometimes
stays for quite a long time.
Yeah, her long-term memory
seems quite intact.
But when she mentioned that,
about the skunk lilies,
it was all I could do not
to turn the truck around.
What if this is just her
just being herself?
She's far too young to...
She is young.
And it is hard.
No doubt about that.
A month is a real long time.
I mean, between you and me,
I don't know about the policy myself.
I think it makes it easier for the staff
is what I think.
Look. I'll give you my pager number.
You can call me
whenever you want.
You can call me every day
if you feel like it.
I don't know what to do.
Mr. Andersson,
your wife wrote you this note,
and she asked me to pass it along.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
"Throughout much of the thinking brain,
gooey plaques now crowd neurons
from outside the cell membranes."
"And knotty tangles
mangle microtubal transports
from inside the cells."
"All told, tens of millions
of synapses dissolve away."
"Because the structures
and substructures of the brain
"are so highly specialized,
"the precise location
of the neuronal loss
determines what specific abilities
will become impaired."
"It is like a series
of circuit breakers
in a large house,
flipping off one by one."
That's a great-Iooking coffee maker.
I always meant to get one of those.
I saw they had them on sale
at Canadian Tire.
They gave it to us, my son and his wife.
They live in Kamloops, B.C.
They send us more stuff
than we can handle.
Wouldn't hurt if they spent the money
to come see us instead.
I suppose they're busy
with their own lives.
Not so busy they couldn't
go to Hawaii last year.
I mean, you could understand it
if there was someone
in the family closer at hand,
but, uh... he's the only one.
People do get Ionely,
especially when they're deprived
of seeing someone they care about.
Fiona, for instance.
My wife.
I thought you said
you went and visited her.
I do.
No, that's not it.
She's really settling in well.
Good. Good.
Looking forward to seeing you tomorrow,
Mr. Andersson.
Right. So I'll see you
tomorrow morning, then.
Now, remember,
she may be a little surprised to see you.
Don't be shaken by that.
Just... She hasn't seen you in a while.
She's sort of settled in here.
I understand.
There you are. I'll walk you down to her.
Wow. Narcissus this early.
You must have spent a fortune.
We brought it back here.
Hi, Mr. Andersson.
It's great to see you.
I'm gonna help you find
your sweater, Mrs. Albright.
All right. Here we are.
There is her room, right over there.
You remember from last time
you were here, don't you?
Her nameplate's right on the door.
I'll leave you to it.
There she is. Now you just
go over and say hello,
and try not to startle her...
Remember, she may not...
Well, just go ahead.
Bridge. Deadly serious.
Quite rabid about it.
I can remember being like that
at college for a while.
My friends and I would cut class
and sit in the common room and smoke
and play like cutthroats.
One's name was Phoebe.
I don't remember the others.
Phoebe Hart.
Oh, you knew her, too.
Can I get you something?
A cup of tea?
I'm afraid the coffee's
not up to much here.
I don't drink tea.
Oh.
I brought you some flowers.
I thought they might do
to brighten up your room.
I went to your room,
but you weren't there.
Well, no, I'm here.
So you've made a new friend.
Oh, that's just Aubrey.
The funny thing is I knew
him years and years ago.
He used to work in the store,
the hardware store where
my grandpa used to shop.
He and I were always kidding around,
but he never could get up
the nerve to ask me out.
Until the very last weekend,
he took me to a ball game.
But my grandpa showed up
to drive us home.
I was up visiting for the summer.
Visiting my grandparents.
They lived in a cottage on a lake.
Fiona, I know where
your grandparents lived.
It's where we lived. We live.
Really?
I'd better go back.
He thinks he can't play
without me sitting there.
It's silly. I hardly
know the game anymore.
I'm afraid you'll have
to excuse me.
Will you be through soon?
We should be. I mean, it depends.
If you asked that grim-Iooking
lady over there nicely,
she'll get you a cup of tea.
- No, I'm fine.
- I can leave you, then?
You can entertain yourself?
Must all seem strange to you.
But you'll be surprised
how soon you get used to it.
You'll get to know who everybody is,
except that some of them
are pretty well off in the clouds, you know?
Can't expect them all
to get to know who you are.
Hey, I've been thinking of dying my hair.
What do you think?
Do you think I'd look
good with red hair?
You caught her at sort of a bad moment,
involved in a game.
She isn't even playing.
Well, but her friend's playing, Aubrey.
Now, who is Aubrey?
That's who he is, Aubrey.
You know, they get
these attachments.
That kind of takes over for a while.
Best buddy kind of thing.
Sort of a phase.
Does she even know who I am?
No, she might not.
Not today, and then,
tomorrow you never know.
Things change back and forth all the time.
You'll see the way it is
once you get used to coming here.
You'll learn not to take it so personal.
Learn to take it day by day.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll have to go and fix that now.
Here's Yung Menenikenaha,
desperately clinging
to his one-stroke lead.
Here's the swing.
It doesn't look good.
Looks like he's pushed it
out to the right.
It lands 25 feet from the green.
This must be disappointing.
It doesn't look good
for Yung Menenikenaha.
He was three strokes
on the happy side of par
until these last three holes.
Look at you, Mr. Andersson.
I think you might be
one of our most frequent visitors.
Hi, Fiona.
Oh, you are persistent, aren't you?
I brought you some books.
They don't seem to have
an awful lot around here.
Letters from Iceland by Auden.
We always meant to read that together,
didn't we?
Do you think it'd be possible to talk alone?
Well, I don't know.
Um, Aubrey's card game
starts in a few minutes,
and then we usually go walking,
and then he does his drawing...
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org