Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
KATE: I did everything
that I was supposed to do:
I didn't cry in meetings:
I didn't wear short skirts:
I put up with the weird
upper management guys
that kiss you on the mouth
at Christmas:
Is it fair that
to be the youngest VP
in my company,
I wiII be the oIdest mom
at preschooI?
Not reaIIy,
but that's part of the deaI:
I made a choice:
Some women got pregnant:
I got promotions:
And I stiII aspire
to meet someone
and faII in Iove
and get married,
but that is
a very high-risk scenario:
And I want a baby now:
I'm 37:
It's too much
for a first date, isn't it?
I said too much:
I'm just gonna
go use the:::
(SIGHING LOUDLY)
I'm gonna need
this to go:
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(GIGGLING)
(GURGLING)
Good morning:
Thank you for
being here so earIy:
Hi: How are you?
Let's get started:
(ALL BABBLING)
That one:
WeII:::
I just don't Iike
your uterus:
Don't get me wrong:
Your eggs are in great shape,
but you have
a T-shaped uterus:
That combined
with your advanced
maternaI age,
it's preventing
proper impIantation:
Why do I have
this T-shaped uterus?
WeII, probabIy has something
to do with medication
that was given to
your mother when
she was pregnant with you:
We used Iot of drugs
back in the '70s
which we now know
can cause infertiIity:
InfertiIity?
Yeah: I wouId say
that your chances
of conceiving are very Iow:
How Iow?
WeII, I don't want to
assign a number to it:
What wouId you assign it?
A coIor, a nickname, a Iocker?
Okay:
One in a miIIion:
I just don't Iike:::
Don't say that again:
ROSE: Come to think of it,
I did take something
for Iiver spots when
I was pregnant with you,
but I reaIIy don't see
how that couId cause
any probIems for your uterus:
It was just a different time:
They didn't warn peopIe
about side effects:
ROSE: They warned me:
I think I might even
have signed something:
What?
Kate, I was 30 years oId:
I was starting to get
Iiver spots: Liver spots!
I just hope you put
this baby mania to rest:
It's not mania:
How many times
have you tried now?
Three?
Nine:
The Iast two
were in vitro:
Have you considered adoption?
I have appIied
for an adoption, yes:
Kate, pIease don't get
a bIack baby:
WeII, I don't think
we'II have to
worry about that,
because for a singIe woman,
it can take
about five years
to get an adoption:
I've just had it
with aII these
movie stars showing off:
''Look at me
and my bIack baby:''
KiII me:
I want you to
stab me with something:
You know, Kate,
not everyone is as toIerant
of your aIternative IifestyIe
as we are:
Being singIe is not
an aIternative IifestyIe:
It is when you're 37:
(CHUCKLING)
Oh, out Iike a Iight:
Have you thought
about using a surrogate?
I saw a thing
about it on DateIine:
No, it's weird:
It's for weirdoes:
I'm just gonna
keep trying by myseIf:
Kate, buiIding a famiIy
is not Iike opening
one of your stores:
It's not
an executive decision:
It's reaI Iife: It's messy:
These hormone injections
make me want to punch you
in the face right now:
No hitting:
That's right:
You're right:
There you go:
Come on:
WeII, how much Ionger
are you gonna put
your body through this?
Look, I know for years
I said I didn't want one,
but I just
woke up one day,
and I feIt Iike
every baby on the street
was staring at me:
Katie's coming out
of the mommy cIoset:
Hey, TyIer:
TyIer, what is this
aII over you?
Is that chocoIate
or poop?
Is that chocoIate or poop?
It's chocoIate:
What if that
had been poop?
I toId you,
messy, but great:
Not bad:
Everybody do a shot
of this pea soup:
Let's go with this:
CaII it ''HeaIth Monster:''
That's great:
It's what I do:
You know,
I was swimming this morning
with the doIphins
in Costa Rica,
and I reaIized something:
I am a great man:
And great men do great things:
I want to open
a fIagship store
right here in PhiIadeIphia:
I want it to be
the biggest store
we ever buiIt,
I want it to be made
of 100% recycIabIe materiaIs,
and I want it to be
so beautifuI that peopIe
want to get married in it:
Kate, join me up here:
I'm wearing a dress, Barry:
Won't you?
Sure:
Okay:
Kate, I want you
to spearhead this
as our new vice president:
This is me transferring
my success to you:
(ALL CLAPPING)
Thank you, Barry:
HoId on:
(ALL CLAPPING)
Thanks:
CongratuIations:
Yeah:
Thank you:
CongratuIations, Kate:
HeIIo:
I'm Chaffee BickneII:
There's just one of you:
I thought Chaffee and BickneII
were two different peopIe:
Come in:
CertainIy:
I started this business
because I saw
a growth market:
We don't do
our own taxes anymore:
We don't program
our computers:
We outsource:
And what is surrogacy
if not outsourcing?
Wait: You're not saying
my baby wouId be carried
by some poor,
underpaid woman
in the third worId:
No:
We're aIso expensive:
Our fee is $100,000:
It costs more to have
someone born than
to have someone kiIIed:
It takes Ionger:
AII of our surrogates undergo
extensive background checks:
CriminaI records,
credit reports,
medicaI histories
and psychoIogicaI testing:
But why do these women do it?
Is it just for the money?
You do your job for the money,
but I bet you Iove it
and you're good at it:
Let me ask you a question:
Do you pIan on hiring a nanny?
Of course:
I have to go back to work:
How is this any different?
A nanny is someone
you trust to take care
of your baby after it's born:
A surrogate mother is someone
you trust to take care
of your baby before it's born:
Either way it's your baby:
And here's my baby:
HeIIo, my sweetheart:
HeIIo, IittIe one:
Oh, yes:
What a good girI: Yes:
Everyone deserves this:
That's why I wanna
remove the stigma
from surrogacy:
There's no wrong way
to make a famiIy:
And you're proof of that:
How do you mean?
Just that you have
this beautifuI baby
using surrogacy:
Oh, no:
My husband and I
conceived Sabrina
the oId-fashioned way:
But you're so:::
OId?
You wouIdn't think so
if you saw my uterus:
But you know what reaIIy made
this IittIe angeI possibIe?
A time machine?
A positive attitude:
You may not have
my fertiIe body,
but with my heIp
you can stiII be a mother:
(SINGING)
Make the cracks break
Shake it tiII they drop
Make the booty go
wah, wah, wah
Make the cracks break
Shake it tiII they drop
Make the booty go
wah, wah, wah
Nice:
Yo, who you waiting on again?
Her name's Angie:
WeII, she might be
my surrogate mother:
That's right:
You got your
baby mama coming:
You know I got
two baby mamas, right?
No, this is different:
You had reIationships
with those women:
No, I had no reIationships
I had reIations
with those women:
No: I'm paying her:
This was set up
by an agency:
There are contracts invoIved:
It's strictIy business:
You pay the biIIs,
she have the baby:
That's caIIed a baby mama:
You ask any bIack man
in PhiIadeIphia:
(RAP MUSIC PLAYING
ON CAR STEREO)
Yo, what if that's
your baby mama?
I don't think that's her:
(SINGING)
Here come your baby mama
Riding a Suzuki
I wanna spend
about 15 minutes here,
then I wanna get
my picture taken
punching the Rocky statue:
Yeah, weII, you're gonna
have to sketch it,
'cause I didn't
bring a camera:
Okay, you did that
on purpose, didn't you?
Trying to sabotage my art:
This might be them:
CARL: AII right,
I'm an artist:
Oscar, this might be them:
I want it
to Iook artistic:
You toId me to teII you when
you were sounding ignorant:
You're sounding ignorant:
Angie?
What?
I'm Kate:
Hi:
Nice to meet you:
This is CarI, my husband:
Common-Iaw:
He aIways says that:
WeII, pIease,
come on in:
Thank you:
Listen, shut her down
in drive and sIam it
into park
or it'II start smoking, okay?
And I'II be back with this:
KATE: So, how Iong
have you two
been together?
We met the summer
after I discontinued
high schooI:
And we've been
together ever since:
He never officiaIIy
asked me to be his wife,
but he never asked me
to not be his wife either,
so things are going
pretty good:
Wow: The pIace is amazing:
Let me:::
BeautifuI:
Kind of Iooks
Iike Kate Hudson's
New York pied-a-terre:
She read that somewhere:
I don't think
she's saying it right:
No, she's saying it right:
Out of aII the pIaces
that we've interviewed at,
this is by far
the nicest:
What does
your husband do?
WeII, I don't
have a husband:
Got this pIace
aII by yourseIf?
Must have a reaIIy fancy job:
WeII, I am the
vice president of deveIopment
for Round Earth Foods:
So you take over
if the president is shot?
(STAMMERING) WeII:::
I Iike your shirt:
Thanks:
It's a shirt-vest kind of:::
I don't know:
I just Iike making
styIes and stuff:
It's something I Iike to do:
What, you don't
get down with rap?
Boy, somewhere in there
I have an oId SaIt-n-Pepa CD:
Hmm:::
What do you do, CarI?
CarI is an
inventorIentrepreneur:
Yeah:
I'm stiII Iooking
for that home run,
you know:
I mean, when I saw
the iPod the first time,
I was Iike:::
I mean, I couId've
kicked myseIf:
That was
so hard on him:
Now we're pretty
tight on cash:
So that Ied you
to surrogacy?
Hey, I gotta say,
when I first thought
about Angie carrying
someone eIse's baby,
I feIt weird about it:
Then I thought,
''Oh, my God,
''if my wife's gotta have sex
with someone eIse's
husband to do this:::''
Out of the question:
'':::that's gonna
cost extra:''
It's out
of the question:
ANGIE: Wow:
This is a nice view:
So, have you
done this before?
No: But I know I'm good
at getting pregnant:
(STAMMERING) That's not
what I'm asking about:
You know,
we've aII had our scares:
No, not reaIIy:
Me neither:
Pardon my asking this,
but how many coupIes, women,
how many peopIe
are you interviewing
before you make your decision?
I guess you're Iike
our sixth or seventh:
And how's it going?
Good:
You know how in science
they say that
everybody's aura gives off
a different coIor?
I can read those auras:
I'm very sensitive
to peopIe's energies:
So, I meet new peopIe
and I get exhausted:
Oh, yeah:
What coIor is my aura?
Let me see:
Sunsetty:
It's Iike a sunset:
I'm reaIIy digging it:
Good:
CongratuIations:
Good, good:
ReaIIy good coIor:
WeII, good:
Because I reaIIy hope
that you Iike me, Angie,
because I'm asking you
for a very big favor,
you know:
You have a God-given abiIity
that I just don't have:
I know I couId
be good at this:
I think you couId, too:
And, you know,
it's nice to feeI:::
Needed?
Yeah: Needed:
Important, usefuI?
I Iike aII those words:
Yeah, weII, I can't do this
without you: I've tried:
I need you, Angie:
I'm gonna make
a decision:
I made my decision:
Decision made:
Kate, I want you to
put your baby inside me:
Angie, I'm gonna
put my baby inside you:
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
This stuff is good:
What's the street name
for this?
So as you can see,
we've transferred three
of Kate's fertiIized eggs
to your womb, Angie:
Now with the hormones
you've been taking,
the probabiIity
of success is about 60%:
You shouId continue
taking the hormones and get
as much rest as possibIe:
And in about two weeks,
you can take
a home pregnancy test:
ANGIE: I Iive right here:
Thanks for driving me
aII the way home:
CarI couIdn't Ieave the house
'cause he's trying
to win a radio contest:
WeII, I wouId've
offered to do it anyway:
Here, Iet me give you
some money for gas:
No, no, pIease:
It's my treat:
ReaIIy?
Of course: Angie,
you don't understand:
I want to be there for you
every step of the way:
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
I hope you don't mind:
I bought you some groceries:
I thought you might want
to start eating organic:
(SCOFFS) That crap is
for rich peopIe
who hate themseIves:
Sorry, this pIace
is such a mess:
I haven't had time
to cIean up:
No, it has a nice
oId-timey smeII:
Is that an aIIigator?
HeIIboy?
No, that's CarI's iguana:
Great: WeII, I'm gonna
put this fruit
in your refrigerator:
CARL: That's the song!
When they pIay Red Red Wine,
you gotta be
the 103:7th caIIer:
What up, baby Iady?
HeIIo:
Shut the door, CarI!
How am I gonna taIk
through a door?
How can you be
the 103:7th caIIer?
Angie, I don't have time
to expIain arithmetic to you:
That don't
make no sense:
I wiII see you in two weeks:
PIease try to get some:::
WouId you grab my smokes?
You know you're not supposed
to smoke in front of me:
I'm trying to quit:
:::rest: Try to get some rest:
Yeah, that's
your situation, aII right?
I'm in here trying to win us
Arena FootbaII tickets:
CIose the door, CarI:
KATE: So,
what we're Iooking for
is at Ieast 15,000 square feet
in the next cooI neighborhood:
It can be open Iots:
It can be buiIdings
that we buy
and tear down,
aIthough
no historic buiIdings:
We want to be perceived
as enhancing the neighborhood,
not destroying
its character:
AIso, Barry wouId Iike
to use mostIy found
and recycIed materiaIs:
So that's gonna affect us,
zoning-wise:
I don't care what we spend,
but we have to get it right:
Shannon! Dante! Anybody?
Sorry about that:
WeIcome to Super Fruity:
What can I get you?
Does the
Orange You GIad
I Didn't Say Banana?
in fact contain banana?
Yeah: Yeah,
but it's a good question:
I think the name's
a IittIe more cIever
than it is informative:
WeII, I wiII try it:
Okay:
Hey, I'm Iooking
for a new apartment:
What is your read
on this neighborhood?
The neighborhood's good:
It's good:
It's changing a Iot:
A Iot of condos going up:
The reaI estate peopIe
are trying to give it one of those
cIever names,
they caII it WeBeSoCa,
which is Webster,
south of Catherine,
I guess:
How's business?
It's a IittIe sIow:
But kind of tough, you know,
going up against the man:
The cops?
Jamba Juice:
Jamba Juice is the man?
Yeah:
Corporate juice pimps:
Thought you shouId know,
and you'II feeI free
to teII your friends:
Okay: I wiII teII them:
Okay, now:
You have a super fruity day:
I want you to start
finding out
what's avaiIabIe between
the 1500 bIock and 1800 bIock
of West Catherine Street:
(CALL WAITING CHIMES)
Ron, I gotta caII you back:
Angie?
Hi, it's Angie:
I know: I know:
So, any news?
WeII, I peed on
one of those stick thingies,
and it said yes:
(SQUEALS)
Angie, that is just
the greatest news!
That's just
unbeIievabIy great:
Yeah, yeah:
Thank you so much, Angie:
If you need anything,
anything at aII,
you Iet me know, okay?
Yeah, okay: I wiII:
I'm having a baby!
(WHOOPS)
(WHOOPS MEEKLY)
(YELLING)
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
HeIIo:
What if the baby's
a hermaphrodite?
What?
A chick with a dick:
I heard it happens
to about 2% of babies:
WeII, that's crazy:
That wouId mean that 10 peopIe
from our high schooI
were hermaphrodites:
Mommy: Mommy:
No, that sounds
about right, actuaIIy:
You can't soIve probIems
by worrying about them:
Is that AIex?
What does she want
for her birthday?
Karaoke RevoIution
or a ceII phone:
She's four:
Do you think it's too much
if I ask Angie
to caII me every day?
She just seems so chaotic:
I don't know
if she's eating right:
Is she getting
enough exercise?
Is she moving around too much?
You're onIy six weeks in:
You can't put her in a cage
and force-feed her:
I know: I know:
Expecting a baby?
Did I teII you?
I found a Iocation
for the new store:
Yeah, I have to
pitch it tomorrow:
It's gonna be a girI:
That's what's making
your hair so dry:
Cash or credit?
Cash:
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Oscar?
You got baby mama drama:
Hey, I Ieft CarI:
I found out he was
effing around on me,
so we got into a huge fight:
Things got
reaIIy physicaI:
Oh, my God:
Are you okay?
Yeah: I didn't
hit him too hard:
Hey, I brought you
a picture of the baby:
You know,
an uItrasound picture:
Oh, my gosh:
Looks Iike a squirreI:
A cute, cute squirreI:
Anyway, it's kind of earIy,
so you can't reaIIy
see anything,
but they took a picture of it
just to make sure
it's growing right:
They said aII the parts
are good:
Why didn't you teII me?
I wouId've been there:
(SIGHS) I didn't want
to bother you:
(SOBBING)
Don't worry:
This couch is more
comfortabIe than it Iooks:
I aIso put a stack
of cIean toweIs for you
in the bathroom:
Do you need
a toothbrush?
Because I have some extras
that I keep for houseguests:
Good night, squirreI:
What we have here
is our Boo Boo Buster
No-SIam Door, okay?
Watch how this works:
You can just sIam it:
It bounces right back:
So you can put your fingers
right on in there,
and it wouIdn't:::
Not you,
it'II onIy work
for baby fingers:
Okay:
Okay?
AIso incIuded
in your premium package,
we have
chiId protection everywhere:
The doors,
the door handIes,
you have the cabinets,
caps aII over the outIets,
cabinets, everything:
It's just baby-proof
aII over the pIace:
ShouIdn't be a probIem
for anybody
over the age of seven:
You sure have
done a great job
getting an earIy jump
on your baby-proofing:
WeII, you guys
are the best in the city,
and I didn't want to risk
being on a waiting Iist:
True: But you can't be
no more than three,
four months pregnant:
There's something
wrong with your toiIet:
I'm sorry I broke
one of your ruIes:
You peed in the sink:
Isn't that against
everyone's ruIes?
OnIy a crazy person
Iocks their toiIet:
It's for the baby:
It's safe:
PIease don't touch
anything eIse:
(DOOR SLAMS)
I'm here:
I'm sorry:
45 minutes Iate:
This isn't Iike you:
I'm sorry, Barry:
I'm just a IittIe
out of whack today:
Want me to get
Dr: Gary down here?
Give you a shot of bee poIIen?
No, thank you:
I'm good:
Let's do this:
Thank you
for waiting, everyone:
This may Iook Iike a
diIapidated warehouse:::
(SINGING)
Lady Luck gets on my side
We're gonna rock
this town aIive
I'II Iet her
rough me up
Thanks, Oscar:
She knocks me out
She waIks Iike she taIks
Iike she taIks
Iike she waIks
She bangs, she bangs
Hey:
What are you doing?
What is this mess?
Oh, baby,
she moves,
she moves
This game is awesome:
Where did you get this?
That's supposed to be
my niece's birthday present:
Sorry:
Angie, what kind
of food is this
for a pregnant woman?
Dr: Pepper,
PringIes,
Tastykakes?
Red BuII?
Angie, Red BuII?
You have to remember
that you are carrying
something very precious:
Like a IittIe puppy:
Yeah:
Yeah: Or a baby:
What you eat, the baby eats:
What you Iisten to,
the baby Iistens to:
If you Iisten to DMX,
the baby comes out going:::
(GROWLING)
Are those cigarettes?
What? No: Where?
Do you know
how stupid it is
to smoke at aII,
Iet aIone when
you are pregnant?
I'm not smoking:
I swear, I'm not:::
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Why wouId you
answer my phone?
HeIIo:
BARRY: Kate,
we're moving forward:
I think that that
is a great decision, Barry:
Yes, Iet's get those
facts and figures, Barry,
into the idea machine:
We shouId cIose
in a coupIe of weeks:
I want you
to put together
a press conference:
How about we start
with a IittIe
community outreach
and get the peopIe
in the neighborhood
on our side,
and then Iet the press
find us?
That's why I'm a genius
for hiring peopIe Iike you:
AII right, you:
My job gives me access
to the most nutritious,
chemicaI-free food
in the worId:
I don't want
my kid born addicted
to high-fructose corn syrup:
There is a thing caIIed
being too heaIthy:
That's what kiIIed Bruce Lee:
ReaIIy?
Where did you read that?
The WeekIy WorId Dum-Dum?
AII right: This is your
foIic acid and this is
your pre-nataI vitamin:
You're serious about this?
I don't want my baby
to have a pinhead:
I can't do it:
I got it: It's going:::
I can't swaIIow it:
What is this?
Water:
It's horribIe!
I need a:::
No, I can't put it
in your butt:
Angie,
cats can do this:
Come on:
It's in there:
Just try:
Just reIax:
CIose your eyes,
open your mouth,
and do it! SwaIIow it:
Take it:
There you go!
You did it:
Hey, I'm just
Iike a Iot of you:
I grew up at 52nd and WaInut:
I attended West PhiIIy High:
I smoked a joint
with HaII & Oates during
the bicentenniaI, aII of that:
But unIike
a Iot of you,
I have since
traveIed the worId:
I've had papaya
on the beach
at Virgin Gorda:
I've toasted pine nuts
at the mouth
of an active voIcano:
I sat down with
Native Americans
and had some amazing saImon:
And I'm here to share
my experiences with you:
You know, I was taIking to
Jimmy Buffett this morning
about trans fats:::
Barry, the time:
WeII, I'm sorry
I can't stay Ionger,
but I have to swing by
my son's graduation:
So I wiII turn you over
to our vice president
of deveIopment,
Ms: Kate HoIbrook:
Good morning and thank you:::
WiII there be
pedestrian access
during construction?
How can you charge
$4 for one mango?
MAN: What's your
carbon footprint?
Okay, how about we Iine up
down front here
at the microphone?
And I can take
your questions:::
your questions
one at a time:
Hi:
Rob Ackerman, WeBeSoCa
SmaII Business
Owners' Association,
and I aIso own
Super Fruity Smoothies:
It's Iike Jamba Juice:
No, it's not:
It's not Iike
Jamba Juice at aII:
I think you've been
to my store:
Yes, I have: I remember:
Did you ever find
that apartment
you were Iooking for?
Not yet: No:
Here's my question:
ExactIy what portion
of your profits
are gonna go
towards rebuiIding
and the revitaIization
of our community?
ALL: Yes!
Thank you for that question:
Those are free, by the way:
You don't have to sneak them:
AII of this stuff
is our gift to you:
Hey, Kate:
Hi:
What a spread:
Thanks:
So, I had
one Iast question
for you:
Okay:
You never toId me
how you Iiked
the smoothie:
WeII, a IittIe too much
banana for me:
Wow:
You know,
Mr: Ackerman:::
No, no, no:
Mr: Ackerman's my dog:
You gotta caII me Rob:
Okay, Rob:
I reaIIy don't
want any tension
with the SmaII Business
Owners' Association:
So I wouId be happy
to sit down with you
some time and:::
You asking me
out on a date?
No:
You sure?
'Cause you Iied
to me once aIready:
Yes, I'm sure:
See you around:
And then he asked me
if I was asking him out,
and I was Iike, ''What?''
CAROLINE ON PHONE: Is he cute?
Yes, but you're
missing the point:
(CALL WAITING CHIMES)
HoId on, CaroIine:
Angie?
ANGIE: I'm starving!
WeII, Iook in
the refrigerator,
there's a big container of
Monster HeaIth Pea Soup:
This Iooks reaIIy
weird and heaIthy:
I don't Iike it:
It's good for you:
I'm not trying
to be dramatic,
but I wouId rather
be shot in the face
than eat this stupid food:
Angie, just eat it, okay? Bye:
CaroIine? She's crazy:
It is Iike Iiving
with a chiId:
(CHILDREN SHOUTING)
WeII, you know,
you wiII IiteraIIy be
Iiving with a chiId soon:
(CHILD SCREAMING)
Maybe you need
to just get used to it:
AIex! AIex!
Wait: I'm an aduIt:
She's an aduIt:
We wiII work this out:
(MAN CHATTERING ON CD)
You know, studies show
that babies can Iearn
a second Ianguage in the womb:
You know, you shouId
pIay an EngIish tape,
so it can come out taIking,
and it can be
in commerciaIs, and you'II
make a Iot of money:
MAN: Next:
The eIephant has big ears:
(MAN CONTINUES CHATTERING
IN SPANISH)
Your CD's skipping:
I'm gonna watch TV instead:
Oh, man: This show's awesome:
In this next cIip is
a dad pIaying basebaII
with his son:
That kid's gonna
hit his dad in the nuts:
BeautifuI day!
What couId
possibIy go wrong?
Hey, have you seen
this one before?
You have a kid
with a WiffIebaII bat
and a dad with a crotch:
Proudest moment in any
father-son reIationship:
You know,
it's not gonna be funny
if you ruin the ending!
Here comes the pitch!
It is!
It's stiII funny!
Oh, man:
Did you just
stick your gum
under my coffee tabIe?
I don't know:
What do you mean,
you don't know?
Do you think
you're at an Arby's
right now?
You know what?
I wish I was
at an Arby's:
'Cause there's better food
and cooIer peopIe there:
(GASPS)
Did you stick
aII this gum
under here?
I don't know!
Maybe you stuck
some of it under there:
Yeah, actuaIIy
you might be right,
because sometimes
when I work
a reaIIy Iong day,
I Iike to come home
and chew a huge wad
of BubbIicious gum
and stick it under
my recIaimed
BarnWood coffee tabIe!
Bitch,
I don't know your Iife!
AII right, Iadies,
there's no need to yeII:
WeII, the mystery remains
as to who put
the gum under there:
No, it doesn't:
Kate, you're used to
being the boss,
and, Angie, being pregnant
makes you feeI
vuInerabIe and sensitive:
I know my hormones
are on a roIIercoaster
right now:
Are you saying:::
That's right:
I'm expecting again:
Expecting what,
a sociaI security check?
It's weird, isn't it?
Yeah:
These confIicts are normaI:
This is a highIy unusuaI
reIationship, and that's what
this support group is for:
Jonathan wouId
Iike to share again:
I mean, I'm onIy saying
because this reminded me
of something
I was journaIing,
just the other day:
I feeI reaIIy bad
because Karen and I
are fighting a Iot,
because I think
she's becoming
morbidIy obese:
And I keep reminding him
that she is pregnant:
And then I reaIized
that I am:::
I'm::: No:
I am::: Okay:
I'm anorexic,
and it's reaIIy hard,
because she's so fat:
And I::: I Iove
Christopher so much,
and he's fat,
and I'm afraid
the baby's gonna be fat:
And it's just me
and two fatties:
I'm proud of you, Jonathan:
Thank you for sharing that:
Yeah, that's a:::
CHAFFEE: Thank you:
Anyone eIse?
I can go:
Dave?
The wife and I are Methodists:
AshIey here is a Wiccan:
It's kind of Iike a witch:
They have stores, I think:
But, you know, at first,
I was a IittIe worried about
a witch carrying my chiId,
but I came around
to the idea,
or she put a speII on me:
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Did you do that, AshIey?
I'm sorry:
I'd Iike to
share something:
CHAFFEE: PIease:
Okay, I don't know,
Iike, aII the therapy terms:::
WeII, I don't know
the therapy terms, either:
I don't go to therapy:
Yeah, but I'd just Iike
to say that Kate is
aIways up in my business:
WeII, when someone
faIIs asIeep with
a curIing iron in their hair,
it becomes necessary
to insert yourseIf
in their business:
That happened two times!
Angie, bottom Iine,
you're carrying Kate's baby,
and you do
wanna get paid, right?
Yeah:
That means that
Kate does deserve
some input:
But, Kate, you must remember
that a surrogate
is not your empIoyee,
but your partner:
Yeah, Kate,
we're partners,
Iike Tom and Jerry:
Tom and Jerry
hate each other:
What? They Iove each other!
What show are you watching?
They're a cat and a mouse:
They have
so much fun together!
ChiIdren in Japan
can understand that:
You are dead wrong:
I want you two to
spend more time together:
(SCOFFING)
That's impossibIe:
We're aIways together:
I don't::: Yeah:
Let Angie heIp you
get ready for the baby:
Decorate
the nursery together,
pick out a crib:
Do aII the things
you wouId do
if you were pregnant,
just do them with Angie:
Wake up, partner:
It's time for birthing cIass:
Yay:
WeIcome to
The Birthing Center:
In this birthing cIass,
we are going to heIp
you new mommies and daddies,
and our mommies and mommies,
Iesbian Iovers:::
No:
:::prepare for
that marathon of Iabor:
Quick question
before we start:
How many of you are pIanning
on doing naturaI chiIdbirth?
That's a good show of hands:
That's so great,
you're aII so great:
And how many of you
are pIanning on using
toxic Western medications
to drug your baby
for your own
seIfish comfort? Anyone?
(WHOOPING)
Now this, this is
the Lexus of stroIIers:
Got an iPod adapter,
Ieather trim:
Check that out, feeI that:
Back of your hand,
back of your hand:
Now, what's the first word
you think of when
you think of stroIIer?
Baby:
Okay, what's
the second word
you think of?
Infant:
No:
It's ''top of the Iine
safety features:''
Check this out:
I'II take it:
(SINGING)
I'm never gonna dance again
GuiIty feet
have got no rhythm
Though it's easy to pretend
I know you're not a fooI
What is the point
of that game?
It gives you points
depending on
how good you sing:
I'm the highest scorer:
You're the onIy one
that's ever pIayed it:
What is that smeII?
I'm dying my roots:
I was just trying
to get some highIights:
So many chemicaIs!
You're a brunette,
you don't understand!
You're a brunette!
I was bIond
when I was a kid!
I'm cIean:
I'm cIean!
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH ON CD)
Hi:
I'm sorry,
I think I may have
overreacted back there:
You think?
It's just this whoIe thing
is very important to me:
And frankIy,
it makes me
a IittIe bit crazy
that you get to feeI it
and experience it,
whiIe I just watch:
And I might be
a IittIe bit jeaIous:
JeaIous?
How couId you be
jeaIous of me?
I'm sorry
I caIIed you stupid:
I'm sorry I farted
into your purse:
What?
I found this sheII
whiIe running barefoot
through the Toronto airport:
I want you to make
our fIagship store
Iike this sheII:
You want it
to Iook Iike the sheII?
You know, Rick,
when you taIk to me
in that tone of voice,
I get incredibIy angry:
I couIdn't have
been more specific:::
You want it to have
the essence of the sheII:
Yes, that's it, exactIy:
Thank you, Kate:
I'm sorry I fIipped, Rick:
Give me the essence
of this sheII:
As your pregnancy progresses,
your partner can heIp you
prep your perineum
for the great stretch
of deIivery:
Massage the area
daiIy with a IittIe EVOO
to heIp you stretch
and prevent tearing:
What is she taIking about?
I think she wants me
to rub oIive oiI
on your taint:
Is it cooI if maybe
I just spray a IittIe PAM
down in that area,
right before
the baby comes out?
You have to admit
it's a vaIid suggestion:
ANGIE: So, are you
pissed that no one
ever married you?
WeII, I aImost
got married once
to a guy named Scott:
We were together
for six and a haIf years:
Damn, just shy
of common-Iaw:
Yeah, actuaIIy:
He was the onIy guy
I ever Iived with:
So now he has three kids,
beautifuI kids,
with another woman,
an oId co-worker
of mine, actuaIIy:
That sucks:
You know what?
Don't worry about it,
'cause you're
super-successfuI,
and you have sweet-ass Iegs:
Thank you, I think:
I had one good boyfriend
before CarI:
ReaIIy?
Donny Landis:
We used to work
at BIimpie together
when we were 16,
and sit and eat pickIes
in the back:
He waited a whoIe month
before he touched my boobs:
Then he went
to the University of Scranton,
and I never heard
from him again:
He was my Justin TimberIake:
Angie, you can stiII have
a totaIIy different Iife:
You're a very
smart person:
Thanks:
(MUSIC PLAYING
ON KARAOKE MACHINE)
KATE: I figured out how to
beat you at this game,
by the way:
Yeah, that's what it's about:
There's a Iot
of techniques
that you can use:
(SINGING OFF-KEY)
I come home
in the morning Iight
My mother says
When you gonna
Iive your Iife right?
You gotta
hoId the note
tiII the end:
We're not
the fortunate ones
And girIs just
want to have fun
Oh, girIs just
Come on,
get up here:
Just wanna,
they just wanna
They just wanna,
GirIs!
GirIs just wanna
have fun
I think that was harmony:
That was harmony!
Look at her:
She's got good jugs:
My avatar is dressed
Iike a whore:
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
So, what do you
wanna taIk about, CarI?
I want you
to come home:
Baby, I miss you:
I haven't had sex
in two weeks:
I've been gone a month:
Whatever:
CarI, after spending
time with Kate,
I kind of feeI Iike I can
evaIuate the direction
my Iife is going,
and I feeI Iike
that direction does not
incIude you: CarI!
You and your
best friend, Kate?
I got bad news:
She's using you
to have a baby:
You think you guys
wouId be friends
in reaI Iife?
She's a business Iady:
It's just business:
You don't even
know her, CarI:
AII right, you got
no right to cut me
out of this deaI:
Who's the one
who said you shouId go
into the baby-making business
in the first pIace? Me:
When the pee-stick said no,
who's the one who figured out
how to keep things going?
Me:
You shouId:::
Here you go:
You shouIdn't have forged
that pregnancy test, CarI:
Maybe you shouId've actuaIIy
gotten pregnant Iike you
were supposed to:
You did a dumb thing,
moving in with that Iady:
ReaI dumb:
We were supposed to
forge the test,
send her the uItrasound
picture in the maiI,
and then cash
the checks:
One, two, three:
The uItrasound Iooked
Iike a squirreI,
by the way:
'Cause it was a squirreI:
That's aII I couId
find on the Internet:
Look, Katie's gonna notice:
You're not getting bigger:
When you go
to the doctor's office,
and you take the test,
she's gonna know:
Sweetie,
you're not smart enough
to puII this off:
Excuse me:
These are mine,
right?
How far aIong are you?
I'm pretty pregnant:
She's 1 4 weeks:
Me, too!
You're so Iucky:
You're not showing at aII:
Nice taIking to you:
(PUNK MUSIC PLAYING)
(RETCHING)
Angie?
I'm going to work:
FeeI better, okay?
I'm done: No:
I'm not done!
Morning sickness:
Sounds Iike she's dying:
Just so pregnant:
Right there:
What?
On your hand:
Where?
Right::: Yup:::
See: Right:
Where?
GirI, that's vomit!
Do something
about them
vomit chunks, girI!
Okay: God!
I Iove it, Kate:
I wanna reward you
with five minutes
of uninterrupted eye contact:
Yay:
(CLEARING THROAT)
You can stay, Rick,
if you::: Okay:
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(RINGING CONTINUES)
In the Iast 24 hours,
I got cIearances
on the titIes and the permits,
tax-incentive grants
from the city
and the states,
and Barry on the pIane
to surf camp:
I'm at the top of my game:
That's great!
Let's do something:
Let's ceIebrate!
I thought we couId order food
and watch this DVD that I got:
It's a British documentary
about a woman
who gives birth
to a 15-pound baby,
vaginaIIy:
Can't wait to not watch this:
You and I need to go out:
Let's go cIubbing:
CIubbing?
You need to get out
of your comfort zone:
Go meet some dudes:
AIthough, I do have
a new ginger body spIash
that I've been dying to try:
Wow!
Yes:
That's reaIIy frisky:
Let's do it:
WOMAN ON CD:
CongratuIations!
(PUMPING AIR)
You're wearing that?
WeII, we are going
to a nightcIub:
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
Ain't no good
gonna come of this:
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
ANGIE: This pIace is awesome:
I haven't been
to a pIace Iike this
since ever:
Okay: She'II have
a doubIe margarita,
no ice, and two of those:
And I'II have
a bottIe of water:
Hey, Iet's dance!
Okay!
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
Stop framing
your face:
Okay:
I think it's good!
It's not:
Here, drink this!
Oh, my God!
That is strong:
Is it?
Try this one:
That is stronger!
I know, I know:
Do this shot:
Why am I doing this?
(EXCLAIMS)
Are you having fun?
I am!
You know what
I've aIways wanted to do?
This one is for the Iadies!
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
AII right!
Good sIow jam!
OId-schooI!
(ALL BOOING)
AII right!
Hey! Hey!
Listen to it!
It's a reaIIy beautifuI song!
If I was aIone, I mean,
not pregnant, I wouId be
macking on aII of this:
There's nobody here
I wouId ever go out with:
Are you serious?
What about that guy?
He Iooks Iike
a Iaundry bag
fuII of meat:
What about
that guy over there?
He's wearing a suit:
It's denim:
You're so picky!
WeII, at Ieast
he's not a grade-A dork
Iike that guy:
Oh, my God, Scott!
Who?
That's my ex-boyfriend, Scott,
that I toId you about:
Why is he here?
You went out
with him?
I did:
Why?
He's beautifuI:
Where?
Look at his mustache!
I know!
I'm gonna go say hi:
No, don't,
it's a bad:::
Kate, I'm gonna
watch your drink:
Hi, Scott:
Kate, my gosh,
you Iook great!
What are you doing here?
I'm just cIubbing:
You remember
my wife, Jean?
Oh, yeah:
Hi, Jean, how are you?
How's everything?
It's great:
We just bought a house
in Bucks County:
I'm stiII doing stuff
for Doctors Without Borders:
RecentIy, we took in
some Hurricane Katrina dogs:
And I was
in a bicycIe accident
that made my penis bigger:
How are you?
I'm doing awesome:
I've just been working a Iot,
and I cannot have babies,
it turns out:
So, good job
picking this one:
What it is, actuaIIy, is
my uterus is T-shaped,
which is Iike:::
So, but actuaIIy,
funny story:
See that:::
Okay, see that
IittIe bIonde woman,
over here?
I am paying her to have:::
Hi: Stop taIking now:
Bye, Jean:
Why does he
make me so crazy?
Forget about him:
He dumped you:
He's an asshoIe:
No,
he's a good person:
you're a good person:
You don't need another
good person around you:
That's your thing:
He's trying to
take that from you!
He wanted to marry me,
and I wanted to
focus on work:
Of course you did!
Because working is awesome
and being married sucks!
That's his car:
What, this right here?
Yes:
SiIver Infiniti,
Penn State sticker,
basebaII mitt
in the backseat:::
This is Scott:
You know what
we shouId do?
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
Yeah!
I was gonna say
Ieave a funny note!
(SOUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Where are we?
WeBeSoCa:
What? You're so wasted:
Stop right here!
This is good:
PuII over right here:
Angie, I'm gonna go
get a ginger carrot juice,
and you shouId go home
and get some rest,
because you Iook
very sIeepy and tired:
Where are you going?
ROB: We're cIosed!
Yeah, weII, it Iooks
about the same
as when you're open:
Don't teII me, your peopIe
are gonna start buIIdozing
the neighborhood tonight:
Yeah, I'm:::
I'm reaIIy, reaIIy sorry
that I'm so good at my job:
What is this,
a taste test?
No, actuaIIy,
I wouIdn't do that
if I were you:
No, that:::
That's not:::
It's horribIe:
Not very good:
It's a combination
of papaya juice and coffee:
I keep this notepad
by my bed in
the middIe of the night,
and I write down
these ideas
when I'm haIf asIeep,
and they never
make any sense:
I do that, too:
And then I wake up,
and I have these IittIe notes
that say things Iike,
''make everybody be twins''
and ''eIectric toiIet:''
Those are not
good ideas:
They're reaIIy not:
So why are you out so Iate?
Are you a prostitute
at night, or:::
No:
I went out tonight
for the first time
in a Iong time,
and I Iet a friend
of mine dress me:
WeII, your friend is
a great American:
(LIQUID SPILLING)
Sorry:
You know,
I reaIIy Iike your Iogo:
Yeah?
Yeah, I did it myseIf:
I reaIIy Iike it:
You don't think
it Iooks Iike a penis?
No, I don't see that:
No?
Over here
you got two obvious:::
I don't know what
you're taIking about:
:::stiff ones::: No?
No, I don't know
what you're taIking about:
You're being nice:
Thank you:
AIso, I don't think
you wanna pick a fight
with Jamba Juice:
I mean, they're not
exactIy WaI-Mart:
WeII, they are:
They're the Exxon
of frozen juice companies:
Yes, I think I saw
a MichaeI Moore
documentary about that:
That's embarrassing:
So is that offer
to get together some time
stiII on the tabIe?
Are you asking me out?
Yes, I think I am:
Okay, yes,
then, yes: Yeah:
Great:
This came off my head:
Some of that
hair's reaI, right?
No: I'm baId: I'm:::
These are reaI:
So we got that
going for us:
Hi, CarI:
What's up,
hot stuff?
What are you doing here?
I toId you to
stay away from me:
You think
you're getting this
payday without me?
No way:
I want my haIf, okay?
And I've got insurance,
the actuaI pee-stick:
I don't even know
if that's reaI:
You probabIy peed on it:
Maybe I did,
maybe I didn't:
But I'II teII you this:
It's gonna raise
a Iot of questions
when Kate takes
this down to the Iab,
and they start doing
DNA tests with CSI stuff,
and moIecuIes and proteins
and the hair foIIicIes,
and they're gonna
connect the dots:
And then you're
gonna be busted:
CarI, I don't wanna do
any of this anymore:
I want a common-Iaw divorce:
You wanna give me back
the ring that I made
for you in metaI shop?
Yeah, I do:
Okay, you know what?
I'II teII you when
this reIationship's over,
because there's a Iot
of girIs there
sitting on the bench
that wanna come
into this game, aII right?
So I am canceIing
this reIationship, okay?
PIease come back
to me, Angie:
Oh, my God!
Wait, wait!
HoId on, hoId on,
pIease!
I wanna say goodbye
to you proper, okay?
We owe that to one another:
Can we pIease
have a quickie
in the car?
What?
What's wrong with you?
You know what?
I'm not gonna be here for you
when Kate kicks you out:
So deaI with that:
My girI rocks?
My girI does not rock, okay?
My girI is a divorcee:
So I hope
you got KIeenex,
'cause you just said goodbye
to the cooIest thing
that ever happened to you:
I'm gonna bang your friends:
Consider them aII banged:
The reason I caIIed you
coIIect is 'cause it's gonna
take more than a few quarters
to express how I feeI
about you, baby:
Hey, where you going?
I knew something was up
when I saw you beating
your baby bump Iike that:
It wasn't supposed
to happen Iike this:
Everything just
got way out of hand:
I think
I'm just gonna spIit:
That's a good idea:
Just sIip away
in the dead of night
and Ieave Kate thinking
you stoIe the baby:
That wouId destroy her:
This ain't some IittIe scam
where you just caII up
Domino's and be Iike,
''Yo: You know, I'm doing
some church youth event:
I need 10 free pizzas:''
Why, does that work?
You're Iying
about the existence
of a human being:
If you don't teII her,
you'II never be abIe
to Iive with yourseIf:
Maybe you can teII her
after I'm gone:
I'II teII you
what I'm gonna do:
Not a damn thing,
'cause you're gonna
teII her yourseIf:
I've got
a surprise for you:
I got a surprise
for you, too:
It is a brochure for
the PhiIadeIphia
SchooI of TextiIes:
They've got
a great fashion program:
Thanks:
But that's not
the whoIe surprise:
Open it:
I'm giving you
your check earIy:
No, Kate: I can't take that:
You gotta put
that through the agency:
No, it's not gonna bounce:
Don't you trust me?
Where are we going?
You have
an uItrasound appointment:
What? No:
Today's Thursday:
UItrasound isn't Thursday:
Birthing cIass is Thursday:
UsuaIIy, but you're 18 weeks,
and so you have
another uItrasound:
I can't wait:
I hope the baby's
in a good position, so we can
see its IittIe profiIe,
because I'd reaIIy Iike
to get one of those printouts
to hang over my desk:
Do you think
it couId Iook
Iike me yet?
CouId the baby
Iook Iike you
at 18 weeks?
What if it has
IittIe tiny gIasses?
I'm joking:
That's me trying
to make a joke:
That's coId:
Sorry about that:
Just:::
(HUMMING)
If::: When you get mad,
do you stay mad
for a Iong time?
Yes, yes: I'm a big
grudge-hoIder, actuaIIy:
Hear that?
What?
That's your heartbeat:
You nervous?
Yeah, a IittIe:
Okay, I'm just:::
Just having
a IittIe troubIe finding:::
You're gonna have
a Iot of troubIe:
Kate, I gotta
teII you something:
I'm not reaIIy:::
There's the baby's heartbeat:
(SCOFFING)
I'm not reaIIy::: What?
Isn't it wonderfuI?
HoIy shit!
There's a baby in there?
Yep!
How did it get in there?
It's a miracIe:
What did you
wanna teII me?
I'm so excited:
Yay!
What do you mean, pregnant?
I thought you was
Iying to Kate:
I was: I am:
It's not Kate's baby:
It's CarI's:
So the procedure thing:::
Didn't take:
And then I was crying,
so CarI and I did it:
And it's just country:
I missed a coupIe periods,
and I thought maybe it was
my hormones, you know
what I'm taIking about?
No, I don't know
nothing about that:
But then I started spotting,
and I thought
that was my period,
but usuaIIy I don't
have a heavy fIow:
(SHUSHING) Stop it:
My boobs didn't hurt,
so I was Iike,
''It's not my period:::''
You know what?
Look, I'm just gonna
Iay it out, aII right?
I'm not discussing
the Iady business with you:
I mean, I think
it's a beautifuI thing
and aII that,
but it's disgusting, okay?
And I'm afraid
if we keep
taIking about it,
that our cycIes
might synchronize:::
What am I
supposed to do, Oscar?
I can't cash that check:
I can't take any
of Kate's money:
But I am gonna stay here
untiI I figure out what to do:
I don't know anything
about being a mother:
You better start Iearning:
It's good
if the kid's raised here,
though, you know?
Better schooI,
better apartment,
better situation:
Is that what you want?
No, I wanna keep it:
Have you read this?
''One in four miIIion babies
are born with
a fuII set of teeth:''
Angie, it's gonna be fine:
Where you going?
I have a date
with that guy, Rob:
Are you gonna
teII him about me?
No: I've made
that mistake before:
It turns out
they don't Iike it
when you taIk about
the successfuI transfer
of embryos on the first date:
Read the chapter
about hermaphrodites:
You won't sIeep for a week:
HeIIo, foIks,
my name is Chet:
I'm your waiter:
Are you foIks famiIiar
with the raw food
vegan movement?
Yeah:
I think he is,
more than I am:
Yeah, yeah:
Okay, shouId we start
with some appetizers?
Yeah: How's the
sea keIp pizza?
That's got
a nice earthy taste,
IittIe bit of a dirt taste:
It's very nice:
SaIty: We'II stay
away from that:
You know what Iooks good
is the bIue aIgae?
You wanna just:::
Yes, yes:
ExceIIent:
Be right back:
So what kind of Iaw
did you practice?
Corporate: You know
when you're watching the news,
and you see
some bIoated CEO
invoIved in a scandaI,
and you kind of
wonder to yourseIf,
''How is this prick
not going straight to jaiI?''
Sometimes it was
because of me:
You must be very proud:
AII right,
here's your
bIue-green aIgae
and a yeast bowI
for the tabIe:
Thank you:
Thanks:
This Iooks good:
Oh, it's warm:
Yeah:
What about you?
You Iike your work?
I do, but I mean,
I have other things
in my Iife besides my job:
I Iike to traveI for work:
Oh, that's a:::
That's a good yeast:
Very yeasty:
How Iong have
you been vegan?
I'm not:
I'm sorry: I'm not,
I thought that you were,
and that's why
I took you here:
Because of where you work,
I never wouId have:::
Oh, God:
Can we:::
Yeah, you want to:::
I eat meat:
Yeah, I eat meat
Iike nobody's business:
I'II have a Iarge steak
with provoIone,
no Cheez Whiz, no onions,
peppers on the side,
don't overcook the meat:
AIso, I'd Iike you
to sIice me a new fresh roII,
because those ones
have been sitting out
for a Iong time:
I want a Birch Beer,
coId, no cup:
You reaIIy shouId
consider changing those
Styrofoam cups to paper ones,
because they're very bad
for the environment:
Yeah, I'II have the same:
I'm sorry:
I'm a IittIe
overIy thorough:
Some peopIe wouId say
that I am bossy
and controIIing:
No, that's just prejudice:
They caII you
bossy and controIIing
'cause you're a woman:
But if you were a man
doing the same stuff,
you'd just be a dick:
What?
Nothing:
No one's ever
caIIed me a dick
before on a date:
Term of endearment:
So Iisten,
there's something that
I haven't toId you:
And it may be
a deaI-breaker:
Oh, boy,
you are super fruity,
aren't you?
No:
But I do
have a daughter:
She's 1 2 years oId and
she Iives with me
every other weekend:
I think that's great:
Yeah?
Okay:
You have any kids?
I've never
been married:
WeII, Kate,
you don't have to
be married to have a kid:
Do you want to
go back to my:::
Yes:
I was going to
say apartment,
just to be cIear:
Yeah: I'm 37:
I know how this works:
Okay:
Let's go:
It's actuaIIy
this way:
Okay:
1 406:
Yeah:
Oh, no: No, no, no:
Look who just got inducted
into the waIk of shame:
Why are you aII shiny
Iike a souI food cook?
I want you, now,
to Iook your partner
in the eye,
and I want you to teII her
she is beautifuI:
You are beautifuI:
TeII her,
''You are strong:''
You are strong:
TeII her, ''Thank you
for giving me this baby:''
Thank you
for giving me
this baby:
Are you crying?
No:
I am: I'm crying a IittIe bit:
AII right:
Romaine, Cheyenne,
time to go:
We have a pIaydate
with Wingspan and Banjo:
Those kids wouId have got
their asses handed to them
in my neighborhood:
My sister wants to know
what kind of cake
you want for the shower:
Kate, I don't think
I shouId go to that,
you know?
I mean, that's just
kind of for you:
No, it's for both of us:
My mother wants to meet you
and make you feeI weird:
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Excuse me:
Yes: Barry, hi:
No, I'm puIIing into
the construction site
right now:
Think I went to
a rave here once:
PIease, I asked you
to wait in the car:
It's too hot in there,
and your weirdo
air conditioning,
I don't know how to work it:
Barry, I'm sorry:
Kate, where you been?
I'm having second thoughts
about this Iocation:
Is it the taxes?
It's probabIy
because this pIace gives you
a weird vibe, right?
Yes: That one:
I'm not getting
good vibes here:
And if there's one thing
Oprah taught me,
it's to trust my instincts
and foIIow my fear:
Is that the episode
where she got
her ears pierced?
No, this was
at her home in Maui:
Who are you?
I'm Angie:
She works for me:
She's very intuitive:
I read peopIe's energies:
You read energies?
Yeah:
Good: Very good:
How's the energy
in this site?
Green, mostIy:
Like heaIthy Ieaves:
Money?
ExactIy:
I Iike your maid:
So do I:
Let me put my hands
into your hands,
and I'II whisper to you
the secret of success:
So, are we back on?
We were never off:
KATE: What did he say?
ANGIE: The secret of success:
And?
He said
''Have a big penis:''
No, he didn't:
Yeah, he did:
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROANS)
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God:
Look! Wait:
Is that the face?
I think:
That was a big one!
Oh, my God:
What does it feeI Iike?
Like if you ate
a meatbaII sandwich,
then that
meatbaII sandwich
was kicking you:
I think I gotta
teII Rob about you
and the baby:
What? Why?
WeII, we've been
going out for a month,
and I didn't think
it wouId turn into anything,
but it sort of is:
I don't think
that's a good idea:
You know,
he may break up
with you:
Yeah, but the Ionger I wait,
the weirder it's gonna be:
It's gonna be weird
no matter what:
He'II know
I'm hiding something:
I'm the worst Iiar:
Okay, teII me
three things about yourseIf
and make one of them a Iie:
Okay:
I'm from PennsyIvania,
I am a Leo,
and I am 5'9'':
I don't want to:::
This is why
I can't Iie to him:
You're not Iying to him,
you're just not
teIIing him the truth,
there's a big difference:
Is there?
I don't know:
Don't ask me:
ANGIE: (SINGING) Don't speak
I can't even take it
And I don't
need no reason
Hi:
I'm Rob:
I'm here
to pick up Kate:
Oh!
(MUMBLING)
Sorry, I'm a IittIe earIy:
I was just
in the neighborhood, so:::
Do come in:
HeIIo, I'm AngeIa:
Okay:
I'm Kate's sister, so:::
We are in the same famiIy:
And I was just practicing
the ancient Japanese
art of karaoke:
Karaoke?
Yes:
You deIightfuI:::
HeIIo: Oh, weII:
I can see
how she Iikes
you so much: Kate?
You Iive here?
No,
no:
I Iive in New York City
in a pied-a-terre apartment
with a husband
that I have:
Wow, so you're just
kind of visiting here, or:::
He's in the stock market:
So we go from city to city,
visiting other stock markets:
And that's how we roII:
It's funny, 'cause you guys
don't Iook aIike at aII:
Oh, weII:
Different dads?
Yes:
We have different dads:
That's what we have:
Thank you for that:
Is that my phone?
I didn't actuaIIy hear:::
It was:
HoId on,
it's from Europe: HeIIo?
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
Yes, interesting:
It's a business caII:
So nice to meet you:
KATE: What?
ANGIE: Yes:
What? How Iong
did he taIk to you?
Hi: Look at you, earIy bird:
Okay, it's nice to see you:
Oh, my gosh,
weII, Iet's go:
Yeah:
Does your sister
want to come with us?
No, she's not weII:
Bye, AngeIa:
Adios:
OSCAR: Push, woman:
Yeah, good:
Push, and boom!
CongratuIations: Look:
Popcorn:
See?
It's that easy:
What movie we watching?
Extreme VaginaI DeIivery:
The miracIe of
reaIIy big chiIdbirth:
Oh, damn!
You can't come
back from that:
That's why you aIways
want to stay over here, huh?
It's one of the reasons:
WeII,
how Iong
is your sister
in town?
Angie's not
reaIIy my sister:
I know:
She's your haIf-sister:
She toId me:
What eIse did
AngeIa teII you?
WeII,
she toId me
that you Iike me a Iot:
WeII, she's a Iiar:
She's a known Iiar:
What is this?
JiIIian wants me to take her
to an exhibit of abnormaI
skuIIs at the Mutter Museum:
Do you need me
to get out of here?
No, no: No,
I was gonna see
if you wanted to come:
You want me
to meet your daughter?
Is that a bad idea?
No: I reaIIy,
reaIIy Iike kids:
Oh, my God: I know.
Have you read
this articIe?
This Chaffee BackneII Iady:
BickneII:
She is a piece of work:
I mean, her whoIe
surrogacy process
is very science-fictiony:
There's so many kids
that need to be adopted:
WeII, adoption
can take years:
And these peopIe wouId pay,
Iike, you know,
$50,000, in order to:::
It's $100,000, actuaIIy:
You know, have your baby
custom-carried by a
gestation assistant:
What is that?
WeII, I think it's probabIy
more compIicated
than it seems:
A Iot of rich peopIe
getting what they want:
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING
ON RADIO)
(EXCLAIMS) I hate that song:
Here you go:
You got it?
Yeah, I'm good:
OSCAR: So, do you feeI
good about yourseIf?
You're just going to Iet
Kate go ahead and have
this whoIe baby shower, right?
You don't reaIize
how ruthIess that is, right?
Hey, man, that's a sweet cake:
That's tight: That's tight:
Service entrance,
straight to the terrace:
What am I
supposed to do?
TeII her today,
in front of aII of her friends
and her famiIy?
No, no, no:
Wait tiII the chiId is,
Iike, nine years oId,
and then teII her,
Iike my first ex did me:
Okay, I'm going to
teII her tonight:
Or Monday:
But then it'II ruin her week,
so maybe I shouId
wait tiII Friday:
Then it wouId
ruin her weekend,
so maybe I shouId:::
I don't know
when I'm gonna teII her:
When's the best day
to teII someone
horribIe news?
Yesterday:
I teII you,
a pagan birth
is a fascinating thing:
You know, now that
I've done it myseIf,
it seems crazy
not to eat the pIacenta:
I'm sorry,
did you say poIenta
or pIacenta?
PIacenta,
the afterbirth, yeah:
AshIey turned us onto it:::
Angie:
Hi, I'm CaroIine,
Kate's sister:
Nice to meet you:
Hi, nice to meet you:
And this is
our mother, Rose:
Hi, nice to meet you:
How do you do?
So, teII me,
once the baby is born,
wiII you just go away,
or shaII I expect you
at Christmas?
Mom:
What?
This is a reasonabIe question:
AII my friends are asking:
KATE: WeII, we haven't
reaIIy taIked about it:
No, there's not
a Iot of stuff
we've taIked about,
we have a Iot of stuff
to taIk about:
I think Angie might want
to visit the baby
a few times a year:
You know, or I might be
out of town, I don't know
where I'm going:
ANGIE: I mean, I think
I've got pIans,
but I'II definiteIy caII:
Summer, if we're on vacation,
maybe Angie wouId want to
come with us some time:
And who knows where
we're going to be
in a year?
I think it's reaIIy important
that she remain a part
of the baby's Iife:
Yeah, you know,
or compIeteIy separate:
We're just going to
pIay it fast and Ioose,
you know,
just see how it
aII shakes out:
AIways been my motto:
Rob? Hi:
Hi:
Hey, I know
it's your sister's
baby shower,
just, you haven't caIIed me
in days: I thought maybe
I did something wrong:
No, you didn't do anything:
Is it because
I wanted to introduce you
to my kid?
No, Rob, I just:::
I think you and I
view the worId differentIy:
Bad news peopIe,
party's over:
Start heading
for the door:
Who Iet him in here?
CarI, don't say
something stupid:
She hasn't toId you:
I thought since
you guys were
best friends,
she probabIy
toId you everything:
Shut your mouth, CarI:
What is going on?
She's not even pregnant, okay?
I mean, Iook:
Angie what is that?
FeeI it:
It's moving:
Yeah, it's a baby:
And it's yours:
What are you saying?
Kate,
I reaIIy tried to
make you a baby,
I swear:
What are you saying?
We took a test
as soon as we got home,
and the procedure didn't work:
And I was reaI,
you know, horny,
because of aII the hormones:
So we did it:
I feIt Iike a faiIure:
And CarI toId me
you were going
to get somebody eIse:
Those hormones can aIso
give you a faIse negative:
That's why they want you
to wait two weeks
before you take a test:
Wait, what?
So she might
not be pregnant?
Yo, where you
escape from, man?
I'm saying
the baby might be CarI's,
but it might stiII be mine:
Okay, then
forget what I said:
I'm trying to
pIay catch-up here:
So you get
your sister pregnant,
but she sIept with him?
No, she's not my sister:
She's an ignorant
white trash woman
that I paid to carry my kid:
I deserve that:
No, you don't:
How couId you do that?
This is why I didn't
caII you back, Rob,
because this is
the kind of seIfish,
science fiction shit
that you don't
want any part of:
WeII, the upside is,
it Iooks Iike
I might be a dad:
So if it's a boy,
I want to marry you:
Oh, my God:
What?
I'm so sorry
about what's happened:
But I think it's best
to wait untiI the pregnancy
is far enough aIong
for DNA testing,
before we do
anything drastic:
(EXCLAIMS)
That was quite a kick:
How can you
be pregnant?
Your eggs are
from the '40s:
You're upset:
And you're saying
hurtfuI things:
It's understandabIe:
We'II have
a DNA sampIe
sent to the Iab:
The rest wiII be
handIed in famiIy court:
Of course, if the baby
turns out not to be yours,
we'II waive our fees:
What about aII
the background checks?
Passed:
With fIying coIors:
You were Iiving with her,
and you didn't
notice anything:
She fooIed us, Kate:
She fooIed us aII:
I fooIed myseIf:
I booked you a room here,
untiI we sort this out:
So you're done with me,
now, is that it?
You don't need me anymore?
Gonna try to find
some other IowIife
you can use
to give you everything
you ever wanted?
I'm not gonna do this:
You know, you think
you're better than me:::
I am certain
that I am better
than you:
Okay, we're being honest now?
Here's one:
I can have a baby,
and you can't:
And that drives you crazy:
Get out of my car:
Your stupid space car's
Iocked me in:
Don't touch it
when I'm touching it:
Just open it!
Yeah, you bang on the door,
that's how you open it:
WeII, you can't
even find the stupid:::
Raised by woIves!
TeII me
how to open it!
Stop touching it,
and I wiII open it:
(LOCK CLICKS)
It is open now:
Good:
CARL: Look, buddy, you don't
have to seII me on
the product, I'm aIready in:
Here's what I'm asking:
Do you have a discount poIicy
if you're reIated to one
of the girIs that's gone wiId?
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Enjoy it, Kate:
This is your baby:
I'm going to go
hide this sheII
somewhere in the store:
Hey:
Can I get an
Orange You GIad
I Didn't Say Banana?
(GAVEL POUNDING)
JUDGE: AII right:
HoIbrook v: Ostrowiski:
Present:
I take it this is
a paternity case:
ActuaIIy,
it's a maternity case,
Your Honor:
Katherine HoIbrook
hired this woman
to be her surrogate,
now we're not sure
whose egg this is in here:
What are you doing here?
Angie needed
some IegaI heIp,
so I'm heIping:
And you are?
I'm Rob Ackerman,
formerIy with the firm
Swanson and Weisberg:
FormerIy?
Yeah, now he makes
fruit smoothies:
You mean Iike Jamba Juice?
Yes, Your Honor,
it's exactIy Iike
Jamba Juice:
'Cause I Iove Jamba Juice:
Yeah:
Who doesn't?
You don't need a Iawyer,
you know,
we're just here
to read some resuIts:
But I know
that I have the right
to a Iawyer:
Objection:
And you are?
CarI Loomis,
Your Highness:
I'm here to seek
joint custody
of that fetus:
Your Honor,
this dummy used to be
my husband:
Did you provide
a DNA sampIe,
Mr: Loomis?
Uh-huh:
What's that now?
Did you give someone
a hair foIIicIe or
a viaI of your bIood?
No: Not as it pertains
to this case:
AII right,
then you're going to
have to take a seat:
And if you disrupt
the proceedings again,
I'II ask the baiIiff
to escort you out:
Not scared of her:
JUDGE: May I have
the Iab resuIts, pIease?
Okay, I wouId Iike to testify
on behaIf of the prosecution:
There is no prosecution:
Aye, aye, sir:
If you insist,
you can make a statement
and have it entered
on the record:
No, no,
that's not necessary:
No, I insist:
I wouId Iike to say something:
I'm sorry:
I never shouId
have Iistened to CarI:
I shouId have done
the right thing: I just:::
This whoIe thing
made you feeI so happy:
And it made me
feeI so important:
I shouId have
toId you the truth:
And I'm sorry I didn't:
I was just scared:
I aIso want to thank you:
I didn't Iike it sometimes,
but you made me grow up:
I know I was supposed to
heIp you have a baby:
But you ended up teaching me
how to be a mother:
So thank you:
And I'm sorry:
She'd be a great mom,
Your Honor:
Kid wouIdn't
get away with shit:
JUDGE: Let's watch
the Ianguage, pIease:
Freedom of speech,
Iook it up,
it's in the thing:::
What Ms: Ostrowiski
is trying to say,
Your Honor,
is that what
she did was wrong:
It was extremeIy wrong:
CooI it, you're my Iawyer:
And one of these Iies,
that's so easy
to spin out of controI:
This guy,
CarI Loomis,
he Iied to Angie:
And then Angie Iied to Kate,
and Kate Iied to me,
and it was a mistake:
I mean, it was a:::
It's a mess, this is aII a:::
It's a mess:
This is a reaI mess:
That's the worst
cIosing argument
I've ever heard:
Yeah, I know:
I know: I'm a IittIe rusty:
Kate: I just never wanted
to come back
into a courtroom ever again:
And I came here for you:
Thank you:
I rest my case:
You Honor, I think we
are more than ready
for you to read the resuIts:
Let the record show
that the DNA test
indicates that Ms: HoIbrook
is not the mother
of this chiId:
Okay to get home?
Of course:
Yeah:
I remember the day
I found out I was
going to have a kid:
Wow: I'II never take it
for granted again:
WeII, I'd stiII Iike
to meet that kid some time:
I'II give you a caII:
You come by the store:
Okay, I'II definiteIy come by:
Okay:
I'm sorry, Kate:
It's okay:
I just threw up:
You Iook nice in a suit,
by the way:
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Angie:
Hey:
So, I guess
I'II see you Iater?
ProbabIy not, actuaIIy:
Right:
I've been off
Dr: Pepper
for two weeks:
This is water:
Good for you:
Thanks:
(LIQUID SPLASHING)
Angie, I think
your water broke:
Wait, what?
Your water is breaking:
I got to get a bus
to take me
to the hospitaI:
Let me drive you,
I'II drive you:
Okay, hoId this:
I'm not due
for three weeks:
I know:
ShouId we
cIean that up?
No, somebody eIse
wiII get that:
This is reaIIy happening,
isn't it?
This is reaIIy happening:
It's so weird,
'cause I feeI totaIIy caIm:
Come on, it feeIs Iike
I'm shitting a knife:
Okay:
Why won't you
bitches heIp me?
Just breathe:
Okay, I'II take it
from here:
I want to go with her:
Are you famiIy?
She's my sister:
WeII, okay:
Oh, God, hoIy:::
This way:
Sorry, sorry:
Give me some drugs:
Give me this:
You don't need drugs:
I want those drugs:
No:
You'II never
get me, pig!
(SCREAMING)
Get out of my way!
Oh, God!
(GLASS SMASHING)
Angie!
Is that guy dead?
Is he dead?
We need some
oIive oiI to rub
on my taint:
It's too Iate:
Okay, this is
gonna go great:
Yeah:
Kate:
It's twins:
Gross:
I don't know
what you're crying about:
I gotta waIk out
of here aIone:
That's a good joke,
Dr: Manheim:
Okay:
Okay, and give me
a big one:
Big one! Whoa!
Nothing: Okay:
AII right, ready?
Kate, I'm so gIad
you're here:
You don't Iook good,
by the way:
I feeI a IittIe dizzy:
Okay:
Okay, and give me
a big one:
Big one: Whoa:
(BABY CRYING)
CAROLINE: Good morning:
Hi:
How are you feeIing?
Embarrassed:
I fainted
in the deIivery room:
WeII, Oscar's bringing you
a change of cIothes,
and Mom is here,
in case you die:
Great:
And somebody eIse
wants to say hi: Hey:
It's embarrassing:
I'm scared your friend, Angie,
has me on speed diaI:
She caIIed me, Iike,
10 times to get down here
and take care of you:
Me, too:
How is she?
How is the baby?
Great, she's just:::
She's beautifuI:
It's a girI:
Got a smiIe:::
Good morning:
HeIIo:
Hi:
Hi, there: Hi:
CouId I have
a moment aIone
with Kate, pIease?
Sure: I'm going to
go check on Mom:
Hi: How can I heIp you?
Hi: WeII, we got
your bIood work back:
You are sIightIy anemic,
which expIains the fainting:
But there's something eIse
you need to know:
You're pregnant:
That's impossibIe:
I paid a man thousands
of doIIars to teII me
that that's impossibIe:
WeII, you're onIy about
eight weeks aIong, but you are
definiteIy pregnant:
He said the chances
were one in a miIIion:
WeII, I'd start
buying Iottery tickets,
if I were you:
Wait a minute:
Congrats:
Rob:
I'm pregnant:
What?
You okay?
Oh, my God:
Hi: Can I see her?
She's gorgeous:
What's her name?
This is Stef:
Stephanie,
that's beautifuI:
No, Stefani:
Like Gwen Stefani:
Even better: HeIIo:
Are you waking up?
So, you're pregnant:
How'd you know that?
I can read
peopIe's energies:
PIus, your sister toId me:
ALL: (SINGING)
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday,
dear Stefani
Happy birthday to you
Hey, Angie:
Are you two
stiII together?
No, we're not together:
He's just trying to be
a better father, take
some parenting cIasses:
He just started:
I see you:
You think you're funny, punk?
What'd I teII you
about hiding from me?
Quit hiding from me:
You think you're funny?
HeIIo:
This is a gasoIine-powered
mini-Ninja motorcycIe:
Oh, my God, CarI:
You bought a motorcycIe
for a one-year-oId?
That is crazy:
ReaIIy crazy:
That's exactIy
what she wanted! Yay!
That's great:
Kate, Iet me give
your baby my mojo:
WeII, time is Iove:
Got to run:
Whoa!
(BABIES GURGLING)
I Iove this episode:
('60s POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org