Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Your friend is late.
He'll be here.
Oh, yeah?
I do have other bidders.
I personally vouch for this man.
Oh, well,
I trust you, Michael, but...
you see, with each degree
of separation...
comes a degree of uncertainty.
Mr. Turner.
Mr. Vas.
The KGB once tried
to set me up...
so I had to kill
three of their agents...
and then I hunted down
their families.
The point is, if I sense
anything out of the ordinary...
No, the point is, I haven't seen
anything from you yet...
to justify a payment
of $20 million.
So, before I hand over
a small fortune...
and risk my life,
I want to know 100%...
that you can, in fact,
deliver the device.
That's the point.
Very well.
Michelle... owner's manual.
This is your show of good faith?
Well, you're still alive.
You consider that
a show of good faith.
- What do you have for me?
- Down payment... $1 million.
So, when do I get the device?
Let's say ten days.
Michael,
you take that telephone...
and I will call you
and tell you how to proceed.
You keep it on you all the time.
As for you, sir,
the next time we meet...
I suggest you be on time.
Nice coat.
Well done.
See you around.
- So far, so good?
- Yeah, so far.
- Kevin's got a tail.
- Is it Vas?
They don't look Russian,
but they don't look friendly.
We'd better go back for him.
You ordered us not
to jeopardize our cover, sir.
Hey, turn left.
Turn left!
Kill him!
- Ambush on the castle steps.
- Come on, faster...
Let's go!
Get down! Get down!
There he is! Pull over!
You're jeopardizing the mission.
Uhh!
You are the mission.
God, that was close.
Did you see who they were?
Kevin?
Doesn't this all smack
of extreme desperation?
A nuclear bomb that fits neatly
into a carry-on suitcase?
Kevin spends two years
getting close to these people...
in order to position you
as the buyer.
Vas won't deal
with anyone else...
and we have nine days
to make this work.
I'd say desperation
was the order of the day.
Maybe Vas set Kevin up.
My guess is,
it's a rival buyer.
Could be Pakistanis,
Chechnyans, North Koreans.
- Libyans.
- Try the entire Middle East.
Adrik Vas is a businessman.
He'll take anyone's money.
Why kill Kevin
if they could just outbid him?
We have deeper pockets.
He priced them out of the game.
- Who do you think it is?
- Well, the cold war is over.
These guys
don't wave flags anymore...
and fanaticism,
terrorism is global.
Whoever it is decided
to eliminate the competition...
and force Vas to deal with them.
So, the future
of the so-called free world...
may rest in
this young man's hands.
Jake Hayes here...
Big-time Tickets.
Whatever you want, I'll get you.
Yankees, third base line.
Knicks, courtside.
Rangers, on the ice.
Masters, I'll put you
on Tiger's tee, a'ight?
No matter what you want,
I got it for you.
Big-time Tickets.
What you need?
Come on, man. You call me
three hours before tipoff...
against the Lakers?
The Knicks sell out every game.
Since I like you, for 850,
I'll get you section 24, row 9.
Twelve back from the bench.
Right behind Woody
with a good view of Spike...
unless he's got that
turban thing on his head...
lookin' like Yasser Araneck.
Check.
Hold on a second.
What's up? Big-time Tickets.
Jake Hayes. What you want?
Checkmate.
"Lion King"? I can't do that.
Jake Hayes here.
Big-time Tickets.
Mr. Johnson, you gonna
go to the game tonight...
or you want to do some business?
Shit, he's kickin' your ass!
Don't look at me.
You need to watch that castle...
'bout to bitch-slap your bishop.
Ehhhh! You lose, Opie.
Damn!
OK, so I'll give you
four hundred for the two.
- Yo, Jake, let's get a slice.
- Hold on one second.
Hello? Big-time Tickets.
Hey, man. I can't.
You always workin'.
Hey, honey. What's up?
OK, I'm gonna
pick you up from work.
Then we'll talk all about it.
Love you, too. Bye.
I gotta pick up
my girl, man.
So check this out...
you're gonna do this, right?
I'm gonna do this.
You're gonna do this.
Then you're gonna do this.
But I'm gonna do this...
and when you're
thinkin' about this...
I'm gonna do this.
Then the game's over.
So why don't you
give me $20 right now...
- and we'll save twenty minutes?
- Screw you.
You didn't know chess
was a contact sport, did you?
Hey, honey.
Julia Benson.
She's a nurse's aide.
They've been together
three years.
She lives with her sister
and brother-in-law...
in Jersey City.
Amazing resemblance
to Kevin, sir.
Yeah.
Like seeing a ghost.
I don't know how
you're gonna react.
Heh.
Come on. Wait a minute.
I should've known.
The mood swings,
the weight gain.
What weight gain?
You're pregnant.
I want everybody to know.
Hey, everybody!
My woman's havin' a baby,
and we're gettin' married!
I'm not pregnant.
We don't have to get married.
Marriage is a big step.
We should wait a while.
We're young.
I'm moving to Seattle.
Seattle, like,
Seattle Supersonics, Seattle?
Wait a minute.
That's pretty far.
I got offered a job there.
What kind of job
are you gonna get in Seattle...
that you can't get in New York?
A friend of mine
from junior college called.
- Who?
- Kenneth.
Your ex-man Ken?
He's managing a company
out there, and he offered.
So, you're leaving me
and going back to Ken.
No.
- Are you leaving me?
- Sort of, but it's not...
So, you're leaving me
and going back to Kenneth?
- That's what I asked you.
- The Ken part is just business.
And what's the leaving me part?
Pleasure?
Pain.
Your sister put you up to this.
She never liked me.
- It's been three years, Jake.
- I know it's been three years.
We're in the same situation
that we were in when we met.
Meaning, we're not married.
We're not married,
we can't afford to get married.
And it doesn't look like
it's ever gonna change.
You know, poor people
do get married.
I know, but I don't feel
like fighting with you...
every day because we're broke.
Marriage is hard enough
without being poor.
Hey, what happened to the love?
What happened
to all that romance?
You know I love you.
But you are living
in this fantasy.
It's like you're waiting
for some kind of miracle.
I gotta live in reality.
I am not gonna be young forever.
So you gotta put yourself
back on the market...
while the merchandise
is still fresh.
You act like there's
a damn expiration date...
on your forehead!
Come on, come on.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You think I like
living like this?
Movin' tickets, hustlin' chess,
DJing at these little clubs?
I should've stayed in college.
I messed up.
I'll go back to college.
I love you, Jake.
I love you, too.
But I...
So, when are you leaving?
Couple weeks. But I...
We'll talk before then.
Why?
Jake.
- What's up, man?
- Hey, what's up?
- What's wrong?
- Julie left me.
Sorry. I gotta go.
But I'll catch you tomorrow.
I'm all out of love...
I'm so lost without you...
I know you were right...
Believing for so long...
I'm all out of love...
What am I without you?
I can't be too late...
Hey, you get
your shit together...
or I'm gonna have
to fire your ass!
That's right!
I want you to come back
and carry me home...
Away from these long,
lonely nights...
There's no easy way...
It gets harder each day...
Please love me
or I'll be gone...
I'll be gone...
I'm all out of love...
I'm so lost without you...
I know you were right...
Believing for so long...
I'm all out of love...
What am I without you?
It can't be too late...
To say that I was so wrong...
Julie, I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Big-time Tickets.
Yeah, for what game?
How much you want to spend?
Yeah, I can get it.
So, where you at?
Where the hell's that?
Thank you very much.
Now, take off.
Whatever.
- Hop out.
- Hey, what's up?
- Give me your phone.
- What's up?
Hey! Come on, now!
What y'all want?
- Hey, come on!
- Relax.
You know how hard it was for me
to get a cab to come up here?
I hope y'all givin' me
a ride back.
I know you're cops, man.
What do you want, money?
Oh, I understand.
Y'all shot somebody,
and now y'all need a suspect.
Mr. Hayes? Jacob Hayes?
I'm Officer Oakes,
that's Officer Seale...
Officer Swanson, Officer Carew.
CIA? What's that for?
"Crackers In my Ass?"
You're gonna arrest me
for scalpin' tickets?
We just want to talk to you
about something.
- About what?
- About your brother.
You got the wrong guy.
I don't even have a brother.
That's just a picture
of me in a suit.
You could've got that
off the internet.
I saw a picture of Bill Gates
with three titties on the net.
OK, September 8, 1970...
Bellevue Hospital,
New York City...
a woman registered
as Mary Jeffries...
gives birth
to identical twins...
but suffers complications
and dies the next day.
- What about the father?
- Thomas B. Jeffries.
Presumed alive.
Whereabouts unknown.
The state
rarely separates twins...
but one of the infants...
Jacob... that's you...
was diagnosed
with severe lung infection.
You still have the scar
from the chest tube...
the incision mark.
An administrator at the hospital
altered the birth record...
to give the healthy child
a better chance at adoption.
A week later,
Roger and Glenda Pope...
took in Kevin Jeffries.
The Popes never knew.
Kevin never knew.
So, I have a twin brother.
Big deal.
What's the CIA
have to do with this?
He couldn't send me a letter?
Your brother's dead.
How?
A helicopter crash.
We need your help, Mr. Hayes.
Your brother was working
on something with us.
My twin brother was CIA?
Yeah, a clandestine operative.
And just before he was killed,
he set up a deal.
What kind of deal?
A very important one.
So, we need you to stand
in for him, just briefly.
- Pretend I'm him?
- Yeah.
- For how long?
- Nine days.
Nine days is not standin' in.
Standin' in is an hour.
Nine days is goin' on tour.
- Is this shit dangerous?
- There's some risk.
What kind of risk?
We talkin' bad credit risk...
or a bullet in the ass risk?
- You'd be well compensated.
- For a bullet in the ass risk?
I hope that's a lot
of compensation. How much?
Throw out a number.
- A billion dollars.
- You've overshot.
I don't know what kind of budget
you're working with.
We were thinking
somewhere in the region of...
let's say... $25,000.
Fifty. Yeah, fifty.
I figure you started with 25,
so I know you got more.
You ain't gonna give me
all your money. 50,000.
This is what I'm thinking,
Mr. Hayes.
With $25,000, your girlfriend
Julie could go to college.
She wouldn't have to go
to Seattle.
Or work with Ken.
OK, here's what I'm thinkin'.
You're gonna give me
$50,000 tax-free.
OK, 50,000 after taxes
after the job is done.
Half now, half after.
Ten now, forty after.
Unless my mother had triplets...
you're gonna give me ten now,
ninety after.
OK, you got a deal.
- So, when do we start?
- Now.
This is your brother's file.
Study it.
So there's homework.
- Preparation.
- OK.
Let's see, Dad sits on the board
of the New York Stock Exchange.
Mom, co-artistic director...
at Lincoln Center.
Must've been nice.
In my foster house,
we were so poor...
we used to lick stamps
for dinner.
Let's see.
Prep school at Exeter.
Then college at Dartmouth.
Served in the Naval Academy.
- That's right.
- What'd he serve, lunch?
Oh, man."Rhoades scholar."
- So my brother was real smart?
- Yeah.
Damn, the CIA is cheap.
Y'all could've got me
a queen size.
What's this, jack size?
Hey, what's "Zachod" mean?
It's Czech for "bathroom."
You'll find the room labelled
with phonetic translations.
Why?
Because the deal goes down
in the Czech Republic.
- Czech Republic?
- Here's a dictionary.
How do I get an outside line?
I need somebody to feed my cat.
You don't have
an outside line or a cat.
So what am I
supposed to be doing here?
There's a tape in the VCR.
It's a video of your brother.
Watch it. The way he talks
and the way he moves.
I know there's a lot
to deal with here...
but we're all behind you.
We'll start in the morning.
You got any questions?
Yeah, if my brother
was such a genius...
then how come he's dead?
- 5 A.M.
- Hey, I don't do 5 A.M.
So, bottom line,
what are our chances?
I'd say anywhere between
nil and zero.
Why do you say that?
I grant you,
he's got potential.
He's pretty street-smart.
In 6 months, he could probably
fool his brother's parents.
But eight days?
You gotta be kidding.
Probably get himself
killed on this mission...
and anyone else
who goes along with him.
Would you like to be replaced
on the mission?
Why? You're going ahead
with or without me?
That's precisely
what I'm saying.
Well, sir, when do I tell him
what this mission involves?
If I were you, I would tell him
as little as possible.
Don't put anything
into his head he can't use...
and certainly nothing that
could pop out at the wrong time.
- OK.
- What's he doing now?
He's studying.
We told him to learn...
a few key phrases in Czech.
He seems dedicated.
What's he saying?
He said, "I haven't had
my period in three months."
Now what?
"Where's the hospital?
I have a vaginal infection."
This is gonna be
really interesting.
Can't wait to get started.
Rise and shine, Mr. Hayes!
5 A.M., and all is well.
How about three more hours
of sleep and some breakfast?
How about a nice shower?
Aah! Aah! Hey!
What's wrong with you?!
Good morning.
Today we'll be covering
basic operations protocol...
for the acquisition
of foreign assets...
a procedure we like to call
"The Three I's"...
identifying the target,
initiating the contact...
and infiltrating the network...
Now you do it like him.
Man, this is buggin' me out.
I feel like Michael Jackson...
lookin' at old album covers.
Look at this guy.
He looks like me,
but it's not me.
- Yeah.
- So, what did he like to do?
What kind of sports was he into?
What kind of music
did he listen to?
He liked music.
Jazz and classical.
- Classical, like Run-DMC?
- He didn't like rap.
What 29-year-old brother
don't like a little bit of rap?
He didn't listen to rap.
So, what kind of sports
was he into?
Skiing.
OK, so you got skiing,
the Navy, no rap.
We'd have had a lot in common.
- Sir.
- Hmm?
What time?
OK. All right.
Thanks.
So, what's up with
you and Swanson?
- Hmm?
- Aw, come on, man.
I see there's something
goin' on there.
You got a little
something goin' on...
Look at you. You're blushing.
Do you mind if I say something
to you, Mr. Hayes?
My friends, Officer Seale,
Officer Swanson...
they have faith in you.
I don't.
And that creates a problem...
because you're in so deep
with us now...
we can never let you go.
So you'd better
learn this stuff...
stone-cold by 0500 hours
tomorrow morning.
Or what?
I'll kill you.
Can we start
a few hours later tomorrow?
Aah! Aah!
Aaah!
Get dressed.
It's 4:59!
The new terrors in rock...
On every block...
Late for school,
late for work...
But ahead of these cops...
My credit is shot,
end up dead in a box...
But so my life
ain't as pathetic as Pac's...
Right away
blow your life away...
So light your haze,
hold tight grenades...
So when it blows
I'm slightly grazed...
Kuniva might be crazed
unleashin' unlikely rage...
Next time you hear a verse
from me I might be caged...
Swirl.
Checking for sediment.
Sniff...
And taste.
Morning, Mr. Hayes. 5 A.M.
No, 5:01.
I believe in people tryin'...
I believe in people cryin'...
I believe
in people breathin'...
I believe in people bein'...
Pope. Kevin Pope.
Ha ha ha! Look at this suit.
Man, I got initials on my cuffs.
The only thing I ever have
on my cuffs is steak sauce.
They say "M.T."
What's that for?
Michael Turner.
But I thought I was Kevin Pope.
Kevin Pope is Michael Turner.
Michael Turner
is Kevin Pope's cover identity.
He is a very successful,
very knowledgeable...
very sophisticated
international dealer...
in fine antiquities.
Well, if I'm Jake Hayes
playing Kevin Pope...
playing Michael Turner,
then I should get two checks.
Cheers.
This is a very rare
expensive cognac.
What do you think?
Dry. But never precocious.
I love your shirt.
Egyptian broadcloth?
Three days.
Pretty impressive.
Yeah, he's bright.
- I think he can do it.
- He's got my vote.
I said he was bright.
I didn't say he was capable
of saving the world.
- Let's run a real test.
- Like what?
Send him up to New York.
Put him in Kevin's apartment.
Let the neighbors, the doorman,
everybody get a look at him.
See if they buy him
as Michael Turner.
Might even serve
a double purpose.
Whoever tried to kill
Kevin as Michael Turner...
probably doesn't know he's dead.
Might still be looking for him.
So we dangle him as bait,
keep him in the dark.
- He'll be protected.
- What do we tell him?
You're giving him a chance
to practice being Kevin.
That's all you need to tell him.
You're the boss.
You see the van
in front of us?
The one behind us?
Those are our guys.
Here's my cell phone number.
Use it if you get
into any kind of trouble.
- What kind of trouble?
- Any kind.
Shark attack?
Call you. All right.
Could you pop the trunk?
Take this.
Get yourself some shoes.
Little punk.
Mr. Turner, welcome back, sir.
Thanks, Jim.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
How was Europe?
Like another country.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Whoo!
You could put this on MTV Cribs.
Man, this is dope!
God damn.
So if I paid taxes...
this is where
the money would go, huh?
Could have
a Puffy party in here.
Let's get some music in here.
Whoa-oh-oh!
What's that music?
- Just hip-hop stuff.
- It's terrible.
Jake, it's your
downstairs neighbor...
Mrs. Patterson.
Don't forget the radio.
OK.
Hi, Michael! Welcome back.
Mwah. Mwah.
- Vera, how are you?
- Fine, thank you.
Hi, Annabella.
We just came in and the doorman
said you were back.
- Annabella missed you.
- Oh, you're far too kind.
I've been waiting desperately
for you to come back.
- Oh? Why?
- I bought a little treasure.
Come on down and tell me
if I got a good buy.
- Oh, OK.
- Hold your baby.
- Yes, my baby.
- How was your trip?
This is gonna be a disaster.
Hello! Go see your nanny, baby.
What do you think?
Is it a good piece?
Uh...
- It's exquisite.
- Ooh! Do you think?
Go ahead, pick it up. Feel it.
Just see how delicate it is.
Pick it up, right?
Yes. Just grab it
and pick it up.
Michael...
that's what we keep
the doggy treats in.
Of course, I knew that.
I was just getting it...
out of the way
so I could see the...
- The vase.
- Of course, the vase! Yes!
May I ask, how much
did you pay for this?
150,000.
Good lord! What you gonna
put in it, cocaine?!
He fooled the doorman,
he fooled the neighbor...
and the neighbor's dog.
What more do you want?
Oakes, we need to know
who's after that bomb.
You're willing
to sacrifice him to find out?
Don't be dramatic.
He's got plenty of protection.
I'll tell you when to pull him.
Never safe,
you're never sure...
Somethin's all wrong...
Hope y'all not watching this.
I don't have
to watch this, do I, sir?
- Oh, no. Holy shit.
- Code red. Code red.
Code red! Code red!
Parish, McCain, cover the exits!
Help! Help! Help!
Raah!
Unh!
God.
Whoa!
Aah!
Unh!
Sir, he's headed for the roof.
- We need him alive.
- Yes, sir.
- Whoa!
- Oh!
Drop the knife.
Hey, Elvis, if you drop
the knife and step down...
no one is gonna hurt you.
So...
who's got Jake?
Aah!
Well, these last
ten minutes will be used...
as a teaching aid on how
an operation can get totally...
- Screwed up, sir?
- Thank you.
We'll find him, sir.
Yeah? Where are you?
The corner of eat shit
and fuck you!
I'm not gonna let you trace me!
Bye! I'll call you back!
I'm stuck in traffic.
I ask you to do...
Give me that!
Yo!
Run fingerprints, DNA,
anything we can get...
on the guy
who jumped off the roof.
- Yes, sir.
- He looks Afghani, sir.
Don't assume anything.
Just find Jake.
- Yes, sir.
- Jake...
Kevin was murdered!
And they're gonna murder me!
- Let's meet some place...
- No more bullshit!
We lost him
because we lied to him.
No, you lost him
because you lost him.
We treated him like an idiot.
He had a right to know
what we were doing with him.
We're wasting time!
Find him and bring him back...
and spare me your conscience.
Spare my conscience.
- Take it easy, buddy.
- Bye.
It's called chillin'...
6 million ways to live...
6 million ways to live life...
Yeah?
Hello? Pam, it's Jake.
Can I talk to Julie?
- She don't want to talk to you.
- Who's on the phone?
I need to talk to Julie.
Please. This is serious.
It is Jake?
Wait, let me talk to him!
- She's moving on.
- Give me the phone.
We don't need
no more trouble, Jake...
and you ain't nothing
but trouble.
Two suits came around today
looking for you.
Give me the phone!
Hey, hey, hey.
Shit, your phone's tapped.
If Julie's there,
tell her I love her...
and, Oakes, if you're listening,
kiss my ass!
- You get a trace?
- No.
Tch. He hung up.
It's called chillin'...
6 million ways to live...
6 million ways
to live life...
Mr. Hayes, where are you?
Where in the hell are you?
6 million ways
to live lavish...
6 million ways to live...
6 million ways
to live lavish...
Beyond all the misery
and mathematic...
From the 6 million ways
to live...
6 million ways to live...
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org