Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
That's the pawn shop my friend
from the OC told me about.
It's surrounded by the Feds.
They're watching these Russians.
There he is.
- Oh, yeah.
- His name's Roman Bulkin.
What are you doin'?
Are you crazy?
They know what you look like.
What are you gonna tell 'em?
No more than I have to, if that.
- One twenty-two. George.
- That's 4-8-8 Sunset.
Subject's approaching
northwest corner.
You've got a lot of balls.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
There's half a dozen
undercover cops outside.
Don't give 'em a reason to come in.
Nyet!
Now, did you take this picture?
Go to hell, you greasy wop
son of a bitch.
Now you're the one
that's gonna need protection.
You go now.
Is that chest hair real?
Roman, look at me.
The next time you send someone over
to kill me, make sure I'm home.
Have a nice day.
Yes!
Like that?
Scorchin'!
Mr. Palmer.
- How are you doin', Marla?
- All right.
- You got a second?
- Sure.
So, what are you
doing here, Mr. Palmer?
Well, you know, when I was a kid,
I went to a Jimi Hendrix concert
and this pawn shop here
has got a '68 Stratocaster,
the same guitar he used to play.
And the guy won't sell it to me.
This guy look familiar to you?
Maybe from back
in your Brooklyn days?
Yeah. That's Joe Lupino.
Joe Loop.
Is that his head shot?
Couple's in Griffith Park last night,
two dudes pulled in,
one of them's wearing
one of those pimp hats,
they pop the trunk, toss out a body
that's been worked over by a baseball bat.
It's Joe Loop.
- Baseball bat, huh?
- Baseball bat.
Yeah, and they pulled
a Mama Cass on him, too.
The coroner found half a ham sandwich
stuffed down his throat.
You wouldn't happen to know
what Joe was up to, now, would you?
No, but I wouldn't be surprised
if he was in the record business.
Think it coulda been a mob hit?
Maybe. Except for the ham sandwich.
There he is.
Right there.
See the two seats next to him?
That's where we are. Come on.
Chil. Do you think Steven's
gonna remember me?
Edie, believe me,
you're hard to forget. Come on.
- Edie, over there.
- Got it.
- How'd you get these seats?
- I have a friend.
They're incredible.
Your attention. Please.
At the conclusion
of tonight's game.
Listen for the Laker wrap-up show
on your Laker flag...
Oh, my God!
Look at you!
Baby, you look gorgeous.
Oh, my God!
You look incredible!
- How are you?
- I'm great!
Well, look at you.
Look how those legs go up
and make an ass out of themselves.
You still got that Aerosmith tattoo
on your ass?
Where would it go?
It's working.
Well, I tell you what,
why don't you park that right there?
Tell me something.
What was that stuff you put in our clothes?
Do you mean the lavender water?
Yeah, the lavender water.
- I can't believe you...
- I'll never forget that smell.
Joe Perry's still talking about that.
Oh, my God!
Steven, I want you to meet
my very good friend.
It's an absolute honor to meet you.
The shylock.
Yeah.
I saw you on Larry King.
It was you and...
- Ariel Sharon.
- That was a hell of a show.
- Yeah, thanks, man.
- Yeah.
Robert, listen to me.
There's no problem.
No one's left the Chicks.
We're gonna play the gig, bro.
Ciao.
Linda's gonna play the gig?
What do you think?
Where the hell is Joe Loop?
I haven't seen him.
Not since I paid him.
Gave him what he had coming.
Christ.
I'm bangin' the phones
from dawn till dusk.
Bobby finally wants the Chicks
to play Last Samurai,
but we don't have Linda.
I feel you, man.
- My man.
You guys will never guess
who I saw today.
Chili Palmer.
Has anyone not seen him?
I'm at the Boot Barn on Sunset,
and I see him talking to this cop
in a Crown Vic.
You guys remember the pawn shop
by the bakery?
Yeah, I know that place.
Stolichnaya?
It's thick with Russians.
Well, one of 'em walks out,
points his fingers like a gun at Chili.
Jesus Christ.
The guy in Chili's house,
the dead guy?
I read in the paper he was Russian.
So?
So these Russians are probably
the ones that killed Tommy Athens.
And they know Chili can identify 'em.
Why you trippin', man?
Why am I trippin'?
I'm trippin', G,
'cause there is actually
someone who wants
Chili Palmer dead more than me.
I say we help him get what he wants.
Bam!
'M a believer
The future is now
t starts today
Damn, she's good!
She sings, she writes her own stuff.
She got it going on.
Not only does she write
her own stuff,
I mean, she's got the voice,
she's got the look.
This girl's the whole package.
She wanted me to put her
in a movie.
- You know, struggling singer...
- That makes it big.
Exactly.
Look, she sounds cool,
don't get me wrong,
but I gotta tell you guys,
I'm not one of those singers
who shows up in movies.
I made it this far
without having to do it.
No, Steven. We don't want you to be
in a movie with her.
Then what's this all about?
I know that look, Chili.
I mean, what are you thinkin'?
I'm thinkin' of a song.
One of yours, Steven.
Sweet Emotion.
I love that song.
I mean, it's a classic.
Do you mind my asking you,
what were you thinking
when you wrote that?
What was I thinking about?
Man, at that point in my life, Chil,
we were neck deep
in Toys in the Attic.
I mean, I had this high.
This buzz was going on, see?
This incredible emotion
like I never felt before.
Or maybe it was just the rock 'n' roll.
That is interesting.
Would you like to know what I think?
I don't think it was the rock 'n' roll.
I think it was your daughters.
My daughters?
Mia, Liv.
Nah. They were babies back then.
That's right.
And you were a father for the first time,
feeling things you had never felt before.
It's different than music and tours.
This was pure.
You wanted to be with them,
you wanted to protect them.
No. This high you were feeling,
that wasn't rock 'n' roll.
It wasn't?
It was the love you felt for your girls.
That sweet emotion.
It was. You're right.
I never thought about it like that.
You see, Steven, you and me,
we're not that different from each other.
That's why you can understand
why we care about this girl Linda Moon.
I'll give it some thought.
Yes!
You know what else...
I can't believe Linda's gonna play
with Aerosmith.
How about this idea?
We get Linda to do a duet with Steven
and use his name to promote her CD.
Oh, my God,
that's genius, Chil.
You know, there's something
I've been wanting to do for a long time.
Yeah? What is that?
Don't move.
Did you put the TV on?
No.
I didn't think so.
Stay here.
He took a second look at you
But he's in love with me
Well. don't know
where that leaves you
Oh. But know where stand
'Cause you ain't woman enough
to take my man
Elliot, what are you doing?
I've been waiting
on your ass all night.
Got so goddamn bored,
I made some tea, I put in my video.
You broke into my house?
You told me you were gonna call me.
I left you a message two days ago.
Elliot, I said I would
get you the audition, and I will.
When? When?!
What the hell are you waiting for?
If you don't mind my saying,
I don't like your attitude one bit.
Now apologize.
I'm sorry, Chili.
All right.
It's... I bought a brand-new suit,
I bought new shiny red boots,
I got my new headshots done.
I even prepared a monologue
from Bring t On.
Well, then do it.
Well. don't know
where that leaves you
Oh. But know where stand
said...
You guys have to go to nationals!
What is this, hush money?
We don't need you.
Why are you so mean?
I'm just trying to be strong
for my squad.
And I'm trying to make it right.
You wanna make it right?
Then when you go to nationals...
...bring it!
I'll bring it!
Don't worry.
I never do.
Scene.
Is that the only monologue
that you got?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Well, that wasn't bad,
but you gotta remember,
when you're doing a monologue,
you don't do both parts
of the conversation.
You choose one continuous speech.
And you might think about
doing a part that's written for a man.
Right.
Now, you sing, right?
Yeah.
- Raji directed the video, though.
- Well, I like it, I like it.
But you might think
about singing a man song.
Okay.
Yeah. Thanks.
- Thanks. Thank you.
- All right.
Come on,
give me that eyebrow thing.
Look at that.
I mean, that's somethin'.
When are you gonna call me?
When your phone rings.
Okay. All right.
You guys can keep the tape.
I got another one.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- See you, Elliot.
Red aluminium.
I hear we can help each other.
So I've got ten seconds alone
with Madonna, right,
and I'm like, "Look, I sat front row
at Blonde Ambition tour.
I am not intimidated
by your sexuality... "
What's up?
- We heard about Aerosmith.
- How about that?
Where the hell was I, you guys?
I mean...
- Where's Linda?
- I don't know, man.
Linda hasn't shown up.
I haven't seen her since yesterday.
What do you mean
she hasn't shown up?
I'll call her.
Linda.
Do sound like Linda. Bitch?
Who is that?
Yo, Vanilla Ice, just put her
on the damn phone.
Miss Moon's about ready
to go on stage right now.
You wanna talk to her.
You best wait till after the show.
Bee-yatch!
What are we gonna do?
They're making her perform.
I'll handle this.
Itchi gitchy ya-ya da-da
Mocha-choca-latta ya-ya
Creole Lady Marmalade
Voulez-vous coucher avec moi
ce soir?
Voulez-vous coucher avec moi?
We come through with the money
and the garter belts
Let 'em know we 'bout that cake,
straight out the gate
We independent women,
some mistake us for whores
I'm sayin', why spend mine
when I can spend yours
Disagree? Well, that's you,
and I'm sorry, I'ma keep playin'...
This ain't no damn negotiation.
We got a contract.
You're making a mistake here,
believe it.
You want your money, you better
get your ass out there on stage.
I ain't doing this.
You gonna perform or not?
How about not?
Hi, honey.
Hiya, Chil.
We were just talking
to your friend Linda here
about the kind of Spice Girl cash
she can make if she stays with the Chicks.
Well, I can see
by the dressing room
that it's just a preview
of good things yet to come.
At least we can afford to record her.
Don't think I don't know
that NTL is broke.
Come on, honey.
Let's go.
You know what?
This is bullshit.
You wanna go?
After all I did for you?
Fine. But let me tell you
something, sweetheart.
- You're a dime a dozen.
- That's right.
We got gigs lined up,
recording sessions scheduled.
There are dozens of girls
who are dying to take your place.
Here. You want her so bad,
you're gonna need this.
What is this?
It's where Linda's contract is.
Are you trying to set me up, Nicky?
I don't go by that name anymore.
Then why don't I call you Joe Loop?
Seeing how he doesn't
use his name anymore, either.
What are you talking about?
Nicky, look at me.
Do you even know
where Joe Loop is?
How the hell do I know where he is?
Why don't you ask Sisqó?
Man, we can handle this shit
like gentlemen,
or we can get into some gangsta shit!
You shouldn't talk shit
about what you don't know.
What? Do you mean
that you beat Joe Loop with a bat
and dumped his body in Griffith Park?
Raj, what the hell is he talking about?
He's just talkin'.
It's impossible
that you're this stupid.
That's probably his gun
you got stuck in your waist there.
Look, all I know is
Raji told me to come here
if I wanted my money
for the Viper Room gigs.
,
Am I gonna pay you or not?
Are you gonna honor
your goddamn contract or not?!
Then you get paid!
This man can't do shit for you!
Oh, yeah?
Then why is she playing
with Aerosmith this weekend?
What?
- Yeah!
- Oh, my God!
We'll leave some tickets for you
at will call.
- You didn't tell me!
- Yeah!
You hit the goddamn hit man.
The man was bad at his job, man!
Yeah. Just like you, stupid-ass.
- Look, you know what?
- What?
- I'm so sorry, Chil, for real.
- Why is that?
Because I didn't even
wanna come here.
Raji said he was gonna pay me
the money he owes me,
and I'm broke, so...
Look, at least we can
get my contract back.
Believe me, honey,
there is no contract.
This whole pawn shop thing's
a set-up.
It's Nicky Carr's way
of getting my head blown off.
What's this?
Well, now imagine my surprise.
We out getting Mongolian barbecue,
and we come across
your little weak-ass ride.
Did you leave any food in Mongolia?
What do you get on those Hummers,
about, what, 12 miles to the gallon?
Nine.
Thank you, Mr. Goodwrench.
Now, I told you you had till Friday.
Your time is running out.
I know how
the days-of-the-week thing works.
You'll get your money.
Well, consider this a courtesy call.
Because come tomorrow,
my nine gonna be a lot less courteous.
Since you are being so courteous,
I'd like you to meet Linda Moon.
Linda, this is Sin.
And Dabu.
Yeah, I know who you are.
You did the remix
on Samurai Soul's album, right?
Linda Moon.
You the girl with...
Could you make your dining experience
a little less obtrusive?
So, you the girl with that big voice
I've been hearing so much about.
If you ever decide
to get out the bargain basement,
maybe I can remix a song for you.
No. You're too pricey for us, Sin.
A brother gotta get paid, right?
Miss Moon.
Chop, chop.
Yeah.
Dabu.
Player.
Damn.
Can you stop playing with that thing?
You ain't gonna figure out
your two-way, Elliot.
Why don't you take a break
and daydream about things
that you like, man?
Like, you know, flying on a unicorn
with chocolate-covered cherries raining.
I'm not the one
who disrespected you, Raji.
Nick did.
Not me. Nick.
Man, Nick ain't even my boss.
How's he gonna do me like that?
We're supposed to be partners.
Damn.
Raji, Nick left a message for you.
If you go near Linda, he'll see
that you suffer excruciating pain
and never walk again in your life.
In other words, he'll break your legs.
Why's he gotta say it
all poetic like that?
Why can't he just say
"I'm gonna break your legs," man?
Nice ass won't get you
through your whole life!
When you turn 30,
you better have a personality.
You don't need him anymore, Raj.
I say it's time you took Nick out.
What about Chili Palmer, genius?
Man, you can't even work your pager,
you sittin' there schemin'.
You'll get to Chili in good time.
Don't worry about Chili.
Nick's the problem.
Man, if I take Nicky out,
all roads lead to me, Elliot.
You don't think about shit, man.
Not if it ain't you who does it.
I'm talking about a set-up, bro.
Hello.
- Sin LaSalle?
- Yeah. Who wants to know?
Shut your punk-ass mouth!
NTL owes you 300 large. Right?
Chili Palmer was gonna pay you,
but Nick Carr says, "Sin LaSalle?
Man, I wouldn't give my money
to that Alabama porch monkey. "
Alabama porch mo...
Nick Carr said that?
Man. You heard me. Fool!
He told Chili to give him
the 300 grand instead,
in exchange for some contract
and whatnot.
Look, man, you want your chips?
Do you want your chips?
Then you best see Nick Carr.
C-A-R.
If I want my chips?
Yeah, I want my chips.
Who is this?
I'm the one schoolin' you, son.
That is beautiful.
You did it.
Man, let's get some Roscoe's
up in this bitch.
You want some chicken breast?
Some collards?
Some yams?
Some waffles, man?
Extra syrup.
I love Roscoe's.
You know, I never told you this.
You know what I love about Roscoe's?
I could take one drumstick
and put it in my mouth
and suck all the meat off it at one time
and then just pull out that bone.
Don't be puttin' your sucked-on drumstick
with my chicken breast.
You better keep that shit...
I'm serious, man.
You better keep that shit separate.
The only thing wet on that shit
better be the syrup.
What's up?
It's Raji.
- Hey, baby.
- Hi, Daddy.
- How you doin'?
- Good.
Yeah.
- School was good?
- Yeah.
You had a good day at school?
You know what,
we gonna skip ice cream today.
Let's drop her off real quick.
Yeah.
Detective, my husband was
an amazing man.
Please.
But he didn't leave NTL
in the best financial position.
Well, we spoke
with his assistant Tiffany,
and she told us about an incident
involving an insurance salesman?
Yes.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Fine.
Mrs. Athens.
Please, call me Edie.
Well, Edie, we have reason to believe
that this gentleman
was not an insurance salesman at all.
Really?
I don't understand.
Do you think it's possible
that your husband was involved with the...
...the Russian mafia?
The Russian mafia?
I mean, not that I know of, but...
I did find something.
Maybe this will help.
I found it in Tommy's desk drawer.
"Nick Carr. "
It's a pawn ticket.
Pawn ticket.
I wanna pick this up.
Get your black ass out of here.
You know what you tell a man
with two black eyes?
Nothin'.
He's already been told twice.
Now, are you gonna
get me what I came for
or are we gonna have a problem?
Da.
- An envelope?
- That's it.
They bought it.
You're up.
How much can I get for this?
And don't worry, your hair looks fine.
Damn! I'm walkin', man!
I'm walkin'!
Have you lost your...
Sit yo' ass down.
I'm fine, I'm fine!
Hang up the phone, Nick.
Stop it! Shit, man.
Good-bye, Marty.
Sin, good to see you, bro.
Sit yo' ass down.
Sin, I can explain it to you.
You best hope you didn't lie to us.
I'm just sayin'
if I could explain what happened,
we could maybe get
on the same page here.
You know what I'm sayin'?
Jesus Christ.
What the hell's going on?
- It's a misunderstanding.
- Shut yo' ass up!
Your man here says
you got our money.
I can explain it to you.
- Raji said that?
- It's a misunderstanding.
Would you shut it up?!
...excited here, man.
Let me tell you something.
NTL owes us 300 grand.
Now, from my understanding,
Chili Palmer took that money,
gave it to you for some contract.
Raji said that?
He's full of shit.
Watch what you say,
'cause we will drop his ass.
Take him outside.
Fine.
Come on, man, easy!
Don't land on my Porsche.
Man!
This ain't cool, man!
Come on, man.
Pull me up, man!
You can't hang me like this!
Stop this shit, man!
It's a long way, man!
Come on, man.
Pull me up, man!
Come on.
There's cameras all over this bitch, man.
You're gonna be
all over the surveillance, man.
I'm asking you, please!
Help! Help!
Stop playin', man!
Stop bullshittin', man!
Man, there's a law office
down there, man!
I'ma wake the lawyers up.
Lawyers, what's up?
Lawyers, can you see me?
It's Raji from Carosell.
C-A-R-O...
I'm gonna drop yo' ass.
You can't hit me, man.
You can't hang me over a thing
and hit me!
Pull my ass up!
Sin, my bro.
Would you cut the "my brother" shit?
You're insulting my mother.
I'm not in business with Chili Palmer.
I'm the one trying to get him out.
The piece of shit stole my act.
You son of a bitch.
You set me up.
Who the hell are you?
I give you ticket,
and you tell me Chili Palmer come
to my store and I kill him.
But nyet.
No Chili come.
Yo, Tolstoy.
Take a number.
The cops come with ticket.
Cops? What cops?
Excuse me, Vladimir?
I don't know how they do it in the Ukraine,
but I believe I was here first.
Be cool, nigger.
Nigger?
Look, you don't understand.
This is how Chili Palmer operates.
It's like a game between us.
He knows I tried to set him up,
so he did it right back to me.
Then game is over.
No more set-ups.
- No more...
- You know that video's got you!
Nigger cops.
Have you lost your mind?
I mean, how is it that you can
disrespect a man's ethnicity
when you know we've influenced
nearly every facet of white America,
from our music to our style of dress,
not to mention your basic imitation
of our sense of cool...
walk, talk, dress, mannerisms.
We enrich your very existence,
all the while contributing
to the gross national product
through our achievements
in corporate America.
It's these conceits that comfort me
when I'm faced with the ignorant,
cowardly, bitter and bigoted
who have no talent, no guts,
people like you who desecrate
things they don't understand
when the truth is
you should say, "Thank you, man,"
and go on about your way.
But apparently,
you're incapable of doing that.
So...
,
And don't tell me to be cool.
I am cool!
Racial epithets.
Why does it always come down to that?
Makes me sad for my daughter.
You need money?
I got you!
I got you.
Focus.
Sin, I'm the one who promoted you.
I'm the reason
you're even owed 300 grand.
I'm telling you, you want Chili Palmer.
Pull my ass up!
Bring his ass back inside.
All right, I want y'all to give it up
and lay it down
for a good friend of mine... Linda Moon!
There was a time
when I was so broken-hearted
Love wasn't much of a friend of mine
The tables are turned, yeah
'Cause me and them ways have parted
But that kind of love
was the killing kind
Yeah
All I want is someone
I can't resist, yeah
I know all I need to know
by the way that you kiss
I was cryin' when I met you
Now I'm tryin' to forget you
Your love was sweet misery
I was tryin' just to get you
Now I'm dyin' 'cause I let you
Do what you do down on me
Baby
'Cause what you got inside
It ain't where your love
should stay, yeah
Our love, sweet love, ain't love
till you give your heart away
Yeah
I was cryin' when I met you
Now I'm tryin' to forget you
Your love was sweet misery
Baby
I was tryin' just to get you
Now I'm dyin' 'cause I let you
Do what you do down on
Baby, baby, baby
Baby, baby
She's a diva.
Told you.
She's gonna be huge.
Ain't that right, Joe Perry?
Baby, yeah
I was cryin' just to get you
Now I'm dyin' 'cause I let you
Do what you do,
what you do down on
Baby, baby, baby, baby
Baby, baby
Yeah
Linda Moon!
- Linda Moon!
- That's right.
Give it up, L.A.!
I said Linda Moon!
You expect me to follow that?
That was incredible.
I feel like I can't even breathe right now.
Well, 20,000 people will do that to you.
Oh, my God.
Listen, you were great.
Good luck.
And you know, the crowd's
only gonna get bigger for you.
- Thank you.
- See ya.
Linda Moon!
Careful what you wish for.
What about our girl, huh?
- She was amazing!
- Amazing.
- To Linda Moon.
To you.
You know, you said something
when Elliot was here,
that you wanted to do something.
What was that?
I think it might've been
something like this.
Are you just using me
to get into the music business?
Edie, I like you.
Good.
Wake up.
- What is it?
- Listen!
What's wrong?
I didn't leave the stereo on.
It sounds like
Knockin' On Heaven's Door.
All right, I'll check it out,
I'll check it out.
Evening, gentlemen.
Interesting choice of music.
That cold black cloud's comin' down.
Gotta love Dylan, man.
Biograph. It's a great album.
You know, we wouldn't have
this song without it.
But we would've.
Because, you see, Dylan wrote that
originally for that Peckinpah movie
with James Coburn.
You're in no position to correct me.
It was to a soundtrack.
Pat Garrett and Billy the Kid.
Yup. Same song they played
when Slim Pickens died in his wife's arms.
Right?
This man knows his westerns.
Good movie.
Gentlemen, thank you very much
for that VH1 moment in music history.
Time's up.
I want my money.
All right, well, tomorrow
you come by the office
and we'll deal with it.
How bad you want this?
Know what that is?
It's Linda Moon's contract.
- Nick Carr give you that?
- Much to his dismay.
,
I just doubled it.
And you got one minute
to come up with my money.
And at the end of that time,
I wanna smell money or smell blood.
It's your choice.
Sin, I want you to hear something.
I don't wanna hear shit.
You call that a minute?
You don't even have to say nothin'.
I already know. I know.
I can't help it, man!
Don't give me no gun, then.
You know what I'm gonna do.
Look, Sin, you're a music producer.
You gotta hear this.
Look, shoot me later,
but hear this now.
Like you've been left alone.
But you know deep down you're wrong
wonder. Have you ever. Ever felt
a little unsure
But then again secure?
Tell me. Have you ever felt
just like letting go?
What the hell is going on here?
Ain't no reason...
I'm playing Sin the CD.
Yeah. I noticed.
Sorry to wake you, Edie.
But your girl here's got a good voice.
I mean, the first song was nice,
but this one...
powerful lyrics...
just resonates with me.
You know what Sin said,
he said it's all there,
he just needs to put his touch on it.
That's it.
That's exactly what I said.
So, how is Sin proposing to do this?
Let me produce her.
I'll fatten up her sound,
give her some edge.
Maybe even add in a little... a little...
...a little blues guitar.
Yeah, huh?
Man's got a point, Edie.
Nothin' against Hy Gordon,
but the man is white.
That's true, Sin.
But what's that gonna cost me?
Well, just a producer's credit.
And a little something
on the back end.
Which could end up being millions.
Only if I make it a hit.
Tea?
What's with the finger?
What's that?
That's not gangsta.
Got you.
- What do you want. Raj?
- Sin LaSalle produced her single.
So?
Man, that bitch hung me out a window!
Now he gets to be a producer?
I ain't havin' it.
At least he's not hanging out at strip clubs
in the middle of the day.
Listen to me.
Chili called.
He said Linda played with Aerosmith
and killed.
Tried to offer me some kind of a
back-end bullshit deal to promote her.
Can you believe the balls on this guy?
So what you sayin'?
He's gonna make her a big star?
Not if he's dead.
Are you sayin' we can smoke him?
I'm saying you and Elliot
take care of him.
And I'll forget you tried to take me out.
Elliot, you home?
Elliot? Chili Palmer.
Got you an audition
on a Nicole Kidman picture.
T's next Tuesday at 3.00.
Give me a call.
No, he ain't.
Delete that shit.
I love that blues guitar.
It's nice.
I mean, it's lyrical, but it's tough now.
I could almost see the video.
We should get Shotgun
to do the video.
Now, he tight.
We'll never get him.
The man's the Scorsese of music videos.
It won't happen.
The man was my production assistant
on Get Leo.
I'll get him.
Linda! T was beautiful.
But when you do the hip thing.
need like a... more hip.
Like a... sexier hip.
Like a bigger. Sexier hip.
You... you'll do it.
I'll be back.
Okay? Right on action.
It's late. Shouldn't you
and Baby Huey be sleeping?
That's it?
No "Hey, Nick"?
"Good to see you, man"?
"Did you lose weight?"
She's good, bro.
You get Miss Bangkok in there
and you've got something.
Well, you always had an eye
for talent, Nick.
I think it's time you, me, and Edie
had a little talk.
You wanna talk business,
you talk to me.
You leave Edie out of this.
I'm already in negotiations with Edie.
I'm just coming to get you.
Is that right?
Well, if it isn't Flea Diddy.
It's P. Diddy.
Don't be comin' up in here
like you know anything about rap.
I bet I know more than you do.
You probably don't even know
who the Sugar Hill Gang is.
But I know who
the Bust A Cap In Yo' Ass Gang is.
Let me tell you something, Chil.
When I told you I wanted us
to work together, I was being genuine.
I could tell.
But now that Linda's making
a name for herself,
she's gonna need a real professional
managing her career.
So I'm gonna need
that contract back.
You know, just take it.
It's yours.
It takes a big man to realize
a bigger man swings a bigger dick.
Nobody's a bigger dick than you, Nick.
So what the hell is this?
That's Linda's contract.
We thought you'd appreciate the irony.
You know how turnabout's fair game.
Fair game. I like that.
That could be the name
of my next girl group.
Take care, Chil.
You disrespected me.
Move yo' ass.
It's a damn shame, Chili.
'Cause now what you're gonna do
is have to go commit suicide
up in a dark alley, man.
There goes your audition.
What audition?
I left you a message.
Stop bullshittin', man.
- At home and on your two-way.
- You didn't leave me a message.
I checked my messages.
Nobody called me.
Sounds like maybe
somebody erased your messages.
Check your two-way.
Go ahead.
Stop this shit.
We got business to take care of.
- You need help?
- All right.
There you go.
Is that it?
Just hit that button?
How could you do that, Raj?
What are you talking about, man?
Why am I standin' here?
You've been erasing my messages?
I have an audition on Tuesday.
What?!
Ain't no damn message on that thing.
Green light's on, man.
- How could you do that, man?
- Why you trippin' on me like that?
- E. Weazy!
- Elliot, be cool, man.
Cap easy in yo' ass!
- How could you do that?
- You actin' crazy, man!
Put the gun back
where it belongs, man!
You never wanted to see me in movies!
- Come on, sugar tank.
- After all these years, "sugar tank"?
- Come on, man. Check in.
- You afraid of the big gay man?
I'm your ace, man!
I've been your ace!
What? They got me!
Get 'em! They got me, Elliot!
They got me, man!
- Tuesday, right, Chili?
- That's right.
Sorry about your comrade, comrade.
- What the hell is this?
- Don't know.
- What the hell?
- Nick Carr!
You're under arrest
for the murder of Joe Loop.
And now, the final nominee
for MTV's Best Video of the Year.
Linda Moon, with her performance
of her smash hit Ain't No Reason.
Tell me, have you ever felt
like the sky was falling down
But the sun is gonna shine again?
Tell me, have you ever felt
like you've been left alone
But you know deep down you're wrong?
I wonder, have you ever,
ever felt a little unsure
But then again secure?
Tell me, have you ever felt
like you've been left alone?
But you can't 'cause you know
Ain't no reason to
No, no, no, no
No, no
Have you ever felt like giving up
But you know you love him
way too much?
I wonder if you've ever felt
Yeah
To
No, no, no
Ain't no reason to
No, no, no, no
Somethin', somethin'
Somethin' goin' down
Yeah, yeah, yeah
No, no, no, no, no
Ain't no reason to
No, no, no
No, no, no, no
Ain't no reason to
No, no, no
Tonight, you've heard
the five nominated songs. Dabu.
Yeah, I'm Dabu the Great,
you know what I'm sayin'?
We got the Dub MD's in the house.
Yeah.
The Best Music Video Award
goes to...
Tell 'em, Dabu!
First Believer. And now this.
Ain't No Reason To.
Linda Moon.
Fourth award of the night!
Yes!
- Sin.
- Linda Moon, what up?
Thank you.
Thanks.
This is amazing.
First, I would like to thank
my producer Edie Athens.
I'd also like to thank Hy Gordon
and Sin LaSalle.
Thank you.
And last, but not least,
I would like to thank the guy
who has believed in me
from the very beginning.
He made all of this happen...
Chili Palmer.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org