Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Yeah, good morning, Sergeant.
I've been trying to reach Detective Barrett
but he doesn't return my calls.
Would you like to leave a message, sir?
No, I wouldn't like to leave
another message.
Doesn't anyone down there give a damn?
Doesn't anyone down there
work for a living?
Would you like to leave a message, sir?
Don't you know
how important this is to me?
I know, I just...
You know, I thought
I was going to be able to work it out, but...
But I couldn't get
the money together, you know.
All my friends think I'm going to be there,
what am I going to tell them?
You know, I mean,
there's going to be other field trips.
Not to The Lion King, there won't.
Look, Dad, if you weren't going to pay for it,
you should have just said so
and saved me the humiliation of having
to tell all my friends that you're a loser.
Hey, this is Hank. I must
be out, so leave a message at the beep.
I know you're there. Pick up the phone.
Pick up the phone.
Pick up the fucking phone,
you fucking faggot.
- Andy, I'm here.
- Where have you been?
Here. I called in sick.
And what the fuck were you doing
with that fucking asshole?
- I was scared, all right? So I...
- I didn't say anything about
A fucking gun, God damn it.
But we got to talk.
Andy.
Meet me at Mooney's.
You still can't get by? To see Mom?
- What am I going to say?
- Don't say anything. Fuck.
- Who else knows?
- Nobody.
- You didn't tell anyone?
- No.
- No one saw you talking with Bobby?
All right. Nobody saw you here?
No, come on, it was crowded, it was busy.
No, no.
- Did he rent the car with you?
- Did he what?
- Did he rent the fucking car with you?
- No, no, no.
All right, did you...
- You picked him up?
- Yeah.
- At his house.
- Did anyone see you there, at his house?
- Did anyone see you at his house?
- No, no.
- Nobody saw you at the house?
- No.
Did you clean the car?
Did you wipe the car down?
- Did you wipe the floor?
- Yeah, I totally... Totally, totally.
- Did you leave anything in the car?
- No, of course not.
We're probably okay.
If they don't connect the car to us,
we're probably okay.
That's what I was thinking.
- Go back to work, totally normal.
- Okay.
I'm so sorry, Andy. I'm sorry.
I don't think I can get through this.
Shut up.
- I loved her so much.
- Just shut the fuck up.
If he had to take somebody out,
why couldn't it have been him?
One new message.
This is Mike Steuben calling
from Auto Rent for Mr. Henry Hanson.
Mr. Hanson, you returned a car
the other day.
It seems you forgot
some personal items in it.
Please give me a call at 555-2649
and ask for Mike Steuben.
Again, that number is 555-2649. Thank you.
End of messages.
Okay. God.
Okay.
Hello, you've reached
Auto Rent. Our office is currently closed.
- Our business hours...
- Fuck.
Fuck!
Okay. All right. It's okay, it's okay.
Excuse me?
That's right, sir. It's $255 plus tax.
But for an additional $17,
I could upgrade you to a luxury.
Or, for... Yes.
No, that's right,
the mid-size is $255 plus tax.
Unless you'd like to upgrade to an SUV,
which I could offer you for 29...
Excuse me, is Mike Steuben here?
No, I know, I'm just looking for Mike.
So, would you like to upgrade to the SUV?
No, no. No, mid-size is fine, sir.
No.
Thank you for calling.
I'm sorry.
Good morning, how can I help you, sir?
Yeah, I got a message from Mike Steuben.
Apparently I left something in a vehicle
that I returned last Saturday.
I think it was a CD.
Oh, well, you would talk
to Mr. Steuben, then. He's the manager.
Yeah, I know, so could I speak with him?
I'm sorry, he's not here.
You'll have to come back.
- When will he be in?
- I don't...
He won't be in at all today.
Well then, maybe you can help me.
Oh, no. Sorry, sir.
I'm sorry, excuse me.
- Do you think...
- I'm sorry.
- Will he be in tomorrow?
- Yes, Auto Rent.
No, I...
No, I didn't say that, sir.
That's not up to me.
No.
Excuse me, can I get a beer? Thanks.
That's the guy, that's him.
Yo, buddy.
- This guy?
- Yeah.
You were with Bobby Lasorda, Saturday?
- What?
- I asked you a fucking question.
What? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- What's your name?
- I'm Hank.
- Hank what?
- You know what?
Come. Why don't you... Let's go.
Follow me, we can talk over here.
- Come on. Have a seat.
- Is this all right?
Yeah, this is perfect.
So...
What's the deal, huh?
- My sister is quite all of a sudden a widow.
- Yeah.
She says you and Bobby had some work.
Bobby said it was work.
Work that involved him
getting shot and killed,
but not you getting shot and killed.
No, I just got him the car.
- I'm so sorry.
- What the fuck does that mean?
Well, Bobby said that he needed
to rent a car, but that he...
This was Friday night
and he didn't have a credit card,
so I told him that I would rent him a car.
And I owed him some money.
You know. That's it, I swear. It's...
I'm so sorry.
- So what? You're lying.
- No, I'm not.
Because if Bobby wanted a car,
he would have fucking stolen one.
Chris, go fucking wait outside.
Let me handle this.
You got a driver's license?
- A what?
- You know, the...
The driver's license you show
when you rent a car?
Yeah.
- Let me see it.
- Yeah.
All right, sure.
Here.
- Henry Hanson.
- Yeah.
This is your address, right?
Yeah, sure.
I'm going to be straight with you, chico.
You mind if I call you chico?
People call me Hank.
Bobby was a piece of shit.
I know it, you know it. That's not the point.
The point is that piece of shit
was the father of my sister's child.
And he was paying the bills.
And now he's dead.
And I'm thinking,
who's going to pay all these bills?
I'm so sorry.
Sorry ain't going to pay the bills, chico.
I know, I know.
We need to negotiate a settlement,
so make me an offer.
Ten grand, done. It's 10 grand.
I consider us even.
If you don't like 10, I can make it 15.
- No.
- My sister wants me to kill you.
Or I could call the cops.
But I don't like cops.
And the cops ain't going to pay
my sister's bills.
So, I think a settlement
is pretty fair all-around.
- Day after tomorrow, chico.
- Can I?
Here. 8:00.
You fucking crazy?
I was hoping that you had
something left over from the settlement.
Lend you money? You owe me $2,000.
Shocked to shit you'd even ask.
Martha,
I'm in serious trouble.
I don't give a shit
what kind of trouble you're in.
The next time you show up here,
better be to pay me.
Listen, tell Danielle I love her.
If you loved her,
you'd pay her fucking child support.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
She was a wonderful person.
Wonderful woman.
She was a wonderful woman.
God bless you.
There's no way I can make this scene, Andy.
He was always such a baby.
Yeah.
- Hey, Gina.
- I can't really talk right now.
Andy needs me. I got to go.
Gina, Gina.
Excuse me, is Mike Steuben here?
- Not till noon, can I help you?
- Yeah, yeah.
I returned a car last Saturday
and I guess I forgot something.
Hanson?
That's right, Hanson.
Yeah, and I'm pretty sure it was a CD.
Hang on.
Here we go, Mr. Hanson.
- Great.
- I just need to see some ID.
Yeah, you know, I...
I lost my license.
You have a credit card,
the one you used to rent the car with?
Yeah.
- Yeah, this one.
- All right.
Okay, great.
- Thank you.
- Take care.
- Hello?
- It's me.
Andy, Jesus! Fuck, man, we got problems.
Hi, Andy.
This is Jake at the office.
Really sorry to bother you,
but the auditors are coming tomorrow.
They've noticed a few problems.
It's pretty urgent,
so give a call when you get this.
You're going to have to get
some sleep tonight.
Have you given any thought to the store?
I mean, you're going to have to give it
some consideration. It's just gonna...
I could open it up for you, you know,
while you're at the hospital.
A few hours a day.
So people know you're still there.
I should burn the goddamn place down.
Andy, this is Jake.
Now I hope you're checking your messages
because we have a real mess here.
The auditors say that
there's two terminated employees
from your department still drawing checks.
And there's something about
unpaid O ASDI taxes.
Look, you need to call us...
I got to go to the office tomorrow.
There's a problem.
I'll go in the morning. I should be back later.
Okay?
His mother's dying,
and he's going back to work.
Yes!
Pick up the phone.
I know you're there,
pick up the phone, you fucking faggot.
Andy, I'm here.
What are you doing here?
You don't have an appointment.
- You know the deal, you can't just show up.
- I know, I'm sorry.
Come back in an hour, tonic water.
My mom's dying.
Bummer.
Next time, make an appointment.
Stupid piece of shit.
Stop talking to me like that.
What the fuck?
Are you going to get tough?
Are you going to hurt me?
Why was there even a gun?
Why was there even a fucking gun?
I gave you all the information you needed.
Why was Bobby Lasorda even there?
- Why the fuck?
- I didn't think I could do it alone.
I should fucking kill you.
How are we going to fix it
so your shit don't fall on my shoes?
So, think now, who else knows?
"Commit her body to the earth.
"For we are dust and to dust we shall return.
"But the Lord Jesus will change
our mortal bodies to be like his in glory.
"So let us commend our sister to the Lord. "
She hated it when I barbecued.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to be
what you wanted me to be.
I've never been very good
at talking about feelings
or showing you
that kind of affection or support.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to be the father you wanted.
But I guess I wanted you
to be better than me.
And I thought that if I push...
It may not mean anything to you,
but I want you to know
that I really do love you.
And I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm just so sorry.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to be
the son you wanted.
You did the best you could.
Still, yeah.
Manage to seem to still like Hank.
He was a lot more of a fuck-up than I was.
- He was the baby.
- Yeah.
- He needed us more.
- Yeah, he needed you more.
You sure it wasn't his cute looks
or his puppiness?
You were the first.
The first always has it rougher.
Yeah, so I'm told.
You know, the four of you,
I never felt like I was part of the club.
Beautiful birds of a feather.
You sure I'm your son?
Gina and I have got to get back to the city.
Andy?
My dad.
Andy.
Okay.
Why don't we pull over?
My dad.
Oh, God.
It's not fair! It's not fair!
All my life I've been afraid
of becoming like him. All my life!
All my life with you, and it's not fair.
He can't just say he's sorry
and make it all go away.
It's too late.
It's not that easy!
It's not fair! It's not fucking fair!
No, Dad.
Oh, God!
He can't do that!
Andy.
- I'll be back in a bit.
- Where are you going?
I'll be back soon, I just got to...
I got to deal with some stuff.
What's going on?
What if you come home and I'm not here?
You got some place you got to be?
Your boss called
and he wants you to call him right away.
Are you in trouble?
They just miss me.
Where are you going?
Something has to change.
- What do you mean?
- I mean that this just isn't working.
- What's not working?
- The life that we have.
It was really bad before Rio
and now it's even worse.
You never tell me anything
that's going on anymore.
I don't understand.
Neither do I.
What was that in the car yesterday?
I could help.
I don't need any help.
Do you realize
that I've been having an affair?
What's that supposed to mean?
Means I've been fucking another guy.
Every Thursday, me and your brother, Hank.
We get together and we fuck.
Not only that, he loves me.
And he still finds me attractive.
All the time.
Not just on vacation.
Hank?
Yeah, Hank.
Aren't you gonna say anything?
Are you gonna get angry?
- Where are you gonna go?
- I was just gonna go to my mother's.
How're you gonna get there?
I was gonna take a cab.
I could really use some, some money.
I'll go to the bank later.
Here.
Hi, you've reached Gina and Andy.
Leave a message.
Please hang up
and try your call...
Come on.
Last person I ever thought I'd see again
as long as I lived.
Charlie Hanson.
You're still a crook?
You come all this way to insult me?
Did you hear anything about a holdup
at the Westchester Shopping Mall?
What would I know about Westchester?
That's just for upstanding citizens
such as yourself.
Have you heard anything?
Why would I hear anything about anything?
I sell diamonds.
- And fence them.
- Never!
Did you hear of a young guy
called Bobby Lasorda?
Wrong tree, Charlie.
A couple of punks shot my wife in a holdup.
She's dead.
I'm sorry.
I don't give a shit
about your little side business,
I don't care about anything anymore,
except finding the guy who did this.
Do you know anything?
I remember when Charlie Hanson
started out on the streets.
Young and cocky, good cutter.
A long time ago, Charlie.
You always hated my guts,
you called me a crook,
but you didn't know shit
about how the world works,
or what some people will do for money.
I guess,
now you know, Charlie.
The world is an evil place, Charlie.
Some of us make money off of that,
and others get destroyed.
He walked in here,
he looks a little bit like you, Charlie.
He walked in here and I almost knew him,
right off the bat.
Hello.
It's me.
Andy, Jesus, man, we got problems.
What do you mean, problems?
Bobby's girlfriend's
got a fucking brother, okay.
And the guy is blackmailing me, all right.
He said he's gonna go to the cops, all right,
or kill me if I don't pay him $10,000.
All right, all right.
Just stay there, I'll be right over,
I'll figure something out.
- Andy, this guy isn't fucking around.
- All right, I'll figure something out.
Andy, Jake needs to see you.
They're all in the conference room
with the IRS guys.
They're going all the way back
- through your accounts.
- Just fuck 'em, I got to go to my dad's.
I'm gonna have to tell them you were here.
For God's sake, say something.
Okay.
We're in trouble.
The worst trouble imaginable.
You're aware of that, right?
So, why don't we try and fix it?
There's almost no choice,
but you're gonna have to follow my lead.
No questions, no hesitations.
I've done that before, all right,
and that's how come I'm standing here,
with my life going down the fucking toilet.
Fuck you, fuck you, I'll do it alone.
You can sit here and wait till you go to jail
and take it up the ass
for the rest of your fucking life.
Let's do it already, what's your idea?
Sorry, what's your idea?
What's Bobby's girlfriend's name?
Chris. Yeah, Chris.
Chris.
Call Chris, tell her to get her brother
over to her apartment.
- What for?
- We'll meet him.
He figures we owe him $10,000,
we have to resolve it.
Resolve it how?
Play it by ear, see what happens,
maybe we pay him.
He's never gonna let us off the hook.
All right, we're gonna be paying him back
for the rest of our lives.
Hey, you finally figured out
something for yourself.
Let's just get the money, see what happens.
Where are we gonna get $10,000?
No, that might be easier.
Call Chris.
Taxi!
Andy, Jesus Christ! You're gonna kill him.
Come on.
Shit.
Hold the bag. Hold out the fucking bag!
Hold it open like this. Hold it open like that!
I got it, I got it.
- Oh, shit, do you want these?
- Just put it in the bag!
Put it in the bag!
- Out.
- Got it.
Oh, my God, Andy.
- Did you touch anything?
- Did you go crazy?
- Are you fucking nuts?
- Did you touch anything?
- Wait, you didn't have to kill him, all right.
He's not gonna go to the cops. All right?
He's a drug dealer.
Yeah, I guess he'll just go
to some other dealers and suppliers
and that's all we need,
is 10 South Americans chasing us
for the rest of our lives.
Did you touch anything?
I don't think so.
- You don't think so?
- I don't think so, no!
- No, I didn't touch anything!
- Think, God damn it, you think!
- I don't... I don't like this, Andy!
- Did you touch anything?
- I don't like...
- Shut up! Shut up!
- Did you touch anything?
- No.
Are we good?
Let's go.
You got the money, chico?
I don't like wasted trips.
You don't look happy.
Mind if I call you groucho?
No, I don't mind.
Like what you're seeing?
- Yeah, a lot.
- Stand up. Stand up!
- All right, all right.
- Turn around.
- All right, all right, all right.
So how we gonna do this?
Gladly pay you the money, got plenty of it.
How do we know you're not gonna bleed us
for the next couple of months?
I just want enough to take care of Chris.
That's nice, my brother
wouldn't take care of me like that.
Hey, what do you say, Chris,
should I trust this guy?
- Yes.
- Speak up. What?
Yes.
I don't think so.
No, Andy, don't, don't, don't...
- What did you say?
- No, you can't do that, I won't let you.
- You won't let me?
- No, no more,
you kill her, you're gonna have to kill me.
Not such a bad idea.
You know, in fact, it's a pretty good one.
You know I know.
What do you know?
I know.
I'm sorry.
I fucked it all up.
Just do it.
Do it.
Go ahead.
Come on.
You'd be doing me a favor.
Get the hell out of here.
Get the hell out of here! Go!
Go!
Hank! Hank!
Move out of the way,
move out of the way.
You'll have to move your vehicle.
Move out of the way.
Hi, Mr. Hanson.
Stick your head in. If he's awake now,
you can spend
a couple of minutes with him.
Dad?
I never meant to hurt her.
I just needed money.
There wasn't supposed to be any gun.
She wasn't supposed to be in the store.
Everything just went wrong.
It's okay, Andy.
It's okay.
Nurse, the heart monitor
cut out for a second.
It does that, don't worry.
If it happens again, just press reset.
Dad.
Nurse!
Emergency personnel, code blue.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org