Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I've lived in the
theatre since I was a kid.
What I don't know about acting
isn't worth knowing.
Now, you may be 20 years
old and just beginning,
but I think you're a genius.
You've got magnetism,
but no idea how to use it.
You have to grab the audience
by the throat and say:
"Now, you buggers, you
pay attention to me!"
and remember this,
when you're on the stage acting,
the theatre is the only reality.
Everything else, the world outside,
what civilians call the real world,
is nothing but fantasy.
And I bloody well
won't let you forget it.
The trouble is, darling,
I'm an incurable romantic.
I believe in love,
I believe in happiness,
I believe in us.
(Archie) No, you don't.
You're just saying that.
There's someone else, isn't there?
I love you, I do.
I do, I
love you--
and I used to believe
we'd live happily ever after.
Didn't you?
With every fiber of my being.
only now...
[Audience applauding]
[Car honking]
[Clock bell tolls]
[Door squeaking]
Good morning, miss Lambert.
Good morning, Margery,
is anyone with my lord and master?
(Margery) No.
Darling, what are you doing here?
I want an answer, Michael.
What's the question?
What did I say to you
before we went to sleep last night, hmm?
Uh, I give up. What did you say to me
before we went to sleep last night?
I said I was tired.
It seems a perfectly natural thing
to say before you go to sleep.
Christ, Michael, you can be
an irritating little shit!
Julia, Julia, really,
if your public could
only hear your language.
I want them to hear.
I want every bloody one of them to hear.
I'm tired. I am utterly exhausted.
I need a holiday.
Just admit it, Michael.
you've never understood what it means
to carry a play,
to sweat it out night after night.
I'm the only one who takes it
seriously, Michael, you know that.
All you do is count the money and
think it's a bloody great lark.
Take the play off.
But we'll lose a fortune.
Our partner won't like it.
To hell with dolly!
[Sighing]
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
God, I didn't mean to be so vile.
It's just I'm-- I'm
near to breaking point.
Everything's so tedious.
[Sighing]
I want something to happen.
What?
I wish I knew.
Please. please close the
play at the end of the month.
[Exhales]
Yeah. I really do
have to think about it.
We can't have the theatre dark.
Hmm?
I'll try and see what
I can do. I promise.
Hmm?
Please.
I promise.
Thank you.
You were very quiet
leaving the house this morning.
Well, I didn't want to wake you.
You were dead to the world.
Hmm. I did my exercises
and went for a run.
Exercises, running...
God, Michael,
you're the vainest man in London.
Me, vain? nonsense.
[Giggles]
I just want to preserve my magnificent
good looks for as long as possible.
[Chuckling]
Oh, yes, speaking of good looks,
did you notice that
young man as you came in?
No.
He's an American.
Son of a friend of a
friend of Eddie Gilbert's.
I can't see what that's
got to do with me.
He admires you tremendously.
Oh, he sounds frightfully intelligent.
What's his name?
Can't remember.
Uh, unfortunately,
he's as poor as a church mouse.
I thought we might give
him a spot of lunch.
Well, he's awfully
good-mannered, for an American.
(Julia) uh!
Rubbish mail, Margery.
Yes, Mr. Gosselyn.
Uh, I would like to
introduce you to my wife,
Julia Lambert.
Julia, this
is-- this is--
this is the young man
I was telling you about.
He wants to learn the business,
so we're starting him
off with our accountant.
It-it's an honor to
meet you, miss Lambert.
I wonder if we could persuade you
to come and eat a chop with us.
Michael will drive you back after lunch.
Gee, that's real kind of you.
You two take the lift,
I'll take the stairs.
Last one down's a sissy.
Miss Lambert,
could I-- could
I ask you a favor?
I can't give you any more
room, if that's what you mean.
No, no, no, it's, uh... I wonder...
would you...
would you let me have a photograph?
Of course.
Gee, that's swell of you.
I've seen you in
"Farewell, my love" 3 times.
You haven't. Have you really?
It's such a silly play.
Oh, it's not the play,
it's you. You're just... just great.
I'm glad you liked me.
Liked you? I loved you.
[Elevator thudding]
[Door squeaking]
- I won.
- (Julia) What?
Well done.
Come on, Mr... uh...
all an actress like Julia needs
is a vehicle.
It's the actors the public go to see,
not the play.
That's true in my case. I'd see
you in anything, miss Lambert.
But you know what I'd
really like to find out?
How did you start?
How did you get to be where you are,
owning a theatre, top of the tree?
Clean living and hard work. Cigarette?
We owe it all to a rude, foul-mouthed
brute called Jimmie Langton.
We were in his repertory
company in Middlesbrough.
He knew all there is to know
about theatre and acting.
That's where I met Michael.
That's how we began.
I was a rotten actor.
Yes, but you have presence.
The audience always
gasps when you come on.
It's his dazzling good looks, you see.
Gee, this is fascinating. fascinating.
Dreadfully jealous of him?
You're very sweet, but
I know perfectly well
that all I can play are
diplomats, lawyers and politicians.
I'm more interested in
the business side. that's--
Yes, but you know as well as I do
that we'd be nothing without Jimmie.
I always lay a place
for him at the table.
Just in case he turns up.
He's been dead for 15 years.
Yes, but you never know.
He was a monster.
Uh, how do you spell your first name?
T- O-M.
[Laughing]
[Nib squeaking]
[Gramophone playing]
[People clapping]
[Car honking]
(Dancer) Hoy!
Hoy!
(Archie) For God's sake,
don't torture yourself like this, Laura.
[Julia sobbing]
No one will ever know
how much I loved him.
He was my earth, my moon,
all the stars in the firmament.
Farewell, my love.
[Audience applauding]
Bravo! Bravo!
[People laughing]
No, there's nothing left for me now
but to tour Canada and Australia,
God help me.
Nonsense, miss Lambert.
It's not nonsense.
[Sighing]
I've decided to retire
and let myself go.
I'll have potatoes for lunch
and potatoes for dinner.
Beer. God, I love beer!
And treacle pudding and
cherry tart and cream.
Cream, cream, cream, cream, cream...
[Breathing deeply]
as God is my judge,
I'll never eat a lettuce leaf again.
[Doorbell ringing]
Oh, God, I bet I know who that is.
Good afternoon, Evie.
Oh, Mrs. De Vries, what a surprise.
Uh, I hope this isn't inconvenient
but I have to see miss Lambert
on a business matter.
She isn't having one
of her afternoon naps,
is she?
Wait a minute.
[Door squeaking]
Guess who's here.
Show her in.
Business, she says, but isn't it funny
how she always manages
to time her visits
when you're lying stark bollock naked.
Enough of that, you dirty-minded slut.
Show her in.
Mrs. De Vries.
(Dolly) Julia, darling.
Dolly, dear. hmm.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I always seem to call when
you're-- you're otherwise engaged.
[Laughing]
- Tea?
- Lovely.
Ignore me. I'll-- I'll just
sit here quiet as a lamb
until you're done.
So Evie said
something about business. Hmm?
What? Oh, yes.
Um, Michael tells me you
want to close the play.
My husband's a devious little runt.
Oh, that's unfair.
He was perfectly right to consult me.
We're partners. the 3 of us.
A perfect combination.
My money, his know-how, your genius.
I'm exhausted, Dolly.
[Grunts]
I feel twice my age which makes me 90.
I'm bored. Life has
nothing in store for me.
You mean that, or are you acting?
I never know when you're acting.
I'm not acting.
I'm near to having a breakdown.
I feel as though my
life's come to an end.
All right. All right.
All done.
Oh, thank you, you're a dear.
Uh.
Are you really near a breakdown, Julia?
Oh, I don't know. I don't know.
I'm in such an odd state at the moment.
[Inhaling]
It's as if...
It's as if the curtain's
come down on act 1,
but I have no idea
what happens in act 2.
[Inaudible mimicking]
I- I'm in a sort of limbo.
Waiting for something
to happen. But what?
What?
Oh, please, Dolly, be my friend.
Oh.
Make Michael take the play off.
I need a holiday.
I could visit-- visit
my mother in Jersey,
and then visit you in France.
Oh. I could swim in
your pool. In the nuddy.
[Laughing]
(Woman) Lovely flowers for someone.
(Evie) Oh, hello, a
blooming florist's shop.
Who sent them? Mrs. De Vries?
Very likely. Or Lord Tamerley.
Here, don't forget,
you've got dinner with him
after the show tonight.
Yes, I know.
Expect you'll have to
turn on the waterworks
for him again as per usual.
I wish you'd teach me to cry real tears.
The times I've needed them.
Oh, here's a card.
[Humming]
From Mr. Thomas Fennel,
Tavistock Square.
What a place to live.
Who the hell do you suppose he is, Evie?
Oh, some feller knocked all of a heap
by your fatal beauty, I expect.
Probably cost a fortune.
Went without dinner for a week.
Oh, pull the other one.
[Man singing]
Beginners, please, miss Lambert.
Mmm-hmm.
Well, whoever Mr. Thomas Fennel is,
I think it's all right
having a young man send me flowers
at my time of life.
I mean, it
just shows you--
How do you know he's a young man?
He's probably over 80.
Go to hell.
[Band playing]
[People talking and laughing]
# I'm on my way I'm on my way
# I'm busy 'cause I'm on my way #
[People applauding]
Thank you.
Julia Lambert.
The champagne now, my lord?
Thank you, Antoine.
And for you, madame Lambert?
I'd prefer beer but I mustn't,
so I'll make do with bubbly.
Thank you.
[Giggling] It's for you. Open it.
[Woman singing]
Oh.
It's a portrait of Clairon.
She was a great actress,
and I believe you
have many of her gifts.
Charles, you are sweet.
I thought you might like it.
It's by way of being a parting present.
You're going away?
No. But I shan't be seeing you anymore.
Oh, Charles, not again.
[Inhaling]
No. this is becoming a ritual. Why?
We have such a beautiful
friendship, Julia.
It's unique in my
experience, but people talk.
They don't understand.
And even though we know the truth,
if we go on seeing one another,
there will be a terrible scandal.
No, there won't.
Michael and I lead separate lives.
That's why we're so happily married.
More or less.
Jumped-up little tart,
that's what she is.
Never stops acting, on-stage or off.
She's just one big pose.
Dashed pretty.
Shut up, Rupert, don't
show your ignorance.
I know all about her.
We were both born
in the channel islands, Jersey.
Her father was our
doctor. A Jersey doctor!
You can't get more common than that.
It's only common sense, darling.
I don't want to lose you.
I-- I have few
friends. Real friends.
You're the only person in my life
with whom I can be entirely myself.
I'm terribly low at the moment.
I-- I
need you.
Let's go on seeing each other. Please.
Uh, please forgive us intruding
like this, miss Lambert.
My friend and I are
such very great admirers.
And I wonder... do you remember me?
Florence Coltraine, isn't it?
[Whispers] Correct.
Rupert and I want you
to settle an argument.
I think I used to know
your father in Jersey.
He was a doctor, wasn't he?
He used to come to
our house quite often.
Actually, he was a vet.
He used to go to your house
to deliver the bitches.
The house was full of them.
# Life is just a bowl of cherries
# don't take it serious
life's too mysterious
# you work, you save you worry so
# but you can't take
your dough when you go #
[Exclaims]
I'm sorry, I didn't
mean to frighten you.
T- O-M.
You remember.
Did you like
the-- the flowers?
Oh, Mr. Thomas Fennel, Tavistock Square.
Yes, of course, thank you.
Well, uh, I couldn't
decide between a single rose
and every flower in the store.
Is that why you're here
at this time of night?
To find out if I received the flowers?
No. You see, I don't have a phone yet.
[Door opening] And I...
[Wilson clearing throat]
Um...
You wouldn't come to tea
with me one day, would you?
I don't see why not.
Will you really?
How about next Friday?
138 Tavistock Square, 4:30?
[Laughing]
All right. I'll be there.
Gee, that's swell. See you then.
# The sweet things in life
to you were just loaned
# so how gonna you lose
what you've never owned?
# Life is just a bowl of cherries
[Tom and Julia laughing]
# so live and laugh at it all
# (Chorus) Life is just a bowl of cherries
# don't make it serious
life's too mysterious
# you work, you save you worry so
# but you can't take your
dough when you go go
# keep on repeating "it's the berries"
# the strongest oak must fall #
Oh?
I saw you drive up.
I'm afraid I'm on the 3rd floor.
I hope you don't mind.
And if I do?
[Both chuckle]
We're there.
Thank God for that.
[Door squeaking]
[Julia panting]
[Laughs]
The gas ring's in the bathroom.
Oh.
It isn't the Ritz, but it's home.
No, it's-- it's
charming. It's so London.
It reminds me of my early days.
[Laughing]
I have to put coins in the gas meter.
Oh, yes, so did I.
[Both laughing]
Have some cake. I bought it specially.
Oh.
I shouldn't, but I will.
[Laughs]
[Sighing]
You know something? You
ought to be in movies.
Real actresses don't make films.
But beautiful actresses do.
Hmm.
Well, I saw you in "Nobody's
perfect" on Broadway.
I was 14 at the time.
I wish you hadn't told me that.
[Both laughing]
I stood outside the stage door
and, uh, I got your autograph.
You asked me my name. I told you.
You knew how to spell it then.
[Both laughing]
What's so funny?
You remind me of something.
What is it?
My husband. In a scene we had to play.
He didn't know how to sit down.
[Both laughing]
Jimmie made him do it
over and over again.
Uh, I can't stay long.
I must have a nap before my performance.
But you've only just arrived.
And you-- you can't
go without, uh,
without, well, seeing the view.
It's really great.
If you just come over to the window...
Isn't it terrific?
(Tom) I just love London.
It's so big, but it's
also kind of friendly.
And all those people,
each with their own lives.
I can't explain it.
When I first came to London,
I stood in Piccadilly Circus
looking at the lights
and the people and the taxis,
and I said out loud:
"One day I'm going to conquer you."
And you have.
Have I?
I wonder--
[Sighing]
Look at my hair.
[Julia panting]
Uh, here.
Oh?
Thank you.
And I thought you were
such a shy young man.
When am I-- when am
I gonna see you again?
You want to see me again?
What do you think?
I'll ring you up one of these days.
Uh, my hat...
Oh, uh...
Good. Well, uh, I have a phone now.
And the number's museum-4516.
So promise you'll call soon.
On my honor.
[Laughs] You know, don't come down.
I can see myself out.
[Birds twittering]
For Christ's sake, Julia,
what do you think you're doing?
you're supposed to be playing a whore,
not a schoolgirl with a
crush on her gym master.
You kissed him
as if you were frightened
of catching his cold.
When you kiss, you should feel
as if your bones are
melting inside your body.
Tongues, darling,
that's what it's about, tongues.
Now, I know you're a virgin.
don't give me the waterworks,
Julia, I'm too old for that.
You're a virgin, so what you have
to do is find a handsome young man,
like your juvenile
man, Michael Gosselyn.
Go back to your rooms,
take your clothes off, lie
on the bed, open your legs
and ask him to give it to
you hot, sweet and strong.
If that doesn't improve your
acting, then nothing will.
Right, let's do it again.
[Julia laughing]
What's so funny?
[Sighing]
I feel as though
I'm a 2-year-old.
That's 88 years you've lost in a week.
[Giggling]
Tell us the secret,
we'll bottle it and make a fortune.
Hmm.
[Door closing]
Damn it all, miss Lambert,
you don't look so bad.
You can go on
playing 25-year-olds,
30-year-olds for a
good long time yet.
And then what?
Whoo!
Mothers, grandmothers and old maids.
[Snorting]
Bugger playwrights.
Can't write for women.
They're all men, that's the trouble.
[Telephone ringing]
[Sighing]
Yes?
Good morning.
[Julia laughing]
T- O-M.
You promised to call me.
(Julia) Give a girl a chance.
(Tom) when am I going to see you again?
As soon as I have a moment to spare.
Come to tea after the matinee.
Oh, I'm not falling for that one again.
How about dinner after the show then?
If you insist.
I do.
[Piano playing]
# On the silver screen
# he melts her foolish
heart in every single scene
# although she's quite
aware that here and there
# are traces of the cad about the boy
[Laughing]
# Lord knows she's not a fool girl
# she really shouldn't care
# Lord knows she's not a school girl
# in the flurry of her first affair
# will it ever cloy this odd diversity
# of misery and joy #
- I told them:
Look, there's lord Crumley over there.
And I think that's lady Laweston.
What have you been reading, Debrett's?
Debrett's? No, the tatler.
[Laughing]
Oh, you have to know who's
who to get on in this town.
Oh, you want to get on, do you?
I want to get on you, Julia.
Don't be disgusting.
But I want you.
I do.
[Glasses clinking]
You're the loveliest girl that one
I want you.
[Giggling]
Your conversation's
frightfully limited, Tom.
Dance with me.
What time is it?
Oh, well, uh, I... I
forgot to put on my watch.
Have you pawned it?
No, no, I just, uh,
I-- I dressed in
rather a hurry tonight.
# They'll never believe me
# they'll never believe me
# that from this great big world
# you've chosen me... #
[Laughing]
[Julia screaming]
[Continues laughing]
He treated you like a tart.
Which of course is what you are.
(Julia) He was my earth, my moon,
and all the stars in the firmament.
[Whispering] The photo's
in the wrong place!
Farewell, my love.
You were wonderful tonight, my darling.
[Whooping]
Bloody marvelous.
You almost made me cry.
Only almost?
I'll kill whoever set the photo.
Thanks, Archie.
And what've you done to your eyes?
Hmm? Some new makeup?
I've never seen them
shine like that before.
Your call, Mr. Dexter.
Hmm.
[Archie laughing]
Sorry about the photo,
it won't happen again.
Hmm.
Your call, miss Lambert.
You're forgiven.
[Audience applauding]
What's the matter with her?
[Julia exclaiming]
Darling, Julia.
You were quite wonderful tonight.
I'll say. Absolutely first-rate.
Thank you.
Yes, I believe I was
firing on all cylinders.
And I'm starving, absolutely ravenous.
Evie, what have we
got for supper tonight?
Tripe and onions.
Oh, how divine. I
adore tripe and onions.
Michael, Michael, if you love me,
if you've got any spark of tenderness
in that hard heart of yours,
let me have a bottle of beer.
Beer? Yes.
Julia. Just this once.
Oh, Evie, that's for you.
Uh, please?
Julia, I think it's a damn shame.
(Julia) What is?
Well, that you're taking the play off.
The good news is,
I've found an Italian company
who wants the theatre for 3 months,
so I said they could have it. Hmm. Mmm.
I'm sure your mother's
as excited as I am
at the thought of being with you.
We'll have such fun at my place, Julia.
You could do anything you like.
Rest. anything.
I've changed my mind. I don't know why,
but I'm beginning to enjoy
myself again. oh, but--
let's run through the summer
and then find something
new for the autumn.
But I've... I-I've...
I've told the Italians.
Then un-tell them.
And I was so looking forward to France.
Stars will be stars.
I forgot.
What?
Hmm...
[Exclaims]
Oh, my God. A cartier.
Well spotted. When's your birthday?
November 20.
Hmm.
Happy birthday.
Uh, but it's not November 20.
Don't be so pedantic. Open it.
Oh, that's the one thing
I've wanted my whole life.
Thank you.
[Giggles]
Uh, geez, it's lousy
I can't give you anything in return.
Give me that watch you
pawned to buy me supper.
Have you redeemed it yet? Ah! thanks.
It'll amuse me to wear it.
I love you, Julia.
[Sighing]
This is total insanity.
I'm old enough to be...
[Laughing]
God, I'm a fool,
I'm such a bloody fool.
Good morning, Evie. where's my wife?
In your study.
- My study?
- Mmm-hmm.
What's she doing there?
Exercising.
Exercising?
[Grunting]
What are you doing?
Swimming the channel, what
do you think I'm doing?
Yeah, but why?
[Panting]
Miss Phillips said my
tummy needed tightening,
So I'm tightening it.
[Grunting]
Oh.
Oh, yes, I had a thought.
We should take a country house
for the summer.
What do you think?
[Julia grunting]
I'll talk to you later.
[Continues grunting]
(Michael) So do you think a house
for the summer's a good idea?
Yes.
Golf, swimming, tennis.
It'll be especially good
for Roger. He loves golf.
Then he'll have to decide
what's he gonna do with his life.
I think he should go to university.
He doesn't want to,
and we shouldn't insist.
It's his life.
Oh, yes, I had another idea.
You remember that young
chap I introduced you to?
Which young chap?
That American good-looking fellow.
Remember?
[Clearing throat] No.
He wants to learn the business.
Tom Fennel's his name.
American, you must remember.
Vaguely.
Well, he's frightfully good at his job.
He's a wizard with money.
Lots of American ideas for avoiding tax.
What about him?
Well, I thought we might invite him down
for a couple of weeks to
spend his holiday with us.
Why would we want to do that?
He'll be company for Roger.
He's only a bit older.
Roger will like him, I'm sure of it.
Shall I ask him?
Hmm.
Ah!
(Julia) Remind me to keep exercising.
So, will you come and stay?
Michael says the house is
frightfully comfortable.
Probably not.
I'm going abroad for a couple of months.
(Julia) What fun.
Well, you'll be busy, won't you?
Looking for a new play, reading scripts.
So, what do you think?
He hasn't done justice to your eyes.
As a matter of fact,
there is a play that interests me.
It's about an older woman
who has an affair with a younger man.
Oh, a farce.
Why do you say that?
Well, because everyone
laughs at the older woman.
No, not in this play. It's all serious.
The act 1 curtain's good.
It comes as a shock to her.
What does?
That she's fallen in love with the boy.
And it happens just when everything
seemed to her so dull and unpromising,
as if her life was over.
She finds the affair exhilarating.
And everyone keeps telling her
she looks 10 years younger.
I trust she doesn't confess to the boy
that she loves him. That's always fatal.
Does it sound like something for me?
Oh, don't be ridiculous, Julia.
No, your public would
never stand for it.
If such a woman asked me,
I know what advice I'd give her.
- What?
- Break it off at once.
It will only end in tears.
But, Charles, she can't do that.
Why ever not?
Because she's fallen in love with him,
That's why. She's helpless.
Hmm.
The character in the play.
[Door opens]
Dolly, old thing,
how are you?
I haven't seen you for ages.
Sit down and make yourself, uh,
comfy.
So, come to see that
the old firm's raking in
the dividends for you?
Michael, I'll come
straight to the point.
You know I'm not one to gossip,
but-- but I'm
upset about Julia.
[Sighing]
I think you ought to know that
people are beginning to talk.
What the devil do you mean?
Well, it's absurd that at her age,
she should make herself so conspicuous
with a young boy.
Oh, you mean Tom Fennel?
don't be such a fool, Dolly.
I'm not a fool.
When someone is as well-known as Julia
and they're always seen with the
same man, naturally people talk.
Tom Fennel is a very
good type of American.
He's clean, honest and by
way of being a gentleman.
He's boring, dull, common and a snob.
He's just using Julia.
He's a little gold digger.
Can you look me in the eyes, Dolly,
and tell me you really think
Julia's having an affair with him?
No.
Ah.
the truth is, Michael,
I've hardly seen her.
She never telephones anymore, and...
and...
I understand, Dolly, believe me.
[Sniffling]
She's very fond of you, you know that,
but she's bound to have other friends.
I don't think chaps
should talk about their wives to others.
I think it's frightfully bad form
but let me explain
something to you about Julia.
Sex doesn't mean a thing to her.
it was different in the beginning.
Then she could be somewhat
tiresome sometimes.
But after she had Roger, she changed.
Having a baby seemed to settle her.
All those instincts went
into her acting, you see.
Gossip isn't good for business, Michael.
I mean, if Julia had one flagrant
affair after another, nobody would notice
but-- but this boy,
he's half her age.
The public has always looked up to you
as such a devoted and loyal couple.
And so we are, damn it. In our way.
Devoted, united, but not...
How shall I put it? Not possessive.
We're a very modern couple.
[Lighter clicking]
(Michael) Hello, Roger, my boy.
Hello, daddy.
Glad to be finished at Eton?
No mummy?
No, it's Saturday. she's got 2 shows.
3 and 4 pence, sir.
She'll be down first
thing in the morning.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, sir.
Here, let me give you a hand.
She's bringing a young
chap down with her,
your age more or less.
A yank. I think you'll like him.
[Birds chirping]
[I get a kick out of you
by Frank Sinatra playing]
# I get no kick from champagne
# mere alcohol doesn't thrill me at all
# so tell me why should it be true
# that I get a kick out of you #
[Sighing] What's the matter?
Nothing.
Tell me.
It's... I-- I-- I just don't...
I'm worried sick, that's all.
What about?
Tell me, Tom. What?
It's money, I owe money.
Oh.
Is that all?
I thought it was something serious.
Well, it's ok for you, Julia,
but I just can't afford
all the things we do.
Nightclubs, restaurants.
Sweetheart.
How can you let a trifle
like that upset you?
Don't worry about it.
I'll give you the money.
No, I-- I couldn't take
any money from you.
What nonsense.
Why grudge me the happiness
it gives me to get you out of a hole?
# I get a kick out of you #
[Ducks quacking]
(Julia) I thought tonight
we might play Mahjong.
Do you play
Mahjong, Tom? no, I--
Sorry, um, no can do. We're going down
to the pub to assess the local talent.
(Michael) Oh, I might come with you.
The barmaid is an absolute stunner.
God, you're all so vulgar.
Well, mummy, you have an early night.
It'll do you good.
You're looking awfully fagged.
[Michael humming]
More wine?
[All clamoring]
(Woman) First word.
(Archie) First word.
(All) Film. Cinema.
3 words. The first word...
She'll never get this
one. Never get this.
(Archie) Small.
(Woman) Very small.
Oh, um, wee. wee, wee, wee.
(Man) Wee.
(Archie) 2nd word.
There you go.
(Archie) 2nd word, fly.
Very nice, Julia.
Wee, wee. wee, wee. wee, wee, wee, wee.
Julia, Julia, Julia,
we're in mixed company.
[Laughing]
(Woman) Oh, let's do the 3rd word.
(Archie) 3rd word. 3rd word.
Winking! winking!
Oh, oh, oh.
- "Wee Willie winkie!"
- Yes.
[People cheering]
Yes. yes, you idiots. "Wee Willie winkie".
Shirley Temple, God, you're stupid.
I don't get "Willie."
Oh, well, they did.
It-it's an English thing.
Ah.
Ok.
[All chattering]
(Avice) Hello, you.
(Tom) Hey.
[Avice squealing]
(Roger) More water.
(Avice) No, stop it!
[Boys laughing]
(Roger) I told you.
Oh, no. I just dried
off, Tom, I hate you.
[Tom laughing]
I'm going to get you back.
(Roger) You're an uncivilized oaf.
And you're running away.
(Girl) Come on, Michael,
you promised me a dance.
So I did, sorry.
I might be out of practice.
(Grace) Answer my question, Julia.
(Julia) What question?
Would you?
Would I what?
Tour in the second Mrs. Tanqueray
for 17 pounds a week.
And it's a 6-month tour, darling.
6 months.
No, I can't be away
from home for 6 months.
What would Archie do without me?
Oh, he'll think of something.
Mmm.
they're so bloody
mean, these managements.
I said, "give me 18
pounds and I'll do it."
And he said, "18 pounds? 18
pounds!" Cheeky little sod.
What are you doing tonight?
I don't know.
Do you know that girl's name?
Which girl?
Oh, that's Avice Crichton.
"You couldn't have her for 80 pounds,
never mind 18 pounds."
I thought that was witty.
Don't you think that was witty?
Hilarious.
Well, they're not
number-one dates, darling.
Oh, not at all.
Lowestoft, bournemouth and chesterfield
and Christ knows where else.
6 months...
Mummy, we're going to London to have
supper and do the clubs, all right?
No. No, really not,
you've all had too much to drink.
Tom hasn't. He's driving,
and one of the girls has a car.
[Laughing]
[Brakes squealing]
[Crickets chirping]
(Tom) Yeah. Yeah, we had a great time
[Roger groaning]
[Roger chuckling]
[Car doors closing]
(Roger) Good night, old man.
Good night, pal.
[Door squeaking]
[Door closing]
Are you-- are you crazy, what
do you think you're you doing?
I was about to ask you the same thing.
Go back to your room.
I've hardly seen you
since you've been here.
You've seen Roger more than me.
We haven't been alone.
What's wrong with you?
You haven't held me,
you haven't kissed me.
Shh.
[Sobbing] Can't you
see the state I'm in?
And-- and tonight-- tonight,
going off like that,
not a word to me, with that little tart.
Oh, Avice Crichton is not a tart.
Avice Crichton certainly looks like one.
I'm going back to London tomorrow.
Good. I hope you remember
to tip the servants
or do you want me to
give you the money, hmm?
These are yours, take them back.
Don't be such a bloody little fool.
You think I like being a kept boy?
You think I like being
humiliated like this, huh?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm
sorry. I didn't mean it.
That makes it even worse.
I should never have let
you give me these presents.
you lend me that money.
By the end of the
month I'll pay you back.
I've apologized.
Don't go to London tomorrow, please.
[Sniffling]
I love you, Tom.
Please.
I'm tired. I want to go to bed now.
[Sobbing]
(Jimmie) Now, that's
the real thing, Julia,
or my name's not Jimmie Langton.
but I've got some notes.
You're still going over the top.
You've got to learn restraint.
And for Christ's sake,
stop crying, will you?
We all know you can turn your
tears on and off like a tap,
so turn them off, will you?
[Sobbing]
Well, bugger me,
you really are crying
this time, aren't you?
I can't say I wasn't moved,
but you've got to learn to do it
so that it seems real.
seems to be real,
that's the art of acting.
Hold the mirror up to nature, ducky,
otherwise you'll become a nervous wreck,
take to drink
and end up a piss artist
playing gin-sodden whores
all over Scotland on number-3 tours.
Technique, that's what
I want you to learn.
Technique.
[Knocking on door]
I saw the light on. can I come in?
- Yes, of course.
- Is something wrong?
- No.
- You've been crying.
No, no, just a bad dream.
What is it, sweetheart?
We picked up a couple of girls tonight.
Who did?
Tom and me.
Oh.
Tom made me promise I wouldn't tell you.
He said you'd be furious.
Were they tarts?
No, they're on the stage.
Joan asked me if I could get her
an understudy in your next play.
Yes, tarts.
I just had to tell you.
Tell me what?
I thought it was about time
I found out what it was all about.
Roger, what do you mean?
Love.
Love?
It's not that great, really.
I don't know why everybody
makes such a fuss about it.
Mummy, what's the matter?
You are upset.
Why are you crying?
Oh, because you're such a little boy.
Don't cry.
Hmm.
I needed to tell you.
It had to happen sooner or later.
It makes me feel so old.
"Age cannot wither her,
nor custom stale her infinite variety".
If I'd been Cleopatra,
I'd have put whoever said that to death.
[Laughing]
To tell you the truth,
I didn't enjoy it much.
Oh, you're so very, very young.
I'll grow out of it.
Hmm.
[Laughing]
I may go abroad for a while.
Oh, where?
I don't know. Italy, France. abroad.
I say,
about-- about
that under study,
is there any chance for Joan?
Tell her to write to me.
Thanks. Good night.
Good night, darling.
An understudy, my foot.
[Exhales]
[Footsteps approaching]
Wait. Hold it.
[Door creaking]
It's from you know who.
I don't want to be disturbed.
Good matinee?
All right,
but I'm not feeling very well.
Draw up a chair. Sit down.
What's the matter?
Nothing. I haven't been sleeping.
I had a post card from Roger.
He's in Naples.
Says he's having a great time.
Yes, but you haven't come
here just to tell me that,
have you?
No, it's something else. I, uh...
I can't pay you back
the money that I owe you.
I know I said at the end of last month.
But I just don't have it.
I could pay it off.
I hate having to ask
for more time. But...
Don't be such a bloody
little idiot, Tom.
It's so humiliating, Julia.
Geez, when you said
you'd pay my tips for me,
how do you think that made me feel?
I said I'm sorry, I didn't mean it.
I was jealous of you
spending so much time with Roger.
I was jealous.
I was jealous of you going out
and having a good time without me.
Is that so horrible?
I should never have
accepted anything from you.
You're everything in the world to me.
You know that.
I love being with you.
I don't want to lose you.
I have few friends. Real friends.
And you're the only person in my life
with whom I can be entirely myself.
[Gasping]
Let's... let's go...
[Exhales]
Let's go on seeing each other. Please.
Oh, Julia.
[Giggling]
(Evie) Well, I've always said,
you're lucky you can cry
without your eyelids swelling.
Go to hell.
Well, you're looking a lot happier,
I'll say that for you.
I hope with good reason.
If you're thinking what
I think you're thinking,
then stop thinking.
All the same, Evie,
you know what I think?
No, what do you think?
What mugs men are.
Well, they can't keep
it in their trousers,
[Julia laughs] that's for sure.
You're a revolting hag.
[Julia giggling]
Yes, I am happier.
Everything will be all right now.
[Sighs] I can't help feeling...
I wish I didn't.
Deep down, I can't help feeling...
What?
A certain contempt for that boy.
He's so transparent.
# Life is just a bowl of cherries
# don't make it serious
life's too mysterious
# you work, you save, you worry so
# but you can't take your dough #
# when you go, go, go
# so keep repeating... #
Are you dancing with
me or with someone else?
I'm sorry,
I-- I-- I, uh,
I can't get over what her
royal highness just said to me.
What? What did she say?
She said I ought to come
and see them in the country.
And I was just thinking,
you think it's ok if
I asked her to dance?
Oh, you're such a dreadful snob, Tom.
I know. That's why England's
the best place for me.
I'm glad we quarreled.
We're closer now than we've ever been.
[Julia giggles]
[Avice moaning]
[Avice panting]
[Tom moaning]
[Both moaning]
[Tom grunts]
[Bell tolling]
Tom?
What?
Can I ask you a favor?
Anything in the world.
You know Julia Lambert well, don't you?
No, not well, slightly.
Oh.
Have you been to bed with her?
Are you crazy?
She's old enough to be my mother.
What about her?
I heard on the grapevine
that she's doing a new play
called "Nowadays",
and there's a part for me in it.
So I wondered if you...
If I'd talk to her?
Yes. Please, Tom,
I'm doing a Sunday night
performance week after next.
Terrible play. Lovely
part. Good shop window.
If you could get
her to see me in it--
Is that all? Consider it done.
I can get Julia Lambert
to do anything I want.
She eats out of my
hand. The part's yours.
Don't be daft,
I'd be lucky to get an audition,
never mind the part.
You'll be in that play or
I'll never kiss you again.
Must say,
never thought you'd keep this up.
Nor did I. But tummies will be tummies.
Saw the preliminary
budget for "Nowadays".
hmm. looks promising.
Must start auditioning. By the way,
have you ever heard of a
girl called Avice Crichton?
The name rings a bell.
I'm told she's rather good.
I was wondering if she might play Sybil.
Guess how I heard about her.
How?
Through Tom.
[Pedal clanking]
He says she's clever.
She's playing in a Sunday night show.
Tom thinks
it might be worthwhile
to go and have a look-see.
- Well, why don't you?
- Can't.
Going down to sandwich to play golf.
Staying the night.
Would it bore you awfully to go?
Tom'll take you.
I'll think about it.
Hmm, am I late or were you early?
The curtain goes up sharp at 8:00.
I hate getting to a
play after it's begun.
Remind me, uh,
what's the name of the actress
we're going to see tonight?
Avice Crichton. You met her.
She came to lunch at Taplow.
- We even fought over her.
- Did we?
- Mmm.
- I don't remember.
I can't wait to hear
what you think of her.
She's so nervous knowing
you're gonna be out front.
You know, these performances are like
rehearsals, but I said you'd understand.
BotToms up.
I had a letter from Roger.
He's having a fine old
time. He's in Rome now.
- Oh, yeah?
- She's awfully pretty.
Who are we talking about now?
Avice Crichton.
Oh.
Yeah, she's got a great
figure. And she's very fair.
What with platinum and peroxide,
there's no lack of blondes these days.
Hers is natural.
I wonder how you know that.
Keep the pace, Julia, don't rush it.
Nice and easy.
[Coughs]
God, this is undrinkable.
He'll have to make a fresh pot.
Julia, please don't.
[Bell tinkling] We'll be late.
The first few minutes don't matter.
But I said we'd be there on the dot.
She's got a very good scene
right at the beginning.
I'm sorry, but I can't
go without my coffee.
Wilson, can you make a fresh pot?
[Sighing] This tastes of bitter aloes.
[Laughs]
Bravo!
[Audience applauding]
[Laughs]
[Piano playing]
(Avice) What time did the
doctor say he was coming?
Any moment now.
Which one's Avice?
The pretty one.
(Avice) Oh, Cynthia,
I do hope he will be able to help me.
(Prompter) "He's meant
to be a miracle worker."
He's meant to be a miracle worker.
[Gasps]
I do so want to see again, Cynthia.
[Sobbing]
[Piano continues playing]
[Exclaims]
[Sobbing]
[Knocking on door]
Miss Lambert, this is such an honor.
You were great.
I'm so glad to meet you again.
And it's awfully good
of you to come round.
I- I'm afraid it's not much of a play
but I took a fancy to the part.
Oh, my dear,
Please don't weep. You're nervous.
And nerves are the respect
we pay our audience.
It was only the first few moments.
After that, you were
splendid, quite splendid.
- Thank you, miss Lambert.
- Of course.
Thank you so much.
Good night, miss
Crichton, and thank you.
You're so good at being blind.
Oh, thank you.
Ask her.
Miss Lambert,
is it true
you're putting on a new play soon?
Yes.
If there's a part for me in it,
could I audition for you?
I'll tell Mr. Gosselyn about you.
If you were to put
in a good word for me,
that would help so much.
I take my husband's advice
more often than he does mine.
Oh, and good night. Please, cheer up.
You should go a long way.
[Exclaims]
[Gasps]
[Screaming]
You didn't think much of her, did you?
On the contrary, I think
a great deal of her.
She's so energetic.
I don't feel like going to a restaurant.
Bolton, straight home, please.
Michael's away. We can talk.
Tell me,
have you been to bed
with Avice Crichton?
Of course not.
Why not? She's pretty.
She's not that sort
of girl. I respect her.
Hmm, do you know what I think?
I think you're madly in love with her.
Are you?
There's no need to
break up the happy home.
Yeah, I'm sorry. I don't
know why I did that.
You did it
because you haven't the
guts to tell me the truth.
You're in love with
that girl, aren't you?
Why not admit it?
Is it because you think
it would harm her
chances of playing Sybil
in the new play?
You ought to know me well enough by now
that I would never let sentiment
interfere with business.
What do you mean?
I think she's rather a find.
I'll tell Michael.
I'll insist she plays the part.
Oh, Julia, you're wonderful.
Hell, I'm so fond of you.
You...
I'm fond of you.
I've liked going to bed with you.
And it pleases me to think
that you liked going to bed with me.
[Laughs]
But let's face it.
I've never been in love with you
and you,
you've never been in love with me.
We both knew it couldn't last.
Hmm.
You're in love with
that girl, aren't you?
You might as well admit it.
Yes.
Go now. Please.
[Door closing]
For Christ's sake, Julia,
what do you think you're doing?
You disappoint me.
Oh, dear, oh, dear, you really do.
After all I've taught you?
You can't just stand there
like a spare prick at a wedding.
For Christ's sake,
Julia, assert yourself.
It's you that matters. You. Only you.
All's fair with love
and the theatre, ducky.
[Julia sobbing]
No one will ever know
how much I loved him.
he was my earth, my moon,
and all the stars in the firmament.
Farewell, my love.
[Audience applauding]
Oh, evening, Mr. Gosselyn.
I didn't expect you back tonight.
How was the golf?
Erratic.
How was the girl?
Oh.
- Brilliant.
- Really?
Very talented.
Yes, but can she act?
Oh, she has to play Sybil.
She's very pretty. Audition her.
You'll see what I mean.
(Michael) I saw the play tonight.
(Julia) Hmm. We took 5 calls.
[Toothbrush clattering]
Julia, I've got something to say to you.
Don't fly into temper, just listen.
What is it?
Why did you give such
a lousy performance?
- A lousy performance?
- Mmm-hmm.
That just shows how little you know.
I've never acted better in my life.
Balls. You were awful.
They adored me tonight.
The public are jackasses.
You were barnstorming.
False from beginning to end.
How dare you speak to me like that,
you little shit?
Get out of my room! What do you know?
You can strike me,
you can swear at me, you
can yell the roof off.
The fact remains that your
acting has gone all to hell.
And I'm not going to
start rehearsing nowadays
with you playing up like a drama
queen suffering from asthma.
Get someone else to play the part!
Don't be stupid, Julia!
I'm taking the play off on Saturday.
And then I want you to go abroad.
Have a break.
Go and see your mother in Jersey.
We'll start rehearsing
"Nowadays" when you...
when you get back.
Am I really that bad?
(Michael) Yes.
Don't let the world
outside cheapen your gifts.
And what Jimmie Langton used to say:
"Your only reality is the theatre."
I hate myself. I'm a slut.
I'm just a rotten bitch.
Rotten through and through.
Nevertheless, you're a great actress.
Not tonight.
No. Not tonight.
Oh, darling, I'm-- I'm
tired out. I...
So stupid of
me. I should--
[Shushing]
You're right. You're right.
[Sniffs]
The only thing is to go away.
Thank you.
[Seagulls cawing]
(Mrs. Lambert) It's so good to see you.
And no drafts,
that's very important, Julia, dear.
Aunt Carrie and I will be very careful
to see that you never sit in a draft.
And you must wear
socks and woolen vests.
I would sooner wear a shroud.
Oh, well, we will
discuss it in the morning.
[Seagulls cawing]
(Turnbull) Miss Avice Crichton.
Good afternoon.
I'm Michael Gosselyn.
Good afternoon, Mr. Gosselyn.
What are you going to do for us?
I thought I'd do something
from "Twelfth night".
Viola.
Ggood. In your own time.
"Make me a willow cabin at your gate
and call upon my soul within the house"
Now do it as if you've got a cold.
I beg your pardon?
Can you do it again,
but this time
as if you've got a bad cold in the nose.
[Nasalized] "Make me a
willow cabin at your gate
[Dolly snickering]
"and call upon my soul within the house
[Sniffs]
"write loyal cantons of contemned love
"and sing them loud
even in the dead of night
[Laughing]
Halloo
your name-- "
Thank you. Can you do a sneeze?
A what?
Can you do a good, big sneeze?
I think so.
[Avice inhaling]
I've got it. Tom, I've got it!
I've got it! (Tom) you got it!
[Mooing]
[Bee buzzing]
She's coming.
Don't over-dramatize, dear.
Just say, "Here's a telegram,"
as if it's the most
natural thing in the world.
Yes, but I hate telegrams.
Um, Julia, dear,
sit down and, uh, don't be alarmed.
What's happened?
Well, I'm afraid there's
a telegram for you.
Oh.
[Exclaims]
Oh, how lovely.
[Seagulls cawing]
I only realize now
how terribly I've missed
you all these months.
And I you. God, I've missed you.
come on, tell me all the gossip.
Oh, let's see.
Johnny Gore-Barker has run
off with Bunty Robinson.
- No.
- Yeah.
He can't have.
She looks like the back of a bus.
Oh, I don't think Johnny Gore-Barker
knows what a bus is, front or back.
Everyone's talking about this new girl,
- but of course you know that.
- What new girl?
The one who's to be in your next play.
Her name's Avice Crichton,
something like that.
Michael says she's to
be the new Julia Lambert.
Yes, yes, he wrote to me.
It was my idea. I'm delighted.
She's very pretty.
How madly generous of you.
(Charles) And London was
full of your mischief, Julia.
(Julia) Was it?
It sounds as if you
needed a hand to hold.
Are you through the worst?
I think my vanity
was more wounded than my heart.
I'm so sorry, Julia,
sorry that you've suffered.
I love you. I always have. Always will.
Charles, we're miles from home.
There's no one here who knows us.
Just... honey...
What?
don't let your vanity
be wounded again, um.
I'm not worth it.
There'd be no reason.
I love you
in-- in my own way.
Julia, we've always
known what that means.
You can't be in the
theatre and that naive.
I love you more than you can imagine.
But...
But what?
I play for the other side.
[Laughing] Charles.
Oh, darling.
[Seagulls cawing]
[Car honking]
[People chattering]
Hello.
(Julia) Oh, Grace.
I'm so happy you're with us!
Well, it's not much of a
part, but it is the west end.
Hello, dear.
[All chattering]
Hello, Michael,
I'd like to introduce
our distinguished author,
Mr. Walter Gibbs.
Oh, I can't tell you
how proud I am that you're on "Nowadays".
How sweet of you.
But you've given me a monstrous
speech at the end of the play.
I hope I can learn it.
You remember miss Crichton.
Miss Lambert. Oh, how could I forget.
She's playing Sybil.
Miss Lambert, I just
want you to know--
Have you seen Tom recently?
Uh, once or twice.
Miss Lambert, I just want you to know
I'm going to give my all in this part.
I'll give it my absolute all.
Now, now, you mustn't
be a little spendthrift.
All right, everybody, we'll start.
(Woman) Yeah.
So, if you'll find a chair.
"Oh, Millicent,
"then I asked if he could help me.
"I asked if he would give
me a letter to the bank.
"He lifted the towel.
"His nose was bright red
and his eyes were streaming.
"He looked awful. He said:
[Nasalized] 'I'm afraid I
have a nasty cold in my nose.'"
[All laughing]
Good.
"I hope you didn't catch it from him.
you can't afford a cold
with so much to do."
Go on.
"Then he sneezed.
"I don't think I've ever
heard such a sneeze, Millicent.
[Inaudible miming]
(Avice) "It began with a
monstrous intake of breath.
"Wait, wait. I'll show you.
[Avice inhaling]
[Avice gasping]
[Sneezes]
[All laughing]
"I said, 'bless you.'
"And he said, 'I won't say thank you
[Mimicking] 'as it's meant
to bring misfortune.'"
"We should have seen through him.
"Then it would never have happened.
"But nowadays
"we're only interested in appearances.
And he did have the most
beautiful appearance."
Uh, mumbo-jumbo. Bad
luck to say the last line.
[All clapping]
(Michael) Right, well, I think
we should call it a morning.
All right?
Couldn't be better.
Good reading.
Pleased with the company?
You've cast it splendidly.
The girl's clever, isn't she?
Yes, isn't she?
- Well, give my love to Roger.
- Ta.
[Door closing]
I wouldn't say this to your face,
so I'll say it to your
back. [Mirror squeaking]
I've missed you.
And I've missed you, Evie.
I did the usual things.
I saw the sights. Worked
hard at my Italian.
And went to the opera a good deal.
Have you made up your mind
what you're going to do yet?
I want to stop living
in an atmosphere of make-believe.
That's your world, not mine.
And it stifles me.
What do you mean?
Once, when I was a kid,
I was standing in the
wings watching you on-stage.
It must've been a pretty moving scene
because I couldn't stop blubbing.
You moved to the side of the stage
near where I was standing
and you turned your back on
the audience, and you said,
in your ordinary voice:
"What the bloody hell the
electrician thought he was doing
with the bright lights."
And then in the same breath,
with a great cry of anguish
you just went on with the scene.
That was acting.
If I-- if I truly felt
all the emotions I was representing,
I'd be a wreck.
You have a performance for everyone.
For the servants, for
daddy, for everybody.
And I don't think you really exist.
Roger!
Once you told me something.
I don't remember exactly what,
but the exact same night
you said the same line on the stage.
Even the things you say are second hand.
All I want is for you to be happy.
You should talk this
over with your father.
Mmm, daddy's worse than you are.
But he only acts one part, thank God,
and that's the
handsomest man in England.
Then talk it over with
someone of your own age, then.
Tom, for instance.
Tom?
I thought you liked him.
No, I didn't like him at all.
You've dropped him, haven't you?
I...
I suppose I have, more or less.
Good. He wasn't worthy of you.
Roger, do you think I'm getting old?
No, not you.
Mmm, Tom's little tart's
in your play, I hear.
By the way,
she's having a fling with daddy.
[Nasalized] "How's
your cousin Millicent?"
and I said you were well.
He wanted to
know-- Michael,
I'm not happy
sitting beside her on the bench.
After all, it's miss Crichton's scene,
I think I'm too dominant here.
Well, move if you want to, but where?
There, on the stool, with
my back to the audience.
All I am is a feed in this scene
and it-- it
feels wrong
to be on equal footing
with miss Crichton.
I don't mind, really, miss Lambert.
No, no, no, no,
I'm uncomfortable. It feels ungenerous.
Michael, what if I'm discovered there
when the scene starts?
(Julia) I could sit facing the swing.
Then I don't have to move.
I can stay here
right until miss Crichton's exit.
(Julia) to thunderous
applause, I've no doubt. Hmm?
Well, I'm-- I'm quite
happy to try it.
Go from the top.
[Singing]
(Julia) How was your
interview with sir Philip?
[Laughs]
Oh!
It was like a scene out of dickens.
[Gasps] He had
the most dread--
You see? It's much better
with me here, isn't it?
Well, yes, it is,
as long as you don't mind being
stuck down there for 10 minutes.
Mind? Why should I mind? I suggested it.
(Stagehand) Lower. Lower.
That's right.
[Singing]
[Exclaims]
It was like a scene out of dickens.
[Gasps]
He had the most dreadful cold.
(Avice) So I said,
"Should I come back another time?
And he said:
[Laughs]
[Nasalized] "No, no, no, no, no, no."
[All chattering]
(Michael) Thank you,
and then give me all
the light you've got.
Can't do comedy in the dark.
Dolly, darling.
(Dolly) How's it all going?
Splendid. How was--
how was France?
Splendid. How's Julia?
Splendid. And the new girl?
- We're ready, Mr. Gosselyn.
- Thank you, Mr. Turnbull.
Dolly, have a seat.
(Turnbull) Thank you, uh, miss Lambert,
Mr. Dexter, miss Crichton on the stage.
(Turnbull) Hold the banging.
(Julia) Michael.
I say, that's awfully plain, Julia.
Precisely. But I want it for 2 reasons.
Firstly, it's awfully
good for the quick change,
just hooks up the back.
Second, I simply don't want in any way
to distract from miss Crichton.
(Michael) All right. Happy, Archie?
Trousers need shortening a bit,
but that's all.
And miss Crichton?
I don't think it fits her properly.
Especially at the waist.
And she's got such a pretty figure,
I think it needs to come
in at least half an inch.
I don't like it.
Julia's being far too angelic.
["Bei mir bist du schon" by
Andrews Sisters playing]
# Of all the boys I've
known, and I've known some
# until I first met you I was lonesome
# and when you came in sight, dear
# my heart grew light and this
old world seemed new to me
# you're really swell I have to admit
# you deserve expressions
that really fit you. #
' "Nowadays" from J. L.'
and the date. Very nice.
Here's the list. Can
you wrap each separately
and have them sent round to the theatre
no later than 5:00 this evening?
Of course, miss Lambert.
I'm so looking forward
to seeing the play.
(Salesman) It will
make a beautiful gift.
Yeah.
T- O-M.
Julia.
Are you getting engaged to Avice?
Oh, this. Oh, no. No,
it's a first-night gift.
She doesn't want to get engaged.
Wants her freedom.
Doesn't want anything to
interfere with her career.
Her what?
Oh, yes, I-- I
see what you mean.
I'm going to be there tonight.
Michael's given me a box.
(Salesman) Will that be all, sir?
Yes.
Tom, how about giving me tea?
At your place. For old times' sake.
Why not?
- Give Avice this.
- Hmm?
It may bring her luck.
[Door closing]
[People chattering]
[Car honking]
(Chamberlain) I have in my
hand, this piece of paper
signed by me, Herr
Hitler, and Benito Macaroni
in Munich.
It is for peace in our time.
However, if there is a war,
then their majesties, the king and queen
and their 2 lovely daughters,
Elizabeth and Margaret rose
and me and the entire cabinet
will set sail immediately for Canada!
You will stay here!
[Laughs]
Break a leg.
(Michael) you're going
to be a sensation.
Terribly sorry.
[Laughing]
[All laughing]
Same from me, Julia.
And you're coming to the
party tonight, aren't you?
Of course, wouldn't
miss it. Thank you both.
Yes, thank you. Thank you.
Yes.
You don't have a whisky handy?
No, no, no, not here. I've
got all that set up in the bar.
Darling, we'll see you later.
Dolly, I'll do the other dressing
rooms and I'll see you in the foyer.
Uh, bring our distinguished
author with you, will you?
(Dolly) Yes, of course.
(Gibbs) Are-- are
we leaving?
Half an hour, miss Lambert.
[Both exclaiming]
So-- so-- so sorry.
[Laughing]
(Call boy) hello, Mr. Dexter.
[Knocking on door]
(Michael) It's me.
[Door closes]
[Knocking]
(Call boy) Half an hour
please, miss Crichton.
Oh, Michael.
Thank you for everything, Michael.
Here's your first-night present.
I'm putting you under contract.
[Gasping]
Michael. here it is.
Sign on the front.
Here you are.
Oh, thank you.
[People chattering]
Good evening, Mrs. De Vries.
[All chattering]
Good evening, Roger.
Charles.
Aunt Dolly.
Sweetheart, don't call me aunty.
Um, we should be going in.
Oh, yes.
I'm nervous. I'm going to get a drink.
It's that way. It's that way.
Join us upstairs. Got your ticket?
[Audience chattering]
(Michael) The first stage, come on.
(Usher) Sir.
(Michael) Thank you.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
[Door thudding]
(Julia) He did have the
most beautiful appearance.
[Audience applauding]
No, no, no, no, no, no. no, no, no.
No, that one, you silly cow. Quickly.
What are you up to?
[Objects thudding]
Well, give it.
[Audience applauding]
[Applause stops]
[Avice singing]
How was your interview with sir Philip?
[Exclaiming]
It was like a scene out of dickens.
[Gasps]
He had the most dreadful cold.
He was in-- in
bed, inhaling.
So I--
so I said,
"Should I come back another time?"
And he said:
[Julia laughing]
(Avice) "No, no."
[Audience laughing]
(Julia) I used to do that as a child.
I was very prone to colds.
In my nose. I sneezed a good deal.
[Inhaling]
[Sneezes]
[Audience laughing]
I was always inhaling
over steaming water and camphorated oil.
Oh, Millicent.
Then I asked if he could help me.
[Julia sneezes]
(Avice) I asked if he would give me
a letter to the bank.
He lifted the towel.
His nose was bright red
and his eyes were streaming.
He looked awful. he said:
[Nasalized] "I'm afraid I
have a nasty cold in my nose."
You're lying to me, Sybil.
You're not putting on that cold
because you've caught it
from sir Philip, haven't you?
Who wrote this balls?
(Julia) Was it because
you snuggled up beside him?
Was it because he made a pass at you?
[Avice exclaims]
Tell me the truth, Sybil.
[Audience laughing]
[Exhales]
He sneezed.
Oh.
I don't think
I've ever heard such
a sneeze, Millicent.
It began with a monstrous
intake of breath.
Wait, wait. I'll show you.
[Deep inhaling]
[Sneezes]
I said...
[Clears throat]
Oh, my God.
(Prompter) "Bless you."
[Audience giggling] "Bless you."
I said, "Bless you."
And he said, "I won't say thank you
as it's meant to bring misfortune."
[Julia mimicking Avice]
Misfortune, indeed.
[Audience laughing]
(Julia) No, now I get it!
Now I understand!
You're dilly-dallying with
sir Philip and young Ben.
[Laughs] No wonder you caught a cold.
Shame on you, Sybil.
Which is it to be?
The old man or the young boy?
[Gasps]
(Julia) Silly question, I suppose.
I know which one I'd choose.
[Audience laughing]
No, no, no, no, don't you go.
Stay exactly where you are.
I haven't finished with you.
Not remotely.
I want to know.
Did he make a pass at you
or did you make a pass at him?
I'm talking about the old man now,
not the young boy.
My God, this is complicated!
[Exclaims]
[Audience laughing]
[All applauding]
God!
God, God.
(Julia) Oh, no, no, don't cry.
[nasalized] It'll only
make you more miserable!
[Audience laughs]
I'll tell you what I
think happened. Huh?
Sir Philip got a little fresh with you,
didn't he?
And you, you, you, you couldn't resist.
It's rather difficult to get fresh
when you have a cold.
What did he say?
[Quavering] "Please, please,
make an old man happy."
[All laughing]
Naughty, Sybil, very naughty.
Trying to have sir Philip on the side.
And I've always found
it very uncomfortable
on the side.
(Julia) I think we should
punish him, don't you?
Or you.
[Sobbing]
Perhaps we should punish you.
But how? That's the question: how?
Hmm?
I know. We'll tell Ben.
[Giggling]
Oh, don't pretend you've
forgotten him. Ben.
B-E-N.
(Julia) Oh, dear, have I upset you?
Never mind, Sybil.
Just remember all's fair in war and...
[Sobbing]
War and...
Ph, hell, the word escapes me.
[Audience applauding]
(Audience) Bravo! Bravo!
(Man) Bravo!
You're a monster.
A wonderful, glorious monster.
It was great! You were superb!
Sweetheart.
- A real tour de force.
- Yes.
[Julia laughing]
Don't change a word.
Keep it just like that.
God, I hope-- I hope I
can remember what I said.
[Julia laughing]
[Michael exclaims]
You're so naughty.
That's why you love me.
Yes.
[Screaming]
That cow!
She is vile, disgusting, cruel.
She is a double-dyed bitch!
We have a hit, Tom. A
palpable hit, my boy.
I want to leave.
I never want to act again.
Don't be so silly, you were wonderful.
Absolutely superb.
And now you're under contract.
It's clear the play's
going to run and run.
So you'll have the opportunity
to hone your performance.
Just think, 8 shows a week for a year,
playing opposite Julia Lambert.
It'll be an experience
you'll never forget.
Just have a great time, have fun.
[Wheezing]
[Shrieking] No! no!
[All chattering]
You're still the greatest
actress in England.
I'm going now. See you at the party.
And try not to be late.
It's going to be simply heavenly.
I'll be there.
Splendid. Oh, darling.
Magnificent. Absolutely wonderful.
# They asked me how I knew
# my true love was true... #
(Antoine) Champagne,
mademoiselle Lambert?
No. Beer. A pint.
Everyone here is talking about
how wonderful you were tonight.
Ah, thank you.
# ...cannot be denied
# they said someday you'll find
# all who love are blind #
Your only reality is the theatre.
Anything else, the outside world,
what civilians call the real world,
is nothing but fantasy.
And I bloody well
won't let you forget it.
Rubbish.
Are you expecting a guest?
Shall I place another plate?
No, thank you, Antoine.
I've decided not to go
to the first-night party.
I want to dine alone tonight.
Quite alone.
# Yet today
# my love has flown away
# I am without
# my love.
# Now laughing friends deride
# tears I cannot hide
# so I smile and say
# when a lovely flame dies
# smoke gets in your eyes.
# So I chaffed them
# and I gaily laughed to think
# they could doubt my love.
# Yet today
# my love has flown away
# I am without
# my love
# now laughing friends deride
# tears I cannot hide
# so I smile and say
# when a lovely flame dies
# smoke gets in your eyes. #
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org