Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
What?!
I didn't say anything.
I know,
but what were you thinking?
Well...
I used to hear about
these dock workers.
They would get welded up
in these kind of places.
And then... they were
never heard from again.
Wally?
You are so fucking
out-of-bounds with that shit!
Let's keep moving.
Forward trim tank,
it looks like.
Better drive some wedges.
Yeah.
So anything I say...
stays here --
this side of the hull.
Yeah. Yeah.
There were survivors
from the sinking.
- Brice and Loomis even, uh...
even tried to fish a few out,
but... Winters had other ideas,
and, uh...
he ordered a gunnery party
topside.
Well, three of us had a problem
with machine-gunning
those men right in the water,
I mean,
even if they were German.
There was an argument.
It got kind of heated.
Well, why didn't you tell us?!
I guess, uh...
I guess we were trying
to protect him --
felt Winters was
a pretty good C.O.,
even if he could be a tough
son of a bitch sometimes.
For his reputation --
you know, his family's sake.
Yeah, yeah, okay, but...
I still don't see
how he hit his head.
Slippery metal.
Bad footing.
Accidents happen, right?
Where the hell did
that come from?!
Near or aft?
Crew, sound off!
Get them out of there!
Get them out!
O'Dell!
Sound off, O'Dell!
-- Oh!
-- Sir!
Fuck, was that you?
The light!
We gotta get him out.
Come on, guys.
- How are we gonna...
Did you see that?
What happened, guys?! Come on!
What happened out there?!
-- Talk to me.
-- Don't touch me.
Did you fix it?
Which one of you boys
was screaming out there?
-- Are we a man down?
-- Don't touch me!
-- Are we a man down?!
-- Shut up!
Who was screaming?!
Come on, grow some dicks
and shut up!
Now, where is Mr. O--
Coors -- where's Coors?
You tell me that's him.
That's gotta be Coors.
He's still alive, right?
Sir...
that is the one person
I can guarantee it's not.
Don't touch me.
Don't touch me!
-- Don't! Don't!
-- Hey, easy.
Easy, Stumbo.
Easy, easy.
-- Easy, easy.
-- Was that a "B"...
dash, dot, dot, dot?
I didn't hear a "B."
Dot, dash -- "A" --
thought I heard an "A."
No, that's not morse.
It's just some shit
got caught up on the bow planes.
Now it's smacking up against --
"C" -- you hear a "C"?
Dash, dot, dash, dot --
definitely a "C."
It's hull sounds.
You guys are getting lathered up
about hull sounds.
Now, would somebody please tell
us what happened to Mr. Coors?
"Back" -- B-A-C-K.
He's back.
And where'd you get
the "K" from?
Dash, dot, dash --
while you were talking.
Hey, champ, you can stay
the hell out of this.
-- And the rest of you...
-- Enough, already, enough!
In the wardroom, 5 minutes.
Keep your mouths shut
till we debrief.
Did you finish the job?
Yes, sir, absolutely.
Right, Wally? Wally?
Oh, yeah, I'm finished.
All right, so, look,
if the weather is good,
we surface tonight,
we recharge the batteries.
We pour on the diesel,
keep pushing for the barn.
Our barn?
Mr. Brice, southern English
port's gonna be
more than two days away.
Two days away, Mr. Brice!
Kingsley here is a navigational
officer. He knows the way.
I know all the ports,
the depths,
where the submarine nets are,
the mine fields.
Yeah, and have
the R.A.F. bomb us
because they mistake us
for a hostile boat -- okay.
There are safety corridors
that we can use --
Considered and rejected,
thank you.
Mr. Brice, both our periscopes
are down, our sonar is gone.
We are blind and nearly deaf.
Our men are in a bad way,
and now we've lost
two of our senior officers.
Welcome to the war, O'Dell.
This has nothing to do
with the war.
Just how much longer
can we not say
what we're all thinking?
No one wants to be the first?
Fine. Allow me.
This submarine is haun--
When I want your opinion,
Miss Page, I'll give it to you.
I am not one of your men that
you can just dismiss, Mr. Brice!
I don't believe
we're alone down here,
and I know some of you think
the same way.
Unless we find
a safe harbor soon,
we're all going to end up like
your friend Mr. Coors.
The loss of Lieutenant Coors
is unfortunate.
It fails to affect our plans.
Attention all hands --
it's daylight now.
I expect to surface... at 1900,
recharge the batteries,
and proceed on base course
back to Connecticut.
- That is all.
You're 10 seconds away
from finding out
what the penalty is
for mutiny at sea,
'cause that's how long
it's gonna take me
to open the armory
and reload that sidearm.
Now, do either of you
care to say anything else
that might further agitate
this crew or me?
Mr. O'Dell?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
We just knock the nose around
a little bit,
we're back on base,
so make it 2-8-5.
Make it 2-8-5 true.
2-8-5 true, sir.
Heading home, boys.
Sound good?
-- Yes, sir.
-- Sounds good, sir.
Hey, you're oversteering.
Mind your rudder.
She's getting
some resistance, sir.
Chief of boat to control.
Chief of boat to control room.
All right, belay that.
Belay that.
I said belay that!
-- Oh!
Rudder at midship, sir.
Um, some...
kind of hydraulic failure.
Oh, Christ.
Must have overshot
our heading by --
170 degrees.
Oh, good. A gun.
Yeah, I needed a gun.
I'll put that
with the prizes.
Okay, I got feathers, crosses,
and strip-show icons...
Rudder malfunction.
When we tried to shut down
the props, no dice.
Wouldn't respond.
We're on a runaway boat,
fellas.
Now, can any of you top that?
Well...
I had a strange thought.
Take a number.
Yeah, but this one's
real creep-show stuff.
What if, when we took on
that kraut ship...
...we didn't sink 'em?
What if... they sank us?
Oh, that's a good twist.
I don't get it.
Might explain how that
dead kraut talked to Stumbo.
I don't get it.
And the controls --
that they froze up.
No, they -- they rusted up.
That's because we're at the --
the bottom of the ocean.
Flooded out.
Of course, I'm not sure what all
that pounding was about.
Those are rescue divers...
pounding on the hull.
Only it's too late.
Shit, I get it.
Hydrogen from the batteries...
CO2, ozone
from the electrical shorts --
that's what we're breathing
right now.
Like those deep-sea divers
that don't get enough oxygen --
head starts playing tricks
on 'em.
We got mechanical problems,
that's all, okay?
We always got
mechanical problems.
Now, please...
will you pinch this shit off?
-- Unless...
-- Oh...
It happened
during the depth charging.
Remember that one?
Rolled right down our deck.
So exactly how far
from England are we?
Can I ask why you're asking?
No.
Right.
Uh, what's our heading?
0-9-5.
Right. Uh...
May I ask why you're asking?
Just in case the boat
can't make it back home...
for whatever reason.
What do you suggest
we do about it, chief?
Come on.
Enough of the guessing games.
-- Pressure blinding the shafts.
-- No, I don't think that's it.
Just lay it out for us, chief.
What about the I.M.O. pumps?
I.M.O. pumps check out.
I don't think it's that either.
The rudder has a dedicated line
from here to the stern.
If we tap into there
somewhere aft,
I think we should regain
our steering.
But where are you gonna tap in?
That's the thing.
The line goes right through
the battery room.
That's a little dicey, isn't it,
without venting first?
Just threading up
new hydraulics, no welding.
Well, where are we at, anyway?
13 percent down.
-- 13 percent hydrogen?
-- Keep your voice down.
Look, I don't know any other
way to regain control --
Fuck if I know.
All right, but you gotta
make sure you're sealed off,
'cause we don't want a repeat
of the Hindenburg here.
Let's keep this quiet.
As if it's a bloody
mechanical problem.
Fore door sealed.
After door sealed.
What's happened here, hmm?
What is this?
Go to the galley.
Get a cup of coffee.
Oh, no, I'm fine, sir.
Really.
You're falling asleep, champ.
-- I'll watch your bubble.
-- Yes, sir.
Lieutenant, a word?
-- Not now.
-- No, Mr. Loomis.
We need to speak right now.
That is a whale, right?
What else would it be?
Come on.
Let's get that rudder working.
Now, maybe this is
just a coincidence.
I know Lieutenant Coors
wasn't too sure
about the last star fix.
But it sure seems like
we're going
right back to where
we sunk that German ship.
Clear the compartment.
Everybody, give us 5 minutes.
Go!
All right.
We're almost all set.
Just repressurizing the line,
see if we can't put the brakes
on this little joyride.
I'll reset the bus.
Shit!
Hey, guys,
we lost power up here.
Shut that goddamn door
before I shut it
with your goddamn face!
What are you saying, O'Dell?
It's not a coincidence?
Somebody put us on this course?
I'm just asking a question.
Let me ask one.
Where were you
when the rudder went over?
Huh?
This course heads back
to England,
and I've noticed you've had
a hard-on for anything English.
So where were you, O'Dell?
Back of the boat... messing with
the rudder assembly?
Or did you get some motormac --
That is the craziest thing
I have ever heard!
Not as crazy
as what you're saying!
I'm tired
of this hoodoo horseshit!
It is not
what you think it is!
It is not even remotely
fucking possible!
Okay?!
After room,
get the chief to pick up.
Hoag!
Maneuvering room, respond.
Anybody, contact control.
- Mr. Loomis, where's our crew?
It's warm.
Loomis...
I-I, um...
Go ahead.
I'm gonna change up my scrub.
Keep looking.
Gotta be somebody.
All right.
All right, chief.
-- We found you.
-- Don't...
Can you feel anything --
your legs, your toes,
anything at all?
-- Don't...
-- Come on.
try to stop me.
You're gonna pull through.
Especially...
- you.
Time to go.
Battery's still working.
What happened?
Sparks... the hydrogen.
Everybody... everybody's...
Loomis...
Loomis?
-- Sir! Sir!
-- Get out of my way!
-- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
-- Get the fuck off me!
Loomis!
- Loom--
He's here.
Did he even have...
air?
Not a bloody foot.
Come on, Stumbo.
Keep trying.
We gotta release that air.
Come on. One more.
Come on, Stumbo.
It's like it's welded.
All I know is what Coors
told me.
And apparently...
Captain Winters wanted to shoot
the German survivors.
Mr. Brice and Mr. Loomis
and Mr. -- Mr. Coors...
wanted to help.
Apparently Captain Winters
lost the argument.
Well, that's interesting.
But it's not what I heard...
from Mr. Brice.
Lieutenant?
Are you sure he came back here?
Looking for me?
I, uh...
Just... reporting, sir,
that the heating is down.
And, uh...
the bow's levers are stuck.
Stumbo's working on it
right now.
And that we show
90 pounds of compressed air
still left in the system,
and I... wasn't sure
if you wanted to use that
when we tried to surface
or use it now
so we can breathe.
Shinola.
Sir?
Running out of shinola, too.
We also wanted to ask you
about Captain Winters --
whether there was anything
you could tell us
about what happened that night
that might help us
to understand --
Don't pretend you don't know.
Just don't pretend anymore.
Well, wasn't that awkward?
Maybe Hoag was right.
Maybe we already bought it.
If not the depth charge,
then... the hydrogen.
If not the hydrogen, then...
maybe the cold.
And if not that,
then we got a big evil spirit
batting cleanup.
-- Jesus Christ.
-- Come on, Stumbo.
There should only be
so many ways a guy can die.
Listen to me.
CO2 hangs low.
It starts from the floor up,
and I need you right now...
-- No, no.
-- to get up on your feet.
-- Maybe I just need to...
-- Stumbo. Stumbo!
-- Let me try.
-- We already bought it.
Come on, Stumbo. Head up.
-- Over and over...
-- I need you to sit up.
-- over and over again.
-- Look at me.
Now look at me.
Look at me.
- Good.
Feel that?
Well, you're alive, then,
aren't you?
You fuckin'...
-- Stumbo...
-- Whoa, hey, hey, hey! Hey!
-- Take it easy! Hey!
-- Relax, man!
Stumbo!
Isn't there a winch or a pulley
or maybe a come-along
in a bowsman's locker?
-- Yeah.
-- Can't we use that?
You know what he's
talking about, Stumbo?
-- Yeah.
-- Well, come on.
Come -- we need it. Come on.
Show -- show me, Stumbo.
We've got to get it.
Okay, come on. Come on.
So, tell me
why three officers
would conspire to kill
their captain
and cover it up.
That's what you're thinking,
isn't it?
What if I am?
I can see I'm not the only one.
Loomis was up
for a major citation.
And Brice was ready
for his own command.
He was from a naval family.
He went to Annapolis.
Coors had this beautiful girl
waiting for him back in Boston
that he was always
talking about, Claire.
These guys had everything
to live for.
By that reasoning...
they had everything to lose.
Are we missing somebody?
Wallace...
Wallace?
- No!
-- No! No!
-- Shh!
-- No-o-o!
-- It's just us.
It's just... us.
- Now, listen...
We're running out of plays
in the playbook.
Do you have... any idea
why the boat is going back
or how we can get control
of it?
I've been checking the
literature on this subject.
And the thing we know
about maledictions is --
Maledictions?
Look it up.
Maledictions don't issue
from Heaven or Hell
but from some unresolved place
in between.
In fact, there's a great --
Wallace...
we're running out of air.
Suffice to say...
the malediction needs
satisfaction
in order to escape
its netherworld.
And if you had to guess...
what would satisfy
our malediction?
Old Man Winters never
got a chance
to go down with the ship,
did he?
Wallace, leave yours here.
We gotta dig up
some more light.
Okay, listen, uh...
Just... Just promise me
you'll stay on your feet, okay?
"Don't pretend..."
"Don't pretend
you don't... know."
2230 hours: Sight target
believed to be
German sub tender.
Winters orders flank speed
to close target
and gain a firing angle.
2315: Loomis checks
target profile against I.D. log,
matching it to target, and
I personally verify the match.
2320: Single torpedo fired
from number-4 tube.
Heard the strike, followed by
collapsing bulkheads.
2330 hours: To confirm sinking
of German ship,
four officers go topside --
Commander Winters,
myself, Lieutenant Loomis,
and Lieutenant
J.G. Stephen Coors.
"Many bodies in the water."
"Ship burning on the horizon."
What are you doing in here?
Go.
A German ship...
of the type
Brice said you sunk.
My ship --
the Fort James hospital ship.
So what you're saying is...
that the submarine
Kingsley saw...
the one
he thought was German...
Wasn't.
So it was an accident?
Not when he left us
in the water to die.
Not when he heard the cries
for help in English.
You actually believe
that Captain Winters would
just leave --
Help! Help me!
No.
Captain Winters wanted to
pick up the survivors.
That means...
Help!
Who mis-I.D.'d the ship?
Who had everything to lose?
Either the battery has
finally crapped out, or...
Or maybe we're here.
Come on.
Let's get some air going.
- All right.
Come on, everybody, pull!
Come on!
Come on! Pull!
Fuck me. This is it.
-- Oh!
-- God, I hate being right.
- Pull!
Kingsley.
Oh, Jesus, God,
we're going down.
It's going up.
It's going up!
- Okay. All right.
Wallace, see if you can work the
radar, get a sweep of the area.
Stumbo, see if you can crack
this hatch. Use a crowbar.
Drain the tower.
See if we can get out that way.
If not, we gotta go out
the forward --
Oh, God.
Hey, fellas...
we have contact.
On SJ radar --
4,000 yards, starboard beam.
It's the same one?
It's the same kraut ship?
-- Are we being choosy?
-- All right.
Uh, Wallace, raise the antenna.
Issue a radio challenge
on the Ariel-6.
Get the ship I.D.'d
as of right now.
Well done, Mr. O'Dell.
But I'm feeling
much better now.
You were saying?
We have a contact.
That may be an opportunity.
An opportunity?
To abandon ship.
Well, I don't know that
that's a friendly out there.
Well, neither do I.
But it seems better to scuttle
now and take our chances
with a surface vessel,
even if it is German.
Scuttle and tell Connecticut
what?
We sunk one of their
finest fleet submarines
because we lost a few men
carrying out our mission?
A few men, sir?
Contact at 2,500 yards.
Might cross the stern.
We'll wait... right here.
Wallace... no matter what
Mr. Brice says,
I want you to go
to the radio shack
and establish a voice contact
with that ship immediately.
You are not the skipper
of this ship, Mr. O'Dell!
And neither are you, sir!
Rain squall.
With a little luck, they
won't see us in all this...
- weather.
Here!
Please!
We're over here!
Help, please!
Help!
On your starboard side!
It's really not safe up here,
Miss Page.
We're going below now!
Aah!
Bury everybody
and bury the truth --
is that it, Brice?!
Like this.
This is how I go.
If that's your plan...
get on with it,
you fucking coward!
Stumbo, man the ports.
Get ready to scuttle this boat!
Just leave!
They'll blame it on a U-boat!
Just get out of here!
They'll never fuckin' know!
Any more advice for me, champ?
500 yards and closing!
Looks like we're definitely
gonna lose some paint
on this one, sir!
I kept looking for some way
just...
just to... take it back,
to make it end right --
some way without
dishonoring Winters.
I was gonna wear this uniform
back to port.
Now...
What should I do, Miss Page?
You give me the light
so that I can signal for help.
I don't...
God, I don't know!
I just figured out
why he didn't kill me, too.
He didn't have to.
Aah!
Hey! Over here!
Come back!
Come back.
Well, you weren't the first
woman that ever slapped me,
and you won't be the last.
But that was a good thing
you done for me back there.
Well done, Miss Page.
Well done, Mr. Stumbo.
Dead but not buried, I see.
Pardon me?
Your vessel.
So, what would you say
if you had to explain it all?
Does seem rather unlikely now,
doesn't it?
Have you thought that...
that maybe
when Captain Winters died,
he just... died, and that was it?
And the rest...
I don't know.
You say whatever
you have to say, ensign.
I'll always believe we were
brought back here for a reason.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org