Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
-Five, six, seven, eight, nine...
-10, 11, 12, 13!
I love you, guys.
You're doing so good, Bella.
Bring your hands up through first,
and open.
How am I gonna learn if you're not here?
Just do what I did.
You can learn from the videos.
You learned from Mom.
The tapes help. Trust me.
Dad, I'm leaving.
She's going to
the American Ballet Academy.
I'm gonna miss you so much.
Me, too. I love you.
I love you, too.
Excuse me, which floor is the audition on?
Following pointe auditions,
we'll continue with adagio,
then we'll pair you for the pas de deux.
I'm gonna need you into two lines.
Boys in one, girls in the other,
starting with the tallest to the shortest
and remember who you're paired with.
At best, I can take six girls and six boys.
The final decisions
will be posted this afternoon.
We have very limited space
for a very limited number of students.
As you know, this is the finest
academy in the country. We value talent,
-discipline, respect...
-And a love of dance.
Also a good thing.
And on a very good day,
we even value Cooper Nielson.
Pease welcome one of our
esteemed judges and instructors.
You have 15 minutes to warm up.
A love of dance.
I was moved nearly to tears.
Hey, we're creating artists, not robots.
And besides, I'm here to bring some life
back in this place. Remember?
You're here because your company
ran out of funding and you needed the job.
Hey, it's a give and take situation.
So, nothing's changed, huh?
I give and you take and take and take.
First position. Demi-plie.
Tendu front.
Demi-plie. Tendu back.
Demi-plie. Tendu. Stay on your standing leg,
don't hang on the bar.
-Miss...
-Von Stroh.
-Richard's daughter?
-Yes, sir.
Nice port de bras. Watch your alignment.
-Miss?
-Parker. Kate Parker.
Billy's daughter.
Now the other side.
Classy.
-Kate Parker? How you doing?
-Good.
All right, you're gonna be dancing
here with Mr. Webb.
-Nice to meet you.
-You, too.
Okay, sorry. Let's stop.
One more time from the top.
Ready?
And five, six, seven, eight...
That is perfection.
Look at those legs.
One of the best dancers, I hear.
Really? What else you know about her?
Her?
Look at him.
Hey, nice form.
"Nice form"?
-What is she thinking?
-She's already a whale.
We have one last spot to fill for a girl.
Here are the top contenders.
Suzanne Von Stroh, Kate Parker, Lily Green.
I just don't think that Green
has the feet or the body.
Agreed. I vote to lose Parker, too.
-I disagree.
-Suzanne Von Stroh has perfect form.
Perfectly boring.
She's a classic prima ballerina.
I see a lot of potential there.
Yeah, potential funding.
Well, unless we figure out a way
to turn this whole thing into a reality show,
academies need funding.
You should know that better than anyone.
The Parker girl's got something, Jonathan.
She's got passion.
-She's too raw.
-She'll refine her skills in the classroom.
She had plenty of time to refine her skills.
And she's going to need a scholarship.
Look, Suzanne has excellent technique
and she might be a superior dancer,
but how many Suzannes do we have here?
What'll she bring to the table?
How about Sleeping Beauty?
How about Swan Lake?
How about Giselle?
How about Twyla Tharp?
Bob Fosse? Jerome Robbins?
Can't we do something
that's from the last 50 years?
Tommy.
Excuse me, sorry.
Yes!
Hey, Bell.
Yep. Nailed it. Just like you said I would.
I'd like an application.
We're filled up for the semester.
We require at least one year
of formal training.
-I just need a chance to...
-I need a current resume,
three references and a DVD reel
including an adagio, pirouette exercises
and a classic variation.
You. Run towards me, take off on the left,
right leg in arabesque.
Well done. Suzanne, right?
Suzanne Von Stroh.
Okay. Listen up.
Dancing is not only about
focus, precision and perfection.
Dancing is about connections.
Connecting with your audience,
connecting with your partners.
So, over the next several classes,
you'll be dancing with different partners
until we find the right match,
one that has connection.
Not only a physical connection,
but also an emotional one.
All right? Okay, let's go. Pair off.
-Hi.
-Hey, what's up?
Mr. Nielson. I'm Kate Parker.
-I auditioned for you the other day.
-I remember.
I was hoping I could speak with you
about my audition.
Miss Parker, this is the best school
in the country.
-We're extremely selective.
-I know.
There are other schools.
But I've been dreaming of studying here
since I was a kid.
-I understand that.
-I'll work harder than anyone else.
I mean, if there's something I did
or something I screwed up, I'll fix it.
Miss Parker, I'm sorry.
I really am. To be honest with you,
I think you've got a lot of talent.
But there's nothing I can do.
Miss Parker. Tell me something.
Why do you think
you didn't get into this place?
Was it because you're not as good
as the other girls that auditioned?
Apparently I'm not.
If you really believe that,
then maybe you should go back
to wherever it is you came from.
Tough first day?
Oh, crap.
The Foundry?
I doubt it's your scene.
A girl like you.
A girl like me?
It's just different than this place. That's all.
-It's loud and sweaty.
-And that's your scene?
Yeah.
What's that look for?
Sorry I bugged you. I'll see you at class.
Where's my car?
Hey.
Hey!
I think you guys have got my car.
It's a '88 Jimmy.
-Michigan plates, right?
-Yeah.
-Three hundred bucks. Cash only.
-Three hundred bucks?
-You're kidding, right?
-Do I look like Eddie Murphy to you?
-Can I have a beer? Thank you very much.
-Here you go, Tommy.
Hey.
-I'm Kate, by the way.
-I'm Tommy.
Let me guess. Cosmo.
Vodka tonic?
A ballerina who drinks beer?
That's awesome.
Can I get another one, please?
Sure.
Cheers!
-Wanna grab a seat?
-Yeah.
-This place is pretty dope, huh?
-It's not really my scene, remember?
Is that your girlfriend?
Lexi? No.
She's dating my buddy Sal.
He owns this place.
She seems to be
pretty interested in you right now.
I think they're just sizing you up.
See what you're all about.
Maybe I should show them.
Hey!
-Dance?
-Yeah!
You know her?
Apparently not.
-That was pretty sick.
-Thanks.
I don't think there are too many girls
at the Academy that can do that.
Yeah, well...
-Maybe that's why I didn't get in.
-For real?
I don't know what brought you here,
but I'm glad you came.
Kate, my buddy Sal.
So, where did you learn
how to dance like that?
I could use some of that energy
around here. Can you start tomorrow?
Seriously? Doing what?
We're a new club. You do it all.
-You in?
-Yeah, I'm in.
All right.
Be here at 6:00.
One, two, three, on her leg. Five, six,
seven, eight. Nice and sharp.
Two, three, four. Okay. Okay.
Allison. Switch with Suzanne.
-One more time from the top.
-Hey there.
Let's hustle. Six. Ready.
Seven, eight, and a one,
two, three.
-The second lift was really good.
-It was pretty good, huh?
Hey. You two get comfortable.
I'm gonna pair you together this semester.
-Nice.
-Tommy, come with me.
See you.
Why don't you try your solo for me?
-Okay. Yeah.
-Yeah? Give it a shot.
Okay. Stop. Stop. Not bad.
You know what?
Maybe it'll help if you just take a look at it.
Okay.
And.
Wow!
I can tell you one thing for sure,
it doesn't get any easier.
-No, man. That was amazing.
-All right. Thanks.
I know you haven't been dancing
as long as the other guys. That's fine.
I'm willing to put in the work.
-I know you are.
-Okay.
But to get to the top,
you're gonna have to find something
that you may not be able
to learn in the classroom.
-Like what?
-Like passion. Fire.
Fire?
You wanna be a guy
that brings the crowd to its feet.
Yes, I do.
How do I do that, exactly?
Look outside the box.
Find that special someone
or something that gets you excited,
-that truly inspires you.
-Like Suzanne?
Hey, if Suzanne's it, great.
She's a good dancer,
which is why I paired you together.
But?
But if she's not, get creative.
That's what an artist does.
And when you find it, make it your own.
All right?
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
-Hey.
Do you want something?
Actually, I've got a favor to ask you.
You got me a job and now I owe you favors?
No.
I've seen you move
and I was hoping for some help.
You've seen me move?
What kind of help do you need?
I need help with pas de deux.
-Pas de deux?
-Yeah. Couples dancing.
I know what pas de deux is. I'm not dumb.
Okay, well, I suck at it and I need some help.
-Well, that's why you're at the ABA.
-Yeah, I know.
They'll give me steps,
but they can't give me what I really need.
And what do you really need?
-Fire.
-What?
My instructor told me to find fire.
What? And I look like two sticks
you can rub together?
Kind of.
-Good luck with that one.
-Forget I asked.
Hey, Tommy. If you still need my help,
I need some extra cash.
-Okay. Where?
-What about here?
-It's got to be off campus.
-I have keys to the club.
I don't know about the club either.
Well, that's about all I got.
No wait, hold up. The club will work.
-Hey.
-What's up?
-Not much. Just trying to warm up.
-Are you all stretched? And ready to go?
-Yeah. Good to go.
Liar. Okay.
Let's see what you got.
Wait, wait, wait.
Keep your hands here, on my waist.
Almost. Let's try that again.
Better. How did you get into this anyway?
You don't really strike me as a dancer.
They taught us ballet at hockey camp.
Helps strengthen our ankles
and work on balance.
So, you're a hockey player.
-All-State, two years in a row.
-And now you're a ballerina.
-It's "ballerano."
-Okay, let's try a lift.
One, two, three.
Yeah. So, after my third concussion,
I figured I'd try something else.
And badminton never came up?
An instructor pulled me aside
and promised me
hot girls wrapping their legs and arms
around me.
Look, if that's what you're here for,
go find somebody else.
-I'm not here to screw around.
-Okay, I'm glad we settled that.
And what about you?
You don't seem like the typical ballerina.
I don't puke after every meal
and have a giant stick up my ass,
if that's what you mean.
But full of grace.
-That was better.
-A little.
Okay, we have got to get serious here.
Dancing is about trust. And connecting.
Okay. We can connect any way you want.
Calm down. Let's try some different music.
You've got to get out of your head.
Stop thinking and just try to feel it.
All right.
Close your eyes.
-Hey, Sal.
-What's up, guys?
Just thought you might want to grab a beer
or shoot the shit.
It's perfect.
Thank you. That's all for today. Nice work.
Tommy. Suzanne.
I don't know what you've been doing,
but you look good.
-Really good.
-Thank you.
I think I'm gonna talk to Jonathan
about the two of you.
See if he can recommend you
to Monica Strauss for The Glass Slipper,
Great. Thanks.
-Yes!
-That's awesome.
What's The Glass Slipper?
Tommy, Monica Strauss is the cutting edge
ballet producer right now.
And she's an ABA alum.
She's doing The Glass Slipper
for Broadway.
It's kind of a reinvention of Cinderella,
This is huge. Oh my God!
We've got to celebrate.
I'll take us to China Grill and we can have...
I haven't had Chinese food in forever and...
Actually, I can't. I already have plans.
Well.
Aren't you the busy one?
Can I get a rain check?
Definitely.
Hey, what's up?
We should go out tonight.
Find out where Tommy's going.
This place is pretty nice.
Whatever! I watched that game.
You didn't even play.
-Tommy.
-Suzanne. Hi.
Hi.
What are you guys doing here?
We make it downtown every once in a while.
So, how about some drinks?
Drinks. Yeah, definitely. Come on.
So, what can I get you guys?
-I'll have a Cosmo.
-Make that two.
Vodka tonic.
Should have guessed.
Can I get two Cosmos
and a vodka tonic, please?
You got it.
Who's that? Your fan club?
She looks familiar.
No way.
Hey.
You were at the ABA auditions, weren't you?
I haven't seen you in class, though.
I guess it wasn't a good fit, huh?
Well, at least you have this to fall back on.
Here's your drinks, ladies.
-Here you go.
-Cheers!
Thanks, Tommy.
What are you doing?
Dance with me.
That's awesome. See you later.
Oh, no, no, no.
Can I help?
Don't you have curfew?
You're such a rebel.
You want to grab dinner tomorrow night?
I'm working.
Okay, lunch.
-Working.
-Okay, now you're just lying.
This place doesn't even open till 8:00.
Actually, I got another gig.
A catering job with Lexi.
Okay, well, when's your next night off?
Everybody takes a night off.
Cooper says I'm improving.
-You are.
-Thanks to you.
Now I just have to convince them
I'm good enough
to be recommended to Monica Strauss.
What?
You know all The Glass Slipper
posters around town?
Monica's casting that show.
I think you need to lower your shoulders
and lift your chest.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Try it like that.
One compliment and now you're the expert?
Last I checked,
neither of us fell into that category.
Yeah, but you hired me. I didn't hire you.
Maybe you should.
All right, Baryshnikov.
Let's get back to reality.
I'll show you Baryshnikov. Come on.
You did it again.
Did what?
If you're gonna audition for next semester,
you could use a little extra practice.
I think once was enough. Again.
-Are you kidding me?
-Again.
One rejection and you're gonna quit?
I've had plenty more than one,
thank you very much.
Okay, but you realize
that's what this business is about.
Rejection after rejection after rejection.
Thanks for the tip.
You're welcome.
If you don't have thick skin
and serious drive, you can just give up now.
Serious drive?
You woke up one morning
and decided to be a dancer
and six months later,
you're at the best school in the country.
You have no idea what it's like
to work your entire life for something,
and then have no control
over whether you get it or not.
What are you talking about?
Do you know how long I played hockey?
Do you know how many times I got
smashed into the boards,
hoping some scout might find me?
Yeah. And you walked away.
I didn't walk away. I made a choice.
I didn't let somebody else make it for me.
What do you care, anyway?
Because you're good. You're so good.
You know,
I thought I was good.
I was so sure I just had that
thing that everyone always talks about.
So I packed my bags, came to New York
and I gave it everything I had.
And guess what?
No one else sees it.
My father didn't see it.
Jonathan Reeves doesn't see it.
If no one else sees it,
you got to think, maybe it's just not there.
Hey.
Why don't you take tonight off?
What?
We can get by without you for a night.
You work too hard.
I work too hard? What kind of crap is that?
Hey.
I just thought you could use a night off.
-Sal, if there's something I did or some...
-Kate!
Put down the glass
and come back tomorrow.
-Fine.
-All right.
Hey.
So, are you free for dinner?
What did you tell Sal?
I told him an ambush was my only hope
of taking you out.
Can I at least go home and change first?
-Yeah. Of course. Come on.
-Okay.
-Reservation for two under Anderson.
-Right this way.
So, what are you gonna get?
Fettuccine's pretty banging.
So, do you have any brothers or sisters?
Yeah, actually. I have a little sister who's 13.
Is she as cute as you?
She's way cuter than me.
That's hard to believe.
What about you? Do you have any siblings?
Yeah. I have a little brother.
-Really? Does he dance?
-No. He's a hockey player.
Do you want him to dance?
Not really.
Why?
I don't know. It was kind of difficult for me,
turning from a hockey player
to a ballet dancer who wears tights.
Yeah, but that's what you love.
I mean, if you really love it,
you shouldn't care what other people think.
You're right.
I bet your hockey friends
loved it when you started dancing.
-I don't know.
-Come on, all those big macho guys.
They'd give you crap if you did
anything in tights.
I guess I'm lucky.
Have they ever seen you perform?
No.
Well, they should. I mean, you're really...
I'm really what?
-You're all right.
-All right?
-You're not so bad yourself.
-Really?
Yeah, you know,
for a girl with no formal training.
Hey!
It's okay. You've got something better.
-What's that?
-Fire.
Not that again.
Yeah, you know,
like two sticks I wanna rub together.
Shut up.
What are you doing? Tommy?
Just close your eyes.
Close your eyes!
-That looks good.
-It does, huh?
-Are you gonna give me some?
-No.
Is that your sister?
-Yeah, it's Bella.
-She must miss you.
I miss her.
I bet she's proud of you.
I haven't really done
anything to be proud of.
What do you mean?
Well, I mean, all I wanted to do
by coming out here was
to show her she could do
anything she wants.
And I couldn't do it.
Just trying is all she needs to see.
Look, I got to get back to the dorm.
Hey, Bell, it's me.
How are you?
I miss you, too.
-Hey.
It's nice weather, huh?
It's freezing.
-Let's get some lunch.
-Okay.
So I was thinking.
You were right.
I do need some help.
So, does this mean you're reapplying?
That's awesome.
Seven, eight. And a one, and a two,
and a three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, lift. One, two.
Stay on your foot.
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
-What is this? Payback?
-I'm just getting started.
Other side. Six, seven, eight.
And a one, two, three, four, five, six...
All right, let's begin.
-Okay.
-First position.
Demi-plie.
And grand plie.
And straighten. You've got to
straighten the back of your legs.
They are straight.
Try it again.
Hey.
Oh, shit!
Prepare. Seven, eight.
And one, two, three.
Keep reaching with the toes.
Good.
Six, reach, seven, eight and one,
and lift.
Tommy, take your place, please. Quickly.
Let's go again, from the top.
Seven and eight and one,
two, three. Nice.
Tommy and Suzanne,
you're a second behind.
And reach.
Nice. And lift.
Oh, fuck.
-I'm sorry. Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
Rest.
What happened?
I don't know. My arm slipped and...
Just make sure that
you keep your center strong.
Okay, people, one more time
from the top. Quickly.
And seven and eight. And reach, two, three.
Sorry again.
I guess my arm wasn't positioned properly.
Your arm? Give me a break, Tommy.
-Excuse me?
-Do I look stupid to you?
-Suzanne, my arm slipped. It happens.
-It's hardly the problem.
There's a reason we have curfew.
-What are you talking...
-This is my career, okay?
So I don't give a shit what you're doing
until all hours of the night,
until it affects my chances
of getting what I want.
-This has nothing to do with you and me.
-It doesn't?
No.
We are partners, for better or worse.
So you screw up,
then you make me look bad.
And I will not let you blow my shot
for some late night partying.
What's up, ladies?
Tommy, Mr. Reeves would like
to see you in his office.
Mr. Anderson.
How are classes going?
Pretty good, sir. Thank you.
Cooper tells me you and Suzanne Von Stroh
are working very well together.
That's good to hear.
That is very good for you.
What do you mean?
Suzanne Von Stroh's family
is extremely powerful.
Her father singlehandedly supports
a substantial portion of this academy.
Really?
And she enjoys
dancing with you very much.
-That's mutual.
-Good.
Because I think the two of you
could go very far together.
Thank you.
You're welcome. So don't blow it.
Sir?
Which part of "don't blow it"
didn't you understand?
Tommy, I want to see you succeed here.
But you got to stay focused.
No distractions.
I understand.
Good.
Thank you. Next, please.
That's Monica Strauss.
Tommy Anderson and Suzanne Von Stroh.
-You were really strong in there.
-Thanks.
Hey, listen.
My father's hosting a function tomorrow
and a lot of his friends
from the arts community will be there.
Cool. Have a good time.
Actually, I was hoping
you might wanna come.
Tomorrow... I don't know if I can.
Monica Strauss will be there.
I'm sorry.
I let it slip that you've been coming in late,
but you have a lot of potential
and I just don't want to see you blow it.
Let me make it up to you.
-You don't have to...
-Tommy,
you know how hard this business is.
I'm just...
I'm giving you an opportunity
to make it easier.
Besides, it'll be fun.
-What time does it start?
-My daddy's driver will pick us up at 6:00.
I wish we could just go back to bed
and sleep all day.
I can't. I told Lexi I'd cover for her.
Plus, you have that school thing, anyway.
Yeah. I know.
They weren't lying.
That place owns you 24/7.
What's this thing for, anyway?
Just another rich guy
trying to impress his friends.
-Daddy.
-Darling.
This is Thomas Anderson.
He's my partner at the Academy.
Tommy, please. Nice to meet you, sir.
Thank you for having me.
Thank you, young man.
Suzanne tells me she couldn't have asked
for a better partner.
I feel the same way, sir.
-Hello.
-Monica.
Tommy and Suzanne are quite the pair.
Very promising. Perhaps they'll show you
what they've been doing.
I insist.
Of course, Daddy. I'll be right back.
So, are you a hockey fan?
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is my pleasure to introduce
my lovely daughter Suzanne
and her escort, Thomas Anderson.
They'll be dancing
Tchaikovsky's Black Swan Pas de Deux,
-What are you...
-It's okay. Just come on.
Tommy...
-Kate, stop.
-Something for school?
-Look, it's not what you think.
-What would I be thinking?
She's my dance partner.
Her family's well-connected.
She wanted me to come
so I could meet some important people.
-So you're using her.
-No.
Just like you've been using me.
Jesus, Kate, I'm not using you.
So, what? I'm dress rehearsal
-and she's opening night?
-Kate, please.
Save it, Tommy.
Hey.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
What's up with the crowd tonight?
We're dying here.
Sometimes you're on, sometimes not.
We're definitely not.
Hey. Remember that first night
when you came in
and got the crowd moving?
-Yeah.
-Would it kill you to do it again?
-It might.
-You can handle it. You're tough.
-What?
-That's what!
You really know
how to work a crowd. Cooper.
-We met before.
-I know who you are.
I'd like to see some of that energy
back at the Academy.
-I hear you're reapplying.
-Who told you that?
I have my sources. I think you should.
We'll see.
So. How are you with a partner?
I can hold my own.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Come on.
Is that all you've got?
I'll speak to you outside.
You were right. The girl can get down.
Yeah.
Thanks for the heads-up.
Well worth the trip.
-What the hell was that?
-Dancing.
There's nothing going on
between me and Suzanne.
She kissed me in front of a roomful
of people, what could I have done?
So I guess now we're even.
Kate, why are you doing this?
We have something.
-Ready?
-Yeah.
Damn, you were hot in there,
and I see a lot of dance.
You really think so?
Of course, it might be those beautiful eyes.
Or that smile.
But yeah. It's also your dancing.
Tommy was right about you.
Tommy?
Yeah. He asked me to come down here
and check you out.
I'll be sure to thank him tomorrow.
You know,
I don't think this is such a good idea.
Sure it is.
I mean, if you're worried about this
-affecting your audition or something...
-No.
Look, it's just not right.
Okay.
I guess I'll see you tomorrow
at the audition, then.
Congratulations.
The four of you are here today
because Monica would like each of you
to audition tomorrow for The Glass Slipper,
There's absolutely no guarantee
that any of you will be hired.
However, you will have a private audition
before the open call.
And Cooper and I will make every free
moment we have until then available to you.
Make sure you get there
with plenty of time to warm up.
Right now, I've got to go and run
next semester's Academy auditions.
All right. All right, line up for lunges, ladies.
Come on, let's go.
-Looks like your friend's a no-show.
-Yeah. Looks like it.
-That's such a pretty scarf.
-Thank you.
So, you're friends with Monica, right?
I guess she didn't want it that bad after all.
-You ready?
-Yeah.
Hi.
-What was that all about?
-Nothing.
So, we should rehearse
for the auditions tomorrow.
-Does that sound good?
-Definitely.
Nice. And I was thinking
maybe we could go to dinner,
'cause you know, you gave me a rain check.
-Do you remember that?
-Yeah.
I know I said Chinese food,
but I really don't want Chinese food,
because it makes me bloated, but maybe
we should do the cafe across the street
from the Academy on 64th.
They have the best thin-crust pizza.
-I'll catch up with you in a minute.
-Okay. Well...
What about our rehearsal, Tommy?
Is your name Bella?
Yeah.
Are you looking for your sister?
-She dances here.
-Is her name Kate Parker?
Yeah.
I'm Tommy. I'm good friends with her.
We practice a lot together.
Is she here?
I don't think she has class today,
but I can help you find her.
What are you doing here?
She showed up at the Academy.
I told her you didn't have class today.
Thank you.
You should have called.
How did you get here?
-The bus. I missed you.
-I missed you, too.
Hey, do you want to check out
my new apartment?
Look, about the other night
with me and Cooper.
It's none of my business.
-Nothing happened.
-Nothing.
You don't believe me, do you?
No, I believe you.
Look, you should go in there.
She's been dying to see you.
Tommy.
I just wanted her to believe it could happen.
Yeah, but you got to believe it.
-So, do you dance here?
-Yeah, every night.
And there's really good music
and lots of lights and people and... Yeah.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
Hey, does she have ID?
That's my sister, Bella.
Do I have to hire her, too?
It's just for the night
and then we're gonna go back home.
-Home?
-Detroit.
Has this got something to do
with that crap with Tommy?
It's about a lot of things.
-What's going on?
-We're leaving.
But I just got here.
And you said I could come stay with you.
Bella, please.
Let me just watch one class.
I promise I'll be quiet.
-I just want to see.
-You can't.
-Why not?
-Because I'm not taking classes.
I didn't get into the Academy.
I auditioned.
But I didn't get in.
Look, there's a bus to Detroit in two hours.
We're gonna be on it and I'm gonna
get my old job back and that'll be that.
Two hours? Tommy said you were gonna...
Look, Bella, I don't wanna hear it, okay?
Just pack your stuff.
-Cab's here.
-Do you have your shoes?
-Yep.
-Good boy.
-Where'd you get that?
-Tommy gave it to me.
He says it's an open call
and that you should go.
-Yeah, well, he's wrong.
-But you'd be perfect.
-No, I wouldn't.
-Why not?
Bell, do you have any idea how many people
are auditioning for this thing?
You're so good.
Back home in the parking lot, I'm good.
But this is just so different.
Would you stop looking at me like that?
Do you really think I can do this?
Excuse me, I'm here for the open call.
-Back of the line.
-Thank you.
-We're gonna miss our bus.
-There's another one tomorrow.
Well, look at you, smarty pants.
Tommy!
-Hey.
-What are you doing?
-Come on, come here.
Kate, Tommy's here.
Hey.
You changed your mind?
-All right. Well, kill it.
-I will.
-See you later.
-See you.
Next 20. Girls only.
This is it.
I'm with her.
Thank you all for coming,
At present, we're looking to cast
Cinderella and her stepsisters,
My associate Nick Hoffman
will take you through the routines,
Hello, ladies. Follow me from the top.
Glissade, jete, glissade, jete, tombe,
coupe, pas de bourree, brise.
Got that? Here we go. Seven and...
Glissade, jete, glissade, jete, tombe,
coupe, pas de bourree, brise.
Let's go again. From fifth.
Glissade, jete...
Turn out that supporting leg.
Let's try it again. Six, seven and...
Glissade, jete, glissade, jete, tombe,
coupe, pas de bourree, brise.
Good. Let's see it all together.
From the top, five, six, seven and...
Glissade, jete, glissade, jete, tombe,
coupe, pas de bourree, brise.
Good, switch lines.
Five, six, seven and...
Glissade... Come on, jump higher.
Come on! Up! Up! Good.
343, 91, 752, 288,
could you please step forward,
We see potential in each of you and would
like to see you back here this afternoon,
Don't forget to bring
a current picture and resume,
And plenty of energy. You'll need it.
39, flawless technique.
Number 39, Miss von Stroh,
please step forward,
It's nice to see you,
your resume is extremely impressive,
Thank you.
you've been taking dance class
since you were 3 years old,
My father saw potential,
so he put me in classes right away.
-And it shows, Thank you, Miss von Stroh,
-Thank you.
752, what's your name, please?
Kate. Kate Parker.
We seem to be missing your resume,
Miss Parker,
It's because I don't have one.
I'm sorry?
I don't have one.
I mean, I could give you
a separate sheet of paper
with my name and measurements on it,
but I figure you already have that.
What about your schooling? your teachers?
I haven't had any worth mentioning
since I was 1 2.
I just taped productions off TV
and mimicked what I saw.
I have one of you dancing Giselle,
And why is it
you never took formal classes?
My dad figured his money
was better spent on lottery tickets.
And that's why you started with the tapes,
You do what you got to do, you know?
-yeah, We do know,
-Thank you, Miss Parker, That's admirable,
Okay, we need 825, 752, 758, 39,,,
Harris will be dancing
the pas de deux with Allison,
Thank you,
Thomas,
-Or is it Tommy?
-It's Tommy. Thank you.
I'd like to see you
with Suzanne von Stroh, please,
Let's see what they do.
We did it.
Hey. Kate.
I just wanted to tell you I really thought
that I deserved this part, but you are just...
-Suzanne.
-No, it's okay.
But you earned it.
You were beautiful. Good job.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Bella.
-Good job, man.
-Thanks, bro.
-What did you think?
-You were so good. I love the ending.
-Do you want to take my flowers?
-Yeah. They're so pretty.
-Mr. Reeves.
-You were excellent. Both of you.
Thank you, sir.
-Tommy.
-Hey, man.
I remember you auditioned for me,
Miss Parker.
I did. Last semester.
I'm sorry it didn't work out.
We could have learned a lot from each other.
Thank you, Mr. Reeves.
Next time someone like me tells you
you're not what they're looking for,
remember this moment.
'Cause whatever you had to do
to get through that and end up here
is exactly what it takes
to be great.
You should be very proud of yourself.
I'd better go give your dad a call
and tell him he's already won the lottery.
-Good night.
-Bye.
I'm so proud of you.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org