Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Humans.
- Andrew,
- Yes?
It would mean so much to me
if you would be an usher at my wedding.
One is unfamiliar with this term.
How does one "ush"?
You help people to their seats.
You wear a tuxedo.
- One would wear clothing?
- Yes.
One has never been asked
to wear clothing.
- It would be an honor.
- Great.
- One still is all thumbs.
Installed what?
Um, an alarm.
If you try to enter Andrew's brain
while you're making this repair,
the police will be alerted.
Also, you should probably know that-
if you actually injure
Andrew's brain or positronic
pathways in anyway,
my lawyer, the good Mr. Feingold,
will be happy to sue you.
He will sue you
for the lost value of Andrew's
income until the end of time.
Well, I think
we understand each other.
Good.
Sir, one more item of business.
As long is one is in the shop,
can you do work on one's face?
One wishes to have
more expression.
One has thoughts and feelings
that presently do not show.
You want your thoughts and
feelings to show on your face?
Yes, like the contempt
that you are showing me right now.
Well, we have done
some experimentation.
We are able to give robots
superficial responses...
which mimic human expression.
- One has read that there have
been NDR upgrades.
- Yes, yes.
We've worked up
a dozen experimental models
with expression capabilities,
sleeker body types.
We ran some market surveys and decided
not to go ahead with the line.
- Why not?
- Negative consumer reaction.
There's a growing fear that
robots will continue to make...
the human work force obsolete.
Andrew has worked
for me for over 1 5 years.
There's no danger of anyone
losing their job to him.
Surely there's no concern
performing these modifications
on an old-style robot.
True.
But procedures like that would
be prohibitively expensive.
It is understood that you will attempt
to rivet one.
- Screw, Andrew.
- Really? How much?
That is roughly
one's monthly salary.
It's more than I make
in a year.
Hmm, not bad for-
- What did you call him
last time we were here?
- Household appliance.
- Household appliance?
- Household appliance, yes.
May the peace of the Lord
be with you always.
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride now.
It is my pleasure to present
Mr. and Mrs. Frank Charney.
What?
Good evening, sir.
Magnificent night.
You look very sharp
this evening, Andrew.
Thank you, sir.
- It was quite challenging
for the tailor.
May one continue
wearing clothing?
- If it suits you.
- Are you serious?
As always.
Well, I suppose so.
We'll have to find you some
other stuff, though.
You can't wear tails all the time.
Really? How sad.
- Sit down, Andrew, please.
- Thank you, sir.
- It was a wonderful wedding,
wasn't it?
- Oh, yes, sir.
And, if one may say,
you are a spectacular dancer.
- Well, that's very kind.
- Not at all, sir. It's the truth.
Did you record the day?
Every second, sir,
is in one's memory bank.
Well, let's watch it,
shall we?
Sir?
Is everything all right?
Um-
They've both gone now,
Andrew.
Well, things change.
Things always change.
People move on.
It's as it should be.
But, uh,
what I realized today is
that, uh,
I'll never stop missing them.
Sir?
One is still here.
And one is glad of that,
Andrew. Thank you.
- Good night, sir.
- Good night, Andrew.
Lloyd! Come here.
What did I tell you
about throwing sand at people?
What did I tell you?
Now apologize to Andrew.
I will not apologize to it.
- Him.
- It.
- Lloyd.
- Sorry.
One understands why
some animals eat their young.
I'm so sorry, Andrew.
Are you all right?
You seem very quiet.
How does one
obtain freedom?
- Y-You wish to leave us?
- Not at all, Little Miss.
One merely wishes
to be declared free.
But why? You have
so much freedom here.
Until one is ordered
to do something.
Andrew, it's been years
since anyone's given you an order.
But you may still request one
to perform tasks.
Well, we ask all the time,
but it's a request, not an order.
But that's not enough
for you, is it?
One has studied your history.
Terrible wars have been fought
where millions have died...
for one idea:
freedom.
And it seems that something that means
so much to so many people...
would be worth having.
Sir, would now be a good time
to speak with you?
It's always a good time,
Andrew. You know that.
It is everything
in one's bank account.
Why would you want to give me-
To purchase one's freedom.
One wants to be free.
One would, of course,
still obey the three laws...
and serve you
in exactly the same fashion.
The only thing that would change
would be the form.
One would no longer be
your property.
You want to leave.
That's what this is about, isn't it?
Not at all, sir.
You are one's family.
Then why ask for this?
Oh, I see.
You're in on this.
We've talked about it, yes.
So you ordered him to do it,
and he obeyed.
No. He makes
his own decisions.
- But you put the idea in his head.
- No, Father, you did.
You've given him hundreds
of books to read.
It was simply a matter of time
before he became intrigued
by the idea of freedom.
He learns and grows
all the time,
and it's because of you
and Andrew's abilities...
that he's become every bit
as complex as we are.
Good morning, sir.
- You take your check back,
please, Andrew.
- Why, sir?
You are free now.
I must ask you
to leave this house.
But sir,
I don't wish to leave.
You wished for freedom,
you must accept the consequences.
- Then I will remove my belongings.
- Yes.
Where will you go?
I will look for
a residence nearby...
so that if you ever
need anything, sir-
That will not happen,
Andrew, thank you.
There's no need
to be close by.
- If you command me
not to do this, I will obey.
- I command nothing.
You're free.
Then- called or uncalled-
I am always at your service.
Andrew,
you've stopped referring
to yourself as "one."
A home of my own.
Andrew?
- Andrew?
- I'm inhere.
Little Miss.
Is something wrong?
He asked for you.
It's time.
- The robot's here.
- Andrew.
- Hello, Miss.
Sir.
- How are you, sir?
- Well, I'm dying, Andrew.
Otherwise I'm fine.
Wonderful to see you again.
I'm very happy to see you, Andrew.
It's been a long time.
Yes, it has, sir.
I wanted to-
I wanted to tell you...
that I was wrong.
You're never wrong, sir.
Then don't contradict me.
You were right
to want your freedom,
and I'm glad
that you have it.
Thank you, sir.
Andrew,
you were very good to us.
It was an honor
serving you, sir.
I want to seek out
my own kind.
In order to understand
my destiny,
I must know if there is
another like myself.
NorthAm Robotics will not
return my inquiries,
and now that you have
finally passed the bar, Lloyd,
I want you to sue them for
information of the whereabouts
offal NDR series robots,
if you don't mind.
The Freedom of Information Act
doesn't quite cover suits by robots.
- Not yet.
- Mother, I'm a very busy man.
I do not have time
to help...
it pursue
some ridiculous lawsuit.
Lloyd, sweetheart,
I do love you,
but sometimes I have to wonder
if you really are my child.
Well, that's mutation,
Mother.
The miracle of genetics is
I'm not you.
No, you've always been
more like your father.
So that's why
you divorced him.
Sorry.
Andrew, what would you do if I got
the information on these other NDRs?
I would seek them out,
each and every one.
So you'd be gone
for quite a long time.
Oh, yes.
Several years if not more,
if my calculations are
correct.
I'd love to help you.
Did he not breast-feed?
"Dear Little Miss,
my journey is nearing the end
of its tenth year,
and I still have not found
any robot that bears
any similarity to myself.
and I still have not found
any robot that bears
any similarity to myself.
I have thousands of miles to go,
hundreds of cities to visit,
so I have not given up hope.
Love, Andrew. "
Hello.
My last name is Martin.
Hey, get off the field.
"Dear Little Miss,
my journey is nearing its end.
I have exhausted all possibilities
save for one final ray of hope.
I've learned of an NDR robot
that has recently been rebuilt
back home in San Francisco. "
Take as many as you need.
Oh, then you should love them.
I'll be right back.
Take as many as you need.
- Thank you.
- You're quite welcome.
- Whoo
- What you want
Baby, I got it
- Whoo, whoo
- What you need
Do you know I got it
- Whoo, whoo
-All I'm askin'
-Is for a little respect
When you come home
-Just a little bit
- Hey, baby
when you get home
- Just a little bit
Just a little bit
- Mister
I ain't gonna do you wrong
while you're gone
-Ain't gonna do you wrong
if I don't wanna
- Whoo
- Whoo, whoo
- All I'm askin'
- Is for a little respect
when ya come home
- Just a little bit
- Baby, when you get home
Just a little bit
- Yeah
Hi.
- Is this yours?
- Oh.
Thank you.
I'm looking for Rupert Burns.
Oh, you've come
to the right place.
- Come in.
- Certainly have.
Huh.
- Do you have a name?
- Of course I do.
Galatea.
You have an amazing...
agility.
You were dancing
in the market.
- Did you like that?
- Very much.
Dancing is
the sportiest sport,
and we're so much better
at it than humans.
I can't believe
I finally found you.
When did you know?
- Know what?
- That you were unique.
Oh, I knew that right away.
Me too.
You and l-
we're the same.
We have personality!
Is your personality chip
turned on?
- Isn't yours?
- No.
Sucks to be you!
I think personality is
much more fun than intelligence,
don't you?
- Baby, baby, sweet baby
- I think so.
There's somethin'
that I've just got to say
Can I help you?
Your robot is just
a standard NDR, isn't she?
Yeah, I'm afraid so.
Why does she have
the ability to dance?
'Cause l, uh-
I put a modified skeletal chip
into her during a rebuild.
- How were you able
to do that modification?
- My father taught me.
He created the android unit
at NorthAm Robotics.
He's responsible for
the technology that allows you
to mimic human expression.
- What happened to him?
- Well, NorthAm laid him off
when they shut down the unit,
so he started this place,
and I took over when he died.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- He would have been
absolutely thrilled to meet you.
I-l-I'm Rupert Burns.
- It's a real honor.
- The honor is mine.
- Hey! You and l- we're the same!
- Let's get loco, robo!
Whoo-hoo!
- Shut her off or I will.
- Oh.
Okay.
Thank you.
Is this your father's work?
Yeah- Well, it's-
it's our work, you could say.
I haven't really been able
to restrain myself from continuing...
to tinker with the relentlessly
unfashionable android technology.
As a matter of fact,
I've actually gotten to a point...
where I can pretty much
exactly replicate the external
physical appearance...
of a human being.
- Remarkable.
- Thank you.
- Amazing!
- Yeah.
Unfortunately, nobody seems terribly
interested in funding my research.
- But-
- I am.
I will fund your research.
Yeah?
That'd be cool.
Thank you, darlin'. Okay.
Andrew, I want to make it
very clear:
This is an external physical
upgrade only in the strictest
sense of the word.
You'll feel nothing.
None of your internal mechanisms
will be changed.
You'll still be subject
to the parameters
of your positronic brain.
- Is that clear?
- Understood.
Okay, good. Now,
have you given any thought
whatsoever as to what age
you'd like to be?
Officially,
I am 62 years old.
- Let's take off 25 years.
What do ya say?
- Fifteen.
- Twenty. Good.
- Perfect.
Now, Andrew, believe it or not,
the secret to all this is actually...
- imperfection.
- Imperfection?
Yeah. Things like...
wrinkles, uh,
less-than-perfect teeth,
details like fading scars,
little pockmark-
Look at my nose.
See my nose?
- It's bulbous and slightly irregular?
- It is.
Well, I'm the only one
who's got my nose,
and that's what makes me, me.
We need to incorporate
these features into your design...
so that you can be
the only one of you.
That's what makes us unique,
is those imperfections.
I see.
Like the shape of your head.
- What about the shape of my head?
- It's huge.
Oh.
But lovely.
Thank you.
Oh.
Ah. Oh.
- What happened? What's going on?
What happened?
I saw the inner me.
- Is it ready?
- Okay.
Please, be careful.
Don't drop me.
- I'm being careful. Oh, my God!
Just relax,
relax, relax.
Why did you do that?
That wasn't very funny.
Just keepin' ya
on your toes.
- I don't have any toes.
- You do now.
I do.
And hands.
And fingers.
How do I look?
See for yourself.
Thank you.
- Beautiful.
-Sorry.
- Who are you?
Andrew.
Andrew?
You look wonderful,
even younger.
- How do you do that?
- Do-Do I know you?
Well, I know
I look different too.
- I've had an upgrade. Touch it.
- What?
- No, oh, no! No.
- Sorry, the face.
What's going on?
You leave her alone!
- Who are you?
- Andrew.
No. Andrew?
- Yes.
- But Andrew's a robot.
- Yes, I am.
Well, now, an android.
- He's had an upgrade.
- I know that.
- Oh!
- Hello.
Hello! It is you.
- You know him?
- Yes.
- You know me?
- Who are you? No?
- I'm Little Miss. Yes.
- That's Little Miss.
- No.
- No? No?
- No, that's Portia.
- Portia? Yes.
- Portia?
- Yes.
- Who's Portia?
- My granddaughter.
- Your granddaughter?
- Yes. Yes.
- Is this some kind of trick?
- No.
- You're Little Miss?
- Yes.
Why do you have to look
like her?
- There is and can be
only one Little Miss.
- Really?
- Yes!
- It's a genetic resemblance.
Sometimes it skips a generation.
- I don't care. I don't like it.
- I can see that.
But if you took a moment,
which I see you're not
inclined to do right now,
you'd realize Portia and I
are very different people.
- Why is she imitating you?
- What's so funny?
- You are.
I'm not trying
to be funny.
Things have certainly
changed around here.
That happens
after 20 years.
I have so much to tell you.
Come. Come with me.
It is you.
Yes.
Portia.
- Hello, my friend.
- Hello, Little Miss.
Whose daughter is she?
- Lloyd's.
- Oh. Now the rudeness makes sense.
Go.
Go home to your master.
You don't have a home,
do you?
I don't have food.
I don't eat.
Come in. We'll keep
each other company.
I know you don't like me.
Well, I don't like you either.
I just wanna make that clear.
- It couldn't be more clear
if you spat in my face.
- I can't.
I don't have
a mucous gland.
Would it be possible to have
a slightly longer conversation?
May my canine companion
enter also?
Thank you.
Is this your sculpture?
No, I'm restoring it.
I'm a preservation architect.
It's quite horrendous.
How ugly was it
before you restored it?
- Listen. First, you get mad
at me because of how I look.
- Mm-hmm.
Tonight you show up at my door,
announce that you don't like me,
and then you criticize my work.
Once again, I apologize
for telling the truth.
But it can't be helped.
It's my programming.
What is it exactly
that you want?
Family.
My last name is Martin,
I am so named because
your great-grandfather
and grandmother...
considered me to be
a member of your family.
Now, Sir is dead.
Little Miss is getting older.
You don't like me, but at least
you'll talk to me if I knock
on your door long enough.
- Is that a joke?
- No.
Would you like to hear a joke?
This Buddhist walks up
to a hot dog vendor and says,
" Make me one
with everything."
- Andrew, do you- do you have
any friends at all?
- No.
Only Woofy, who's very sweet,
but not very challenging
on a conversational level.
That is the extent
of his skills.
- So you want someone
to talk to?
- With.
- Even if that person doesn't like you?
- You can't have everything.
Is that right? Is it,
"You can have everything"?
Seems like some people do,
so I'm somewhat confused
on that level.
- Sit down. Let's talk.
- Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Hey there, handsome. Andrew,
could I get you anything to drink?
- Sorry, I have no stomach.
- Oh. Could I get something for him?
- He has a stomach. Yes.
- Do you think he's hungry?
- How is she?
- She's sleeping.
What happened?
She had a stroke.
Mm. There you are.
Little Miss.
Hmm.
She's gone?
It's cruel that you can cry
and I cannot.
Here is a terrible pain
I cannot express.
Will every human being
that I care for...
just... leave?
I'm afraid so.
That won't do.
Andrew, this is remarkably impressive.
You did this all by yourself?.
Yes. I downloaded every known
medical textbook into my memory.
I studied them. That's how I came up
with these drawings.
I know they're very primitive
and not entirely complete,
but that's why I need you
to fill in the mechanical gaps, Rupert.
This is another upgrade.
It's considerably more than an upgrade.
I mean, you're-
You're talking about
a profound transition...
from the mechanical
to the biological.
I realize that, and I believe
it is the ideal marriage of both fields.
Not only that, but this stuff
could cut both ways.
I don't think that any
existing prosthetic devices
or artificial organs...
hold a candle
to what you've designed here.
You could use these
in human beings as well.
Exactly.
Wow!
- What a piece of fecal matter.
- Shit.
- Excuse me?
- What a piece of shit.
I know that.
No, that's way you say
when you're frustrated.
You say "piece of shit."
- " Piece of shit"?
- Yes, but-but with feeling.
Oh. What a piece of shit.
- More.
- What a piece of shit!
- Good, very good.
- Thank you.
Now, are you aware
that what you've essentially
designed here...
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org