Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Minton, warden wants to see you.
Get up.
- Me?
- Now! Walk!
Put your hands behind your back.
- [Knocking on door]
- Come in.
Minton, I'm glad you could make it.
- You can take the cuffs off him.
- Sure you wanna do that, Boss?
I said take 'em off.
It's all right.
I already got 'em.
It's a matter of dislocating the wrists.
[Snaps]
[Cracks]
Ew! Ew, that is creepy!
- You can wait outside.
- [Shudders]
Have a seat.
Warden, if this is about me
fighting in the yard, it...
Cigar?
Thank you.
Brandy?
Sure.
You know, you wardens should complain.
'Cause in the movies,
they always make you look like assholes.
[Laughs] Well,
I don't plan on being a warden forever.
- Is that right?
- Tell me, Minton.
What do you think of this place?
It's OK, for a prison.
Not the prison. The land.
It's a nice sized property. Great views
of the foothills and city. Level grade.
I'm assuming there's
bedrock beneath us.
Easy access to downtown.
I see some nice development potential.
- Too bad you got a prison on it.
- Exactly.
You know, it's no accident
you came to Oaksburg.
I pulled a few strings
to get you here.
What made you wanna do that?
Come here.
Oaksburg Estates.
I'm a silent partner, so to speak,
with some private investors
who would like to develop this land
into timeshare condominiums.
I believe that's
your field of expertise.
- True.
- 'Course, all this is only possible
in the event the prison
ever closes down.
- Makes sense.
- You know, I'm in the prison business.
I know how to break a man's will,
crush his spirit.
But them real estate contracts,
those things put a real hurt on you.
That's where you come in.
- What's in it for me?
- How would you like to be out of here
in a year?
- But I've got a mandatory minimum.
- Wardens have great discretion
getting early parole, especially
to non-violent, first-time offenders.
- Prisons are crowded, you know.
- The system is corrupt.
Me likey.
But you gotta move the luxury units
closer to the lagoon.
That'll double rents.
Parking goes underground.
Wasting space. Eight extra units.
Whoever designed this is a moron.
- How will you get rid of the prison?
- Let me worry about that.
Tell me more about them parking spaces.
[Stan singing in Spanish]
You strapped?
He ain't gonna know what hit him,
nah mean?
Ah!
That's gonna scar, you psycho.
- Whoo!
- [Grunts]
You want that shiv, don't you?
You made that with a melted toothbrush
and a razorblade?
- That's very creative.
- Ah!
Look what I made
with three bars of soap and a shoelace.
[Chuckles] Cracker, please.
Hoo! Hoo! Hoo!
[High-pitched warbling]
Come on, race traitor.
- Ah!
- Ooh!
[High-pitched warbling]
Oh!
- [Neck cracks]
- Ha!
Hee-yah!
He's all yours.
This gonna be fun.
[All shouting]
Hey, Stan. What'd you do to Patterson?
I just roughed him up a little bit.
- Why?
- Somebody took a shiv to his ass.
They say he'll be shitting sideways
for a month. [laughs]
Now I know
what schadenfreude feels like.
- What?
- Schadenfreude.
It's German for when you feel good
because your enemy's anus is violated.
Oh.
You know you're getting that on me.
[Stan on phone] I'm doing great.
You guys are pussies.
That's terrific. Hey, listen, pal.
I need your help.
I can't get Mindy's lawyer
to return my call.
If we wanna go through
with this divorce,
you're going to have
to contact her personally.
Stan.
Yeah. I'll get right on that.
- How's the appeal coming?
- [Laughs]
Believe it or not, I'm looking
at the Madam Foreman right now.
- [Laughs]
- That's great.
[Stammering] I gotta go now.
You know, duty calls.
All right. Thanks, Lew.
I'll talk to you soon.
[Grunting, farting]
Ain't you Charlize Theron?
Oh, look what fell out there.
[Laughing] So I had them
exchange the beef for horse meat.
- Clever.
- That's Stan.
Minton, I'd like for you
to meet Mr Dang.
He's on the prison's board of governors.
They let Vietnamese mafia on
the prison board of governors?
Your finger tats.
[Laughs] Like you say, Stan,
the system is corrupt.
Mr Dang's family happens to be
my partners in Oaksburg Estates.
Oh, good, 'cause I was just
going over the contracts.
The language gets rather vague
on gross versus net liability.
I'm sure it's unintentional, but that
could screw you in the long run.
Could it? I'll have my lawyers
correct that immediately.
I got an excellent lawyer for that.
He specialises in it. Lew Popper.
Popper? I'll be sure to contact him.
[Laughs] Come on, Dang,
let's check out the floor show.
[Shouting]
It looks like the savages
are ready for the inspection.
[Gasque] Well, give me a few more weeks.
I'll even have 'em readier.
[Dang] I'm counting on that.
Would you like a strawberry?
- I grew them in my own garden.
- Thank you.
Minton? Strawberry?
No, I'm good.
[Gasque] Maybe I picked 'em
a little too soon.
I don't think that's it.
[Stan on phone] People
are scared shitless of me.
Very good, Stan.
Is there anyone there
who can challenge you?
Nah. I got it all under control.
What's the matter, Stan?
You sound... distant.
I don't know. It's just...
Don't you ever find yourself
feeling sorry for anybody?
You might as well ask me
if I feel sorry for the maggots
I grind into my morning coffee.
[Laughs] That's how I feel too.
Listen, I gotta go.
Make me proud, Stan.
[Woman] Come on, baby!
Do it to me!
- [Popper] Oh, yeah!
- [Woman] Are you using me?
- [Popper] No!
- [Woman] Don't you love me?
- [Popper] Yeah!
- [Woman] Show me!
- [Phone rings]
- [Shouting]
- Do you love me?
- Yeah. Hello. Hey!
Excuse me. Excuse me. Yeah.
Hi, Stan. Yeah.
I think I have good news.
- [Woman] Do you love me?
- Yeah. I think the... I think the...
The Madam Foreman is just one orgasm
away from giving you your appeal.
[Stan] That's great, Lew.
And gross.
Heard from Mindy or her attorney?
Uh, no.
But don't say I don't earn my money.
[Laughs]
Hi, fellas.
I don't believe I ordered Chinese.
I guess I could go
for a little pot-sticker.
[Shorts] Who are you writing to?
No one special.
You've been sitting there for a while
writing to no one special.
You know, Stan, I've been here for a
long time. I can handle a lot of things.
Like having to spend the rest
of my life in this shithole.
But there's one thing I do regret.
I could never make it work
with Miyoshi.
Oh, she was the only person
who ever loved me for me.
I was too pigheaded to realise it.
[Sighs] I'd give anything
to change the way I behaved.
How did you behave?
I killed her.
Oh.
Alcohol wasn't something that always
brought out the best in me, Stan.
[Stan] Dear Mindy, I've been
thinking a lot about you lately.
About us.
I realise now that you were right.
I was pigheaded and selfish.
Leaving me was probably
the best thing for you.
And I'm truly sorry.
I never should have hurt you.
I know now why you wanted
to have a baby with me.
It's just another way
for us to love each other
even more deeply.
I hope, someday,
you'll be able to forgive me.
Love always, Stan.
[The Master] Hey, baby.
Now, I know all of you want to get back
to your weightlifting and basketball
and masturbating, so I'm gonna
try to keep this short. All right?
I am throwing away all of these
violent video games and movies.
[All groaning]
Don't do that! No! Come on, man!
From now on, I want you guys
watching more wholesome entertainment.
And frankly, a lot of the rap music
you brothers listen to
- was too hateful towards women.
- [All laughing]
What is up with that?
You like women, right?
[All] Yeah!
Now, on the other hand,
the Mexicans are onto something
with mariachi and salsa music.
[Cheering]
It's positive, easy to dance to
and you never get tired of it.
- Shorts, give us a taste.
- Here we go.
[Salsa music plays]
[Man singing in Spanish]
[Cheering, whistling]
[Cheering]
Holy shit.
- All right. All right, all right.
- [Music stops]
That's Afro-Cuban. I asked
for mariachi. But you get the point.
All right? Now, lastly,
and most importantly,
from now on, there will
be no more rape at this prison.
- [All shouting]
- No, no!
That's right.
Anyone who rapes another inmate
- will have to answer to me.
- [Man] Boo!
[Stan] I will not be kind.
- Excuse me, Big Stan.
- Yes, Juanito.
Why you putting your nose
where it don't belong?
My men are aggressive and hard.
Sometimes they need a way to work off
that excess energy. What's it to you?
- OK. Well, first off, good question.
- Thank you.
What is it to me?
Well, frankly, I just don't like it.
And let me show you why.
Robbie, come up here.
You, Robbie the hippie.
Come up here.
[All whistling]
All right, all right. Robbie, how long
is your sentence here at Oaksburg?
- Five to ten.
- Five to ten years.
What exactly did you do
to earn that sentence?
- I sold marijuana.
- [Laughter]
- A shitload of marijuana.
- [Cheering]
Thanks, Robbie. Go sit down.
He sold marijuana.
He was a marijuana dealer.
I'm not here to argue about drug policy.
I don't think they're tough enough.
- [Protesting]
- Whatever.
Butjust because Robbie was guilty
of selling dope
doesn't mean he deserves to get raped
up the ass every day for ten years.
I just don't think that's fair.
- [Murmuring]
- Some of you are here
because you're habitual drunk drivers.
Some of you have a fondness for crack.
- [Laughing, murmuring]
- Some of you robbed a bank.
- I'm talking to you, Lee Otis.
- [Laughing]
But that doesn't mean you should
get raped. It's just not fair.
- Yes, Carnahan.
- What about guys convicted of rape?
- Can we rape them?
- [All] Yeah!
Rape the rapists.
Seems appropriate.
Punishment fitting the crime and all.
Go ahead.
- [Cheering]
- [Man] That's what I'm talkin' about.
- How about them child molesters?
- [All] Yeah!
Yeah, them too. Good point.
Anyone else?
[Cheering]
[Big Raymond] Big Stan!
- What about the counterfeiters?
- [All] What?
Counterfeiters? Big Raymond,
you're the only counterfeiter here.
[Man] Yeah!
Wait a minute.
Do you just want somebody to?
[All] Aw!
OK, here's another thing
we gotta clear up.
There's a difference
between homosexual sex and rape.
- Now, Big Raymond.
- Hm?
There's someone here
who wants to have sex with you.
- [Man] Not me!
- OK? How about it, anyone?
Yeah. Yeah.
[Laughter]
Tyler!
- Great!
- Man! [giggles]
You two have fun.
But wear protection.
- [Cheering]
- [Big Raymond] OK.
All right, grow up. Look, if you've got
a problem with that, then that's...
[farting, groaning]
Nurse!
[Farts]
Now, those two are about to have
consensual homosexual sex.
A beautiful, beautiful thing.
The total opposite of rape,
- which is not allowed.
- Except for rapists and molesters?
- We can still rape them.
- No, you can't.
- [All] What?
- I changed my mind.
Bad habit. Quit cold turkey.
- [All yelling]
- If you're not happy with it,
- you're welcome to fight me.
- [Groaning]
I didn't think so.
All right, you're dismissed.
Beat it.
- Good speech.
- You think?
- I should have opened with a joke.
- No, it was good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Sorry about the mariachi.
Let it go.
Hey, Big Stan.
Check out the lovebirds.
- One for you!
- [Giggles]
Mm! One for you.
Good for them.
I have something important to show you.
Let me eat, will you?
Hey, Big Stan.
- Can we talk?
- Make it quick.
I wanna thank you
for what you did out there.
- I didn't do anything...
- Don't say you didn't do it for me.
Because you did, didn't you?
- A little.
- Well, thanks.
- Yeah. Thanks, man.
- [Juanito] Julio!
Get back here!
What's up with you? [speaks Spanish]
Shut up!
[Speaking Spanish]
Hey, Big Stan.
I like what you said.
I wanna join your gang.
- I don't have a gang.
- Yes, you do.
OK, you're in.
[Man clears throat] Me too?
- Yeah, you too.
- [Giggling]
- All of you.
- Thanks.
- [Laughing]
- Yeah! Ow!
All right, can I eat now?
- [Big Raymond] Yes, you did!
- He's gotta eat.
I told you I had something important
to show you.
From Mindy.
She wants to see me.
[Laughs]
Hoo-hoo-hoo!
[# Los Ninos de Sara: La Cubanita]
[Shouting, laughing]
Shake hands.
Try to get along, huh?
[Speaking Spanish]
Thanks.
- Excuse me, man.
- No, that was my bad.
No, really. It was my fault.
There's a pickup game of hoops later,
if you wanna play.
I'd like that.
[Cheering]
- Happy birthday.
- Ah! Thank you!
- Oh, look, a shiv!
- Yeah!
- Hey, homes.
- Mm! Mm!
- Hey.
- Hey!
[Horn squawks]
Stanley! Honey bear!
I loved your letter!
- [Mindy laughs]
- I missed you so much.
Before we go any further, there's
three little words I need to hear.
- I was wrong?
- Good boy!
It looks like
a nursery school picnic out there.
It's Minton.
- What do you mean, it's Minton?
- Well, first he banned rape.
It's to the point
that anybody gets beat up,
they run and join Minton's gang
and Minton beats up the bad guy.
The truth, he's got them too scared
to look at each other funny.
- We ain't had a fight in three days.
- I thought I saw Ingleberg fight
that big Mexican yesterday, Jesus.
Oh, no, that was more in the nature
of a lovers' quarrel.
Ingleberg forgot their
two-week anniversary.
That wasn't very nice of him, was it?
Well, they made up. You should
have seen the cake Ingleberg made.
- It was special...
- You get out of here right now
and get Minton up here!
You understand me? I mean right now!
- Now hurry!
- [Door closes]
I'm notjust saying this, but I think
that was the most amazing sex
- we've ever had.
- [Giggles]
I guess being away from me
this long made you crazy.
Well, yes, I guess.
The Master's opened my eyes, sexually.
He showed me all these different
positions in the Kama Sutra.
- The Master? You been seeing him?
- Yeah, he's staying at the house.
I've learned about massage
and strengthening my Kegels.
- [Knocking on door]
- That sleazy son of a bitch!
- [Bullard] Minton, time's up.
- But Stan, I...
- Warden wants to see you now!
- Wait. I don't want you to see him.
You tell Master Dickface I'm gonna get
out of here soon and kick his ass!
Don't tell him.
You're not allowed to see him.
I said now, convict!
- Minton!
- Not allowed to see him!
- I love you, sweetie-cakes!
- Let's go.
Cocksucker!
[Gasque] I'll bet you didn't know
I was part psychic.
That's right.
I'm able to see into the future.
- I didn't realise.
- Let me tell you what's going to happen
one week from today.
The board of governors
is gonna come to inspect the prison.
And something awful happens.
Some prisoners find a way
to smuggle weapons into the yard.
And a full-scale riot breaks out.
And as the prison board watches
in absolute horror,
my men are forced to shoot
into the yard in order
to end the melee.
In the ensuing scandal,
the Board chooses to sell the property
to a Vietnamese family
based in San Pedro.
And everybody lives happily ever after.
Especially me.
Now, if the events that I foretold
do not come to fruition...
...I will be very disappointed.
And when I get disappointed,
Mr Deng over there
likes to stomp on men's spines
like they was bubble wrap.
I spent 35 years of my life
in this stinking cesspool.
And I will not walk away
without something to show for it.
Your little prison reform
ends right now.
You play ball,
you might get yourself a parole hearing.
How many will get killed?
Who cares? They're all animals.
Bullard!
- Escort Mr Minton back to his cell.
- Yes, sir. Come on, Minton.
Stan, you ever have two Asian men
pounding your balls
after sex with a questionably
attractive older woman?
No, I can't say I have, Lew.
Madam Foreman won't return
any of my calls.
You better go for that deal
the warden offered you.
- So there's nothing else I can do?
- I'm sorry, pal. It's over.
You're in real danger.
Get yourself out of there
as soon as you can:
[Giggling]
[Gasps]
Bullard.
Tell the warden I'll take his deal.
I want out of here.
- [Salsa music plays]
- [Shouting]
Hey, Stan. The Nazis were saying
the Virgin Mary tortilla's a fake.
- That's not cool, homes.
- Hey, the Nazis were saying
the Virgin Mary has no power.
Constantine was pacifying
the Byzantine priest by giving him
a goddess to pray to. They've been
watching the History Channel.
- What?
- What are you gonna do about it?
I'm not gonna do anything about it.
What's up with him, man?
Hey, Stan. Stan!
The Brazilians won't
stop calling Farib an Arab.
I'm not an Arab! I'm Persian.
What do I care?
You look like an Arab.
Hey, listen up! All of you!
You're all on your own!
You hear me?
I don't care what any of you
do to each other!
Hey, you guys!
An interracial book club.
You guys all hate each other.
So stop pretending you don't.
- You don't know about Macbeth.
- Fuck you, motherfucker!
[Shouting]
Yeah, that's more like it. Yes, sir.
Big Stan?
We need to talk.
I thought you cared about us.
Well, I don't.
[Patterson] Hey, little cracker.
Why don't you sit over here,
my little white brother.
Here, have mine.
I'm gonna need to shave your head.
Put a couple little tattoos
on your forehead, huh?
Come on, eat up.
I was wrong about you.
We all were.
Stay out of the yard tomorrow.
You hear me?
D-block houses some
of our most hardened offenders.
But here, we have Oaksburg's
greatest rehabilitation story.
Stan Minton. Stan, I'd like for you
to meet the board of governors.
Not going in the yard today, Stan?
- I don't feel well, warden.
- Maybe this will make you feel better.
Due to Stan's exemplary behaviour,
the parole board has agreed
to meet with him today.
Well, we better be moving along.
The shit goes down at 12.30.
At 12.35,
I'm in the real estate business.
[Muted dialogue]
[Laughter]
Stan! Honey!
- I'll deal with you in a minute.
- Everything OK?
Both of you.
[Woman] Next up is prisoner 5824.
In the matter of Stanley Minton.
You have your files.
[Woman] In his time here, Minton
has accrued an exemplary record.
And let it be noted,
he's a first-time non-violent offender.
[Ticking]
Hold up!
Before we vote, Mr Minton, is there
anything you'd like to add?
I'd just like to say, um...
[clears throat]
...l've really learned a lot.
And I'm ready to get back to work.
[Woman] Good, we like to hear that.
Here's the yard where the prisoners
come to exercise.
That's where Charlie the Fly
tried to fly over the wall. [laughs]
Well, in light of Warden Gasque's
recommendation,
I think we have a pretty
clear-cut case for parole.
Mr Minton?
How would you feel
about getting out of here today?
Mr Minton?
Did I mention I'm in real estate?
[Laughs] I got my eye on some property
real close by here
- I can't wait to develop.
- Hm. That's commendable.
You know, while I was in here,
also, I joined a biker gang.
Satan's Paedophiles.
Anyway, they said when I get out,
they'd love to camp next
to the grammar school near here.
I hope that's not a problem.
They're pretty cool guys, except
when they drink and do crystal meth.
Which is almost every weekend.
But most of the people I sell to,
they don't need to know about that.
'Cause, uh, they're old ladies, mostly.
Not too good with fine print,
if you get my drift.
Tell me, is your grandma still alive?
I bet I could make her a sweet deal.
By the time I'm through with her,
she'll give handjobs behind the pharmacy
to pay for arthritis medication.
Two at a time, you know?
Stuff you see in pornos.
Anyway, that's a nice top you have on.
Seriously.
Mind lowering it?
I'd love to see some boobage.
Let me see that, woman. That's sexy.
Let me see that.
Let me touch one of them.
Let me touch one of them. Can I? Please?
Parole denied!
Take him back to his cell!
What colour are your nipples?
I bet they're pink! Light brown?
Dollar size or quarter?
Stan, did we win?
Let go of me. I'm in a hurry.
Have no fear, Stanley.
I will continue to take care
of your wife while you're gone.
- Thanks a lot, pal.
- No thanks needed.
I cherish Mindy's company.
Since my addiction to cigarettes
made me impotent,
I've had very little contact
with the fair sex.
Impotent?
I used to think smoking was cool,
but a limp dick spells nerd
in any language.
- You're impotent. That's great!
- Not really.
Baby, I love you.
I'll write to you as soon as I can.
OK.
[Mindy screams]
That's my boy.
Love you, baby!
- He's running!
- Code red!
Watch the prisoners file in.
[Phone rings]
The Master has taught you well.
Don't tell me.
You studied with The Master too?
- I am his number one.
- [Scoffs] I didn't see that coming.
There are many things
you will not see coming.
Oh, really? Like what?
Hmm.
[Grunts]
- Whoa. Take it easy.
- I have been taking it easy.
[Both grunting]
[Man] I wanna break me off
some chocolate.
[Man 2] Come on, hold the line.
- Top you up here?
- Thank you very much.
- How are you doing?
- [Indistinct chatter]
Yeah, good.
I don't think The Master
prepares you for this.
Here comes the eagle.
[Screaming]
[Indistinct chatter, laughter]
[Grunting]
[All shouting]
Are those weapons?
Hoo, hoo, hoo!
Ah!
[Groaning]
Somebody didn't strengthen
their titties.
Whoo!
[Shouting]
It looks like a riot.
- [Panting]
- [Grunting]
[Shouting]
Whoo!
- I celebrated too early!
- Ah!
Warden, can't you do anything
to stop this?
- Bullard, prepare to fire.
- [Cocks gun]
[Shouting]
Whoo!
Whoo! Whoo!
Finger of death.
[Sniffs]
That's you.
[High-pitched warbling]
I don't know if The Master
prepared you for this.
Hoo!
[All shouting]
- Ready to dance, motherfuckers?
- Handle your shit, bitch!
Fire at will.
Don't fight!
[Salsa music plays]
[Laughing]
Why aren't you firing?
- Fire that weapon.
- I can't do it, boss.
Well, why the hell not?
They're just dancing.
Give me that rifle.
What the hell are you doing?
[Gasque] Restoring order.
They've clearly lost their minds.
Warden, it's over.
Look at all these witnesses.
It's over, warden.
You did this to me.
- Where did that come from?
- What do you think I've been doing
with The Master for the last six months?
[Sighs] Thank God.
You did good with Dang.
But you're still
my number two student.
- Number two?
- She'll kick your ass.
I might like that.
Ready position!
Focus!
Lock! Punch!
- Kick! Double punch!
- [All] Yah!
Ready position!
Lock! Punch!
- Kick! Double punch!
- [All] Yah!
- It's time, Minton.
- Just a minute, warden.
Looks great, guys.
Thanks, Robbie.
OK, everybody, I gotta go now.
- [All groaning]
- I'll miss you too.
I want you guys to be especially nice
to our newest inmate
and best disbarred lawyer
in the world, Lew Popper.
- Welcome aboard!
- Lew!
- Is the ban on rape still in effect?
- I'm pretty sure.
- [Chuckles]
- [Shorts] Hey!
Permission to give Big Stan
a group hug.
- Permission granted.
- Come on, gang!
[All shouting]
Hey, little homey,
thanks for giving me my teeth back.
- My pleasure.
- [Speaks Spanish]
[Speaks Spanish]
- Where you going, cracker?
- I'm going home, man.
- I think Big Stan is staying here.
- Oh, yeah?
Oh, shit!
[# Los Ninos de Sara: Vagabundo]
[Patterson] I'm Big Stan.
No more rape. [laughs]
Aw, very creepy.
My cracker.
Be good, huh?
Bye, Stan!
[Big Raymond] Hey. Hey.
Whoo!
- Big man.
- Bye, Big Stan.
Say bye.
Stan!
Sweetie.
Hey, handsome.
- Where's Mindy Junior?
- In the car.
- She's being kind of a brat.
- Isn't the nanny helping?
Yeah. I think he
still sneaks cigarettes.
Yeah? I'll talk to him.
[Coughing]
Hi, precious. Hi, The Master.
- Say hello to your father, child.
- Hi.
- Rumour is you're sneaking smokes.
- Shh.
- How's her technique?
- She stinks.
But so did you at first.
You sure? I don't remember that.
- [Mindy] Stan!
- OK, baby.
[Mindy] Let's go, sweetie!
[Mindy] Whoo-hoo!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org