[Ship horn blows]
[Car brakes squeak]
WOMAN: Uh! Uhh!
[Ship's engine chugs]
Unh!
BO^ What do you think, lrving?
He makes this
cheap dago move on me...
Bo Weinberg...
the man
who took out Vincent Coll...
the man who held
Jack Diamond's ears...
so he could put the gun
in his mouth...
who found the rackets
he was too stupid to find...
who made him something more...
than the lowdown
fucking ganef that he is.
The schmuck.
l should expect something else.
He pulls me off the street
in front of my girl...
like he don't know no better.
Schmuck.
Don't talk to lrving.
Talk to me.
BO^ Men talk.
lf they are men, they talk.
They have a disagreement,
they discuss things.
But you,
l don't know, Dutch...
l don't know what stinking
womb of pus and scum...
and ape shit you came out of.
DUTCH^ You should understand
l am past the madness part.
l am past the anger.
Don't waste your breath.
You never
paid your debts, Dutch.
You never paid me
what l was worth...
you never paid nobody
what they was worth.
[Door bangs]
DUTCH: Hey, Bo, look
who came along for the ride.
BO: The more l done for you,
the more like a brother...
l was to you,
the least l counted.
l saved your life
a dozen times!
DUTCH:
Hey, kid, you like boats?
BlLLY^ l don't know yet.
BO: Protected you!
[Door closes]
l did your shit work...
and l did it
like a professional.
You always
had a way with words, Bo.
You got more words than me...
being l haven't been
to high school...
but l got a good head
for current events...
so l guess it all evens out.
What's even?!
l made you a millionaire!
l handed you a fortune!
You got more money
than you know what to do with!
l built this organization--
the beer, the unions...
the numbers,
$20 million a year...
you'd run it like
some goddamn candy store!
Look at it this way, Bo.
l'm the one sitting here...
and you're
the one sitting there.
Who would you rather be
at this moment?
-Come on.
-Uhh!
lt's all right, lrving.
You can bring her up.
BO: No!
No, Dutch!
DUTCH:
Ahh, feeling better?
You can sit her
down there, lrving.
Come here.
This is
a very good malt whiskey.
Go ahead,
it'll settle your stomach.
This is between me and you.
Leave her out of it.
Bravo, sweetheart. Bravo.
You know what you're doing,
don't you?
l'll bet you know how to do
just about everything.
BO: Dutch, for Christ's sakes,
it's over, it's done.
Did you say something, Bo?
You can see the trouble
your Bo is in...
right, Bo?
Show her how you can't
do certain things anymore.
Show her
how the simplest thing...
like crossing your legs
or scratching your nose...
it can't be done anymore by you.
Sure, he can scream,
he can shout...
but he can't lift his foot.
He can't open his fly.
He can't tell you
what time it is.
Little by little,
he's taken leave of his life.
lrving, is there a cabin?
Down below aft.
The back end.
Mr. Class Act, Bo Weinberg,
moves against his best friend...
against the man he works for.
That's class.
All right, miss,
if you'd be so kind.
BO: Dutch.
So, tell me, l'm just curious...
when did you two meet?
How long have
you and Bo been lovebirds?
Just this way, miss.
l have not had the pleasure
of meeting you before...
but it is clear
that Bo is in love.
lt's clear that he's...
BO^ lrving.
Put me out, lrving.
l'm begging you,
put the muzzle to my head.
l can't do that, Bo.
Please, lrving.
Sorry.
l could give you a drink.
Want a drink, Bo?
BO: You listen to me, kid.
You take some advice
from old Bo Weinberg.
This man of yours
ain't gonna last long.
He's obsolete.
You know what that means?
lt means he's finished,
he's done.
He's up against
tougher guys than him...
and they're better organized.
lf you're as smart
as they say you are...
you'll look out for yourself.
You'll listen
to old Bo Weinberg.
[Sighs]
How'd you get into this, kid?
Uh, juggling.
lt was juggling got me into it.
There ain't been a beer truck
around here for weeks.
What the hell does that mean?
What are you, stupid?
No, l ain't stupid.
What does it mean?
lt means we could sit here
till the cows come home.
The Dutchman's hiding out.
Dutch Schultz
don't hide from nobody.
The heat is on.
Joey's brother
works for Dutch Schultz...
and he said the heat is on.
Joey Faye's brother?
How'd he get a job
working for Schultz?
-He caught on.
-How?
l don't know.
He caught on.
Dutch took notice.
Yeah, Schultz noticed him.
KlD: Give me a cigarette.
Ladies and gentlemen, l have
the pleasure to present...
the Phantom,
the world's greatest juggler.
KlD:
The world's greatest jerk.
He has come to us directly
from a tour...
of the crowned heads
of Europe...
and he will juggle
not one, not two...
not three, but four balls.
Count them.
KlD: Ohh, wow.
[Kid imitates trumpet call]
This is
never before attempted...
in the Bronx, New York, USA.
KlD: You can join
a circus now, Billy.
SECOND KlD:
Hey, shut up. Look.
KlD: You can marry a seal,
or something. Ha ha!
KlD: That's him.
-That's Schultz.
-Oh, my God.
He drives a black Packard.
-How do you know?
-He's got a gun.
Everybody knows.
l'm telling you,
it's very simple...
but l think l've got
this whole thing under control.
Then do it, Counselor.
Pay them off.
-Look at that kid.
-What's he doing?
[Truck engine starts]
[Clapping]
DUTCH: Hey, kid, come here.
Come here.
MAN: Arthur.
Arthur, can l just
finish this point...
l'm trying to make?
lt's very simple.
l know you don't like
to talk about money...
but l need about 10,000 more
to cover these guys.
l realize it seems like a lot.
$10,000
is a lot of money...
but these are the best
attorneys on the east coast.
They have
a lot of connections...
and if we do happen
to go to trial--
DUTCH^
This doesn't go to trial.
l know we're not going
to trial.
[Breathing hard]
A capable boy.
Arthur, look, just look.
Can you give me
an answer on this?
DUTCH^ You want an answer?
l'll give you an answer.
How come you're the cheapest
lawyer l could find...
and you still cost me
all this dough?
lrving, he always wants
a little money.
KlD: Hey, Billy!
Did you see that?
He just met Dutch Schultz.
What you got there?
Now he's a big-shot.
ALL^ How you doing?
What's going on?
Let me look at it.
Want to see me double it?
No, l want to look at it.
Hey, Billy!
Hey, Behan!
Get your ass back here!
Come on!
Share the wealth, Billy!
[All yelling]
Hey!
[Horse neighs]
Arnold!
Arnold Bobbich!
Whoo! Arnold!
-You still got it?
-Yeah.
Well, go get it.
BlLLY: Wow. Does it work?
Sure. l mean, l think it does.
You gotta clean it up first.
-ls there bullets in it?
-No.
See how the serial number's
been filed off there?
That's the sign
that it's a mob gun for sure.
l'll give you $3.00.
You have $3.00?
Where did this come from?
Dutch Schultz.
Now give me my change.
You lying son of a bitch.
[Girls singing in Yiddish]
BlLLY: Ma, l'm going out now.
l'll be back in a while.
[Singing in Yiddish]
[Tapping on window]
[Music stops]
The government's after him,
the cops are after him.
Everybody's after him,
and there he is.
Like he ain't got a care
in the world.
He noticed you. So what?
BlLLY: So what?
You think a guy like me
has got a lot of choices?
You notice John D. Rockefeller
offering me a job...
or the Yankees asking me
to play shortstop?
No. This is it.
Becky, listen to me.
You don't understand about
a guy like Dutch Schultz.
He grew up around here.
He was a nobody, just like me.
But he had brains and guts,
and look at him now.
l bet he's the richest man
in New York.
l mean,
he's got the racetracks...
he's got the nightclubs.
He controls
the whole liquor business...
he's gotten
into the numbers racket.
Dutch Schultz
is the number one...
and he noticed me.
l'm telling you, Becky...
l know whatever happens
to me in my life...
it's gonna have something
to do with Mr. Schultz.
What are you gonna do?
l'm gonna find him.
How are you gonna find him?
Don't worry, l'll find him.
[Footsteps]
Hey, Harry, how you doing?
Great. Right on schedule.
[Dog barking]
[Men talking
and telephones ringing]
What's going on here?
ls this a joke?
Lulu.
[Dutch shouting]
All you have to do
is what you're supposed to do.
Stop dicking me around!
All you have to do
is make the deal.
United States of America
wants me to pay taxes. Fine!
l'll pay the fucking taxes!
lt's not as simple as that,
Arthur.
Stop with the papers
and listen to me a minute!
Look around you.
What do you see in this place?
l got 20 desks here, right?
How many men you see sitting
at these desks? Ten!
Doesn't an empty desk
mean anything to you?
Don't you understand
every week this goes on...
that l lose money,
l lose my banks...
l lose my men to
those dago scumbags downtown?
DlXlE: Arthur,
you don't seem to understand.
You don't hold all the cards
in this situation.
What do you mean
l don't hold all the cards?
l'm paying you
an arm and a leg, aren't l?
l'm paying off half the judges
and cops in this town.
What do you mean,
l don't hold the cards?
These are my favorite.
Arthur, this is
the federal government.
Al Capone is serving
41 years for tax evasion.
We'll beat it,
but it'll take a lot of money...
and a lot of time,
you understand what l'm saying?
[Telephone rings]
Who are you?
[Ring]
A kid with luck.
DUTCH: Yeah?
Well, we could use some.
MAN:
We haven't heard from George.
Yeah, he's always
straight with me.
lrving, come in here
and close the door.
l want to talk to you.
You forgot the coffee.
-That's it for today.
-OK, Otto.
-Wipe the board clean.
-Right.
-You play the numbers, kid?
-No, sir.
-Good. You got a mother?
-Yes, sir.
Don't let her
play the numbers, either.
But l'll tell you what,
l'll put you onto a sure thing.
A horse?
OTTO^ The world is numbers,
not horses.
For instance, l'll tell you
how much money...
you got in your pocket.
lf l'm right, l win it.
lf l'm wrong,
l'm gonna match it...
and you'll have double
what you had before.
-How's that?
-All right.
O TTO: Count your money.
Don't let me see it.
-l know how much it is.
-Good.
Now double that in your head,
and add three.
All right.
-Now product that by five.
-Product?
Multiply that by five,
subtract six...
and tell me
what you come up with.
279.
-You just lost 27 cents.
-Yeah!
O TTO: You might consider
the study of numbers.
Question--
What's 125th and 3rd?
A street corner.
There's a candy store.
lt's one of
our numbers houses.
[Glass breaking]
Son of a bitch.
MAN: Let's get out of here.
[Tires screech]
BlLLY: Otto sent me.
Ain't nothing l can do.
l work for them now.
You tell him that, hear?
You see what happens
when l try to do right?
You can all go to hell,
as far as l'm concerned.
All white men together.
You tell him that, too.
Sounds like Jack Kelly.
DUTCH^ See, kid?
l don't start these things.
l'm just
this good-natured slob...
that people think
they can walk right over.
-You in a gang?
-No, sir.
No? How do you expect
to learn anything?
l hire from gangs.
That's the training ground.
Did you ever hear
of the Frog Hollow gang?
No, sir.
That was the most famous
of all the Bronx gangs.
That's where the original
Dutch Schultz came from.
He was the toughest street
fighter that ever lived...
so they named me Dutch Schultz
in my neighborhood.
lt was like an honorary thing.
Most of the gangs now
are just dumb kids.
DUTCH: ls that right?
l think,
for the real training...
DUTCH: Yeah?
You gotta go right to the top.
O TTO: You're supposed
to see Bo Weinberg.
Hey, Otto, you ought
to listen to this kid.
You'll learn something.
O TTO: Thanks.
What?
O TTO: Jack Kelly's gonna be
at the Beakman barber shop...
tomorrow morning at 9:00.
Good.
We'll let Bo handle this.
You give him a ring.
l tried to get Bo for two days.
l can't find him anywhere.
Where the hell is he?
He's supposed
to be minding the store.
All right, kid,
l want you to be...
at Broadway and Nassau
at 9^00 in the morning.
BlLLY^ What do l do?
What you do is,
you don't ask any questions.
[Talking and laughing]
[Police whistle blowing]
[Horn honks]
NEWSMAN^ Extra, extra!
Get your ''Daily Mirror!''
-Kid.
-Mr. Berman.
-ls that the car?
-Yes, sir.
NEWSMAN: Extra! Extra!
Get your ''Daily Mirror''!
-You sure that's him?
-Yes, sir.
DUTCH^ l'm gonna have
a talk with Mr. Kelly.
OTTO^ Not yet.
Wait'll Bo gets here.
DUTCH^ Bo?
l don't need Bo for this.
-Not now.
-l'm just gonna talk to him.
NEWSMAN: Gangland murder!
Barbershop slaying!
Gangland murder!
DUTCH: ''Grisly.'' There was
nothing grisly about it.
lt was a professional
piece of work.
Look at this. lt was neat,
clean, end of story...
good-bye and good luck.
LULU^ They'll think
one of the guineas...
or the coloreds
slit his throat.
BO^ So, how do l know it was
the Dutchman right off the bat?
Aw, it's good to see you, Bo.
We thought you was dead.
BO: Well, obviously l ain't.
You couldn't wait 24 hours?
You couldn't wait
24 hours for me...
to come home and do this
the right way?
Believe me, it was done right.
OTTO^ Where were you?
l called around...
nobody knows where you are.
LULU^ He was with some broad.
This was no broad.
This was a lady, a real lady.
O TTO: Where'd you take
this real lady...
that's more important
than business?
Wherever it was,
she wasn't complaining.
You could've called,
checked in.
We never know where you are,
what you're doing.
You're always with some dame.
We're running a business here.
Arthur's going on trial.
You're supposed to be in charge.
You got complaints
about the way l run things?
DUTCH^ All Otto's saying is if
you're gonna shack up, fine...
but we didn't know
where you was.
What he's trying to say is,
the way you handled it...
just wasn't too fucking smart,
that's all.
That's all.
Look at it this way, Arthur...
you're the one on the lam,
and l'm the one on the town.
Who would you rather be
at this moment?
You know what l mean?
[Piano playing]
# Pack up
all my care and woe #
# Here l go,
singing low #
# Bye bye, blackbird #
# Where somebody waits for me #
# Sugar's sweet, so is he #
# Bye bye, blackbird... #
BO^ ls that a great tune, huh?
[Laughs]
Hey, kid,
take this to Mr. Schultz.
# Oh, what
hard luck stories #
# They all hand me #
That's right, watch your toes.
[Both laugh]
# ...late tonight #
# Blackbird, bye bye #
[Trumpet solo]
BO^ l could do that easily.
Come here.
Yeah, that's right.
[Both laughing]
What?
Bo Weinberg's
double-crossing us.
O TTO: He met with
one of the other gangs.
He offered to cut them in
on our whole operation.
That's a lot of shit.
l can't believe that.
The meeting took place
on the tenth.
Saratoga.
The Piping Rock Casino.
The barbershop
was on the tenth...
why we couldn't reach him.
He said he was shacked up.
He didn't say who with,
or where.
No, no, no,
it doesn't make sense, Otto.
Why would he do something
like that?
O TTO: Arthur, nobody thinks
you're gonna beat this rap.
Word on the street
is that you're as good as dead.
Maybe Bo's just looking
to the future.
What are you talking about?
You know how far back we go.
Come on, l can't bel--
What do you want?
Yes, sir. The bartender
asked me to give you this.
Thank you.
[Door closes]
[Jazz ballad playing]
[Whispering]
BARTENDER^
Good night, Mr. Weinberg.
-l'm going to the bathroom.
-OK.
[Billy snoring]
[Whispers] Kid.
-Huh.
-Kid.
Mr. Weinberg.
Dutchman's
got you working late?
Yes, sir.
Where are you from, kid?
The Bronx. Bathgate Avenue.
Jerome Avenue.
[Billy laughs]
Say hello to a friend of mine
from the Bronx.
Hello.
Mr. Weinberg, this is $20.
Yeah, get some sleep, kid.
BlLLY: Thanks.
Thanks a lot.
You know what a loyal man
is worth these days, kid?
His weight in gold.
You remember that.
He lied to me, Otto.
He lied to me.
l will take him down,
and that is a sacred vow.
OTTO^ You have to be careful.
Bo has many friends.
DUTCH^
He was the best...smart.
l never had to tell Bo
to do anything twice.
l would say it one time,
and bang, it was done...
and it was done right.
Hey, anybody in there?
l promise you, kid,
it was done right.
You get high marks for this.
lRVlNG: The fire inspector.
Must be payday.
l'll talk to him.
Come on, open up!
He had balls.
Nobody had balls like Bo.
Let me talk to the manager.
He's not here.
Come back later.
l remember one time,
the guineas wanted him...
to take out one of their guys,
and you know what he done?
He put on a cop's uniform.
Where's the manager?
Hey, where you going?
You can't come in here.
This is a private meeting.
What's the matter, pal?
You got a problem, huh?
[Screaming]
You want a payoff, huh?!
l'll give you a payoff!
[Banging]
[Breathing heavily]
Get this load of shit
out of here.
Fucking fire inspector.
What's next, the mailman?
l can't take it, Otto.
l can't take it
when it's all over the street.
l'm going to have to get
Hines to deal with this.
-lt'll cost.
-Do what you have to do.
DUTCH^
lf l have to go to trial...
l'm not going to trial
in the city.
l want it in the boondocks.
Oh, Bo...
what have you done to me?
Close the door.
BlLLY^ Mr. Berman.
What are we going to do?
He killed that man.
Forget it.
You didn't see anything.
You didn't hear anything.
Nothing happened.
You even think about it again,
you're as good as dead.
Listen to me, kid.
You're the upcoming generation.
Things are going
to be different for you.
You need different skills
from these guys.
lt'll be streamlined--
not so much fire in the street.
And when that happens,
if you're lucky...
you may not have to kill anyone.
And what that means is,
no one will have to kill you.
Let's go. Get the lights.
Here's your salary--$12.
Now, this $50 is my money.
l want you to buy
a new pair of pants...
a nice jacket,
shirt with a tie...
pair of shoes with laces.
lt's a personal
embarrassment to me...
to see the way you dress.
And l want you to get a valise
to put the clothes in.
And buy something nice
for your mother.
Where am l going?
Mr. Schultz is having
a trial coming up...
and we have decided
he'll get a better deal...
if the trial
takes place upstate.
ls that all right with you?
And l want you
to buy a book to read.
What do l need a book for?
You gonna do what l say
or give me a hard time?
-Mr. Berman?
-Yes?
Who is this man you're meeting?
lf you want to stay
in the crime business, kid...
you got to stop asking
all these questions.
[Car approaches]
His name is Hines.
He's a district leader
for Tammany Hall.
He's on our payroll...
takes care of problems
like this.
[Car door closes]
[Ship horn blows]
HlNES: So, Otto,
you're looking good.
Good to see you.
lt's a pleasure.
[Speaking indistinctly]
[Dog barking]
BlLLY: These guys ain't like
anybody you ever met.
They want something--
boom--it gets done.
And the money--l swear...
you never seen money
like this in your life.
So what?
How much money can you spend?
That ain't the point.
Let me tell you,
money can do anything.
l bet you never had
anything in your life...
that somebody else
didn't wear first.
Here.
Get yourself something nice.
Come on, Arnold,
we're having a party.
-Where?
-Where do you think?
ARNOLD: Just don't break
anything this time.
BlLLY: Don't worry.
[People chattering]
Hello.
Mr. Klein, how are you?
KLElN:
Look at you, wearing a suit.
Mr. Rosen, you're looking good.
-How are you?
-Very good.
Girls, girls, girls.
-Hey, Charlie.
-Hello, Billy.
-Hey, Mrs. Thomas.
-Billy, don't you look swell?
-Thank you.
Hi, Ma.
l got a job.
The thing is,
it's in the country--upstate.
lt's just for the summer.
Ma?
This is for you.
Billy Behan, look at you--
the richest man
on Bathgate Avenue.
[Chattering]
[Music playing]
[Sighs]
[Both laugh]
You're bad.
DUTCH^ Let's go to work.
-lrving.
-Miss, this way.
What?
What's the matter?
-Come on.
-Bo, what's going on?
[Car engine idling]
[Tires squeal]
-Good evening, Bo.
-Leave her out of this, Dutch.
DUTCH^ This must be love.
Tch. What is your name, miss?
BO^ Her name is Lola.
DUTCH^ That can't be.
l know all the girls named Lola.
You must be Arthur.
[Ship's engine chugging]
Kid, go see what he's doing.
He don't have no respect.
Go see if she's all right.
BO: Do what l told you.
DUTCH: You know what
l'm talking about, don't you?
Hmm? You don't care about
what's dead, do you?
Because
l'm telling you right now...
except for a few details,
he's dead.
Can you understand that?
[Sighs]
You can forget about the dead,
can't you?
l think you've forgotten
already, haven't you?
Well?
l'm waiting.
lt's either a yes or a no.
-l--l...
-What?
DUTCH^
l'm sorry. l can't hear you.
What?
[Sighs]
Yes.
Aw...that's too bad.
That's too bad for Bo.
Because if
l thought you loved him...
l might've changed my mind.
[Thunder]
OK, kid.
Take the lady to her apartment.
Don't let her
make any phone calls...
although l don't think
she'll try.
She'll pack some things.
Stay with her until l come back.
Somebody will call you up
on the house phone...
to bring her down.
You got it?
[Thunder]
[Laughs]
Have you ever seen
such a terrible night?
DOORMAN^
Good evening, Mrs. Preston.
[Woman singing aria]
HARVEY: Drew?
Drew?
l have to pee, Harvey.
l thought you were out
for the evening.
You all right? Drew.
HARVEY: Now tell me
what you've gone and done.
You didn't ditch him.
l thought you were
so wild about him.
DREW: Harvey, l don't
want to talk about it.
HARVEY: lt's perfectly
all right with me.
l never could stand him anyway.
DREW: Listen, l'll be
going away for a while.
You can't mean it.
Going away?
Where? For how long?
We're supposed to be going to
the Willett's this weekend.
To say nothing of dinner
tomorrow evening with Dwight.
Which was your idea
to begin with...
if l'm not mistaken.
DREW: Darling, you'll just
have to make excuses for me.
HARVEY^ There's certain
proprieties to be maintained.
You are my wife...
or have you forgotten?
Harvey, what's the point
of making a fuss?
There's a certain limit.
A bit of scandal
isn't the point...
but sooner or later,
you'll get in over your head...
and then what will you do?
Expect you to come
to the rescue like always.
[Telephone rings]
Get me another drink,
would you, please?
[Ring]
lf that's my gangster,
tell him to wait.
[Dutch strikes match]
Mrs. Preston,
you got a first name?
Drew.
Drew? You're the first Drew
l ever met.
DREW: You're the first Dutch.
[Cows mooing]
O TTO: All right, we have
28 days before the trial.
That means 28 days
to show these folks...
that Dutch Schultz
is one of them.
Starting off,
we call him by his real name...
Mr. Flegenheimer.
Everything is quiet and polite.
We're plain folks,
just like them...
who got the government
on their backs.
They understand that.
We don't get into fights.
No feeling up the chambermaids.
From now on,
you eat with your mouth closed.
-This is horse shit.
-No foul language.
No booze, no dames, no fighting.
This is different from the city.
These are decent people.
Make sure you act decent.
-Where's the book?
-Huh?
l told you to bring a book.
Either you listen,
or you go back to the Bronx.
lt's not some kind of picnic.
Take this to Mrs. Preston.
ls that coffee?
Yes.
Hmm. Thank you.
LULU: l once met Alvin Pincus,
who ran with Pretty Boy Floyd.
-He always said banks was best.
-Look where he is now.
Going for the dough
in the one place...
that's under lock and key,
you gotta be stupid.
-Yeah, but--
-Stay with the car, Lulu.
You got anything to tell me
about the girl?
Her name is Drew Preston.
You want to explain
what she's doing here?
We got a trial coming up.
She's the kid's governess.
The properties
are being observed.
-The what?
-The properties.
DREW^ Wait a minute.
There. You look handsome.
[Laughs]
That's a compliment.
-Please come in.
-Thank you.
lt's very nice
to make your acquaintance.
May l introduce
my business manager, Mr. Berman?
And Mrs. Preston, who is
the governess of my prodigy.
lt is a pleasure to meet you.
l'd like to open
a checking account for $10,000.
OTTO^ And the rest
in a savings account.
Of course.
Excuse me a moment.
l'll get my head accountant
to take care of the paperwork.
Honey, you are looking at the
patron saint of the boondocks.
Arthur, if l make
a tiny criticism...
do you promise not
to get all sulky and pout?
-What?
-lt's protege.
-What did l say?
-Prodigy.
lt means ''Child genius.''
Thank you very much,
Mr. Flegenheimer.
We don't often get famous people
in our little town.
Yeah, l know what you mean.
Look, if it's
all right with you...
Mr. Berman will stay here
and work out the details.
l'm sure
there'll be no problem.
Say, young fella,
what's the younger generation...
reading these days?
Ah, yes.
What's your name, son?
Billy, uh...
Bathgate.
With youngsters like this,
we don't have to worry...
about the future
of this country, do we?
[Laughs] No, we don't.
l hope to see you soon.
Yeah, right. Come here.
Let me see that, will you?
What do you got there?
What is this?
Was this your idea?
Don't look at me, boss.
You?
This was your brainstorm?
Yeah.
l love it. What'd l tell you?
The kid's all right.
He's my prodigy.
l know how to pick my words.
You're my prodigy.
Get in the car.
We ain't got all day.
Mickey, l got an inspiration.
-lnspiration, right?
-lnspiration.
What kind of church is this?
lt's Catholic.
They put a lot of work
into this place.
''G,'' 58.
''l,'' 1 7.
-''G,'' 51 .
-Bingo!
And especially Mr. Schultz...
for so generously donating
a special cash prize of $25.
Dollar, a dollar five,
who'll go a dollar five?
Put the ring in there.
lt's not frozen.
-5 dollar, 10 dollar, 1 5.
-All righty.
Ten chickens here
in the two crates.
Bid 25 cents anyone?
25, now 30, now 5.
l'll give you $100
for the chickens...
and how much
you want for the farm?
[Car horn honks]
[Honks]
[Horse neighs]
[People chattering]
l try to talk to him,
but it's impossible.
Sometimes he listens...
and sometimes
he won't listen at all.
Looks like he's going
for the farm vote.
DUTCH^
l hope this helps for now.
lf you need more later,
l can't promise...
but l'll do what l can,
Mister...
Chambers.
-Chambers.
-Thank you, sir.
God bless you
for what you're doing, sir.
Mickey...who's next?
Yeah, well, Dixie's here.
-What are you doing here?
-Hello, Arthur.
Come here.
Give me some more coffee.
Why aren't you in the city?
What are you coming up here for?
Arthur, we need to talk.
Why didn't you call me up?
l didn't want to say this
on the telephone.
Say what?
The government turned down
our offer.
-So double it.
-No. They won't settle.
The prosecutor's
determined to go to trial.
Aw, shit.
So we'll take care of him, too.
DlXlE^ No. lt's no soap.
He can't be bought.
He said that?
What do you want?
l got your coffee.
[Clatters]
Put in on the table.
Why are you always listening?
Will you go upstairs
and tell Mrs. Preston...
to take you to a museum
or something?
Get out of here!
Go to the zoo.
Do something useful.
l need the suite.
[Clock ticking]
BlLLY: Mrs. Preston?
Mr. Schultz
said l should wake you.
He said he needs the room...
so we should go
to a museum or something.
Mrs. Preston, l don't think
this was such a good idea.
Mr. Schultz didn't
say anything about this.
One of things
about being in a gang...
is you got to follow orders.
So far, everything
they asked me to do, l done it.
DREW^ Did it.
l mean it.
l think we ought to go back.
[Birds chirping]
Mrs. Preston?
Mrs. Preston!
[Breathing heavily]
Mrs. Preston, are you all right?
How was it when Bo died?
Could you tell me, please?
[Wind blowing]
[lrving and Billy grunting]
Unh!
lRVlNG^ You got him?
Hold onto him.
Unh.
Take care of my girl, kid.
Don't let him hurt her.
Get her away from him
before he hurts her.
You hear me?
Promise me.
-Say it!
-l promise.
-Unh!
-Aah!
Mrs. Preston!
[Gasps]
Did he really
ask you to protect me?
Yes.
lt's strange.
l mean,
that he would think...
that l couldn't
take care of myself.
And you promised him you would?
Yes.
You always keep your promises?
Uh-huh.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Yes. Yes.
She's a very lucky girl.
O TTO: They may not be thinkers,
but they do think.
DUTCH:
What is that supposed to mean?
O TTO: They remember Bo.
DUTCH: l remember, too.
What he did
he brought upon himself.
l am upset, too.
Just because l don't
go around talking about it...
O TTO: They liked Bo.
They don't appreciate his
lady friend's presence here.
DUTCH: That is
their hard luck, isn't it?
What do you think the odds are
l'll beat this rap?
-l wouldn't bet on you.
-Why not?
We come up here,
take the time, the trouble...
the effort
to set things right...
make a good impression,
and you bring along this broad.
DUTCH: All right,
you made your point.
[Breathes deeply]
What?
She was there when Bo got it.
That is correct.
She never should've
got on that boat...
and she never should've got off.
When the time comes...
l'll smack her around
a little.
And that's all it'll take,
l promise you.
O TTO: Don't fall in love
with her, Arthur.
Boy, you are
some picnic tonight.
l said
don't fall in love with her.
[Floorboards creak]
[Key jangles]
[Cocks gun]
-Who's out there?
-Nobody.
DUTCH: Jesus Christ,
you scared the shit out of me.
lt's nothing.
The citizens of Onondaga
are hard-working people...
who usually get
the short end of the stick...
but our forefathers
have dealt you...
a couple of cards
in your favor...
and you people
know the law...
isn't nothing but what
the people say it is.
l have great confidence
that the people in this town...
know l hold the same virtues
of right and wrong.
And if l just may wax poetic
for a moment...
[Door opens, both laughing]
Mrs. Preston,
you got to be careful.
[Laughing]
Otto saw us.
l mean it, Mrs. Preston.
You got to watch out
with these people.
Why? [Laughs]
They don't like anybody
to have something on them.
[Laughs]
Do l have something on them?
Do l?
You were on the boat.
That makes you a danger to them.
lf l have something on them,
then so do you.
BlLLY: Yeah.
You're right.
lf l don't catch on...
then l will
have something on them.
lf Mr. Schultz decides
against me, that's it.
There's nothing anyone can do.
Let me tell you something
about your Mr. Schultz.
He is a very ordinary man.
[Laughs]
Now you've got something on me.
[Gunshots]
[Chickens clucking]
[Cocks gun]
[Gunshots]
Who's the better shooter?
-lrving.
-Why?
He got them all in there.
Nothing's wasted.
DUTCH: This ain't
ladies embroidery.
lt don't have to be neat.
lf you got the time
to set it up...
and you need a clean hit,
you send lrving...
but if you're in a tight spot,
you want Lulu next to you.
Boom. lt's all over
in a couple of seconds.
[Crickets chirping]
[Train whistle blowing
in distance]
Guess this is about as far
from where l come from...
as you can get.
Where's that?
The Bronx. Bathgate Avenue.
We live in a tenement.
Who's ''we''?
My mom and me.
She works in a laundry,
gets $4.00 a week.
You probably spend
more than that for lunch.
Maybe you don't appreciate
the position you're in.
What position is that?
You're Mr. Schultz's girl.
No, l'm not his girl.
He's my gangster.
Besides...
you're the one
who's been looking after me.
So far you seem to be
doing all right on your own.
[Laughs] Meaning?
What? Meaning?
Tell me. Come on, tell me.
BlLLY^ Well, because...
Yes?
[Laughs]
Because Mr. Schultz
is a pushover for blondes.
How do you know?
Because l read it in the paper.
l don't read the papers.
How are you supposed
to know...
everything you need to know
if you don't read the paper?
What is it l need to know?
Maybe if you don't work
for a living...
you don't need
to know anything...
but some of us are trying
to learn a trade...
and we have to be up
on the latest developments.
Here's the latest development.
PRlEST:
Arthur, do you renounce Satan?
l do renounce him.
-And all his works?
-Yes.
-And all his promises?
-And all his allurements?
-Yes.
[Speaking Latin]
Mr. Luciano, please place
your hand in position.
[Speaking Latin]
[Bell ringing]
[Chattering]
As l said before, Mr. Luciano,
thanks very much.
l'm just honored
to enter the Catholic Church...
on the ticket
of such a man as yourself.
l appreciate your coming.
LUClANO^ Where's Bo Weinberg?
ls he here today?
l'm sorry.
He couldn't make it.
LUClANO^ That's too bad.
l never met him, but l hear
he's a man of character...
a man to respect.
DUTCH^ Yeah.
l'm sure he would've liked
to have met you, too.
l'm making a party later,
and l'd be happy--
l wish l could, but
l got to get back to the city.
Take care of yourself.
Yeah.
DlXlE: Mr. Luciano,
thank you so much for coming.
You honor us with your presence.
[Car departs]
[Music playing,
people chattering]
[Train whistle blowing
in distance]
WOMAN: Where were you?
WOMAN^
Oh, is that where you went?
Yes. Fred told me about it.
[Laughing]
You're late. You were supposed
to be here this morning.
-lt's a long drive, Otto.
-Take off your hat.
Where's Dutch?
l ain't got all night.
Excuse me.
Mr. President...
Where were you?
This was a big day for me.
Do you tell Julie
Mr. Luciano himself...
showed up here today?
You were supposed to be here
a long time ago, Julie.
You're lucky l'm here at all.
DlXlE: Julie, nice to see you.
How was the drive?
Father Mclnerny,
l'd like you to meet...
Mr. Julie Martin,
my business associate.
Ah. And what do you do,
Mr. Martin?
He's the president of
the Metropolitan Restaurant...
and Cafeteria Owners
Association.
Well, sir, you are in
the finest restaurant in town.
That's your problem.
You're in the country now.
Mind your manners.
Right. Now tell me why
you got me to drive up here...
so l can get out
of the goddamn country.
You got a big mouth,
you know that, Mr. President?
l've got some business
to discuss...
with this gentleman,
so if you'll excuse me...
Otto.
JULlE: l earn, l earn!
The money l pay, expenses!
[Dutch laughs]
What costs are
you talking about, Julie?
l didn't dream up
the protection racket...
so you could steal from me.
You didn't dream up nothing!
l made the rackets.
l run them for you.
Don't raise your voice to me.
l'm not across the street.
You've been yelling at me
all night.
JULlE^ l'm the one
with the baseball bats.
l'm the one
who throws the stink bombs.
who squeezed $2 million...
out of those restaurants
last year--me, alone.
Don't you feel obliged
to make it good?
To make what good?
The $50,000 that
Otto says you're light.
Otto's wrong.
Otto's never wrong.
He says you've been skimming.
-Skimming?
-Yeah.
No, not skimming.
Money that l'm entitled to.
You're entitled
to $50,000 worth?
-You're damn right l am.
-He's entitled to $50,000.
Let me
tell you something, pally.
You tell me something, pally.
l got every maitre d'
in the city on his knees...
when l walk in the door
because of who l am.
Let me explain something to you
in plain English.
Uhh! [Gagging]
BlLLY^ Oh, my God.
Kid, see if
you can find the shell.
My eyes aren't
what they used to be.
DlXlE^ Arthur, you killed
a man right in front of me.
He stole $50,000 from me,
Counselor.
l'm a member of the State Bar.
l'm sitting right here.
O TTO: Calm down, Dixie.
Nobody heard a thing.
Everybody's asleep.
l was seen with him
at the reception.
He left right after that.
Mickey drove him.
We have witnesses. Relax.
Relax? He shoots a gun
in the man's mouth...
in the middle of a sentence,
he wants me to relax?
Take Dixie to his room.
Lock him in.
l have to walk into
a courtroom tomorrow.
LULU^ You'll get over it.
O TTO: Kid, go downstairs.
Bring up the elevator.
Make sure nobody sees you.
[Door opens]
What's the matter, lrving?
lRVlNG^ lt's not coming out.
-What the hell are you doing?
-What's going on?
BlLLY^ Shh. Be quiet.
Go back to sleep.
Listen, nothing has happened.
Do what l tell you.
Don't ask about it.
Don't say a word
to Mr. Schultz about it.
Forget it.
Now l've got something on you.
[Elevator door closes]
Hello, Operator.
This is Mr. Flegenheimer.
There's been an accident,
and l need a doctor.
[Door opens]
Sure, l'll hold on.
[Door closes]
Hello, Doctor.
This is Mr. Flegenheimer.
We've had a little accident,
and l'd appreciate it...
if you could come over
and take a look.
Thank you.
No, it's nothing serious.
About how long will that take?
Fine. That's just fine.
Room 35, Terminal Hotel.
[Hangs up phone]
Uhh!
Jesus, Lu, you don't have
to break his fucking nose.
Uhh.
Take your hands away.
Come on.
Just put your head down.
Let me do the work.
All right?
That's good. Just relax.
BlLLY: Uhh.
A little more over there.
That's it. That's a good boy.
Just let it drip there.
BlLLY: Oh.
lrv, give him a handkerchief
and get him out.
lRVlNG^ Here.
Up you go.
DUTCH^ Now listen.
You don't have to worry
about the Dutchman.
l take care of my own, OK?
Easy, easy, easy.
Don't you think twice
about Julie Martin.
He tried to take
what was mine...
but you l love--
and these guys.
And l would do anything
for them.
They know my word is my bond.
They know it's better than
the Prudential Life Assurance.
Look at this.
Not a complaint out of him.
ls that something?
ls that a trouper?
He takes the good and the bad.
He takes all. Very good.
He wants to be in the gang.
All right, kid.
You're in the gang.
Put the heavy ones up front.
Otto wants to see you.
MAN: Right over here.
[Knock on door]
Come in.
Put some ice on that.
Close the door.
l want to talk to you
about Mrs. Preston.
l think she has seen
something in you.
l wonder if
it's the same thing l see.
l don't know.
l don't know what she sees.
Mrs. Preston has got it
in her head...
that she wants to be in court
to see the show.
Now, can you imagine
what's going to happen...
when the newspapers
get ahold of her?
Mr. Schultz is a married man.
Mr. Schultz is married?
We're all married men.
We've got mouths to feed,
families to support.
This has been a tough
son of a bitch for all of us.
Now listen.
l want Mrs. Preston
out of here, fast.
She can go to Saratoga,
see the races.
She can go to
Lake George or Hong Kong.
l don't care where she goes,
but l want her out of here...
and l'm depending on you
to get her out.
Do you want me to leave?
BlLLY: The way
Mr. Berman explained--
l don't care about Mr. Berman.
There'll be
a lot of reporters--
ls that what you want?
l want to hear it from you.
He said they're going
to ask questions.
Do you want me to leave?
lt's for your sake.
l'm asking you a question.
Do you want me to leave?
[Sighs] No, l don't.
[Door opens]
lt's polite to knock, Arthur.
Am l missing anything?
l've decided Mr. Berman
is right.
l'll be going to Saratoga
for the races.
And l'll be
taking Billy with me.
DUTCH^
ls that all right with you?
Hmm?
l asked you a question, kid.
[Whispering]
l just want to tell you...
[Continues indistinctly]
Now everybody's happy.
Mr. Schultz,
you worried about the trial?
No, l'm not worried.
l've been in
worser spots than this.
How does it feel to be
public enemy number one?
DUTCH: That's something
you made up for the papers.
l'm no public enemy.
-So, what are you?
-Public benefactor.
Then how is it
that you were arrested...
eleven times
before the age of 19?
DlXlE^ Those were all cases
of mistaken identity.
REPORTER: ls this a case
of mistaken identity?
No, this is minor stuff--
income tax evasion.
REPORTER: Are you sure
about that, Mr. Schultz?
DUTCH: That's right.
l'm no gorilla.
l never killed nobody...
and l never caused nobody
to get killed.
REPORTERS^ Mr. Schultz!
DlXlE: That's all the questions
we can take.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
[Reporters asking questions]
[Horse neighs]
BAlLlFF^ All rise.
[Door closes]
JUDGE: Court is in session.
Please be seated.
Listen, l'll handle this.
Mr. Berman told me...
Mr. Schultz owns
a piece of this hotel.
He said they've
taken care of everything.
DREW^ Absolutely.
DOORMAN^
Welcome back, Mrs. Preston.
-lt's good to see you again.
-Thank you, Charles.
-Good afternoon, Mrs. Preston.
-Good afternoon.
We're always delighted
to see you, Mrs. Preston.
Hello, Francois.
l've kept your suite
available, of course...
and if you need anything,
please don't hesitate to ask.
DREW^ Thank you.
-Mister--
-William Bathgate.
Your room is just there.
And Mrs. Preston...
[Speaking French] Give the room
instructions to the valet.
-He will handle everything.
-Very good.
Has Mr. Preston told you
we were coming?
Yes, just not this soon.
When he calls...
MAN: Good to see you again.
[Music playing]
WOMAN: Mark my words.
[Band playing dance music]
[Unlocking door]
Good night, Billy.
Good night.
[Soft music playing]
[Earrings clatter]
[Telephone rings]
[Ring]
l won't tell him if you won't.
lt ain't funny, Mrs. Preston.
You think Mr. Schultz
is an ordinary man.
You're wrong. He's not.
He's a maniac.
What we're doing...
this is how people
get themselves killed.
And what way is that?
They don't stop
to calculate the odds.
They don't stop to think.
Can you calculate the odds?
Yeah.
Yeah, l used to.
l used to think
l had a charmed life.
l was one in a million.
l had my wits.
Whatever happened,
l would be fine.
But now l've...
l've lost my wits.
l've lost my place.
[Telephone rings]
Listen to me.
You're smarter than he is
and braver.
[Ring]
And you'll live longer
if you're not afraid.
[Ring]
Oh, my poor Billy Bathgate.
[Laughs]
You made a promise
to protect me...
and l'm not making it
easy for you, am l?
No, ma'am, you're not.
[Birds chirping]
Are you awake?
Hmm?
Can you hear me?
BlLLY^ Yes.
l'm having breakfast
with the gang.
What? What?
No, no. My gang.
Here. l've written it
all down for you.
Meet me later at the track.
[Laughs]
[Door closes]
[Ring]
Hello?
Where were you last night,
the two of you?
We call,
there's nobody there.
Mr. Schultz doesn't like
that kind of thing.
ls there something
l ought to know about?
We had dinner at the Brook Club.
Mrs. Preston met some friends--
silly people, nothing.
O TTO: Not for you, kid.
Make sure she's at the track
in her box...
by the third race,
box number 50.
BlLLY: Why? What for?
Don't you know when somebody's
trying to look out for you?
And one more thing.
You don't have
to sit in her lap, got it?
[Hangs up]
Jesus Christ.
Get me the Savoy Plaza Hotel
in New York City.
Savoy Plaza?
l'd like to speak to
Mr. Harvey Preston.
Mr. Preston, you don't know me.
l'm calling from Saratoga.
[People chattering,
brass band playing]
-A club house ticket, please.
-Yes, sir.
WAlTER^ Sarsaparilla?
Yes. l'll be right back.
Thirty-five cents.
Why don't you keep the change?
MAN: OK, we got 50
across the board!
That's Election Day!
[Men shouting odds]
Thank you very much.
WOMAN^ Over here!
John, let's go over here.
WOMAN: Over here.
MAN: $50.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
[Bugle plays post]
[People chattering]
MESSENGER^ Excuse me, please.
Hey, hey, hey. Come here.
MAN:
Oh, Harriet, over here!
Take these flowers
down to Mrs. Preston.
-Mr. Wilson.
-Phil.
Good afternoon, ladies.
CHARLO TTE: All of sudden
she just popped up...
right there
in the Atlantic Ocean.
BlLLY^ l got to talk to you.
Something's gone wrong.
l think you're in
a lot of danger right now.
Don't be so melodramatic, Billy.
Mrs. Preston,
this is not a joke.
Aren't they the most beautiful
things you've ever seen?
DREW: Who do you like
in the next race, Charlotte?
CHARLO TTE: Um...
MESSENGER^
Flowers for Mrs. Preston.
[Gasps] No. Look at these.
[Gunshot]
[Crowd cheering]
DREW: Come on.
Come on.
Come on, Royal Honor.
Billy, there was something
l wanted to tell you.
Do you remember that man
who came to church?
Which man?
The one at
Mr. Schultz's baptism.
The one he respects so much.
Yes. Luciano.
l've met him before.
BlLLY: Where? With Bo?
DREW: Mm-hmm. l was drunk.
Did you ever tell Mr. Schultz?
No. You think l should have?
Go, Royal Honor!
Go! Come on!
Go! Go! Come on!
Go!
Uhh.
Damn.
WOMAN: l won! l won!
l'm going to go bet.
No, l'll do it.
You stay here.
All right.
Put $50 to win on Phantom Fox.
Satisfied?
Don't get up.
Don't leave until l get back.
[Laughs]
What if l have to pee?
BlLLY^
l'll bring you back a can.
[Sighs]
l love you, Mrs. Preston.
Carter!
WOMAN^ Hello, Drew, dear.
LULU^ What's the rush?
-l thought l saw lrving.
-You did.
MAN: Good to see you,
my darling.
Fancy meeting you here.
DREW^ l hope so. Ha ha ha!
[Dramatic music playing]
Oh, hello.
MAN^ Excuse me.
Carter.
-Drew, darling.
-Carter. Ha ha!
HARVEY: Darling!
Harvey.
Harvey, what are you
doing here?
Harvey!
For God's sake, l've been
looking everywhere for you.
l got the damnedest
telephone call.
What the hell's going on?
lt's the husband.
Come on.
You should've told us.
How was l to know?
[Car engine starts]
-What's this all about?
-lt's the husband.
lRVlNG^ Come on.
What's with
the state troopers?
l don't know.
The guy's a big shot.
The kind of stuff
big shots do, l guess.
lRVlNG^
You didn't see this coming?
BlLLY^ Sure, like l saw it
coming with Lulu.
lRVlNG: l don't get it.
She must've figured out
something.
BlLLY: Nah,
she didn't know nothing.
lRVlNG: Did she seem like
she was scared to you?
Uh-uh.
She's not like ordinary people.
She's not scared of anything.
[Dramatic music playing]
JUDGE^
Have you reached a verdict?
Yes, we have, Your Honor.
JUDGE: Will the defendant
please rise?
As to the charges,
how do you find the defendant...
guilty or not guilty?
MAN:
We, the members of the jury...
find the defendant...
not guilty.
[Crowd cheers]
[People chattering,
piano music playing]
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
-Congratulations.
[Slurps] Thank you.
-Hello, lrving, how--
-Yes. l'm good.
-Are you OK?
-Yeah.
Come on in, come on in.
-ls Mr. Schultz here?
-Yeah, he's upstairs.
l'm sorry about
what happened to your nose.
-Oh, don't worry.
-lt was an accident.
Mr. Schultz
is waiting for you upstairs.
He wants me to go up there?
Yeah, and have a good time.
Hey, look who's here.
Close the door, will you?
l like a little privacy.
Did she say anything?
Who?
BlLLY: Mrs. Preston?
Yeah, l think
that's the lady's name.
Yeah, she said
she liked you. Very much.
She said you have class.
She said that?
Well, who knows?
ln a better world,
in another time...
DUTCH: What?
They've issued
another indictment.
This time it's Dewey.
lt's the state.
DUTCH^ What is it
with this state income tax?
And if l beat that,
what's next, city tax?
And after that,
Borough of the Bronx tax?
And then Bathgate Avenue tax?
lt's not fair, Otto.
OTTO^ We'll wait this out
in New Jersey.
l'll get in touch with Hines
and work something out.
What does a man have to do
to deserve a break?
To be able to reap
the fruits of his labor?
l'm gonna get Dewey.
l am gonna get that bastard.
You can't kill Dewey.
He's too big.
l want to know where he lives...
what time
he comes out of his house.
OTTO^ You gotta arrange it
with the gangs.
You cannot just go ahead
on your own.
Otto!
Don't you ever tell me what
l can or cannot do, Otto.
You work for me.
You do as l tell you.
ls that clear?
[Door slams]
All right.
We'll be moving across the river
to New Jersey for a while.
Remember Hines?
From Tammany Hall, the fixer.
Right now he's our last chance.
There are 1 7 one thousand
dollar bills in there.
You tell him we're waiting
for an answer...
at the Palace Chophouse
in Newark.
You should've seen him
at the height of his power...
when he had a grip on things.
He was a king back then.
You never saw
the real Dutch Schultz.
A terrible thing
when the money won't flow.
l'd hoped never to see the day.
Nothing makes me sadder
than to refuse...
such a generous offer.
Mr. Hines, we need
your help with Dewey.
Mr. Dewey is a prosecutor
who wants to be president.
There is nothing l can do.
You tell Mr. Schultz...
that the business
between us is over.
Mr. Schultz
ain't gonna like this.
He's always been
very generous with you.
-He deserves--
-He deserves nothing.
DUTCH: That son of a bitch.
That goddamn son of a bitch.
What does he mean,
he won't take my money?
Suddenly my money's
not good enough for him?
He's a nothing, that scumbag.
l'll take that money
and stick it in his teeth.
Forget about him.
You got other problems.
DUTCH: Don't tell me
to forget about him!
You promised me Hines.
You told me he'd take
care of us, and now this?
ls this how good
your judgement is these days?
Listen, you don't worry
about Dewey, all right?
Dewey is as good as gone.
OTTO^ You made
an agreement with Luciano.
DUTCH^ l don't need
his advisement on this.
He drove hundreds of miles
to stand up for you in church.
DUTCH: He didn't have the
decency to break bread with me.
l don't trust that man.
O TTO:
The man is sympathetic.
Dewey's everybody's problem.
Luciano knows, the Dutchman
gets knocked down, he's next.
Meantime, l'm the one
in the frying pan!
Now, let me tell you
for the final time--
l will take Dewey out...
and Luciano and his men
will thank me for it.
Listen very carefully.
They will come and they will
thank me for it.
Mrs. Preston told me
something about him...
about Luciano.
She said that she thought
she'd seen him before.
What are you talking about?
She said--
She said she was drunk...
but she was
pretty sure it was him.
She said she was with Bo.
DUTCH: You hear this kid?
This is what l'm talking about.
This is why l say
that he is my prodigy.
Uhh!
What else did she tell you?
What else went on
with the two of you?!
-All right.
-lt's all right.
l'm fine. What?
-He's just a kid.
-l know. l'm calm.
[Sighs]
Get up.
What did l do?
That's for not telling me
sooner, kid.
BlLLY^ l tried.
l didn't have the chance.
You should've come
to me right away.
Even so, l didn't
hear the rest of you...
give me the word on
our downtown compare.
-That's not fair.
-Shut the fuck up, Lulu.
You're ugly and dumb,
and that's the truth of you.
Otto, get Dixie on the phone.
l want him over here
right away.
Right.
Fix me a rye.
Make it straight up.
DUTCH:
That conniving dago scum.
Can you tell me how
you know what he respects?
Me, l like something,
l tell you...
l don't like something,
l tell you that.
You cross me,
l fucking kill you.
Everything is clear.
Everything's above board
and honest, right, lrving?
[Telephone dings]
l see the whole world
ganging up on me.
l see the man who takes me
into his church...
the man who makes me
his brother...
and embraces me,
kisses me on the cheek...
is the same man
who turns my Bo against me.
ls that love...
or is that
the Sicilian kiss of death?
l don't care how many DA's
come after me.
Whatever has to be done,
l'll do.
They think
that l am finished...
but l will show them.
Come on, boys,
give me a smile.
Heh heh heh.
The Dutchman's
making a comeback.
What is this?
l asked for scotch.
Can't you do
one damn thing right?
But you just told me--
l'm fed up with you.
You're fired.
What?
l don't want to tell you twice.
Get out of here.
-Why?
-Know why l'm firing you?
You always want to know
the reasons for things...
always asking questions,
poking your nose...
into things
that don't concern you.
-But you--
-Always interrupting.
And most of all,
l'm sick of the sight of you.
Mr. Berman--
l don't want to hear
anymore, now beat it.
You can't fire me.
l work for Mr. Schultz.
Mr. Schultz does the hiring,
l do the firing.
Here's your severance pay.
Get lost.
O TTO:
What's the matter with you?
Can't you get it through that
thick lrish skull of yours...
that we don't want you?
None of us.
We never did.
[Door closes]
Now, there goes a kid
with luck.
HlTMAN: Get him, Charlie!
[Grunting]
Don't say a fucking thing.
[Screaming]
-l heard shots!
-What's going on?
Somebody call the police!
Come on.
All right, move it!
[Car starts]
HlTMAN^ Go, go, go!
-Get down!
-Uhh!
Uhh!
Dixie?
What the hell'd
you bring him here for?
Dixie, what's going on?
What's the matter with you guys?
You double-crossed him.
You sold him out,
you son of a bitch!
Ohh! Uhh!
Bravo, kid.
DlXlE: Tell these guys
to get rid of him.
What's the matter, Dixie?
He was at the chophouse.
He's a witness.
Sorry, kid.
What are you gonna do
when he crosses you...
like he did Mr. Schultz?
-Don't worry, he won't.
-No?
Why don't you ask him
about the money?
What money?
He was sitting
on 5, 6 million in cash.
We didn't come across anything
like that, did we?
Lucky, we've been
all through this before.
They were broke.
They didn't have the money
for payoffs or for salaries.
What about the safe, huh?
Otto Berman had a safe.
l took a look inside.
lt was empty.
There was nothing in it.
That's not true. l saw it.
lt was full of cash.
DlXlE: He's lying. You gonna
listen to some punk kid?
He's nothing, nobody.
All he did was sweep up.
They never let him
near the money.
How come Mr. Berman
gave me this?
[Struggling]
Here, here.
This is a lot of money.
Dixie, if you're
holding out on me...
it's not the right way to start
a business relationship.
Maybe we ought to have
a little talk.
Charlie, Pete.
Lucky.
Lucky, l told you the truth.
Don't worry, Dixie.
This won't take long.
What am l gonna do with you?
You got brains, you got guts.
l like that...
but Dixie's right.
You know too much.
So, what am l gonna do?
But maybe l know
a few things, too.
For instance, l know
where Bathgate Avenue is...
l know where
you buy your cigarettes...
and l know the laundry
where your mother works.
l guess it all evens out,
don't it?
Take care of yourself, kid.
Can l have my money?
Sure. Why not?
l'll be looking in on you
from time to time...
just to see how
you're getting along.
Remember that.
Hey, kid, you want a ride?
No, thanks. l'll walk.
[Car starts]