Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Subtitle by: D.Sync
dsync89@yahoo.com
Black Christmas
* Silent Night music playing *
Hey, who leave the god damn
front door open?
Oh, by the way how come I was the only
one there working today?
We were there the whole
afternoon, Barb.
A likely story.
How does it look?
***
You got your Santa costume ready?
Yeah ...
What time the little bastard
arrive?
- At one o'clock.
- Terrific.
Hello?
Pardon?
Who?
Barb, it's to you.
Long distance.
Oh, great.
I'll take it in the other room.
Could you guys shut up in there?
I can't hear a damn thing!
Hello!
Mom, hang on, I can't hear you.
Operator, I can't hear ...
what's coming from the other end. Can you ...
No, we just having a little party.
No, I had a couple.
Oh come on,
I'm not drunk.
No, no ...
I had some stuff I had to do
in the afternoon ...
And then I was just gonna get
the 720 train to the city.
Oh come on, you got
to be kidding ...
Why can't I come too?
Who the hell is he?
Good night.
See you next week.
Hey call before you come,
I have to get my parents ...
I'll just get a couple of
my friends and we'll go.
All right.
Yea sure I'll be fine ...
I'll see you around.
Hey, Chris, wait up,
I need a ride.
Put the christmas music back on.
Who wants to go skiing
for two days?
Yeah, sure, Barb.
My mom has a house in Mount Valley.
Who else wants to come?
- Yea, sounds like fun.
- Great.
- What about you Clare?
- No thanks Barb, I made some
other plans.
I'll get it.
Hello?
Hello!
Hey, quiet!
It's him again! The monnah.
Powikszy some options among
listed repertoire.
This is a person?
No, Clare. That's the Mormon doing their
annual obscene phone call.
Shh ...
/ You big cunt ... you big cunt ....
/ Let me lick it ... Lick it ...
/ Lick it ...
/ You big cunt,
/ pretty big cunt.
- Not bad.
/ Fuck my juicy cock /
/ I'll come over to you and you can ...
/ suck it ... suck it ...
Listen you pervent! Why don't you go over to Lambda-Ko?
They could use a little of this.
/ You big cunt, you want my fat cock ...
Why don't you go find a wall socket and stick your tongue in it,
that will give you a charge.
I'll stick my tongue up
your pretty pussy ...
You fucking creep!
I am going to kill you.
Well, super-tongue strikes again.
Fastest tongue in the west.
It's sick byo ...
I really don't think you should provoke
somebody like that, Barb.
Oh listen, this guy is minor league.
In the city I get two of those a day.
Maybe.
But do you know a town girl was raped
a couple of weeks ago.
Darling ...
You can't rape a townie.
You really are too much,
Barb.
Come on, this is a sorority house,
not a convent.
I'll see you later.
I'm gonna go pack.
Come on, Clare, she
didn't mean anything.
No, really Jess, it's okay.
I have to finish packing anyway.
Doesn't she had enough trouble sitting in here
without you getting at her all the time.
Come on.
I know professional virgin when I see one.
Hey, I can't get my hands out here.
Speaking of professional
virgins ...
Here we have, the queen of bozes.
Where have you been?
I have been shopping. You know how the
store is most spectacular at this time of year.
Mrs. Mac, come on to the other room, we got a
surprise for you.
Where have you been?
Me and Maxine has been looking
all over for you.
Oh, little puss ...
Okay, let's see ...
Claud?
Is that you, puss?
Kitty ...
Who is that?
Who is it?
Claud?
Dear, girls ...
This is really beautiful.
It's really lovely.
Come on Mrs. Mac, put it on.
Put it on? Oh come on I'm
not going to bed.
Come on, please.
Put it on.
Anything for you girls because
it's Christmas.
Okay, girls, party is over.
Let's get this junk clean up.
Oh yea, come on, everybody takes a little
something and it won't take long.
Come on, that's it girls.
Just a little cooporation.
- Let's just get you out.
- I'm tired.
Good night.
Booze.
There you are ...
Good night, good night ...
Merry Christmas!
Jess, you girls are just
too good to me.
Oh nonsense, Mrs. Mac.
Hello?
- Hello, is Jess there please?
- Yes, wait a second, Peter.
Jess, it's for you.
It's him.
Hello?
Hi, how's the party?
It was good.
Too bad you couldn't make it.
I had been practicing for four days straight.
I am really wiped out.
Jess, dear ...
You won't forget to put off the lights.
You've got to find some time.
I've got to talk to you.
You sounds funny.
What's the matter?
Nothing is matter.
I just want to talk to you.
Why don't you tell me now?
Because I want to talk
to you face to face.
Jess, I haven't been to bed in three nights.
And it's not the mood to be playing games.
Look, Peter, we'll talk
about it tomorrow, okay?
- Okay, I'll be in room 30 all day.
- Alright, I'll see you around 14:00.
I'm just terribly exhausted.
- It's okay ... I love you.
- I know.
- See you tomorrow.
- Yes, goodnight.
Clare?
- Oh, thank you.
- It's okay.
Sorry, I should have been keeping a better
watching at them.
- I think so.
- I said I was sorry.
Excuse me...
I hate to bother you, I can
see that you are busy.
But I wonder if you can help me?
You see, I'm suppose to meet my
daughter here at 1 o'clock.
It's half past now, and
she's still not here ...
Here name is Clare Harrison,
do you know here?
Clare Harrison?
Yeah ... I think so ...
I know she lives in a sorority house.
It's called the ...
... Pi-Kappa-Sigma.
Oh, of course.
Kappa is a sister sorority.
Some other girls were over here today,
but I haven't seen Clare.
The place isn't far, I will tell you
how to get there.
Ho, ho, ho ... shit.
Santa, please.
Look she's suppose to me going with me
for this weekend, dammit.
Well we decided that we'll go skiing
for a few days.
Yeah, I've been looking forward to this
for three weeks. Bitch.
Isn't Santa naughty?
Ho, ho, ho ... fuck.
I just don't know, Mr. Harrison.
Her clothes are all packed and ready to go.
I'll take you to the common room.
They are having a party today for underprivileged children.
Yes, I know.
I am very disappointed in
this atmosphere.
I intend to do something about it.
Who is this?
Oh, that's a friend of Clare.
Very nice young man from the town,
Chris Hayden.
I didn't sent my daughter here to be drinking and ...
... picking up boys.
Clare is a good girl, Mr.
Harrison.
I wouldn't want you to get the wrong idea about that.
She is a good girl.
I am sure you will find her
in the fraternity house.
In fact I could show you the way.
I have to go to a store near there.
If you wouldn't mind
giving me a lift.
I know where it is.
I will be glad to
give you a ride.
This is very kind of you, Mr.
Harrison.
I'll just get my bag.
"I didn't sent my daughter here
to be drinking and picking up boys."
Tough shit ...
I was supposed to be responsible ...
... for the moral of every girl
in this god damn house.
The leaning tower of Pisa
if they can get up there.
I'll do my best ...
I don't know what the bastard
expect of me.
For Christ sake ...
Claud?
Is that you, Claud?
Here kitty, kitty, kitty ...
Come on Claud. Come say
goodbye to mommy.
Is that you, Claud?
Jesus, Claud.
Look what you made me do!
And let's ...
Come on Claud, here kitty, kitty, kitty ...
Come on Claud, I got to go!
Here, kitty!
Damn it Claud,
you little prick!
This is very kind of you ,
Mr. Harrison.
I think I will get out of here ...
What?
I am pregnant.
Jessica, that's fantastic.
I don't want it.
You don't want it?
No. I want to have an abortion.
You can't made a decision like that.
You haven't even ask me.
I wasn't even going to tell you.
Jess ...
I want us to have a baby.
Peter, I can't ...
Oh Christ, Jess.
Don't you ever consider anyone but yourself?
I've thought this out very carefully and
I know what I'm gonna do.
Do you know how important this
afternoon is to me?
Yes I do.
Why don't you just get out of here.
Jess!
I want to talk to you tonight.
There is nothing to discuss Peter.
- I think there is.
- I'm not going to change my mind.
We'll see. Will you be there at 9 o'clock?
- Yes.
- Okay, I will see you tonight.
Yes, dear.
I am sure there is nothing wrong.
Yes, I just been talking to
a friend of hers.
She's going to call her out for me.
Yes, if we don't have any luck
I'll go to the police.
Well I don't think I'll be able to go home tonight.
It's a bit late to head out now.
Good-bye, dear.
Hello?
Hello!
Oh hell, not again!
/ Billy.
Billy?
I'm sorry, you have the
wrong number.
/ Do you know what a
mother should do?
/ Where did you put the baby?
You got the wrong number ...
/ Where did you put the agnes, Billy?
Look I'm telling you, you have
the wrong number!
Hold it, hold it ...
Jesus ...
Could you just give it to
me one at a time?
Well what the hell are you
planning to do about it?
You ... Shut up.
You know, for a public servant
I think your attitude really sucks.
Shut up.
Now, Mr. Harrison, if you convinced that
your daughter is missing ...
... you can fill up one of these forms.
I don't know if there's any consolation, but
90% of the time girls who reported missing from the college ...
... they're out of campus somewhere
with their boyfriend.
Thanks, but that's not much of a consolation.
- Oh ... - Let me help you.
- Thank you dear.
You know we got to get Mr. to fix this door.
I must had called that son of a bitch a hundred times.
Mrs. Mac, there was another one
of those calls just now
What about it, dear?
It was weird.
Some woman screaming ...
... then a man wailing.
Clare Harrison father was here today.
Really? I'm sorry I didn't
get to say goodbye to her.
Well, you still might. Clare didn't
meet him where she was suppose to.
I thought she was over to
the fraternity.
Here, you have ...
And let it lean Mojesz.
Excuse me.
Could you give me the number of
the sorority house? Please.
Yeah, sure.
It's a ...
Fellecio ... 2 0 8 8 0
What?
Fellecio. It's a new exchange.
FE.
So now I know what it mean ...
How do you spell it?
Capital 'F', 'e', little 'l', 'l'
'a', 't', 'i' 'o'.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
Chris!
Break!
Hi, what's up?
- Do you seen Clare today?
- No, she went home.
No she didn't.
No one knows where she is.
Are you serious?
I thought maybe she was with you or
at least you might have heard from her.
No, not since last night.
Her father came to pick her up at 1 o'clock
today and she didn't show.
So he went down to the police
station with Barb.
What happened?
- They didn't take it seriously.
- Why?
I don't know.
Probably confused that with
someone where you leap.
Well um.. She is out for Christmas holiday,
but ...
... there was a bad practice over at the
highschool this afternoon.
when not wrcia home, her call
the best przyjaciki, Melody,
but there is no one knew.
She is only 13 years
old, Lieutenant ...
My husband is a trucker and
he is out on the road,
So I came over here.
Is it really so unusual for
her to be just a few hours late?
Oh yes, she should have been home at noon.
We are going to buy a present for her father.
Nash, you stupid son of a bitch, you got
a big goddamn mouth!
What the hell are you talking about?
- Hi Chris, how is your brother?
- Can I talk to you?
What's up?
I want to know why nothing is being done about
Clare Harrison being missing and ...
... And why does... this idiot getting away
with saying the things he does?
You are a friend of Clare Harrison?
Yeah I have been taking her out.
This is Jessica, she live
in the same sorority house as Clare.
Alright, come on in. Sergeant,
put me the file on the Harrison girl.
And take care of this.
Try to eat something, Mr.
Harrison.
You know, starving yourself isn't
going to help the situation at all.
No, thank you very much Mrs. Mac, but
I just have no appetite.
I feel I should be doing something,
but I don't know what.
Why don't you just try to
stop worrying.
The best thing you can
do is stay right here.
If only I knew what
he was doing.
Did you know ...
It's very little known fact, but ...
... did you know that there is a certain
species of turtle ...
There is a certain species of turtle.
That can screw for
three days without stopping.
You don't believe me, do you?
Well, I mean how can I
make something like that?
Barb, dear, I, I, I ...
No, really ...
They just three days ...
24 hours a day, for okrtk,
up, up, up ...
Can you believe that?
Three days?
I'm happy if I
get three minutes.
Do you know how I know this?
Because I went down to
the zoo and I watch them.
It was very boring.
Actually I didn't stay for the
whole three days.
I went over and I watch the zebras, because
they only takes a few seconds.
You think it's my fault
don't you?
Barb, stop it.
Don't shit me. That's all what you all thinking.
Why not just come on out and say it?
You think that I drove her away, and if
she is dead you're gonna blame me.
Barb, for God sake ...
If that's all what we all thinking why isn't
someone just come right out and say it?
Barb, you have too much drinking.
... Mr. Harrison
I don't give a shit out of Mr. Harrison!
I'm sick and tired of everyone in this house
enunciating stuffs and not coming out with what they mean.
Barb, why don't you go upstairs and
lie down for a while.
Shut up.
And you leave me alone. Damn you.
You think it's my fault that you
have been employed all this afternoon.
Barb, you are drunk.
Go to bed.
Yea, sure ... ... fine.
- Any news?
- Yes, where Mr. Harrison?
He's in the dining room.
- We won't be long, Mrs. Mac.
- Alright, dear.
- Phyl, Phyl ...
- Yes?
- I'm sure Clare will be alright.
- I hope so.
I just want to tell you that I'm going to
go to my sister's for the holiday so I,
I might not be here
when you get back.
Well, that's okay. Just check out on Barb
before you leave, could you do that?
- Of course, I will.
- And you take care.
We'll give you advice, Mrs. Mac.
Mrs. Quaife and Mr Harrison have
asked me to extend their thanks to you ...
... for coming out this cold night to help.
Mrs. Quaife has told us that Janice
most likely came through this park,
... on her way home from school today.
So the first thing we will do search the park.
When I tell you, I want you all to assemble
at the south edge of the park,
with your assigned officer.
Then we'll just walk through the park.
Spread out evenly.
/ Are not distracted.
There will be two sets of dogs leading the way.
Just spread out
and follow them.
George, stay out from the franks.
Now if any of you find anything, I want you to send
someone out immediately to report it to me.
Is that clear?
Are there any questions?
Okay, lets go.
* Mrs. Mac singing *
Alright ... I hear you!
Claud?
Where are you?
How did you get up on
the attic, Claud?
Shit ...
Oh right, God damn it,
You can wait.
Claud, are you up here?
Jesus Christ, I don't see how it
could be up here ...
Claud.
Jesus, Claud ...
Now look at what you make me do.
Jesus ...
I've got to clean this place up one of these days.
Claud?
I can't see a damn thing.
Claud... God damn it, Claud,
I'm going to have you fixed.
Hey!
Anybody there?
I'm gonna have to split. Peter is coming
around and I'm late already.
- It's cold.
- We'll coming home soon too.
I am freezing.
- We'll let you know if there is anything happen.
- Bye.
Jess? Is that my baby?
Please wait ...
Jeeeess!
Hello?
Who is this?
What do you want?
Why are you doing this?
Who are you?
For God's sake, what are you doing?
I know what you did, Billy!
Stupid Billy!
Billy! Billy! Billy!
Stop this!
Jesus Christ, Mrs. Mac?
Mrs. Mac! Are you home?
Mrs. Mac, are you up there?
Yes, hello?
I had been getting obscene phone calls, and
I want to know what can be done about it?
Yes alright, I'll hold.
But only for a moment.
Peter, Jesus,
you scared the hell out of me!
Why don't you say something?
Yea? Well, . ..
You scare the hell out of me too.
What's all the yelling about?
I have been upstairs
having a little sleep.
Hope you don't mind, but
I'm got a little cold up there waiting for you.
- Sorry, I was late, Peter.
- Yeah ...
Clare Harrison is missing. I was out
with the search party looking for her.
Yes, hello ...
I want to report something.
No, I don't want to hold!
- How does the recital going?
- How do you think it went?
Peter, what kind of a
game are you playing?
I thought you wanted to talk.
So why don't you quit attacking me and
we try to have a rational adult conversation?
Yes, now stay on the line.
Calm down, lady.
Let's have the story.
Oh yea? What's the address?
Number 6, Belmont Street ...
How many calls?
Ringing your operator?
Oh yea ...?
Well, miss, we're very busy here.
There has been a child
murdered in the park.
I do not know when we will be
able to are the classes.
Probably just one of your
boyfriend playing a little joke.
Yea, I'll report it and
tell them as soon as possible.
I'm sorry, miss.
Jess, what's wrong?
A little girl was found murdered
in the park.
What?
The search party that was looking for Clare
found the little girl murdered.
And Clare is still missing.
Clare is alright.
Is she?
Listen Jess, I know
that you are upset.
But I've got something to tell you.
I'm leaving the conservatory.
- Peter ...
- Well just hear me out.
Will you hear me out, please?
I live in one room for 8 years
and I'm tired of it.
I'm tired of having to line up behind six people
everytime I want to take a bath. I'd had it.
I am quiting the conservatory and
we are getting married.
Well, say something.
Do you remember when we first met?
You told me about you wanting to
be a concert pianist.
How it was your greatest dream.
And I told you about some of the
things that I wanted to do.
I still want to do those things.
You can't ask me to drop everything
I've been working for ...
and give up all my ambitions,
because your plans have changed.
Be realistic, I can't
marry.
Sure you can.
What is it change?
We could be married and you can still
do anything that you wanted to do.
Peter, I don't
want to marry you.
Alright ... What about the baby?
- I didn't want to bother it with you sir.
- Oh you didn't.
No .6 Belmont Street,
that's where you daughter is?
Yes it is.
A high school girl has been murdered.
Mr. Harrison's daughter is missing.
And now that the house where she lives
keep getting out obscene phone calls.
Don't you think we have
to look into it?
Well, lieutenant, I guess ...
Sure.
Thank you, lieutenant.
Yea thanks, lieutenant.
Sergeant Nash.
Could I speak with you
for a minute?
Yea, sure, Lieutenant.
What's this?
That's the number of
the sorority house.
- "Fellecio"?
- Yea, a password wywoawcze.
You don't understand?
Yea. "Fellecio." One of the girls that was
in here afternoon gave it to me.
- She gave it to you?
- Yes.
Nash, I don't think you could pick your nose
without written instructions.
I know. Something dirty in it.
You selfish bitch.
You're talking about killing a baby
as though you are having a  ...
Now can you see why I
didn't want to tell you.
- What the hell are you trying to do to me?
- What are you doing to yourself?
Jess ...
Let's get one thing straight.
You are not going to
abort that baby.
Peter, you're not going to tell me
what I can and cannot do.
- If you are going to get an abortion ...
- I think you better leave ...
- If you are trying to get an abortion ...
- I said get out.
You are going to be very sorry.
Hi, Peter.
I'll get Jess.
- Jess, are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Any more news?
No, but there are some people here to
see about the phone calls.
Jess, this is Lieutenant Fuller.
.. I'm sorry ...
Graham, Bill Graham.
- Do you today will be present in the house?
- Yes.
I would like to put a tap on your phone, but
I need your written permission to do that.
Okay.
Okay, Bill, go ahead.
I would like to see Clare Harrison room.
- Where is the telephone.
- There's one in the living room on the hall.
Clare's room is up here.
- How many girls live in this house?
- Okoo ten.
Hey, this is Bill Graham, 6 Belmont Street,
working on the line 5596114th
Great.
This afternoon I got a call from a woman
and I thought it was a wrong number.
But then she start to
screaming at me.
Who was the last one here to
see Miss Harrison?
- I think I was.
- When?
Last night, about 22.30.
- Is this the way she left her room as far as you know?
- Yes.
- What is this?
- We are having a party last night.
- She drink a lot?
- No, hardly at all.
Does she have any emotional problems?
No, not Clare.
Who is she seeing besides
Chris Hayden?
- With no one.
- You sure of that?
So you seen a lady the last
time this morning?
- Last night.
- Right, last night.
- Has anyone seen her this morning? - No I didn't.
- All the others girls are gone for the holidays.
- Can I get a list of their phone numbers where I can reach them?
- Sure. There is one on Mrs. Mac's room.
- Who is Mrs. Mac?
- She's our house mother.
- Is there anyone in the house right now?
- Yes, another girl, Barbara Collard.
She is upstairs asleep.
She is not feeling too well.
- Is she the one that was at the station today?
- Yea.
Yea well... Let her sleep.
Were there any deliveries yesterday, or was
anyone working in the house, anything like that?
No, I don't think so.
Mrs. Mac would know.
- Is all the sisters number on this list?
- Yes.
Graham, how is it going?
You about finish?
Yes, what I've done is I've
tapped this phone so that when it rings
It will rings at the station too.
At the same time I'll be at the phone company
checking out on the location of the source of the call.
Are there any other phones
in the house?
- Yes, the house mother has another one.
- But it's on another number,
and nobody is calling.
You're gonna have to keep this guy on
the line as long as possible.
We got a mechanical system here and
it takes a while.
I know it's not very pleasant.
Girls, can I show you something?
- See the car outside?
- Yea.
We got one of our men in it, so you
got nothing to worry about.
Yeah ... sure.
About Boe ...
I just know Clare is dead.
I can just feel it ...
Come on now Phil,
we don't know that.
Poor Mr. Harrison, I feel
so sorry for him.
Hey, hey ...
- How's Chris?
- He's okay, you know Chris.
I'm sorry, Jess.
I guess I'm just exhausted.
I've been taking these pills from my cold
and they knock me out.
Will you be okay if
I go up to bed?
Yes, of course.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, go up and get some rest.
- Call me if there is any news.
- I will.
Thanks.
So, are you all okay?
Okay, sure ... yes.
Yeah, look, I'm gonna need
about 10 more minutes.
Now be sure you tell those people again that
they got to keep this guy on the line.
Right.
We will certainly look into that.
Thank you very much.
Graham already at the
switching station.
When a phone rings at the house there,
this phone ring too.
Great, thanks.
- Lieutenant, someone from Scarborough.
- Okay.
Barb, what's the matter?
Easy, relax,
you'll be okay.
I guess ...
I guess... I had a nightmare.
I dream this stranger was
coming into my room.
I guess this is why they
give me asthma huh?
Don't take it too serious, it's alright, Barb.
Just relax.
Hey, it's just me, Billy.
It's alright, all right ...
Shh ...
Pretty Agnes ...
Don't you tell what we did,
Agnes ...
Jean!
- What?
- Jean, get the children
in the car.
- What's going on?
- Please, just get them
into the car.
- Okay kids, let's go.
- Come along children, hurry.
Miss, miss ...
Thank you.
Merry Christmas.
There was a little girl murdered over
in the park tonight
Yes, I heard.
Your phone's ringing.
- Oh yes, excuse me. Good night.
- Certainly. Good night.
Testing.
Bill Graham.
Trace call coming in on ...
Hello?
Who's there?
No Billy, no!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Oh my God ...
Hello?
Jess, we didn't get him.
There wasn't enough time.
You'll have to keep him on the line longer.
Oh I see.
When you said: "Oh my God",
did you recognize something?
No, I just feel like
it's getting to me.
When he called before, did he used
more than one voice like this?
Yes, yes, he did.
He used several different voices.
Jess I'm gonna ask you, who was the guy that
was just leaving when I arrived in your house?
- My boyfriend, Peter.
- Everything fine?
Jess, I'll have to call you back in a little while.
Are you alright?
I'll call you back in a little while and
we'll go get him next time.
Bernie, call a doctor.
I let no son of a bitch ...
trespass on my land
in the middle of the night!
And I don't care what
kind of uniform he wear!
- What the hell is going on here?
- He fired on a police officer.
You god damn right!
I'll do it again too! The bastard was trespassing!
If you think it was Peter, then why
don't you just tell the police?
Well because I'm
not really sure.
Well he should be stopped.
Whoever it is, it should be stopped.
I didn't even have a minute sleep around here.
There has been so much noise in the house.
What the hell was all
that yelling about?
Barb has a asthma.
She's having a nightmare.
- Is she alright?
- Yes, she's fine. She's sleeping now.
He repeated almost word for word what
Peter said to me tonight.
- Could it be just be a coincidence?
- Oh God, Phil, I don't know.
I was so confused.
Oh look Jess, I really don't
think it could be Peter.
You know I don't like Peter much, but I
don't think he's got sick.
I don't believe Peter would do this.
He's so gentle most of the time.
Oh God Phyl,
you know I'm really getting scared.
Look, are you sure that cop is
still out there?
Yep, he's there ...
Hello?
Jess?
Yes?
(Whisper) It's Peter ...
Look, Peter,
Don't cry.
We can straighten things out, there
is nothing to get so upset about.
It's Bill Graham.
You want me to trace that one?
- Yea, try and get it.
- Right.
Jess, we can't do this ...
Peter, where are you?
Please, Jess ...
You got to know how I feel for the baby ...
Don't do this.
Jess, don't hurt the baby.
- Stop this, Peter.
Please, tell me where you are.
Shit ...
I'm sorry, the call
just not long enough.
Yes?
Jess, Lieutenant Fuller.
You want to tell me what's that all about?
You listen to that?
Yes. What did he mean about
killing the baby?
Jess, it's important that
you tell me.
I'm pregnant.
I told him I didn't want to have the baby.
When did you tell him this?
Today.
Just today?
You're sure?
Yes.
"We can't kill the baby", that's
a strange way of putting it.
Peter is an artist.
Neurotic, maybe?
No, normal like a
lot of people.
Jess, are you telling
me the truth?
I've got a feeling you are
holding something back from me.
Now I don't want it to be Peter.
But if it is, he needs help.
Do you know what I mean?
The sooner the better.
Think back ...
Was Peter with you any of the time since
you got one of these calls?
Yes ...
Yes he was here. He was at the
house tonight when the first call came.
That's right, it couldn't
be Peter.
Phyl, it couldn't be Peter.
He was here.
He's obviously upset about something.
I'd like to talk to him.
Can you tell me where
can I reach him?
He lives at home Bakerw.
But when he gets like this, he usually goes on to the
recital hall at the music Conservatory.
Look Jess, if you get any more calls,
you're gonna have to keep him on the line longer
You're not giving us enough
time to get a trace.
I'm trying, you know
it really upsets me.
- No, right, of course. Look, you're doing fine.
I'll talk to you later. - Okay.
- Thank God.
- I know it couldn't have been Peter.
Well, what can I tell you?
We covered the entire campus area ...
and working our way towards the lake now.
Where do we go from there?
Start them out from the south end of town, have them walk
through way to town, then from house to house.
Jess, you want one
aspirin or two?
- Two please.
- Okay!
Jess! Jess!
What are you doing?
Some kind of
search party.
Sorry to scare you miss, but we
are with the search party.
What do you want?
Well we wondered if you see
anything peculiar tonight.
Not until you got here.
Phyl ...
Well, they scared the
shit out of me.
Sorry miss, but you do know that there
was a girl killed in the park tonight?
Yes, we heard.
We are just helping the police to look
for the killer.
Well we would like to ask you in.
But our dog died last night.
We don't want to bother you at the time
like that.
We were just wondered if you
notice anything suspicious here tonight?
Oh no, sorry.
Well, you just keep your doors and windows locked
and you will be safe.
- Thanks a lot.
- Yes we will.
And remember there might be others from the
search party around.
So don't be afraid. We'll be around
seeing that you are safe.
- Well, Thank you.
- And remember to lock those
doors and windows.
Already I will this murderer.
Seriously, are you sure
all doors and windows are closed?
Nash!
Get the dean of
administration on the phone.
Tell him I want all the records on
the Peter Smythe, a music student.
And have a car meet me out front.
Barb? Are you awake?
Phyl!
Are you there?
Hello?
/ You bitch pig.
/ Billy! / Billy!
Lieutenant!
The guy is on the phone again!
/ Billy!
/ Where is Agnes?
/ Agnes ...
/ Mommy?
/ Where is your baby?
This is Graham. It's
140, terminal 55th
Lieutenant Fuller.
Yes, Nash. What is it?
A phone coming is on the other line, sir.
They say they got a trace on this one.
Yea let's have it.
He says the calls are coming from
No 6, Belmont Street.
For Christ sake, Nash, you got it wrong.
That's where the calls are going in to.
That's where they are
coming from too, sir.
Oh shit ...
Jennings ...
/ Jennings ...
Jennings, where
the hell are you?
Nash ...
Nash!
Yes, sir.
Look, I can't get through to Jennings.
I want you to call the girl.
Nash, be calm.
Don't tell her that the guy is in the house.
Just tell her to put down the phone and
walk straight out the front door.
I'll be there in 5 minutes.
Nash, if you blow this
I'll kill you.
Phyl!
Phyl, where are you?
Please answer me.
Hello?
Who is this?
It's Jess.
Miss Bradford, this is
Sergeant Nash.
Are you the only one
in the house?
No, Phyl and Barb are upstaris asleep.
Why?
Alright, now I want you to do exactly what I
tell you without asking any question, okay?
No questions.
Now just put the phone back on the hook, walk through
the front door, and leave the house.
What's wrong?
Please, Miss Bradford, please
just do as I tell you.
Okay. I'll get Phyl and Barb.
No, no, don't do that,
Jess!
Jess, the caller is in the house.
The calls are coming from the house.
Jess!
Jess, get out!
And don't go up there!
Don't go upstairs, Jess!
Miss Bradford!
Miss Bradford ...
Barb ...
Phyl ...
Phyl! Barb!
Please, answer me!
Phyl, Barb! Please
answer me!
Jess ... Jess!
Are you alright?
Jess, are you in there?
Jess ...
Jess, is that you?
Jess, are you in there?
Jess, why didn't you
answer me?
Why are you hiding there?
Jess, you had me worried.
What are you doing up here?
Jess ...
I knew it. I knew it in
my gut that it was that kid.
Why would Peter start
killing people?
I don't know.
He must have made the calls after each murder.
How long do you think it will take before
I can talk to her?
Just a couple of questions.
- What time will her parents get here?
- A couple of hours.
I'll stay with her until it all ends. But the condition that she's in,
I wouldn't count on talking to her before tomorrow afternoon if I were you.
Did someone notify
Patrick Cornell?
- Who?
- Phyl's boyfriend.
It's okay, I will do it.
Lieutenant, I think we got to take these bodies to
the morgue in Lincoln Ville.
The hospital doesn't have facilities to
handle these bodies in one time.
Well, tell the coroner,
they can start the autopsy right away.
I'll notify the parents
for identification.
Yes, sir. I think that's wrap up everything
around here sir.
State labs guys will be here
in about an hour.
Reporters, sir, and television news guys are
taking up pictures.
Get them hell out of here.
Tell them that speak to them
at the police station.
Okay, people, please to d.
Yes, the girl's father is upstairs,
but he can't attend you.
Would you keep it down please,
we got a sick girl in here.
He is in shock.
He got to go to hospital.
You will be alright,
Mr Harrison.
It's me, Billy ...
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org