Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Who's that?
Where you going, huh?
Wait...!
It’s you, isn’t it?
What happened?!
Help!
What the fuck is going on?
I know you’re here!
- You don’t even know my name!
- No. I know your voice!
Just say one more word!
I dare you!
Your dead friend
said the same thing!
Don't let them leave!
Do not let them leave!
You idiots!
- Let’s go!
- You fucking jerks, stop them!
Come back!
Get back here!
That's it! That's it for you!
Ladies, no more food for you!
Every day we go without food,
one of your men will die!
We collect from now on!
You missed!
He's dead!
What’s going on?
Where are you? Where are you?
- Are you okay?
- Just go get the food.
They told me a man was killed.
I... I killed him.
Now there’s gonna be a war.
They’re going to want revenge.
We’re gonna barricade our doors.
We’ll use our beds like they did.
Whatever you say.
I’ll get the food.
Oh, shit!
- Barricade it. Barricade it!
- You got the door?
- Two beds!
- So fucking what...
if send the women there twice a
month? We'll get fucking fed!
Stand it up!
Barricade the thing!
What I suggest we do is we find
out who killed their leader...
and offer them up like
a peace offering.
- We don’t know what they’re gonna...
- In exchange for food!
They have a stock pile!
We’re in a state of war.
- And we started it.
- Yeah, exactly.
And I suggest we find out who killed
the leader, and we offer to the...
Look! Look!
If they won't give us food,
I say let's get it ourselves!
- I agree!
- Then, let’s go!
Okay, I think he's right.
If anyone's willing to go,
I think you should raise your hand.
That’s about the most ridiculous
thing I've ever suggested.
How about,
Whoever doesn’t wanna fight...
simply slip away right now,
and no one will know you were here?
And for those that are left, gather
around me, and we'll make a plan.
Here. Here.
Okay, how many of us are there?
- One.
- Two.
- Three.
- Twelve.
I can see twelve of us.
- What?
- She can see?
Don’t touch my fucking bed!
- What are you doing?
- What?
- I heard something!
- Someone’s here!
- Who’s there?
- I heard somebody!
I have a chair over here.
If anybody could happen...
Let’s go, come on!
Grab the person in front of you.
Stay in a tight group!
Alright.
Straight ahead.
What...
If we go back!
We can’t go back! Come on.
Let’s move!
- What’s that?
- Smoke.
Fire!
Don’t push!
It’s okay! It’s okay!
Stay there!
I’m gonna come in get you.
Upstairs.
Watch!
- Here. Here I am. Hold on to him.
- They’re going to shoot us.
Guards! Guards!
You see what is going on?!
Guards!
We’re free!
It’s empty.
Go on in.
- Step up.
- We’re in a shop.
Everyone, please, stay together.
I don’t wanna loose anybody else.
Step up. All right.
I’m gonna go look for food.
- I’ll go with you.
- No, I can do better on my own.
Stay here and look after each other.
It’s something you can do better.
Get out!
This place is occupied!
There are other groups out there.
Do not leave this spot.
I know you can do it.
But how can you carry the
food back on your own?
Is there anything?
Is there running water?
I'll look for bottles.
- I guess there’s electricity.
- No.
Are there any signs that
people can still see?
What's happening?
I miss you.
I miss you so much.
Here’s a supermarket.
I’ll go in.
- Okay.
- Step up.
I’ll stay here.
I know my place.
Stay off my fucking spot!
I'm coming back! I'll fucking kill
you! You stay off my fucking spot!
Give it to me, you thief!
You thief! You thief! Give it back!
Hey! Hey!
I can here you near
my fucking spot!
Go! Go! Go!
What do you have there?!
What are you eating?!
Smells like meat!
- No! No!
- Stop!
Let on!
It’s me! It’s me!
Go! Go! Go!
Okay.
Are you alright?
Are you okay?
Okay. Okay.
- I have... I have to stop.
- Stop. Stop.
Stairs.
- You’re all right. You’re safe.
- Thank you.
I’ve go back and get those clothes
before I forget where they are.
Here, eat something.
I’m just trying to say...
people screaming out loud...
that God is hiding...
that we failed and
that God is punishing us.
This is not what is happening. God,
it’s not. This is not the God’s way.
What is happening to us reminds
me of what happened to St. Paul.
Paul used to kill Christians,
used to persecute them...
but the Lord came to
him and converted him.
And not only converted him,
but blinded him.
This is what's happening to us.
- Here!
- Here I am!
Here.
Here, I have a jacket.
- I have a jacket.
- Thank you.
That’s terrible.
- Who would do that?
- Someone who went blind.
And then he went crazy.
Since he couldn’t see...
he didn’t want his statue to see.
- I don’t think so, little man.
- I don’t know if it’d be possible...
for a blind man to paint
the painting like that.
- Yes, they could.
- Or likely a priest...
who saw what happened,
and had a crisis of faith.
No, but seriously, all those people
made me think of how lucky we are...
that we have a leader with vision.
So, I think it’s up to you to
decide what we should do next.
Well...
I think we should stay here tonight,
try to get some sleep.
And then, tomorrow, I was thinking
that we could go to our house.
It's pretty near here,
and it's big...
so it can accommodate everybody.
Where are you, dog?
Still there?
No. Don’t follow that dog.
He’ll lead you to a fire hydrant.
Too proud to be a seeing eye dog.
Twenty seven.
Five four.
Black hair.
Brown eyes.
I don’t wanna know
what you look like.
But how can we know each other?
I know that part inside
of you with no name.
And that's who we are, right?
When you went to look for food,
we talked to this man...
that was part of a group
that moved around together...
trying to find food and shelter.
Each night they slept
in a different place.
I asked him why he didn't
sleep in his own home.
And he said he didn’t know
where it was anymore.
- Yeah, he lost it.
- They're welcome to it...
if they can find their
way to my little room.
I think it’s okay. Here we are.
Here we are. Looks fine.
Come in. Come in.
I can’t believe it.
It’s exciting.
Okay. Careful. Just because
the door was locked...
doesn’t mean that no one’s here.
Hello! Hello!
Hello! Is anyone here?
Maybe we should take
our shoes off. Right?
That’s a good idea.
You can leave them by the door.
We don’t wanna mess the place up.
We just arrived.
If you wanna take off
your clothes too...
we have plenty of
clean ones upstairs.
- Thank you.
- Are you talking to me?
No, to everyone. Our clothes
are just as dirty as our shoes.
- Here? All together?
- Come on!
She’s the only one who can see!
If it makes you feel better,
it’s getting pretty dark.
All right.
If you insist.
I'm sure you've seen worse
sights than this old body.
I want you to feel at home here
because this is your home now too.
Thank you both. We're all flattered
that you would offer your home.
It's our pleasure.
Kick us out when you had enough.
Or when I become
too much of a burden.
Just tell me, and I’ll just
wander off like an elephant.
- You’re not an elephant.
- I’m not a man, either.
- You’re plenty of a man, babe.
- I...
I don’t know.
I haven’t seen myself in so long.
I must look ridiculous.
No, no. Dirty and skinny.
But not ridiculous. Not at all.
- And what about me?
- You’re beautiful.
Yeah. Not like you.
- You’ve never seen me.
- But in my dreams you’re beautiful.
How come you never appeared in my
dreams but I know you’re beautiful?
Well, that’s why blindness
is a gift to the ugly.
- Come on, you’re not serious.
- No...
but I suppose I was
more beautiful before!
We were all more beautiful before.
Is anyone cold?
- It feels so good!
- I'm having a great time!
Hello?
It's me.
- I brought you some hot water.
- Oh, thank you.
- I’m gonna pour it down, okay?
- Okay.
- Feels good?
- Feels good.
I hope we can find
the boy's parents.
What do you hope for?
Nothing is more ridiculous than
the desires of an old man.
Tell me. I wanna know.
You wouldn't understand.
- Why that tone of voice?
- What tone?
That one.
What I hope is that we
can go on living together.
- As we are. Like this.
- Blind?
For me nothing has been better.
- I’d want us to live together.
- Together with me, or with everyone?
Don’t make me say.
I want to know.
Are we alone?
Is anyone listening?
Good.
I wanna live with you.
I remember that New Year’s.
It was cold, but I didn’t mind.
All right. At this end of the table
we have pees and carrots.
At the center we've olives in a bowl
and some crackers on a small plate.
And, at the far end of the table,
we have anchovies.
Anchovies!
Don't we have a special bottle of
something sparkling for our guests?
There's nothing like water.
Clean water.
I'd like to propose a toast.
To our family.
- To our human family.
- And the dog!
- And the dog! And the dog!
- Salute!
Much better than any champagne.
I see you.
When I touch you like this,
I see your face.
So beautiful.
It's all I need to remember.
- Tell me, is this working?
- Let’s see. You take another one.
Take another of me in the face.
Blind inspiration.
There’s coffee,
if anybody wants some.
- I’ll have some, please.
- I want some too.
I need to wake up.
Honey? Honey?
I think we should get together
and talk about what we need to do.
There’s not much food left,
and I'm worried about security.
- Okay.
- I can pour it for you.
It’s hot.
It’s you.
It’s you! Oh, my God!
It’s everyone at here.
Hi.
- What?
- I can see you!
- What are you saying?
- What?
- Yes.
- What are you talking about?
- Everything is beautiful!
I can...
- What?
- Oh, my God!
- What do you mean, you can see?
- Hey, you! I can see you.
I got back my sight!
- What is it?
- Come here.
- I can see!
- How?
- You’re lying.
- What?
- Really?
- You have your sight?
- Yeah!
You’re kidding!
- You’re eyes!
- Nice to meet you.
- Oh, my God!
- He can see!
- I can’t believe it!
- He sees! He sees!
- I thought he was kidding!
- No.
- Hey, you guys!
- What this mean?
I can see everybody’s face!
- Oh, my gosh!
- I know. I can’t believe it!
I can see you. I love you guys!
You guys are so beautiful!
At that moment...
the same unspoken thought
occurred to everyone,
"He was the first to go blind.
Perhaps...
we will all regain
our sight in turn. "
So the celebration was
not entirely selfless.
The next days,
the next weeks...
would therefore be
sleepless with anticipation.
They would see again.
This time, they would really see.
But who would be so timid...
as to cling to this
blanket of blindness?
Who would be so
foolish as to fear...
that its intimacies might be lost?
And what of this woman...
who is now so strangely silent...
who has borne such a
terrible weight...
and is now so suddenly free?
Already she could imagine the
voices of the city, shouting,
"I can see!"
"I'm going blind", she thought.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org