---------------------------------------------------------------------
Bounce (2000)
Imdb: http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0186894/
---------------------------------------------------------------------
Releases:
1080p brrip
fps: 23.976
---------------------------------------------------------------------
Audio:        English
Subtitles:    -
CD:           1/1
---------------------------------------------------------------------
Subtitle:     SRT
Language:     English
---------------------------------------------------------------------
Translated by (unknown)
Subtitles  by (unknown)
Modified   by .donaldus. (re-sync)
---------------------------------------------------------------------
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Hey,Jim, you ready
for your Christmas present?
We're now the biggest little ad agency
on the West Coast.
- Oh, we got it back?
- Yeah. I pitched. They caught.
We closed. We got the Infinity Airlines
account for the next two years.
- They love us. Yeah.
- This is great, Buddy.
I thought he was gonna
give me a corsage.
Thought he was gonna
kiss me right there.
- did he sign?
- Yeah, I got the signed contract
in front of me. I'm looking at it.
You want a quote? He said,
''I can't see why we would ever leave.''
- Buddy, this is great.
You did great, man. You did it.
- Yeah.
Yeah, no problem.
I'm on the 6:00 flight.
I think I'm flying free for life.
Hey, Buddy, you really
came through on this one.
- Well, what can I tell ya?
- That's some Christmas present.
No problem, man. All right.
I'll see you in a bit. Bye.
Is it supposed to snow
like this all night?
Thank you for your patience
this snowy holiday season.
- If you have not met--
- Shit.
O'Hare is hell with runways
and a couple of TCBYs.
- L.A.?
- Yeah. Why? Does it show?
I-- I think I, um, flew out with you
on Tuesday. Ron Wachter.
- Oh, yeah, yeah. Buddy Amaral.
- Hello, Buddy.
Good to see ya. I don't know. I've seen
worse. I think we'll get out of here.
- Good.
- Hey, Buddy. You made it out.
-Janice, I was gonna call you.
- Yeah, I was gonna hold my breath.
Nice talking to you.
- So did we like your dog-and-pony show?
- Well, what can I say? You know?
- Love at first sight.
- Mmm, lucky us.
- So you on the 6:00?
- Yes, I am.
-Just about to push it back.
- No.
- Mm-hmm.
- Goddam it.
Well, time for a drink?
Yeah, that's why they called me in
on my day off. Drinks with the freight.
So next time? Yeah? I'll call ya.
Whatever.
Oh, sorry. Sorry. It's this bag.
- I don't know where I am.
- It's all right, man.
You got your whole, uh,
Let's Go.: Europe thing happening there.
It's-- I understand.
Eurail pass, yogurt...
get stoned, see the Anne Frank house.
- Sorry?
- Sit down.Join us. Have a drink.
- Hi.
- This is Mimi.
- We've known each other
for, uh, what? Five minutes?
- I think she's bored with me already.
- Well, thanks. Sure. Why not?
The line at the snack bar
is like an hour.
Let me guess. Uh, English teacher?
- Let me guess. Agent.
- Advertising.
- It's like agenting without the heart.
- What? Am I that much of a cliché?
Hey, don't look at me.
I'm just sitting here eating nuts.
- And I'm not a teacher. I'm a writer.
- A writer?
That's what I started out at.
Couldn't make a living.
- I write for TV.
- TV, huh?
So, that, uh,
''I'm so much better than you'' look...
I saw on your face when
I said advertising, I must have,
uh, must have imagined that.
- Maybe on his face you imagined it.
- I got nothing against advertising.
- It pays me, I guess.
- That's right. It does.
- What-- What do you do again?
- I told you I'm with
the National Organ Center.
- I'm in development.
- You got to love that.
I mean, she's in organ development.
Can't, uh--
She has this whole great speech on here
that David Crosby gives, actually...
about, uh, transplants and stuff.
It's pretty, uh, pretty compelling.
I write plays too. That's what I was
doing in Chicago. A play of mine opened.
- Oh? Good for you. Where?
- Yeah? What TV shows?
Oh, it was no big deal.
It was a little theatre.
Oh, I'm here again next week.
I love plays. What's it called?
No, it closed. It closed.
Um, it was a limited-- It was--
It's called Lilacs in the dooryard.
I wonder why we have plays any more.
Hello. We got movies.
Check a movie out.
You know what I mean?
Hmph. Not in here.
- Yeah.
- What's a ''dooryard''?
It's from a Whitman poem. ''When lilacs
last in the dooryard bloomed.''
Well, yeah, I mean--
What is a dooryard?
Oh, look.
They just put sandwiches out.
Oh, great. Okay.
Oh, man. Another line.
You know, I think I'm actually
gonna go check on my flight.
- You guys want me to check yours?
Where ya headed?
- Great.
- Yeah.
- Dallas.
- Dallas?
- L.A.
- Oh, yeah, L.A., me too.
- Okay. I'll just be back in a minute.
- Thanks a lot.
- All right.
- And, uh, thanks.
- You don't know what a dooryard is.
- I--
This is what it is.
You have no idea. You--
Oh, this Greg guy
better stick to writing TV.
Did you read this review?
Boy, they don't like something,
they don't keep it a secret, do they?
- Oh, here he comes.
- Hey, we thought we'd lost you.
So you're still on for 1 0:00.
They say it's gonna take off.
- Nothing for Dallas yet.
- Oh.
Yeah, it'll be tomorrow
at the earliest.
Bet the airport hotels are swamped.
Hey, you know what? Why don't you take
this hotel voucher? Room's guaranteed.
I'm gonna stick around here
and see if something opens up.
- Oh, what? You took a bump?
- Hey, you know.
Two coach tickets, anywhere
in the U.S. or Mexico, plus 200 bucks.
I did this show down in Mexico, and
I promised my kids I'd take them, so--
- Well, 200 and coach? It's--
- What? I should have haggled?
Oh, he's pulling your leg.
You did great.
Tell my wife that. Abby.
I just gave her the good news.
Turns out I was supposed to work the
Christmas tree lot with Scott tomorrow.
I forgot.
It's a father-son Cub Scout thing.
- You have any pictures?
- Yeah, sure.
- Oh, she's pretty.
- Isn't she?
- Yeah.
- Our neighbour Donna and Abby.
They went to the mall and
did these glamour photo things.
- How old are your boys?
- Scott's seven and Joey's four.
- Oh, he's so cute.
- Say hello.
Oh,Jesus. You're not taping over
the Crosby speech, are you?
Oh, relax. I fast-forwarded.
Crosby's fine. He's there. Okay?
Here you go. Say something
for the transplant, uh, kids.
Well, uh, save a life
and become a donor.
Do what David Crosby said.
What did David say?
Uh, ''Sorry I drank.
Thanks for the liver.''
We-- We are here, for one thing, to
celebrate the opening and the closing...
- Oh, no, please.
- of the new play,
When Lilacs Something On The dooryard.
- Right. That's it.
- And we're here with the author, uh--
- Greg.
- Greg--
-Janello.
- And I want to say that the critic
for the Chicago Weekly Times...
- is an idiot and an asshole...
- You read the review?
and wouldn't know a good play
if it punched him in the face.
- And, Abby, please, forgive him, huh?
- Infinity Airlines...
- Yeah, please.
- is pleased to announce...
- He did it for you...
- whoever you are.
- I did. I love you.
- the boarding of Flight 82
to Los Angeles.
- Uh, that's me.
- First-class passengers--
- Well--
- I'm gonna go to the men's room.
So it was great meeting you guys.
Thanks for, you know, nuts and...
- Yeah.
- everything.
- You too, man.
- Yeah.
- Nice meeting you.
- It was nice hanging out
with you guys, okay?
- All righty.
- Hey, good luck getting,
uh, wherever you're going.
You too. Good night.
See ya.
Well, if you ever get to Dallas.
Hey, Greg. Greg!
- Hey!
- Go sell a Christmas tree for me.
- What?
- Go ahead. Take it.
No, I-- I want the layover,
if you know what I mean.
You know, Mimi, organ development,
video camera. Think about it.
This is incredibly generous.
I just wanted to say that.
It's a comp. It's free.
Take it. It's fine.
Oh. Oops.
- Hey.
- Hello, sir.
- I really appreciate it.
- Look, man, you're doing me a favour.
- You're saving my marriage.
- You hear me?
- You have no idea.
- Take care of yourself.
- Thanks a lot. All right. See ya.
- All right. Take it easy.
- It was great meeting ya.
- Your ticket?
You know what?
You just took it.
What?
- Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the final boarding call...
- Still have that, uh, hotel voucher?
for Flight 82 to Los Angeles.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the final boarding call...
- Don't you just love air travel?
for Flight 82 to Los Angel--
Can I get you something else, sir?
Something to drink?
What? Sorry.
Can I get you something to drink?
Some coffee, soda, water?
Oh, no, thanks. I'm fine.
- E-mails--
- Ever since America--
- What time is it?
- We're here at
the O'Hare Airport Sheraton...
- where friends and family
of passengers of Flight 82...
- Something happened.
have gathered to await bulletins
from Infinity Airlines.
Now, once again,
if you arejust tuning in, about an hour
and eight minutes after take-off...
Infinity Flight 82, the last flight to
take off from O'Hare before it closed...
disappeared from
radar screens over Kansas.
Now this has not been officially
confirmed by Infinity...
but we're hearing reports
from Marysville, Kansas...
that a crash site
indeed has been found.
Hello? Mom, what is it?
Is something wrong?
Chicago.
No, he's coming back tomorrow.
What--
What?
Oh,Jesus. They said Infinity?
No, no, no. Okay,
he's-- he's-- he's not taking that.
I spoke to him. Mother, stop it.
Will you put--
Will you put Les on the phone, please?
Just put--
Oh--
Les, what's the flight number?
Oh, thank God.
No, he's not on that flight.
He's coming back tomorrow.
He-- He hasn't even left yet.
Tell her--
What is she saying?
Because he probably doesn't know.
He's in an airport hotel or something.
Listen, I'll-- I'll call you
as soon as I know anything, okay?
I just don't want to tie up the--
the phone right now.
Okay.
Now with 56--
Aviation sources tell us that
in an air disaster of this magnitude...
those aboard the plane,
208 passengers and eight crew members...
would be unlikely to survive.
Witnesses near the scene,
some 7 5 miles northwest of Topeka...
report seeing a huge fireball
seconds after impact.
We are looking now at pictures
of the field--
- Hey,Janice.
- Oh, God, Buddy!
- I knew three girls on the crew,
and the co-pilot was my friend.
- Yeah, listen.
We got a problem, okay?
The roster's not right.
- Oh,Jesus.
- You got to get into the system.
- Can you do that?
- Who was he?
J-A-N-E-L-L-O. Greg Janello.
Was he on that flight?
Thank you.
Okay, so, um, Flight 31 ?
That's leaving when?
Okay. Thank you. Thank you.
Okay. See? Now you can relax.
- I just wish he would call me.
- Yeah, well, he's asleep.
You don't get news reports
when you're sleeping.
Come on. Drink this.
Then I'm gonna go home.
And if you need me,
I'm just across the street.
Don't you have anything better
than this to eat? I'm so hungry.
- I want something bad.
- Mama?
- Hey, what are you doing up?
- Can I watch TV?
No, silly-billy.
Ya can't watch TV.
Now come on.
Let Aunt Donna tuck ya right back in.
I'll take care of him.
Oh, my big boy!
What time is it in Chicago?
It's 9:00.
Jesus Christ, Donna.
Where the hell is he?
- I don't know.
- Hey.
There is someone at the door.
Mrs Janello?
- Are you from the airline?
- Yes.
I'm Kevin Walters,
and this is Ellen Seitz.
- Um, ma'am, the reason that we're--
- No. He's-- He's taking a later flight.
When's the last time
you spoke to him?
Um, well, last night
at about 8:00.
Uh, 8:00.
That's 1 0:00 p.m., Chicago.
We have conflicting manifests.
One of them--
We can't tell yet
if it's accurate or not--
One of them lists your husband
on Flight 82.
No, see, I know he got-- he got--
he got bumped. He's on a later flight.
Um, we have a crisis centre at LAX.
That's where the first news will be.
Okay.Just a minute.
- Nope.
- Okay, okay. We're gonna go together.
- And Jack is gonna watch the children.
- Donna. Do not cry.
- please do not cry.
- I'm not crying.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are making
our final approach into Los Angeles.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
- So this flight was okay?
- Well, it landed.
- Yeah.
- You know, that's good. How ya been?
Okay. How you been?
Those poor people.
It's terrible.
Mrs Janello. This--
Oh! Oh, no! Don't touch me!
Don't touch me! Don't touch me!
Stay away! No!
- You want a drink?
- Uh, no, thanks.
Infinity's already called. They want us
to help out with damage control...
TV spots, print, you know.
Yeah.
Weather conditions there
improved somewhat this afternoon...
allowing for the removal of several
sections of the downed plane--
So you might want to go easy
on the drinking.
- I don't want you hung over.
- Along with the aeroplane's
data recorder...
which was located
and retrieved earlier today.
- So first thing tomorrow, okay?
- The fuselage section--
- George, line three.
- Got it. Thanks.
- Yeah, take down the blue ones.
- They're waiting on ya.
- Hey, Dionne, where's Jim?
- Yeah.
- No, they're all in a meeting.
-Jim?
- Conference room.
- Hey. What is this?
What happened to six months trying
to create a consistent, you know,
brand image in the public eye?
Who okayed-- What is this?
This is dog shit.
Buddy, come on. It's just
giving families numbers to call, okay?
- It's not like tomorrow's ad.
- Hey, weren't you supposed
to be on that plane?
No, I, uh, stayed over another night.
What do you mean, tomorrow's ad?
- I think you want
to recut the commercial--
- That's Todd Exner, damage control.
- please, people, um--
- Infinity.
- We don't have a lot of time today.
- I'll be brief.
I want to thank you all for your ideas,
but, uh, I'm gonna recommend...
to the board that we go
with the concept that, uh,Josh
and Sharon have been working on.
That's Karen actually.
It's based on a wire photo
out of Chicago.
I'm gonna need someone to lock down
the rights on this pronto.
Is that a joke?
You gotta be kidding me.
You're not gonna run
this sentimental, self-serving crap.
- Excuse me?
- I mean, who cares how
Infinity Airlines feel?
Who gives a shit?
They crashed the plane. So what, right?
Uh, happens all the time.
They'll do an investigation.
The FAA in ten months will say
it was a hydraulic line...
or a fuel line or a rudder
or something, right?
I mean, shit happens.
It happens to TWA. It happens to Delta.
It happens to United. Why are we gonna
take responsibility for bad luck?
I don't think we want
to hide our heads in the sand.
plus, you don't originate campaigns.
Okay, Karen? Neither do you,Josh.
We all do, together.
Buddy, this is not about
running the ball around you.
Okay, let's get on this, all right?
I want to fax a copy
to the board by noon.
USA Today, New York Times,
Chicago Tribune, L.A. Times.
Okay? Come on. Let's go.
She was the little girl who won prizes
for her art in grade school...
swam on her high school team...
married her college sweetheart
and started a family.
While the people of Infinity
mourn the loss of Carol Wilson...
flight attendant...
the people of Clayton, Missouri,
mourn the girl they grew up with.
Hey, Buddy. Look, I can cover you for
like five months of staff meetings...
but not six, okay?
Will you call me, please?
Carol, who told friends...
¨¨When you fall down,
get up and try again. '¨
Who said, ¨¨When it's dark outside...
it's up to us
to look for the light. '¨
Boy, kind of makes you wish you crashed
more often, doesn't it, Todd?
There are 2 1 6 stories of our friends
and family on Flight 82.
This one is Carol's.
And this year's winner for
the best national campaign is...
Tang-Weller-- client: Infinity Air,
the ¨¨We Remember¨¨ series.
- You sit down.
-Jim, what are you doing?
- Sit down.
- No,Jim. It's my account.
- It's my account.
- please.
- Can't you control this idiot?
Next year. Next year.
Congratulations.
Uh, this is terrific. Thank you.
Thank you for this award.
It's great.
Uh, boy, it's so heavy.
That's what you're
supposed to say, right?
That and, uh, ''Oh, this is
what it looks like up close.''
It's, uh-- But thank you.
This is great. Uh--
It's good to see all of you.
It really is.
'Cause I've been, uh-- I haven't
been around much this year and, uh--
You know--
See, I was supposed
to be on that flight.
Yeah.
It's ironic, 'cause I could have
been one of those people who--
who believed so much in
Infinity Airlines that they were...
glad to die just so it could show
how well it handled it, really.
You know, isn't that
what we're sayin'?
''Hey, we crashed,
but we're hurting...
and we're humble, and, uh,
we're ready to sell some tickets.''
All right. Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Um, thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
Shame about the dead people. It's an ill
wind, but it blew us right onto the map!
please. Come on.
It's fine,Jim. I'm fine.
All right. Get off me.
No more. No more.
So is there a party after?
Now that you're done with rehab,
what's next? Uh, meetings, counselling?
No, I'm good. I'm fine.
I just want to get back to work.
You know what? You should take
your time. I mean, we're in good shape.
How could you be in good shape?
I've been gone for 90 days.
Hey, hey, you've been gone for a year,
since the crash, but who's counting?
- You look good though.
- Yeah.
- Think it'll take?
Hmm? Feeling good?
Good.
Ah, here.
Two floors, 24,000 square feet.
Uh, employee and client parking, and
within one block we have two banks...
a Kinko's and
a couple dozen Starbucks.
- Oh, what's the rent?
- No, no, no, we buy.
I've already got a deal with the owner.
You know, he wants to get out
of the landlord business.
Old guy, not very sawy. He'll do it
for 1 .8 and without a broker.
Wow. Sounds great.
When do I, uh--
When do I get to see it?
That is assuming, you-- you know,
you want my input.
Look, it's gonna be great, Buddy.
You're gonna love it.
Don't fight it because
you were out of the loop.
I-- I know, man.Jim, come on. It's
great. It's fine. It's gonna be great.
- Oh.
- Okay?
Just--Just excuse me
for a second.
Sure you want to do that?
Whoop!
Wrong drink. It's mine.
It's apple juice.
Right.
Uh, you don't want to stare at me
like that in the men's room.
It's sexual harassment.
Are you kidding? I'm not gay.
No, but I am,
and you are my boss.
- At least, officially so.
- Since when?
Since about a week after
they shipped you to palm Springs.
You had some sort of a breakdown
during an awards ceremony?
Or that-- That's what I heard.
It wasn't a breakdown, okay?
It was an episode.
- What do you do here exactly?
- Uh, p.A. Office floater.
I work with the computers mostly.
Would that have been your first drink
since they released you?
Boy, you got some nerve, kid.
Relax. I'm a drunk too.
Six years sober. AA and NA.
- We hired you?
- Well, I had to sign
a no-episode clause, but yeah.
Look, if you want some help with
your reentry, I'd be happy to oblige.
Just, you know, don't screw up.
There's a lot of really
nice people working here,
and why should they pay for your shit?
'Cause I own 20%% of the company.
And in case you were picking pimples
when they covered this in your rehab...
alcoholism is a disease.
Yeah, yeah, they--
You can catch it from open bottles.
You're not gonna make me feel guilty
for something I had no control of.
Oh, oh, you're--
you're that type. Cool.
When was the last time
anything was your fault?
I don't believe this guy.
Did they do AA up where
they dried you out? You know,
the whole 1 2 steps, all that jazz?
Yeah, yeah, they tried,
but I don't believe in God.
He'll be crushed when He finds out.
You're not gonna last
a week sober.
- Fuck you.
- Welcome back, Boss.
Hey, pS, you're fired.
Livin'in the middle of the ocean
With no future, no past
And everything
that's good right now, well
I don't wish for it to last
I'll step through brilliant shades
Every colour you bring
'Cause this time, this time, this time
Is finejust as it is
And today is whatever
I want it to mean
Today
Is whatever I want it to mean
Yeah, hey, hey
Ooh, hey, hey
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah
- Hello?
- Uh, just a minute.
Okay, come on. Get in here.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
- Hi. Hello.
- Hi.
I'm sorry. I just had to,
uh, put the dog in the bathroom.
Hi. I'm Abby Janello,
Vinegrove Realty.
Buddy Amaral, just driving by,
saw your sign.
You know what? Actually
the dog's not supposed to be here...
but, um, my friend who was
supposed to-- to watch him--
he can't be left alone--
she has a doctor's appointment.
Everything's fine and then,
involuntary urination.
Well, I hope the doctor
doesn't keep her waiting.
No, the dog.
Oh, right. You're kidding.
That's very funny.
- Well--
- This is a wonderful property.
It's, uh, Buddy, right?
Are you interested?
You want to check it out?
You know, it'll just take a minute.
Sure.
Um-- Sorry. The last, uh, person
I showed this to smoked.
- ...in coffee prices should the bad
weather continue in South America.
- Um-- Oh, crap.
Uh, there's been a lot of interest
in this property.
Turn down the news.
That's better, right?
Um, okay. Well, here is the set-up.
And there's my card.
Um, that beeper number's actually--
Ow! I'm-- I'm actually between beeper
numbers at the moment, so, you know--
-Just ignore that. Um--
- Maybe you should let him out.
So, um, what, uh--
what line of business are you in?
What's his name?
- The dog. What's his name?
- Fred.
You know what?
He-- He-- He doesn't like people.
And he's not trained,
because I've only had him a year.
Hey, Fred, it's okay.
Hey, Fred, Fred. Come on. Got ya, Fred.
See? I'm great with dogs. Fred.
Rottweilers are great.
I had one when I was a kid.
Fred, good boy. Here you go. See?
Yeah. Um, you know what?
Actually, do you mind coming back?
Oh, my God. My-- My boss is--
My boss is coming right now...
and, uh, well, I think it would be
better if you came at like noon.
-I'm sorry. Is something wrong?
-I didn't say it was a Rottweiler, okay?
I saw you-- I saw you
with the dog outside.
That was half an hour ago. You said you
were just-- you were just passing by.
I was. I was passing by
half an hour ago.
I went to a meeting,
and I came here.
I swear to God if you say one more word
I'm-- I'm gonna open this door.
All right, calm down. Whoa.
All right, hold on.
All right. Y-Y-You don't understand.
Everything's fine, okay?
- Easy. Easy, Fred. Fred! Fred!
- Get out!
Fred! No, Fred!
- Buddy! Stop it!
- Lady! Lady!
- Buddy! Buddy! Stop it!
- I'm just lying here!
- I'm not doing anything!
- Not you! The dog!
- Buddy! Come on! Buddy!
- Dog? What? Ow! My leg!
Come on! Let's go! All right.
- You told me the dog's name was Fred!
- Sorry.
- Damn it!
- My God!
- I probably pissed him off
calling him Fred.
What was I supposed to do, you know?
You can't go around telling a client
that they've got a dog's name!
- Are you all right?
- No, I'm not. Look at this.
Look at the jacket, the pants.
I didn't see a licence on the dog.
Does the dog have a licence?
Oh, my God, please.
You don't understand.
I cannot lose this job, okay?
If you cause trouble, I-- I-- please!
You've got to let me take care of it.
I got him about
a year ago for my boys.
They like him. It's just--
It's a lot of work, and-- I don't know.
I think they think of him as
a consolation prize for their father.
He, um-- divorced me last year.
Well, we-- we divorced each other.
Oh.
I didn't do it to bribe them.
I swear.
I just thought that, you know,
it'd be a good distraction.
Worked better on Joey,
'cause he's only five.
Yeah, I was almost married once
myself a couple of years ago.
- Really? What happened?
- Oh, I don't know.
Some couples are lucky.
Some aren't.
Yeah. We weren't so lucky.
Greg used to, uh, write for
this TV show called The Midnighter.
Did-- Did you-- Did you ever
watch that? It was syndicated.
He wrote some episodes.
I mean, I mean, he still, you know,
writes episodes 'cause he's on staff.
You only took two puffs
of your last one.
That's 'cause I don't really smoke.
Yeah, well, last year
I started chewing the gum, you know?
Because my friend Donna--
She was trying to quit smoking.
And she found out that the gum
was soothing to the nerves.
So I started chewing it,
then I got hooked on the gum.
And then I got TMJ from the chewing,
so this is just to get me off the gum.
I'm ten days off the gum.
Sounds like a good plan.
Next week you'll be on heroin.
- Oh, God.
- Hey, mister.
- Hey, mister, it's ready.
- See?
- Oh.
- An hour or less.
- Look at that.
Um, listen, when you--
When you get the bill, you know...
for having the pants rewoven,
I want you to send it to me.
There's my number. I'm serious.
please. please. Not a discussion.
Thank you.
Oh.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
Come on, babe.
Well, it was nice
to meet you and Buddy.
You, uh-- You weren't really interested
in seeing any property, were you?
Copies. Sign's still up there. And
you launched into your whole spiel...
- Okay. Okay. I know.
- and the dog and I--
I'm sorry.
- It was nice to meet you.
- Yeah, you too.
- Take care.
- Bye-bye.
Oh, for God sake!
What the hell did you eat?
- The thing about heroes
is they demand more--
- Yeah,Judy.
Tell Karen that the-- the colour
on the GMC animatic is way, way too hot.
And before we test, I want
to go non-announce on the VO.
Keep-- You know, get the guy
who did Southwest for us last summer.
- You-- L-Listen to this.
- In the tradition
of the great GMC truck--
Yeah. Okay? Not that.
Come on, you guys.
Get it together. Oh.
Hey, Scott, I said lights out.
I mean it.
- Hello.
- Uh, hello. Uh, is this Abby Janello?
Uh, yes, this is--
this is her-- she?
- Uh, this is Buddy Amaral.
- Oh.
- You know, the guy from the strip mall.
- Mm-hmm. Of course.
Um, did you-- did you get
an estimate on the pants?
No. don't worry about the suit.
I-It's business, right? Listen.
My firm, Tang-Weller,
we're, uh, we're relocating here.
We're trying to get out
of this building, and our current
realtors aren't quite cutting it.
I thought, you know,
maybe you could help us out.
Me? Uh, you know what?
I don't, uh--
We have about 7,000 square feet here.
We need about three
or four times as much.
To buy, not to lease.
Somewhere under two.
- Can you do that?
- M-Million? Two-- Two million.
Yeah. What do you think?
You know, why me? You know,
I honestly don't have the experience.
'Cause you're hungry.
You'll try harder, you know.
I'm hungry because I suck, okay?
You know what? Let me put you
in touch with Norma, because
she's really the one that handles--
You know-- You know, I just--
I would rather that, uh, you did it.
And could you come by the office
around 1 0:00 on Monday?
And it'd be great
if you had two or three properties
to show us right then, you know?
Same area.
Venice, Santa Monica, Marina del Rey.
And there's one property
in particular that I'd like you
to show us on Abbott Kinney.
- 1 8385--
- Uh, hold on one sec.
1 8385 Abbott Kinney.
The seller is primed.
In fact, he doesn't even
have a broker, so, who knows?
Maybe you can book
a double commission.
I can give it a shot,
you know, but, uh--
Great. I'll call you
at your office tomorrow
and fax you over the specifics--
- Say thank you.
- What?
- What we're looking for.
- That kind of thing.
- Say thank you.
- You okay with this?
Uh, uh, yes. Yeah, sure.
It's fine. Thank you.
Great. All right. Good night.
- He wants to give me some business.
- I'll bet.
Yeah, yeah, I know. I know.
But when do you need it by?
Hi. I'm Abby Janello.
I'm here to see Buddy Amaral.
I'm early. Should I just
sit down or-- Oh, sorry.
- Okay, well, it's on its way.
- Excuse me. Hey.
- Abby?
- Oh, hi.
Hey.
Gee, I hope you're not getting too
optimistic. You're, uh, packing already?
Oh, no, there were-- Uh, there were--
there was a problem with this.
Uh, the matt job.
I don't think they were acid free,
which is key for matting.
You should always make sure
that your matts are acid free.
Otherwise, you'll, uh-- you'll--
- Have acid.
- Exactly.
Well, I read through
the materials...
that you faxed over about your set-up
and your business here and, uh--
Oh, I-- I don't know
much about advertising...
if you don't count Bewitched.
Well, we got our share
of twitching noses here...
but with our drug intervention
programme, that's on the decline.
-Joke.
- Oh, that's very funny.
- Did you find any properties?
- Yeah, I, uh--
I have three besides
the one that you mentioned.
- The owner gave you the listing?
- Yeah, but I had to promise him...
that I'd get a higher price
to make up for the commission.
Um, there is an offer for 1 .8,
but it-- it seems fishy.
Yeah. Look, you know what?
When you bring it up to Jim,
just say you found it.
- Who's Jim?
-Jim's my partner.
partner and boss, sort of.
Remember Larry Tate?
He doesn't always like my ideas. Uh,
I think if you said it was yours just--
- Oh, I don't know. I don't know
if I'm so comfortable with that.
- No, it's fine. Believe me.
- Ah, you must be--
- Abby Janello, Vinegrove Realty.
- You must be Larry.
-Jim.
Jim. I'm pleased to meet you.
Ah. Well, hey,
any friend of Buddy's.
Um, so you two guys
met at palm Springs?
- No. No, I--
- Well, should we get going?
Is your car outside?
Uh, yeah. Listen, I've got the, uh,
meeting with the attorney at 1 :00...
so we should probably
take two cars.
Okay, um, I'll drive us,
if that's okay with you.
Uh, sure. Great. I just have some papers
in the car that I should--
- Or we can just meet you
out right out front?
- Okay.
Don't, uh, mention palm Springs.
- It's supposed to be anonymous.
- Oh, right. Oh, right.
And-- And-- And you made
a Larry Tate crack before I came in.
No.
Half an hour maybe.
She's got one more space to show me,
so I should be there before--
Ah, shit. No.
Not this building.
Oh.
Buddy. Can I speak with you?
I do have other--
- This is the building.
- Oh, you think so?
No, no, no. This is the building,
the one I want. The photos?
Oh. I gave her the specs.
I guess there's only so much
inventory on the market, huh?
I wanna kill him.
I mean, we had a deal and now
he goes and gets himself a broker.
Look, we can't let her show us this.
We gotta get out of here
before the broker shows up.
Hey, Abby, when's the, uh,
seller's broker showin' up?
Um, I'm-- I-- I'm the seller's broker.
It's my listing.
Look, I understand
your disappointment...
but the seller
was bound to get some advice.
No one would let him
do a deal of that size without
a broker or a lawyer or someone.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
And how did he happen
to, uh, find you?
Um, I approached him. Look, he's gonna
list it 2.1 . That's still under market.
He was gonna sell it to me for 1 .8.
Well, say you go in at 1 .9,
what were you putting down?
Well, we were thinking of, uh, 30%%
of 1 .8 at a fixed eight and a half.
You'd be tying up a lot of cash
for a commercial property.
I mean, I say you go in at 20, 25, at
the most, and free up some of that cash.
Thirty percent of 1 .8 is what?
540 K.
I say you go in at 20%% of 1 .9.
That's 380 K.
Meaning we finance
1 520 at seven and three-quarters,
and I can source that cheaper for you.
That's, um, 1 0,880 a month.
That's a $ 1 ,200 difference.
- You can pass that on easy.
- I don't know.
Are you, uh, waiting for me to offer
to kick in some commission?
Well, this is an easy deal for you.
It's not like you had to knock around
for six months to find it.
Okay, one point.
That's a cheque for 20 K at escrow.
But that's it, you know, because he can
get 2.1 if he waits even two months.
But, you know,
whatever you want to do, so--
Well, thank you for your time.
All right, all right. Bring her
by my office, and, uh, I'll sign it.
- Thank you. Yes, I will.
- Mm-hmm.
Wow. How long you been doing this?
Oh, my God. I don't even know
where the words came from.
I did feel terrible
about lying though.
Oh, you didn't lie.
You just didn't tell the whole truth.
Yeah, well, like I tell my kids
that that's called lying.
My God. Norma is gonna die.
This is so out of my league.
I always got the feeling...
that she gave me the job out of pity,
you know, my divorce and--
Well, maybe this will
get you off strip mall patrol.
God, wouldn't that be great?
Um, so, why did he think
that we, uh, met in palm Springs?
Is he mixing me up with
a girlfriend or something?
Hmm. I don't know.
I might have told him you were a friend
of a friend.Jim doesn't like realtors.
I'm the salesman, you know? He doesn't
like salesmen. I like salesmen.
Greg had a thing
against salesmen too.
He wouldn't let Scott sell
chocolate bars for the school...
'cause he didn't want
his kids selling anything.
I mean, he still doesn't.
And now I am. It's funny.
Okay, so, um, do you just
want me to write this up here or--
- Yeah, that's fine.
- Okay.
Um, thank you. I owe you.
Don't worry about it.
- Take care.
- Okay.
- No, those two racks stay there.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, thanks.
Well, we're gonna have trouble
from Legal on eight.
You know what? Forget it.
Ship it. Let them tell us.
- There you are.
- Go!
- Thanks.
- Hey!
- Hey. What are you doin' here?
Uh, well, I was just
in the area, I guess.
Wow. It looks like
the move's on track.
Yeah, yeah.
It's, uh, this weekend.
- You need Jim?
- Um, no, I just, uh--
- Um, I just wanted to--
- What?
Well, I wanted to thank you.
I, uh-- Well, I got
two tickets for the Dodgers.
I know you like them,
because I saw your coffee mug.
They're for Friday.
I thought we could, you know,
go or-- if you want...
or-or you could just have them.
Both, if you're-- if you're--
if you're seeing some--
I mean, if you have a friend
who likes them.
Well, that's really nice.
I-- I-- I-- um-- Thank you.
Oh, shit, Friday.
I have, uh, a business dinner.
These clients are coming down
from San Francisco. Otherwise--
No, that's been moved
to Monday, remember?
- Is it?
- Mm-hmm, and it's a lunch.
Well, great. The Dodgers.
- Excuse me. I think this is my seat.
- Oh, hi.
Um, somebody--
I think that's back there.
- Someone's sitting here.
- I didn't hear you leave
- I'm sorry.
I wonder how am I still here
And I don't want to move a thing
It might change my memory
Oh, I am what I am
I'll do what I want
But I can't hide
-And I won't go
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How ya doin'?
- I won't sleep
- pretty good, but I feel bad.
- I think I told you
to come way too early.
- No, this is great.
I can't breathe
until you're resting here with me
And I won't leave
And I can't hide
- I can't breathe
- Oh, come on! Come on, come on.
Beat it out!
Beat it out! Beat it out!
- Until you're resting here
- He's out now.
With me
- You're still here, huh?
- Yeah.
That was rude of me, I think.
I should have taken longer.
Oh, I am what I am
I'll do what I want
- But I
- Could I have the hamburger and fries?
Can't hide
And I won't go
I won't sleep
And I can't breathe
Until you're resting
here with me
-And I won't leave
-Um, may I have the grilled cheese and--
I can't hide
I cannot be
Until you're resting
here with me
You know, I don't think
I've ever bought a woman
a grilled cheese sandwich before.
Well, that's what my boys
always order, and after a while...
you know, you kind of
get hooked on 'em.
- There's probably some kind of gum
for that too, right?
- Oh, I am what I am
I'll do what I want
- You want to sit for a while?
- But I
- Can't hide
- Yeah. Sure.
- Is this your car?
- No.
This is Greg's, my-- my ex.
Mine's in the shop, so--
Sittin' in cars at the diner.
I never did that, did you?
No. No diners.
Bars.
- I had a baby in a car.Joey.
- Really?
I mean, not actually in the car.
We made it to the ER, but--
Not this car.
It was a Datsun. Remember those?
I had it in school.
I was-- Well, Greg was driving...
and I just knew
I was gonna have this baby...
and he would not pull over.
So I got it in
my mind that, you know...
I didn't wanna have the baby
in the front seat.
You know, like it wasn't safe.
So I tried to climb in the back seat...
and I broke his nose with my foot.
I had this contraction, and, pow.
I just got him right there.
And he could not drive.
I mean, the blood was pouring.
So I had to drive the rest
of the way to the hospital...
screaming and crying and driving.
And he had a beautiful nose.
I mean, you know,
a good face, handsome, but...
a beautiful nose.
That's all I could think about
the whole time I was delivering.
Oh, I ruined his nose.
And later, you know, he didn't
even know he did this, but--
When we'd have a fight, you know,
he'd kind of touch his nose like--
You know, like Danny Kaye
in-- in White Christmas with the arm.
Like, ''You owe me, pal.''
Oh, God, it used to make me so mad.
What?
I don't know how women
get so brave. That's all.
You think that's brave?
I was so scared.
God, I'm always so scared.
It's not brave
if you're not scared.
Well, you have a good face too.
Okay. Well, um, thank you.
- Thanks for the tickets.
- No problem.
- Good night.
Good night.
- What do you think?
- It's fine.
You get a window. I get to work
for a guy who gets a window.
What are you doing in here already?
It's not even 8:00.
I'm early.
How'd the date go with the realtor?
- It was fine, I guess.
- Fine, huh?
I thought she was nice.
What happened?
What is this, Gay Confidant Day?
You want me to hang on
while you go get a blow-dryer?
Hey, I don't give a shit.
I'm just making conversation.
Well, it went fine, you know.
I'm not interested, so, uh--
If she calls, just, uh, tell her
I'm out or tell her I'm busy...
and take a message and tell her
I'll get back to her, okay?
And if she calls back?
Just keep taking messages.
She'll get the point.
You know, that's what
I love about working for you.
It's a total freedom from
hero worship. It's very refreshing.
Look, you're the client.
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm just saying it's not in sync
with your brand positioning.
It's Jim on three. Urgent.
Right. Okay.
Can I call you right back?
All right. Thanks. What's up,Jim?
No, it's Abby.
It's Abby Janello. Hi.
Hey. Oh. I-- I just--
I thought you were somebody else.
Um, how are ya? I, uh-- I had
a really good time the other night.
Really? Um, listen,
I'm just across the street...
and I've got all these extra sets
of keys for the doors and everything.
I thought maybe I could, um,
you know, buy you and Jim a drink...
to celebrate moving in.
Jim's in a meeting,
uh, and I-- I don't drink.
- Uh--
- Oh.
Um, uh, uh, okay.
I can just, uh, mail them.
How about ten minutes?
Okay. Great.
I'll see you there.
You know what, Seth?
That's not funny, okay?
You don't know what
you're messin' with.
- Hey.
I ordered you a club soda.
Hope that's okay.
Yeah, that's fine.
You know, my husband
didn't drink either.
Not even champagne at our wedding.
I used to drink.
I just don't any more.
Oh.
- AA?
- Yeah, six months.
Oh, well, that's great.
I had an uncle
who was in AA...
and he was, like,
a really bad drunk.
So was I.
I'm sorry. I--
I don't know why I said that.
The drinking wasn't the worst part.
It was the thinking
I was such hot stuff.
I've always been
one of those people.
Born salesman. A closer.
- p eople person.
- Ew.
But I wasn't,
not by a long shot.
It's like how everybody thinks that
they have a-a good sense of humour...
or good taste...
or they're a good driver.
I'd be driving along
and I'd, uh...
happen to look up
in the rearview mirror.
And there'd be all these...
bloody people
and crashed cars in the street...
and I'd think, ''Jesus, there's a lot
of bad drivers in this neighbourhood.''
That was me with people.
I'd like to, uh--
I'd like to tell you
that I've wised up...
but I don't know.
Yeah.
I get it.
You're bad with relationships.
And as a person who's standing...
in the road ahead of you, thanks.
I'll be, uh...
getting on the sidewalk now.
- Abby--
- No, you know, it's okay. I--
I took a shot, you know?
I think I misread stuff...
and I'm sorry.
I'm just really grateful to you for
throwing me the sale and everything.
Bye.
Abby. Abby.
- Abby, wait a second, all right?
- I am not divorced, Buddy.
My husband died
a little over a year ago...
and I am sorry that
I wasn't honest with you about it.
But you know what?
It's too soon for me...
and it is way too soon for my boys,
so just leave me alone.
- I'm sorry.
- Everybody's sorry.
And nobody's to blame except,
you know, sometimes I think...
exactly the opposite is true.
God. Do you have a cigarette?
- No. Abby, I-I think--
- I'm sorry that I lied to you.
But I like thinking
of me and Greg as divorced.
Everybody's divorced.
Feels like a decision we made...
instead of fate or bad luck
or chance.
- plane crash.
- Come on, please.
Let's just go back inside
and start over, okay?
Don't be nice to me.
Everybody is nice to widows.
You were the first person in over a year
who was nice to me who didn't know.
Listen, I was wrong in there.
I just didn't want you to think
I was this great guy.
I wanted to tell you
before you found out for yourself.
I got scared.
What is it that you want, Buddy?
Your company.
The pleasure of your company.
I want your input
on video rentals.
I stand there for hours,
and I can't pick anything out.
I want someone
to say good night to.
A last call of the day.
I don't have a last call of the day.
Do you?
Don't feel sorry for me.
I'm happy.
I'm widow happy.
I'm widow-with-two-kids happy.
If you grade on a curve, I'm happy.
I don't feel sorry for you.
- Okay?
- Oh.
Well--
Okay, then nothing
with knives, snakes...
or women that have to go
undercover as hookers.
The videos.
Okay.
Don't worry. I don't think
he's bored, do you?
Honey, it's a cookout.
Of course he's bored. Aren't you?
So how far has it gone?
Nowhere. You know, he's nice.
It's not-not a big deal.
Mm-hmm.
It's just that, um...
you know when you go to a table and
a guy does that, like, halfway thing...
like he's gonna stand up?
He does that.
I love it when guys do that.
Mom? Mom, can I be excused?
Yes, you may be excused.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
CD-Rom, not AOL, okay?
It costs money.
Hey, do you have, uh, ¨¨Where's Waldo¨¨?
I'm eight, okay?
- Come on,Joey.
- Mama?
- It's okay.
You can take that in.Just don't put
the-- don't put the drink on the desk.
- Okay.
- I knew I shouldn't have
brought up Waldo.
Well, he is eight.
I mean--
- Hey, here, let me help you with that.
- Oh, no, no, no.
I'm gonna do it later.
And you're ready for take-off.
Hey, Scott.
What are you doing?
- Losing.
- pull up! pull up!
Yeah? Is it hard?
I'm done.
You can play.
And you're ready for take-off.
We're losing altitude.
pull up! pull up!
Sorry.
He's still, uh, very angry.
- Thanks. It's okay.
- He's angry at me.
He's angry at Greg.
He's angry at Joey.
This is great.
And he's scared to fly.
You know, I was thinking of maybe
taking them on a little flying trip...
somewhere close so that
if they can't make it,
I can rent a car and drive back.
That sounds good.
It could work.
That's a nice computer.
Yeah.
Greg got it to, uh,
celebrate his play.
He had this play on in Chicago.
That's why he was there.
¨¨Lilacs in the dooryard. ¨¨
Not the title I voted for.
I mean, who knows what a dooryard is
anyway? It's weird.
He wasn't even supposed
to be on that flight.
Even the paperwork was all wrong,
you know?
Which really made me crazy,
because it got me thinking...
like, if I was, you know,
getting the boys ready...
to put them on the bus,
and Donna would say...
''Oh, I'm going down there, you know.
I'll just take them.''
And I would think...
''Well, which one's supposed to crash?''
You know? I mean, do I send them
with Donna or do I put them on a bus?
Which one is doomed?
Or is the whole thing
gonna happen tomorrow?
It's crazy.
Abby--
What?
Do you have a good lawyer...
for your case against the airline?
Uh, I don't really know.
I think so. You know, I'm just sort of
in with the group of other families.
I have his card right there
if you want to see it.
I've got a meeting
with him on Thursday.
Yeah. Well...
what I can do, if you like...
is have our lawyers call around,
ask some questions about him.
For free.
Oh, I see. You, uh--
You're after my money now.
- Is that it?
- Yeah. Well, not just the money.
What the money can buy.
Hey, Scott.
- Uh, thank you very much.
- Yeah, thanks. Thanks for coming by.
- It was great to see you.
- I'll let myself out.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
See you, pal.
Okay, coming.
- Hi.
- I'm sorry. I just--
I didn't know where to go,
and Donna has the kids.
That's-- That's fine. I'm glad I was--
I was here when you called.
Come on in. Do you want, uh,
some dinner or a drink or, uh--
Here, sit down.
I settled.
I saw my lawyer today,
and I settled.
Okay.
It's not okay.
It's like saying, you know,
I'm fine. I'm over it.
That's what everybody
wants me to feel anyway...
even Donna,
who's been so good.
Or my mother.
''Only a plane crash, sweetie.
You gotta bounce.''
That was her take on it.
So that's what I've been doing--
bouncing.
It's just like crashing, except
you get to do it over and over again.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
I mean, I can imagine
how that might feel.
It's the way they talk about him...
like he's this saint.
And I don't even recognize
who they're talking about any more.
It's not that he wasn't
a really good man, you know?
He was.
He was a really good man.
But he wasn't perfect.
He was a little tight with money,
for one thing.
I want to blame him...
or to be angry at him
or whatever because...
when I don't...
he gets really far away.
God.
And I did love him, you know?
I really did love him.
You sure you don't want me to drive
you home? At least follow you?
No, I'm fine.
Listen, I know what you're thinking.
I'm this widow and
I've got these two kids...
and I'm probably not ready.
At least, that's what I think
to myself half the time.
So--
You're off the hook, okay?
You don't have to say another word.
Can I see you this weekend?
No.
No, this weekend is our little
test trip down to palm Springs.
Oh, right.
We had to drive to the funeral,
because Scott wouldn't get on the plane.
And I really don't want my kids to spend
the rest of their lives afraid to fly.
- But Monday, maybe.
- Yeah.
Or I could come with you guys.
Uh-- I wouldn't mention Waldo.
I did promise them the water park.
What, they're afraid
of water now too?
- Come on. It'll be fun.
- Okay.
It's a--
It's a big plane, right?
I think so.
'Cause those would be better
for the kids.
The captain let you
go up there and everything.
Whatever.
That was all right, huh, guys?
- There was a few bumps,
but I was, you know--
- Sir...
- fine, right?
- do we need to discuss
a little attitude adjustment...
- before we get to the water park?
- Get on.
- Come on.
- What do you think?
Though you may not drive
A great big Cadillac
Here, let me test this out
for you, because I'm worried
that maybe it's not--
- You may not have
- Yeah, it's good.
- I don't know.
- A car at all
- What do you think?
- Can you handle it? Hey!
- Got it!
- You got it. Very nice.
- Yes!
- But just remember
Forget it. We don't wanna go
on this dumb ride anyway.
- We want snow cones down at--
down at the bottom.
- Hey, hold on.
Abby? Abby? Abby?
Just be thankful
Can you teach me how to--
how to dive, Mom?
I'm scared! I'm scared!
That was fun!
That was a good one!
Hey, Mom!
Mom, Mom, Mom, Mom!
All right. No, no.
Let me go now. Let me go.
You may not have
A car at home
-Just be thankful
- driving to the bank
Sunroof top
digging the scene with gasoline
For what you've got
Ooh, ooh
- Hey, boys.
- Yeah?
- You ready?
- Yep. Where is it, Scott?
- Oh, yeah. It's right down here.
- I wanna do it.
- Okay.
- Okay, close your eyes and pick one.
- What is this?
- Oh, come on.Just do it.
We'll tell you later.
You can open your eyes now.
Okay, now read it. We couldn't decide
on a name, so it's up to you.
- Uh, ¨¨Darth.¨¨
- Yes!
- That was mine. That was mine.
- It was my second choice, okay?
The boys don't think you should have
the same name as the dog.
That's good, because, uh,
that's a good name for him.
Darth-- because the dog's black
and he-he kind of looks like Vader.
No, that's your new name.
Hey, seat belts, please.
What are you, uh, doing tomorrow?
You tell me.
There's just something
that I wanted to, uh, tell you...
which is sort of hard to say...
so I wanted to just tell you now
that I was gonna tell you...
so that-- so that, uh, you know,
tomorrow you'd hold me to it.
You know, it's probably nothing.
It's not a, you know--
- It's just something I wanna tell you.
- Then tell me now.
No, I'll tell you tomorrow.
It's, you know--
I mean, uh, you just gotta
make me tell you.
Oh, great. Well,
this'll be a fun 24 hours.
It's nothing. Relax.
It's fine, you know.
All right.
Well, whatever it is...
thank you for today.
It was the least I could do.
Can I help you?
- Hi.
Are you--
Are you Mrs Janello?
Yes.
Now that I'm here,
I wish I'd just mailed this.
Hi, I'm Mimi prager.
Hello.
Here.
Would you like to come in?
And I hadn't looked at it
since then...
but I, uh, I was looking up
this speech I'd given...
and there it was.
I remembered the review for his play
was in the Chicago papers...
so I checked their archives
and, uh--
Well.
You probably don't even wanna see it.
You know, I just-- I thought...
- since I had this business trip, and--
- Thank you.
I'm sorry.
He seemed like a very nice man.
Oh! Uncultured creatures!
- I hate it when she does that.
- Hey,Joey, Scott.
Hi, Mr Amaral.
What's going on? Shh.
- Where's your mom?
- She's in the bathroom.
She's been in since Rosie.
- Boy. Who was on Rosie?
- I don't know.
Abby?
- You all right?
- I'll be out in a minute.
Okay.
- Let go!
- Give me that!
Guys. Hey, Scott. Hey.
Hey, stop.Joey, Scott.Joey, Scott,
your mom's trying to relax, okay?
Okay? Relax. Watch TV.
What do you wanna watch?
- I wanna watch my video.
- All right, great.
Scott. Scott!
Scott, stop it.
Scott, don't hit your brother, okay?
- He bit me.
- Well, he's younger than you.
Joey.Joey, apologize, all right?
Say you're sorry. Can you do that?
Can you do that for me?
- Say you're sorry.
- That's Dad!
- We are here to celebrate...
the opening and the closing, sadly...
of the-- the new play
Lilacs Something On Your Dooryard.
- That's you.
- We're here with
the author tonight, uh--
- Greg.
- Greg--
-Janello.
-And I would like to say, for one
thing, that the critic for the Chicago--
- That's G-A--J-A, not G-I-A.
Hey, that's my dad!
I wanna see that!
You knew him?
When was that taken?
- Uh--
- Boys.
- Go to your room until I call you.
- But that was Dad.
Scott, please.
- Who gave this to you?
- Mimi.
Mimi prager. Remember her?
Abby-- Abby, I said
I was gonna tell you something.
Remember I said I had something to tell
you? That's what I was gonna tell you.
That's a lie. Another lie.
He took my place,
and I felt responsible.
And I wanted to make sure
you were okay-- you and your kids.
Who the hell do you think you are?
God? Some goddam angel...
come to make sure
the victims are alive and well?
You lied to me.
I mean, I never expected
to fall in love with you.
God, you're a liar.
No. You know that's true.
I want you...
out of this house.
I don't want to see you again.
I don't want you to call.
I don't want to hear your voice
on my machine.
- Look, you have to let me explain.
- You son of a bitch.
You lied to me. Get out!
What's wrong, Mom?
Do you want me to say what you did
in front of them?
Because I will do almost anything
to get you out of here.
You better go, Mr Amaral.
Yeah, I think so too, Scott.
I think you're right.
I'm gonna go.
- I'll call you.
-Joey, come out here.
I want you to say goodbye to them.
I don't want another guy
just disappearing from their lives.
Abby, please.
Mr Amaral won't be
coming around any more.
Abby--
You can leave,
or you can say goodbye and leave.
Uh, I gotta go away for a while.
- Why?
- Because I, uh...
I kept a secret from your mom.
You're not supposed
to tell a secret.
Well, then it wasn't a secret.
It was just--
I just didn't want to tell her.
Why can't you say you're sorry?
I am sorry.
Don't worry about it,Joey.
All right? Come on.
Come on.
Okay, you have to let me call you.
Get out...
before I tell them who you are.
Hi. You've called theJanello house.
You can leave a--
please leave us a message.
Thanks. Bye.
Hey, Scott.
Uh, she's not home...
and even if she was--
She doesn't wanna see me.
Nope.
You know, Scott, I'd understand it
if you were pretty mad at me too.
It's okay.
All right, pal, I'll see you.
Did he say anything
about Christmas trees?
- What?
- My dad.
He was supposed to sell Christmas trees
with me the next day, and...
maybe that was why
he got back on the plane.
And he did and it crashed, so...
I was just wondering
if he said anything about that.
Well--
Nah, he didn't mention that to me.
Yeah, he just said, you know, he--
He said he just wanted to get home.
Everybody at the airport...
kind of just wants to get home,
that's all.
Yeah, because he didn't need
to sell those trees with me.
I didn't even want to.
Everyone has fake ones anyway.
Yeah, no, he just-- he just--
He said he wanted to get home to work.
I remember him saying something about
work, but, uh, nothing about any trees.
I'm sure of that.
Do you think I should tell my mom?
Because maybe she thinks...
it's because she yelled at him
over the tree thing.
You know, Scott,
I don't think, uh...
your mom will believe me.
But you believe me, right?
- Yeah.
That's good.
Could you help me with these?
Donna, he should've told me.
Of course.
Lying like that is terrible.
It's like telling people
you're divorced when you're not...
or that you found a property
for your biggest client on your own...
without help.
Look, he just wanted to see
if you guys were okay.
Yes, but then he should've
left us alone.
Yeah, I keep forgetting.
Who bought who the Dodger tickets?
Look, guys screw up.
That's what they do.
It's in their manual, right after
''Love your grill, leave socks on floor.''
But if you can't forgive him,
you can't.
It's not that I can't forgive him.
Do you know how I spent the night
after he left?
Trying to figure out if I was glad...
that he didn't get on that plane.
If I say I'm glad he's alive,
I'm glad he found me that day...
or if I lie and I say I'm not,
either way it feels like...
I'm doing something wrong
to someone I--
to both of them--
to him and Greg.
Being with him is like
making a choice.
You don't have that choice, Abby.
You have other choices.
It just can't be him, that's all.
Okay, then, fine.
But whether it's Buddy...
or someone else a year from now...
whoever you choose will be there
because Greg isn't.
That's just how it is.
Hey,Jim.
Seth said you wanted to see me.
How's it going, Frank? What's up?
Are we being sued or something?
Infinity Airlines,
according to its marketing Vp...
is deciding today whether our services
will be required in the future.
What? Why?
Apparently, they received,
uh, some information...
that you coerced an Infinity employee
to illegally...
board a passenger
under your name onto Flight 82.
Yeah. I mean, we dealt with this
a year ago after the crash.
It was a computer problem
or something.
They have a correct version
of the roster in their system.
Yes, they do.
Uh, you know a Janice Guerrero?
She was fired six weeks after
the accident for altering the roster--
removing your name, in fact,
and adding the name of a Greg--
What does this have to do with
our-- our situation with Infinity?
The suit is being brought against
Infinity by the victims' families.
They wanna prove that the airline didn't
follow procedures, even technicalities.
So Infinity wants to make sure
that if you get called to testify...
that you tell the court
what you told us today--
that you did not persuade this
gate attendant to board someone else.
- Is this woman gonna testify?
- Maybe.
But she's not the most credible witness.
She's a bitter ex-employee, ax to grind.
Infinity's position is that
the roster screwup...
is a harmless computer glitch,
it's no big deal.
They just wanna know
if you have a problem with that.
Mr Amaral?
If you're just joining us, it is day 7
of the civil trial against Infinity.
And believe me, tensions which have been
running high since this trial began...
are likely to reach
their peak today.
The plaintiffs in this case are
the survivors of three passengers--
two of whom, ironically, were seated
just across the aisle from each other...
in seats 1 8--
And here comes today's
principal witness.
Her testimony
about the flagrant disregard...
for safety procedures
was extremely damaging.
We're gonna move over and just see
if we can get a word with her.
Uh, Miss Guerrero?
Miss Guerrero, we're live here.
Do you feel that
your testimony was--
Quick question.
Miss Guerrero?
please, please. No comment.
Thank you very much.
Hey, I'm gonna go get the kids.
You wanna come along?
We'll grab some dinner.
No, no, I'm okay.
I'm fine, thanks.
Okay. I'll be back.
- Mr Amaral.
- Yes.
You were scheduled to be a passenger
on Flight 82, were you not?
Yes, that's right.
In fact, when the plane went down,
your name was on...
the first list of passengers,
was it not?
Uh, that is correct.
But instead, a Mr Greg Janello
was in your seat, isn't that correct?
- I believe so, yes.
- You believe so?
Uh--
Yes, he was in my seat.
Do you know how Mr Janello happened
to be on that plane occupying your seat?
- No, I don't know.
- Excuse me?
I'm-I'm-I'm just very confused about a
lot of things that happened that night.
- I don't--
- Well, you're not confused...
about having just taken an oath
to tell the truth, are you?
- Objection, Your Honour.
- I'll rephrase, Your Honour.
Mr Amaral, did you have a conversation
that night with Mr Janello?
Mr Mandel, I had a lot
of conversations with a lot of people.
You know, everything was delayed...
and I-I, uh, don't remember every--
This is Mr Janello.
Did you have a conversation
with this man?
Yes, I did.
And did you offer
to switch boarding passes with him?
- No, I did not.
- No?
I just gave him mine.
I didn't take his.
And when Miss Guerrero
recognized you at the gate?
- Yeah, I talked her into it.
- By telling her if they didn't board
you or someone claiming to be you...
they'd have to wait while they took
your luggage out of the hold?
- Basically, yeah.
- Are you aware that airlines...
have to deplane the luggage of
passengers who don't make the flight...
- as an anti-terrorism measure?
- Yes.
It's, uh, so that somebody
doesn't check a bomb...
and then not get on the plane.
Mm-hmm.
So this employee of Infinity...
disregarded a safety measure due to
her desire to make the schedule?
- Objection. Argumentative.
- Sustained.
You know, she-she was just trying
to do me a favour. It wasn't--
No one's blaming you, Mr Amaral.
It wasn't your job to make sure
the airline...
followed their own safety procedures,
now, was it?
He was scared.
Excuse me?
I didn't remember that until now.
Not scared, just nervous.
Not a good flier.
He told me he used to be braver
when he was like me--
by himself, no family.
No, uh...
people in his wallet.
He had a wife now...
two kids.
Two boys.
And he knew that, uh...
if something happened to him...
if he didn't come home...
that wasn't something that
anybody could make up for.
If you-- If you tried, I mean.
Only somebody who, uh--
Only somebody who didn't
understand anything would try.
But I didn't know that then.
I just thought, here.
It's a ticket.
It's free. Take it.
You'll be fine.
And he did.
And he died.
So that's what I gotta carry.
I'd just like to say that I'm sorry.
You're excused, Mr Amaral.
Am I?
Excused?
Infinity Airlines today settled
the last of the lawsuits...
that have gone to trial as a result
of the 1 999 crash in Kansas...
in which the 2 1 6 people aboard
Flight 82 lost their lives.
- Hey, Seth.
- Hey.
Word is you pretty much
single-handedly sank Infinity.
Yeah. I noticed a chill
on the way in.
Yeah? Well, bundle up.
Uncle Jim wants to see you.
Could you do me a favour
and type this up for me, please?
- I thought Jim's speech was nice.
- Yeah, but everyone else-- Whoo.
I know. I don't think
I've ever been to a farewell party
where the theme was relief.
Well, I like to leave a place happier
than when I found it, you know.
They were happy, all right.
I was dodging cartwheels all afternoon.
So are you gonna find a new job
or are you gonna go out on your own?
- I stole you plenty of office supplies.
- Yeah.
I don't know. I'm kind of
all sold out, you know what I mean?
I told Jim you could handle
the transition.
He said he was gonna move you into
account traffic.
He came up with that all on his own?
Yeah, roughly.
Means you get your own assistant.
Is this you asking me for the job?
You want to, uh, catch
an AA meeting tonight?
Yeah. Uh, there's the one--
Hey.
Uh, I-I need to get back to work...
and take down
the ''Good Riddance'' banners.
We love the new building.
Lots of space, and...
even more after today.
I resigned about three minutes
before Jim was gonna fire me.
You're moving.
Yeah. I can't afford
this place any more.
How are the boys?
They're good.
Scott told me
that you came to see him.
And he told me what you said.
Well, it wasn't Scott's fault.
Or yours.
Or even mine,
which is something that I thought...
for a really long time.
And you really helped me see that,
and I wanted to tell you, so--
Can you just stay for, like,
a few more minutes?
please?
You know what Greg said
that last night he called?
That he had met some really
nice people in the bar.
And I think he was right.
Abby, wait.
What?
Should I sell this place
right away or, uh...
lease it out
until the market peaks?
I was hoping
you could help me handle that.
Why me? I mean,
I really don't have the experience.
Yes, you do.
Can we try?
I know you're scared, Abby.
I am too.
It's not brave
if you're not scared.
You'd better not be waiting for me
to kick in any commission.
Deal.
Come on. I'll show you
how it looks from the beach, okay?
Been running from these feelings
for so long
Telling my heart
I didn't need you
pretending I was better off alone
But I know that it's just a lie
So afraid to take a chance again
So afraid of what I'd feel inside
But I need to be next to you
Need to be next to you
Oh, I, oh, I
I need to share every breath with you
Share every breath with you
Oh, I, oh, I
I need to know I can see
your smile each morning
Look into your eyes each night
For the rest of my life
Here with you, near with you
Oh, I
I need to be next to you
Need to be next to you
Right here with you
is right where I belong
I'll lose my mind
if I can't see you
Without you, there is
nothing in this life
That would make life
worth living for
I can't bear the thought
of you not there
I can't find what I feel any more
'Cause I need to be next to you
Need to be next to you
Oh, I, oh, I
I need to share
every breath with you
Share every breath with you
Oh, I, oh, I
I need to know I can see
your smile each morning
Look into your eyes each night
For the rest of my life
Here with you, near with you
Oh, I
I need to be next to you
I need to have your heart
next to mine
For all time
Hold you for all of my life
I need to be next to you
Need to be next to you
Oh, I, oh, I
I need to share
every breath with you
Share every breath with you
Oh, I, oh, I
I need to know I can see
your smile each morning
Look into your eyes each night
For the rest of my life
Here with you, near with you
Oh, I
I need to be next to you
Oh, I need to be
Need to be next to you
- Oh, I
- Share every breath with you
Oh, I
I need to feel you in my arms, baby
- Oh, I
- In my arms, baby
Oh, I
I need to be next to you
Oh, I, oh, I
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player