Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
-  [Pop]
- [Man] I love you.
I love you.
[Woman]
Yeah, whatever.
- Love stinks.
- [Chorus]  Love stinks
-  Yeah, yeah, love stinks
-  Love stinks
-  Yeah, yeah
You love her
and she loves him
And he loves another
You just can't win
So it goes
till the day you die
This thing they call love
It's gonna make you cry
I've had the blues
the reds and the pinks
One thing for sure
-  Love stinks
-  Love stinks, yeah, yeah
- Magazine?
- [Pilot Over P.A.]
Good afternoon, everyone.
This is your captain speaking.
Sorry for the delay.
It should be just a few more minutes.
Thanks for your patience.
[Watch Beeps]
[Call Button Dings]
- Can I help you?
- I don't know. Can you?
May I help you?
Yes. I would like to know
why we're behind schedule.
It'll be just a few more minutes.
Can I get you something to drink?
I don't know.
Can you?
Right this way.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Hi. I'm Jennifer.
Wait until the last minute
to pack?
Nope.
Got my first period.
- Oh.
- Good afternoon, everyone.
This is your captain again.
We're making our way out to the runway
and should be taking off shortly.
- Enjoy the flight.
- Does it gross you out to know
that I'm bleeding right now?
Why should it?
It's just biology.
We could have sex right now,
and I wouldn't even get pregnant.
Do you have orgasms?
I don't think that's
any of your business.
Yeah, well, you're still young.
What are you, ten?
- Twelve.
- [Scoffs]
[Sighs]
So, do you live in L.A. or New York?
- L.A.
- Me too. My dad ran off
with his secretary,
so my mom and I
moved to California.
Your parents
still together?
- No. Yes!
- What's that mean?
They're divorced,
but they're getting back together.
- That's great.
- I have the whole thing planned out.
You're getting them
back together?
I've already talked
to my father about it.
I'm gonna explain to my mother
how the divorce is ruining my life.
- Maybe they're not in love.
- You have to work at love if
you want it to last forever.
- Who says love should last forever?
- They're married.
- They're divorced.
- They shared vows.
They made commitments.
They have responsibilities.
Someone needs to remind them of that.
My mother says, "If love's
broken, you have to throw it out
with the rest of the trash."
That's exactly what's wrong
with grown-ups. They're lazy.
- You're an idiot.
- Well, you're an idiot.
You're ugly.
[Airplane Engines Rev]
- Try breathing.
- [Labored Breathing]
Take a deep breath.
It'll help you relax.
- I'm hot, not relaxed.
- Oh.
This is just how I am.
One... two...
three... four... five...
six... seven...
eight... nine.
Twenty-two.
Hut, hut, hut.
- [Crowd Cheering]
- [Man] Halftime!
[Announcer]
And that's halftime,
with the Knights
leading the Gophers 14-7.
It should come as no surprise
that this year's homecoming king...
is tonight's star quarterback,
Cameron Fitzgerald.
What good is a king
without a queen
So, let's give
a royal Harding High cheer...
to this year's homecoming queen,
Jennifer Burrows.
[Boy] Bow down
to my queen and king.
Jennifer Burrows?
Gopher, do you mock
my queen?
- Huh?
- I thinketh that you do.
And for that,
you shall die!
[Cheering]
[Grunting]
Whoo!
[Mumbling]
Run it over.
Run the head over.
No! No, don't!
Aha! Yes!
- Are you all right?
- My head.
You're going to
be okay.
No, my head.
Where is it?
Hey.
How's your head?
Oh, it...
it's not so good.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
You don't remember me,
do you?
No. Should I?
No.
We were on a plane
together once.
[Laughs]
Oh, my God!
Ryan
- You're "Counting Ryan"?
- Yeah.
Of course I remember you.
Once a month I remember you.
I must have told that "period on
the plane" story like a million times.
- Not me.
- [Giggles]
You wanna go grab
a coffee or something?
What about your boyfriend,
the king?
Don't have a boyfriend.
Hate commitments.
I figure, why limit yourself
when there's a world
of possibilities out there?
Well, maybe all those possibilities
distract you from what you really want.
I mean, that's why
I don't watch cable.
- What?
- There's too many choices.
Lucky your school
has a uniform.
You know, you might just wake up
and have to pick out an outfit.
And then with all those choices,
you might end up walking
out of your house naked.
- That's dumb.
- Yeah, well, you're pretty dumb.
Don't call me dumb.
Why not? It's true.
You are. You're dumb.
Dumb, dumb, dumb,
dumb, dumb.
No...
- you're dumb!
- [Laughs]
- Hey, so you wanna go?
- No.
- Why not?
- Because this... us...
- [Sighs] We don't click.
- Since when?
Since now. Since right now.
Does this feel like we're clicking?
I was only talking about
going and getting a cup of coffee.
You know,
maybe decaf for you.
It just doesn't
make sense to me.
Fine.
- Fine. Fine.
- Fine.
[Man]
You know what I do what I do
Riding my wave
once again
It's always the same
It never ends
Riding my wave
once again
It's always the same
It never ends
[End]
- [Watch Beeps]
- What-What time is it?
Time for me to leave
for the airport.
That's impossible. I set
my alarm exactly one minute
before you had to leave.
I set mine three minutes before,
just to be sure.
- I love you.
- [Woman] Gopher boy?
- What's wrong?
- Uh, nothing.
- It is you.
I don't believe it.
Are you going to school here?
Uh, yes.
Oh, uh, this is Betty.
Betty, this is...
Jennifer.
Hi. How you doing?
Gopher boy and I
go way back.
Please stop
calling me that.
Okay.
Well, um, I guess
I should get going.
- It was good seeing you again.
- Yeah.
Bye.
- Gopher boy?
- It's a long story.
- [Knocking]
- Help! Is somebody there?
Hey, a little help
here, please.
Somebody, hello?
Open up!
Excuse me!
- Hello. Whoo!
- Whoa!
Wow.
- Are you all right?
- Oh, I'm fine.
I am... I'm fine.
You're Ryan, right?
- Yeah. Hey.
- Hey!
I'm Hunter.
Your roomie, Hunter.
What were you doing
in the trunk?
Right. Uh, well, um,
well, I got to the room...
first, here, before you,
and, uh, I thought that
it would be, you know, funny...
if, uh, if I popped out of the trunk
and surprised you.
Surprise! And, uh,
the rest is history.
Wow, we haven't even known
each other for 20 seconds
and already we have a story.
This is gonna be great.
- So, uh, so how are you gonna tell it?
- Uh...
- Tell what?
- Our story. Oh, oh, I know.
I know. You'll probably say I was
gasping for air and you saved my life.
- Well, I...
- Actually, that's
a great way to tell it.
Chicks love drama.
You're good, man.
[Scoffs]
Thanks.
Wow, really good. I'm gonna have
a hard time keeping up with you.
Ha. Come here.
Oh, man!
[Sighs]
Four years.
- Huh.
- [Sighs]
[Woman]
Yeah, I know a girl
Can't remember her name
but I know what she wants
She wants to be
everything
So, is she your
high-school sweetheart?
As a matter of fact,
she is.
Good for you.
Where is she going to school?
Seattle.
Oh, a long distance.
- So?
- Good luck.
We don't need luck.
We have a very strong relationship.
We weren't together over the summer,
and everything was fine.
Mm. What was she gone,
a month?
Six weeks, two days.
You visited
back and forth...
maybe three times,
called each other every night?
That's right.
You have to put in the work.
I've seen it happen
a hundred times.
Last year, every long-distance
relationship in my dorm...
was over
by the second semester.
- Wow.
- Just keeping it real.
[Man]
Next in line, please.
So, where
are you living?
- Herman Hall.
- Oh, I can give you some tips.
- Do you live there?
- No, no, but I do have friends there.
I live off-campus
with my boyfriend.
- What? You have a boyfriend?
- Mm-hmm.
Who?
- Punker Winters. He's a musician.
- Next in line.
He's great.
- You're living with one guy?
- Yeah.
You've made a commitment that prohibits
choices in the name of love?
Uh-huh.
Isn't it crazy what falling head
over heels can do to a person?
- Next, please.
- That's me.
Yeah, I know a girl
All she wants is...
I came as fast as I could.
What happened?
[Gasping]
He dumped me!
Why?
Because he fell in love
with somebody else.
- Oh, God. Who?
- I don't know who, Amy,
and I don't care who.
The point is,
is that he dumped me.
Well, how did you find out? I mean,
did you catch them or something?
Oh, God, in this bed?
No. Oh, God, no.
No, no, no,
he just told me.
- He told you.
- Yeah, we made that whole pact.
You know, that if you meet
somebody else, you're gonna
tell the other person.
Yeah, well, no one
ever takes that pact seriously.
I mean, you just say it
to cover your own ass.
Yeah, well, I'm really lucky
because my boyfriend,
he's really loyal
to his pacts.
- Well, how did you find out?
- At the club.
What, did he yell it
over the music?
- No, no, no, it was the music.
- No.
It was the same club
where we first met.
It was the same club where
we first decided to move in together.
It was the same stage
where he first sang that song...
"Jennifer, Jennifer,
this heart is made for two."
And I'm just sitting there watching him,
and I'm thinking how much I love him,
and how I can't believe
that I can love somebody that much.
And then he sang
this brand-new song.
A little something called...
? Jennifer, Jennifer?
? You asked me
to be true?
? What can I say?
I found someone new
Do-doopy-do-wah
-  Jennifer, Jennifer
- That's horrible.
[Indistinct]
Actually,
it was pretty catchy.
By the second chorus,
everybody was singing along.
- What did you do?
- Nothing.
I don't think I've ever
felt this way before.
I'm a complete idiot.
I mean, why didn't I just listen
to my instincts, you know?
- Why didn't I listen?
- Hey, well, look on the bright side.
I mean, now you get
to move in with me.
Oh, well, I know things look
pretty horrible right now,
but, you know, it's just
gonna take some time...
'cause that's what my therapist
keeps telling me.
To hell with your therapist,
Ame, really,
because I just need
to feel better... now!
Do-dooby-do, my ass.
It's tough out there, man.
You don't know how lucky you are.
- Betty and I broke up.
- What?
You're kidding. When?
- A couple of days ago.
- Why didn't you tell me?
I don't know. I guess
it's just now kind of sinking in.
Well, this is
great news.
- Now you and me can hit the circuit.
- You and I.
- Right.
- I don't think so.
Believe me,
it's way easier with two of us.
See, you pretend to be my idiot cousin
in for the weekend.
All of a sudden,
I'm sensitive.
You get drunk,
start coming on too strong,
I beat the shit out of you,
I'm masculine.
I don't think
I'm ready for that.
Well, we could trade off.
You can hit me first if you want.
It was two days ago.
I think I need a little time.
You're right.
I'm sorry you're hurting.
So let's get drunk
and go see some strippers.
- I'm not that hurt.
- Shh. Please.
I'm fine. Breaking up was
the right thing to do.
We were just...
going in different directions.
Mm.
- Whoa, hit me.
- No.
No, no, no.
Come on. Do it.
- Hurry. Before she leaves.
- Who?
- You know her?
- Kind of.
- Okay, then I'll hit you.
- No.
- Hey.
- Hi.
How you been?
Good. You?
Great.
- So, I see you're all settled in.
- Yes.
- Did you get Fridays off?
I got Friday nights off.
I'm sure you do.
Oh, uh, Jennifer,
this is Hunter.
Hi.
Well, you know,
I'd love to stick around,
but, uh, I have to go to the train
station to pick up my cousin.
He's an idiot.
My whole family is, actually.
Me too.
Yeah, me too.
I'm an idiot.
I'll see ya.
I got dumped.
- Hmm?
- Yeah, music man.
Michael... dumped me.
Oh.
How's
"long-distance Betty"?
I don't wanna talk
about it.
But I just told you
about my whole breakup.
Come on. I mean,
it couldn't be worse.
Why? Why do you
wanna know?
- Misery loves company.
- No!
You'll just find some way
to use it against me.
[Gasps] Okay, okay, maybe I might
have done that in the past,
but I've changed.
I have. I'm scarred now,
and I look at life very differently.
Okay.
- You were right.
- It was the long-distance thing.
- Yes, but not for me.
- I knew it.
I was fine with it.
I would go there, she would come here.
If I told her I would call her at
a certain time, no matter where I was...
- You would call.
- I would call.
If I told her to call me
at a certain time when I'd be home,
I would always be home.
I mean, I loved her, so none
of that ever seemed like work to me.
But it did to her,
right?
- Yeah.
This one weekend, I was down there,
and we were kissing each other good-bye,
and her roommate came by
with her boyfriend.
They were both carrying
these bags of laundry,
and Betty
just started crying.
I asked her, "What's wrong?"
And she said...
"We never get to do
our laundry together."
She was right. We never did get
to do our laundry together,
and that was it.
You broke up
because of laundry?
I send mine out.
Not laundry, exactly. Just all
the things that couples do together...
- that couples should do together.
- Uh-huh.
We just didn't have the time anymore.
She couldn't handle that.
- Why didn't you move there?
- Scholarship.
- Well, she could have moved here.
- Wow, so that was it?
- Yeah.
- I mean, she needed something
that I couldn't give her.
- Oh, no.
There's a lot of other
little things too.
Too many differences
make relationships impossible.
Michael and I didn't agree
on anything... ever.
That's what I loved about it.
We fought, shouted, had sex.
I mean,
it's what I miss.
That doesn't sound like
a very healthy relationship.
Yeah, but what do you know
about healthy relationships?
- Excuse me?
- I'm saying, who are you
to judge my relationship?
- Well, see, I knew this was a mistake.
- What?
I'm just saying that you were
in an unhealthy relationship.
It's about having to like things
all the time. It's about surprises.
I mean, love is exciting
and it's thrilling...
and it drives you so insane,
you just think you're gonna explode.
It's the whole point.
Then I guess Michael
didn't get the point.
Oh!
Oh, yeah
Riding my wave
once again
It's always the same
It never ends
You've never been to her apartment?
That is some weird shit.
No, it's not.
[Scoffs]
She's just being careful.
See, there's no point
introducing me into her world,
unless she feels secure
in our relationship.
I admire that.
What are you doing today?
I've got a scuba-diving
class at 3:00.
Really.
No, that's a lie.
I lied. I can't stop.
I'm lying about everything.
It started so I can impress
girls, and now I can't stop.
You know, you should really
see someone about that.
- Yeah, I am.
- No, you're not.
See? I can't stop.
I can't.
The next time I catch you lying, I'll
expose you for the fraud that you are.
You wouldn't.
- I would.
- You're not lying.
- I'm not.
- Huh.
What are you
really doing today?
Dance class.
So, my therapist keeps telling me
to expand my horizons.
But, with this guy, all I did
was pretend to be someone I wasn't.
And I just can't handle it
anymore, you know?
- That's why you're
breaking up with him?
- Yeah, I know,
but do you think
I'm being too cowardly?
I mean, my therapist wants me to take
more responsibility for my emotions,
but I just don't think this is
the right time for that, you know?
It doesn't matter how you do it...
phone, fax, E-mail, song.
It's all the same message...
Adios, amigo.
Yeah, but you have to be
nice about it.
Amy, are you breaking up
with your boyfriend,
or am I breaking up
with your boyfriend?
You know what? I wouldn't really
call him my boyfriend.
I mean,
I barely know the guy.
- So, don't worry about it.
- Yeah, but he just seemed
so sweet, you know?
- I don't wanna see him get hurt.
- I know.
[Knocks On Door]
[Exhales Deeply]
- Hi.
- Uh, hi.
- What are you doing here?
- Well, I was coming to pick up Amy.
Oh. Ha. Interesting.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm Amy's roommate.
Is she here?
We need to talk.
- We're not right together?
- I'm just telling you what she told me.
I don't think you should
take it personally.
Why do people say that?
How could I not take it personally?
- It's me she doesn't like.
- Okay, fine. Take it personally.
- Why didn't she tell me?
- Because she didn't
want to hurt your feelings.
- And you did?
- No, no. I didn't know it was you.
I mean, I knew it was a Ryan,
but I didn't know it was you Ryan.
- This... sucks!
- [Speaking Latin]
- What?
- It's Latin for
"Don't kill the messenger."
You know what?
You're having too much fun with this.
- I'm trying not to.
- Try harder.
[Laughing]
Look. It's not funny.
Oh, no, no, I'm not laughing at you.
I'm laughing at them.
You see, chicks, they love making guys
jump through hoops.
This isn't a hoop.
She broke up with me.
No, it's a test. See, she's testing you
to see how much you really want her.
- You think?
- I know.
Look. You've got...
You've got to swim across the moat,
bust down the castle door,
slay the dragon...
and that's... that's not a euphemism...
and sweep her off her feet.
- You're right.
You're absolutely right.
- Of course I am.
- We were great together.
I even made a chart.
- Sure you did.
It proved how perfect
we were together.
- Now all I have to do
is prove it to Amy.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- What?
- You've gotta do more
than show her pie graphs.
You gotta weep... openly.
Yeah, you should have
quit while you were ahead.
Squeeze the lids. Turn on
the sprinklers. You need the tears.
The tears of-of a man who
can't breathe another second
without the love of his life.
Hold on.
I got just the thing.
- Here.
- What's this?
Icy Balm.
A little dab under your eyes,
you'll be sobbing
like a Miss America.
Oh, wish me luck.
Today, I learned
second position.
Ladies! Yo!
Did you know that they rearranged
all the desks in the library?
- No.
- Yeah, it's completely different.
I spent two hours
trying to find my desk.
And if it wasn't
for the Diet Coke stain,
I wouldn't have
found it at all.
Do you wanna know where they put it?
On the third floor.
Not the second, not even the fourth,
the third. Third.
Number three.
- And that would be a bad thing.
- Please. It's a disaster.
- You wanna hear how your breakup went?
- I totally forgot.
Was it horrible?
Do you think we can still be friends?
I don't know.
He seemed pretty shook up.
- Oh, poor guy.
- Wanna hear the weird part?
- I kinda know him.
- You do?
We run into each other
once in a while.
Well, do you think I did the right thing
in having you break up with him?
- I don't know.
- I do. It was just putting...
- It was putting
too much pressure on me.
- Yeah, I can see that.
On the other hand,
maybe that's what I need.
- [Doorbell Rings]
- What if that's him?
[Screaming,
Gasping]
Oh, my God, you're crying.
He's crying.
Why are you doing this to me?
It's over.
Do you understand me?
O-ver.
- [Screams]
- Ryan!
Ryan, it's not so bad.
People break up all the time.
I can't see!
I think I'm blind!
Nice patch.
Thanks.
You didn't have to wait.
I'm not waiting.
Can't a girl enjoy a lollipop in
the middle of the afternoon...
in front of
the free health center?
Oh.
Who also feels maybe
a little bit responsible.
You didn't do anything.
Yeah, well, I mean,
I didn't put the Icy Balm in your eye,
but I did break up
with you, remember?
Yeah.
- Where are you going?
- For a walk.
Try to forget
today ever happened.
- Can I come?
- What for?
Can't a girl enjoy a walk in the middle
of the afternoon with her ex-boyfriend?
Will the girl continue to refer
to herself in the third person?
Did Ryan Walker
just make a joke?
I don't know.
Let me ask him.
Wow. You know, you're pretty funny
when you're depressed.
- Well, get ready for comedy.
- Another one.
Yeah, a few more and I'll have
to take you back to the clinic...
so they can fix up your busted gut.
[Chuckles]
- You lost it.
- Not funny?
Let's put it this way,
any more of those,
and I'm gonna have to
break up with you again.
[Bongo Drums]
[Teacher Yelling Instructions]
Seven... eight.
Hey.
How's it going?
Get ready.
Another braided spiral.
[Groans]
Hey.
How you doing?
Hey, excuse me.
Question.
Exactly how far
can you bend over?
[Jennifer]
Do you come here a lot?
- [Ryan] Yep.
- It's really beautiful.
One of the greatest structural
achievements in the history of man.
You're the second person
to call me that this week.
You know the only way to build
something that awesome?
Alien slaves
from outer space?
Perfect planning.
Doesn't it make
so much sense?
You examine a situation,
you plan a course of action,
you execute it.
Everything
works out fine.
But it doesn't.
Yeah, well, that's 'cause most things
in life just aren't that simple.
Does that look simple
to you?
I mean, you couldn't imagine
how complicated something
like that is to create.
I thought you were just
using it as a metaphor.
- I am.
- For a relationship.
- Yes.
- Yeah, that's what I thought.
I mean, I know I didn't know
Amy incredibly well, but...
it just felt like
everything added up.
Are you a math major?
No, structural engineering.
Oh.
- I'm done with it.
- Engineering?
Relationships.
They're just...
too much.
It's not worth it.
- [Speaking Latin]
- Huh?
"I hear you, brother."
Latin.
- What... What is it with the Latin?
- My major.
- Latin? Why?
- Yeah. Why not?
What are you
gonna do with it?
I'm going to Italy
for my graduate school.
And after that?
I don't know.
See? You're amazing.
I could never do that.
- You mean not have a plan?
- Or something.
But, then again,
why would you
ever need a plan?
I'm sure you've always
had everything you wanted,
whether you knew
you wanted it or not.
You know, that's true
because the first time...
that I ever really wanted something
and went for it was Michael,
and it turned out great.
Wow. See, I just figured
you being a junior and all,
you'd have it
all figured out by now.
Yeah, that's
what you think, huh?
No, but I'm dumb.
Isn't that right?
And uptight. A-And ugly,
if I remember correctly.
Oh, no. Oh, no. I said all of that
before I was on Prozac.
You're on Prozac?
I wish.
- It's a joke.
- Oh!
Oh, it's okay.
I should go. I still have some more
studying to do. Finals.
Me too.
I'm gonna stay.
All right.
- So, I'll see you around.
- Yep.
Hey.
I'm sorry about Amy.
It's okay.
Bye.
Riding my wave
once again
It's always the same
It never ends
Riding my wave
once again
It's always the same
It never ends
[Continues, Indistinct]
Did you get
all your classes?
[Chuckles]
All but one.
Oh, the elusive one.
Yes.
So, did you have
a good summer?
Yeah, yeah.
I just went back to L.A.
- Oh.
- What about you?
Stayed here. Learned how
to butter bagels for a living.
Surprisingly easy,
actually.
You just swipe it once
back and forth.
- I take mine plain.
- Of course you do.
So, summer was good?
Yeah.
Everything's good.
It's good.
Uh, Jennifer,
are you okay?
I pushed him away. I mean, I literally
did everything in my power...
to make sure
that he dumped me.
Well, obviously,
you didn't like him.
No. That's the thing.
I thought it was just a summer fling,
but I actually...
I started to like him.
Oh, then, why did you
push him away?
I don't know.
I just...
[Sniffles]
It's just such
a pain in the ass, you know?
Yes. Yes, it is.
[Sobbing]
Oh.
Well, what about you?
I mean, did you get any
this summer?
Well, I... No.
You've got
the right idea.
You know, we should do this
again sometime.
I mean, not the whole
crying thing, but...
you know, this.
Sure.
No matter how I try
I just can't get you off my mind
Just another lawsuit.
[Phone Rings]
- Hello.
- [Jennifer] Hello.
Wanna go do something?
- No.
- You haven't even heard my proposal.
Well, that's the beauty
of our friendship.
I don't even need to hear your proposal
to know my answer's no.
I'm the beauty
in our friendship.
- I'm hanging up now.
- You can't.
- Give me one good reason.
- 'Cause...
'Cause I've rigged an explosive device
to your telephone...
and your whole place
will blow.
Oh, well,
I've been burned before.
Come on.
I can't study anymore.
I'm getting too smart.
People start shunning me.
- Only if you beg me.
- I just did.
In Latin.
[Speaking
Latin]
Oh, oh, baby
don't wanna stop this feeling
- Come on!
-  It all feels so new
'Cause no one makes me feel
the way that you do, you do
No matter where I go
No matter what I do
No matter how I try
I just can't get you
off of my mind
I always think of you
No matter where I go
I just can't get you
off my mind
- You weren't gonna go.
- I was too.
You weren't.
You weren't going.
Ladies first.
La... Okay.
- Fine.
- [Laughs]
Why don't I count
for you?
- [Laughs] Okay. Yeah.
- Yeah?
- All right. One...
- Uh-huh.
- two... three!
- Two. Three. Here we go.
You know,
I can't help you.
No, you can help me
at the bottom.
That you do, you do
No matter where I go
No matter what I do
Do you think I'd look good
with a goatee?
-  I just can't get you
off of my mind
- No.
- Hmm.
-  Get you off of my mind
[Dance Rock]
Wait, wait, this is crazy.
I'm not a natural dancer.
- No. No one in my family is.
- Just move. Have fun.
We're here to have fun.
Just you and me and that patch
of pubic hair on your chin.
Just follow him.
Do what he does.
Stop the rock
Can't stop the rock
You can't stop the rock
Shake my paranoia
Can't stop the rock
Move me, move me
Dancing like Madonna
into the groovy
Shake my paranoia
Move me, move me
Dancing like Madonna
into the groovy
[Instrumental]
Stop the rock
Can't stop the rock
[Instrumental]
[Continues, Indistinct]
- This isn't so bad.
- Good.
You might not
ever get rich
Let me tell you it's better
than digging a ditch
There ain't no tellin'
who you might meet
A movie star, a movie star
a movie star, a movie star
At the car wash
Car wash, yeah
-  Work and work
-  Well, those cars
never seem to stop coming
-  Work and work
-  Keep those rags
and machines humming
Work and work
[Instrumental Continues]
-  Car wash
- Ow.
You've never been
with a woman before?
No. I lived with the monks
my whole life, until yesterday.
I walked into
the monsignor's office,
turned in my rosary beads and collar,
got my deposit back and now here I am,
playing this strange game
of sticks and balls.
It's called pool.
Pool. Oh, I have
so much to learn.
I'll teach you, okay?
No, put your hand here.
[Laughs]
- Aah!
- Oh.
- Don't hurt him. He's a priest.
- Oh, I'm a priest.
How would you like to have a religious
experience with that cue stick?
[Groaning]
Run, Father, run!
[Whimpering]
[Both Laughing]
So, you wanna come up
and dry off?
- Uh, I don't know. Is Amy there?
- Probably.
Uh, no. No, I think
I'm just gonna go home.
- Gotta write in the diary?
- Something like that.
- Okay.
- Um...
You know, as much
as I hate to admit this,
I had fun tonight.
Yeah, me too.
It was good, clean fun.
Maybe we can go there
once a week and do our laundry.
It's cheaper than the place
I take mine to.
[Both]
Morocco.
What's up?
You kids go swimming?
- Yeah.
- That's great. So, uh...
So what's going on now?
'Cause my plans kinda fell through.
I invited Ryan up,
but he's going home to bed.
- Really.
- I'm tired.
- He's tired.
Uh, yeah, I'm kinda...
tired myself.
Actually, we should
get outta here.
Ooh! Good night.
You coming?
Hey, I gotta hand it to you, man.
Very cool back there.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
She's begging you to come up,
and you're holding back.
- She's probably going nuts right now.
- I don't think so.
Did you hear the way
she said "bed"?
Man, you could almost
smell the linens.
- You're way off on this one.
- I don't think so.
- You in a hurry?
- No. No, why do you ask?
That's him.
Get him!
Oh, shit. Come on.
You better start
praying, Father!
- Who the hell is that?
- I have no idea.
Okay, listen. Best thing for you
to do is just forget it ever happened.
- Forgotten yet?
- No.
- How about now?
- Man, no.
Jeez, you're like
an elephant.
[Amy] Oh, great.
You're just in time for cookies.
- They look good.
- Oh, no, not those.
See, I thought it would be nice
to have a snack when you got home,
but I didn't know
when that would be, so I just guessed...
and made a batch around 8:00,
but they burnt.
So, I did another one
around 9:30, and then they burnt.
So, I waited a little longer
before I put in the third batch,
and now you're home.
It's perfect.
They'll be ready in about two minutes.
- Oh.
- Why are you wet?
- Ryan and I, we went dancing.
- Oh.
- Are you in love with him?
- What?
- Are you?
- No.
- I don't believe you.
- What are you talking about?
We're just friends.
Yeah, but he's in love
with you, right?
Actually, no.
No, I don't think so.
- Well, then what do you do
all the time you're together?
- I don't know.
You know, we do stuff.
We talk about stuff.
Why? I mean, you have me
to talk about stuff.
Sometimes it's nice just to have
a guy's opinion about things.
[Scoffs] Like what? Who has the
best pizza, and who has the best tits?
Gino's Pizzeria, Susan Sarandon.
Why are you acting so weird, Ame?
You're the one
who's acting weird.
I mean, you're the one
spending all your time...
with a guy you're
not even interested in.
My therapist thinks that
you may have some issues.
- You're talking to
your therapist about me?
- Of course I am.
I mean,
I worry about you.
Listen. If you ever
need to talk, I'm here.
[Timer Dings]
Oh, I left her number
on your pillow.
- Whose?
- My therapist's. Good night.
- See that guy there?
- Huh?
He's the kind of guy who walks with
his feet, if you know what I'm saying.
[Laughs]
- Come on. You do it.
- Okay.
[Ryan] She's the kind of girl
that likes crackers in her soup.
- No.
- What do you mean "no"?
- That's wrong.
- No, it's not.
- Yes, it is. It's a judgment.
- Why?
Some people put crackers in their soup
and some people don't.
- Exactly.
- No, the point is to sound like...
you're making a judgment about somebody
where there's no judgment to be made.
- It's a nonjudgmental judgment.
- No, no, no.
- That's stupid.
- No, it's funny. I'm laughing.
Yeah, 'cause it's stupid.
You wanna hear something
even more stupid?
I'm going on a date
tonight.
- Really?
- Do you think I'm nuts?
- No, no. I think it's great.
- Really?
You should get back
in the saddle.
Uh, no, no. I'm the kind of cowboy
that doesn't like to ride.
- Yeah, you see, that one's not funny.
- Yeah, I know.
-  [Rap]
-  Come and stop with the lyric
and I look inside
My best friend said
who is that guy
[Continues, Indistinct]
Ladies, how we doin'?
-  [Continues]
- What?
Hey, it's
beautiful out, huh?
- It's... It's...
-  Straight cold, say you're cold
Got straight play
[Phone Ringing]
Hello.
No. I'm not good
at that kinda thing.
You should call Hunter.
[Piano]
[Man] After all that time
in investment banking,
I decided to do something
for myself.
I sailed for ten years.
Finally, I reached a point in my life,
I said, "I don't wanna do
all the work. I wanna have..."
Jen, oh, thank God
you're here, sis.
Billy, what's wrong?
Kurt, this is Billy, my brother.
- Billy, this is Kurt.
- Hi.
Nice to meet you, Billy. I was just
telling your sister about my boat.
- No, there's no time for boats.
- Why? What happened?
It's mother.
She's sick.
- Oh, my God, what happened?
- I just told you, she's sick.
- Sick how?
- Uh...
Yeah, sick how?
You know, sick,
like the last time.
No, I wasn't there last time.
Explain it to me.
There's no time for questions.
Mother is sick. We have to go... now!
Sorry.
- Look, are you insane?
- You were great.
"Sick how?"
I felt like such an idiot.
You were great in there.
Really.
- [Chuckles]
- Thanks.
Thank you.
Oh, man.
You know, next time I was thinking
about trying it with a limp.
Baby steps, Ryan.
Baby steps.
Uh, tonight?
No, it's tomorrow night.
- No, they changed it.
- Who did? Ryan?
- No.
- Well, I can't go.
- Why not? What are you doing?
- Staying in.
I was planning
on staying in.
I was gonna give myself
a manicure and a pedicure...
and do a deep-rinse
conditioning.
Well, can't you do all that
this afternoon?
No, because I have class
this afternoon.
Class that I have to go to because
I have to talk to my professor...
about my paper
that's due on Monday,
that I was gonna finish
while my nails were drying...
and proof after I did my hair
so that everything would be done
before the party.
Can't you do all that
tomorrow?
No, because tomorrow
I'll be rushed and probably tired...
and I have to get
everything done.
See, I have to.
I can't believe they changed it.
It's Friday.
You got all weekend.
What's that
supposed to mean?
That's like on Monday saying,
"You've got all week."
[Scoffs]
[Man]
Got the ripped, rippled chips
Rippled chips
chips, chips, chips, chips
-  Are you ready
- [Coughs]
Oh, yeah
All right
We're gonna
groove tonight
Oh, yeah, all right
We're gonna groove tonight
-  Oh, yeah, all right
- Yummy.
Oh, yeah, all right
We're gonna groove tonight
[Man Rapping,
Indistinct]
- What do they want?
- Who?
They. Them.
The chiquitas.
You know, I'm busting my ass out there,
trying to fit into their little mold...
of what makes an interesting, sexy guy,
and I cannot figure out what they want.
- What do you want?
- I don't know.
Get laid. Have fun.
Have someone love me for who I am.
Oh, and, uh,
who is that exactly?
You're... You're right.
You are absolutely right.
I mean, what... what's wrong
with being from the country?
A simple kid raised on
fresh eggs and good values,
who had to get up
at the crack of dawn every morning...
with a three-legged dog named Lucky by
his side to help his pa with the cattle.
- Hunter, you're not from the country.
- Yeah?
Oh, jeez, Ryan,
what do you want me to say?
Hi. My name is Steve.
I grew up in the suburbs...
with two working parents,
two sisters and a two-car garage.
I have no real identity,
nor do I have a clue
what I'm doing or what I wanna be.
Wanna go out?
- Your name is Steve?
- You know,
the whole point of college...
is it's a place where
you can reinvent yourself.
No, it's a place where you can
define yourself. Your name is Steve?
Yes. Yes. To be honest,
I'm not so crazy about "Steve," okay?
- Why would anyone else be?
- That's who you are.
Oh, really?
It's just that easy?
Then, why don't you drop
the cool guy act and go tellJennifer...
- how you really feel about her?
- What?
But you'd better do it quick
before she leaves with that guy.
I don't feel that way
about her.
Seeing her with that guy right now,
it doesn't bother you?
No. She goes on dates
all the time.
- We talk about her dates.
- And you're fine with that?
- Yes. Yes.
- Honestly.
Okay, then, how come you're
here all by your lonesome?
Look. If you're waiting for
a girl to just walk over...
and do all the work, you
got another thing coming.
- They don't do things
that way. Trust me.
- [Woman] Excuse me.
- Is your name Ryan?
- Yeah.
- I think you're in my statistics class.
- That's nice.
What are the odds?
- You're Engineering, right?
- Yeah.
I'm Electrical.
Not me, my major.
Can you believe
how much work they give us?
But I like it, you know, because there
are so many people floating around here,
like negative ions,
with no place to go.
I'm a laser. I know what I want,
and I go straight for it.
Oh.
[Chuckles] I feel like there's
an armature spinning in my head.
- You wanna sit down?
- Uh, sure, sure.
But, actually,
I was just leaving.
It's because
I'm too forward, isn't it?
No, not at all. There's just these two
assignments that I've been putting off.
I told my girlfriend
that I would meet her...
twenty minutes ago.
- You have a girlfriend?
- Yes, I do.
- Now I feel really so stupid.
- You're not stupid.
I just...
I really have to go.
Hey, sis. You okay?
Yeah, I'm great.
Thanks, Billy.
See, amor, amore.
You say it
so beautifully.
All right, so I'm gonna
take off, then.
- Okay.
- See ya, bro.
So, how'd you get
rid of him?
We fooled around for a while,
and then I told him,
"Hey, I got
an early class."
- You fooled around?
- Uh-huh.
Hold on. Now, when we're
talking about "fooling around,"
are we talking about
"fooling around" or...
We're talking about
"fooling around."
Oh.
It's not like
we had sex.
- I didn't say that.
- Couldn't find a condom.
- You would have?
- Yeah. Probably.
I have midterms coming up.
I gotta relieve the stress somehow.
- Wow. That's amazing.
- What?
Ju... Just that
on any given date,
the possibility exists
that you'll have sex with a guy.
Isn't that the point of dating,
possibilities?
It's not like I know what's gonna
happen in advance. I don't.
Sometimes I think it'd be
a whole lot easier to have sex...
than have to sit there and think
of something clever to say.
Granted, I haven't been
in that situation in a long time,
but I just can't sleep
with somebody unless I like them.
- So, you think I'm a slut?
- I didn't say that.
- We're just different.
- Yeah, you sleep with no one.
- So?
- So, do you know any other single,
20-year-old college guys who
never sleep with anyone?
- Who don't even try?
- Hey, maybe you're trying too hard.
Ryan, you don't try
at all.
I just think that it might be making
things weird between us.
What? What are you
talking about?
Are we friends?
I mean, am I your friend...
or have I just become
your girlfriend substitute?
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
It's like with me in your life,
you never have to try.
That's the beauty
of our relationship.
You'll just never get hurt again as
long you pretend I'm your girlfriend.
Yeah. Yeah, maybe
we shouldn't hang out anymore.
Ryan?
I am so sorry.
I didn't mean that.
- Yeah, you did.
- No.
I love hanging out
with you.
I do. You're my most favorite
person in the whole world.
I don't wanna change
anything.
- Maybe you're right.
- No, I'm wrong.
You're just waiting
for the right girl to come along,
and you don't take
sex lightly.
I think that that's
a great quality.
No, l-I think I am
hiding behind you or... or us.
There was this girl
at the party the other night.
A girl girl?
You didn't tell me.
I just blew her off.
Why?
I don't know.
Maybe I should have
given her a chance.
Yeah, you shoulda.
Well, you still can.
Why not, right?
Yeah, why not?
[Softly]
Yeah.
So, is she cute?
Yeah, I guess.
Is she
cuter than me?
No. She's thinner.
[Chuckles]
Oh!
[Man On TV]
Let me get this straight.
- You think that's
totally normal.
- [Woman] Yes!
[Scoffs] I have the exact same top.
How come it looks better on her?
'Cause she's anorexic,
has fake boobs and a personal trainer.
- Are you saying I should
get my boobs done?
- Yeah. Totally.
- [Laughing] Okay. Come on.
- Aah!
- You can't say this isn't fun.
- No, can't I?
When's the last time
we did this, huh?
I mean, just you and me.
It's nice. Don't you think?
Amy, of course
it's nice.
[Chuckles]
I have an idea. What if you...
had to fail a couple
of classes and move back?
Would that be so bad?
I mean, it's just...
Italy's so incredibly far away.
Yeah, that's the beauty of it.
[Chuckles]
What about me?
What am I supposed to do next year?
- Nothin'. Just like you did this year.
- Mm.
Ame, maybe with me gone, you know,
you'll just get off your fat ass...
and go and have
some fun, huh?
I don't want to do "nothing" without
you, and I don't want to have fun.
- And I have a great ass.
- You do.
No, you do, you have a great...
You have a great ass.
- [Laughs] Oh!
- Mm.
[Smooching Sound]
Hey!
What are you doing?
I'm kissing you.
Oh, God.
God, I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
l-I don't know why
I did that. I just...
l-I really wanted
to kiss you.
- Oh, my God! I'm such an idiot!
- No, Amy! A-Amy!
Hey, buddy.
Watch this.
[Chuckling]
It's like a bridge.
It is a bridge.
- Yeah, you're absolutely right.
- [Chuckles]
- Hi!
- Hi.
- Mm.
- Is Katie coming?
She's gonna meet us at the bar.
I just talked to her.
- Really?
- Uh-huh.
This is great.
This is great!
She will be the first
to experience the new me.
- Oh, this oughta be good.
- Oh, no, I'm serious. No more lies.
It's like you said, buddy.
I don't need to pretend...
to be someone else
for someone else to like me.
- Hey, that's good!
- Yeah.
What you see is what you get:
Hunter Unplugged.
Don't you mean
Steve Unplugged
[Rock]
- [Jennifer] So, Megan seems nice?
- [Ryan] Yeah, she is.
That, uh, Paul guy. Didn't you go
out with him a couple of times before?
- Yeah. It's working out.
- Good for you.
Hey, Jen. Megan here has never been
to the Automotive Museum.
Imagine that.
Yeah.
[Chuckles]
Hey, did you guys read
how the zoo animals tried...
to reorganize their cages
in alphabetical order?
Apparently,
the aardvarks started it.
That's right, but
the zebras, they vetoed it.
- Yeah, how did you know?
- I just... I don't know.
I don't get it.
- [Chuckles]
- Me neither.
So, uh, Katie.
How are you liking Berkeley?
It's a bit overwhelming,
right?
Katie's a double major
here on scholarship.
- I don't know how she does it.
- How do you do it?
I can barely juggle
napping and sleeping.
Well, this may sound a little weird, but
I spend a lot of time with the elderly.
That doesn't sound weird.
It sounds
a little weird.
Think about it this way:
when you're sitting with someone...
who's been through two wars,
marriages, kids, grandkids,
money problems and disease...
I mean, getting a "B" on a biology exam
doesn't seem like that big of a deal.
- I think we should do
what the Eskimos do.
- Mm?
Just kick the old people
out of the igloos.
Leave them for the polar bears
and the storms at sea.
The minute they can't go on the big hunt
anymore, you gotta get rid of them.
I mean, otherwise... otherwise, they'll
just suck us dry. Those bastards.
- You're kidding, right?
- No. No, not at all.
And take away their driver's
license too, while you're at it.
Hmm?
What?
Suddenly, you're not allowed
to have an opinion anymore?
I did what you said. l-I wasn't just
agreeing for the sake of it.
I wasn't just making things up
so it would look like we had
something in common.
I did what you said.
I was being honest.
Yeah, but come on. You don't have to
say everything that comes in your head.
So, now I'm being
too honest?
- [Sighs]
- You know, I don't know
what you want from me.
I don't know what
anyone wants from me.
[Ryan]
So, what happened?
[Jen] The whole beauty of Paul was
that he was never going to settle down,
and then he fell
in love with me.
There's nothing worse
than a bad boy gone soft.
- [Scoffs] Don't I know it.
- He stopped drinking,
stopped taking drugs,
he even stopped cheating on me.
- No wonder you dumped him.
- Yeah.
It just wasn't
working out, you know?
What's up with what's-her-name?
Mary?
- Megan.
- Whatever.
- It's okay.
- That's it?
- What am I supposed to say?
- Well, do you like her?
Is she "the one"?
I don't know.
I'm workin' on it.
- You're the one who wanted to go.
- I thought it would
make me feel better.
- And?
- I don't know.
- I mean, it's such a lot of bullshit.
- Bullshit?
Just show me a movie that takes place
six months after they get together.
- You know, when everything
starts falling apart?
- Jennifer.
It's just that I don't think
that any of us know who we really are,
so how are we supposed
to know who Mr. Right is?
-  No you can't hurt me now
-  You can't hurt me now
How do you know
he's Mr. Right?
Is it because you're
both wearing black?
Drinking cappuccinos?
You both have tattoos?
[Sets Down Cup]
Who... Who here has
ever been dumped?
Okay, who here
has... has dumped someone?
I mean, we've all
been in love,
but we never know
that it's not true love until it's over.
So, what if...
there is no "one"?
Or two, or three,
or four or five?
I mean, what if
there's no such thing as true love?
But we're just
too afraid to admit it, so...
we keep on
dressing up.
We keep on pretending to be
something that we're not.
We keep turning
our lives upside down,
losing ourselves in
something that we hope...
is better than what
we think that we are.
What if that something
that we're looking for...
just doesn't exist?
You know you can't
touch me now
You can't hold me now
And I got plenty of time
[Continues, Indistinct]
- You okay?
- [Sniffles] Yeah.
Fine. I was just working
on my fear of public speaking.
[Sniffles]
Why does everything
just have to be so...
- just so?
- I don't know.
You're shakin'.
Well, you let me drink all that
damn caffeine. [Laughs Nervously]
[Groans]
I don't know
what's wrong with me. I...
Maybe you're
gettin' your period.
[Chuckles]
Yeah, maybe.
Wai... Wai...
wait a second.
No.
I can't imagine life
Without you by my side
This is love, babe
That I'm feeling
And I'm hopin'that
you're feeling the same
-  Way
- [Chorus]  Way, too
Things tend
to slip my mind
Like how you like to wine
And dine, babe
With romantic lights
You mean a lot to me
in so many ways
-  Lately
-  Have I told you I love you
-  Have I told you
-  You still mean the world to me
-  Lately
Have I told you I love you
I'll be your wishing well
Tell me what you want
Babe
Don't think twice
of our love
I say these things because
I love you
But it's hard to explain
And I'm hoping that
you're feeling the same
[Female Chorus]
Oo-ooh, oo-ooh, oo-ooh
Oo-ooh, oo-ooh, oo-ooh, ooh
You know
that all of my
Feelings are inside
[Fades]
[Birds Chirping,
Dog Barking]
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Where are you going?
- Class.
Oh, no, you're not.
You're staying right here.
- [Chuckles]
- Where I can see you.
I really... have to go.
You never go to class.
I know.
But that's why I have to go.
Wait.
I'll make us breakfast.
It's okay.
I'm late.
I'll see you later.
Is this about Megan?
- No.
- I'm gonna tell her.
Well, maybe you shouldn't.
Oh.
[Softly]
We'll talk about this later. Okay?
Yeah, okay. Okay.
Just stay as long
as you like, and, uh...
Well, you know
where everything is.
Jen!
Jen. Hi.
Um, I have to talk
about what happened.
Amy, it's okay.
No, it's not okay.
But it is okay,
because I've been thinking about it,
and I think what happened is...
that you're my best friend and
I love you and I think I got jealous...
when you were spending
so much time with Ryan,
and then, with you
graduating and everything...
and then I think in a weird way,
I was just desperately trying
to keep things the way they were,
and I did what I did
because I was afraid of losing you.
Isn't that amazing?
Yeah, without therapy. I came
up with that completely on my own.
I was thinking about us
and all the time we spent together,
and then it hit me
like a thunderbolt.
By kissing you, I was
trying to prevent change.
But maybe change
isn't always catastrophic.
Before we met, I didn't
know you at all, right?
- Right.
- Yeah, that was a change!
I mean, that was a great change.
I loved that change.
I mean, who knows? I mean, maybe
I'll kill myself by midterms next year.
But, then again,
maybe I won't.
You know?
Maybe it'll be okay.
And that's the beauty of change.
You know, you never know
how things are gonna work out.
- So, everything's okay?
- Yeah, never been better!
- Ohh.
- [Giggles]
You know, Ryan's
in your bed right now.
- Yeah.
- You know he's naked, right?
- But you know I'm curious, right?
- Yeah.
- So? What happened?
I think I was
afraid of losing him.
Megan!
Oh!
[Laughs]
[Jennifer] I'm the one
who told him to start dating.
And then he did.
And I didn't get to see him as much,
and then the whole thing with Paul
happened, and seeing him with Mary...
- Megan.
- Whatever. I just
wanted to be with him.
It was a huge mistake.
Huge. Huge, big fat mistake.
We're friends.
We're great as friends.
So, what are you
going to do about it?
I have no idea.
He takes this kind of thing
so seriously,
and the last thing in the world
I want to do is hurt him.
- [Grunts]
- Go to hell, Ryan. Go to hell.
[Ryan]
What if I'm in love with her?
- Are you?
- I don't know! Maybe.
- [Scoffs] What does that mean?
- I don't know.
I just... don't want things
to be weird with us.
Uh, buddy, if you're looking at me
for answers, I'm flattered, but, uh,
you've come
to the wrong place.
If I just pretend
like nothing happened, then I'll be...
lying to myself about
feelings I might be feeling.
But if I tell her how I might
be feeling, she'll run,
because that's what she does.
And I know that
better than anyone.
And that's the last thing
I want to have happen.
[Sighs] Being yourself,
not being yourself...
Welcome to my world.
- Does this feel weird to you?
- Oh, yes.
Okay. Well, maybe we should
talk about this.
- I think that would be good.
- All right. It's just...
I had this feeling...
that things might get strange between
us because of what happened last night,
- and I don't want that to happen.
- Me neither.
'Cause we're too good together
to let that come between us.
- It was a mistake.
- You think so?
- Yes.
- Yeah, I think you're right.
I think that we just,
you know, we got carried away,
in the moment,
and... you know.
Yes.
Last night was
really special to me...
because you're really
special to me, Ryan.
But that's all it was:
it was an incredibly special night.
I just got worried
that maybe,
you know, we'd give it more
importance than we should.
Uh, no.
I'm totally with you.
Great.
- You didn't tell Megan, did you?
- No. No.
- It's probably better not to.
- Yeah.
[Chuckles]
Well, I feel so much lighter. Do you?
Yes.
[Chuckles]
- So you wanna go fill up on vittles?
- Sure.
Yeah.
Actually, you know what?
I shouldn't.
I'd like to, but I still
have some more studying to do.
- [Sighs] Really?
- Yeah. It's pretty important.
Okay.
You call me?
- I will.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
[Man]
Oh, oh, yeah
Baby
I've kept it inside
for the longest time
And I can't
keep keepin'in
All this love
that is in my heart
Maybe it's safer
not to say that I care
-  Maybe this road
won't lead me anywhere
- [Line Ringing]
- This is Ryan. Leave a message.
- [Answering Machine Beeps]
Hey, it's me.
Where ya been?
What's going on?
Okay. Well,
you know the number. Bye.
Tell you what I'm feeling
If I keep
these feelings in
-  And if I don't say the word
-  lf I don't say the word
How will you hear
what's inside my heart
How will you know things
If I don't tell you now
Oh, oh
I'd give anything
To be in your dreams
And I can't stand
standing by
With this dream
locked inside my heart
-  My heart
[Ringing]
- This is Ryan. Leave a message.
- [Beeping]
Hey, it's me again.
Um...
Guess I thought
I might catch you at home.
Is everything okay?
Would you call me back? Please?
- All right. Bye.
-  I may never get the chance again
-  To tell you that I need you
- [Chattering]
Tell you
what I'm feeling
If I keep
these feelings in
-  And if I don't say the word
-  lf I don't say the word
How will you hear
what's inside my heart
How will you know things
If I don't tell you now
How will you know
you're inside my soul
[Fades]
Ryan Walker, where
the hell have you been?
- Hey.
- Where have you been?
Studying.
Well, what's going on?
- How are you?
- Good.
- Busy.
- Yeah. Me too.
I'm all done, so I guess it's good-bye,
Berkeley, and hello, real world.
[Chuckles]
You wanna go...
do something?
No. You know, I should really
get back to studying.
Okay.
So, I guess
I'll see you around.
But I'm gone.
I mean I'm gone in a few days.
Guess you won't have time to plan
my bon voyage party, huh?
- Oh, yeah. Italy.
- Yeah.
- You must be excited.
- Oh, you know me.
Any excuse not to shave
under my armpits. [Chuckles]
- I'll be here.
- Yeah?
Wh-When's your last exam? I mean, do
you want to go celebrate or something?
Nah, I'm leaving
right after it, so...
Okay.
I guess we'll talk.
- What's going on?
- What?
What? This!
This! What is this?
I don't know.
Nothing's going on.
Really? Because I just
ran into Megan, and she told me
that you broke up with her.
Is that what this is about?
Because I thought I told you
not to tell her anything.
Yeah, I know.
- Well, are you upset? Are you...
- No!
- So what's going on?
- I don't know!
Things are different.
But I thought
we talked about that.
Ryan, I thought that we said that we
didn't want anything to be different.
I thought we said that having sex
was just a huge mistake and...
and I mean...
I mean, it was weeks ago now.
I thought we'd go back to being just
friends. I thought that would just...
- Why was it a mistake?
- What?
You and me. Why was that a mistake?
I'm curious.
We've already talked about...
What, do you want to go over it again?
No, you want to talk?
Let's talk.
Was it a mistake because
anything that comes close to
real intimacy freaks you out?
Or just that I'm not
good enough for you?
Ryan, you...
you kissed me, and...
and I responded.
But I wouldn't have done it if I thought
it was gonna end our friendship.
And neither would I.
Ryan, if I could
take it all back, I would.
Take it.
It's yours.
Put it on the shelf
with all your other one-night stands.
Why are you doing this?
Look, that night was as much
a surprise to me as it was to you.
But being with you was like going
to a place that I had never been before.
And after you fell asleep,
I just laid there, staring up...
at those cheap fluorescent stars
you have stuck on your ceiling.
And after a while,
they just started forming a pattern,
this weird, glow-in-the-dark
pattern that linked together
our entire relationship.
And for the first time,
everything seemed clear to me,
like one
logical progression.
It felt like you and I were
the greatest plan ever made,
and I had
nothing to do with it.
Being with you made me feel that maybe
I didn't have to keep planning anymore,
because it felt like
I was actually living,
and that for once in my life, I wouldn't
have to work so hard at being happy.
That it could just happen.
Nothing will ever hurt me as much as
your reaction to that same experience.
- Ryan...
- What? What?
You want to go hang out at the library
and pretend like nothing happened?
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
I don't know what to say.
Look, you don't
have to say anything.
I have to go.
Have fun in Italy.
[Sniffles]
I'm gonna miss you so much.
I'm gonna
miss you too.
E-mail me about
anything, okay?
You know,
school, food,
tall, dark, handsome
Italian guys.
Okay? I want
to know everything.
- Okay, you gotta stop crying now.
- Yeah, you stop crying.
- I'm the one looking down
the barrel of a very lonely...
- Oh!
...final year.
Jennifer?
Jennifer.
- Hey.
- Where are you going?
- Italy.
- Right now?
Miss?
- How are Ryan's exams going?
- Good. Good. They're goin' good.
- He's doin' okay?
- He's doin' great.
He really...
He-He couldn't...
All right, that's a lie. He's in love
with someone who's not in love with him.
How do you think he is?
Are we gonna go?
[Jennifer]
I love you.
[Amy]
Bye.
- [Driver's Door
Closes, Engine Starts]
- Hi.
Hi.
- Are you a... friend ofJennifer's?
- Yeah, yeah.
I'm-I'm Amy.
Amy? Yeah, yeah.
I've heard of you.
Amy. Of course.
Nice to meet you.
And, uh, your name?
- Hmm?
- What's your name?
M-My na...
My name?
[Stammering, Chuckling]
You know, it's, um...
It's Steve.
My name is Steve.
Mm-hmm.
Well, it's nice to meet you, Steve.
Going to Europe
for the summer?
Oh. Yeah.
[Sniffling]
Yeah, I just, uh...
I just graduated.
- Congratulations. In what?
- Thanks.
Um, Latin.
Latin. How interesting.
What are you going to do with that?
Um,
I have no idea.
Well, don't worry. I spent four years
at college studying English.
- I didn't have a clue.
- Really?
Really. Now I run
my own company.
- Oh.
- You'll figure out what you want.
[Ryan's Voice] Why was it a
mistake? Was it a mistake...
because anything that even gets close
to real intimacy freaks you out?
- Stop the van!
- [Driver] What?
- Would you please stop the van?
- I can't pull over!
- Pull over 'cause I'm gettin' out!
- [Passengers Clamoring]
I can't stop the van.
We're in the middle of a bridge...
And if I don't
say the word
-  lf I don't say the word
-  How will you hear
what's inside my heart
- Ryan?
-  How would you know that
If I don't tell you now
[Ryan] Nothing will ever hurt me
as much as your reaction...
to that same experience.
If I don't tell you now
Ame?
Wha... What are you
doing here?
- I don't know.
- Oh, what's... what's wrong?
- What happened?
- I don't know. I just, uh...
- I just can't...
- [Man Coughing]
Is somebody here?
- Yeah. [Chuckles]
- Who?
Oh, it doesn't matter.
Just tell me what's wrong.
- Amy, who's here?
- [Door Opening]
- [Satisfied Sigh]
- Hunter? Hunter!
- Hunter?
- It's a long story.
- Hunter, where's Ryan?
He's on his way
back to L.A.
[Softly]
Oh.
I think he was catching
the 4:00 shuttle.
- 4:00?
- Mm-hmm.
- Which airline?
- Sky Southwest.
Thank you.
[Laughs]
- [Sighs Deeply]
- Hunter?
You can call me Tiger.
- [Laughing]
- [Roaring]
[Jet Engines Whining]
[Pilot On Intercom] Good afternoon,
folks. Sorry about the delay.
We'll be headed out
for the runway in just a minute.
[Sighs]
- [Bell Dinging]
- Put your seat back, please.
- Can I help you, sir?
- I don't know.
Can... you bring me
a glass of water, please?
I'm sorry, sir. You're gonna have
to wait until we're airborne.
Just be a few minutes.
Te amo.
Te amo, Ryan Walker.
I think she's
talking to you.
Please, ma'am. You're going
to have to take your seat now.
Did you hear what I said?
I love you.
And I'm not going to Italy.
I'm staying here with you.
- It's too late.
- No.
Everything that you said about that
night, I felt it too. And it scared me.
I was scared to lose you.
But I was even more scared...
to let myself love you,
because every time that I let love in,
somebody comes along
and takes it away.
And it just hurts so bad.
But I'm tired
of being afraid.
Ma'am? Hi, I need you to turn around
and put your seat belt on.
I just made the most important decision
of my entire life.
- You want me to put on my seat belt?
- Yes, I do.
Okay.
[Seat Belt Clicking]
What about six months from now?
How do I know you'll be happy then?
Well, how do I know
you'll be happy?
I mean, how do
we know anything?
How do we know that the plane
isn't gonna crash?
- [Woman] We're gonna crash?
- All righty, I'm not asking you again.
You're required by law to fasten
your seat belts. Both of you. Now.
- [Sighs]
- [Seat Belt Clicking]
I need you.
And that's a really hard thing
for me to accept.
But it's a whole lot easier
than imagining my life without you.
I want to do laundry
with you, Ryan.
But you send
your laundry out.
- Not anymore.
- You want to switch?
Yeah.
[Stewardess]
Will you two please sit down?
[Seat Belt Clicking]
- Oh.
- What? What is it?
It's just the whole laundry thing.
It's a metaphor, right?
[Chuckles]
Don't worry. I'll show you how.
[Engines Whining]
[Gasping]
One, two, three, four...
You should just try breathing.
It'll help you relax.
...seven, eight...
- Trust me?
[David Mead,
"The World Of A King"]
[Ends]
[Beeping]
[Sniffing]
That's lovely.
My mother wears
the same scent.
Looking for
something... Oh!
- Ooh. Oh.
- I got it.
- All right.
- So sorry. [Chuckles]
I'm really...
Actually, I was...
I was in the market
for some Cheetah pants.
[Woman Chattering]
[Laughing]
Oh, my God.
You're all
Victoria's Secret supermodels.
What are you doing
in our dressing room?
Well, all the other
rooms were full.
And I, uh, I had to change.
So...
This is where
we get changed.
Right.
[Nervous Chuckle]
Well, don't let me stop ya.
[Laughs]
- [Chuckling]
- You're fun.
And we love
funny guys.
Have you ever been
with four women before?
Once I had lunch
with my mom and her three sisters,
but I don't think
that... counts.
[Mouthing Words]
[Farting]
- What?
- [Farting Continues]
No, that's not me.
I swear.
- We know. It's us.
- Supermodels fart?
[Supermodels]
Yes.
How do you think
we stay so thin?
[Farting]
- Does it turn you on?
- [Farting Continues]
Uh... yeah.
- You do it.
- What, fart?
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
- Don't you want to turn us on?
Yes!
Yes, I do.
Okay.
[Chuckles]
Fart.
My uncle
died this way.
He shot an aneurysm.
- Less talk, okay? More fart.
- More fart.
More fart.
[Loud,
Bass Farting]
[Groaning]
- Huh? Huh?
- God, that was so...
- [Supermodels Groan Disgustedly]
- What?
Where are you goin'?
Hey!
Didn't I
turn you on?
There you have it.
Every night, for the last week.
Same dream.
So, what do you
think it means?
I don't know.
Were you breast-fed
as a child?
I knew this
was a mistake.
[Apollo Four Forty,
"Stop the Rock"]
[Filtered, Machine-Like
Voice, Indistinct]
Can't stop
Can't stop the rock
You can't stop the rock
You can't stop
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org