Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
When you see him,
tell him I'm still here.
Your friend
has got the grippe.
One of his lungs is full of fluid.
He will recover. But travel with you?
Not a chance.
He's very weak. No resistance.
What do you expect?
He is an alcoholic.
Here is your friend.
What the hell are you doing here?
Your mother asked me to come.
She wants me to bring you back home,
but the doctor said
it's out of the question for you to travel.
I wouldn't, even if I could.
I think...
I think she's dying.
Walk with me. I'm meant to exercise.
Did you go to my house?
Did you meet Kurt?
Yes.
He wanted you to know
he was waiting for you.
It's rather a pleasant change,
when all your life
you've had people looking after you,
to have someone to look after, yourself.
I thought you'd want to go back
to Brideshead one day.
Brideshead?
Are you mad?
The place would still be full of her.
I wouldn't go within
a hundred miles of the place.
I need to sit.
I'm sorry.
Whatever for?
Everything.
It's all right.
Truly.
I asked too much of you.
I knew it all along, really.
Only God can give you that sort of love.
Come home, Sebastian.
When you're well enough.
Don't finish it like this.
This is my life now.
I'm happy here.
I miss you.
How sweet of you to say that.
Dear Charles,
it was my fault for
bringing you to Brideshead.
Run away.
Run far away and don't ever look back.
I'm sorry.
You must be so proud of him.
- Was he away long?
- Two years,
and it doesn't feel like a day.
Hello, Charles.
Did you know I was on the boat?
If I said no, you wouldn't believe me.
You're married now.
Yes.
- You haven't changed at all.
- Neither have you.
- How ridiculous.
- Yes, isn't it?
Tell me this is fate.
- What?
- Nothing.
Tell me.
I was thinking about Sebastian.
Mummy died without
ever seeing him again.
I know.
Let's go up on deck.
- Are you sure?
- They're all asleep! Come on!
Come on!
Sorry.
- So where's Rex?
- I drowned him.
Forgive me, Rex!
Lady Julia, fancy meeting you here.
- Mr. Ryder.
- Could I possibly get you a drink?
Dry martini, please.
One dry Martini,
one whiskey with water.
Please, allow me.
So, why did you marry Rex?
I don't know. Because he wasn't you.
- Because he was rich.
- Because he was Catholic.
Because Mummy approved,
God rest her soul.
I thought he was my painted savage.
It turns out he was
thoroughly up to date.
Thank you.
Now, no more talk about Rex.
He's in England.
- Do you have children?
- No.
No.
- What will you tell your wife?
- Wait until London.
I have a viewing to arrange.
I'll sort it out. It'll be fine.
- Where shall we go?
- Somewhere abroad, like Daddy.
- What about Italy? Capri?
- Antibes.
- Seville.
- Verona.
- Paris.
- Brideshead.
- No!
- Why not?
- It's the loveliest place on earth.
- I can't go back there.
- Not after this.
- Nonsense.
- We've nothing to apologize for.
- No.
Besides, Rex is there.
Leave it to me.
I'll settle things with Rex.
I'll settle everything.
Trust me.
I do.
- And stop worrying!
- I will.
Good afternoon, ma'am.
- Lovely day.
Mr. and Mrs. Ryder.
Look, that's the Duke
and Duchess of Clarence.
- They want to buy one!
- How very gracious of them.
Make an effort, Charles.
I've got you the cream of Mayfair.
Mrs. Ryder, good day.
Charles, how charming you look.
Anthony.
I heard, quite by chance, at a luncheon,
that you were having an exhibition.
So, of course, I dashed impetuously
to the shrine to pay homage.
Where are the pictures?
Let me explain them to you.
This is simply charm.
Simple, creamy, English charm,
playing tigers.
But enough of art.
They tell me you are happy in love
and that is everything, isn't it?
Or nearly everything.
Everyone's talking about it.
So, it's Julia now.
And it used to be Sebastian.
Do you think I should warn her?
Warn her about what?
How apropos that you'd have
chosen jungles for your canvas.
I always thought you
were the lamb to be slaughtered,
when all along it is they
who are hunted.
There really is no end to your hunger,
is there, Charles?
Why do I feel so nervous?
- Don't be.
- Who are all these people?
- Politicians, money men.
Rex thinks there's a war
coming with Hitler.
He wants to do well out of it.
- It's all he talks about.
- Hello, Julia.
- Hello, Rex.
- Good evening, Rex.
Mr. Ryder,
welcome back to Brideshead.
I hear you're making
quite a name for yourself.
- Could I have a word with you?
- Later, I have guests.
It's cold.
Not here!
- Sorry.
- Let's go back to London.
- Let me settle everything with Rex.
- And then we'll leave?
- Yes? Charles?
- Yes.
If that's what you want.
Hello, Bridey.
- Hello, Julia. Just up from London?
- Yes.
Welcome back to Brideshead, Charles.
- How's your family?
- Fine, thank you.
- Rex still entertaining?
- He's got business.
I'm sorry he's not here.
I have a little announcement to make.
Well, come on. Out with it.
- I'm engaged to be married.
- Congratulations, Bridey.
Well, who is she?
- No one you know.
- Is she pretty?
I don't think you could
exactly call her pretty.
"Comely" is the word
I think of in her connection.
She is a big woman.
- Fat?
- No, big.
She's called Mrs. Muspratt.
Her Christian name is Beryl.
But, Bridey, where did you find her?
Her late husband, Admiral Muspratt,
collected matchboxes.
You're not marrying her
for her matchboxes, are you, Bridey?
No, no.
Matchboxes were left
to Falmouth Town Library.
I'm just holding them for collection.
Why are you laughing?
- I hope you'll be very happy.
- Thank you.
- I think I'm very fortunate.
- You sly, old thing.
When are we going to meet her?
You must bring her here.
- I couldn't do that.
- Why not?
Well, you must understand,
Beryl is a woman
of strict Catholic principle,
fortified by the prejudices
of the middle classes.
I couldn't possibly bring her here.
I don't understand.
It may be a matter of indifference
to you,
whether or not you choose
to live in sin with Charles,
but on no account would Beryl
consent to be your guest.
How dare you talk to her like that?
Bloody offensive thing to say!
Really, there was nothing
she could object to.
I was merely stating
a fact well known to her.
Take no notice of him, my darling.
So,
got you. Sorry about the delay.
I'll be outside.
The door? Door's made
from all the works of Dickens.
I had it installed especially. Want one?
No, thank you.
I know what you're thinking.
How vulgar can it get?
You wanna know the secret?
I do it on purpose.
It amuses me to offend
their delicate sensibilities.
So, you wanna take my wife off me?
You know she can't marry
a divorcé, right?
- Against the rules.
- Well, at least she'll be free of you.
She'll never be free.
Don't pretend
you've been faithful to her.
Who said anything about faith?
I bet you'd love to get your hands
on the house, though, wouldn't you?
All those pretty paintings.
All those pretty views.
Let her go, Rex. You never loved her.
The only thing you ever had
in common was religion.
Wrong. When I decided to marry Julia,
I wasn't a Catholic.
I converted before the wedding.
Bet she didn't tell you that.
- I guessed.
- Oh, yeah?
You're the type.
You people,
you never learn.
You could have had it all
if you'd been a little more flexible.
I did what I had to do.
They want a Catholic,
I'll convert to Catholicism.
It's a great religion.
You sin all you want, then you confess.
Problem solved.
You gotta woo these people.
This family don't live in the real world.
- They're mortgaged up to the hilt.
- Get to the point.
You want my wife? Make me an offer.
- I'm not just giving her away.
- Don't do this. It's demeaning.
Try a little harder.
You're a rich man, Rex,
you've already got what you wanted.
You can never have enough
of what you want.
No, you're right.
You're taking her off my hands.
That's a favor.
I'll tell you what I'll do.
You give me a couple of your jungle
pics, and I'll give you an annulment.
I hear you're worth collecting.
Come on, Charlie boy, say yes.
You know you want to.
You don't have to speak.
Just nod.
I'll have my driver take me to London.
He can pick up the paintings
in the morning.
You know she's mad.
Can't even give you children.
Lost the only one we had.
Julia?
I'm so sorry. I didn't know.
- It's just a shock.
- Shh.
Shh. Don't.
I've always known, ever since nursery.
I tried to be good, I really did.
I tried. I married Rex.
All through the backgammon
and cigars, I tried.
But it's not enough. It's never enough.
God had to punish me.
So he took my little stillborn...
My child. My girl.
With you, I thought I could
really and truly be free.
But coming back here, it's like a thread,
an invisible thread drawing you back,
inch by inch,
until all of a sudden,
you're a child again.
And that voice inside your head,
the one that Mummy planted
all those years ago in the nursery,
every night in the nursery,
filling your head with it.
And the voice is telling you,
whispering,
"Wicked little Julia,
bad little girl, living in sin. "
And here I am again with you,
living in sin.
It's over. It's over now.
- Everything set?
- That's everything, sir.
- Thank you, Wilcox.
- Best of luck, sir.
Who's that?
Go back. Turn around.
I have to go back.
- Staff, immediately!
- Yes, sir.
Come on, quickly now!
I'll help with that.
Come on, hurry!
- Yes, sir.
Shall I help, Tompkins?
- Hurry!
The sedan chair.
- Right, very gently. Very gently.
Hurry.
- Get a move with the chair.
Come along, come along.
Somebody got the rug?
Up. Gently.
Clear the stairs, please.
- Could I have the medical bag?
- Father!
- Dear Julia.
Come on, please. Come on!
I'm sorry, I was to call,
but we have been traveling
without a stop for three days.
It was Cordelia,
she was visiting us in Venice...
What happened?
- We want the bed ready
as soon as possible.
His heart. Some long word at the heart.
Hurry up.
He's dying.
He has come home to die.
Come on, everybody, that's it.
Chop-chop.
Come along.
We must get Lord Marchmain
to the great dining room.
Thank you.
He's sleeping.
Do you think we should
let Sebastian know?
You could, but I doubt he'd come.
The last I heard of him,
he was still struggling rather.
The monks have him as a porter
in the hospital in Morocco.
He seems to like it.
I think they've rather taken him
under their wing, dear old thing.
Still, salvation of a sort.
Bridey, you need to call for a priest.
I'll have a word with Father Mackay
about dropping in this evening.
Julia, your father doesn't want a priest.
All he wants is to die in his old home.
Our father's soul, all sinners' souls,
face mortal danger.
It is our duty as Catholics
to see that we do all in our power
to save those we love from themselves.
Hateful woman.
She wants me dead.
What about you?
- Do you want me dead?
- No.
You know the family
are sending for a priest.
They seem determined
to drag God into it.
Why should you care?
You don't believe in God.
You said so yourself.
Have you suddenly
become my conscience?
I've already seen Sebastian
ruined by God.
I don't see why I should watch it
happen again with your daughter.
How very caring of you.
You forget, I was there.
I watched that woman crucify my son,
little by little, and I was silent.
What does that say about me?
You're not responsible
for what she did.
But are we not also
our brother's keeper?
You, Charles, and me?
I let Sebastian down.
I let everyone down.
This way, sir.
Dear, no, that's too many!
- Papa...
- Your father needs to rest!
- Get him away.
- I've brought Father Mackay to see you.
- Get him away! Get him away!
- Out!
Everybody out! Out! Out!
- I'm so sorry, Father.
- Not at all. Give him time.
I've known worse cases
make beautiful deaths.
What were you talking
to my father about?
He doesn't want a priest.
Please, Charles.
Please don't interfere with matters
that don't concern you.
Julia...
Let's get out of here.
We'll go to Italy.
- Capri.
- I can't leave now, my father's dying.
When this is over,
I can make you happy.
- Why should I believe you?
- Believe me.
You just bought me from Rex.
What are you talking about?
According to you,
I'm worth two pictures.
I thought I'd fetch at least three.
Don't be ridiculous.
- That was Rex.
- You agreed to it, Charles.
- I had no choice!
- You agreed!
I thought I was doing the right thing.
I thought I was doing what you wanted.
No, you thought you were getting me
and the house, together.
- Is that really what you think?
- You tell me. Please, tell me.
What does Charles Ryder really want?
Can you imagine what it was like
for me to be invited into Brideshead?
Me,
Charles Ryder,
"the painter from Paddington,"
as your mother so sweetly put it.
There was no humiliation
I would not have endured
just to be part of that dream.
And your mother, that woman is more
alive now than she ever was.
She's in every brick,
every stone, every slate.
Sebastian was right.
We should run away.
- Why did you bring me here?
- We can still leave.
- Bridey...
- Don't interfere, Charles.
Now, try and remember your sins
and tell God you're sorry.
I'm going to give you absolution now.
And while I'm giving it,
I want you to tell God you're sorry
you offended him,
and then I want you
to make a sign, if you can.
- Amen.
Amen.
Please, God,
please, if you're there, forgive him.
Forgive me. Oh, God, forgive me.
Let him have a sign.
Sebastian used to loathe this painting.
Daddy gave it to Mummy
as a wedding present.
Tell me.
I wanted too much.
It's nobody's fault.
But you're not coming with me.
I can't shut myself off from His mercy.
Can you understand that?
I don't want to make it easier for you.
I hope your heart
breaks.
But I do understand.
I have to let you go.
Whether by fate or the
divine ironies of some higher power,
I find myself returned once more
to Brideshead.
Let it go.
Did I want too much?
Get him out of my sight!
Did my own hunger blind me to
the ties that bound them to their faith?
Am I only now, shadowed by war,
all moorings gone,
alone enough to see the light?
Worst place we've struck yet.
No facilities, no amenities,
and the nearest village
is a five-mile walk.
Mind you, there's a rumor
of a big push coming.
They'll be shipping
us off to France soon.
Yes, very soon.
Where are the family now?
Does anyone know?
Some Lady Flyte lives
on her own here, normally.
She's overseas
with the women's service.
Her elder brother died in the Blitz.
They're all Roman Catholic.
- I take it you're not religious, Hooper.
- Me? God, no. Can't see the point in it.
You're born, you live, then you die.
Do you have any hopes
for the future, Hooper?
Hopes? Oh, aye, plenty.
It's our time now. You watch.
The old ways, all this, they're gone.
Future belongs to us,
so long as we don't get shot.
How about you, sir?
You got someone
special waiting for you?
Me? No.
I've loved and lost
for more than one lifetime.
Would you like me
to drive you back, sir?
No, not yet. Carry on, Hooper.
Very good, sir.
Sergeant!
Subtitles by LeapinLar
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org