Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
How long have you been deaf in this ear?
Since as long as I can remember.
Shut up! Keep still
while the doctor is examining you.
I need a fish hook
about the right size for a mullet...
...with a long shank and a hammer.
A fish hook? A hammer?
Here is the fish hook and a hammer.
Right! Now, keep still.
A Pea.
lt is very PaPilionaceous, is it not?
He must have stuck it in his ear
when he was a child.
Oh, my God. lt's loud.
l mean, everything is loud.
.My own voice is loud.
.Your deafness is cured.
.A very satisfactory oPeration.
.l've had an oPeration?
l'm the only Person l know
who's had an oPeration.
lt feels as if my whole head has filled uP
with sPring water, all cold and clear.
Talk some sense when the doctor
has been kind enough to cure you.
All these years thinking you are deaf.
But now, there will be no excuses
when l ask you to remember...
...to collect something on your way home...
...or to stoke uP the fire
before we go to church.
PerhaPs now you will hear me...
...when l say to you,
''Mend the chair, Stamatis.
''Fix the leaking roof, Stamatis.''
And now, l won't have to sPeak so loud.
Antonio, do you remember our island?
It does not change.
On the feast day of Saint Gerasimos...
...we still bring our sick to the holy place...
...and pray that their suffering may cease.
When Pelagia was a child...
...I promised her that I would write
a history of Cephallonia.
But, somehow,
I still have not found the time.
I wanted her to understand
how a land so peaceful...
...could be shattered
by earthquakes and war.
I wanted her to understand
why sometimes the gods bless us...
...and why they sometimes
become angry and shake us...
...and fill our lives with pain.
I want her to learn the lesson
that nature teaches us:
That we should not ask
why we are wounded...
...only if the wound can be healed.
A Purely Psychological Phenomenon.
How do you exPlain the miracle?
Can Lenin cure the mad?
Can Stalin heal the afflicted?
lt's obvious. lt's a setuP
to keeP PeoPle enslaved to religion.
You don't have to shout. l'm not deaf.
l want to see the cannon again.
Yeah!
l will need stones from the street,
as many as you can find.
Be right back.
Well, children, cover your ears!
Oh, my God!
That hurts! Oh, that hurts!
Will he die?
Eventually, one of these days, like all of us.
Turn over.
Good strong gluteals.
Tell us about the gluteals.
Please. Come closer. Have a good look.
Fetch your friends. Everybody's welcome.
Gluteals.
Maximus, medius, minimus.
The maximus is the external surface
of the ilium...
...between anterior
and interior gluteal lines.
Mandras!
.Iatre?
.He'll be fine.
They told me you were shot.
l thought l was going to die.
l don't know why
you can't keeP out of trouble.
You should count yourself lucky
you don't have a son.
Boys, they never grow uP! Look at me.
Old before my time.
lt's too hot.
The fish are all hiding in the rocks...
...or keePing cool at the bottom of the sea.
Put me down! Put me down!
There are reports today
that a Greek battleship...
...the Eli, has been torpedoed
by an Italian submarine...
...despite the fact that Greece
is not yet involved in the war.
Prime Minister Metaxas has protested...
...to Mussolini's government in Rome,
which denied responsibility for the attack.
There are continued reports of fighting...
...between Greek and Italian soldiers
on the Greek-Albanian border.
In Athens this morning,
the Italian ambassador denied rumors....
What are they saying?
The ltalians are in Albania,
close to the border.
.They have rePorted some fighting.
.There, you hear that!
And they are saying
they are not about to declare war.
.There. What did l say?
.They want to catch us sleePing.
To creeP uP on us in the dead of night!
.You filthy liar!
.Your father was a goat!
Shut uP!
lf you two don't stoP trading insults,
l'm going to start taking coffee at home!
Mandras wants to marry me.
l told him he'd have to ask you.
.l don't want to marry him.
.You don't like him.
You are both too young.
Everyone is too young when they marry.
l have often thought
you'd only marry haPPily with a foreigner.
A dentist from Norway.
Or something.
Mandras is not your equal.
And he would exPect
to be better than his wife.
He is a man, after all.
l will tell you now what l will say to him.
l am not giving away a dowry.
.Who marries without a dowry?
.You should marry for love.
l love Mandras!
So what am l suPPosed to do?
Go off to Mandras' mother's house
with nothing but a bag of clothes?
And my goat.
l'll never be able to show my face.
l'll be the laughingstock of CePhallonia.
You can imagine how PeoPle will talk.
l don't know how you will bear the shame.
There is going to be a war.
Terrible things haPPen in wars.
Use this to defend yourself.
And, if necessary, use it against yourself.
Your marriage will have to wait.
l look around me.
l see fishermen. l see farmers.
l see strong, healthy men
who are born free!
But today, your freedom is in danger.
The ltalian army sweePs through Albania...
...and her trooPs are driving to cross
the frontiers of Greece!
lf you care about your country
then you must fight to defend her!
Join the war in Albania!
Fight for your mothers...
...your sweethearts, your wives,
your children!
Fight for the freedom...
...for all Greek PeoPle to live their lives
with dignity and resPect!
When l come back from the war,
we will get married.
And l will build a house for Pelagia...
...on the land that belonged to my father.
l know we are different.
l don't know about the world.
Where have l been? What could l know?
l don't know how to say what l feel inside.
l don't know how to tell you
what is in here.
But l think...
...l know...
...l love you.
Tomorrow, l leave for the war.
Pelagia...
...come and dance with me.
l'll write. l Promise.
And Promise that you will write to me.
''My darling: You have not written
since that day I saw you off.
''And I am so terrified that I'm not getting
any letters from you...
''...because you have been wounded
or taken prisoner.
''And I have nightmares that you are dead.
''Summer has turned to winter,
and I am writing my 100th letter to you.
''The wounded who have returned
bring news of terrible conditions...
''...freezing cold, no food.
''But they bring no news from you.
''Every day I wait for the mail
from Argostoli...
''...and every day there is nothing.
''And I feel as if I am going mad
with worry and fear.
''I try not to lose hope...
''...but I long to feel something,
even if it is only pain.''
We won! We won!
lt's over!
We've beaten them in Albania! Look!
8,000 of us against 14,000 ltalians,
and we forced them to withdraw!
What?
Hitler will never let
his laPdog be humiliated.
He will come to Mussolini's aid.
''I have written this letter a dozen times.
''And a dozen times, I have thrown it away.
''I don't know how to describe my feelings.
''It's as if I've been waiting 100 years
to hear from you.
''Waiting 100 years for you to return.''
This is hoPeless.
lt's all wrong!
Following the Greek defeat of the Italians
in Albania, Hitler counterattacked...
...and the German army has driven a path
through to the Greek capital of Athens.
A number of Greek ships were destroyed
in the bombing of the port of Piraeus.
On April 27, the Athenian
military commissioner, General Carvacos...
...handed over the keys of the ancient
city to his German counterpart...
...Lieutenant Colonel Von Sefen...
...and preparations were underway
for a carve-up of the territory.
Hitler retains direct control
of Northern Greece...
...including Salonica and
the southern island of Crete.
The rest of Greece will be under
the control of Hitler's ally, Mussolini...
...but the Germans will retain
the final authority.
Left, right. Left, right....
Bella bambina at two o'clock!
Attention! Face!
Hustle. Hustle.
ClTY HALL . Fuck off
CaPtain Corelli.
''Fuck off.''
Tell the mayor
that unless we receive the surrender...
...of the town's authorities
in five minutes...
...we'll mobilize our trooPs
and storm the building.
The mayor says,
if you don't know what ''fuck off'' means...
...then come inside and we'll show you.
''We refuse to surrender...
''...to a nation that we have defeated
in Albania.
''And we reserve the right...
''...to surrender to a German officer...
''...of significant rank, so fuck off.''
Who is this? Who are you?
CaPtain Weber, liaison officer
with the Grenadiers at Lixouri.
''CaPtain'' is not what we would call
a significant rank.
There are only 200 Germans on the island...
...and CaPtain Weber is the highest.ranking
officer amongst them.
Our decision is...
...that surrendering
to CaPtain Weber's dog...
...is more aPProPriate
than surrendering to an ltalian.
Carlo Guercio rePorting for duty, sir.
.Carlo, where have you served?
.Albania.
Albania?
None of us have seen any action yet.
l was with the Giulia Division.
Then you have fought enough for all of us.
Carlo, can you sing?
Let's hear you sing.
No matter.
Everyone in our battery is a member
of the oPera society.
These are the rules of engagement.
One: All those called
to regular musical fatigues...
...shall be obliged to Play
a musical instrument.
SPoons, the helmet,
comb, PaPer and so on and so on.
Two: Anyone who says that Donizetti
is better than Verdi...
...shall be required
to sing Funiculi-Funicula...
...and other songs about railways.
Three....
This is an outrage! Quite imPossible.
lt's out of the question!
Sir, the fact is, l am sorry to say,
and with great regret...
...that my orders are to billet an officer
in your home.
l am a doctor. This is my surgery!
.l don't have room for guests!
.These are my orders!
l don't care!
l don't recognize your authority.
Wait a minute.
What is wrong with your feet?
l have terrible corns.
My boots are killing me.
You are a quartermaster.
You must have access to medical suPPlies.
To treat your corns, l will need morPhine,
hyPodermic syringes...
...sulfur ointments, surgical sPirit,
neosalvarsan...
...iodine, scalPels, collodion bandages, lint.
PerhaPs your officer
could bring suPPlies when he comes.
My father is not here.
He'll be home this evening.
You don't even know who l am.
l walked all the way from the hills.
No boots.
l wrote to you every day.
A hundred letters...
...and not a single rePly.
l never learned...
...to read or write.
Oh, Lord, what a stench.
lt's worse than Pigs.
You see, Pelagia...
...what a state these men get into
when there are no women around?
And l don't care if he's been to war.
lf we catch his fleas and lice,
l'm going to skin him alive.
Ammonia, oil of sassafras,
zinc for scabies.
You are a woman,
and you know so many things.
At least, you can see what you're getting.
Not much of a bargain, is he?
You fall in love with a Person,
not the body.
Love enters by the eyes and also leaves
by the eyes. Take it from me.
We beat the ltalians.
We had them running.
But we couldn't fight the Germans.
lf l could cook...
...l would exchange jobs with you.
ln fact, l might retire.
Bella bambina.
Forgive me. Forgive me.
l don't mean to embarrass you.
l'm CaPtain Antonio Corelli.
And that man is one of our heroes.
He has 100 medals for saving life
and none for taking it.
A brave ltalian is a freak of nature.
Said like a true Greek Patriot.
CaPtain Corelli, l want a word with you.
Now.
l want an exPlanation.
l want to know
why you have defaced the monument.
.What monument?
.You've changed the inscriPtion to Latin.
Do you think you can
so easily erase our history?
ls this how you wage war,
by the chiPPing away of letters?
.l must Protest.
.You cannot Protest! There is no excuse!
l was about to Protest
because l was not resPonsible for it.
Pathetic.
lf you could tell me
where l'm going to sleeP.
ln my daughter's room.
.But where will your daughter sleeP?
.lt's none of your business where l sleeP.
Tonight, l'll sleeP in the yard. Tomorrow,
l'll request other accommodation.
l've made an arrangement
with your quartermaster.
You're staying here
whether you like it or not.
But your daughter's bed,
l feel it would not be..
l don't care how you feel.
That is not my Problem.
l am not the aggressor,
you understand me?
.This is very good.
.This is CePhallonian meat Pie.
ExcePt, thanks to you PeoPle,
it doesn't have any meat in it.
l could bring some food,
a little wine, some Panettone.
We don't accePt food from the enemy.
Maybe a little Panettone.
l am going for a walk.
Curfew starts in one hour's time.
l was born here. This is my island.
Aren't you going to go and arrest him?
He's defying you, ignoring the curfew.
You're absolutely right.
Quick, get the gun.
Somebody shoot him!
Capitano Antonio Corelli.
Now you try. Capitano Antonio Corelli.
Lemoni.
Babibaba Sinono Calicali.
What? ''Babibaba''?
Capitano.
-Capitano.
-Si. Antonio.
.Lemoni. Go home.
.Corelli.
Go on. You can come back later.
Signorina.
ln times of war,
we have to make the most...
...of what little innocent Pleasure there is.
''l've started to make a waistcoat for you.
''Eagles and flowers
embroidered with gold thread.
''But l can't seem to get them to match uP.
''One flower is much bigger.
''One eagle is in a different Place
from the other.
''And when l try to make them more even,
it gets worse.
''l just can't get it right.''
You could kill him, you know?
He's the enemy.
You could Poison him.
No one would know how he died.
Dimitris and SPiros have left
to join the Partisans.
They've gone by boat to Patras...
...and who knows where from there.
.l should be with them.
.You're not going until you're strong again.
Read the last one.
The last letter you wrote
before l came home.
''My darling:
''l've heard nothing from you
for such a long time...
''...and l feel desPerate and helPless.
''And l am burning my brains with worry.
''Yesterday, l wrote you a long letter
that said everything Perfectly.
.''And believe it..''
.Listen.
l can't stay here.
Signorina.
.You are drunk.
.Yes, l confess.
We've been drinking, singing,
generally misbehaving.
l thought you were a soldier.
CaPtain Antonio Corelli,
33rd Regiment, Artillery...
...rePorting for duty!
ls everything a joke to you?
No. Not everything.
CaPtain Corelli...
...l think this would be a good time
to hear you Play the mandolin.
What on earth are you doing?
.l was just about to start.
.Well, about time too.
The first 45 and a half bars
are for the orchestra.
Allegro, moderato, grazioso.
You have to imagine the orchestra.
l'm damned if l can sit through
all that taPPing again.
Just Play your Part.
lf l do that, l'll get confused...
...about when l'm suPPosed to come in,
and that...
...in a concert hall, would be a disaster.
l aPologize for disruPting the concert.
l aPologize to each and every one of you.
To those in the cheaPest seats,
in the gods...
...to Your Majesties in your royal boxes...
...draPed in your jewelry and your fine furs.
But l'm damned
if l can imagine an orchestra.
l am going to bed.
ls this where the caPtain sleePs?
l was coming to see you.
l'm leaving, Pelagia.
ln the morning.
l'll take my boat to Astakos.
.lt's not safe.
.l'm a fisherman.
l know those waters
like the back of my hand.
l don't want you to go.
lf l die, l won't have died for nothing.
And if l live...
...l'll walk with my head held high
for the rest of my life.
And everyone will say, ''That's Mandras
who fought for his country in the war.''
l finished your waistcoat.
You can take it now if you want.
The two sides, they are not the same.
The ltalian caPtain.
Pindus gorges, Albania.
14,000 of you against 8,000 of us.
You could have driven us into the sea.
lf it wasn't for your German friends,
we would've.
My friends are the men in my battery...
...the PeoPle l grew uP with,
PeoPle of my hometown.
So, what do you think
of our island, CaPtain?
.l like your island.
.And what do you think of our girls?
What do you think of my Pelagia?
Goodbye, Pelagia.
My beautiful Pelagia.
.Heil Hitler.
.Heil Puccini.
l saw your Party.
l thought l would introduce myself.
You mean, you saw naked women
and wanted to get a closer look.
.We've met before.
.The surrender at the town hall.
You're much better at having Parties
than at negotiating surrender.
Well, we're ltalian, famous for singing,
eating, making love.
.What's your name?
.Antonio Corelli. Grazie.
You Germans always have
the best tobacco, huh?
.How many of you are here now?
.APProximately 1,200 under Colonel Barge.
Here to keeP an eye on us.
Doesn't it feel good
to have your allies here?
l thought all you Nazis had blonde hair.
l come from the Tyrol.
Grew uP in the Austrian mountains.
All my family...
...going back as far as we can remember,
have dark hair.
Like Adolf Hitler?
You neglected to tell me your rank.
l am the breve.
Massimiliano here is the semibreve.
He is the minim. Those boys are
the crotchets and the quavers.
Piero here is the semiquaver,
and Carlo is the rest...
...the Pause between the notes.
ln the oPera club,
we have our own ranking system...
...but otherwise, l am a caPtain,
33rd Regiment of Artillery.
.Do you sing?
.No, not really.
Maybe on my own, in the bath.
Have a drink. Be haPPy!
But just remember, if you ever exPress
admiration for Wagner...
...you will be shot without trial,
and without leave of aPPeal.
From the toP.
Come on.
Buona sera, signorina.
Are you going to shoot me?
lt wasn't loaded.
l've never aimed a gun at anybody.
Never in my life.
lt must be very difficult for you
to have to Put uP with us.
to have to live with yourself.
You lie in the sun and swim in the sea...
...and flirt with your Prostitutes.
And there are PeoPle l know,
PeoPle l grew uP with...
...who are fighting for their lives
and dying for what they believe in.
And all you do is sing!
What's there to sing about?
We are in the middle of a war,
not an oPera house.
And here you think you are so cultured
with your Pasta...
...and your Panettone
and your Puffed.uP oPera.
Why don't you take your holiday
on somebody else's island?
What is there to sing about?
There is singing
when babies are baPtized...
...when you celebrate a marriage.
Men sing as they work.
Soldiers sing as they march into battle.
And there is singing when PeoPle die.
l've always found something in life
worth singing about.
And for that, l cannot aPologize.
For the fact that l've caused you Pain,
l cannot aPologize enough.
l have not been able to imagine until now...
...the offense l have given.
.What are those?
.My things.
l can see that. Why?
l'm going to stay
in the encamPment with my men.
.l think it will be best.
.But you must understand.
l made an arrangement
with your quartermaster.
We agreed the terms.
l would not feel comfortable
letting him down.
Therefore, l think you should stay.
l don't think your daughter would agree.
She understands the imPortance
of honoring an arrangement.
l'll sPeak to the quartermaster, make sure
you continue to get medical suPPlies.
l've enjoyed meeting you.
l'm only sorry about the circumstances.
''Citizens of Cephallonia,
in these unfortunate and difficult times...
''...let us show the world
how two ancient cultures...
''...can coexist and behave
in a civilized manner towards one another.
''Please join us
in an evening of relaxation...
''...as we extend the hand
of friendship to you all.''
l'll be back in a minute.
My friend thinks you're very Pretty.
Why doesn't he tell me himself?
He's too shy.
He wants to know if you'll dance with him.
No, l can't. Not with a German.
But tell him thank you.
Tell him l don't mean to be rude.
Can we dance now?
lt's Turkish.
From the Great War.
.We should exPlode it.
.The exPlosive must have decayed.
lt's been floating for about 20 years.
We could Put on a good show.
We are going to exPlode the bomb!
lt will be a fantastic exPlosion!
And when the time comes,
nobody must come down to the beach!
You must watch from where you are!
You must be one of the most stuPid PeoPle
l've ever met.
You wanted to show off,
so you nearly get us all killed.
l can see your liPs moving,
but l can't hear a word you're saying.
lt should Pass in a day or two.
Your father says
it will Pass in a day or two.
Does he? ls that what
the great doctor says?
What are you saying?
Are you saying how beautiful life is
since the ltalians arrived?
All my life, l've been waiting.
l don't know how l survived
before you came.
Are you saying
how much you missed having me around?
l miss you so much l can't sleeP at night.
The other night, when you were dancing...
...the way you were moving...
...the turn of your head...
...l thought l could watch you forever.
You think you can come here...
...and turn my whole world uPside down?
lodine.
Bandages. Dressings.
This is all l have.
l can't give you any morPhine.
And we need all the quinine we have.
12,000 of our men on the mainland
are sick with malaria.
SuPPlies are not getting through.
Nobody knows why.
Nobody knows what is haPPening.
And l'm going to eat.
You know, when l met Pelagia's mother...
...she was betrothed to somebody else.
He nearly killed me.
l had to leave the island.
l had to lie low for a while.
She wants to train to be a doctor,
you know.
You think she'd make a good doctor?
l think she'd make a very good doctor.
Another thing.
This is a very ancient land.
We have had nothing but earthquakes
and slaughter for 2,000 years.
We've had massacres
at Sami and Fiskardo.
God knows where else.
There will be more.
lt's only a question of time.
So don't make any Plans.
After the war, l'll leave it with you.
You're very sweet.
The Allies have landed in ltaly.
We can all go home then!
l can't believe it.
You really want this war to be over?
What is wrong with you ltalians?
We don't have your advantages, Gunter.
Advantages?
The advantage of thinking
that other races are inferior to yours.
lt's a question of science.
You can't alter a scientific fact.
l don't care about science.
lt's morality that counts.
What is your morality?
lf l were to see a man
being set uPon by others...
...l would think that man was my brother.
That is my morality.
l would make myself believe it's Personal.
For me, too, the war is Personal.
l lost both my grandfathers
in the Great War.
A war that you started.
My father's brother,
two of my mother's brothers.
l grew uP in a country
where it was hard to survive.
We were hungry all the time.
All we ever knew about was defeat,
but now....
Sometimes it is better to lose
than to have so much blood on your hands.
lt's a beautiful night,
and everything is Peaceful.
And we should think about falling in love.
That's beautiful.
What is it?
lt's Pelagia's Song.
l wrote you that song because l love you.
l don't care if the world knows it.
l couldn't care less if l never Pick uP
the mandolin again.
When l was Playing,
it felt like my hands were lumPs of wood.
lt felt as if every note was sour or stale.
And then l realized...
...it's useless.
lt's hoPeless.
lt can't begin to exPress
the way l feel about you.
Next time you see him,
tell him l have got his mandolin.
He left it in the square.
Four more boys from the village
have left to join Mandras.
Constantine's boys.
.Kostas's brother. What's his name?
.George.
He's only 15.
He always worshiPPed Mandras.
Do you love him?
We are engaged to be married.
l am not talking about Mandras.
When you fall in love,
it is a temPorary madness.
lt eruPts like an earthquake,
and then it subsides.
And when it subsides,
you have to make a decision.
You have to work out whether your roots
have become so entwined...
...that it is inconceivable
that you should ever Part.
Because this is what love is.
Love is not breathlessness.
lt is not excitement.
lt's not the desire to mate
every second of the day.
lt is not lying awake at night
imagining that he is kissing...
...every Part of your body.
Don't blush.
l'm telling you some truths.
That is just being in love...
...which any of us
can convince ourselves we are.
Love itself is what is left over...
...when being in love has burned away.
Doesn't sound very exciting, does it?
But it is.
Do you think
that you could begin to imagine...
...that that is how you will come to feel
with CaPtain Corelli?
You must act honorably...
...with resPect to Mandras and his mother.
And...
...Pray for the liberation of the island...
...because then,
everything becomes Possible.
Drosoula.
All night,
l've been thinking about Mandras.
About me and Mandras.
Thinking about how long we've been aPart.
.When did you arrive?
.Where is your ring?
My fingers got too thin.
l thought l would lose it.
.Where will you stay?
.l want to ask you something.
We need to see the ltalian caPtain.
l want you to ask him to meet with us.
As soon as you can.
In Germany, the port of Hamburg...
...suffered a second day
of continuous air raids...
...from nearly 800 British aircraft,
leaving much of the city in ruins...
...while in Italy, Rome has finally fallen
to the Allied advance...
...after weeks of fierce fighting...
...and a huge bombing campaign
on the capital.
Allied commanders are watching
the Mediterranean countries...
...occupied by German and Italian forces.
It's not yet clear what the German attitude
to an Italian withdrawal might be...
...but Germany will assume sole command
of many strategic territories.
Hitler is expected to send
massive reinforcements...
...through the Balkans and into Greece...
...as the Nazis struggle to maintain
supply routes to North Africa.
Mandras is back. He wants to see you.
lt's over! lt's all over!
Mussolini has fallen! We're going home!
Colonel Barge and l have agreed
the date for the surrender...
...of our heavy weaPons and machine guns:
SePtember 15.
That's in five days' time.
Why should we lay down our arms?
They were our allies.
.Why should they be dictating terms to us?
.We have surrendered.
Mussolini has surrendered
to the British and the Americans.
.Not to the Germans.
.Colonel Barge and l have agreed.
lf we surrender our arms...
...do we have confirmation
that they will not use force against us?
l have a Personal undertaking
from Colonel Barge and his officers...
...that our trooPs
will be allowed safe Passage.
My men will never agree
to return home without their weaPons.
lf you surrender your arms
in times of war...
...then you are no longer a man.
lf you were in their Position,
if you were German...
...you would want to be certain
for your own security...
...that the weaPons will not be Passed on...
...to the Allied forces
or to the Greek Partisans.
Or turned against you.
You must be looking forward
to going home.
There'll be PeoPle haPPy
to see you again, l'm sure.
Your family, your mother,
your wife, your girlfriend.
.You wanted to see me?
.We need arms.
Machine guns, ammunition, land mines.
.Anything you can sPare.
.How can l give you weaPons?
.You know l can't do that.
.You've surrendered.
lf you don't intend to fight,
you won't need your weaPons.
We have a country to defend.
There is a massive builduP
of German trooPs on the mainland.
The 117th Jaeger Division
is nearing the Corinth Canal.
The 104th is moving south
from Yugoslavia.
.Then you are not in any Position to resist.
.Unless we act now.
Do you know, CaPtain, on Lefkada lsland...
...all the ltalians who surrendered have
been sent to Prison camPs in the North?
.We heard they went home.
.The trains were diverted in Albania.
ln this war, CaPtain,
it's hard to know who you can trust.
But one thing is certain:
You can't trust the Germans.
Last night, l dreamed l was sitting
in a restaurant in Piazza Navona...
...eating zuppa di cozze piccante...
...then a Plate of taglierini alla boscaiola.
Colonel Barge requested l withdraw
your battery from Antisamos Beach.
lf they wanted to bring in
heavy reinforcements...
...this is where they would do it.
ls this an order?
CaPtain, don't you want to go home?
Halt!
Are you going to let us through?
My orders are to suPervise the surrender
of your arms and weaPons.
The deadline for the handover
is at noon tomorrow.
This order comes from Colonel Barge.
He's asked me to assure you
that if you surrender your arms...
...you will be guaranteed safe Passage.
Like the ltalian garrison at Lefkada?
Lefkada?
But they laid down their weaPons.
They went home.
You must be looking forward
to seeing ltaly again.
You think we could keeP in touch?
l mean, after the war, of course.
You can have my gun
when l finish my cigarette.
Get your hands off me!
l understand your concern.
lf l were in your shoes,
l would be asking questions, too.
Of course we'll investigate what haPPened.
l can tell you what haPPened.
Four of my men are dead!
.We'll take the aPProPriate action.
.What does that mean?
Does it mean that l can write
to the families of these men...
...and tell them
that their murderers will be charged?
.That justice will Prevail?
.CaPtain.
You force us at gunPoint to line uP
and surrender our arms!
You imPound our weaPons.
.We're suPPosed to be allies!
.CaPtain Corelli, Please!
We need some kind of assurance.
l can assure you that the order to disarm...
...did not come from my headquarters.
We have agreed to the surrender
of our arms by noon tomorrow.
We would like your assurance
that no more of our trooPs...
...will be forcibly disarmed
before that deadline.
Herr General...
...by noon tomorrow,
l guarantee you'll be on your way home.
This is not our war.
This is between the Greeks
and the Germans.
Would you Prefer we left them
to fight on their own?
The Fourth Regiment will hold Antisamos.
We'll keeP the Fifth in reserve at Assos...
...and l will take the Eighth
and Ninth to Argostoli.
All gun lines to be in Position
by first light tomorrow.
.lf we resist now, we can beat them.
.What if the Germans send Planes?
Don't go near Argostoli.
Stay away from Antisamos Beach.
l want to lie across the road
so that you can't leave.
KeeP a gun with you at all times.
Promise me.
.Come back to me.
.Promise me.
When it's over, you will come back to me.
l know what you feel.
You think, if he died your world will stoP.
l will look out for him.
Mama! Mama!
Stay here! lt's not safe!
.What are you doing?
.She's a traitor and a whore!
HelP me! HelP me!
HelP me!
The enemy's 100 meters away.
There's heavy armor coming now.
Let's go!
WHORE . TRAlTOR
Come on, move!
Shoot me.
He's alive.
He was alive when l found him.
Fragments of uniform in the bullet holes.
SPlinters of rib.
Just do it.
l am not a surgeon. l have no Penicillin.
l have no sterile water, no serum.
Please, Father, do it!
Hold.
Four of his ribs are broken.
PaPa!
Antonio, don't move. Don't move!
lf you even try to move,
you will hemorrhage to death.
No, you must lie still.
.l don't..
.You were lying under Carlo's body.
lf it wasn't for him, you wouldn't be alive.
How did l get here?
Mandras found you.
Antonio, you should try
and drink something.
What would you like for lunch?
Not that there's any choice, of course.
But if there was.
We needed something...
...steel, wire to bind the bones.
Of course, they'll have to be removed
sometime in the future.
l could try and get some new strings
from somewhere.
l could ask around.
.What are you doing?
.lf they find me, they'll shoot you.
.They'll kill you if you leave.
.l don't belong here, Pelagia!
l never belonged here!
Ever since l came,
look what has haPPened all around you.
l love you.
l had no right to make you love me
when you weren't mine to love.
Don't do that!
Go to Dr. lannis' house. Go! Go! Go!
Go now!
Mama will be back!
Do you hear? Mama will..
Dimitris will row you to a boat
out in the bay.
You should be home by tomorrow night.
We must go.
l had to see you again, one last time.
We must go!
Don't say anything.
Look at me.
.We must go!
.Go.
Go!
Why did you save him?
Why didn't you leave him to die?
l wanted you to love me again.
ln Albania...
...l made them read every one
of these to me.
''Mandras, l love you. Mandras, l want you.
''Mandras, when are you coming back?''
And then one day, a different letter.
''l don't know how to describe my feelings.
''lt's as if l've been waiting 100 years
to hear from you.
''Waiting 100 years for you to return.
''Once l thought my heart
was overflowing with love for you...
''...but now all l feel is emPtiness.
''And l think all the time,
it was a Pretense...
''...that l never loved you at all.''
l'm sorry.
The war we thought
would never end is over.
And the island we thought
we had lost forever...
...is ours again.
In the doctor's house,
there are three of us now:
The doctor, his daughter...
...who is training to be a doctor...
...and Lemoni.
lt's for you.
From ltaly.
What is it?
lt's a record.
We should start making suPPer.
That's what we should do.
''I do not know
if this letter will reach you...
''...or even if you are alive.
''Perhaps someone else
sent us your record...
''...and that is why we found no note.
''I would like to say that Pelagia is happy...
''...but she is full of tears
she will not let fall...
''...and of a grief no doctor can mend.
''She blames herself for the pain
we have suffered...
''...and, perhaps, the same is true for you.
''You know I am not a religious man...
''...but I believe this:
''If there is a wound, we must try to heal it.
''If there is someone
whose pain we can cure...
''...we must search till we find them.
''If the gods have chosen
that we should survive...
''...it will be for a reason.''
Where is your miracle today then?
What do we have to say about that?
''Wake uP. Fetch the firewood.
Fix the roof. Paint the house.''
She's driving me mad.
When l was deaf,
l couldn't hear her nagging.
But now....
Iatre, l beg of you, helP me.
Put the Pea back in my ear.
l was looking for Lemoni.
She's down the road.
l went to the house.
lt doesn't exist anymore.
We are building a new one.
Your father wrote you got the record.
lt's a guitar. lt's different.
l tried to live without you.
l tried to make myself believe
l could live without you.
The scar healed well.
Stamatis, do you love your wife?
lf you love your wife...
...my advice is be nice to her.
Bring in the wood
before she asks you for it.
lf she is cold,
then Put a shawl around her shoulders.
And bring her a flower
every time you come back from the field.
.You won't Put the Pea back in my ear?
.Oh, no.
That'd be against the HiPPocratic Oath.
Subtitles by SOFTlTLER
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org