Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Was he worried?
- Nope.
He says, whatever's going on with you,
he's sure you're going to work it out.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
(PEN TAPPING NERVOUSLY)
Boy, time flies.
How was your 72-hour meditation?
Pretty enlightening.
Yeah, I'm proud to say
I'm completely rehabilitated.
Very interesting resume, Charlie.
Is there a private school
you haven't been kicked out of?
- Why? You checking up on me?
- Don't flatter yourself.
Sorry.
Principals have access
to academic records.
As you know, I'm the principal,
and as principal I will do my best
to help you graduate with
what you will need to survive in the world.
But I'm not always the principal.
Sometimes I'm other things.
Really? Like what?
Like Susan's father.
Oh.
Don't worry, Charlie,
I'm not gonna call you into my office
and have one of those intimidating
father-boyfriend talks.
I'm not that kind of dad.
Well, thank you.
Because if I were one of those dads,
I'd probably say how my job
is a distant second to my daughter,
and so help me God, if you get out of line,
I will take a massive steaming dump
on your life.
(EXHALES)
Good to have you back.
(DOOR OPENING)
- SUSAN: Hey, Murph.
- Hey.
- Hello.
So, how does this work?
Do I just talk, or... Does Murphy listen?
Well, he's bound
by a confidentiality agreement.
But he can leave if you want.
- Yeah, maybe just for this first time.
- All right.
Sorry, Murph.
Yeah, yeah, I heard you.
It's not like
I'm your fucking business partner.
So, what did my dad want?
He just wanted to welcome me back.
He didn't say anything about me
hanging out with you?
Not really.
Maybe the way to do this
is to ask a question.
What question?
Charlie, I don't know.
You're the professional.
All right. Well, I guess the obvious one is
how do you feel about your dad?
You mean, besides the fact that this
stupid job turned him into an alcoholic?
Okay.
How do you feel about that?
I think it actually bothers him
more than me, to be honest.
But there was the night.
What's "the night"?
The night he found out
my mother was having an affair.
He was plastered, waving this.38 revolver
around, threatening to kill himself.
Wow.
So, your mom left and you stayed, right?
Yeah, pretty much.
Well, he promised to get rid of the gun,
and then he went into treatment
for a while.
And then, for whatever reason,
he decided he was into boats.
You know, it's like someone said,
"Hey, you, you're crazy.
Chill out and get a hobby."
(SIGHS)
- Susan.
- Yes?
I'm still waiting for you to tell me
how you feel about your dad.
Ah.
You're tough.
I guess what I'm trying to say is it just...
It kind of sucks having one parent ditch
and then the other one lose their mind.
I mean, how can I possibly hope
to turn out even remotely functional?
Yeah.
Well, I kind of do feel better.
I'm glad.
Well, thanks for listening, Charlie Bartlett.
(CHUCKLES) No problem, Susan Gardner.
(SIGHS)
Susan?
(MUSIC PLA YING ON BOOM BOX)
Hey.
Listen up.
All right, due to the booming economy
of our fine school,
Dr. Charlie Bartlett here invites you all
to a private party at the Drive-In Club,
which will be the most raging party
in the history of Western Summit.
MURPHY: Charlie! Charlie! Charlie!
ALL: Charlie! Charlie!
(ALL CHEERING)
(SINGING) Head filled up with fear
It's obvious you love the skin you wear
I need to lie down
Need some air
Messing and mussing your tie-dyed hair
You're making a big mistake, mister
Dustin Lauderbach wants a minute
with you, dude.
Come on, is this really necessary?
I was hoping to get a chance to enjoy this.
No, man, he's captain of the football team.
All right.
Who's gonna fix that, that voodoo?
All right, first of all, I'm sick of football.
I mean, zero desire to do this in college.
What do you want to do?
Try not to laugh,
but I was thinking of
going to Paris to study painting.
That's cool.
Have you mentioned this to your dad?
No way. Quitting football isn't gonna
go over very well,
let alone hitting him up two seconds later
for money to spend a year in France.
Well, what about your mom?
She only hears half the stuff I say.
What is that? There's a word for it.
Menopause.
So, what should I do?
Well, I think one of our duties as teenagers
is to occasionally piss off our parents.
- So, go for it, okay?
- Yeah.
Thanks.
I think Dustin Lauderbach may be a...
I think you're just jealous 'cause
you don't have any artistic ambitions.
Fuck you, dude. In fifth grade,
I played Linus in
You're A Good Man, Charlie Brown.
And I was good.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Wow, I didn't know that.
If I'm jealous, if,
it's because only guys
like Dustin Lauderbach
can get girls like Whitney Drummond.
You wanna hook up
with Whitney Drummond?
No. I want to do it right.
That's the kind of girl
you go dinner and a movie with.
I don't know,
you'd have to clean up quite a bit.
(SCOFFS)
Not in this life.
So, why did you stop
doing the school play?
I kept getting my ass kicked
by people like me.
Murph, we really have to have
conversations like this more often.
Oh, bite me.
Here you are. You're coming with me.
I am, am I? Where are we going?
Well, Dr. Bartlett, I think it's high time
you stepped into my office.
Wow. Beats the hell out of my office.
(SIGHS)
So, what now?
Now I'm going to ask you
a series of questions,
and if you answer honestly,
you shall be rewarded.
All right.
All right. Question number one.
And this one is a little selfish on my part.
- Okay.
Is your interest in me
any way related to the fact
that my dad is the principal?
What? Why would it be?
Because I know you get a kick out of
doing things that might get you in trouble.
Well, I'm not gonna deny that, but no.
I pretty much liked you
from the first moment that I saw you.
And I had no idea who your father was.
Was that my reward?
Mmm-hmm.
I think I'm ready
for the next question then.
What's the deal with your father?
Does that really have to be
the next question?
Yes. The harder the question,
the greater the reward.
He's in prison.
My mom went into
a pretty bad depression
when he got arrested.
So, when he was out on bail,
he took me out for ice cream
and he told me I had to take care of her.
So, I promised him I would.
And I've been taking care of her ever since.
So, who takes care of you?
Susan?
I've never done this before.
I know that, Charlie Bartlett.
... I can enjoy this girl-like boy
(SINGING) I'll paint the room white
Just give me something to destroy
You got your green light
For us, it's time
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(COUGHS)
That's really bad for you, you know?
- Hey. What are you doing?
- I'll be right back.
Oh, my God! Charlie, get in here!
Ladies and gentlemen,
how are you all doing tonight?
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
My name is Charlie Bartlett
and I am no longer a virgin!
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
Thank you!
For crying out loud.
(SIGHS)
KIP: I can't think of any reason
to stay on this planet.
No one at school even knows my name.
The idea of even making contact
with another human being
is like trying to defy gravity.
There's just no point in being alive.
Charlie, listen to
what Mr. Gardner has to say.
Kip Crombwell overdosed
on a handful of sedatives last night.
Is he okay?
He's okay, yeah.
He's gonna be fine. He's home.
And you might want to thank him later
for not telling his parents
where he got the drugs.
If anyone could prove it was you,
this would be a different story.
Charlie, how could you do
something like this?
What happens now?
You tell me.
If you can explain what you're doing,
or better yet, why you're doing it,
that would be a good start.
Look, I'm helping these kids, okay?
Nobody else is listening to them.
I encourage you to listen all you like,
but let's face it,
- you're not a professional.
- No.
And these medications
have a legitimate use.
They've helped a lot of people.
It's a generational thing.
You know, teenagers always find a way
to abuse something.
And why not, right?
Being zonked out of your mind
is a lot more fun
than dealing with your problems.
Excuse me for asking,
but are you speaking from experience or...
You know,
that's not an appropriate question.
- That's okay.
- Okay.
Yeah, I sought treatment for some issues.
You're not doing that anymore?
Got to the point where I felt
I was ready to stop, so I did.
- How's that going for you?
- Some days are better than others.
Do you want to talk about it sometime?
No, I would not
like to talk about it sometime.
Charlie, come on.
What are you doing this for?
I don't know.
I guess...
I'm really happy here.
For the first time, everybody likes me.
There are more important things.
Look, I know. Everybody keeps
saying that, but the thing is, is I'm 17,
and popularity is pretty damn
important to me.
Charlie, there are more important things.
Like what?
Like what you do with that popularity.
Look, I've been around a while,
you know, long enough to say this.
What you do in this life matters.
(DRAGNET THEME PLA YING ON TV)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hey, Kip.
Hey, Charlie.
How are you feeling?
Fine, I guess.
They had to pump my stomach.
(GROANS IN SYMPATHY)
- How was that?
- Pretty disgusting.
But now I get to just
play video games all day, so...
Cool.
So, are you still,
like, a suicidal maniac or...
Well, it's not like all my problems
just went away.
Yeah, I guess that makes sense.
Look, Charlie, it's cool
that you came by and everything,
but there's really nothing that you can say
that's going to make me
feel any better, so...
Nothing? Why not?
No one knows I exist.
The last time a girl spoke to me
was in the third grade.
I have no friends and I'm an idiot.
You at least have friends.
How would you possibly know
what it's like?
- I just think you're missing the big picture.
- What big picture?
- The universe.
- What about the universe?
(CHUCKLES)
Well, the universe is a pretty big place.
Yeah. It's infinite, theoretically.
Right. Which means there's probably
life on other planets.
Not life like we think, but, yeah,
probably at least single-cell organisms.
Well, see, that's my whole point.
I mean, you could've been born
a single-cell organism
on the planet Zortex.
In fact, given the odds,
it's probably more likely.
But you weren't.
You were born a human being.
And not just any human being
in the history of human beings,
but a human being
that gets to be alive today,
that gets to listen to all kinds of music,
that gets to eat food from every culture,
that gets to download porn
off the internet.
So, really, you have everything to live for.
You feel better?
Not really.
Well, at least I tried.
- Hey, do you want to play some Killzone?
- Yeah.
(CHUCKLING SMUGLY)
Dude!
- So, you're not selling drugs anymore?
- No, no. I'm searching for new enterprises.
- Like what?
- I don't know. You got any ideas?
You're talking to someone
who can never get anything done.
I've been trying to write a play, but,
you know, no one wants to read any of it.
Well, is it any good?
I don't know.
You can read it if you want to.
Sure.
Nope.
Sorry, guys, there's just no way.
- You didn't even read it.
- I read enough to know that it's a bad idea.
Why?
By virtue of the fact that it's inappropriate.
I'm not jazzed about
taking the heat for you two
having those kids doing
whatever they're doing in there.
But it's true. It has truth.
It's about us and the way we see things.
Mr. Crombwell's right.
We want to see something like this here.
Look, it may not be perfect,
but Charlie's gonna help me with it.
Great. That really puts my mind at ease.
Look, I'm really trying
to do the right thing, okay?
I thought that's what
you wanted me to do.
Yeah, I do,
but does it have to be this play?
If it helps your decision,
I'd be considerably less likely
to end my life if you said yes.
You've got to get it through Drama Club.
- Thank you, Mr. Gardner.
- Yeah.
You won't be disappointed.
Don't make me regret this.
So, what do we do now?
Well, don't worry about the Drama Club.
I'll work it out.
I kind of just don't know
what to say, Charlie.
No worries.
Don't fucking argue with me.
Listen, I just wanna remind you
how much this is worth!
- I know.
- Let me keep the Xanax.
- No. No Xanax. Everything.
- Charlie...
You're a dick.
No! No! No!
- Murph, give it to me.
- No! No! No, Charlie! No! No!
Excuse me, everyone.
May I have your attention?
I have an announcement to make.
Due to complications
with the insurance companies,
I will no longer be providing medication.
(STUDENTS GROANING)
I'm sure this will mean that a lot of you
are done speaking to me and that's fine.
However, for those of you
that are still interested,
I will be holding sessions in my office
free of charge.
Thank you.
I'm one of those people
not speaking to you.
Well, let's get started, shall we?
- Hey, Charlie.
- Hey, Whitney. What's going on?
I don't know.
Well, I think you have
something to tell me,
but you're worried what I might think.
I guess.
I really think that
there's something wrong with me.
Why is that?
Well, I've been crying a lot.
Like, at cheer.
I've slept with almost every guy
on the football team.
All of them?
Well, maybe not all.
But all the backfield, anyway.
Well, do you like any of these guys?
Not really.
I mean, I know they don't want to be
my boyfriend or anything lame like that.
But they try to sleep with me,
and I don't want to say no to them.
Well, look, I don't know, maybe you should
take it slower, you know?
Enjoy yourself.
I mean, there are plenty of guys
at this school
that would do anything to take you
to dinner and a movie.
Give me a break. Like who?
(DOORBELL RINGS)
- Hey, Whitney.
- Hi, Murphy.
Wow, you actually brought flowers.
They're pretty lame, huh?
- I've never been on a real date before.
- That's okay, Murphy.
I've never been on a real date
before either.
- By the way, I like your shirt.
- Oh, thanks.
Okay. Thanks, Charlie.
- Hey.
- Hey, Henry. How's it going, man?
The board completely ignored the petition
to get the cameras out of the lounge,
so they've basically blown us off.
Next thing you know,
they'll put in metal detectors
and start doing random locker searches.
We have to do something.
We need you, man.
I don't know, Henry.
I am already on thin ice with Gardner.
If I lead a protest,
I think he'll have me assassinated.
We need to do something.
All right, look,
if you want to lead a protest,
it's not like I'm gonna stop you, but...
Thanks, Charlie.
(TAPPING)
This is a school, not a prison.
Thanks, because I couldn't read the sign.
This is a school, it's not a prison.
This is a school, not a prison.
(TEACHER CHATTERING)
SEDGWICK: Cameras, protests,
insubordinate kids.
Would any of this have happened
without Charlie Bartlett?
He's all I hear about these days.
"Charlie Bartlett told my son this.
"Charlie Bartlett told my daughter
to do that."
Our lives would be a whole lot easier
if we just expelled him.
You really think that's what he deserves?
Do yourself a favor.
Don't get fired over this kid.
Look at this.
Look, I don't think there should
be cameras in the lounge, but...
(STUDENTS CLAMORING)
I don't even know what to say.
I kind of see where
your dad's coming from, too.
Since when do you care what he thinks?
I don't know.
He's given me a break a couple of times.
Yeah.
(FEEDBACKSCREECHING)
Attention, all dissenting students
of Western Summit High School.
You have two minutes to disperse.
If you have not at that time,
you will be suspended.
No! See, we have a right to be here.
They can't kick us all out.
There has to be a better way
to handle this.
- Okay. Can you help me out?
- What are you gonna do?
Could you go over there and tell them
to break it up and come back tonight?
Okay.
STUDENTS: This is a school, not a prison!
This is a school, not a prison!
Hey, guys, Charlie wanted me to ask...
Charlie wants us to go home
and come back tonight, all right?
Susan!
- What did he just give you?
- What?
- That's just...
- Shut it! I'm talking to my daughter.
- What is in that pharmacy bag?
- None of your business.
- Susan...
- I don't need any assistance from you
handling my daughter.
Do you understand?
Try saying one more word
and see what happens.
Come on, you really think
I don't know what's in the bag?
Yeah. I really don't think
you know what's in the bag.
Where are you going?
You're not going anywhere.
Whatever.
Susan Gardner, get your ass
back in the house on the count of three,
or you're grounded.
What makes you think
you're still in control of what I do?
I don't think. I know. It's a fact.
What are you looking at? One!
I would not make me choose
between you and Charlie if I were you.
You don't have to choose.
Drug dealer! Dad!
I'm your father.
This is a boy who goes to my school. Two!
Charlie Bartlett has done more
for your school than you ever will.
Three!
Hey! Don't touch her!
Oh, shit. I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
Well, you did it. It's done.
Whatever. Let's go. Come on.
I'm really sorry I did that.
It's not your fault.
So, Charlie Bartlett assaulted you.
Well, now it's up to you.
Do you want to press charges or not?
HENRY ON MEGAPHONE: Now, we're
gonna get these cameras out of the lounge.
We're gonna figure it out tonight.
Hey, look who it is, everybody.
- CROWD: Charlie! Charlie! Charlie! Charlie!
- Charlie! Charlie! Charlie! Charlie!
(ALL CHEERING)
How you all doing tonight?
(CHEERING)
My name is Charlie Bartlett.
If there's one thing I want you guys
to walk away with tonight,
it's that you guys don't need me.
I really mean it.
You think I'm any less screwed up
than you are?
I get up every morning
and I look in the mirror
and I try and figure out
just where I fit in.
And I draw a complete blank.
And you guys are looking to me
to tell you what to do?
You need to stop listening to me.
(SIRENS WAILING)
And stop listening to people telling you
who you should be.
And stop listening to the people
that are telling you
you're not good enough
to do the things that you want to do!
(STUDENTS CHEERING)
You guys have all the answers.
You're under arrest for assault.
(STUDENTS BOOING)
Charlie!
STUDENTS CHANTING:
Charlie! Charlie! Charlie!
- Charlie! Charlie! Charlie!
Okay, party's over.
I want you all out of here now!
Have I made myself abundantly clear?
We want to know
what the hell's gonna happen to Charlie.
- Yeah!
- ALL: Yeah!
I'd be more worried about yourselves.
Thanks to him,
the Class of '83 Student Lounge
is now The Charlie Bartlett
Detention Center.
Bullshit! Come on!
Get the cameras!
Well, every time I feel you're
coming round, you're going down
You hit the ground with every force
It makes no sense or sound
Emergency, Western Summit High School.
(STUDENTS WHOOPING)
God bless your soul, girl
Now you got the whole world
It's your eyes that make me smile
Oh, yeah
Well, I guess now is as good a time
as any to tell you.
You're fired.
(SIREN WAILING)
It's your eyes that make me smile
Come on.
Wasting time hanging out
Oh, yeah
Come on, Charlie.
Your mom's here to bail you out.
What's gonna happen to the other kids?
Well, there's gonna be an investigation.
But since all the cameras were destroyed,
they're gonna have a hard time
figuring out who did what.
Well, I'm prepared
to take full responsibility.
Charlie, go home.
- Are you mad?
- I don't know how to feel, Charlie.
Well, Mom, I think you should be mad
because I just got arrested
and a bunch of my friends
just trashed a building.
I am aware of that.
And I'm having a hard time being mad
at you when it just might be my fault.
No, Mom, it's not your fault.
Don't say that.
No, some of it is.
I treated you like an adult for so long,
you missed out on being a little boy.
And now we're paying for it.
With a vengeance, I'd say.
But you are just a kid, Charlie.
You understand that, right?
And that doesn't change just
because I don't know what to do with you.
Mom.
I wouldn't know
what to do with me, either.
Well, I think it's safe to say
that you're grounded.
Really? How long?
That's a good question.
What is the standard?
Usually, like, 24 hours.
Well, seeing as you've acquired
a misdemeanor, we'd better make it 30.
Okay.
- Get in the car.
- Okay.
(SUSAN HUMMING
YANKEE DOODLE DAND Y)
(SIGHS)
- Hi.
- Hey!
How are you feeling?
A little nervous, I guess. But that's normal.
Yeah. How's your dad?
He's holed himself up in his study.
That's usually a bad sign.
You could've asked him to come,
you know.
Really? What am I going to say?
"Hey, Dad, you want to come
sit with a bunch of people
"that are really glad you were fired
and watch me on stage?"
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hello?
Principal Gardner?
Hello? Principal Gardner?
It's me, sir. Charlie Bartlett.
Hello?
(BOTTLE TOOTING)
Oh, this better be good, Charles.
I came to invite you to the play.
Well, thank you for that,
but I am just a little tied up right now.
- What are you doing?
- Venting. Just venting a little bit.
Is that your new word of the day?
Sure as shit is.
(EX CLAIMS)
Word of the day, "venting."
Explanation. That's kind of how I deal
with my little life's frustrations. I vent.
As in "to vent," original derivation
from the Latin exventare.
Jesus!
Everybody needs to vent a little
now and again, don't you figure?
Some of us are privileged enough
to vent to you in the boys' room stall,
and the rest of us just have to settle
for less conventional methods.
Like, I don't know,
a bottle of booze and a handgun.
(GUN FIRES)
I'm sorry. I'm not putting you on edge
with my behavior, am I?
That's all right.
Maybe you could put the gun down.
Park it, Chuck!
In case you're not aware of this,
I'm entirely displeased with you right now.
I was racking my brain to figure out why,
and I think it's because
you've taken everything from me.
Why did you do that?
Do you have anything enlightening
to say to me right now? 'Cause if you do,
I'd appreciate it if you'd spit it out.
I don't know.
Maybe some of
that post-pubescent psychobabble?
Maybe a pearl of wisdom?
I don't know what to say to you.
I mean, I don't know how to help you.
I really want to.
Come on, Doctor!
What have you got for me?
I don't know what you want from me.
I don't need you to say anything to me
and I don't need you to save me!
All right, then, what am I supposed to do
in this situation?
You know, I'm just a kid!
I'm just a stupid kid!
Stop the fucking presses.
Run that by me again. You're a what?
I'm just a kid.
I get it.
It's tough. I was a kid once, too.
Oh, fuck!
(MUTTERING INAUDIBLY)
- No!
- What are you...
(GRUNTS)
(COUGHING)
What the hell did you do that for?
You were going to kill yourself.
I can't kill myself.
I've got too many responsibilities.
You okay?
Yeah.
Never, never attack a drunk guy
with a gun. Do you understand?
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
Come on. Let's get cleaned up.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Hey, Charlie. See if that fits.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
How's your head? You all right?
It's okay.
Well, we should go
'cause we're going to miss the play.
I doubt she's going to be happy to see me.
No, you're her father,
and she loves you very much,
and you're totally missing it.
Fair enough.
- What about you?
- What about me, what?
What about your father?
You know, when I checked up on you,
I was half-hoping to find something
to make me feel justified
in kicking your ass out.
Then I found out about him.
There are worse crimes than tax evasion.
Yeah, but it's not worth
losing your father over.
Okay, so, stay mad at him forever.
How's that working for you?
Some days are better than others.
LANCE: Come on, Monica. Just try it.
It'll give you such a high.
My God, you are, like,
totally peer-pressuring me.
I've never done it before.
Just do it. Trust me.
You know you want to.
I just don't know anymore.
She used to be my little girl.
I mean, what do you think
they're doing behind that door?
There's no way to know that.
And, besides, isn't it more interesting
to just trust them and see what happens?
I just don't understand why it's
so important to you that I do this.
'Cause it's fun and it'll feel good.
Okay, I'll give it a try.
(PLA YS ARPEGGIO ON GUITAR)
(SINGING) If you wanna sing out, sing out
If you wanna be free, be free
There's a million things to be
You know that there are
If you wanna live high, live high
If you wanna live low, live low
There's a million ways to go
You know that there are
You can do what you want
The opportunity's on
And if you find a new way
You can do it today
You can make it all true
And you can make it undo
You see
You only need to know
If you wanna say yes, say yes
If you wanna say no, say no
There's a million ways to go
You know that there are
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
I must say, of all the kids
applying for a summer internship,
you have quite a checkered history.
I understand. And I'm sure
you have a whole stack of people
with perfect backgrounds
and no disciplinary record.
Really, I'd do anything to work here.
Well, let's get on with the interview.
I've got a hell of a day ahead of me.
Would you like to talk about it?
Do you know what it's like
to fall on the floor?
And cry your guts out
till you got no more?
Hey, man
Now you're really living
Have you ever made love
to a beautiful girl?
Made you feel like
it's not such a bad world?
Hey, man
Now you're really living
Now you're really
giving it everything
And you're really
getting all you gave
Now you're really living
what this life is all about
Well, I just saw the sun
rise over the hill
Never used to give me
much of a thrill
But hey, man
Now I'm really living
Do you know what it's like
to care too much
'Bout someone that you're
never gonna get to touch?
Hey, man
Now you're really living
Have you ever sat down
in the fresh-cut grass
And thought about the moment
and when it will pass?
Hey, man
Now you're really living
Now you're really
giving it everything
And you're really
getting all you gave
Now you're really living
what this life is all about
Now, what would you say
if I told you that
Everyone thinks
you're a crazy old cat
Hey, man
Now you're really living
Do you know what it's like
to fall on the floor?
And cry your guts out
till you got no more?
Hey, man
Now you're really living
Have you ever made love
to a beautiful girl?
Made you feel like
it's not such a bad world?
Hey, man
Now you're really living
Do you know what it's like
to fall on the floor?
And cry your guts out
till you got no more?
Hey, man
Now you're really living
Just saw the sun rise over the hill
Never used to give me much of a thrill
But hey, man
Now I'm really living!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org