Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
In the days around the world.
The faith of humanity was taken
in a small box of metal.
In a secret location.
Architects, engineers and scientists
and concluded that there was only
a hope for our future.
Building a city under the ground.
To keep the public
protected.
For future generations.
Custody.
Programala for 200 years.
For the city in 200 years.
Você. will not live long.
We can help.
Growing up with the knowledge
from the outside world.
Future generations
Will not suffer a loss.
For the good of humanity.
The box was entrusted to
first lady.
What would happen to his successor.
How to account for years
happening.
The box went hand in hand.
Without knowing the inside secrets.
Just know you should
be open when the account expires.
But it took another destination.
The chain was broken.
The house was put aside and
forgotten.
And when the city was
start the stopwatch.
The box was opened.
Hey, Dad hear that?
Activity does not seem good.
I hurry.
This is a great day.
I hope we do not have to
use this and not being able to control it.
You have a mission, this is not the point.
What?
6,7,8 ...
Come.
If so, this week.
Producers have only
enough power.
If he goes, let's all.
This is very bad.
This place is in the park.
I will not sit and wait
she collapses.
Fixarei generator, costing
whatever the cost.
Congratulations.
At the time of this opportunity.
His mission.
Wait.
His grandmother is right?
Yes, we're fine.
Okay Mr.
If.
Hi
Hello Mr miles.
Called the book of the city.
You must sign to enter.
You can wait.
We swear:
Eternal loyalty to our city.
Declare gratitude to the buildings
we inhabit.
Flourish like flowers in the river.
As we flew past
generations.
Having a beautiful heart.
In addition to temperament and forever
for the well-being.
Our city to enjoy the
world.
It is true.
Be the first to discover
its future.
Young forward.
Not out loud.
Assistant electricity.
Work on the generator.
Assistant to the lookout.
You need to work with the class.
Constructor.
It's fun.
Assistant store.
Ok.
Potato peeler.
Coming from hand.
Domestic worker.
Vital work.
Choose a young girl.
Working in the pipes.
Scream it so that everyone can hear.
I am a slave of the pipes.
You're very lucky girl
this is an important job.
Servant.
Take one.
Messenger.
Change.
What?
Please, you have to
to do.
Want to work in the pipeline?
I do not want to be assistant electric
and work on the generator
I do not want to be a messenger;
I do not want to lose my time in
throughout the city.
Yes
What?
If.
Thank you.
What was your mission?
I am a messenger.
That's wonderful.
Congratulations.
Grandma, Grandma.
Where is the money?
I am a messenger.
You should not do that.
There can be messengers.
Today was the day of
award. Remember?
Where is Popy?
I was helping out.
Here is the poppy.
Poppy.
Poppy did not know where you were.
Here.
It is for you.
I did.
If I can see.
What is this?
It is for their graduation.
I mean to serve?
Let's find out.
There's more to stay the same
monitoring the bus.
The thing is ...
Pay attention.
Put a lot of attention.
You'll see.
What no one else will notice note.
And no one else will know what we know.
What do you get
All I have.
What do you do, what will be
get.
This is a good starting point.
When I said.
The father is very useful.
I did not want to eat?
I am not hungry.
Sure.
You're weak.
Good night.
I will put the voices for you
sleep ok.
No pressure or not.
Be there before the sun comes out.
Sister shoes are ready.
Hello I'm Ray Clare, the system
sparks fell again.
Brent's me Hearl.
'Take that.
Take care of my children.
In case you change your mind.
Sr.
Where to go?
Lina presenting Mayfleet
for work.
You are a Mayfleet.
In other words, please.
8 hours.
Go all.
It is beautiful.
Take it with pride.
Take care.
Always keep in place a
appropriate
I will.
The session will be on the block.
Stop.
I need to tell you the rules.
1. When a customer ...
Leave a message
doing good.
2. Always read the red letters
so people can sign.
3. Our customers pay 25 cents
for each message no matter how far he is.
And go quickly.
I go fast.
Okay, I'm impressed.
Now go.
That over your clothes you wear.
Here are all the tools
you need.
I think the attraction --
these boots are fine.
Need for traction
this.
And this is their home.
Put your shoes and come.
Very good.
You have a rockcod.
This.
What you have left.
All right, put your name on it.
Why?
In the event that something happens.
Before you dive
to put your name on it
to find out who he was.
Use this.
I think I know who is
wrong with the generator.
Well
Made.
Sister
20 cents please.
Slowly.
Hey.
I am.
Look at you.
I was told.
Why you is my first message.
Wait, I'm ready.
Weapons of SWERA
plant.
If this is a potatoes, then
I am 16 and I'm sexy.
Help!
I have one thing in my hand.
I can see.
It is larger than a house.
Just trying to go along
the river.
Sister
A belt of things up by
feet.
Pc. I do not know what
idea how she was.
Why would someone want arriezgaría
in jail.
Everybody knows that
take much to get out of there.
There is much further to
that the world there.
His father was the only one they arranged
potatoes.
Deeply sorry.
Keep it up.
Help me with this.
We need to make a new plan.
Are you new plan?
We do not make new plans
since the second decade.
Pudes patch well.
Hold.
Review it.
What was it?
Is warming up?
This measure.
Far.
Absent is not good.
What will happen?
The same as usual.
What is this?
The frost.
What about the black box
they can ...
Calm down.
Take that much lower.
What is the name of this tunnel?
The tunnel is 25.
And this is 26.
How do you know?
Come on.
Low.
What do we have?
And this ...
One moment, that's not my
work.
They were eternally.
And not know it.
I was too
busy.
We can go to the generator?
I already have enough for the generator.
This tunnel would be.
What are you doing here?
I work in this part.
I know you, your brother
is in my class.
Thanks for the information.
So why are you here?
No, I'm coaching.
And I'm sorry you lost.
Get out of here.
You okay?
Whats up
Come on.
Please.
Where are you?
You okay?
If.
Something is happening.
What was that sound?
It is the generator.
You can solve the case.
Maybe sooner.
No time.
We must do something.
There was a man this morning
From then returned.
He said he heard something.
Did you ever think you had
an exit?
I have an idea.
Attention to all workers.
I need to get to the bottom.
Stay safe, OK.
Doon.
Wait.
Forget it.
I think I came to this.
Why is that?
I came back from that.
Not so.
Can I keep it?
Mrs. I go home and review
to my friends.
We have to go.
Tell everyone.
We like 7 minutes.
In parts as ever.
Grandmother.
There is something I have to do.
It is very important.
My great-grandfather, told me that ....
Sorry.
No.
Spit it out.
Ruining the furniture grandmother.
She found him.
Is this was what I want?
Are you sure?
These are special?
I do not care.
All right.
Remember.
Grandma I have to go back to work.
Ok.
No more questions.
The generator is broken.
Thank you very much.
I have a message.
For Shna silly.
Oh, I am, what happened?
Maltor send it.
Did he do?
The wanted to tell you that no
can come for lunch today.
He says his house is far
for him and he is very tired.
A message for the mayor.
Its interior is sheep.
Morning messenger.
What brings you here?
I have a message for the mayor.
Very good.
This way please.
These paintings are all
Mayors in the empire.
Seventh is the mayor of hot.
I am a relative of him.
He is my Biza Biza ... I do not know
It was in that range.
It is the 7th mayor.
Continues to live in
same place as he did.
Passage.
I remember the days of release.
She is a descendant of our
The 7th mayor.
Really?
Lina Mayflead.
This is a name for a messenger.
Can you see your feet?
I see you got the job.
What is the message?
It was Mr. Loop.
His sheep is complete.
Thank you.
What are these boxes on
Mr portraits.
It is part of the message?
No.
I was just curious.
Thank you.
That's right.
Keep it up.
And will continue for the blind.
What is this?
Cover small ears
I said back.
And for good returns.
Delivered the message.
We were here for a long time.
I can see that.
The generator had not failed
this year.
The latter is a separate generator.
And nobody knows that back.
What can you do?
What can you do
about it?
How can you explain this?
Will you give me a headache.
Brasa.
time ...
Support of life ...
1. It should ...
2. Unlocking ...
It is very beautiful.
Give me 20 packages.
Or you can give me 15.
You can not have just 15
3.
Do not tell me that.
Yesterday I had several on the market.
But not today.
I do not understand the funny.
Do this and ask who has
Next.
I have to find.
You need to stay in bed.
I found grandmother.
Thank you.
What is this?
I told her what?
For now we talk enough.
Você. should be asleep.
There is no medicine that can give you?
There is no cure, sorry.
And I gave everything I could.
Can you help me with that.
Let's see.
Stay tuned.
Do not bite.
What did he do it indoors?
Poppy endpoint.
It is only the light, do not worry.
Ok.
Grandma, here we go.
Grandmother.
You have to share this with Poppy, but
I think it's big enough.
¿Poppy is what makes it work
The system generator?
You know your side.
I think dealing with it
last year.
Oh, well, singing is very important.
We are happy heart.
We are fortunate.
I do not feel very lucky
lately.
There is nothing to worry about
that's why.
Blackouts concern us
for all.
The aid will arrive.
Help?
Who build the city
dear.
Manufacturers.
That's right.
The manufacturer will come again
and fix it.
Whatever it is a grandmother.
Let's find out.
I promise.
These are roles.
That's why you the fact.
This is ...
Nobody remembers him.
Come on, I do.
What are we doing here?
The builders something left.
Maybe what we find.
Come on, open it.
It is not supposed to be.
Elder wrote these instructions.
They sound like them.
Come on.
We must show
What do you think?
I think they are instructions.
If.
Whatever it is, why he had
in a circle?
I mean, I know ...
That's it.
IT.
What?
IT ... exit.
Looks run it.
I do not think it was supposed to have
to leave here.
These tunnels do not appear on the map.
They are like roads to nowhere.
That may be.
What was that?
I do not know.
Run.
Wait, here.
Come on.
Run, run.
It is the only chance.
Thanks for another great idea.
You never her alive.
Hunger is just der suddenly
like us.
After these tunnels.
Completely lacking complete.
No problem, the generator
will not work.
Very soon will be black
for the better.
This is my name.
He was the man I was before
who drowned.
Ahorgar.
Strange.
There is no water for irrigation.
How could ahorgar?
Why?
we must find out
this is the only thing left us.
This is what scares me most.
Do not count anything.
It's like not understand.
Please, dear.
Do not do anything stupid.
Something like this is bad.
How did she die?
Do we really drowned?
His father thought I
could.
He believed that there was a way out.
I could not dissuade him.
I said I was better than us
stay and fix our problems.
But it is illegal to enter the unknown.
Why is it illegal?
His father said: The river flows in one direction.
So he has to come from somewhere.
But you have to hit early
something.
I do not know.
The tunnel buoy.
End.
Yes, my father died.
He was alone.
All others came before
that clutter.
We have to consider bringing
cash to the mayor.
Yes
What now, please.
Who knows the situation.
It is a time of trouble.
Our problems are brave.
We need answers.
But beyond the answers.
More important than the answers.
We need solutions.
And to find such solutions.
I think there should be a
investigation.
I am here to testify.
The creation of the force
work.
To do research
the black box.
There are some volunteers?
Today we, the people.
We are united against them.
Give me that.
Sr.
Let him.
Pineapple.
Pineapple, not since my
Grandma was a girl.
Where did you get that?
Where did you get this food?
I gave a lover.
You do not have a lover.
It is not official.
But this guy really liked him.
Explore a lot.
Especially by alla.
Are empty, but you want to
are not empty.
And give me something from time to time.
You are wrong.
All this will get worse,
Why not enjoy it now?
There it is.
I need to tell you something.
I was looking for 351
to the north.
Before he had a message.
All you have to do
the door is open.
There's a lot of food.
I thought I was lying to find
a solution.
He should lie.
Found the solution.
Sit well.
Go to sleep.
Stay there.
What is this?
It is an answering machine is left
my parents.
Before that happened.
Anybody home?
Do not let my dear.
This is the voice of my father.
Bren's me.
Take care of my son.
I am inside.
What happens?
I lied.
Where are you going?
See you in the green house ok.
Good night young people.
What progress?
For the song.
Oh, good.
It is very good.
Well
Good night.
Dad, did you hear.
I heard that the response
this is so.
Apparently, it is an answering machine.
I hear you, you said you were made
to enter.
You do not think the city?
Why is that?
For me.
Dad.
Please.
I was wrong.
No, you were right.
There is an exit.
If, of course not.
I have someone who murirera.
Dad is a departure in
roles.
And you have to tell me, what you know.
I do not know anything.
Nothing for you.
The manufacturer has left instructions.
The manufacturer has nothing to do with
this.
Yes, I did.
They did, I do not have evidence.
Shows them to me.
The great days of singing
Hold on.
Happy days of singing young lady.
I need to talk in private.
Very good.
What do I need to tell you is
secret and very important.
What is this?
The mayor has a box in the depths
full of food.
I am sure that they are willing to
the worst.
Does the mayor steals?
You are going to the shops and so on.
That is shocking.
Shocking.
I am in Chock.
We have to bring it.
Come with me.
When we arrested
to go and where is the room.
You expect to where we going?
Take your part Honor.
Lina Mayfleet Do you remember?
She is accusing.
From what?
Stealing food for the people of fire.
I bought a whole and within each house.
I do not know why you think such a thing.
We saw his room, we saw
inside.
Nós.
She and her friend Doon Harrow.
What the box?
It's mine.
It is a bit unusual.
Where did you get it?
You are a descendant of one of the mayors.
Yes, sir.
She is the 7th Mayor's family.
Things sometimes get lost.
Can I look at this box?
Why?
What is inside the box?
I think it's a matter of the mayor.
The house, give me.
It is not theirs.
Give me the box!
No.
Remove it.
Now.
Move it.
Him.
Be quiet.
You want to be here?
I can not hear, I have a bad ear.
You can talk ...
Harrow destination.
We are looking for Destiny Harrow.
It's bad.
And that is not cursed my son.
The prison is the worst place
where you can go.
The builders were wise
when they said
We need to keep dry liquids
joins in for the blessing.
Him.
Sure there.
Hey treacherous.
You start.
Is the child.
Just a minute.
What do you do?
They come to me.
Who?
The guards.
Why?
I do not know.
What is this?
We later for the great
day of singing.
Excuse me Mrs.
Lina trying Mayfleet.
She is not likely here
continue in his job.
Ok.
If you do not care.
Excuse me, but rude.
He knows that, the mayor is giving
a reward.
At home.
She will find in the house
green with a friend.
Does that help?
REQUESTED
Rewarding
Come on.
Why are destroying everything?
Silly.
A warning.
If you think that is helping
for them.
Why is that?
I have information that I received this
tomorrow.
Who gave that information?
It is confidential.
What I need is to understand that.
If you're in return.
The lock.
They can hear it, they can see.
Você. tell me.
Otherwise, there will be consequences.
If you're worried that you'll see your hero
I hope he will give me information.
For the night with the mayor.
We will find.
Come on.
What is this?
My dad did this.
He does not seem to be very safe.
That will see.
Have you ever done something?
What do you mean with your father?
Harrow voice on the machine
answering machine.
I found the name of his father was
Laurence.
Parrol Harrow.
On his behalf.
It is for sure.
You are a child.
This means that our fathers
tried to run together.
Try.
But we do not have time to be coming back
for us.
Hold on.
Now you stay here.
And quietita.
Hi
She is here somewhere.
Do you see anything?
No.
Here is your day.
From time to celebrate the year
for our city.
The voice of life.
In the world of darkness.
This is covering.
This plan miraculous.
This dazzling ingenuity.
It is our city of coal.
They began to sing.
I have something to show you.
What was the mayor.
Will you give?
Not exactly.
The generator.
Okay, I have to get there.
I must follow.
Wait.
Poppy.
Come here.
That's it.
Poppy.
Maybe you know.
We need help.
We have to bear.
Wake up.
We need the door to the generator.
Obviously, there is a wrench.
Well, where is he?
I do not know, it's not my job.
Wait.
Something is not right.
He is very smart, you would not
so simple.
What is the easy part?
Walking toward the back.
It will be everything.
Doon.
There is something behind these
lockers.
Come on, walk.
There must be a way to go.
That's good.
Jackpot.
Given intelligence.
What is this?
Style is another.
Still, it is very low.
What will strike.
You must take off the road.
It is not supposed to hide
the head.
We have to follow instructions
exactly.
What has to say.
Access ... something ... something ... room.
Come on Poppy.
It should be an area that
seek.
Now.
He has control.
Door.
Come on, come on.
Well done.
You okay?
Set ... complete confidence.
Ok.
What follows,
Set ... 2 to completely stopped.
Completely stopped
Displayed.
Stay here.
What are you doing here?
This thing is stuck.
I am libero.
And what are you doing this?
It is my job.
Try this.
Yeah.
Is working.
It is the exit.
It is the way to do it.
What kid?
Come on.
You okay?
Yes
We gotta go now.
But I have to keep this
sustained.
No, come with me.
You will.
Go away.
It's all mine.
You okay?
We have to go.
'We're not seeing that happen.
There is no option to go.
Hold on.
Work.
Mirko.
Free.
You told me that I stay.
Wait.
We were me and you.
Teneíamos a deal.
Open the door.
He said.
We're going to the right.
The right.
Ok.
Drop.
You're there!
This is something we never heard.
One step at the time!
Do not charge!
Discharge care with the baby
It was raining.
There is nothing better than this.
It is blue.
You can see it.
Hello!
Do not listen to you.
Are very far.
But we have to decircelos
in some way.
We have to tell you what
There are up here.
Lina and placed their Destination
Hopefully in a rock.
And fell.
The rock, could have been arrested
somewhere roof.
But, he continued.
And their luck took another
course.
And the message passed on the way.
Now things were clear
for all.
From all this.
Wine of the flame burning.
Throughout the darkness.
So we could live again
on earth.
On air and light.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org