Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Come on!
Don't worry, my little friend.
Thallo will take you.
Someone coming.
Sounds like a man. A young man.
-Who has the eye?
-l do!
-Then give it to me.
-No! l want to be the first to see him.
What do you see, sister?
What do you see?
Yes! A young man, not plump
but well-made.
Have no fear. l come in peace.
Come a little closer so that we
can get a better look at you.
-We are honored by your visit.
-What can we do to help you?
-l need your advice.
-Then you must come a little closer.
You see, my two sisters here
are somewhat deaf.
-l still can't hear him.
-Suppose we were to move...
...a little closer to him.
Now!
-Noise, what's that noise?
-What, what? Where is it?
Bubo! The eye! Go for the eye!
-Where is it?
-What is it?
-What's wrong?
-lt's gone! lt's got the eye! The eye!
-Don't drop the eye!
-Oh, no! Where's the eye?
-You have it!
-Never fear. lt is safe.
Give it to us. Give it back.
-On one condition.
-Anything!
-We must have it now!
-You will have it.
-After you answer my question.
-Ask, then.
How may a mortal man
face and defeat the lKraken?
The lKraken is invulnerable.
100 men could not fight him.
An army could not kill him.
Nothing is invulnerable.
There must be a way.
Perhaps, one way.
But a way even more dangerous
than the lKraken itself.
-Tell me.
-Give me the eye and l'll tell you.
First, tell me.
The head of Medusa. The Gorgon!
One look from the head of Medusa
can turn all creatures into stone.
-No matter how huge and powerful.
-And her blood is a deadly venom.
A Titan against a Titan!
-You must win Medusa's head.
-She's not going to give it to you.
-As a present.
-As difficult and dangerous...
-...as to vanquish 1000 lKrakens.
-Your only chance against the lKraken.
Give us the eye.
We have answered your question.
One more question.
lf the eyes of Medusa...
...even after her death can turn
all living creatures into stone...
-...what about the blood?
-Deadly and poisonous.
But you have touched the eye.
As it has the power to give sight...
...so it can make your red cloak
proof against the blood.
The eye is all powerful. We can
tell you no more. Give us the eye.
-You have told me the truth?
-We swear it.
-The rest is for you. Seek Medusa.
-On the lsle of the Dead.
-At the very edge of the underworld.
-Give us back the eye!
-Give us the eye! We must have it!
-Here, catch.
-Where is it? l want it!
-lt's my turn!
Where'd it go?
Give it to me!
One of you has it!
The sands of time
run like quicksilver.
We'll be across these mountains
tomorrow, near the lsle of the Dead.
And then, Medusa.
l wrote a play about her long ago.
l was partial to tragedy in my youth.
Before experience taught me
that life is quite tragic enough...
-...without my writing about it.
-Medusa.
-She was priestess to Aphrodite.
-Yes, and a most beautiful woman...
...by all accounts.
She was seduced by Poseidon. They made
love in the temple of Aphrodite.
And that goddess was so jealous
that she punished Medusa.
She transformed her into
an apparition so horrible...
...that one look from her
will turn any living creature...
...into stone.
l'm so afraid for you.
lt must be done.
We've no other choice.
-Tomorrow you return to the city.
-No, l'm coming with you.
Then sleep now. We ride at dawn.
So little time together.
So little time.
Sleep now. Sleep.
The river Styx.
The River of Death...
...has strange powers.
So l've heard.
Time to see if the legend is true.
Here. You'll need this.
For Charon. The ferryman.
Remember, one look from her
is enough.
lf you must see her, use the inside
of your shield as a mirror.
Her reflection cannot harm you.
Never look her in the face.
Remember, now it's three against one.
Guard well the shield.
For one day, it will guard your life.
Find and fulfill your destiny.
Thallo!
Hello, my wet friend.
No.
No, our task is not complete.
lf you can fly....
Good.
And if he's still alive...
...you must try to find Pegasus.
Great Zeus, below on Earth
it is now the eve...
...of the longest day.
Very well.
Release the lKraken.
Perseus has won.
My son...
...has triumphed.
-A fortunate young man.
-Fortune is ally to the brave.
What a dangerous precedent.
What if there are more
heroes like him?
What if courage and imagination
became everyday mortal qualities?
We would no longer be needed.
But for now, there is sufficient
cowardice, sloth...
...and mendacity down there on Earth
to last forever.
l forbid any revenge
against Perseus.
He has done well.
He will be rewarded.
This will make a fine heroic poem,
you know.
Or perhaps a play.
Oh, don't worry.
l won't leave you out.
Perseus and Andromeda
will be happy together.
Have fine sons...
...rule wisely...
...and to perpetuate his legend...
...I command that from henceforth...
...he will be set among the stars
and constellations.
He, Perseus, the lovely Andromeda...
...the noble Pegasus
and even the vain Cassiopeia.
Let the stars be named
after them forever.
As long as man shall walk the Earth
and search the night sky in wonder...
...they will remember the courage
of Perseus...
...forever.
Even if we, the gods,
are abandoned or forgotten...
...the stars will never fade.
Never.
They will burn till the end of time.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org