Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Hi, Jack.
You keep smiling.
You hear me?
Whatever you do,
you keep smiling.
Yeah, I'm gonna do that, Jack.
Yeah, so what happened to you,
buddy?
Oh Christ... Oh Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ.
Chuck, I wanted to talk to him!
He'll be here in a few days.
Weather is clearing.
He's grabbing a flight
with some transport boys.
What is it?
I would give anything not to
have to tell you, Ethel Ann.
What?
Tell me what?
Tell me what?!
Hello?
Could I speak to Ethel, please?
Yes, this is Ethel.
This is Jimmy Reilly.
I found this ring
on Black Mountain
Where the plane crashed.
And I thought it might belong to
one of the airmen who got killed.
For Christ's sake!
Sorry.
Are you there?
Yes.
The ring says 'Ethel and Teddy'.
Ann.
Ethel Ann.
That's my name.
Oh, right.
Only, on the list of
dead guys there was
Sorry.
On the list of... deceased
there was Teddy Gordon
So I called the veterans people.
Only they said he wasn't married,
but he left everything in his Will
to Ethel Roberts.
And they had an address
They said you'd probably moved.
But you haven't.
The ring
Would you like me
to send it to you?
No.
No, no, no.
But it's yours.
No, it's his.
But he's... I mean, he's not here.
Then you keep it.
All right.
And we were married.
Well, they said you weren't.
Hello?
Maybe she was cut off
Shall I call her back?
No, leave her alone.
You go home.
Can I leave it here?
What?
The ring.
It won't be safe
with granny around.
Mr Quinlan.
Thanks.
I'll let myself out then.
Come on, Jack.
Teddy, this is crazy.
I can't do this.
Well, you got him then.
We got a bit of a problem too.
We don't have time for a problem.
I'm not allowed to do this.
I haven't taken Final Orders.
The Lord works in mysterious ways.
She's gonna be here any second.
She's here now.
I think it was my mother's.
Ethel Ann?
He's marrying you?
Your folks
will never agree to this.
That's why they're not here.
Jack will you give me away?
Please.
Sure.
Wilbur,
are you going to marry us?
I can't.
You don't have a licence
Is this a church?
Yes.
And is God here?
What do you mean?
This man is going to war.
I love him.
I want God to protect him.
So I'm asking you
is He here right now?
Yes.
Then marry us... In His sight.
You got rings?
Just the one.
One ring?
Well, it's the ring you gave me,
Teddy.
I had our names put inside it.
I'm gonna marry you with it and
then I want you to take it with you.
I got it for you, Ethel Ann.
This way you can remember me
wherever you go.
Okay. Okay.
Say the words, Wilbur.
Matrimony is a holy state not to
be entered into lightly.
Because in the eyes of God
this is forever
And I mean forever.
Forever.
Teddy... do you take this woman,
Ethel Ann,
to be your lawful wedded wife
all the days that you shall live?
I do.
Ethel Ann do you
take this man, Teddy,
to be your lawful wedded husband?
I do.
I'll be yours till the day I die.
You better do whatever
you're gonna do with that ring.
Jack, will you?
By the power vested in me
by the state of...
No... can't say that.
Just say what you can say.
By the power vested in me,
by the God of Love...
who sees all things,
and hears all promises...
I now pronounce you man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Bloody great!
Do you know who we are?
No.
We know who you are.
You're a lucky lad, Jimmy.
Those Republican bastards
could have found you
if we hadn't been watching you.
Why were you watching me?
Do you know him?
No.
Yes, you do.
I don't.
He's lying to us.
Can you tell me who this is?
Me.
That's me.
Thank you.
And this man?
That's Mr Quinlan anything.
He's not done anything.
Where did you get those?
What about this one?
Have you seen him?
Take your time.
You've already told us a lot.
Hasn't he?
I haven't told you anything.
Yes, he has.
You've identified
two photographs.
That's very helpful.
His name is Cathal Thomas
By the way...
didn't you say
that you had seen him?
Or did you deny
not having seen him?
Yes.
No.
I didn't say anything.
But you just did.
He said yes.
I don't wanna help you.
But Mr Thomas will think that
you have been helping us.
That's what he thought
about this gentleman.
And, yes, you do know him.
That was his body
you found this morning.
But I thought that was
from the airplane.
Afraid not.
He was buried
there six months ago.
By Mr Thomas, actually.
As a punishment for helping us.
Thanks for finding him.
Now all we need to do
is find Mr Thomas.
Why don't we keep
the lad for a few days?
Let him watch some dirty videos.
I'll put the word out
how helpful he is.
Don't... don't be doing that.
Or of course
I could let you go right now.
But if, if I did do that could I
rely on your help in the future?
Like keeping an eye
on Black Mountain.
Letting me know
if you see him up there.
Yes?
Yes.
I didn't hear that.
Did you say you are
gonna help us or not?
Yes or no?
Yes.
Good.
If we let you go
without roughing you up
they'd be suspicious,
wouldn't they?
So... say thank you.
Thank you.
Oh, Jimmy, where have you been?
Oh dear God!
You stupid idiot!
Mr Quinlan,
what are you doing here?
Mr Quinlan...
Jesus, it's you!
Don't hurt me, please.
You know me, then?
How come, when we've never met?
What did they do to you?
I told you not to go up there.
Would you look...
Leave him alone.
I told him about you, Cathal.
I'll get you a cup of tea, son.
You're a bloody liar.
You've been talking with
the Special Branch, Jimmy.
You were seen.
I said nothing.
You found a body.
But you couldn't
keep your mouth shut.
You went to the police.
No, they were on the mountain
were watching for you.
They were they now?
So, let me guess
They showed you my photograph.
Right.
Asked if you'd seen me.
And what did you say?
Yes or no?
Yes
No... I don't know, I got confused.
Confused?
Little creep.
Do you want a bullet in the knees
or would you rather lose your balls?
Jesus, Cat!
He's just a kid.
He knows nothing.
Good for nothing
This is all your fault.
I kept telling him
not to go up the mountain.
Digging up the past.
Why can't you just let things lie?
We wouldn't wanna be
digging up your past.
Don't you dare!
Shut up, the pair of you!
I got something planned
on that mountain.
So if I see you again there
will be another body up there.
He's my grandson, Cathal.
I'll shoot him, Eleanor.
Don't think I won't.
You better see me out the back.
I heard you were in trouble
Come here to find you.
Found Cathal instead.
You all know each other?
Yes.
You need to get out of Belfast
for a wee while.
But I've nowhere to go.
Yes, you have.
What's all that for?
I want you to do something for me.
I need to know if she's all right.
Who?
I want you to go to America.
I think you should
take it back to her.
All right?
Listen, you Republican shite
the IRA can be most unpleasant.
But if you mess with us,
you won't recognise
your granny's body.
Who are you?
Friends of Mr Maguigan.
He says you'll help us
find Cathal Thomas.
We know he's around here,
and up there in the mountain.
All you have to do
is lead us to him.
Yes.
We're watching,
Jimmy Every second.
I'll get it.
Yes?
It's me... I'm really sorry,
I had to call you.
Please, I need some help.
Jimmy?
I found a body, on the mountain.
I found a body!
What are you saying?
What are you telling me?
They never found a body.
Don't you tell me that,
you little bastard!
I'm an old woman,
and I wanna be left alone.
No, it's the IRA.
They buried a man on the mountain.
I found him.
I have to get out of Belfast.
Mr Quinlan said I should ask you.
What do you want me to do?
Can I come and stay?
What, come here?
Please, just for a wee while.
Please.
But I don't even know you.
Mr Quinlan wants me
to bring you the ring.
I could give it to you... Please.
Just for a couple of weeks,
till it blows over.
Well all right, you can come.
Hey, Jack.
Chuck.
Good trip?
The worst.
This one is Teddy's.
Yeah.
Looks like you got yourself
a story there
Yeah.
She been crying?
No.
I have.
What happened to you?
Oh, I got shot up over Bremen.
Plexiglas in my eye
I might lose it.
I can't fly, can't even shoot.
I'm out of the war.
Ethel Ann is looking after me now.
That's good seeing how he
wanted you to take care of her.
He should have asked you, Jack.
She doesn't love me,
but I know she could love you.
I wish he'd asked you, Jack.
Well, he didn't.
And we promised.
You're the man, Chuck.
Let's do this.
Hi, Jack.
You better come inside.
What the hell is going on here?
She doesn't tell me a damn thing,
just someone is coming to visit.
Who?
Where from?
Ireland.
Belfast.
Belfast?
I don't wanna leave her alone,
Jack,
but I can't
take much more of this.
All right.
Go on, get out of here,
both of you.
You look like hell.
You wanted me to grieve
Would you go to
the airport for me, please?
I'll send Peter.
No, I want you to go yourself.
I don't even know who this guy is.
Neither do I.
Marie says he's from Belfast.
Well,
that is none of her business.
Look
Ethel you have got to talk to her.
Will you take your hands off me?
And who the hell
do you know in Belfast?
Who is this guy?
His name is Jimmy Reilly,
he's arriving at 12.10 tonight
on American 301.
Would you meet him at the airport?
You listen to me!
If you don't talk to Marie now,
you're gonna lose her.
She's gonna go.
You just tell her what happened,
she'll understand.
Listen to me.
All the love she ever got
was from her daddy.
All the kisses and hugs and
bedtime stories
and cuddles never from me
You think now
she will understand why?
I think you should
give her the chance.
Well that's what I intend to do.
Now, please go.
No, don't do that, please.
Just... come on in.
I'm sorry.
I'm real glad you're safe.
Look at that foot.
Must be hard for you,
not racing around.
Yeah.
- Let me take these.
- Thanks.
Did they find a body?
No.
So there's no proof?
Ethel Ann, he's gone.
We could arrange
a memorial service.
Why?
We're the only ones
who will remember him.
There's no family now.
No children.
Was that his case I saw you
put in the hall?
I brought his things
back for you, yeah.
Let's bring it in.
Open it up.
There's plenty of time for that.
No.
No, let's do it now
Please.
Hiya.
You must be Jimmy.
How do you do?
I'm great.
I'm just great.
Come in, please.
Oh, thank you.
Through there.
Why did you do this?
This is Jack's son, Peter.
Jimmy Reilly.
Hello.
How do you do?
Nice to meet you.
Let me take that.
And this is my daughter, Marie.
Jimmy Reilly.
Hello... How do you doody?!
Did we speak on the phone?
Sit down, Jimmy.
How was the flight?
Oh, it was fantastic.
747 all the way.
Well, not all the way.
We had to fly to London first
then right across to New York.
And they gave us meals and all.
No charge.
And they had little
things of salt and pepper,
sachets, I've got some here.
And they had little bottles of Irish.
Free.
And there was a film.
And then we had to fly
from London to New York,
then from New York to Detroit,
and from Detroit to Branagan.
And it was really fantastic.
Jack, do you remember
when we used to take two,
three, maybe four days
to do the same thing?
We'd have to go from Belfast
to Iceland to Newfoundland.
Yes.
Dad... you all right?
Yeah, why don't you take
these cases upstairs.
Oh, thank you,
but this one is for you.
Mind if I put this on your table?
No, go ahead.
Just let me get the flowers there.
They made me open it up.
This whole thing is for me?
Yes.
They couldn't believe
what I had inside.
Look at this.
Part of the aileron.
Starboard wing.
And these are switches from
the radio operator's position.
And this is a piece of
Plexiglas curved,
from a gun turret.
And this... a pressure gauge.
Oxygen.
They had to breathe oxygen,
you know, they went that high.
Oh Jesus Christ.
All right, momma, that is enough.
Tell me what
this is about right now.
Look... is this all right?
I mean, this stuff
is just fantastic
for me and I just thought would
you like to see the ring?
The what?
The ring.
It's my secret Mr Quinlan said
I can't keep secrets, but I can.
Except I told Mr Jack in the car.
What are you talking about?
I found it on Black Mountain.
Where the plane crashed.
In the war The B-17.
The B-17?
A B-17 'G' turret
It had the new chin it had double
50 calibre machine-guns.
And that's where I found the ring.
What ring?
Whose ring?
Mr Gordon's.
Well, your dad's.
Before he was, you know killed.
In Belfast?
Yes.
Are you just gonna
let this happen?
My daddy wasn't killed in Belfast.
He died here
a couple of months ago.
And his name wasn't Gordon,
it was Harris.
Chuck Harris.
Wasn't it, mom?
Of course, he couldn't be
your dad You're too young.
Shall I put these away?
Maybe you don't
have a place for them.
I have a place.
Peter,
there's some tools out back.
A crowbar, some hammers.
Would you bring them to me,
please?
What... now?
Yes,
I need to take down this wall.
Stop, momma!
Don't
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Take it easy!
This was daddy's house!
You are not going to smash it up.
This was
never your daddy's house.
He just let you believe it.
Then whose house is this?
Which of you gentlemen is
going to bring me the tools?
That's what you really want?
He kept all your letters.
I guess you don't
have a place for these.
Oh, I have a place.
Did he have any photographs,
postcards?
Pocket.
Right side.
He never even got to write these.
Ethel Ann maybe we ought
to take some of this stuff down?
No.
Nobody should touch this wall.
We could make an album,
take the photos and
put them in a scrapbook.
This is his wall.
This is his house.
I don't want anybody
Ethel Ann, this is your house.
He left it to you.
He wouldn't like it
you living here every day,
this stuff staring down at you.
He was gonna build a shed out back.
We'll just use the wood.
Do you want us to build you a shed?
No.
No, I want you to board it up.
Don't touch it, just cover it up.
Is that really what you want?
This Teddy who was he?
Jimmy?
Sergeant Teddy Gordon.
Rear gunner on B-17337833.
He crashed June 1st, 1944.
He was killed.
Gordon?
Mrs Gordon.
All those years daddy lived in
another man's house.
I'm getting out of here right now.
Marie, your mother needs you.
You shut your mouth!
Shut your mouth!
He loved you!
In spite of all of this,
he loved you.
But you never did, did you?
And all of his life he knew...
...you locked your love behind
a god-damn wall!
There was no proof.
And it was all I had left of him.
I don't care about him.
You bitch!
You shut daddy out!
And then you shut me out!
All of my life, all you have
ever done is shut us out!
Peter, can I please
come stay with you?
Go and get in the car.
You were kids then.
The both of you.
But you haven't been kids
for 50 years.
That wall should have
come down a long time ago.
Mrs Harris?
Mrs Harris,
I brought you the ring.
Gentlemen, the city of Belfast,
dead ahead.
Skip?
Do you think you could
fly this thing backwards?
Can't see a damn thing back here.
Oh, sure you can.
Just look out your ass
like you always do.
Oh, boy.
If the babes of Belfast only knew
what we had in store for them.
Maginty!
Mr Maginty!
Is it a raid?
Relax, Michael.
It's the Americans.
They've a new base near here.
No, I'm talking to somebody else.
You know what that means?
First, we're gonna
win this bloody war. See you tonight.
There will not be a single virgin
in Belfast by the end of the year.
Hey, Teddy!
Hiya, Teddy.
Hi, Eleanor.
Why don't you join in the party?
Find some girl for yourself?
I'm fixed, thank you.
Shame.
Gorgeous man like you.
Climb down there.
Don't you know he's sworn
to eternal love?
Just like we are.
I need the powder room.
I won't be long, boys.
Come on.
I need some air.
Okay.
She is great.
In every department.
I'll bet.
Yeah, I'm gonna marry her.
I'm gonna ask her tonight.
Well, she's very
...popular... Jack,
you're drunk.
You got your girl.
Why shouldn't I get mine?
No, get a girl.
Fall in love.
Not... with Eleanor.
Oh, yeah?
Who should I fall in love with?
How about Ethel Ann?
Don't you walk away from me!
You got your love.
You got her and you
gave her away to Chuck.
Not me, no.
Jack wasn't good enough.
I did not give her to anybody!
"If I die, just pass her on
down the line to good
old reliable Chuck. "
Who cares what Jack thinks?
Are you in love with Ethel Ann?
No.
No, I don't love her.
I wouldn't touch her.
I'm gonna marry Eleanor.
Why the hell shouldn't I?
She's a tart, Jack
Jesus, my ankle!
You broke it, you asshole!
I was lying, of course.
I loved Ethel so much it hurt
just thinking about her.
So did Chuck.
Three guys wanted her,
two of them got her,
and then there was me.
And when my ankle healed,
I signed on for more missions.
Stayed to the end.
52 missions.
Jesus, I should have died
100 times over.
Somehow I always came back.
And I could see how broken she was.
Real bad.
She depended on Chuck now.
He needed her.
I mean, he'd have lost
that eye but for her.
She wouldn't move out of
the house so he moved in.
I left them to it.
I got married.
Three times.
The only good thing that
came out of that was Pete.
And your mom wouldn't marry Chuck
for ten years.
Another five before you came along.
Your dad was so happy to see you.
He nearly died ofjoy.
Now you know it all.
Do I?
Why did they wait so long
to have me?
I guess she couldn't bring herself
to believe he'd never come back.
I mean, there was no body.
Everything burnt up.
Is he still trying to
get you to go back?
She's not going back, dad.
How is the Irish kid, Jimmy?
Jimmy?
Oh, jeez!
He's having a ball.
Your mom is taking him everywhere.
Oh God, he's a funny little guy.
She doesn't talk much, but,
oh boy, does he make up for it.
She never did have a son.
There you go.
And I guess I was an accident,
right?
Excuse me.
"I love you, Chuck. "
I never heard her say those words
Not once.
They had good times together.
They made a good couple.
They never spoke.
They both knew
what was behind that wall...
and they didn't say a damn thing
to each other in 50 years.
Neither did you.
Well, we didn't need to.
Everybody needs to talk.
No, honey.
Everybody needs to cry.
And your mother never did.
Not once.
You have to forgive her for that.
Do you ever wish you had just
pushed in and married mom?
Oh, no, don't ask me that, please.
Ask me anything you want,
but please don't ask me
that question.
I was... dead.
We all got killed
or maimed all of us
and Teddy didn't choose me.
And when he got killed,
I knew it was my turn to die next
...and I knew I deserved it!
That is not true.
They got a new navigator,
just a kid and he screwed up
Sorry.
It was my fault.
I should have been on that plane.
Hey, Teddy,
how about that dance tonight?
Get yourself a new girl?
I got me a girl
Same one every night.
Yeah, but she's a long ways away.
No, si she's right here with me.
Tight squeeze down there.
You mind if I join in?
Langford, Langford,
this is F-Fox 338733.
Hell, how low does this cloud go?
All the way down,
by the look of it.
You guys see anything?
No, negative, skip.
It's pretty dark out there.
Brad, you got a fix?
Well, yeah, kinda.
I mean we should be seeing
Belfast right below.
Navigator, you got a fix or not?
I think one of the beacons is out.
It's not making sense right now.
Jesus!
Bloody hell.
Full flaps.
Full flaps!
Jesus!
Jesus Christ!
Two hoses,
seven bar pressure!
Michael!
Michael Quinlan!
What the devil
are you doing up here?!
You'll get yourself killed!
Priority!
Go!
Get down!
More tea, love?
Jesus!
No, thanks, no.
Plenty of tea.
He's late.
Very, very late.
He's not late.
Will you just sit down
or something.
He's here, Michael!
Oh, thank God, he's here!
He's here!
Granny!
Don't be dribbling
on my new shirt, granny.
Jimmy.
Mr Quinlan.
How about you?
Don't shut the door!
We have a guest.
Who?
Hello.
Is this your first
visit to Belfast?
God, I can remember
when there were
hundreds of Yanks around here.
Yeah.
Lovely people,
we had a great time with them.
I nearly married one of them.
He kept saying to me,
"Would you come back to Branagan?".
Branagan?
Yes.
Then he broke his foot.
Then he went back to Branagan.
And I never saw him again
And he was in a fight
truly, a fight over me.
I know you wouldn't believe it now,
but he was.
He were gorgeous.
I'd have had him, all right.
Jack! Jack Etty.
How did you know that?
You mean your Jack?
And my granny?
That's disgusting!
Shut your mouth, young man.
So you would have known Teddy?
Teddy Gordon?
Teddy?
You see, I had so many of them
Well, no, I mean I knew
an awful lot of them.
Very friendly people.
Oh dear.
I have photographs somewhere.
What are you doing here,
Mrs Harris?
That's a rude question!
What a question!
It was her idea
She just bought a ticket and came.
Fantastic.
Dad?
Wake up.
She's gone.
She's gone. She's gone.
Belfast
to look for bits of him.
You're drunk.
Yeah.
I have been for some time.
Jack.
Dad never told her, did he?
That Teddy made him
promise to marry her.
Hell, no.
Why not?
It's like she had
Teddy's permission.
Why didn't you say something?
Because it was none
of her god-damn business!
You're a coward, dad.
And you're a liar.
You lied to Teddy and Chuck,
and worst of
all you lied to yourself.
You've always loved Ethel.
Go and get her!
Don't be stupid.
Oh, for God's sake, Jack,
go and get her.
She's your mother.
Go get her yourself.
No.
You know what,
I have better things
in my life to do.
Mr Quinlan
how was it that night?
Well, they say it hit
the ground somewhere here.
I think this is
where I found it.
The ring?
Yes.
And you're still
finding the pieces?
Yes.
Lots.
A buzzard.
He's here all the time, you know.
Keeps us company.
How about that.
We have them too.
Would you say Mrs Harris,
I'd like to know would you say,
on balance have
you led a happy life?
Well, I have to wait till
it's over and I'll work that out.
You're a strange man, Mr Quinlan
Do you believe in keeping
promises, Mr Quinlan?
Yes.
What about the promises you
make to the dead?
Do they count?
Even more.
I think promises are stupid.
Why?
Well I promise my granny
I'll wash the dishes.
And I mean to, but I never do.
You're never free of the promises
that you make, you know.
Even if you break them,
you're never free of them.
It's the German.
It's the bloody Germans!
It's not the Germans, granny.
We have to get out of the house!
Contact, Pound Street,
one man down.
Wait out.
Are you all right?
I'm so sorry!
It's not usually like this here.
Belfast is a great place really.
Only we have to
get out of here right now.
- Get out? Why? Another bomb?
- There'll be another bomb.
There's always a second bomb.
We have to get out! Come on!
Shit!
No pulse, he's a goner!
There's another fucking bomb!
Shit!
Clear the street!
Get everyone out now!
Leave him!
We'll pick him up later.
Sir.
I'm so sorry.
I really am.
Come on, Mrs Harris.
Granny,
don't be bothering with that.
Granny, get out!
Come on!
Come on, Mrs Harris, quickly.
Move!
Clear the streets!
There's another bomb!
Move, move!
Come on!
Top of the street!
You stupid bitch!
Get out the back door!
Go!
Do not return to your houses!
Right, get that cover hose on.
Get them behind the wall.
Fergus.
Fergus?
Mr Quinlan.
Haven't seen you for a while.
I have friends down here.
Anyone hurt?
Only that poor squaddie.
And they want us to go down there
and get him.
And blow more of us to pieces.
We need to clear this area.
Take her in, would you?
You're okay.
- I know her. No, sir, She's my friend.
- You can't go back. No way.
I told you before,
you can't go down there.
Clear the area immediately!
There's another bomb there!
Get out of this street
Oh my God.
Clear the area!
Oh God.
Get back here!
What the hell are you doing?
Leave me be.
There's something
I have to tell her.
Hold it!
That's as far as you're going.
This is Pound Street, sir,
but we can't get through.
Oh, this is okay.
Thanks. Back!
Move back!
Get body cover on!
Oh God.
Oh Holy God!
Mr Thomas!
Please don't do it!
Come on, quick as you can.
Jack?
Jack Etty?
It's Eleanor.
Eleanor Reilly.
Jesus Christ, Eleanor.
You must be looking for
Teddy's girl.
Yeah, Teddy's girl.
She's over there,
but we've all been evacuated.
There's been one bomb,
and they're saying
there will be another.
Mr Thomas please.
You bloody little eejit!
Get away from here!
Are you trying to
get yourself killed?
We knew he'd be up here somewhere.
Yes.
Thank you, Jimmy.
I'm sorry, sir, no further.
No, wait a second, please.
Mrs Harris?
Come slowly away, please.
There's another bomb here.
I know.
You move away, this is none of
your concern, Mr Quinlan.
Yes, it is.
Yes, it bloody is.
You might survive, you know that?
Just with bits of you blown off.
Arms, legs, eyes.
I've seen it.
Teddy wouldn't like that, now...
No.
Nice try, Mr Quinlan.
You're a brave man.
No.
No, I am not.
Do you think he looked like this
when he crashed?
No
He was alive.
I was there.
Help me, please.
Help me!
What?
Help.
Help me, please.
Please, kid, take it.
Take the ring.
Promise me to tell her she's free.
Teddy says make her own choice
Ethel Ann.
Give her the ring.
Promise me.
I promise.
I didn't take it.
I should have found you.
Told you what he said.
I looked for it.
All my life.
The ring.
You were free.
He wanted me to tell you that.
I'm so sorry.
Goodbye.
Ethel.
Please!
We have to go, Mrs Harris.
Have to go now.
Come on.
No, no! No!
Have you ever been in love,
Mr Quinlan?
No.
Life is hard enough.
So, is it possible to
love more than once?
I know I have.
That's for sure.
We've left it a bit late.
Well, that was my fault.
According to Marie,
it was my fault.
I don't know why I should
get all the blame.
Because you're an easy target.
You're getting too old
and too fat.
How come none of that
ever happened to you?
It happened to me.
Look.
But, if you promise to love
one person and no-one else,
for ever and ever?
You can't make promises like that.
Oh yes, you can.
You can't keep it.
Well worth making it, though.
I'd love to fly.
I'll take you up some time.
Teddy was gonna take me flying.
He promised.
Teddy, Teddy, Teddy
He was the greatest guy
in the world when he was alive.
But once dead, my God,
what a pain in the ass!
What's happening to me?
You're grieving, girl.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org