Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
l can't believe you invited that guy.
He's such a bloody wanker.
Oh, cut it out, Rolo.
God, why are you always
making fun of him?
Give me a break. Sissy Brit!
Who the hell talks like that?
You're such a jerk, Rolo.
You're gonna love this shit.
Pure Costa Rica Freaka.
Hey, Stacy?
While l torch this baby. . .
. . .how about you lick my chest?
-What about my nipples?
-Shut up! Someone's watching us.
A peeper, huh? My kind of guy.
Rolo, l'm serious. lt creeped me out.
All right, all right.
l know a place more private. . .
. . .and romantic.
Check it out.
What do you think?
Should we be doing this here?
lsn't this, like, sacred or something?
What? No, they're dead.
You got any objections, Ricky?
l think you should give it to her, senor.
There he is again.
This guy's gonna be picking his teeth
out of my dump.
Stacy, this guy doesn't
even have teeth.
-Oh, my God!
-Watch the hair, asshole!
Goddamn monkeys.
Oh, my God!
Who needs a love potion?
l whipped up something extra tasty.
So where are we gonna do this?
l don't wanna get caught
in the middle of a cemetery.
Let's at least go inside
that old mausoleum.
Check this out.
Oh, looks like we don't
need you anymore.
lt was probably just the wind.
Okay, we're back in.
Heads or tails?
Heads.
What's tails?
You don't wanna know.
What is it? Too waxy?
-l heard something.
-Was it a strange sucking sound?
What do you think
about smacking me in the face. . .
. . .a couple of times?
Not hard.
Well, kind of hard.
-What do you say?
-No.
-Come on.
-No. Oh, no.
Come on, Kellie. l'm not
asking you to eat my crap.
-No!
-Just slug me.
-Over here!
-No, this way!
Whatever.
Welcome to Pleasure Island!
I'm your host, Coconut Pete.
Put your bags down and meet me
at the pool for a nice drink.
You ready for the time of your life?
Yeah, fiesta time!
Are you ready to party?
-Lars Brunckhorst.
-Right this way.
-How are you?
-Welcome to the island. Keep walking.
Are you ready to party?
Party! Who'd like to party?
-Hey, Lars--
-Welcome to the party!
Follow the officer.
Welcome to
Coconut Pete's Pleasure lsland!
You are here to have fun.
lf you choose not to have fun,
fun will be provided for you.
All right, let's go have some fun!
Bring it down. Left, right. . . .
Hey, how are you? Listen--
Nice fucking hat, pussy!
-You got that bag of grass l loaned you?
-Sorry. You know how it is.
Let me know when
you score some more.
Party, party! l'm Mr. Party!
Hey, Yu. Sorry l'm late.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Yeah, all right.
Go on.
-Who wants drinks?
-Bring it on.
Hey, Dave.
Hey, Carlos.
-Hola, Kellie.
-Can you put something. . .
-. . . ''X-tra'' in my drinks?
-l know ''X-actly'' what you need.
There you go.
lf anyone else is ''E-ager''
to share the ''X-perience'' . . .
. . .l'll be around this ''E-vening''
and will be ''X-pecting'' them.
-Okay, okay. l get it.
-Put it on my tab.
-At least give me one of those.
-Sorry, they're so spoken for.
Fucking bitch.
We're gonna go for a romp
in the jungle before the party.
Oh, l don't know, Stace. l have to play
tennis soon and to be honest. . .
. . .that stretch of jungle gives me
a case of the wonky britches.
Sweet Jesus, you're a f-cake, Putman.
What the hell? You were just
telling me he's a nut cup.
l did not!
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls!
Your host and rock 'n ' roll's
favorite son...
... Coconut Pete!
Welcome to Pleasure lsland.
l love you, Coconut Pete!
Guess you all heard this one.
Back you go, dickweed!
You also know that l took this song. . .
. . .and turned it into a beautiful reality.
This gorgeous group of people
behind me is our staff.
And they're here to take care of you
in more ways than one.
You came here to escape civilization
and we're gonna hold you to it.
No cell phones here,
there are no fax machines. . .
. . .and most importantly of all,
no strings attached.
Coconut Pete, you're under arrest.
-What are the charges?
-For keeping these people. . .
. . .from enjoying free drinks at the pool
from noon to 3.
That would be a crime.
You heard the man.
Free drinks at the pool!
Last one in is a rotten coconut.
-Are you all right?
-Yeah.
-That thing scared me a little.
-lt's just Welkie, the welcome gorilla.
Two idiots were humping him,
so l'm stashing him here.
-l'm Jenny.
-l'm Penelope.
l'm a little lost.
You look familiar.
Have you ever been here before?
Yeah. Well, no.
-So where are you from?
-Nome, Alaska.
l guess you just have
one of those faces.
Take a right up there
to get to the big path.
You better hurry. You'll miss
the drinks by the pool.
Man, look at that chassis on this one.
-Dude. Wanna get nailed?
-Hot goose looking for some gander juice.
-Okay, maybe later.
-l'll get back to you.
Dude, look at that one, dude.
Green bikini? Dude.
-Look at that little cheetah.
-Hair pie.
-Jackie O. Tripod.
-Dude, wha--?
Dude. Check out
that orange bikini, dude.
-Dude, come on.
-Do you want to be grilled by Manny?
Bogey, bogey, 1 2 noon.
Holy shit, dude!
l know that chick.
She's on that TV show. . .
...A.M. Pump-up with Amy Aerobics!
Oh, yeah. She's the one
in the way back.
She was.
Then the palm tree chick died. . .
. . .so she got promoted to palm tree.
Then Amy Aerobics died.
She's the new number one chick,
the new Amy Aerobics.
Amy Aerobics died?
What'd she die of?
She didn't die of a fat ass,
l'll tell you that, bro.
What's up? Dude, don't be gay, man.
-No, l don't think so.
-Hi there.
Hey, Lars Brunckhorst.
l'm the new masseur.
-Hi, l'm Jenny.
-Really nice to meet you, Jenny.
-And this is Yu.
-And really nice to meet you, Yu.
-So you subbing in for lnga this week?
-Yeah.
Well, you better be good.
lnga had some great moves.
Let's see what you got.
Oh, God. lnga never
did anything like that.
Who's the fucking hippie?
-l'll take that.
-Hey! Get your own margy.
lt's not for me.
lt's for our new masseur, Lars.
You serious? We swapped out
a 6-foot Swedish broad. . .
-. . .for this guy?
-l'm 6' 1 '' .
-Cool!
-Don't worry about him.
He's Pete's nephew, so he
thinks he can get away with murder.
At least assault
with a deadly wet one.
-Who wants to limbo?
-Limbo, limbo, limbo.
l'll show you the ropes
at the club tonight!
Look for me. l'll be the cute chick
behind the bar.
Put some Frankie
back to Hollywood.
Dude, whatever.
Dude, this is you! This is you!
Build the high.
Bend it, don't break it.
-Don't bend anything.
-l'm getting so fucking laid tonight.
Yeah, drink, sugar. Chug it down.
Chug it down for me.
What's up, there, foxes and cockses?
Here comes Coconut Pete!
Hey, amigo.
-You must be Lars.
-Coconut Pete.
l appreciate you bringing
me into your life circle.
Pleasure's all mine.
l hear good things about your fingers.
-ls that a tranquility blouse?
-Yeah, it is.
lt's the one you wore
on your album cover.
Pink Crustaceans and Good Vibrations.
l read a 1 977 interview
where you said teal and blue. . .
. . .kept you focused in tough times.
That sounds like something
l said back in '77.
l guess nobody told you you have
to wear the Pleasure Sweater. . .
-. . .on luge duty.
-Yeah, they did. . .
. . .but it's kind of hot in here
and it was wadded up on the ground--
Just put the goddamn thing on.
Hank, give Lars a hand.
Oh, yeah.
-Thanks, Hank.
-Hey, Coco Pete.
l have a present
for you, my friend.
You see the beautiful flower
in the yellow dress?
-She's in full bloom.
-She said she saw you in Tucson. . .
. . .three years ago, 1 4th row.
Excuse me, but weren't you
at one of my shows?
-U of A, '99?
-Yeah!
l remember you. You were in the--
Don't tell me. . .
-. . .fifteenth row.
-1 4th row!
l have a pictographic memory
for pretty faces.
-Hey, how about the grand tour?
-Yeah, sure.
Right this way.
Hey, buddy!
Jesus Christ. That's tequila.
l was doubles partners with
Andre Agassi for an entire week.
l taught Dre to play cocks and quarters.
lf you can believe it,
he'd never played cocks and quarters.
-That's interesting.
-Yeah, it's--
Hey, snowbunny!
Give me a Drambuie, neat.
-You got it.
-All alone, huh?
Don't worry.
No woman, no cry, right, man?
l was quite engaged until
you bullied your way in here.
l heard you.
Something about cocks and quarters?
We have that game here too.
lt's called ''hide the sausage. ''
l beg your pardon? New fellow. . .
-. . .please cut off this minor.
-Come on!
lf there's grass on the field,
then play ball. Right?
Hey, Sammy! Hit me!
Gracias, sheriff.
Legalize it!
Late night fun at the campfire
in one hour. Don 't forget your condoms.
Who wants some tequila?
Who wants some?
What, are you dancing alone?
Sweetie, come here.
-Hi.
l now pronounce you
Mr. and Mrs. Funzy.
You owe me one, bro.
May l kiss the bride?
-Do you work here?
-l do.
-l'm Juan Castillo. l am dive master.
-Like, cliffs or. . .?
Cliffs, rocks, boards,
whatever you wish.
That is a beautiful name. . .
Penelope.
-lt's breathtaking.
-Thank you.
So tell me, what brings you
here to us, Penelope?
Oh, l'm on spring break.
l go to Oral Roberts.
Oral Roberts? ls that anything like
an Anal Johnson?
Because, well, l've done that
a few times.
Or am l thinking of a Dirty Sanchez?
That's the one.
-l don't know what that is.
-lt's not for you.
-Oh, my God.
-Yes. A very magical place.
-Hey.
-Hey, Carlos.
Make it quick,
we got a lot of dishes.
Goddamn monkeys.
-Yu?
-Carlos, these knives are filthy.
When are you gonna clean them?
One, two. One, two, three, four.
Play ''Margaritaville. ''
-Excuse me?
-Play ''Margaritaville. ''
l love that song!
l think you're referring to
my song ''Pina Coladaburg. ''
No, ''Margaritaville. ''
l think you mean ''Pina Coladaburg. ''
A little song l wrote seven and
a half fucking years. . .
. . .before ''Margaritaville''
was even on the map!
Of course, you wouldn't know that,
because you weren't even born yet!
-Come on, let's get a drink.
-l don't need this shit.
-Come on, man.
-Fuck that guy.
-Son of a son of a bitch!
-Yeah.
-Mother motherfucker!
Hey, Jenny.
-Sorry.
-Give me a heads up before you do that.
lt's a habit. l could see how tight
you were from a mile away.
What can l say? Some girls are
just tighter than others.
Sorry.
So l guess l'm talking to a celebrity.
l heard you got your own show?
Yeah. Amy Aerobics. . .
. . .accidentally ate some rat poison.
lt was awful.
l'm still psyched.
l've been waiting a long time for this.
-That's great.
-Hey, Jen.
l will be glad to never have
to do this again.
-lt must be tough living in paradise.
-You love it now, but just wait.
Crab legs, crab legs. . . .
Hey, you guys ever hear the story
of the Machete Maniac?
-Let's hear it!
-Yeah, l don't know. . .
. . .it's probably too scary for you.
-No, no, it's not!
-No, come on, Dave.
-Please, tell us the story.
-All right, what the hell.
This must have been,
like, 1 5 years ago.
We had a kid working at
the club named Phil Coletti.
And one night,
a night a lot like tonight. . .
. . .this gorgeous woman comes into
the club, asks him out to the jungle.
He's like, ''Yeah, why not?''
So they split. And as they start
getting out to the jungle. . .
. . .further and further away
from the lights of the club. . .
. . .she asks him if he believes
in the local legends of the island.
Voodoo? Zombies?
He's not too worried about it.
He just rolls right over,
starts putting the screws to her.
But something doesn't feel right
to Coletti.
But he can't see shit, it's pitch-black,
so he just keeps banging away.
But then, boom!
A flash of lightning. . .
. . .lights up the whole island
and in that one moment. . .
. . .he looks around and sees. . .
. . .not only is he in
the old Mayan cemetery. . .
. . .not only are the other guys from the
resort standing around watching him. . .
. . .but he sees he's having sex
with a corpse.
A cold, white,
dirty-from-the-grave dead body.
And they say Phil Coletti calmly walked
to the groundskeeper's shack. . .
. . .found a machete. . .
. . .and chopped those staff members
into a hundred pieces.
And they say he took
that same machete. . .
. . .chopped his own dick off
and ran screaming into the jungle.
Nobody ever saw him after that.
But from that point on. . .
. . .Phil Coletti was forever known
as Machete Phil.
You're saying there's a totally deranged,
dickless dude running around out there?
l'm saying l don't go
into the jungle alone if l can help it.
Because you can hear him.
And l've heard him.
Crying out:
''Where's my penis?
Where's my penis?
Where's my penis?''
And that boy was me!
You're an asshole, Putman.
-Everybody get laid tonight?
-Hey, Pete.
l know l did.
Anybody seen Rolo, Stacy or Kellie?
They're probably screwing around
in the jungle.
Shit. l'm gonna need somebody
to run Luau Night tomorrow.
Sure, l'll run Luau Night.
Cut up some pineapples, whatever.
-Great. Sam, will you run Luau Night?
-Sure, can do.
We'll get grass skirts,
have a poi-eating contest. . .
-. . .and everyone'll get lei'd!
-Sounds great.
People, please. ls it too much to ask?
Have sex with the guests.
Some of them aren't bad-looking.
Hola, Penelope.
Change!
All right, 200 points.
-Move fast.
-Oh, you're dead, fucker.
You little yellow prick!
You're fucked!
Five hundred points!
-Fucking worm!
-A simple tag would have sufficed.
Eat it, fuck-nut!
Cue pretzel.
Where's pretzel?
Come on, cue pretzel.
Cue pretzel. Pretzel!
-Pretzel!
-What are you guys doing?
Hey, pretzel! Get your twisted,
salty ass out here.
Hey!
Ocupado, bro. Go.
Switch off? Huh?
Sorry, Cliff. l need you in the maze.
-l'm on break.
-Be happy in your work, pear.
Shit.
-Hey, look, l salty.
-Wait, what's your name?
-Listen, Mommy, l call you later.
-Bye.
Shit.
l got you!
Hello?
Lars?
Oh, sorry. l was just
in the middle of my Qi Kung.
Qi Kung?
l should have you on my show.
You're not just into
massage, are you?
Yeah, well, l mean,
body work's still my life.
l've also done the Dianetic thing.
Spent time in the Forum.
Did a little Falun Gong in Bang Chow.
-Know who's got a great philosophy?
-Who?
Coconut Pete.
Have a good time,
all the time. . .
-. . .always eat the worm.
-Always eat the worm. Totally.
-Sign our asses!
Sign our asses!
-What do you know about Fenshi?
-Nothing.
The Snoring Panda.
Not to be confused with Linou Gano.
The Leaking Turtle.
Don't try that in public.
Hey, guys, l'm gonna send you back over
there. You'll get plenty of signatures.
-Come on, hop.
-Go ahead.
-That's amazing.
lt's about connecting
your meridians.
We have energy that flows
through us, connected by buttons.
So, what other buttons
can you push?
Tian-Tu.
The Heaven Point.
Fuck me.
Damn.
Maybe l should take
you home with me.
l don't know if l'd fit in your luggage.
-Holy shit!
-What the--?
-Carlos?
-What's he doing up in the air?
-You're gonna be okay, dude.
-l'm not getting a pulse.
''Naughty Carlos''?
Who's driving the boat?
You never played this game?
We had a cheap Nicaraguan version
called ''Circle Eater. ''
But, you know. . . .
Trying to tell us something?
ls Timmy trapped in a well?
-You must come, quick!
-Follow the banana!
Follow the banana
Oh, man!
-Who would do something like this?
Come on. Just settle down.
-You're making a scene.
-There's a killer on the island.
l know who it is. lt's Machete Phil.
Come out from the jungle.
Cool it. That's just a bullshit
story for the guests.
Hey, hey, it looks like
everybody else is okay.
You gotta see what someone
did to my activities board.
Oh, my God!
-My God.
-Those mother--
''Do your jobs and live.
Tell the guests and die. ''
''Everybody's looking
to find their own paradise. ''
-The hell's that mean?
-We have to get off the island.
We have to get
everyone off the island.
Okay.
Okay, the radio's smashed.
-And we got no boats.
-No boats?
-How could somebody steal both boats?
-l don't know.
The Smiling Smuggler looked
like it was driving on its own.
-On its own?
-Phone definitely been cut?
-lt was not chewed up by jungle rats.
-We have jungle rats?
-What are we gonna tell the guests?
-Nothing. You saw the board.
He's right. We tell the guests
there's a maniac on the island. . .
. . .we're gonna have
1 00 crazed maniacs.
What about the sign on Cliff?
l mean, it clearly said ''Staff only. ''
That means he's targeting us.
-Fucking crazy.
-l don't understand.
Why are they coming after us?
When you're all done with your little
pink-panty meltdown, let me know. . .
. . .because l'd like to get
down to business.
l thought it was time
to bring in the pro.
-Hank?
-Yes, Hank.
The head of security on all my tours.
So, what, he keeps aging hippies from
stealing the bong out of your bus?
lt just so happens Hank used to be
a federal agent. Yeah, that's right.
Head an FBl task force
on serial killers.
Single-handedly caught
the Minneapolis Mangler.
-Who's the Minneapolis Mangler?
-Exactly.
You are aware that l have
served this guy 20 beers a day. . .
-. . .for the last 1 0 years, right?
-Hey, l was in Nicaragua, junior!
When you stuff your intestines back
in your pockets and walk 20 klicks. . .
. . .after a knife fight with guerilla
drug lords, then you talk to me.
Since there's no way off this rock,
we're gonna have to catch this guy.
We couldn't even catch the raccoon
that was stealing my wristbands.
You didn't ask me to catch
the raccoon, did you, Pip?
-Pip?
-All right, now, here's the plan.
You're gonna give this wing nut
exactly what he wants:
You're all gonna do your jobs.
All right, tell us something.
How the hell are we
supposed to do our job. . .
. . .when somebody is killing the dick
out of everybody on the island?
Take it easy there,
menstrual cramp.
You read the poem
on that board out there.
l seen this a million times.
This guy's playing a game
and we're gonna play right back.
Just keep cool
and this cat will come to us.
And when he does, l promise you,
l'll be there with my whomping stick.
Come on, hit it! Hit it!
Definitely not this guy.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
What in the queen's wig
is going on here?
We've got a killer on the loose,
you're throwing a pinata party.
The cut on that pear kid
was left to right.
Left to right! l'm looking
for the left-handed killer, you idiot.
l see.
This is totally fucked up.
l don't even know what l'm looking for.
l don't even know
what l'm doing here.
l've been thinking about that poem
on the board.
There's something really familiar
about those words.
l just can't seem
to wrap my fingers around it.
Can you wrap your fingers
around this?
-Hi, Juan.
-Hey.
-Hey, hi, how are you?
-Good. l made you a hat.
-l don't know what to say.
-Well, say thank you and put it on.
All right, all right.
Thank you. l love it.
You wanna take a walk on the beach?
You know, it's the same here
as it is down there, you know?
Sand and water here. . .
. . .sand and water--
l heard you were being
very bad today, Juan.
What do you mean?
When you were supposed
to be in the maze. . .
. . .you were eating watermelon.
-How did you find out about that?
-Because l see everything, Juan.
You know--? You know what?
l think it's a good idea if we were to go
down the beach a little more far.
The two of us.
Okay.
Oh, you know, l forgot.
l'm supposed to go make s'mores!
-We checked every guest cabana.
-No weapons? Bloody clothes?
Just pornography
and a load of condoms.
-The guy in 1 4 had a wooden Bible.
-Wooden Bible, huh?
That's good, that's a good job.
All right, Jenny, you go
check on Yu. She's freaking out.
New meat, you take over here.
Okay?
Break.
-You'll be all right?
-Yeah.
Sure.
Shite.
Not her best.
Hello, Pete.
''Hope They've Got
Hammocks in Heaven. ''
Great.
And again, Peter.
You dirty bugger.
What's this?
This is crazy.
We can't do this anymore!
Quiet, Yu.
The guests will hear!
We cannot act like there's nothing
wrong. There are guests everywhere.
-We have to tell them.
-No! You saw that board.
-l said, ''Totally tea bag season. ''
-Shut up, gay-rod. Give me a light.
l need you back at the bonfire.
We're gonna make an announcement.
Good, l got an announcement
to make to Roy.
l'm totally bake-ached.
What?
ldiots.
Hey, come to the beach.
We're gonna make
an announcement.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
There's always
one fuckhead like you. . .
. . .trying to shit in the apple pie.
Well, you just shat in the one apple pie
that knows how to shit back.
So why don't you and me, let's just--
Oh, my God!
Shit!
Amy's got some fantastic advice
for everybody.
Here are humans, here is God
and here are we.
You're the girl, Ame!
Shoulders down.
-How are we looking?
-You're looking fantastic!
You're looking fantastic.
This is one of the top five--
Let's do the sun salute!
Crab, crab, crab, shot,
throw it away, salute!
Hey, let's dance!
lt's easier when you're smiling.
-l heard one of our ski boats last night.
-Shit! That's great!
-l heard it for a second--
-lf it's one of ours, this guy's got it.
Not a good idea to look for it unless
you want your dinghy chopped off.
What?
l figured it out.
l know where those lines
on the board came from.
You know that line ''Everyone's
looking to find their own paradise''?
-That's from one of your songs.
-One of my songs?
Yeah, it's off your album
Sea Shanties and Wet Panties.
1 978?
Let's see those pincers, people!
What does the song
have to do with this?
The name of the song
is ''Naughty Cal. ''
-''Naughty Cliff,'' ''Naughty Carlos. ''
-''Naughty Cal. ''
Naughty Cal
Bongo and Tokey
Got tired of living on land
So the three amigos
Took an undersea trip
And never were seen again
Bongo the stoned crab
Got high as a kite
Fell and cracked his shell
Shit, that's the line that
was on the board yesterday.
l didn't know where it was from.
How do you not know
the words to your song?
l don't even remember
making the album. Okay?
Shit, it was '78.
We were all out of our gourds.
lt was kind of crazy times in 1 978.
Oh, man, we had
some fucking parties.
Bongo the stoned crab
Got high as a kite
And fell and cracked his shell
Tokey was lost in a maze all night
''High as a kite till he fell
and cracked his shell. ''
That's like Carlos up in the parasail!
Then ''Lost in a maze. ''
Exactly like Cliff!
So this guy's killing people
according to an acid trip song?
-This is insane.
-Peter, what's the song about?
ls there some sort of
special significance?
Fuck, no. l mean--
l don't know, it's a sea shanty.
And Naughty Cal's this
underwater cowboy.
And Tokey and Bongo
are his buddies. . .
. . .and they go on this adventure
to find Atlantis or some shit.
Let's listen to the next line,
see what happens.
Maybe if l play it backwards.
-Mango bay
-Wait, listen.
But a big, bad orca
And the scary octopus
Were guarding the riverbed
So, what the hell?
''The orca and the octopus''?
ls it the next victims?
Or is it the killer?
Our lives depend on us interpreting
the dumbest song l've ever heard.
Don't hold back. Say what you
really think. l'm not sensitive.
l won about five fucking
gold records in my lifetime.
How many gold records do you have?
Let's see how it ends.
Everybody's looking
To find their own paradise
But it ain 't on Earth
It's up there in heaven
And someday
We're all gonna die
-Jesus.
-Pete!
Yu and Hank are dead.
-Why? What did we do?
-No, man.
Yu and Hank are fucking dead.
You threatening me?
Because if you are,
you hairless lapdog--
Just come and look!
''Don't let this be Yu. ''
She was just trying
to warn the guests.
Hank.
Yu.
Why are we doing
a fashion show?
Because it's Fashion Show Wednesday,
that's why!
Look what happened to Yu! Remember
the warning, ''Do your jobs or die''?
We're gonna put smiles on our faces
and march out there and do our jobs.
-Lars, you're up. Come on.
-You got it.
Lars Brunckhorst, everybody.
Lars is sporting the Pleasure Poncho.
Only $ 1 9.95 at the gift shop.
Thank you, Lars.
I got a bad feeling
about the new guy.
You are right.
lt all started when he got here.
Sam, it isn't Lars or any of us.
Look, l know why
you're defending him.
Pajamas!
Come on, move! Come on!
-Putman, pillow.
-Putman Livingstone, l presume.
Oh, if it isn't Little Lord Fauntleroy!
Pip, Pip, tallyho!
l got it.
ln that song, Naughty Cal
sings about the scary octopus.
Look at Putman!
Putman is the octopus. Hello?
Dave, just go play
with the curtains or something.
We can't dismiss that song.
What about Carlos and Cliff?
What about the fact Hank was buried in
the sand like the treasure in the song?
All right, so maybe the octopus
is the way the next person dies?
How do you kill someone
with an octopus?
Octopus spelled backwards
is ''supotco. ''
-lsn't that Spanish for something?
-''Supotco''? No.
-The word for shoe is zapato.
-Shoe.
Am l the only one who thinks
his head looks like an octopus?
-Here he comes.
-What did l miss?
Apparently somebody's gonna
get killed by a shoe.
lnstead of focusing on the song,
why don't we look for the boats?
-Good idea.
-Jenny, why don't you and l. . .
. . .go search together?
Putman, why don't you
and l go and look for that boat?
Are you daft? l'm not going out in the
jungle with you and your bloody shiatsu.
lf you're the killer,
you'll snap my neck like a twig.
Stick to the shore.
No reason to go in the jungle.
The boats are gonna
be covered with sticks.
-Or branches.
-Oh, thanks much, officer.
Aren't you taking any weapons?
l have all the weapons l need.
Piss on that! l'm taking a machete.
Thanks for doing this, Lars.
You're very brave.
But just be careful, all right?
Good luck, Putman.
Better believe l'll be keeping
an eye on you, Mr. Miyagi.
You're probably intimidated
by cooking for the whole resort. . .
. . .but l think you're gonna
get a big kick out of it.
l bet you watched Yu and Kellie
and most of it is common sense.
Like right now, l'm making my
famous Coconut Pete's paella.
Can anyone guess the secret ingredient?
Come on.
Coconut Pete's paella?
The secret ingredient?
Coconut Pete?
-Coconut?
-Yes, goddamn it! Yes!
Yes!
Jesus, you think Eddie Money
has to put up with this shit?!
Goddamn it! Coconut paella!
Jesus Christ.
What do you think?
Pete's under a lot of pressure.
l don't think we can say for sure.
-l don't know.
-What are you doing?
You know, just hanging around,
looking through the window.
Calamari?
lt's an aphrodisiac, Juan.
What's wrong? You're not afraid
of a little octopus, are you?
When you're done here. . .
. . .l want you to come
inside and find me. . .
. . .because l wanna wrap my
little tentacles around you.
Okay.
No way.
Think about it. The octopus.
She's a weird little chick,
l'll give you that.
Look, it still doesn't
prove that she's the killer.
All right.
Then there is only one way to find out.
Don't be nervous.
l just want our first time
to be wonderful.
So l would say that if you're the killer,
you know, just maybe don't kill me.
Or at least make it,
you know, painless.
With those moves, l bet you could
put me down nice and easy. l'm out.
The reason we're hiding in this closet
is because we think she's the killer.
-Yeah, not too hard, l hope.
-l really like Juan.
When we first met, l was like,
''Who is this guy?
Some local guy coming
down here and--''
l haven't been entirely
honest with you.
You mean you don't really
go to the Oral Roberts?
l mean l just wanted to leave my
past behind me when l came here.
What the fuck are you,
a praying-mantis woman?
God! l have never
been to a place like this.
l mean, it's just so free.
Juan, l have spent
my whole life in a gym.
l just wanted to party
like everyone else.
My coach, Orgrav,
would kill me if he found out.
He would hunt me down
like a deranged lunatic.
-He's really scary some--
-Wait, wait.
You are a gymnast?
Yeah.
-Oh, Juan.
-Penelope.
No, no!
-No!
-Oh, Juan!
l'll be right back.
Okay.
l'm still not sure. l may need a few
more hours to pump her for information.
You're just trying to get laid.
Would you like to be in this closet
while l have sex?
That is a great idea.
Here she comes.
What exactly are your
intentions with Jenny?
You know, Put, during the Sung dynasty
there was a great mystic. . .
. . .Master Tsu Tong Po.
And he once said something very wise:
''lf you love something, set it free.
lf it comes back to you--''
Fuck off, it's a bloody Hallmark card.
Just trying to help you, man.
Well, she has taken quite
a fancy to you, hasn't she?
But l have some ammunition
of my own.
What kind of man would l be if l sat
idly by while you stole her from me?
Do not underestimate me, Lars.
l know things you don't.
All right, Lars,
let's see what you've got.
Look what l found.
Yeah. Shiny.
Hey.
l knew it.
Sick fuck.
Dear God in heaven.
Lars?
Oh, dear God.
No!
-You?
-That's right, love.
Now, take that stupid bag
off your head and give us a kiss.
-What?
-Advantage, Putman.
Putman.
Putman, wake up, Putman.
Putman, it's a dream.
lt's just a dream, Putman.
Farewell.
Keep it clean, keep it clean, mister.
That's a point. That's a point.
Mira, a boat.
He found the fucking boat.
Hang on to your kudos.
-She's not going anywhere.
-What did you do to the propeller?
Nothing. This is the one
that was pulling Carlos.
We could send a group to paddle to the
mainland. We've got plenty of guys.
No chance.
The riptide'll take you out to sea.
You'll be drinking your own urine
in less than 20 hours.
-Where's Putman?
-He's not here?
He left. He ran off into the jungle.
Oh, by ''ran off,'' do you
mean ''got killed by you''?
Did you really think we wouldn't
notice Putman was gone?
-That's ridiculous.
-Why is that ridiculous?
Look, Putman freaked out in the middle
of the night and took off into the jungle.
We went into your room.
Mark David Chapman over here
has a shrine to Pete.
-lt's unbelievable.
-So l'm a fan.
A fan? Man, you're a fucking loon.
Look, nobody here was killed last night. . .
. . .because Lars was
in the jungle killing Putman.
Hey, look, l could never hurt
another person, okay?
l don't believe in violence. l touch
people to make them feel better.
l have an obligation
to get to the bottom of--
-You are the fucking fun police.
-Juan, what the hell--?
Come on, take it easy!
Quit your bickering!
We get through one more night,
the boat will be here tomorrow.
We'll be all right. So come on,
let's just have a drink and mellow out.
l don't wanna mellow out, Pete.
l wanna know what Lars' deal is.
-You come here--
-l don't have to tell you shit, fun pig!
You wanna fun arrest me?
Get a fun fucking warrant.
Until then, stay out
of my fun fucking face!
Come on.
Jenny, you know
l'm not the killer, right?
Look, Lars, it's not so bad in here, okay?
l'll bring you some magazines.
Yeah? You familiar with
the expression ''sitting duck''?
No.
You guys, this is totally fucked up.
Look, Jenny, if he's the killer,
then we have him in this room.
And if not, then at least
we know it's not him.
Did it stink? You bet it stunk.
Oh, shit.
Hey, you guys gonna be
hanging around for a while?
Totally. We're just getting started.
Anyway, that's my mom for you.
Any of you guys have a mother?
Free drinks, whoever catches me.
Shit.
Oh, God!
-Your prayers have been answered.
-You asshole!
No, l'm not an asshole.
l'm just young, dumb and full--
-What the fuck?
-What?
Something just brushed
against my leg. What the--?
-There's seriously something down here.
-What?!
Oh, no, wait.
lt's just my gigantic cock.
-Amy's got some fantastic advice....
-Oh, my God.
-So you wanna get it on?
-Dirk, get out of the pool.
l'm not kidding. Hurry!
-Hey, that's what l call service.
-No!
Get out of the pool!
Somebody help me!
Putman, you're alive.
You put your arms around me.
l assume this means every other
man on the island is dead.
We gotta get out of here. Dirk's dead.
He got electrocuted in the pool.
Really? What was the look on his face?
He must have screamed bloody murder.
You're scaring me.
l just want to know if smoke
came out of his ears. ls that so wrong?
-Putman, where have you been?
-Running in circles through the jungle.
Thank God you're not dead.
We need to get that auxiliary generator.
Wait, hang on. lf Dirk just got killed,
then Lars couldn't be the killer.
-Be on guard, he might be a little cranky.
-Lars? Lars, we're here.
Oh, do give it a rest, Jen.
-He couldn't have.
-He's far too large.
We gotta find Pete.
Pete.
Pete?
You in here, Pete?
Peter, we need the key
to the generator box.
-Damn it!
-lsn't somebody going to get the door?
Who's there?
Who's out there?!
Hey, l think there's a problem
with the lights.
Right?
-Lars will come after us here.
-We don't know for sure that it is Lars.
We don't know if he got out
or if someone else got in.
What is it with you and Lars?
l wonder if you aren't in cahoots.
Let's see, you had sex
with Rolo and he's dead.
-You and Cliff, right? He's dead.
-Give me a break.
l screwed Juan and Pete
and they aren't dead.
-Bloody hell, Jen. Am l the only one?
-Let's get back to the case.
-We have to figure out--
-Why don't you drop the cop routine.
As soon as you drop the
''l've got nothing to hide'' routine, Juan.
You were looking for this letter
from the Encarnacion prison facility?
-What the fuck, man?
-Fuck. Why you are doing this, man?
''Juan shows no signs of the bizarre
and horrible behavior. . .
. . .that brought him to this institution.
We believe him to be fully rehabilitated. . .
. . .and will be an excellent
addition to your staff. ''
-What did you do, Juan?
-l did nothing, Jenny.
What the fuck did you do, man?
Costa Rican prison, that's some
hardcore anal action, man.
-Juan, we have to know.
-What did you do, Juan?
-What the fuck did you do?
-What did you do?
-Tell us!
l did nothing!
-lt's Chupacabra!
-Pete.
No!
God.
-How could you do that?
-Wait, wait. l did not do this.
-l am not a killer.
-What the fuck, man? Then what is this?
You want to know what l did?
You all want to know what l did?
Juan Castillo went to jail. . .
. . .for having sex with a goat.
All right?
What do you want me to say?
We lived on a farm.
And l got lonely!
We were--
We were just a couple of stupid kids.
No, it wasn't Juan.
lt was Dave, wasn't it?
You hated him for what
he did to your parents.
You see, what none of us did know. . .
. . .indeed, what none
of us could know. . .
. . .was David's parents were trampled
to death at a Coconut Pete concert.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Everyone knows Dave's parents
got killed at a Pete show.
-Way to bring up a sore subject.
-What? l-- What?
You think l could have killed him?
He's my Uncle Petey.
You all saw him as. . .
. . .a mellow island songster
and a resort owner. . .
. . .but how many of you knew
that he was afraid of dogs. . .
. . .and that his favorite
spice was rosemary?
How many of you knew that he was
uncircumcised and smelled of oranges?
Yes, that's all well and good, David.
But l'll bet hind to horses
that you inherit the island.
-The island is already mine.
-What?
Pete signed it over last week.
He was going on the road,
where he belonged.
He was forming a super group.
Billy Squier and Eddie Money.
Don Henley was gonna play drums!
Fuck, that would've been tight! Fuck.
He was gonna sell the island
to the Navy for test bombing.
But l told him l could
handle the responsibility.
-Lars.
-No.
No.
Pete.
Oh, my God. Pete.
Bravo, Lars, bravo.
Very convincing.
-You fucker!
-Lars, stop it!
-You ain't nothing!
-Stop it!
-Hold it.
-Let's lock him up again.
-Bring it! You're dead!
-No! Stop it!
-lt's madness!
-We're not locking anybody up.
We're all gonna stay
together in one room.
The boat will be here tomorrow.
We'll go gather the guests
and wait until the morning.
We're gonna do this together.
And we're gonna
make it through the night, okay?
Screw this. l'm not going
anywhere with Lars.
l'm not going anywhere with Juan.
What kind of man has sex with a goat?
Hey, l used a condom.
You told me they were
against your religion.
You know, l need to find Penelope.
l am sure you all understand.
You come anywhere near my cabana,
l'm taking your head off.
Let's get out of here, Dave.
-Come on, Dave, let's get out of here.
-l don't think so.
Jenny, you're making
a most grievous mistake.
l'm still not sure what happened with
that dodgy business back in the jungle. . .
. . .but l'm plagued by the dreams.
l believe l'm safer on my own.
-Well, that plan went to hell.
-Well, at least they left us a torch.
Jenny? Jenny?
l believe l know
where the generator is.
That's the stuff.
Yes.
Damn it. He must have
taken my swords.
l don't care if l have to carve
a spear out of bamboo.
-Listen.
-No, l'm so sick of running from this--
l thought we didn't have power.
-Dave?
-Naughty Cal, Bongo and Tokey
Dave? Dave?
So the three amigos
Took an undersea trip
Never were seen again
God.
-lt's me, it's me, it's me.
-We're all gonna die
-Holy shit.
Oh, my God. The lock's broken.
My God. He's out there.
Quick, under the bed. Hurry, come on.
Go, go. Hurry.
-You'll never fit.
-Go, go, go, go, go.
Come on. Hurry.
What are you doing?
Lars, what are you doing? Hurry.
Lars, please come on!
Lars, come on. He's coming.
Holy shit. ls that how you
escaped out of that window?
Why don't you just do that
all the time?
ls that a fat joke?
What the--?
What the hell, Jenny?
Putman, it was you?
-What? What was me?
-Step back, Putman.
Oh, you actually believe that
l'm the killer. Oh, that's a laugh.
Then what are you doing here?
Well, l just popped by to say--
You perv.
Really, there's a perfectly
reasonable explanation for all this.
You see, it seemed like
such a good final memento and--
You know how good l think
you look in red, in that--
-No!
-Oh, dear God.
Oh, good God.
-Where's the key?
-l don't know.
Lock the door!
-The lock's broken.
-Broken?
You've manacled me to my deathbed,
you Piccadilly whore.
l'm so sorry.
l could never stay mad at you, Jenny.
Quickly, give me the racket,
give me the balls.
-Go, go.
-Quickly! Run!
Get him.
Machete Phil. l knew it.
Oh, God!
Oh, God.
-Go.
-No.
-Go, dear Jen. Go.
Fuck off.
Come on.
l'm sorry.
You! l should've known it was you.
lt didn't surprise me a bit, really.
Goddamn it, Putman. Who is it?
l'm sure you think
l'll go down without a fight. . .
. . .but it's not yet game, set--
-Is he gone?
-What?
Is he gone?
Yeah, I think he's gone.
Soap, please.
Hey, nice helmet, Lars. About time you
two perverts showed up at the party.
Pour it. Pour it.
Jesus Christ, that's blood.
What the fuck?
Oh, God.
We're all gonna die!
Penelope, where's Juan?
l don't know.
l haven't seen him all night.
What the hell is going on?
-Juan. Juan.
-Hold on.
-What are you doing? Let me go!
-Don't move.
Where the hell have you been?
l was looking for Penelope.
Why you are looking at me like that?
You disappeared and now
you show up covered in blood.
Because l just found Putman.
He's dead.
Oh, shit! Sam!
-Oh, my God.
-The mud bath.
Let's go, Peney.
Oh, God.
-Oh, no.
-What?
Sam. Sam.
Sam!
Oh, fuck.
-Get out.
-What?
Get out now.
Did you know that l can hold my breath
for three minutes and 33 seconds?
-Nobody ever suspects the fun police.
-Bullshit. l always have suspected you.
-Bullshit. You did not.
-You are the bullshit!
He's the guy from the
campfire story. Machete Phil.
-The kid with no dick.
-No, that's just an old campfire story.
-What do you piss out of? Your asshole?
-That's just a story!
l have a dick.
l'm not Machete Phil.
l'm Machete Sam.
-Sam, why are you doing this?
-Oh, l remember it like it was yesterday.
l asked Rolo if he had any grass
and he said he didn't have any.
So then l followed him into the jungle.
Would you believe what l saw?
He had grass. My grass!
A huge bag of it.
And he was smoking it
with those two little hussies...
. . .even though he said he had none.
So then-- No, wait, that's not it.
l found out Pete
was giving the island to Dave.
Oh, yeah, that's it.
lt wasn't about the grass.
Although that was incredibly uncool.
It was about Pete giving
the island to that shithead!
All-night-raving, pill-popping
little son of a bitch!
What about me? l deserved it.
l'm the best damn employee
this place has ever seen.
Dave was gonna run it into the ground.
Not on my watch!
This is my home. Pete thinks l'm just
a clown. Good for fun and games.
Well, l got you guys
to do your jobs, didn't l?
Good managerial skills,
don't you think?
Setting you guys up to decipher
that stupid ''Naughty Cal'' song.
Who's the orca? Who's the octopus?
l am the walrus.
l am the walrus!
Get out of here now.
l can't hold him for long.
Try putting him to sleep.
Try the Snoring Panda.
l can't reach it. l can handle this.
He'll orgasm for another
few minutes. Go.
-l'm not leaving you.
-l'll be okay. Get out of here.
lt's gonna get messy.
Go.
-Back to the club!
-Are you crazy?
lt's the most secure building on the
island. lt's where we keep the booze.
There you are.
-Penelope!
-Juan!
Look out!
Look, he's after us.
She's safer with them. Let's go!
Let's go!
Get the gate!
Oh, God! No!
-Oh, God!
-Penelope!
-No!
-Penelope! Penelope!
Stop! God, stop it!
What are you doing?
You'll never make it!
Stop. Please.
Watch out!
Harder!
Hurry! She can't breathe!
Penelope, get up.
Juan. Juan, get up.
Juan, get up. Come on, hurry.
Come on!
Oh, God.
lt's not a party until someone
breaks the Jacuzzi.
Oh, God! Juan!
Lars!
The fun is done.
What happened to the hot tub?
Oh, God!
No!
No, it's not possible.
-What do we do?
-We can lose him in the jungle.
-The jungle?
-l can get us through.
Come on.
-Hurry!
-Go, go, go!
l know where this goes.
Let's go. Come on, quickly.
Go.
-Oh, God. This was your big plan?
-We can do it. lt's high tide.
All right, now, listen.
l know this is going
to sound disgusting. . .
. . .but when you jump, keep your legs
together and clench your ass-cheeks. . .
. . .or else water will fly up your butthole
and pulverize your intestine.
Gross.
Where are you?
l trust you, Juan.
l'm coming. l'm coming!
Jesus.
-Who is this girl?
-She's. . .
. . .my girlfriend.
-Did you see it?
-l saw it.
My asshole. What did you see?
The Randy Rumrunner.
He didn't take it. He sunk it.
Juan, any way you could get
the propeller off?
We could put it on
the Smiling Smuggler.
Consider it done, my friend.
Come on, let's go.
Juan.
ln the boat. ln the boat.
Oh, God.
Where the hell is Juan?
Juan?
-Juan?
-Juan, where are you?
-Oh, my God, you're bleeding.
-lt's okay.
-You should see the other hombre.
-l'll put it on.
Come on.
Juan.
lt's all right. lt's okay.
l cannot imagine
a more beautiful way to go.
Just remember, Penelope:
l love you.
Maybe. . .
. . .before l go. . .
. . .one kiss.
No, no, no.
l meant, maybe you. . .
. . .and Jenny could. . .
. . .kiss each other.
l always. . .
. . .wanted. . .
. . .to see that.
Oh, God.
Juan!
Go. Go, Jenny. Go.
Shit.
-Turn it.
-Why? What are you doing?
Trust me.
-Lars!
-Come on, come on.
Yeah.
-You're bringing us closer to the raft.
-l know.
Yeah.
-Slowly, slowly.
-Okay.
We gotta untie these lines.
Hit it, Jenny. Go.
Yeah.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Oh, come on.
Die!
Son of a bitch.
They'll kick me out
of the Pacifist Club now.
Or at least ask you nicely to leave.
Tian-Tu.
The Heaven Point.
Let's go, Penelope.
Gracias, sheriff.
-Cut it.
-That is so wack.
Knock that shit off, Juan.
You gonna cause a hysterical thing.
Fuck.
That is so cheeba.
-l just lost it. Keep rolling.
-That is some trick shit.
That is so on time.
Off the hook.
Tight. And heavy.
That is so out of the planet.
What other dumb fucking
catch phrases can l say?
Man, l can't hear shit.
l've been standing
next to amplifiers my whole life.
Oh, God, no.
Kind of scared me.
''Tokey took them
to a seahorse whorehouse. ''
Which something. . . .
Which seemed to suggest. . . .
Fuck, l don't know.
Let me try that again.
Here we go. l'll do. . . .
Okay, ready? And action.
But what about the sign on Cliff's neck?
lt said ''Staff only. ''
l mean, that clearly means--
All right, well, tell us, then.
How the hell are we
supposed to do our jobs. . .
. . .when somebody's killing
the dick out of everybody?
Yes.
Hey, listen--
Listen, sugar britches. . . .
-All right.
-Are we cutting?
-Are you good?
-No, l'm not good.
-Okay, cut it. Cut.
Subtitles by
SDl Media Group
[ENGLlSH]
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org