Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
translation by Abdullah Horani
University
New text message
Look what you're missing!
It is crazy here!
Friend ... I have an idea, save
this and publish it in the newspaper.
Hey, Mom, Gina and I are going to go
to see what the university today.
Oh dear, I forgot completely.
Can we do the
next weekend?
I have to go to town
tomorrow night for dinner.
Oh, god, are now seven!
We can not, we have to do now.
Good morning, ma'am.
Oh, man, I'm in the post 23.
She was in the first place.
Hey, can not, what is it friend?
How about gentita?
Hummer, that does not know either.
Oh, kev, can I ask you a question?
Have you read what we
left on the mice?
You mean the
mice and men?
Bingo, that same.
So, let's see if we understand each other,
These two types, are going to be a
woods together, to find rabbits.
I am not an expert but,
They are not, a kind of ...
¿G-A-Y?
Dude, I do not think
're understanding anything.
We can not spell.
Yes, we understand all silly.
Hey, are no longer a girl, did you see?
Well, come on guys. This
and this is yours is yours.
Fast.
Oh, yes.
Goodbye girls.
See what it is charging?
What would you do with them?
Hello mill.
Hi guys.
Morris Hey, what are you going to
I do with all those books?
They are for college, my parents
patearan me in the ass if we do not take it.
Morris, your parents always
you kicking ass.
Did not want to do other
Things here at school?
Let him know what he does.
I already made my choice can not.
Kevin already knew, huh kev?
Yes.
Hey, you grab your
things for school today?
Oh, yes, yes, they are in my ...
If this technique is
charming but llévalos you.
Oh, by the way, but it is fácii
not in a way that is easy for you.
You want to see what's
for this weekend?
Hello!
Hello gina.
I need to talk to his friend outside.
Alone.
Well!
¿Then the taste?
Yes, that's exactly
what am I going to do.
Oh, cool, are going to have fun
Depraved
Bye then we'll see.
See you later idiot.
Have a good weekend.
¿Miami?
When travel there?
Two months ago.
What's our
plans to be together
And the tour to campus
this weekend
Just go without me.
Look.
It is the last year
This is very exciting ...
I want a feast
And I want to have fun
And you ... you are not a lot of fun.
So what? Just do not take much?
But even so we spent well.
As our nights of Friday.
They seem boring.
Do our camping trips
in the schools were together?
Studying together as nerds.
Diego.
Gina ...
In the first year was one thing.
But this is me going crazy.
Supposedly we should
fun, y. ..
You ... You're a loser!
Kevin was completed
The university is just around the
corner and I can not ruin my last year.
This is mine.
Okay, let's see if we understand each other,
Did not you sucked?
No.
Did not you hear me? She left me.
I was abandoned once.
Morris you're a damn
liar, he never had a girlfriend.
Can not shut up, sure that I had.
Remember kev? I was introduced to one.
It was real, we went to
Camp physical together.
Sure it was a freak.
Come on, are you mind?
We have a situation here.
I'm going to do now,
it had everything planned.
Going to college together, married,
have a couple of children, a girl, a boy.
Friend,
That garbage you tell gina?
I leave you with good reason,
you're an idiot.
What friends!
How about fletcher!
Something happens here.
Gina left.
It is in a crisis.
Oh, great.
Huh, huh guys want
go out this weekend?
I do not want to re-emerge.
Oh, that's very bad. I went to visit
Last week my brother,
I wanted to stay.
As you even want to stay,
is the university.
if it is only the university,
is what I thought.
So I went.
And I say at this moment is kids
they are damn few friends Stooges,
It is retarded.
Why? What happened?
You want to know?
When I went.
Not slept for three days
And not that I have
run out of money
Take the card from my parents
is supposed to be for emergencies.
I lost my cell phone that
Reality is my dad.
And the credit card.
But is it that I was doing.
I drugs, driving drunk.
I got blondes.
Brunettes.
I came in my pants,
But do not tell anyone.
I am ashamed of that.
Two girls and me.
With tongue with tongue.
With snacks.
I became a little
tattoo back down
We do not know, it's like
a unicorn murderer.
She looks great.
I fell in love.
Do you content that I slept with someone?
Three times, with different girls.
It was the best order
damn week of my life.
Hey, they should go.
Because we can not have a purpose
weekends as well as the fetcher.
Oh, not to speak
We do not even know if we
was telling the truth.
But we can find out.
The madness, parties, sex.
Everything sounds incredible
It might make me a tattoo
Are you kidding are not they?
If that was good.
The festivities, the drink, sex.
If, morris I'm not kidding.
Perhaps it is gina
reason, I am not funny.
Learning to be fun
is what I need
Have a crazy weekend for
gina is back with a very bad idea.
Oh ... very good
idea. We have to.
Bitch!
They know that I leave, can also
have a weekend more fun.
Yes!
I am so ...
This is definitely
better than in the brochure.
I have a good feeling about this.
Presentiento good, that good feeling
How we're going to have sex?
Because I also have this
feeling and I love it.
I do not know friend perhaps everything.
Let's have fun.
That's my good friend
Here said that the tour to
campus is at 1230 tomorrow
And there will be a warm welcome.
Before the dinner.
Enough, no more
It is the agenda for the weekend!
No more hours now
in college now
You know what that means?
Without parents, free beer
And could not be better than that.
Except ... low speed
Hey, how are you ladies going to class?
No, we are only
these books to a party.
Oh, well, they are going to read, huh?
Hallucinatory
Well, look, let's
stay this weekend
And wanted to know if we
wanted to teach the city.
What college come from?
No, not at the university,
in fact we are in high school ...
Fucking idiot.
We are first-year students.
Jódanse!
Oh, well, then I see the girls.
Hey, nice short.
I'll give you $ 5.
Fornico you and I let you clean my room.
I promise you will not regret.
These rooms are
a garbage stink.
Do not understand is
fourths of students.
look
Are you sure everything
this family legacy?
If my parents met here.
Guys I do not feel
so bad about this.
What?
I'm morris
I am kevin
We are the students of 1st year
Supposedly we are going to be
in your room this weekend.
Oh, right.
Look guys, I'm going to need as
20 or 30 minutes to finish here, okay?
So, come back later.
Oh, it seems that you are exercising.
Oh, yes, that exercising with your ...
It's disgusting.
Anybody can tell me
we are doing?
Relax, it is around here.
I think
I am not perfect these houses
all look alike to me.
Maybe we should go back
and touch the door again.
Shut your mouth.
Well, that would be good to do.
crap
These babies.
Psyche is good.
Hi guys.
How are university?
I'm morris
Hello morris
The smoke of good
Come might find something.
Anyway, it only seemed
Nicely your name.
Jesus.
Good shot.
Good marksmanship.
Cagonas news, guys.
We have been denied promotion.
crap
I think they want to do the hard.
When you get used.
This slave no longer serves us.
It's the shit friends
In order for this university then
What?
Yes, I did not think it would come so quickly.
He can not graduate
You are strong, an institution
I know, I'm afraid of graduating
Apparently not tubiera no talent
That is not true and you know it.
You're good for many things
tell what is good
You're good at ...
TOXIC things
It is the largest in the house
No one does that
is a true gift
Thanks guys
I feel much better
Revealing this here
This is the big house?
Loaded graves or what?
miprimo is here
- Oh yeah? Who is your cousin?
- Toby scott
Quiff you mean?
What?
What is that?
A queer pedorro
It is his nickname was what won the
I hope you find
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
We are in high school, only
we want to go to the party, you know.
Oh, you are children of secondary school?
Go through the door
saw what he did?
- Who is quif toby?
What these guys want?
Some high school boys, they want to stay in order to be
One was the cousin of Quiff do you remember?
That is a fool, remember that to your tongue?
A loser
Are you looking for a party, huh?
Perhaps we should
mostrales where to stay.
Really?
Might do with some college?
Enough!
Shut the fuck up!
These kids, what are their names?
I am kevin and they are morris and can not.
I'm guys are our
Guests this weekend.
Supposedly we have
to stay in ...
But ... our colleague
roommate is ... busy
Already wine
DIJ that perhaps we could talk?
Relax big boy did not want to do
Sorry
he's a little violent
How about showing where to go Siles
to be to keep their stuff?
Feast, feast, feast, feast, feast!
We call this the dining room
Mind the step!
yes, this place stinks like shit.
Remember that allow us to stay
As I said
the rooms are occupied tonight
We feel very badly to be up here
Is that a rat?
No, it was only a shadow.
Oh guys, do not worry, we're going to bring
to the best party this weekend.
In fact I think landes are going to have a party tonight
We love the laders
admire the
Cool
then you'll love
What the fuck is wrong?
- Are you talking about?
No man alone convert
well. Shut the fuck up.
good guys. clever.
It is time for the party.
Let's review.
Condoms ¿?
well.
¿Pads for breath?
¿Bowls?
No jokes, that's disgusting.
Bótalo.
So, are you sure about this?
Relax friend, is a feast for friends.
No?
What? We are here to
know the university, is not it?
Hey, all right kevin. Is
good to hear you say that.
That is, to move
a good time, a good time.
Okay guys, get ready.
This is going to be amazing.
Hey guys, come and
begin to remove their clothes.
Oh, here we go, ladies ...
There are no women here, no?
yes, I think we were deceived.
Hey, look at that. These two
are doing there.
What kind of holiday is this?
Here come the big
Bright kids!
What is that?
Why are we sent to that party?
It seems gay?
I think that farmers would have
left would have been fun.
That was not funny can not.
look, is miprimo
off this weekend.
Perhaps it is doing on purpose.
Do not worry, that's not
was miorina or something.
It was only that of him.
Will went well in the party?
They cited some ¿?
Listen guys, that was not fun.
What is this tone
voice, high school boys!
welcome to college kids.
Enjoy.
Oh shit, this is crazy.
No friend, this is the
damn university.
I RINTING with this place!
Let's go.
Hey, hey. Here are friends.
We were shit
by what they did.
Yes, we believe that you are great.
Yes, it was only a joke,
we did not want to treat them well.
Let's do something for you.
We're going to do some
shots in the body,
And we would love if you
guys are with us.
Oh, sure it does.
Oh really I think
that I am not going to like it.
Yes, I too think that way.
Oh, silly and stupid.
Just do it man, it will be fun.
Okay, you know what?
Fuck, I'm inside.
The bottle.
This is amazing!
Then,
And look.
Who is this guy?
Just in case you need it.
You guys are going to love this.
Where were the girls?
Fortunately the girls
went home early.
Y. .. Where is the girl
of shots into the body?
Good question, mike.
Morris.
Our friend has a lot
taking pleasure in his place.
Lord!
Okay guys, come here.
Where creeen going?
Yes, I thought you were great.
I thought they wanted to have fun.
I think we were wrong.
Returning to his room, ladies.
I think now it is
is putting fun.
Yes, all that tequila is encouraging me.
I think we have to record this.
Hand me that the son of a bitch.
Fílmame.
Very good.
look at this.
Bebe.
sorry, what?
I mean you go, baby.
Oh, yeah, well simuy
So when is your turn?
When you lose it.
Are you having fun?
What?
What do you think, leave this game,
and came to my room?
Yes, I think that step.
Imbécii that.
Do not stand.
Well, where were we?
Who wants a balloon?
Can you please give me a?
Well, well, it takes
dear, this is for you.
This balloon is for you, take a balloon.
How are you?
I have a balloon.
This balloon is for you, have fun.
No.
you have to sustain it,
mad at women.
As to her.
Use the globe
Did not want to go back?
Want to go to the garden or somewhere?
For god.
Are you serious?
I have not heard anything like this since high school.
See you later.
got boobs flat.
You mportaria ...
What?
if, as no ...
As you like.
sitodo the glass as you like.
I have more luck than Bill Gates.
Excuse me, Excuse me.
How beautiful these?
sorry, let me pass.
sorry, please.
This is great.
Wait
Someone comes.
This can not be happening.
Are you sure this is right?
All right.
Relax.
Everyone is down.
I'm never nervous
I've been with a girl.
Okay, I will be gentii.
It was perhaps think that
I'm very drunk.
- But I am ready for this.
- What?
For another ...
Sorry
Your hand is in my pants.
I know, easy.
Cool.
god.
You are very good.
Your hands, I mean ...
Are great.
Usually I run it myself.
But this is better.
Besides I do not have to
worry about ... MIMAM that ...
Among y. ..
Helen.
Hello.
Damn.
I was so close.
crap.
Guys.
Corran.
Why the rush.
Aunqe do not think ever
I Heho with a woman.
Do not tell me the speed for nothing.
Got it?
if, as I got it.
Cool.
I did not know you were so crisp.
if
Kiss me please.
Kiss me.
Do it.
What was that?
- Do not heard anything.
- Are you sure?
- If, just calm down.
What the fuck you know about that?
Y. ..
Not that means but ...
Amy said that under the bed.
Your friend can not.
- Should I worry?
- If tenlo by insurance.
Why did not say that
was above the bed.
That's a good question.
Y. ..
Had a discussion?
if sisomos first-year students.
And what to study?
Photography.
Really?
I love photography.
I'm bad about that but ...
I heard it here
have a good program.
if it is supposed to be the best in the pa s.
Maybe I could some
lessons some day.
if, of course.
That was very horny.
Please tell me that we will continue.
Come here.
What ...
Who is this movie?
And we arrived.
We arrived.
You are different from
other university.
nisiquiera I feel like one of them.
If I can attest to that.
But it's a good thing.
Maybe we will see soon.
if.
I hope so.
Okay, bye.
god, what happens?
What do you want?
Morris.
Wake cute sleeper.
crap.
Do ...
if, all night.
I'm back baby.
I can not believe it.
Hi dad.
Dad.
What are you doing here?
Morris missed the interview.
Cagaste the scholarship.
Everything.
crap.
The interview.
Well it seems that the
Mr Hooper is not coming.
Thank God.
Who are still here.
Sorry for being late.
After the mine this bronze statue.
Hero of the general w. S fielmod
Became a
Secrets of the eavesdroppers.
arljam is finished
my parents no longer support me.
nisiquiera me dicuenta.
Did not you noticed?
Micara did you see?
if this joke was great.
As a baby, say goodbye to that scholarship.
It goes on with your life.
Where the hell is kevin
It should be here,
is the tour to the campus.
Should have had something last night.
Or dead.
Do not you think that something bad
he has gone right?
It is the university that can happen here
You look good
More belludo what I thought.
beautiful, beautiful.
if this is embarrassing, sinisiquiera
I micarne of DENTIFICATION
Who did this?
Those of another group.
¿Micarro truth about this?
- Why do not we go home?
- We 're not going anywhere
- Not yet.
- Why not?
What are you trying to prove?
Do not try to prove anything.
I try to have fun.
That is, I love the new kevin.
Pasandola Are they right?
Return to your home.
It could have been worse.
That may be worse to spend the whole
night tethered to a naked statue.
Look for super gina.
Super boobs
Do not worry about messages
nisiquiera that submission.
They know that ...
MOUNT I have no other concerns.
Really?
In that case, let
a feast for kevin.
Leave it.
Come morris preocuaparte both stops.
Maybe it is the best.
As you can tell who is the best.
Why siestuvieras at home,
know exactly what happen.
situs parents you would have broken the
shit ass for the interview.
Now you will have the opportunity to talk
with the principal and explain what happened
You think that to work?
It is worth trying.
What have you got to lose?
You could do that
china you masturbate more.
I think definitely
volveras to see that.
By the way ...
... I think I soiled much last night.
They are more collegial
hard of what I thought.
have balls Citadines.
sons of a bitch.
It is a charity.
And we have very good service.
Does Ganial naked?
this is not good foxes
it is time to socialize.
I think you better go.
if, perhaps having more
Fortunately sicompran beers.
What is that?
A bar, go to bars right?
¿Bars? sitodo time.
- Every day.
I am always in bars.
Just make sure you bring this kid
Is this guy?
Me?
Yes, you.
I ca ste well.
Me?
See you guys.
I was thinking that maybe ...
We could continue what last night.
Maybe, just about
find a better place.
God save beautiful boobs.
yes, yes.
The vere at one and ten.
I love your tits.
Worth as $ 9000.
Seriously.
As they are friends.
Kevin sees you as well last night.
if your partner also.
I suppose that you painted micarro.
So it will be companions?
It was just a button.
- Have a job yet.
- What kind of work?
It is not the big thing.
We just need to clean up
the house for a feast.
Maybe wash micarro, you know
as I like to have it clean.
Where do I put the keys?
hell, no.
Do I hear some hostility?
Are you serious?
Not believing that living here was free.
Do not clean your
house, no way.
Well, maybe you like your love
know who are still in high school.
Will not know unless you tell.
Well, but clean the house,
maybe it has DIOT.
A working guys.
Tomas keys.
Kevin.
Kevin
Dont waste your time with it.
Not believing that you're the only one.
Or do we?
You are a fucking sick.
Do we have to clean?
I think this weekend
we have to take advantage of it.
It's very funny.
That I spent the whole day
and cleaning up your mess and get everything.
To me that ruin everything.
I love this, you are so DIOT.
Get out of here.
No hiss is a good village.
Come on, is your scholarship is not it?
Come
Come on, you can do.
I trust you.
Lucky brother.
- It is a DIOT.
- Absolutely.
Time running.
Just say that this morning is
Very shocked.
We did not know that
meant those words.
I searched on the Internet.
But I guess that's what happens ...
When you decide to stay in
fraternity house
Instead of the bedroom
we attach.
I know sir.
It was a bad choice.
sidependiera me.
Botaria to each member of the
fraternity of the university.
Know that these animals.
Smelled of the drug balloons
just to get tough.
Really?
It's horrible.
Mr Hooper.
There is no doubt that it is an academic genius.
But the scholarship that we give here.
It is much more than that.
Lord and me.
mifamilia has a large
history at this university.
I would like to continue that legacy.
boy, I think you're going to
having to prove that.
Mr Hooper.
You and your scholarship is
hanging by a thread.
You are so DIOT
Where have you been it's time to leave
Relax, relax.
I have been on the internet.
They are the dentifer.
That is mimuchacho.
Great, what do you pass mill?
What happens?
As questions that kevin
You forget how it feels?
You understand.
What are we going to do?
I want to go from here.
There's nothing you can do tonight.
So let's have fun, take.
nisiquiera looks like me.
dam you're not photogenic.
It's worth it.
You are so ugly.
Ugly, you will feel better.
Lecuisa.
Do you really think I
lecuisa call you drink?
You know what, 10 U.S. dollars entry.
crap.
No money is not based on the monkey.
Let the babies go to.
What was that, not the check.
saw the size of that.
No.
Hombrezote.
Crammed not want.
I said no.
As it is not smooth.
We do not have very good
this weekend.
We're not inside.
Do they think that well when we
we are in college?
Who knows.
Maybe we are not together.
That I know.
You look like a baby that
please do not you shut up.
It is true.
Think of this.
It was over.
Last year of college.
is right, it was over.
One more reason to take advantage
that we are here.
Rather than sit here, let's go.
Where are you going?
To think where we have a
Feast of the fraternity.
And the girls?
Get up Morris.
Esperenme.
You look like a turtle.
Where is michompa?
Want to climb?
What do these children here.
There is.
I want you to know ladies
some very special guests.
Hi guys.
Hello.
Me?
- Hello.
- It is up to a year.
And you are ... which TAPO with feathers.
Are great.
Where we were
Where we were, where we were.
if, indeed, ladies.
These guys are
nice enough.
And paid for all this.
Is that what you did
with our money?
¿Paid this party?
Things are expensive companion.
Look around you.
We have no money or
in for our wallets.
- Yes.
- If
What about that?
Fortunately remained.
I believe it will have an emergency.
That we would like
We have good folks.
Especially.
Hi troy.
Why did you hit me?
Shut up bitch.
What is wrong with that.
It was that kind of village. I like psyche.
Buenos we have to go
to continue socializing.
Have fun.
Nenas.
I'm so horny.
Did you see the size of that?
Basically it is our party.
if, as I see it agree.
I think so.
I do not know.
Come on, siya pay for it
we must enjoy it less.
That is mimuchacho.
Come on.
Esperenme.
Have you ever done this?
But it is not fun, is it not?
- If
Very funny, all right.
Go get a ticket.
I do not want to send more messages.
He changed his mind
Kevin please.
What's going on?
You do not have to do this.
if, and you should
try once a year.
Marica
Me? No, it's bad village.
I had a lot.
You know what, I think I will go to search
Without something to drink alcohol.
There must be something in the frigider.
We love you, but you better watch.
- Well,
- Let's do this.
Be careful with friends.
Bitches to talk, bitches speaking.
Is there alcohol there?
In the punch?
No, nothing like that.
It is a drink alcohol.
Know your new neighborhood.
Really?
The girls will bother you.
After that abandon.
but I think ...
Make a toast.
Can you give me a little punch?
The first thirsty.
Other driver murderer.
That's very good.
sirvete compañero.
You look thirsty.
Thank you
Listen.
sialguien, quien sea, te molesta...
Buscame.
You cover ahead.
Did not you mean back?
¿siquieres por ahí?
Do not miss the pants.
Sal de mipiso.
Hello.
I know you.
I'm glad they have been.
Let me ask a few beers.
No thanks
sibuscan a alguien no se preocupen.
Is a loser.
Do you really are you so jealous?
Give thanks to God that you are alive.
I want to take, I want a little.
That's right.
- Hey.
- Go to hell.
sicomo no.
Es tu carne de ¡dentidad.
mierda
- mira.
- Ladies
Heather how are precious?
We went to look.
We were like two hours ago
si, sin ropa
Go baby
You know I will never leave you
Especially with that of lesbianism
Such things as stink
We do not need this guys
You have boobs
And with these things as gold
You know what we are going to do?
Let us reward ok?
You do not want beer?
I think these funny
I will reward
Latest start
I will bring these beers
Let's bring them go!
Where this mark?
Go back to pelees
man as the son of a bitch!
Nice to see you
What 's wrong quítate
Qué dij¡ste?
Passing your brain
is so small that ...
Es ¡mposible
No seas ¡mbécii y danos una cerveza
Oh, asique quieres unas
beers for her girls?
Saben que hn hecho mucha
shit these past few days
You deserve these beers
In fact ... wait
Hey guys and high Listen to me!
Van'll love this
They see these kids here?
These kids are coming
They are high school kids
Come on, ever too
Collegiate went well
No way!
No!
silencio!
These guys are cool
They are good guys
They want a beer and have a good time
Aquiesta
Its beer
What the fuck!
What are you doing?
What?
Nadie le habla asia el
It is something that will never understand
Do not be a bitch
Jodamos now!
Wait!
Stay away
That is not true
Puedes ba¡lar
What the fuck you doing?
Lord
The person you want to talk
Oh my God!
This impasse
At least we got
beer 300 people
The jodimos not?
Joderla? We lacked Solo with his father
Ed where are you going?
I will come to apologize?
Wait! Esa es miparte favorita!
You see that is funny
Put her again
That seems funny to you?
Sure
Stop being queer
si
They are still schoolchildren around here
I only say
Not happening
What?
I can talk for a minute?
Want to tell more lies?
No thanks
Wait!
I am leaving tomorrow
I thought you were different
But you're like the rest
Have a nice trip
That was ugly
No vas habalrle otra vez?
Probably not
You may this sad for all of us
The only thing I wanted was a
college is much to ask?
Let me
You are worthless
sin valor
These are just a few Collegiate
Collegiate fools!
I can not believe that we are here
Opediendo nuestro tiempo con ustedes
Wasting our damn time!
That fed me repeat
Sorry
What a stupid
Give me a hug
Go and stand over there
And do something
No, I will stay with these jerk
We have some beer
So it's time
Indeed ever
saw a pig before?
Now if
That happens by bitches
mierda! Run!
Suigan corriendo malditos enfermos!
Sick
I can not resist
I never thought to say but
we are next to the school
Kevin what?
Forget anything
sitienes algo que decirlo dilo
Ok want to hear
These filler shit!
I'm that?
- siempre hablas de un jodido juego
Breaking news!
nisiquiera se acostado
As que asiva a ser no kevin?
Bone still hopes that a virgin?
This is great
Whatever shut up!
Stop by the end dammit
de semana que nos traj¡ste
You hear so much for this
Claro, porque fue midea
equivocan'te y poner velas
That left just you
Guys, we're going to stop fighting
You are not a part of this
I am not part of this?
It is assumed that was our weekend
Whatever I did not want to say that
Aquitienen otra
mibeca es mejor que ustedes
Casime olvide de esta
Casino se siobtendré
mibeca de universidad
Since I got everything
Whatever you want your scholarship was
You are an agreed
It's not what I want
know how my parents are
Why do not you wear your
ball and you defend
No es fácii
What's next? Will tell you what job to take?
Or you be?
And leave it!
You know you want more than anything
It is not something that you know shit
Sabes que mors jódete!
It's the last time you defend
Also for your Jodete
bring your shit with us
Ok well continue walking down sisolos
Kevin Fuck you!
Why not drive big
It is the first time that you use?
dile a tus padres que
mierda!
Look nice
Thank you
sigracias
About d elo happened
Already there estube
- Déjame explican'te
Actually I do not want to hear it kevin
Is not who you are
To be honest I was neither
Such a time is what you discover
Colegial o universitario no me ¡mporta
What is so stupid
vine aquintentando cambiar quien era
Because not only was part of this
I thought you were brilliant
Why you want to change it?
Not
Do not know?
Is who I am or what I knew
Occasionally he was responsible
In truth ruin this weekend
Now both are
and also angry with me
You look like the kind of
people who do not make a mistake
A couple of weeks ago
Hold
I slept with ten
It was a mistake
sipuedes decirme
Why not tell everything
Why did
Ie as a kid like jess
For all the wrong reasons
Still looking
He made me feel special
And as good liar
He made me believe something that was
rather than something one night
si
It's like tonight
I learned that the liars and
And I thought you were dumb
mira no soy nada como ese tipo
siento todo esto
Kevin is the real one who speaks?
Or is the improved
kevin speaking university?
This is the real me
Stressed, responsible, collegial
well
disculpa aceptada entonces
bien tengo que irme y
to find guys
Before you go
I can give you some clothes please?
Morris wakes
Kevin?
Where is Carl?
Ok chicos estuve pensando toda la noche
I wanted to say sorry
For all
That was a thing of marc
- What is
Halle mucho de mi
este fin de semana
And you guys
I did not mean what I said
Until you told me gina
que tal vez estaba mal
You are my best friends
We will not allow a
This weekend ends
Either way is fine
Before anyone kevin
Thanks carl
Morris?
sin culpas
They overcame
siento haberme asustado
Hey guys that's very gay!
This is what we have more gay
Indeed the weekend
Let us give a hand
Entocnes estamos bien?
si
- Claro
Ok, there are a lot of
girls what we do here?
Go find yourself
They are all our stuff?
si, han sacado todo
Those damn yankees
si
We're going home now?
- No
Still no
What the fuck did?
I was already clear that
not belong here
Come on guys have to fight for you
We need to go home
After all no
podemos irnos aside simple
I can not do it alone
bien después de todo nos acostaremos no?
Come Morse can not do without you
Come put balls in your face
Ok guys
Vomiting in the order of the Dean
Estubiste desnudo y
fucking thing all week
True, the boys of Brotherhood
siquieres pararte frente a tus padres
Por qué no lo haces aquiprimero?
To topple the son of a bitch
mierda
3,2,1 ...
Insurance will work?
Trust me
It is natural
What the fuck?
What is it?
That you see the wick was extinguished
mierda!
What the fuck
Oh shit
What the fuck is happening here?
Jodeme
Damn
What the fuck?
It's beer
Hey girls
It seems better to quit
have fire next door or something
Accursed
sigue amigo
Wait
I'm going to die we
What is happening now!
disturbando la paz
destroying property
Stealing animals
What the hell is this? We are not
These were cursed alli
Oficial nisiquiera venimos aqui
We are only a handful of college
Frankly I am ashamed
their behavior
hijos de puta!
Relax friend got something on your nipple
Wait!
Dónde esta miauto?
Dónde esta mimaldito auto?
So you go to college?
si, sólo vine para tener
one week you
But we thought you were a university
Really? Thank you
And I guess that's it uh?
Therefore need not be
Stronger
Take tiger
I guess that ...
And again next year?
After this week
I think I did
Además tengo novia asique
A yes?
Who is it?
Someone who knew
It's pretty clear
So I guess that
there will be a photo session
That's all
I think we arrived at the track
Grab this
Ok guys go home
Here come the problems
Hey kevin
Gina
I get your message on video
It seems that tubieron
a crazy weekend
Sure!
We leave in peace
Anyway
I thought a lot about you and me
In us
I would think that the break never happened
Well
I do not think so
What?
I have advanced
Move on?
We have not seen in three days
Many things happen in three days
Gina that guy you saw
I was not
See you
And good breasts
Kevin hopes
Is seriously
And what will make next weekend?
Next week? Not
punished the next 6 months?
Forget it
I can sneak
You know you talk a lot about you
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org