Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Between the years when the oceans
drank Atlantis...
...and the rise
of the Sons of Aryus...
... there was an age undreamed of...
...when shining kingdoms
lay spread across the world.
Hither came Conan,
the Cimmerian, sword in hand.
It is I, his chronicler,
who knows well his saga.
Now, let me tell you
of the days of high adventure.
-We angered the merchant.
-You're surprised?
-We didn't steal all he had.
-We didn't have time.
Why aren't they killing us?
Maybe they want to capture us
and torture us to death.
Conan, help!
-Do you know who l am?
-Taramis.
-Queen Taramis.
-Not my queen.
You have a queen?
But you are a Cimmerian.
Cimmerians have no rulers.
You're a barbarian. You live free.
You owe allegiance to no one.
ls that not so?
lt is and it always will be.
-What do you want?
-l need your help.
-No!
-No?
-You don't know what l'd give you.
-You have nothing that l want.
You were praying, Conan.
What were you praying for?
Look at the shrine.
See what you were praying for.
What is there, Conan?
Think.
Show me the desire
in your deepest heart.
Valeria.
Where is this Valeria?
-With Crom.
-Your god?
She sits by the side of my god.
What l want, you cannot give me.
Yes, l can.
-You can bring back the dead?
-Do as l ask of you...
...and l will.
Wake.
And remember.
Tell me what l must do.
Soon.
-Conan!
-Look!
Doesn't that animal look familiar?
l think it does. l'm sorry about
what happened the last time.
They love us.
We will drink to Dagoth...
...the Dreaming God.
-What do you want me to do?
-To bring back the woman you love?
Yes.
lt is written
in the Scrolls of Skelos...
...that a girl born with a mark
must make a perilous journey.
lt is her destiny.
My niece, Jehnna, has such a mark.
-You will take her on that journey.
-To where?
Jehnna will show you.
Ever since she was born
she's been prepared for this.
There is a key she must find,
a key only she can touch...
...as it was written
in the Scrolls of Skelos.
-Where is it?
-ln a castle.
-Guarded?
-By a wizard called Toth-Amon.
-By a wizard?
-That frightens you.
You're afraid of magic.
And you will have to deal with it.
What good is a sword against sorcery?
-Then you're afraid to go?
-No. l will find a way.
What does this key unlock?
A treasure.
A jeweled horn.
Only she can procure it.
Only she can lead you to it.
And when she has it,
you'll bring her back to me.
Then you will have your reward.
We shall both have everything we want.
Through magic.
lt's all right. Don't be afraid.
-lt's only a dream. Only a dream.
-No, l saw--
-A dream. lt was only a dream.
-l saw--
-Be still. Lie down.
-l saw it!
-No--
-l saw it again!
-You saw nothing! A nightmare.
-l did! l did!
-Go back to sleep.
-l saw it again.
l saw it! l did, l saw it.
Tomorrow, you start your journey.
You need all your strength.
Your destiny's at hand.
Now, sleep.
Sleep.
All our destinies are at hand.
Even Conan's. He doesn't know it.
We don't need him.
l don't need the captain of the guard
to steal a key. l need a thief.
What you need to do
is make sure this dear child...
...returns safely to the palace...
...with both the treasure
and her virginity intact.
l will protect them both.
You better, my friend...
...for she must be a virgin when she's
returned to be properly sacrificed.
One other thing, Bombaata.
We can't have the King of Thieves
near the treasure.
So when the key is
in my niece's hand, kill Conan.
Have the Elite Guard follow.
They will help you.
Conan must die.
Do you think he's handsome?
Very ugly.
No, not him. Conan.
-Can't you judge for yourself?
-But how can l?
How many times have l seen a man?
A real man.
All l've seen is you.
Meaning no insult to you, Bombaata.
Yes, he is handsome.
Conan, wait! We must go this way.
-Not yet.
-But you have to obey me.
Weren't you told?
There are rules to every game.
But there's magic in this game.
l'll have to fight it with magic.
Akiro.
-What are they going to do?
-Have lunch.
Those savages would
have a terrible stomach ache.
Why would they eat someone
so old and sour as you?
They thought if they ate me,
my magic would be in their blood.
At least they could've
washed you first.
l need you.
l'm yours.
-Tell me more about this key.
-Oh, it's not an ordinary key.
-lt's a jewel.
-A jewel?
Yes. The Heart of Ahriman.
Well, can it be worn?
Only by me. No one else dare touch it.
lf there is anything you like here,
try not to take it.
l know when to steal and when not to.
-Get her. Get her!
-What did she do?
She came with the bandits.
The others are dead. Now it's
her turn. After we have our fun.
Don't kill her too soon.
Save her!
Thieves should be hanged.
Conan, there are six
of them against her.
One, two, three....
l think you're right.
And she's tied to the stake!
Do something!
Stop!
-l think we made a friend.
-Wait here.
What do you want?
-To come with you.
-Be off!
Let me speak to Conan.
l said, be off!
Stop!
Leave.
l swear that if Conan let me ride
with him, l will give my life for him.
We shall see.
The castle of Toth-Amon.
lt holds the key.
Come bring her, Conan.
-We leave now.
-ln the morning.
-l'm the leader.
-Lead in the morning. lt'll be better.
-We must rest.
-My thinking exactly.
Sleep.
ln the morning you'll touch
The Heart of Ahriman.
The first to do so
in 1 000 years.
Look!
Jehnna?
Akiro, where is she?
ln there!
-Who took her?
-A giant bird. A bird of smoke.
lnto the boat!
-Somebody should watch the horses.
-Malak!
l didn't mean me!
l'm rowing!
Too late, my friends.
But come.
Come anyway.
How do we get in?
ls there another entrance?
Under here is a way in.
You mean under the water?
You can stay here if you like.
Alone?
They need me!
-Be careful.
-Oh, hold on!
Bombaata.
Wizard it open.
Fine magician you are.
Go back to juggling apples.
Get up! Get him!
That's exactly what l'd have done.
There are two left, Wizard,
and you're behind one of them.
Which one?
-No! Not here!
-Not this one!
l need you!
lt's all right.
Crom!
Out! Out of here!
Hurry! Hurry!
All an illusion.
Help!
Bombaata! Help me!
Bombaata, where are you?
Put me down! Do you hear me?
Put me down!
Look out, you fool!
Bombaata, stop!
Why?
l thought you were going to hurt her.
This is one of the queen's guards.
-Why did they attack us?
-Not by her order.
Wait, wait. This is much better.
Akiro's own magic mixture.
Let me help you.
-What do you think you're doing?
-Covering your wound.
My wound is lower.
We don't want an infection to spread.
l'll spread your head open.
This is what the world has come to.
You try to help somebody...
...and what do you get
instead of thanks?
Threats.
Now yell if it hurts.
l suppose nothing hurts you.
Only pain.
After we return to Shadizar...
...what will you do?
l'll find my kingdom
and a queen to sit beside me.
What kingdom?
The promise l was kingdomed.
The kingdom l was promised.
What queen?
Valeria.
What is she like, this Valeria?
Do you see this woman over there?
-Zula?
-Valeria is like her.
She doesn't look like her...
...but she has the same spirit.
The same....
Strengths?
Strength.
And she's a warrior too?
A great warrior.
A great woman.
Could there ever be...
...anyone else but her?
Another queen?
Lot on your knife.
Not on your life.
Excuse me.
l must get up now.
How do you feel?
Welcome.
You are welcome.
l didn't know women could be warriors.
All my tribe are warriors.
lt seems that men like women warriors.
Some.
Think l could ever be one?
l could teach you how to use this.
Please.
Now, the power is in the wrists.
Oh, l see.
-Like this?
-That's right.
They've got to stay loose.
lt takes practice and strength.
Wait!
Hold on.
lf you're gonna learn to fight,
then learn with a real weapon.
Not with a toothpick.
Here, l'll show you.
Stand like this.
You do it. Try it.
And then swing it over your head.
l'll help you. Swing over your head.
Good.
Now you're ready to take on anybody.
How do you attract a man?
What l mean is...
...suppose you set your heart
on somebody.
-What would you do to get him?
-Grab him.
And take him!
You'd grab him and take him?
Take him!
Like that!
-What did she mean?
-What did she say?
Well, she said
that if she wanted a man...
...she'd reach out and take him.
Good idea.
But then what?
l mean, you've got him.
What do you do with him?
That's easy. You see, you just--
You....
You see, in order for a man
to really know a woman...
...and for her to know him,
they have to....
They have to join.
Join?
Get together.
He has to take his...
...incredible by the--
There you are, joined.
l mean, how do you think flowers grow?
Through this?
ls this the only way?
-We can't go around it?
-l go where l feel myself led.
So l've noticed.
That way.
Shouldn't one of us go back
and stand guard?
Together.
Here, let me help.
Malak, go inside
and see if there's a lock.
-You mean in there?
-Go!
l found something.
Let go. Easy.
''lt is written
in the Scrolls of Skelos...
...that the horn will be found
by a woman-child.
A virgin who will have
a mark upon her.
And when the horn
is placed once more...
...in the forehead
of the Dreaming God...
...Dagoth will arise.
Then let man fear...
...death to the world.
The woman-child will be sacrificed.''
-Stop her! Don't let--
-Be silent!
Crom!
''Death to the world.''
Life for Valeria.
-Her destiny isn't only to deliver it.
-lt's just writing on a wall.
She is to be killed! Sacrificed!
We shall see.
Destiny or not.
Everybody out!
Out!
Wait! lt's worth a fortune!
We come in peace.
Then let us go in peace.
Let the girl come forward.
We've waited for her all our lives.
We are the keepers of the horn.
lt belongs to us.
No longer.
-Who are you?
-Conan.
l have heard of you.
You know the legend
written on the crypt wall?
From the day of my birth.
Then you know what happens...
...if the horn is placed back
in the forehead of Dagoth.
The god will live again.
And we who give him life
will stand by his side...
...and rule the world with him.
You'll die in the great evil
that will come from his rebirth!
-We will control him.
-No one is able to control him!
His power and his evil are too great!
Give us the girl or we'll take her!
Enough talk!
Back to the crypt!
Bombaata, get out!
Out! Let's get out of here!
Behind the dragon is a tunnel.
lt's our only way out.
The jewel! Take the jewel!
Hurry, hurry.
That way.
Malak!
Come on!
lt's the leader. He's a wizard.
He's forcing the mouth open.
Well, stop him! Kill him or something.
-My dagger's gone. You kill him.
-lt's bad luck to kill a wizard.
Wait. There's a better way
to take care of a wizard.
Well done, Akiro.
lnto the tunnel.
Don't stop! Hurry! Hurry!
Run! Run!
-Where are the others?
-They're coming. Don't worry.
-They've gone.
-Taken their horses.
-Or been captured. Let's flee.
-Wait.
Bombaata took her.
Taramis planned it from the beginning.
We get the horn,
her guards will kill us.
Bombaata takes them both back to her.
And her promise to you?
A lie.
-Where are we going?
-To Shadizar!
-What for?
-To stop Jehnna's sacrifice.
But it's her destiny.
lt can't be stopped.
You don't have to come.
-l will.
l won't!
l mean, what's in it for us?
We're not some charitable
institution! We're thieves!
Go! l won't help!
Hey, wait for me!
You know you can't do without me.
Wait, Conan, wait!
Do you have the treasure?
Bring it to me.
Reserves, to guard the palace.
There must be hundreds.
We can't get in there.
Well, you can't say we didn't try.
-The front can't be the only entrance.
-Oh, it isn't--
Behind the waterfall
there's an entrance.
My cousin's sister's brother
dug his way out there...
...when he was a prisoner of Shadizar.
Today is your birthday.
All of Shadizar is celebrating.
Drink.
To life. To Dagoth.
To Dagoth.
Oh, Dagoth.
God of gods.
My cousin's sister's brother
never mentioned bars.
How do we get back up?
They were put up after your
sister's brother's cousin escaped.
Cousin's sister's brother!
l keep telling you!
You said your sister's--
Who cares whose
brother's sister's cousin it is!
What difference does it make?!
At the first sign of life in our god,
the girl must be sacrificed.
Or as the Scrolls of Skelos say,
''A catastrophe will befall us.''
Oh, Dagoth, God of gods...
...power above all power.
Kill her!
Save the girl!
Kill her! Kill her!
She must be sacrificed!
Get back!
Down the steps!
Run!
His horn is his life!
Tear out the horn!
Zula?
l need a captain of the guards.
l see no reason why a woman...
...wouldn't do as well as a man.
You!
Me?
Come here.
l understand that every queen
must have a fool.
-Do l qualify?
-More than qualify.
Will the world's greatest wizard
come forward, please?
At your service.
One can't rule without wisdom.
-Let me instruct you in the mystical--
-Later.
Rule Shadizar with me.
l will have my own kingdom,
my own queen.
So it was that Conan
mourned his lost Valeria.
At length he sought adventure
in distant lands...
...and trod the jeweled thrones...
...beneath his sandaled feet.
Until at last,
he found his own kingdom...
...and wore his crown
upon a troubled brow.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org