Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
We're very proud of Judah Rosenthal's
philanthropic efforts...
...his endless hours of fundraising
for the hospital...
...the new medical center...
...and the ophthalmology wing...
...which, until this year,
had just been a dream.
But it's Judah Rosenthal, our friend,
that we most appreciate.
The husband, the father,
the golf companion.
-For medical problems...
-You're blushing.
...call him day or night, weekends,
or holidays. But you can also call...
...to ask about the best restaurant
in Paris. Or Athens.
Or which hotel to stay at in Moscow.
Or the best recording
of a particular Mozart symphony.
My father is so nervous
about having to speak.
l knew he was nervous when you didn't
eat any cocktail weenies.
He was so courageous all week.
Then suddenly tonight, stage fright.
Judah, you were fine till you
got home from work today.
Any mail?
The mail's where
l left it this morning.
l haven't had a second all day.
lf you're gonna shower, do it.
l have to use it too.
l dread making that speech tonight.
Dear Miriam Rosenthal,'
I'm at the lowest point of my life
as I write you this letter,
I wish to cause no suffering,
but because I'm going through hell,,,
,,,I ask if you can meet me one time,
Your husband and I
are more than friends,,,
,,,and have been deeply in love
for over two years now,
This must be faced,,,
,,,as there are many
ramifications and complications,
Many promises were made, et cetera,
I need an open exchange
with you to clear things,
For all of us to go on,,,
,,, the situation has got to be
confronted in some fashion,
Please contact me at this number,
I want what's best for everyone,
Dolores Paley,
That the new ophthalmology wing
has become a reality...
...is not just a tribute to me
but to a spirit of community...
...generosity, of mutual caring
and answered prayers.
lt's funny l use the term
''answered prayers.''
l'm a man of science.
l've always been a skeptic,
but l was raised religiously.
l challenged it, even as a child...
,,,but some of that feeling
stuck with me,
I remember my father telling me,'
''The eyes of God are on us always, ''
''The eyes of God.''
What a phrase to a young boy.
l mean, what were God's eyes like?
Unimaginably penetrating,
intense eyes, l assumed.
l wonder if it was just a coincidence
that l specialized in ophthalmology.
l'm so proud of you, Judah.
Sharon is, we all are.
All together.
-Why did you write the letter?
-We've been through it.
You wanna destroy my family?
l want her to know her husband.
lt was lying there all day.
By sheer chance, she didn't open it.
You said you'd leave Miriam!
We made plans!
-l didn't.
-You did!
l gave up opportunities!
-Pipe dreams.
-Other men wanted me.
What do you want?
You think this is easy?
l want what you told me
you wanted, to be together.
Otherwise, l don't know what!
l'll jump out the window!
You've been my whole life
for two years. l can't go back.
You turned my life around!
l never said l'd leave Miriam.
''There's no passion left.''
Those are your words...
...unless you lied.
Or there's something l don't know.
-Have you met someone else?
-What? For God's sake, Dolores.
-Dolores--
-What?
Now, look.
l've lived with her 25 years.
The roots are very deep.
l can't go on leading two lives.
You're not doing her a favor by
pretending. l won't be without you.
This won't happen without a fight!
l wanna speak to Miriam!
-Nothing's happening, okay?
-No!
Yes! Listen to me, please.
We'll work something out.
Let me get my thoughts together.
Just don't do anything rash.
Dolores.
What?
lt's gonna be okay.
Oh, God.
-You were gonna wait--
-Annie--
-Then throw me aside!
-Don't dramatize,
I've given you the best years
of my life!
Get out of here!
I know what you are,
Lucky I found out!
Those are my clothes!
That was great.
-The tuxedos, the evening gowns.
-Great.
lt was wonderful to live like that.
This is awful.
Let me get a cab. You stay here.
-You wanna see a movie again tomorrow?
-Sure, Uncle Cliff.
Jesus.
Unless maybe we should
make it a museum day.
l promised your dad on his deathbed
you'd get a well-rounded education.
We probably shouldn't
go to the movies every day...
...even though l'd love to.
While we wait for a cab...
...l'll give you
your lesson for today.
Your lesson is this:
Don't listen to what
your teachers say.
Just see what they look like.
Then you'll know what life
will really be like.
You heard it here first.
l see a cab. lf we run...
...we can kick the crutch
from that old lady and get it.
-l'm back!
-Where were you?
-Just out and around.
-Took your niece to a movie again.
l'm crazy about that kid.
She's just great.
My brother's in town.
He asked us to a dinner party.
-Jesus.
-Please. You gonna make another scene?
-l didn't do that last time.
-You did. Your resentment showed.
l don't resent him. He's a pompous ass.
You don't see it since you love him.
-What did you say?
-Nothing.
You did. You're running down Lester.
-l like your brother Ben.
-You're not jealous of him.
l'm jealous because
he's a TV producer?
No. Because he's highly respected
and he's a millionaire...
...and doing what you'd like to do.
Listen, l can't watch his stuff.
lt's submental.
-He wants to talk to you about a job.
-l don't need one.
Didn't l get honorable mention at--?
The Cincinnati Documentary
Film Festival?
Everybody got honorable mention
who showed up.
Boy, things have really
changed around here.
Wendy, Cliff, meet Lisa.
My sister, Wendy.
My brother-in-law, Clifford.
-Lisa's starring in my new series.
-Not really starring.
You're one of the stars.
lt's an ensemble piece.
-Hello, Lester.
-Hello, darling.
-So glad you came.
-Thank you for inviting me.
Have a drink. l'll be right there.
She gave a bundle to
The Museum of Broadcasting.
-She plays a--
-A lawyer for the ACLU.
Married to a conservative writer.
-So we can get into issues.
-We'll try to be fair.
But knowing Lester,
he'll slant it to the left.
Let's hope so.
-We're shooting here.
-You'll be here?
l wanna shoot more in New York.
-Oh, great.
-l love this town.
Out there is such
a Mickey Mouse environment.
The reason l'm here--
-Hello, Lester.
-l wanna talk to you. Don't go away.
A bunch of us are getting together...
...to build a studio here in the city.
ln fact-- l'm sorry,
just give me one second.
ldea for series:
A high-profile builder,
with grandiose dreams...
...a lá Donald Trump.
Shot in New York.
-Look who's here.
-That's my brother Ben.
Ben, Carol, come here.
Hi, kid. Nice to see you.
-Hi, honey.
-Hi, sweetheart.
-Hi, Cliff.
-How you doing? How are your eyes?
Not so good. lt's not so optimistic.
l've been seeing Dr. Rosenthal.
Lester, don't you want
to talk to Clifford?
Oh, yeah. Step into my office.
-Hi, l'm Lisa.
-Hi. We didn't meet. l'm sorry.
-So are you in TV too?
-No.
No. l'm a rabbi.
You don't wear an outfit or anything?
Public television wants to do
a documentary...
...on the way l talk and think--
lt's part of their
Creative Mind series.
So l told them about you.
Thanks. l'm working on my own thing.
-A little film.
-Wendy told me.
A film about some philosophy
professor, which is admirable.
But this is a chance to earn
decent money, reach a big audience.
Last thing you need
is me as your biographer.
l make these little films on
toxic waste and starving children.
l'll be frank. You're not my
first choice. lt's a favor to Wendy.
-You never work. She's embarrassed.
-l've worked, but nobody pays me.
l know you don't respect what l do.
But l got a closet full of Emmys.
You think that's bullshit.
Fine. l understand.
Maybe l could use the money
to finish my movie.
l do have some debts.
ldea for farce:
A poor loser agrees to do
the story of a great man's life.
And in the process,
he learns deep values.
-What takes you to Boston?
-I'm lecturing at a symposium,
lncidentally, my name's Dolores.
-Hello, Dolores.
-Hello.
-Pretty name.
-Thank you.
-Do you go to Boston often?
-Not very often,
I don't know anyone
in Boston, actually,
-Really?
-Yeah,
-Morning.
-Hi.
A Miss Paley called,
said it was urgent.
Why did you phone me?
l told you l'd call you.
l couldn't help it.
l was going out of my skin.
l have to see you later.
l have to!
Okay.
After work is okay.
l see it.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
What?
l need to take a minute.
What's wrong, Judah?
l'm in such trouble, Ben.
What is it?
l need to talk to someone.
Sure.
l've known you for years.
You're religious. l'm not.
We've differed on many points,
but l do respect you.
-May l confide in you?
-Of course.
Go ahead. Everything's confidential.
l've done a foolish thing.
Senseless. Vain.
Dumb.
Another woman.
Maybe l was flattered, vulnerable.
Maybe because she was
helpless and alone.
But now my life's
about to go up in smoke.
-Can't you break it off?
-The woman won't allow it.
She's young. She's very unstable.
She's an hysteric.
And vindictive.
And it's my fault.
l instigated it. l prolonged it.
l tried to back off,
but l was too weak.
But l promised her nothing.
But did l? l don't even know anymore.
ln the heat of passion,
you say things.
After two years of living
this double life...
...l awakened as if from a dream...
-...and realized what l'd be losing.
-lt's called wisdom.
lt comes to some suddenly.
We realize the difference between
what's deep and lasting...
...versus the superficial
payoff of the moment.
l kidded myself about loving her,
but deep down l knew.
Knowing l behaved selfishly...
...for pleasure,
for adventure, for lust.
Sometimes, when there's real love...
...and true acknowledgment
of a mistake...
...there can be forgiveness too.
l know Miriam.
Her values, her feelings,
her place among our friends.
What choice do you have
if the woman's gonna tell?
You have to confess the wrong
and hope for understanding.
Maybe Miriam's responsible,
in some ways too.
You have to discuss it
and hope for the best.
Maybe you can never
go back to the old life...
...but maybe there's a new one
with maturity and understanding.
Maybe even a richer one.
You know what's funny?
Our entire adult lives...
...we've been having this same
conversation in one form or another.
lt's a fundamental difference
in the way we view the world.
You see it as harsh,
empty of values and pitiless.
And l couldn't go on living
if l didn't feel...
...a moral structure
with real meaning...
...and forgiveness
and some higher power.
Otherwise, there's no basis
to know how to live.
And l know a spark of that notion...
...is inside you somewhere too.
You're talking to me
like your congregation.
True. We went from a small infidelity
to the meaning of existence.
Miriam won't think two years
of scheming and dishonesty...
...is a small infidelity.
How can you do it?
l give up.
God, you're in such wonderful shape.
-For a man my age.
-For any age.
l was athletic as a young student.
You still make love
like a young student.
l don't think we should do this here.
-Why not? We're alone.
-l don't know. l feel self-conscious.
Let's go to the cottage.
You can play me the Schumann.
Schubert.
Schumann is flowery.
Schubert is....
lt reminds me of you. The sad one.
God, you have to teach me all that.
-l'm so ignorant in classical music.
-l'll teach you.
Someday, we'll have a lot of time,
Would you like a drink?
Yeah. Fix me whatever you're having.
Why'd you call the house
last night and hang up?
Just because you've decided
l'm through in your life...
...doesn't mean
l'll roll over and die.
What the hell happened to us?
We had a wonderful few years.
We knew it couldn't go on forever.
-l gave up things for you.
-That's poppycock.
Don't give me that. For God's sakes.
There were no business opportunities.
No lovers begging for your hand.
l prevented nothing. l--
Can we not argue?
l just wanted to talk.
l'm just so rattled.
l had an idea.
l thought if we could get away...
...just for a little while
on one of our trips.
Our trips are my warmest memories.
Not just in our relationship,
but the best times l've ever had.
You're always so relaxed
away from home.
You come to life.
Your whole face changes.
l thought if we could just get away...
...to Boston or Washington
without any preconceived notions.
l can't go away, Del.
-Just a weekend--
-l can't!
-Why not?
-l can't.
-You won't.
-Of course l won't. Right.
Why not?
Because you're very unrealistic,
you know that?
Sit down for a second.
Let's talk.
Look.
l've been--
l've been thinking too.
And if l have caused you...
...to miss opportunities that
might have been lucrative for you...
...l'm perfectly prepared
to reimburse you. l don't want to--
l'm not after your goddamn money!
l wanna speak to Miriam!
lt's her problem too! She should know.
Keep her out of it, all right?
She should know her husband's
a liar and an embezzler.
Don't you dare call me an embezzler.
l know what went on between
those philanthropies and your stocks.
l took nothing, not a nickel.
My conscience is clear.
You needed money to cover
your losses. l saw.
Okay, l needed some temporary help.
For chrissake, after
a lifetime of hard work...
...a man doesn't watch himself
go down the toilet.
Moving around funds
is certainly not stealing.
Without asking?
Every cent was accounted for,
with interest.
-l don't think they'd see it that way.
-So this is your plan?
You'll hold on to me with threats?
Stupid threats and slander--
This is your idea of love?
l won't be tossed out!
l'll speak to Miriam!
For chrissake! Think what
the hell you're doing to me!
Please!
l can't figure it out.
l need you.
Del.
l love New York.
l was born in that building.
Behind the statue there
on the pedestal.
New York is like thousands
of straight lines...
...looking for a punch line.
What makes New York
such a funny place...
...is that there's so much tension,
pain and craziness.
That's the first part of comedy.
But you gotta get some distance.
The thing to remember about comedy is,
if it bends, it's funny.
lf it breaks, it's not.
You gotta get back from the pain.
A bunch of kids up at Harvard
asked me, ''What's comedy?''
This is what l'm trying to say
about getting back from it.
l said, ''Comedy is tragedy plus time.''
''Tragedy plus time.''
When Lincoln was shot,
you couldn't joke about it.
You just couldn't do it.
Now time has gone by,
and now it's fair game.
lt's tragedy plus time.
Okay. We're out.
-That's it? So fast?
-l shot 1 0 rolls on the first question.
l gotta get to CBS. Remember where we
were. Just remember what l was saying.
-All right?
-Excellent.
l think l'm too cute.
l'll be relaxed tomorrow.
More tragedy stuff.
-Halley Reed for Mr. Curtis.
-Would you excuse us?
lf you play your cards right,
you could have my body.
Wouldn't you rather
leave it to science?
l offer you my heart
and you squash it.
When are you gonna work for me?
You'd fire me.
l'm much too opinionated.
-No, no.
-l'll wait.
-l like mental stimulation.
-You tried shock therapy?
-That's good. That's funny!
-We've gotta go.
-l'll be right with you.
-But it's 5--
-Arthur, wait in the car.
-Please?
Yes. Wait in the car.
Yes. l was holding for Mr. Curtis.
Why not come with me to Barbados?
We'll swim, get some sun....
-Sorry. l freckle.
-My best shot. l can't do any better.
Okay. l'll wait.
Please think about it.
Talk to you tomorrow.
Yeah. lt's Halley Reed.
You cut me off.
We haven't officially met.
-Halley Reed, associate producer.
-l'm Clifford Stern.
Can l ask you something?
Why do you bother with this guy?
He's a pompous bore,
and your show does great profiles.
Just between us, l wanted
Gabriel García Márquez.
-That's perfect.
-They like a little variety.
-He is an American phenomenon.
-But so is acid rain.
You really don't like him.
''l love him like a brother,''
David Greenglass.
So why are you doing this show?
They rarely hire an outside person.
l'm doing it strictly for the money.
l'm trying to make my own
documentary on a guy...
...who'd be perfect for your show.
-Who?
-His name is Louis Levy.
Do you have a little time?
Now, the unique thing that happened,,,
,,, to the early Israelites,,,
,,,was that they conceived
a God that cares,
He cares, but at the same time,,,
,,,he also demands
that you behave morally,
But here comes the paradox,
What's one of the first things
that that God asks?
That God asks Abraham,,,
,,, to sacrifice his only son,,,
,,,his beloved son to him,
In other words, in spite
of millennia of efforts,,,
,,,we have not succeeded to create,,,
,,,a really and entirely
loving image of God,
This was beyond our capacity
to imagine,
-He's really interesting.
-l know.
-He'd be wonderful for the series.
-Wanna dump Lester and do him?
-Because l would love--
-We can't dump Lester.
But l could get
some financing for you.
And if all this comes
together right...
...we got some free spots
in the fall schedule.
To get this on your series
would be such a feather in my cap.
That would be my biggest audience.
Great. Let's make it happen.
l've got good footage.
Although we just met...
-...l've taken a liking to you.
-And l to him.
l thought l'd come by.
l got Jenny a present.
-ls that you, Uncle Cliff?
-Yes, l got you something.
l got you a great book, an absolutely
terrific book. How are you?
lt has great pictures
of old New York in it.
Look at this.
This is old Fifth Avenue.
-lt's great.
-Carriages and top hats.
There's a whole section
on speakeasies.
That's the Flatiron Building.
lt's very famous.
l had a creative breakthrough today.
l heard you got some action
on your personal ad. Terrific.
Here's the old Madison Square Garden.
-Jen, don't you have some homework?
-Yeah.
-We'll look at this later.
-Yeah. Thanks a lot.
What's the matter?
l'm a wreck.
What is it?
Barbara.
Barbara, what's the matter?
-l feel sick.
-What is it?
l'm still shaking.
l've been shaking like this for days.
What's wrong?
l've been going out with this man
l met through the personal columns.
Very attractive, He's very nice,
I went out with him three times,
He was never fresh,
He was always a perfect gentleman,
So we both came back here,,,
,,,and Jenny was away, She was
sleeping over at a friend's house,
It was 1,'00 in the morning
or something,,,
,,,and we both had had
a little to drink,
-l wanna tie you to the bed.
-Really?
And rip your dress off.
Have you ever been bound up,
tied up and made love to?
l'm, uh-- l'm a--
l'm a sensible gal.
No more, you're not.
God, Murray. God....
Barbara, l'm shocked at this!
You're my sister.
You're this nice middle-class mother.
What are you telling me?
l couldn't move.
l was tied tightly to the bedposts.
Oh, Jesus, by a strang--
A guy you didn't know.
Now you're gonna tell me
that he robbed you.
No.
He got on top of me and--
-And what?
-l can't say it. l just can't say it.
What? Tell me.
What's so terrible?
He sat over me
and went to the bathroom.
That's so disgusting!
Oh, my God! That's the worst
thing l ever heard!
-Then he took his clothes and left.
-Barbara, you idiot!
He could've cut your throat,
murdered you.
-l'd have preferred it.
-You're such a dope!
l wish l could have sympathy for this.
That's easy for you to say,
but l'm so lonely.
You don't know what it's like
to be by yourself.
l'm sure you're lonely.
lt's painful...
...but promise me you'll never
place another ad.
-lt's ridiculous!
-My whole life is passing me by...
...l don't have anyone to love. l know
that's hard for you to comprehend...
...because you're married.
But it's lonely out there.
You have a wife.
You love her, and that's so nice.
Things are not so good
between my wife and myself.
Don't get any illusions. We've been
coming apart for the last year.
Neither of us has energy to do
anything about it, but it's not great.
A strange man defecated on my sister.
Why?
l don't know.
ls there any reason l could give you
that would answer that satisfactorily?
You know, it's just so--
Human sexuality is just...
...it's so mysterious.
Which, l guess, is--
l guess it's good, in a way.
Yeah, well, l gotta be up at 7.
lt had to be a dark secret
for you to stoop to call me...
...to invite me here.
Jack, don't hit me while l'm down.
You're my brother.
-l was there for you.
-l'm here.
Don't make sharp cracks.
l didn't stoop.
l'm in serious trouble.
She won't take money
or listen to reason.
l considered telling Miriam, but
she'd never be able to live with it.
She's also blabbing about my
financial indiscretions.
Not that l stole,
but l was indiscreet.
lf they look, they might find things.
-What would you like me to do?
-l don't know, she's killing me.
-Want me to have somebody talk to her?
-Like what?
Straighten her out.
You mean threaten her?
That's all l need.
-How else do you keep her quiet?
-l don't know.
Jack, l don't know.
Well....
Christ, Jack, what do you suggest?
What did you call me for?
l hoped you'd have more experience
with something like this.
You called me to do some dirty work.
That's all you ever call for.
Look how bitter you are.
You've staked me plenty of times.
l don't forget my obligations.
Threatening her would
only make it worse.
Forget about it.
What do you want me to say?
How can l forget about it?
l'm fighting for my life.
She will destroy
everything l've built.
That's what l'm saying. lf she won't
listen to reason, take the next step.
-Threats, violence, what can we do?
-She can be gotten rid of.
-l know many people who can be bought.
-l'm not going to comment on that.
Well, what did you want me to do?
Not to do dirty work,
despite what you think.
Anyway, it's gone beyond
just Miriam now.
She's talking financial doings.
l'm out of ideas. l don't know
what l expected from you.
You don't know what goes on in this
world sitting here with four acres...
...and your country club
and your rich friends.
Out there in the real world,
it's very different.
-l've met a lot of characters--
-l know you have.
From 7th Avenue, from Atlantic City.
l'm not like you, l look at reality.
l can't afford to be aloof.
You come to me with a big problem,
then you get highhanded on me.
l don't mean to be highhanded.
l'm irritable, okay?
Okay, forget l said anything.
Let me just get
something straight here.
Am l understanding you right?
Are you suggesting getting rid of her?
You won't be involved,
but l'll need some cash.
-What will they do?
-What will they do? They'll handle it.
l'm talking about a human being.
She's not an insect.
You don't just step on her.
l know. Playing hardball
was never your game.
You never get your hands dirty.
Apparently, this woman is for real.
This thing isn't just gonna go away.
l can't do it.
l can't think that way.
I don't want to know anything,
This is a work of art,
The ropes come off,
-I tie weights to her with catgut,
-That's a horrible word!
Get the angle on this,
She disappears two weeks, maybe three,
Then up she pops, none of this
stuff on her, No marks, A suicide,
-Now, isn't that beautiful?
-It's loathsome, Be sure no one sees,
This only happens in the movies.
We should get back.
Lester's gonna leave the hotel soon.
lt's okay. l've been shooting
him all week. l'm tired of it.
l shouldn't have told you
my weakness is going to matinees.
l go all the time with my niece.
lt's like playing hooky.
We were late yesterday too.
We weren't late.
We didn't miss anything.
Have another cheeseburger.
lt's our lunch hour.
l got everyone at the network
excited over Professor Levy.
l have great stuff to show you later.
Listen...
...l brought you a present.
Great. Now l can get rid of
my few remaining teeth.
-Look at his face.
-A treadmill.
-You telling me something?
-You were bored with the bicycle.
lt's just as boring.
-You're in great shape.
-For a man my age.
-That's exactly what l was gonna say.
-Thank you.
This thing's great
for relieving tension.
-lt's just like the one at the club.
-Where are we gonna put this?
l'll have some 20 men
take it upstairs.
-lt looks like kinetic sculpture.
-lt's not staying down here.
Dad, it's for you. A Miss Paley.
-She's a patient.
-On this phone?
Yeah, she's going through a crisis.
-Can't the service take it?
-lt's probably urgent.
l'm at the gas station
down the road from your house.
l can be there in five minutes.
l'm going to,
unless you meet me right now.
No, Judah.
No. l wanna talk to you in person,
or l'm coming over.
-Calm down, okay?
-You said we're going away.
l want us to be alone.
When we get back...
...l want you to end it with Miriam.
l can't go on like this
and wait forever!
-You don't know what it's like!
-Talk to somebody.
-Like a therapist or somebody.
-Don't trick me!
Christ, l'm shaking.
Listen...
...l brought you a birthday present.
l know how much you love Schubert.
Sometimes, when there's real love,,,
,,,and true acknowledgment
of a mistake,,,
,,, there can be forgiveness too,
I know Miriam,
Her values, her feelings,
her place among our friends,
What choice do you have
if the woman's gonna tell?
You have to confess the wrong
and hope for understanding,
I couldn't go on living
if I didn't feel,,,
,,,a moral structure
with real meaning,,,
,,,and forgiveness
and some higher power,
Otherwise, there's no basis
to know how to live,
And I know a spark of that notion,,,
,,,is inside you somewhere too,
Could you really go through with it?
What choice do l have, man?
Tell me.
Give the people you've hurt
a chance to forgive you.
Miriam won't forgive me.
She'll be broken.
She worships me.
She'll be humiliated before everyone.
This woman plans to make a stink.
-Did you make promises to her?
-No.
Maybe l led her on
more than l realized.
She's so emotionally hungry.
-But it's deeper than just Miriam.
-Meaning financial improprieties?
No.
Maybe l--
Maybe l did make
some questionable moves.
Only you would know that, Judah.
l don't anymore, Ben.
Sometimes it's worse than--
Worse than jail.
lt's a human life.
You don't think God sees?
-God is a luxury l can't afford.
-Now you're talking like your brother.
Jack lives in the real world.
You live in the kingdom of heaven.
l managed to keep free
of that real world...
...but suddenly, it's found me.
You fool around with her,
then when you think it's enough...
...you wanna sweep her under the rug?
There's no other solution but Jack's.
l push one button
and l can sleep again nights.
Could you sleep with that?
ls that who you really are?
l will not be destroyed
by this neurotic woman.
But the law.
Without the law, it's all darkness.
You sound like my father.
What good is the law if it
prevents me from receiving justice?
ls what she's doing to me just?
ls this what l deserve?
Jack? lt's Judah.
We should move ahead
with what we discussed.
How much will you need?
lt's not funny, guys.
You're not thinking funny.
You gotta think with your ear.
Do you understand?
Here's the difference. lt's very easy.
lf it bends, it's funny.
lf it breaks, it's not funny.
lt's very simple. Wait a minute.
Jeff, this is Alva.
-Hi, pleased to meet you.
-Don't shoot this part.
Alva's in the new series.
l don't know what part...
...l just know l want her.
lt's wonderful. You look great.
Trust me, they love you. Be right out.
Don't do that while we're shooting.
Do you understand?
Think of Oedipus. Oedipus is funny.
That's the structure of funny.
''Who did this terrible thing?
My God, it was me.'' That's funny--
Don't do it, they're shooting!
What are you doing?
You will notice
that what we are aiming at,,,
,,,when we fall in love
is a very strange paradox,
The paradox consists of the fact
that when we fall in love,,,
,,,we are seeking to re-find,,,
,,,all or some of the people,,,
,,, to whom we were attached
as children,
On the other hand,
we ask our beloved,,,
,,, to correct all of the wrongs,,,
,,, that these early parents
or siblings inflicted upon us,
So love contains
in it the contradiction,,,
,,, the attempt to return
to the past,,,
,,,and the attempt to undo the past,
See? No limos, no bimbos,
no awards or anything.
-This guy is a thinker, an intellect.
-When you ultimately show this...
...to the people that make the
decision, emphasize his view of life.
-lt's life-affirming. They'd love it.
-This is what l need.
A little interest in my work,
a little encouragement or something.
l got a bottle of champagne
as a prize from Paris.
l got honorable mention
for a documentary l did on leukemia.
-Want some champagne?
-l never say no to champagne or caviar.
Perfect, l have no caviar. l have
oat bran. lt's better for your heart.
He was very eloquent
on the subject of love.
Yeah. Wish l had read him
before l got married.
-lt would've saved my gall bladder.
-What did you say?
Nothing. He wrote an interesting
book on human relationships.
He speaks very highly
of love at first sight.
l fell for my ex-husband
at first sight.
l should've taken a second look.
Actually, it was my fault
as much as his.
You still wear a wedding ring.
Why is that?
Well, l guess l'm just
not ready to take it off.
lt's good. lt keeps me
from getting asked out.
You must have had a terrible
marriage to avoid dating.
Well, no. He was great,
very brilliant. He's an architect.
But if you're gonna have an affair...
...not with my best friend,
in my four-poster bed.
And they didn't have
to finish my pistachio nuts.
That inconsiderate? l hope it
hasn't soured you on marriage.
-l hear myself sounding like a bore.
-Just the opposite. Hello.
Yeah, she's here. How did you know?
Hold on one second.
lt's Lester.
Hello.
Yeah?
Sure, if you want me to.
Okay. At the office at what time?
-9? That's no problem.
-9:00? The building will be dark.
-Nobody's at the office.
-l didn't hear you.
You'll be in a dark room with Lester.
-The office is a spooky place at 9:00.
-Definitely.
-Sure, the hotel is even nearer.
-Don't go to the hotel.
What was that? Room 1 91 1 .
Sure. Okay, l'll see you there.
-You're not going to his hotel.
-What's wrong?
-l better go with you. l know him.
-Don't be ridiculous.
He'll read you your Miranda rights
and tear your clothes off.
He wants to produce something of mine.
Your first child.
l can't be with a guy
who wears shoes and no socks.
-Much less one who says ''nucular.''
-He also says ''foilage.''
You have a copy
of Singing in the Rain?
lt's the one print l own.
lt's a very good 1 6mm print.
l play it now and then
to cheer myself up.
l saw it years ago.
l remember loving it.
They play it on television frequently.
-You wanna watch it? l can play it.
-Really?
-You wanna have dinner?
-Aren't you busy?
No, and you've got till 9:00.
l-- You know, why not?
There's an lndian restaurant,
l'll send out. You know, we could...
...you know....
l love this lndian food.
lt's great. Want some more
tandoori mouse? Just kidding.
-You want some of the curry?
-No, too hot.
My teeth are melting.
Boy, this is the perfect way
to see this movie.
lt's great, isn't it?
When you see Lester later...
...be careful. Because this guy tells
you he wants to exchange ideas.
What he wants is to exchange fluids.
-Yes?
-l have a delivery of some flowers.
Chris and you can't agree
on your honeymoon.
-We can agree on something.
-We don't disagree.
lt's just that l told Chris...
...l wanna go someplace warm
that has beaches.
But l also want to do
things like, maybe, hike.
-l hadn't thought of Australia.
-No, not there.
We should go where we wanted
to go in the first place.
-Where did you want to go?
-We wanted to go to ltaly.
Dad, it's Jack.
-He's on the phone.
-Who?
-Jack.
-l thought we had it decided.
ltaly is wonderful.
Right. We can have sun.
We can have snow, anything.
A lot of my friends
have gone to ltaly.
You won't go there because of that?
Everything came out fine.
lt's over and done with.
No problems. Forget about it.
Oh, my God.
l'm in shock, Jack.
l'm telling you, it's like
the whole thing never existed.
lt's a small burglary, nothing more.
So go on back to your life,
and put it behind you.
l can't speak.
l need a drink.
Jack....
What am l gonna do?
l've got guests here now.
God have mercy on us.
-Mom, you said Mary had acupuncture.
-She's tried it.
-She's been going for a few months.
-She hasn't gone back.
ls everything okay, sweetheart?
You look kind of upset.
Yeah, l'm fine. lt's just Jack.
She's still wearing that collar
when she drives.
Well, sometimes it does work.
We were talking about
Oriental medicine.
A friend consulted a Chinese physician
with an eye problem.
He inserted a cat whisker
into her tear duct.
She's been telling the story
all week. lt's her favorite.
-What happened?
-lt cured her.
-lt did.
-You told me he uses wires too.
Why would you--?
-ln acupuncture, you use needles.
-But very fine.
-But that's a different procedure.
-What do you think?
Judah, what do you think?
l think l've done a terrible thing.
What's wrong, honey?
l left these papers at the office...
...which l absolutely need tonight.
l can't believe l did this.
How negligent of me.
l have a conference in the morning.
-You're not going tonight.
-l must. l have an hour's work to do.
-But we're having a party.
-l'm so sorry.
-Please forgive me. l--
-Don't apologize.
l don't like him driving at night.
-Stanley, l'm so sorry about this.
-Chris, would you go with him?
-Would you like some company?
-No.
Darling, forgive me. l must go.
lt was a wonderful evening.
lf you're here when l get back--
-Don't worry about us.
-l couldn't apologize more.
Let's just finish the coffee.
Sit down.
He'll be back.
I'll say it once again,
The eyes of God see all.
Listen, Judah. There is absolutely
nothing that escapes his sight.
He sees the righteous and the wicked.
And the righteous will be rewarded...
...but the wicked will be
punished for eternity.
Hello?
l want your opinion.
l'm doing a special show on jazz.
l admire her opinion so.
Did you tell them l want
to produce an idea you have?
She wants to do a different
Chekhov story every month.
-He wrote a million.
-That's sweet.
-l'm putty in your hands.
-What will l do with putty?
She's always got a zinger.
This vixen, this minx.
We should really be going.
We have to pick up those airsick bags.
l gotta get up to teach Emily Dickinson
to upper middle-class crack addicts.
-One of my favorite poets.
-Me too.
-''Because l could not stop for death.''
-''He kindly stopped for me.''
The word ''kindly,'' right?
''The carriage held but just ourselves
and immortality.''
''We slowly drove, he knew no haste.''
''l had put away
my labor, and my leisure too...''
''...for his civility.''
-He was a great English student.
-Not that l graduated.
l couldn't graduate, but now
my school teaches a class in...
-...existential motifs in my sitcoms.
-Really?
-Where did you study?
-Columbia.
Columbia? What did you major in?
Law. l graduated from the law school.
-You didn't practice?
-l did. But then l met my husband.
We moved to Europe for a while.
lt's a long, boring story.
l wish you'd go back to your job.
l used to edit newsreel footage.
Floods, fires and famines.
Depressing.
-We don't all have to go.
-No. l do.
We'll go. You two stay
and talk business.
-l could go too, if you'd like.
-Let's go.
-Let's go for a drink.
-l wouldn't mind.
-l'm just exhausted.
-From what? lt's early.
Some other time.
-One little drink.
-Really. Some other time.
Lester was so pushy tonight.
He says it's business with Halley,
but he's after her.
-She really likes him. l can tell.
-You're kidding. She likes him?
What's not to like?
He's attractive, rich, charming.
You're prejudiced.
She put him down pretty good.
He said, ''One drink.''
She said, ''Some other time.''
l loved that. Socked it to him.
-Fine. Enough.
-That was pretty witty.
-How can you say she likes him?
-She was staring at him all night.
-She probably can't believe her eyes.
-You wouldn't pick up on those things.
You're not the least bit romantic.
You're the one who stopped
sleeping with me.
lt'll be a year on April 20th.
Same date as Hitler's birthday.
l'm not discussing that anymore.
l'll bet you she's with him now.
For how much?
l'm serious. For how much?
You really know how to get my goat.
Hi. lt's Clifford.
Yes. l knew you'd be in.
Tonight was a lot of fun.
Wasn't Lester so silly?
He's so self-important.
He was pushing all night.
l was frankly embarrassed for him.
What is he doing there?
You're talking business at midnight?
That could be very dangerous.
You want me to come over?
Okay, if you can handle it.
Okay. l'll see you tomorrow.
l'm in love with Halley.
Lester is making his move.
l can see it.
He wants her just for a conquest.
lt's so shallow,
and l'm crazy about her.
l can't compete with a guy
who's rich and famous.
-He's no competition for you.
-God bless you for saying that.
But you'll find out...
...that great depth and smoldering
sensuality doesn't always win.
You know his brother Ben the rabbi?
He's a wonderful guy.
He's going blind.
He's got a terrible eye disease.
He'll be blind in a few months.
He has a great attitude.
He's really a mensch.
All right. Look left.
Now straight ahead, Ben.
Now to the right.
That's good.
My mother said,,,
...that l should go to the doctor.
Because my eyes weren't so good.
Well, you're an ophthalmologist.
Do you agree the eyes
are the windows of the soul?
l believe they're windows.
l'm not sure they see the soul.
My mother taught me l have a soul.
And it will live on after l'm gone.
lf you look deeply enough in my eyes,
you can see it.
So, what's the verdict?
l want to resolve this
before my daughter's wedding.
-Julie's getting married?
-Time passes quickly, doesn't it?
Remember she was just a baby?
Well, yours too.
Are you okay, Judah?
You don't look so good.
l just haven't been
sleeping that well.
Tell me, if l'm not prying...
...did you ever resolve
your personal difficulties?
Yes, actually. lt resolved itself.
The woman listened to reason.
Did she?
That's wonderful. So you got a break.
Sometimes, to have a little good luck
is the most brilliant plan.
Relax. You're white.
You're gonna have a breakdown.
You expect me to be my old self?
l jump when the phone rings.
-No good can come of this.
-l kept you uninvolved.
The guy who's responsible
is back in New Orleans.
lt's pure evil, Jack.
A man kills for money.
He doesn't even know his victims.
He kills, you pay him
and he kills again.
What was your alternative?
How did l get in so deep?
What dream was l following?
You said it yourself a million times,
''You only go around once.''
l went to her place after.
l had to retrieve
some incriminating things.
l saw her there.
Just staring up...
...an inert object.
There was nothing behind her eyes.
lf you looked into them,
all you saw was...
...a black void.
Can l help you?
l used to live in this house once.
Really? When?
Many years ago.
My brother and l used to race
through these rooms.
He was a wonderful kid.
We were very close in those days.
My father had high hopes for him
but it never seemed...
...to work out for him.
Do you mind if l take a minute?
Everything seems to be
flooding through me.
Sure.
Sol, get on with it, I'm hungry,
-Do you mind, May?
-This is such mumbo jumbo.
Bring on the food.
l apologize for
my disrespectful sister.
This is the 20th century. Don't fill
their heads with superstition.
The intellectual, the teacher.
Spare us your Leninist philosophy
for once.
lf you don't obey,
God will punish you?
-Not me. He punishes the wicked.
-Like Hitler?
We're having a Seder!
Six million Jews killed,
they got away with it.
-How'd they get away with it?
-Open your eyes!
Six million Jews.
They got off with nothing.
-How could men do such a thing?
-Might makes right.
-Until the Americans--
-l don't like this talk at Seder.
Okay! All right!
-I think this is interesting,
-Yeah, you do,
There's this joke,
A prizefighter enters the ring.
His brother asks the family priest
to pray for him.
He said, ''Okay.
But if he can punch, it'll help.''
So you're saying you challenge
the moral structure of everything?
Moral structure? You use
that nonsense on your pupils?
You don't find human impulses
basically decent?
-There's basically nothing.
-A cynic, a nihilist. Back to Russia.
Well, listen. l happen
to agree with May...
...when it comes to mumbo jumbo.
But you come to every Seder.
You pray in Hebrew.
l go through the motions.
Like any ritual, it's a habit.
So you say there's no morality
anywhere in the whole world?
For those who want it, it's there.
Nothing's handed down in stone.
Sol's kind of faith is a gift.
lt's like an ear for music
or talent to draw.
You use logic on him all day
and he still believes.
-Must everything be logical?
-And if a man commits a crime?
lf he--
lf he kills?
-ln some way, he'll be punished.
-lf he's caught, Sol.
''What originates from a black deed
will blossom in a foul manner.''
You're relying too heavily
on the Bible.
Whether it's the Old Testament
or Shakespeare, murder will out.
-Who said anything about murder?
-You did.
Did l?
l say, if he can do it
and get away with it...
...and chooses not to be bothered
by ethics, he's home free.
History is written by the winners.
Had the Nazis won,
future generations would understand...
...World War ll quite differently.
Your aunt is brilliant,
but she's had an unhappy life.
And if all your faith is wrong--
l mean, just what if? lf?
l'll still have a better life
than doubters.
Wait a minute. Are you saying
you prefer God to the truth?
-l'll always choose God over truth.
-l agree with him.
l say, what goes around comes around.
-You okay? l was worried. lt's late.
-l had some business.
Mrs. Ames is waiting.
-Any messages?
-You got an odd one.
A Detective O'Donnell
wanted to talk to you.
l tried to ask him what about,
but he only wants to talk with you.
-lt's not a great movie, but it's fun.
-l liked it.
Maybe l want to be an actress.
l don't want you to be an actress.
Be on the Supreme Court or a doctor.
Show business is dog-eat-dog.
lt's worse than dog-eat-dog. lt's
dog-doesn't-return-other-dog's-calls.
l should check my service.
l don't know why.
l never have messages.
-l call, l hear the girls giggling.
-How's Halley?
She's great. l'm gonna make my move.
But l have this ethical dilemma
because l'm married.
Clifford Stern. Any messages?
Can you check?
My heart says one thing.
My head, another.
lt's hard to get your heart
and head together in life.
ln my case, they're not
even friendly. Yes?
Really?
No.
Okay. Thank you.
What's wrong?
Professor Levy...
...committed suicide.
But we must always remember,,,
,,, that we--
When we are born,,,
,,,we need a great deal of love,,,
,,,in order to persuade us
to stay in life,
Once we get that love,
it usually lasts us,
But the universe is a cold place,
It's we who invest it
with our feelings,
And under certain conditions,,,
,,,we feel that the thing
isn't worth it anymore,
l came as soon as l heard. l thought
you wouldn't want to be alone.
God, it's been terrible. l called--
The guy was not sick at all.
He left a note that said,
''l've gone out the window.''
A major intellectual, and this
is his note. What does it mean?
He was a role model.
-You'd think he'd leave a decent note.
-Did he have family or anything?
They were killed in the war. lt's
strange. He's seen the worst in life.
He always said yes to life.
Now today he said no.
lmagine his students,
how shattered they will be.
Where l grew up, in Brooklyn,
nobody committed suicide.
-Everyone was too unhappy.
-This will put a damper on the show.
l got 600,000 feet of film
on this guy...
...and he's telling how great life is.
l'll cut it up,
use it for guitar picks.
l was thinking,
no matter how elaborate...
...a philosophical system
you work out...
...in the end,
it's gotta be incomplete.
l've been so annoyed all day.
l'm sorry for seeming cranky.
No, l understand. l just thought
you might want some company.
No. Don't do that.
lt's something l've wanted
to do for weeks.
-You must know.
-You're married.
Yes, l'm married.
But, you know, that's
not gonna last. l mean....
Well, you know...
...l'm not ready.
ls there something you're
not telling me?
No.
ls there someone else?
Don't say it's Lester.
lt's me. lt's just me.
l guess l haven't gotten over
my divorce yet, you know?
And also, l feel unsettled
about my career.
l'm very ambitious.
And that's an area that
l'd like to get consolidated.
l just feel, you know, unsettled.
Don't confuse me.
-l'm not trying to confuse you.
-l don't know what l'm doing.
l better go. l should just leave.
-You just got here.
-l know, but l--
-l'm sorry, l didn't mean--
-No, that's okay. l'll see you soon.
l'll just-- l'll be seeing you.
Please come in.
We read about it in the paper.
lt's a terrible thing.
She'd been coming here for years.
-Please, sit down.
-Thank you.
Just a few questions, doctor.
Records show she phoned you here...
...and at your home a number of times.
-She worried about her eyes.
-What was she suffering from?
Nothing serious. She had
light flashes, and they alarmed her.
l never found anything very wrong.
l told her it was just
a common occurrence.
-She was a hypochondriac?
-No. l wouldn't say that.
But she was concerned.
There's nothing she said
you think might be relevant?
Personal life? Friends?
No, not really.
How did she come to you?
l honestly can't remember.
Possibly another patient.
Can l get that name?
lt was a while ago,
and l treat so many patients.
-Might it be in your records?
-No.
No. l doubt it very much.
-Sorry to take up your time.
-That's okay.
lf you remember anything
that might help...
-...will you call me?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
-Pleasure.
You're having a breakdown!
They know she phoned me.
l lied. They saw through it.
-l can't take this.
-Pull yourself together.
l did it. lt's irrevocable,
and l'm gonna pay.
l had to fight an urge
to come clean to the police.
l'm in this with you. l helped you.
l don't wanna go to jail.
You get ideas about confessing,
and you'll drag me down with you.
But l won't let that happen.
-ls that a threat?
-Be a man. You're in the clear.
-You'll have me killed?
-Nonsense.
What did you mean by that remark?
You've helped me in the past. Fine.
l did you a favor. All right?
The time to confess was to Miriam
about your mistress.
Not about this! This is murder.
You paid for it, l engineered it.
lt's over! Forget about it!
-One sin leads to a deeper sin.
-You sound like Papa.
Adultery, fornication, lies, killing.
-Can you shut up?
-Or what? You'll shut me up?
One phone call,
like pushing a button right?
l don't know what's wrong
with you these days.
l believe in God, Miriam.
l know it. Because without God,
the world is a cesspool.
You drink every day.
You never used to.
lt's something new.
-God, it's hot.
-Maybe we should go--
-Don't tell me what to do, damn it!
-Will you calm down?
l don't feel well.
l'm gonna get some air.
No, you stay here.
This homeless story is too long,
I want five pages,
Five real pages,
His secretary types it tighter,
He doesn't take a thing out,
I want Johanson off the show,
He has cancer, Send him flowers,
He's not funny,
I want him off,
Can't anyone write funny anymore? I'm
supposed to write everything myself?
Write, direct and produce it myself?
I can't believe this!
Look at the people out there!
These people are looking for
something funny in their lives!
They're waiting for something funny!
This is terrible.
What are you doing to me?
This isn't a profile
of a creative mind!
It's tough for a woman in this
profession, Men always hit on them,
What is this? When did you shoot that?
l was lurking around the corner.
l couldn't resist.
I don't wanna do it
in a vulgar way,,,
,,,and take it off
from what I see here,
I wanna find out what's in here,
So I gotta spend some time,
have dinner together,
l'm taking over this film.
-You can't finish my film.
-l can't? Read your contract.
-You promised.
-The idea was to show the real me.
l'm not perfect, but l don't
promote values that--
Let me quote you:
''--deaden the sensibilities
of democracy.''
You're fired. Get out of here!
Go! Thank you! Goodbye!
If it bends, it's funny,
If it breaks, it isn't,
Don't get discouraged.
You have your own vision.
Why was he so mad? As if nobody
was ever compared to Mussolini.
l'd no idea you'd cut it like this. l
could've told you they'd never use it.
They want an upbeat profile.
He's gonna re-cut it
and make himself into a saint.
Wendy's right. l'm jealous of him
with his limos and his money.
-You have your own style.
-Listen. Marry me. l'm serious.
That's all l want. Marry me.
l'm crazy about you.
My marriage won't last.
l gotta talk to you.
Can we sit down for a second?
l'm not joking.
l'm really nuts about you.
l'm going away.
Yeah? Meaning what?
l've got a chance to produce
a couple of shows in London...
...and, you know, l couldn't say no.
-How long are you going for?
-Well, probably three or four months.
Three or four months?
Jesus. You're kidding.
What a discouraging thought.
But l think it's a good thing...
...because l need-- Well,
it will give me a little distance.
About 3000 miles, to be exact.
When are you leaving?
Oh, l guess 1 0 days or so.
God, l'm--
God, l'm gonna miss you.
l don't know what to say.
l'm not gonna see you
for three or four months?
l feel like l've, you know,
been handed a prison sentence.
Ben, your daughter
will make a beautiful bride.
This is Barbara,
the sister of my brother-in-law.
Congratulations. l wish
your daughter all the happiness.
Thank you.
Jesus, l'm so self-conscious.
Every single thing on me is rented:
A rented tux, rented shoes,
rented underwear.
You look fine. Do me a favor.
This is your last occasion
with my family. Let's get along.
Oh, and this is Dr. Rosenthal.
-l'm Miriam.
-This is Miriam.
This is Marian and Peter.
How do you do? lt's a pleasure.
-Judah?
-Yes, Ben?
l'm so glad you could make it.
lt means a lot.
What is the matter with you?
You seem so depressed.
Wendy and l finally
decided to call it quits.
Even though the last few years
have been terrible, it makes me sad.
-l'll have a vodka and tonic.
-Me too.
You told me it's been
platonic for a year.
Once the sex goes, it all goes.
Last time l was inside a woman was
when l visited the Statue of Liberty.
Your father's celebrating
enough for two people.
He and Ben will get high
and argue about belief in God.
My dad takes after his Aunt May.
She rejected the Bible because it had
an unbelievable sense of character.
l walked in. l said, ''The Waldorf
Astoria.'' You see the centerpieces?
Did you see the matches?
Lester paid for it.
l can't believe a brother
would pay for a wedding.
That's the sort of thing
Lester's always doing.
-You've known him for a long time?
-Since high school.
They're pretty.
They're very, very pretty.
-Hi, Cliff.
-Cliff, hello.
Lester, how are you? Good to see you.
-My fiancée, Halley.
-Congratulations. My wife, Nancy.
-Jesus, you look wonderful.
-Thank you.
When did you return?
l got back this morning.
l've been trying to call you.
l finally won her heart.
What a romantic story.
We saw each other in London.
l sent her white roses
around the clock...
...all the time, for days.
Then l found out she was allergic.
-Hi.
-Hi. Congratulations.
Good to see you.
So l started pleading with her.
l just begged her day and night.
And l think it was
the caviar that did it.
l've envied this guy for years.
He'd show up with a beautiful woman
all the time.
-But l envy you more now.
-Thank you.
Standing here
in the presence of God...
...the guardian of our homes,
ready to enter the bonds of wedlock...
...answer each of you,
in reverence for God...
...and in hearing of
the assembly gathered here...
...so joyously with you.
-l know the perfect guy.
-Who?
-He's brilliant, attractive.
-There's a hitch. l'm waiting.
There is, but it sounds worse
than it is. He's in prison.
-That's a drawback.
-Nothing terrible. lnsider trading.
He made a fortune in the market.
He'll be out soon.
Very soon. A couple of years.
You mean with good behavior.
l wanted to talk to you.
What is there really to say?
You know, l'm just stunned still.
He's not what you think.
He's wonderful.
He's warm and caring...
-...and romantic.
-He's a success, that's what he is.
-He's rich and he's a success.
-Give me a little credit.
l always did give you
a little credit until today.
We used to laugh at him. The silly
shows he puts on, the way he talks.
He's endearing.
This is my worst fear realized.
l wanted to give you this letter back.
-lt's my one love letter.
-lt's beautiful.
l'm just the wrong person.
lt's probably just as well.
l plagiarized most of it
from James Joyce.
You probably wondered
about the Dublin references.
l hope we can always be friends.
Off by yourself, huh? You're like me.
l always get sad at these events.
You look very deep in thought.
l was plotting the perfect murder.
Movie plot?
Movie?
That's what Ben told me.
He says you make films.
Yeah, but not that kind.
You know, a different kind.
l have a great murder story.
-Yes?
-A great plot.
Yeah.
Hey, l've had too many to drink.
l mean, forgive me.
l know you want your privacy.
No, it's okay.
l'm not doing anything special.
Except my murder story
has a very strange twist.
Yeah?
Let's say there's this man
who is very successful.
He has everything.
-Let me ask you something.
-What?
-Am l a phony?
-Are you what?
-Are you a little high?
-He hates me.
-Who?
Your annoying husband.
Every time l'm with him, l get tense.
-He's angry.
-At what?
Are you kidding?
He's got these fantasies
about changing the world.
ln the end, his films come to nothing.
He's gotta grow up.
This is the real world, the big time.
They don't pay for high aspirations.
You gotta deliver.
Not to mention the fact that--
You're still young.
-You're not getting what you deserve.
-Lester, l met somebody.
That is music to my ears.
And after the awful deed is done...
...he finds that he's plagued
by deep-rooted guilt.
Little sparks of
his religious background...
...which he'd rejected,
are suddenly stirred up.
He hears his father's voice.
He imagines that God
is watching his every move.
Suddenly, it's not
an empty universe...
...but a just and moral one...
...and he's violated it.
Now he's panic-stricken.
He's on the verge
of a mental collapse.
An inch away from confessing
the whole thing to the police.
And then one morning...
...he awakens...
...and the sun is shining,
and his family is around him.
Mysteriously, the crisis is lifted.
He takes his family to Europe
and as the months pass...
...he finds he's not punished.
ln fact, he prospers.
The killing's attributed
to a drifter...
...who has many murders to his credit.
What the hell,
one more doesn't matter.
Now he's scot-free.
His life is completely
back to normal...
...back to his protected world
of wealth and privilege.
Yes, but can he ever really go back?
Well, people carry sins
around with them, l mean....
Oh, maybe once in a while
he has a bad moment, but it passes.
And with time, it all fades.
Yeah, but-- So then, you know--
Then his worst beliefs are realized.
l said it was
a chilling story, didn't l?
l think it'd be tough for
somebody to live with that.
Very few guys could actually live
with something like that.
People carry awful deeds with them.
What should he do?
Turn himself in?
l mean, this is reality.
ln reality, we rationalize.
We deny, or we couldn't go on living.
l would have him turn himself in...
...because then your story
assumes tragic proportions.
Because in the absence of a God...
...he is forced to assume
that responsibility.
Then you have tragedy.
But that's fiction,
that's movies. l mean--
You see too many movies.
l'm talking about reality.
lf you want a happy ending,
go see a Hollywood movie.
Come on, darling.
Let's think about going home, huh?
Nice talking to you. Good luck.
We'll have a wedding like this
for Sharon, and l can't wait.
She'll be radiant.
-You're looking very handsome tonight.
-And you look beautiful.
We are all faced
throughout our lives,,,
,,,with agonizing decisions,,,
,,,moral choices,
Some are on a grand scale,
Most of these choices
are on lesser points,
But we define ourselves
by the choices we have made,
We are, in fact,
the sum total of our choices,
Events unfold so unpredictably,,,
,,,so unfairly,,,
,,,human happiness does not seem
to have been included,,,
,,,in the design of Creation,
It is only we,
with our capacity to love,,,
,,, that give meaning
to the indifferent universe,
And yet, most human beings,,,
,,,seem to have the ability
to keep trying,,,
,,,and even to find joy
from simple things,,,
,,,like their family,,,
,,, their work,,,
,,,and from the hope,,,
,,, that future generations,,,
,,,might understand more,
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org