Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I believe there is a place
where the restless souls wander.
Burdened by the weight
of their own sadness,
they wait for a chance
to set the wrong things right.
Only then can they be reunited
with the ones they love.
Sometimes a crow
shows them the way.
- Because sometimes...
- Iove is stronger than death.
- It's not your fault.
- No, no, no.
- We didn't see.
Let him go!
He's just a kid!
He can't hurt you!
I'm scared, Dad.
Please, Dad, I'm sorry.
- No!
Gabriel...
it's been a long night.
Caressing the marble
and stone
Ah, love that was
special for one
The waste in the fever I feel
How I wish you were
here with me now
They call this
"The City of Angels,"
but all I see around me
are victims.
It's the city of drugs...
and of darkness.
The city ofJudah Earl.
Got a name?
Grace. So what?
My name is Sarah.
Listen, Grace, maybe you want
to get some hot coffee...
and a little bit of food.
What do you want?
Nothing.
Do you want to eat here?
We all have our pleasures.
For some, it's the flesh.
And we provide for them.
For others, it's the drugs.
- And we provide for them too.
Our products feed this entire city.
While other kingdoms fall around us,
we've succeeded...
by being of a single mind.
Succeeded with guidance
from a darker world, Judah.
Do you love me, Sibyl?
All must love you.
Really?
Then why did this sad-eyed
sack of shit betray me?
Hey, well, l...
Hey, l-l-l-I didn't
betray you, Judah.
L-l-I did it for
the business, you know?
I mean, this last...
Batch of yours,
it was bad...
it was a hot mix.
I mean, Jesus Christ, Judah,
it was given 'em seizures...
whoa, get away.
Hey, Judah, your...
your brand...
It should inspire trust, right?
I mean, come on, we can't kill off
all the motherfuckers, huh?
I mean, hey, whoa, there'd be
no one left to buy the shit.
So you destroyed 80 keys
of product without my consent.
Hey, hey, back off!
Get the fuck away from me!
Look at this, Judah. You're surrounded
by these fuckin' freaks, man!
You don't even leave
this fun house anymore, man!
I mean, you have no idea what
the shit is doing to people...
out on the streets, man.
It could ruin your fix with the cops.
I'm not bullshittin'.
I mean, it's bad
for business, huh?
All right, then.
Let's see how bad
this batch of ours really is.
Hey! Whoa! Hey!
What the fuck
is goin' on?
We're volunteering you
for a little quality control.
Oh, jeez, Judah.
I'll make it up to you, I swear!
But you are. Weren't you
listening before, Bassett?
I said we all have
our pleasures.
Mine is the pain of others.
Guess you were right, Bassett.
That was a bad batch.
- Whoo!
I'm almost done.
- Are you okay?
- It stings a little.
That's why they call me
the mistress of pain.
I'll get the other book
out for you.
Let's see this masterpiece.
Go ahead, turn around.
Whew. Spin 'round a little.
Ho, ho, ho. There's nothin'
I can do for you, luv.
Christ, what a downer!
Some kid asked me to tattoo,
"If you can read this,
you're standin' too close."
Right on her bum.
I tell ya, I've had it.
Well, it's better than
pushing ink in Detroit.
Well, you can say
that again, darlin'.
You can say that again.
- I got a little present for you.
- You did?
They do them for
the Day of the Dead.
Thank you.
"Necrophagia,"darlin'...
eat the dead.
"Life is just a dream
on the way to death."
I like that.
Do you want to come
have a beer, girl?
Um, no, I can't.
I gotta go home. I haven't been
getting that much sleep lately.
And what is
the dirty dog's name?
No, I've just...
I've just been having these
really, really strange dreams.
I know.
Sleep with angels.
- Did l...
No!
Talk to me, Sibyl.
Tell me what you see.
I see death returning
from the vale of tears.
Look at them down there,
swarming through
the streets like insects.
It's the same each year, isn't it?
Lighting their little candles.
Whispering their wasted prayers.
This time is different, Judah.
This time someone is coming for you.
He has your name
on his tongue.
It's finally
beginning, isn't it?
What mask will death wear?
Can you tell me that?
I see the face
of one of your victims.
All my sins remembered.
Now we're gonna be
face to face
And I lay right down
in my favorite place
Now I wanna be your dog
Ah, come on
Spider Monkey!
- What's this tattoo look like to you?
- This is a test?
- Come on, man! Tell me what you see!
- Come on!
- A bird.
Think about this!
Think! Think!
- Don't you see two demons?
- No.
I see a bird.
- Fuck you, you fucking fool!
And what's this
in your ear?
Toro, toro!
- Ole!
Look.
- Who are you?
- Sarah.
I had a dream about you.
I saw them shoot you
and your son.
I saw you drowning.
How did I survive?
You didn't.
- You're dead.
- No!
No!
This isn't real.
None of this is real.
No!
Where will we go
Oh, where will we go
This ghost follows
Ah, yes
- Danny! What are you doing?
- Hmm?
- You think you're a man? Come on.
- Yes.
Defense, defense.
The face, the face.
- Yeah, yeah, good.
- Aah! Help!
Want to do bullfighting?
Huh? Do the bull.
- Come on.
- Okay. Uuh!
Danny.
Hey, Dad.
- Yeah?
- Look, I made this.
- Who are they?
- These people?
- Yeah.
- That's you and me.
That's me? And the thing
on top over there?
That?
That's a blue sun.
- A blue sun?
- Yeah, a blue sun.
What was that?
Danny, stay here!
Danny!
Come here.
See no evil.
- No! No!
- You can run.
Run! Run! Uuh!
No! No!
No! Danny!
No!
Leave him alone!
- Dad!
No-o-o! No!
I want to help you.
Danny.
He's not here anymore.
I know.
What's your name?
Ashe.
There's a reason why you've been
brought back, Ashe.
To find the people
who did this to us.
To make them pay.
These were Danny's paints,
weren't they?
Hey, old man
Got something for you
- Change your mind
Gonna make you take it
- Your mistake
is something you own
And I'm the one
who's gonna take it
Hey, old man
Got something for you
Got a real good tip
- Got a real good tip
- Something's wrong
and you don't know it
You don't know it
When will you learn
I'm not your boy
You don't look back
Why do I pick up
your slack, man
When will you learn
I'm not your boy
Hey, old man
Got something for you
Gonna...
- Ahh!
- Ooh!
- Olé!
- Whoop!
- Toro!
- Ah-ha-ha-ha!
Who the fuck are you?
- Does the corpse have a familiar face?
- Flowers for the dead, señor?
We killed you, man.
You're dead!
- Sorry to disappoint you.
- Whoo-oo-oo!
Stop wasting your breath, angelito.
There's nobody out there listening.
- Yee-aagh!
- I'm all your nightmares...
rolled into one!
- Wuh-aah!
Aa-aa-aah!
Oh, geez! No way, man!
- Fuck! Oh!
This shit's flammable, man.
- The others. Who are they?
- Huh?
- Nemo,
- Hmm.
- Kali, Curve and Judah.
- I'll start with Nemo...
And then work my way
up the food chain.
- Where is he?
- Nemo?
- Mm-hmm.
- He's an old pervert.
He hangs out at the Peep-O-Rama
on Deacon Street.
Congratulations, Monkey!
You just bought yourself
a fighting chance!
Pick a card, Monkey.
Come on.
Lady Luck's... a bitch.
Oh...
Jesus, man. Come on, man.
Come on, come on, come on.
You're wasting your breath,
angelito.
- Nobody's up there listening.
I want to be your
Be your rubber ball
- I want to be the one
You love the most of all
Oh, yeah
- I'm your boogie man, boogie man
Turn me on
I'm your boogie man, boogie man
I'll do what you want
I'm your boogie man
Boogie man
Turn me on
I'm your boogie man
Ohh...
I got bad news. Someone torched
the lab on Manchester.
Spider Monkey's
a fucking crispy critter.
Monkey I could care less about.
What about our merchandise?
- It's a total loss.
- He left a sign, didn't he?
I don't know what
you're talkin' about.
Yes, you do.
You've seen it.
You've been marked.
Jesus Christ. Judah, why the fuck
do you listen to her?
Because she speaks the truth.
What's this, Curve?
A beauty mark?
And all the world
will be in love with night.
And pay no worship
to the garish sun.
- Noah?
- Yeah.
Do you believe in fate?
Seems to me it's a question
of... fate believin' in you.
- We're closed for the night!
- Open the fucking door!
I said, we're closed. Aah!
- Fucker!
- Think what you did to me was funny?
- God...
- Some kind of joke? Huh?
- Stop! It hurts me!
Huh? Huh?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm talkin' about this fuckin' tattoo
you gave me! Look at this shit!
- It's a crow.
- You're goddamn right it's a crow.
Did I ask you for
a fuckin' bird on my chest? Did I?
I was going from the fucking design
that you gave me!
Stop it! Stop it!
O-Oh!
Well, what's it gonna be, hero?
Ready to kiss your faggot ass
good-bye?
I think you're shittin' yourself,
you're so goddamn ready.
Fuck you!
Uuh!
- You fucking piece of shit!
- Aah!
- Get up.
- Girl to girl sincerity
Remains
Awkwardly unnamed
- You never kissed
- I'll be seein' you...
- These girlfriend
- sugarplum.
- Lips
Simple choice to fall away
Fall away
Away, away, away
Away
Why is the world
- Falling on me
- Are you okay?
Well, fuck me. What are they
going to be snorting next?
- I can't take this anymore.
Don't worry, love.
Everything'll work itself out.
Did she make
you cry, make you break down
- Aah!
- And shatter your illusions of love
- Fuckin' shit, motherfucker!
Smile, sister.
- Whoo! Hey!
This is a recording.
- Tokens for the bunny booths.
- Live girls.
- It's his wreck. It's all right.
What up, Zeke?
Right.
How ya doin', man?
This is for you.
For you.
You got a name?
- Holly Daze.
- Put your hands in the air
Tonight is a special night
- You want me, baby?
- Put your hands in the air
Tonight is a special night
Check this one
Oh...
Throw your hands
in the air tonight
Uh... I wanna see some sugar.
Check me out, Pop
Throw your hands high in the air
Sugar?
- Right on, sister.
Mmm. Is that for me?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
We're gonna celebrate Christmas
a little early this year.
Mmm. Keep doin' that, baby,
you're gonna go blind.
- Fuck! Fuck!
Oh, yes!
Time's almost up, lover.
Hurry with those tokens.
- Oh, shit, man!
Come on!
Bitch!
Come on, fucker!
Do you want me...
baby?
You...
Me.
- Hey! Fuckin'mime boy!
- Uuh!
One crow, sorrow.
Two crows...
joy!
- Three crows...
- Oh, ah!
A letter!
- Four crows...
- Uuh!
- Uuh! Aah!
- A boy.
- Let him go! He's just a child.
Uuh! Uh! Aah!
- Five crows, silver!
- Aah!
- Six crows, gold!
Seven crows,
a secret never to be told!
Aah! Stop the fuck...
Aah! Please!
No, please!
- Please, just stop! I can't...
- Look at me!
Lights! Camera! Action!
- Aah!
- You killed my son, Nemo.
You took away the only
piece of light left in my soul.
We had to! We had to!
It wasn't our fault!
Was Judah's orders.
Never leave any witnesses.
We didn't have any choice.
We always have a choice!
- Tokens for the bunny booths.
- Go, let's go!
- Live girls.
- Ow! Yeah!
- Tokens for the bunny booths.
- Let's go!
- Live girls.
- Tokens for the bunny booths.
Live girls.
Tokens for the bunny booths.
Live...
In my room I want you here
Now we're gonna be
face to face
And I lay right down in my
favorite place
Holy fuck.
Do you know what they call
a gathering of crows... Curve?
- A murder.
A murder of crows.
Think about it.
Can I help you?
I'm sorry, Father.
I was just watching.
Our doors were open.
What's all this for?
Dia de los Muertos.
Day of the Dead.
We light candles
for our loved ones...
so they might find their way
back to Earth.
Tomorrow night
we will celebrate.
The people will dance and sing
and some will wear masks.
Why?
Some spirits
linger here too long.
They become confused,
mistaking themselves
for the living.
They must be
frightened away.
Santa Muerte.
No soporte.
No lo soporte.
Santa Muerte.
No soporte.
Maybe there is another way.
- How... How'd you do that?
- Magic.
Blow on it.
Go on.
Like birthday candles.
You have power
just like I do.
You have power over this.
That's him!
That's the son of a bitch I dumped
off the pier, I know it.
I saw you kill him.
Look, you wanna tell yourself
some bullshit fairy tales,
that's your business.
- I'm not gonna sit here with
a fuckin'target on my chest.
I'm gonna take
this motherfucker out.
You won't stop him
with guns or knives.
He doesn't feel pain.
His soul has crossed over.
So how do you stop a man
who's already dead?
Can you look Destiny
in the eye...
without flinching?
You tell me.
The crow
is his source of power;
his link between this world
and the next.
Sever that link, and he's
as vulnerable as the next man.
You came back.
Were you married?
My ring...
It belonged to some friends.
Where are they now?
A better place.
What about you?
Danny's mother left
after he was born.
She was a drug addict.
You knocked me out
Bit my lip
- You held me down
- What happens to me...
- And kept me sober
- when I finish what
I'm supposed to do here?
Through all this time
- You go back.
With no regret
Guess that's just the way
I liked it
- Ooo
- And what if I don't want to go back?
- Oh whoa-oa
That tattoo on your chest...
Who gave it to you?
Some bitch down at the Gargoyle.
What's that got to do with anything?
Everything, you idiot!
Find her.
If she gave you his mark,
she's connected to him in some way.
She can lead us to him.
Fool!
Mm-aah!
What do you people want?
A house in the country.
A little dog.
A wife.
Two kids...
- and your fucking head
stapled to my pussy seat.
- Listen...
We're only looking for Sarah.
Where is she, Noah?
I ain't gonna tell you that.
- I wish I could lose control
- But I think you are.
- I wish I could let go
I'm cumming on you
I'm cumming, I'm cumming
Last chance, love.
- Go fuck yourself, you dried-up bitch!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming
I'm cumming on you
I took Danny last summer.
We went up on the bike.
Rode all the way up the coast.
It was cold, I remember.
We could see our breath.
Look at me.
Ashe?
L-Look at me.
No. No.
We can't do this.
I have to find the others.
I have to finish what I started.
- Hey, Dad.
- Yeah?
- Look.
- Who are they?
- These people down here?
- Yeah.
That's you and me.
Sleep with angels.
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to look.
- It's not your fault.
- Lights!
- Look at me! It's not your fault.
You understand?
Action! Action!
Flowers for the dead, señor?
- No!
Stop wasting your breath, angelito.
Let him get out! Let him alone!
He's just a kid!
- What about the kid?
Pain is my power.
Kill them both.
Let him alone!
He's just a kid!
- He doesn't even know who you are.
- Don't, please, don't.
- Hush, little baby
Please don't cry
I beg you!
I beg you, please!
- Kali's gonna give you
eternal life
- Don't! No! Aah!
- No! Aah!
- Nothing personal, sport.
I guess you were just in the wrong
place... at the wrong time. Heh!
Dump 'em!
Ah! Hah!
Sarah's gone.
Ghost man.
Where is she?
You took my son's life.
Some people are
just born victims.
Hush, little baby
Please don't cry
Do you know how to fight?
Do you know how to die?
- Yah!
- Come on.
Hah!
- Hi! Hah!
- Do you want to dance?
- Kali's gonna give you eternal...
Hah! Ah!
- Ah!
Hush, little baby...
Shh.
Don't say a word.
N... No!
Daddy's gonna buy you
a big, black bird!
When I first heard the sound
I couldn't put it down
It made my life complete
Ah, give it to me.
Yeah.
Ain't it neat
And you know
I like it when you
- Spit
Oh, I like it when you
Spit
- Naughty boy!
- And when you do that
You know I'm getting wet
- Wear me on your head
Yeah, that's what I said
I wanna be
your rock and roll
You know I wanna be your
push and pull and it's only 'cause
I like it, whoo
Girl, I like it
Whoo, girl I like it
- Oh, yeah
Waaahh!
Nothing personal,
sport.
- Hey!
- Look out!
Ow!
Fuck you, bird dick!
Time's up, Curve!
My naked cousin
I see him running
All over his land
- Scared as a chick-a-chicken
His naked skin fries
Fries in the sun
But my, my naked cousin
Can cook 'til
he's good, good and done
He's running
Baby, he's running
Yeah!
Wrong place.
Wrong time.
Eh, Curve?
Do you think
I'm afraid of you?
You fucking freak!
Do you think I'm afraid?
- You think I'm afraid!
Can you hear me, Curve?
You're going to die now.
People used to put coins
in the mouths of the dead.
Do you know why?
So they could pay the ferryman
to take them across the river Styx.
What's this?
Open your mouth, Curve.
I want to thank you
for showing me my pain, Curve.
You made me what I am.
Flores.
Flores para los muertos.
Where am I?
The tower.
Everyone finds
their way here eventually.
What happened to you?
Fate happened to her.
Sibyl's been cursed
with the gift of prophecy.
Judah Earl.
She sees things
that are fated to happen.
She cut out her eyes
with a carving knife...
because she wanted to make
the visions stop.
But that only made the visions
stronger, didn't it, dear?
Why did you bring me here?
I'm glad you asked that, Sarah.
You've got a very important part
to play in this little drama of ours.
I intend to capture the crow,
and you, my dear,
are the birdseed.
Sarah.
First you smiled at no one
I found you first
They've grown fine
inside of you
But it hurts if I even see you
Make you smile
I look over and cry
But that's too bad
Get stuck for nothing at all
Look at yourself
You ain't no genius
You won't to find
You won't find me
Go!
Look who's come home to roost.
Aah!
But that's too bad
- You'll get what you pay for
Look at yourself
You ain't no genius
You want to find
You won't find me
I'm coming home when I go
Aah
Ashe is here.
First you fight me
I found you first
They've grown fine
inside of you
- Do you know
what these are called?
Misericords.
Wonderful name,
isn't it?
In the Dark Ages, these were
used to deliver the death stroke...
to the mortally wounded.
They were considered
tools of mercy.
Easy.
- Ah!
- Oww!
- Aah!
Ashes, ashes,
- Oh!
- We all fall down.
No!
You have taken his power.
He is only a man now.
Ah.
Hey, Dad!
If you give up now,
we won't be together.
Danny!
Judah!
What...
What are you?
I'm your shadow, Ashe.
Every angel's got a devil.
I've tasted the blood
of the crow and taken your power!
The crows. They are the souls
who have come before Ashe.
They are crying
for the people they have lost.
Now they have come for him.
Looks like the dead have
forsaken you, my friend.
- Look at you!
- Go to hell!
Already been there!
And I must confess,
I liked what I saw!
Where's your strength, huh?
Where's your power?
You're nothing now, Ashe.
Not even a ghost.
- You want death?
- Yeah!
There he is, people!
Take a good look!
Uh! If you whip him,
does he not bleed?
- Ashe!
Aah!
Sarah.
Sarah! Sarah!
Judah!
Aah!
Oh!
You can't stop me
anymore, Ashe.
You haven't got the power.
There's nothing
but pain for you now.
Pain is my power.
Take him!
Aah!
You can't die.
Oh, God.
Wait!
I wanted to thank you.
Where are you going now?
A better place.
I believe there's a place
where the restless souls wander...
burdened by the weight
of their own sadness.
They wait for a chance
to set the wrong things right.
Only then can they be reunited
with the ones they love.
Sometimes a crow
shows them the way...
because sometimes
love is stronger than death.
Rock on, gold dust woman
Take your silver spoon
Dig your grave
One less challenge
Pick your path and I'll pray
Wake up in the morning
See your sunlight
burning to go down
Lousy lovers pick their graves
but they never cry out loud
Cry out
Well, did she make you cry
Make you break down
Shatter your illusions
of love
Is it over now
Do you know how
To pick up the pieces
and go home
Did she make you cry
Make you break down
Shatter your illusions
of love
And did you know by now
Do you know how
To pick up the pieces
and go home
To go home
Home, home, home
Oh, shadow of a woman
Oh, oh, shadow of a woman
Ooo, yeah
shadow of a woman
Ooo, ooo
Ooo, yeah
shadow of a woman
Come on, come on
Black widow
Ooo, ooo, ooo
Whoo, hey, ah
Shadow of a woman
Black widow
Ooo, yeah
shadow of a woman
Shadow of a woman
Black widow
Ooo, yeah
shadow of a woman
Black widow
Hey, old man
Got something for you
Change your mind
Gonna make you take it
Your mistake is
something you own
And I'm the one
who's gonna take it
Hey, old man
Got something for you
Got a real good tip
Something's wrong
and you don't own it
When will you learn
I'm not your boy
You don't look back
Why do I pick up your slack
When else you been in my bed
Got your picture in my head
God, you are so truly old
Thanks a lot
My future is sold
No
When will you learn
I'm not your boy
Hey, old man
Got something for you
Got a real good tip
No
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org