Ryan, what happened?
It's bad. It's not good.
What do you mean, it's
bad, Wolfe? Talk to us.
Horatio took a round to the chest,
and I got here too late.
He's gone.
What?
He's dead.
Oh, my God.
Calleigh...
Eric, Horatio's dead.
Listen to me-- Horatio's gone.
He's dead.
Where is he? I
need to see him.
I released the body.
What?!
What the hell did
you do that for?
The first responder
waits for the team
to get here!
His team.
I'm sorry!
I didn't want him lying here
in his own blood
on the evening news,
I released the body!
How did you get here so fast?
I was running an errand nearby.
You left that interrogation
for an errand?
I left a stupid errand,
I dropped everything
as soon as I heard
it on the radio.
It just doesn't
make sense.
Let's focus.
Horatio had enemies.
We know that.
This must have been
someone close.
We're gonna find out
who did this.
We find out!
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
片名 第1季第1集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：个人ID
校对：个人ID
Where's Lieutenant Caine?
I released the body to
a federal agent 20 minutes ago.
Why would you do that?
The airstrip's
on government land.
Federal agency
has jurisdiction.
What was the agent's name?
I don't know.
What do you mean, you don't know?!
He had
He signed our release form,
took the remains.
The remains have a name.
Horatio Caine.
Yeah.
We're waiting for a statement
from the department.
Airport personnel are saying
that Lieutenant Caine is dead.
The shot was fatal.
How you doing?
Talked to everybody
from the crew to the tower.
Learn anything?
Private jet took off right about
the time the shot was reported.
It was bound for Puerto Rico.
What about witnesses?
Lot of noise on the ground,
planes taking off.
Nobody claims to have seen
or heard anything.
You know what I
don't understand is
what Horatio was doing out
here in the first place.
Well, this might explain it.
It's the flight manifest
from the jet.
Julia and Kyle were on board.
Where are they now?
Plane landed 40 minutes ago
in San Juan.
I've already talked
to local authorities.
No sign of them.
Well, let's stay on that,
'cause they're either
our two best suspects
or our two best witnesses.
Let's find out
who did this, Cal.
As long as we're
breathing, Frank.
I just can't wrap
my head around this.
Where's Wolfe?
Um, the last I saw,
he was walking the perimeter.
Why?
Something's just not right.
He was here too quick,
and now I can't
find Horatio's body.
Eric, he's one of us.
Listen, I think I'm looking
at our first break.
Got a partial shoeprint
here in the blood pool.
Someone walked
through his blood?
Yeah. Here, look.
Left a little fleck
of some kind.
That looks like
coagulated blood.
One fleck of blood doesn't dry
on its own,
so this could be
from the killer.
I'm gonna rush it to the lab.
Running the fleck
from the shoe print?
Yeah, um, my-my hunch is right.
That blood is definitely
from a different source.
Pop it into CODIS.
I'm way ahead of you.
If ever there was a
time to get lucky.
Yeah, right.
Brett Hanson.
"Armed robbery, attempted
murder, assault."
Deceased?
This guy was killed
in jail yesterday.
So how does a dead man's blood wind up
at that airstrip?
Whoever killed Horatio walked
through Hanson's blood first.
Take off your shoe, Diaz.
You're the only person released from Miami
Dade Detention in the last 24 hours.
Gated out, 4:00
this morning. So?
So you went straight from jail
to the Miami Shores Airstrip?
Nah, I-I don't know
what you're talking about.
We found blood
from a man named Brett Hanson
at the scene of the murder.
You transferred that blood there
on the bottom of your shoe.
We know you're a associate
of Juan Ortega.
Who?
Don't play dumb with me.
You hear me?
Ortega manufactures and sells
fused alloyed bullets.
You know it, and we know it.
He sent you
to kill Horatio Caine
because he was after
those bullets.
Me? Nah.
I was there
trying to catch a flight.
Heard a shot, saw Caine go down.
You know, I figure
I'd take a picture.
Get credit for the hit.
Nice.
You get credit for the hit?
With Ortega? Hmm?
Well, you didn't fly anywhere.
How are you gonna explain that?
Hey, man, no
crime, no time.
Eric! Eric!
No crime, no time?!
Huh?
Get your hands
off of me.
You're going back
to the lockup.
You okay?
Check out this photo
on his phone.
There's a reflection in the blood pool
of the mntenance hanger.
It looks like
there's something on top.
That's not something.
That's someone.
Perfect vantage point
for a shooter.
Let's do this.
Surface is pristine.
No latents.
I've got a bandage.
I spoke to Agent Caldwell
this morning.
He had the same bandage.
If this is about
Manny Ortega,
I already told
Lieutenant Caine...
Ortega murder's
been solved.
I think I know who shot Horatio.
Oh, come on.
You don't think
I killed Horatio?
I've been tracking those
fused alloys for months.
He's helping.
You were trying to track down
the same supplier
Ortega.
Yeah.
And maybe
you got jealous.
I mean, you could want
the case for yourself,
you could be using the collar
to get promoted.
It wouldn't be the first time
a Fed crawled over the body
of a good cop,would it?
You watch your mouth.
Don't talk to me like that.
I'll talk to you
any way I see fit, young lady.
Now, if you've got
nothing else...
Oh, but I do.
It's the release form
for Horatio's body.
It was signed for
by an Agent Dean Redland.
We've matched
the handwriting to you.
The body's out
back, sir.
I don't have to say
another word to you.
I would love that.
In the meantime,
I'm going to get a warrant
for your phone.
You do that.
I've got Caldwell's PDA.
Okay.
If the guy did it, he was
working with someone.
Let's find out who.
Forensics?
No, surface computing.
Oh.
Hey, wait
a minute.
Check out that text.
"It's done."
Yeah, the time stamp
says it was sent
at the same time
H was shot.
And the text log gives us
the recipient's number.
Let's call it, see what we get.
Yeah, this is Wolfe.
Hello?
Ryan?
Yeah.
It all makes sense now.
How you got there so fast,
why you released the body.
Eric, I want you
to relax,
'cause this is not how it looks.
Really?
Because it looks like you and Caldwell
are responsible for Horatio's murder.
Really? 'Cause you're wrong.
He texted you, "It's done."
Yeah, what does,
"It's done" mean, Wolfe?
I was following orders.
Orders from who, Wolfe?
Orders from who, Wolfe?!
Hmm? From who?!
From Horatio.
I don't believe anything
you're saying.
You tell us what you know.
He's alive.
What?
Horatio is alive.
The M.E. was an ATF plant.
Ortega was sending
someone to kill him.
Horatio Caine.
Y quiero saber cuando
esta hecho.
(I want to know it's done.)
Saris wanted him dead, too.
The only way he was
going to survive is
he was going to stage
his own execution.
Every gang that Saris sold
those fused alloys to
are coming after you.
Including someone even
closer to home.
Find the fused alloys,
take down this
entire operation.
But why me?
Because you have a problem
with fused alloys.
And you're a dead shot.
I'm going underground
to flush Saris out.
Caldwell did
the shooting.
I was responsible
for the blood.
That's why I left
the interrogation.
What about the others?
No one knows anything
till this over. Agreed?
Where's Horatio now?
He could be anywhere.
Dad. I heard a noise.
It's me, son.
You're okay.
Horatio?
We didn't think
we'd see you again.
We did just what
you said to do.
We waited
and now we're leaving.
I need more time,
Julia.
What am I supposed
to tell Ron?
I don't want you
to see Ron.
That man is my husband.
And that is your
problem, Julia.
I need four more hours.
Mom, just give
him more time.
Hang on, son.
I need to talk to your mom
alone for a minute.
What's this?
This is the key to a safe place.
There's been a change in plans.
I want you and Kyle to go there
and wait for my call.
Where are you going to go?
I'm going underground.
Thank you for coming,
Miguel.
You called, I'm here.
Lieutenant,
my foundation represents vital
Cuban-American interests from Miami.
Does this affect
my community?
Everyone is effected
by this, Miguel.
I see.
You saved my life three
years ago, Lieutenant.
And I meant it when I said,
"Anything you need."
Those bullets need to come
off the street now
On the phone you mentioned
$10 million.
If you don't mind
me asking,
why can't you go to the police
department for this money?
My... situation
is complicated.
Lieutenant,
I trust you completely.
You will retrieve
these bullets.
Lives will be spared.
If it's the last thing I do.
All right, what do you people
want from me?
You sold some fused
alloy rounds
to a buyer in Miami.
Now, what kind of businessman
would I be
if I gave  my customers, huh?
Then, uh,
Eric here is going to take you on
a little ride through gang
Let you sit up front.
You know in the
"informant" seat.
Let's go.
Horatio.
Back from the dead.
Frank Tripp called.
Said you were gone.
I didn't want to
believe him.
Yelina, the only thing
that matters right now
is Ron Saris believes it.
Right.
With you gone,
he drops his guard
and walks into your trap.
That's my plan.
Is this the cash
for Saris?
That's the money.
What if he asks me
where it comes from?
You convince him you're
a foreign entity looking to buy.
Military perhaps?
Perhaps.
But the $10 million
is incentive.
You won't have a problem.
When I meet with him
where will you be?
I'll be close by.
Yelina, be careful.
Sit up tall, Ortega.
Gang town's coming up.
You can do what you want
to me, man.
It's too late for you guys.
Too late for what?
Balance of power has
already shifted.
Shut up.
Tell us where to find the rest
of those fused alloys.
Stay with him!
Hey, I need you to stay calm--
I'm gonna help you out, all right?
Help me!
Turn your face.
Turn your face away.
Watch your face.
All right.
Seat belt.
Your seat belt.
Come on.
Stay put!
Here we go,
come on.
Watch your legs.
Ortega!
Get down!
Everybody get down!
Everything's gonna be okay now.
All right? You're safe.
All right?
Yeah.
3104!
Shots fired.
Officer needs assistance.
Fourth and Bay.
They openeup
on that truck.
Driver's dead,
guard's injured.
Money's gone.
Perfect ambush.
Fused alloys?
Yeah. They went right through
that bulletproof armor.
All right. Thanks.
Yeah.
You okay?
I'll be fine.
Any information you can give
us will be real helpful.
We stopped at a red.
Something was wrong, you know?
The light just wouldn't
turn green.
It was like
we were set up.
And then
they just started shooting.
Run it, run the red!
Relax.
It's bulletproof
glass. We're safe.
We're going to find
whoever did this.
I promise.
H?
I lost him.
I lost Ortega.
How?
Woman got trapped in her car.
If I didn't save her,
she was gonna die.
Okay, so you did
the right thing.
Let's contact Metro,
see if they can help us.
Why Wolfe?
Why didn't you come to me?
Eric, you were the
obvious choice,
and there was a chance
this was going to fail.
I didn't want
that for you.
It still may.
Let's make sure that it doesn't.
Got something-- clean round.
Well, we get a match,
we might get a shooter.
You know what I don't get?
Why kill the driver?
Fused alloys pierce armor
and kill people, Calleigh.
They can't open that door.
So they needed the
keys to get the cash?
That's exactly right.
I've got epithelials
on this glass.
You get a name, maybe we'll get
closer to those bullets.
Todd Keener.
Age 22, gang affiliation.
The Crypt Kings?
Hold on. The Crypt Kings--
that's not part
of Ortega's gang.
That means
these bullets are everywhere.
Mr. Keener, you know
you left evidence of yourself
at the armed robbery today.
That means we've got you
for felony murder.
I didn't shoot nobody.
Then tell us who did.
I don't rat out
my boys, either.
Oh, yeah?
Well, cooperating's
all you've got.
Well, I guess
we're both losers then.
Take him.
You cops-- you
just don't get it.
You're on
the short end.
Gangs got all the ammo.
You're nothing but ducks
on a pond.
I said get him out of here.
These bullets
are everywhere, H.
What do we do?
I am working on it.
Mr. Saris?
You know, on the phone,
you didn't sound quite this lovely.
Did you come prepared
to do business?
Depends on who you are.
What's more
important is,
who I represent.
I'm listening.
I have a client who wishes to purchase a
large amount of fused alloy rounds.
And who is this client?
Whoever he might be.
His money's American.
And, uh, how many of these supposed rounds
are you looking to buy?
All of Ortega's supply.
Word is, you have
possession of them.
What do you think I am?
You think I'm stupid?
Who are you?
Really?
And who sent you here?
I represent a consortium of
global military interests.
And I'm authorized
to pay you any price.
Okay.
I' sell you all
of Ortega's bullets
and all the gangs
that he sold them to.
Oh, right.
I'll approach those entities
on my own, thank you.
Entities?
The Crypt Kings,
The Rhodes Gang.
I mean, they'll be stripping
all that money off you,
and then they'll strip
everything else... off you.
Let me guess.
You'll buy back the bullets
and sell them to me
at double the price.
Gorgeous, I'm just trying
to protect you.
Sure you are.
You get those
bullets back,
and I promise you...
I'll make you a
very wealthy man.
That's just a
down payment.
Okay.
How am I gonna get in touch
with you?
That's my phone.
You text this number when you've dealt
with the gangs...
and have the bullets.
I keep a boat down
at the marina, okay?
That's where I'm gonna be.
Ortega escaped when the radio car
was rear-ended.
Yeah? Well, there's blood
on the passenger side door,
so Ortega cut himself
getting out.
He's on foot,
headed east.
Let's see what he left behind.
Got a blood drop here.
Oh, yeah, look at that.
That spatter pattern,
angled impact.
Long ellipse with a tail.
Ortega was running for his life.
In this direction.
Got another one.
Let's keep going.
The blood stops here.
Must have stolen a car
from here and gotten away.
It's a dead end.
This is the traffic light
Horatio wanted us to check into?
Yeah, from the armored car
robbery, but luckily for us,
it's an intelligent
intersection,
and it interacts
with a PCS.
The priority control system?
Yup. Those hand-held devices.
When the user pushed a button,
the traffic signal changes.
It's used mainly
by emergency personnel.
Metro reported
a system override.
Eastbound light is green,
and all the others are red.
So that armored car
didn't stand a chance, did it?
If somebody altered the signal,
how do we get an ID?
Well, you know, the beautiful thing
about intelligent
They keep
a record.
They got a database of
every cop, firefighter,
medical personnel.
The emitter's registered
to an ATF agent.
Jake Berkeley.
It's been a while.
I'm sorry.
For just disappearing like that.
I had to go
off the grid.
Is that a euphemism
for not picking up the phone?
I had to rejoin ATF.
I'm back with my undercover
detail with the the Crypt Kings.
Yeah, I figured as much.
An infrared traffic device
was used today
in an ambushed armed robbery.
A man was killed.
What has that got to do with me?
We ran a check
and traced the device
back to you.
I was assigned that thing
from the bureau.
One of the bikers took it.
I haven't seen it since.
The Crypt Kings look good
for this.
We need your help.
That could take some time.
We don't have any time.
Whato you want me to do?
Well, how far undercover
are you?
What are you implying?
Exactly what you think
I'm implying.
I'll see what I can find out.
Crypt Kings.
Howdy doody, fellas.
You're all very scary.
Very scary.
You got all the
bullets, right?
Money first, my friend.
I'm gonna need
all the rounds
that Ortega sold you
guys last month.
Well, minus what we used
in today's heist.
Armored car
job downtown.
Tell you what, for you,
I'll make it
eight bucks a round,
but you got to do the math.
Oh, I've done the math
for both of
us, you moron.
Here it is, okay?
the penny,
double what u paid.
There we go.
I guess we got stones
doing this deal
in broad daylight.
With Caine dead,
are you kidding me?
It's gonna be like
the wild, wild West.
We're all gonna get
rich, me first.
Come on, come on!
Get your guys going.
I got three more
stops in an hour.
Horatio, connection's been made.
Hey, Eric?
Did you get anything
on Julia Winston's Mercedes?
No, nothing, I'm
still waiting.
Where does that leave us?
I'm not sure yet.
Take ???
and...???
Wait ???
???
You ???
That's ???
Ok, ???
???
Who's ???
Diaz's ???
That's ???
We ???
I ???
???
Diaz's cell phone.
Okay, we should
work backwards.
We should do the most
recent phone calls first.
Only one phone call
received today.
From Ortega.
All right, let's ping it
and see if we get a hit.
Okay.
Triangulating.
Searching.
Can you get a clear
picture up here?
Yeah, sure.
Ortega's at an airstrip at the edge
of the Glades.
And so am I.
Hands up! Let me see 'em!
You'll be dead
before you hit the ground.
Taken down by a dead man.
I didn't do it, Caine.
Must be millions
in these bags.
The gangs bought
a lot of bullets.
Ron Saris--
he hijacked everything.
You don't know
the half of it.
Thank you, Juan.
Book him.
Takes care of Ortega.
Saved ATF a bundle--
nice job.
I've got some
bad news for you.
Those bullets
are still on the street.
What? Who's got them?
I'll take it from here.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I brought you something.
Three .45s,
two Mac Tens,
full auto.
Took them from the
Crypt King safe house.
All these guns were used
in the ambush today.
This is amazing.
I'll compare it to the fused
alloy round I've got,
see if I get a match.
You get a match,
I'll give you a whole crew.
How'd you get out
without getting noticed?
I didn't.
They're looking
for me right now,
and if they find me, I'm dead.
That's an incredible sacrifice
to make for the case.
I didn't do it
for the case, Calleigh.
I did it for you.
Thank you.
So what happens now?
Well, ATF will send me
somewhere,
put me on ice
for a while.
Six months, a year.
But there's
no guarantee.
No, there's never
a guarantee.
I was kind of hoping
that you would wait.
I feel like the
last couple months,
all I've been
doing is waiting.
It's terrifying for me.
I wonder every day if
I will see you again,
if something
happens to you
if I would
know about it.
I can't live like that.
What happened to your face?
I had an altercation
with a thug.
It's nothing.
Horatio was so stupid to think that I'd
ever leave you.
Forget him.
Forget that name, okay?
He's dead to us, okay?
You know what?
This right there...
that's only the beginning.
What's in those
boxes, Ron?
Thought you'd never ask.
Fused alloy bullets.
That's the whole shipment.
A whole shipment
in all those boxes,
and we've got more
down in the hull of the boat.
You don't need
to do this.
I've got money.
My money this time.
So, what's our plan?
We're gonna sail
out of here,
you and me,
all these bullets.
I've got a buyer
in South America
who has an eless need
for fused alloys.
Money and me.
And bullets.
What more could
a woman want, right?
A divorce.
A what?
A wh...
What the hell is this?
It's called irreconcilable
differences, Ron.
No, don't do this.
What are you doing?
No.
No, it's not gonna go
down like this, Horatio.
It's my boat-- you
gonna shoot me?
Don't do it, Ron.
Shoot me in the back?
Ron!
We searched everywhere.
There's still no body.
We got to keep looking, Eric.
I'm with you, H,
what do you want to do?
Whatever it takes.
We'll find him.
You and me?
You and me, Eric.
This never ends, does it?
And it never will.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入