Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
(# ''Lil' Red Riding hood''
by Bowling for Soup)
# Who's that I see
walking in these woods?
# Why, it's Little Red Riding hood
# Hey there, Little Red Riding Hood
# You sure are looking good
# You're everything
that a big bad wolf would want
Listen to me.
# Little Red Riding Hood
# I don't think even big girls should
# Go walking
in these spooky old woods alone
# What big eyes you have
You're obsessed with him,
I'm not obsessed,
I'm just highly interested.
Come on, Let's settle this.
Girls, please, sit, sit.
Let Zela read your palms.
Oh, no. Forget it. This is stupid.
so are you. sit down.
OK, Zela, this is it.
My friend here is basically obsessed
with this guy that won't call her back
and we need to know if she should forget
him cold or hold out for the next 20 years.
Well, anyways, whatever you see,
just say 'Forget his ass'.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I need you to read my friend's.
Blood.
- Excuse me?
- I see blood.
so much blood.
OK, that's nice, but...
You too.
You're both in danger.
Need to know?
No, Back to the guy.
It's not the guy.
It's... it's the beast you should fear.
OK.
We're done here.
- Come on, Becky. Let's go.
- Beware the moon.
It feeds in the moonlight.
You can't tell people this shit.
Jenny.
Lay off the crack pipe.
Jenny!
- I'm gonna lock up in the back.
- OK, José.
Hey, looks like you got a visitor.
Hey, there, boy.
Where did you come from?
Come here.
Oh.
Zipper? Zip?
Zipper. Hey, hey, Zipper.
Hey.
- Oh, there you are, I'm sorry.
- Oh, no, He's adorable.
Come here.
I'm sorry. One minute he's here.
the next minute...
Wh... Hey, uh, Brooke, right?
- Do I know you?
- Oh, yeah, We go to school together.
I sit behind you in Government,
Algebra and French.
Oh, really?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, Brooke Mueller, Jimmy Myers.
M- u, M-y,
I've sat behind you for, like, three years.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- OK.
- Hey, Brooke, are you ready?
Yeah, almost, Five minutes.
- I'll see you at school.
- OK, yeah, No, I know.
Hey, I know you.
- From P.E.
- His name's Billy.
- Uh, it's Jimmy.
- You're the dodgeball crotch target.
- You should really wear a cup.
- Stop it, Bo, OK?
I'm just looking out for him, He can't help it,
Every school's got one, the derogatory 'it,'
A geek on his way to fag town.
- Look, I'm not gay.
- Bummer.
You mean you're just
an ass wimp-wad for no reason?
- Yep.
- That sucks.
- Boo!
- Whoa!
You're such a dick, Bo.
Just ignore him, Jimmy.
- I think your dog is gay too.
What's with the Make-A-Wish
charity case, Brooke?
- Hey, Ellie.
- Hi.
- Hello?
- Ellie.
- Hi, Jimmy.
- I'm waiting.
Yeah, I know, I stopped by Tinsel
on my way, to see Jake.
- But I'm your brother.
- I'll be there soon.
- Well, how soon?
- I said soon, OK?
- Do you know what can happen to me?
- Yes.
I know what can happen
to a teenager on Hollywood Boulevard.
- Do you?
- OK, Quit whining.
- Fine.
- Yeah. Bye.
Perfect.
- Excellent, Excellent!
- Cool.
50 grand well-spent.
- OK, Looking good up there now.
- You got it.
- Ellie.
- Hi.
Hi.
- How's it going?
- We're not even close to finished.
I got four days work and the opening's
in two, I am drowning in stress.
Kiss me again.
- What are you doing here?
- That's good, I told you, That's good.
- I haven't seen you in days.
I wanted to make sure you were still alive.
What is this?
It's a medieval torture device.
Which could actually be fun later.
Come on,
I'll give you the two-second tour.
Spanish lnquisition,
Frankenstein's laboratory,
Dracula’s coffin,
What's that?
Oh, that.
That is a sterling replica to commemorate
the 50th anniversary of the Wolf Man.
It was donated by the Chaney estate.
Wow.
Planet Hollywood
has nothing on you guys.
Shh, we don't mention them here.
so, I was thinking,
I'll be here for the opening,
and you'll be here.
So how about we be here together?
If I was actually going to the opening.
What do you mean? You have to go.
It's your big night. You have to show off.
All I wanna do is crawl into bed
and disappear for three days.
Well, even better.
I'll crawl in too.
Excuse me,
I need a signature on this.
Damn. Can you hold on for one second?
-  Right there.
-  Thanks.
Yeah.
Jake?
Is there something wrong?
No. There's nothing wrong. I'm just
stressed out with work and this madness.
I just... I need some time
and some space.
OK.
Just call me, when you feel like it,
you know. No pressure.
I waited over an hour for you.
I'm sorry, OK?
- Do you want to drop it?
- For over an hour, I waited.
Yeah, well, most teenagers
have friends who give them a lift home.
- But then I couldn't inconvenience you.
- Not tonight, Jimmy, Can we just not fight?
Watch out!
-  Are you OK?
- Yeah,
Zipper.
It's OK, boy.
Someone could be hurt.
Find my cellphone. Call for help.
- Hello?
-  Oh, God, Help me, Please!
I'm coming.
Help me, please!
I'm trying to get to you.
- Are you OK?
- Please just get me out of here, I'm stuck.
OK. OK.
Oh, God, Help!
- Help me, God.
- Can you feel your legs?
- I think so, The dashboard's just caved in.
- OK.
- Do you have a jack?
- Uh, yeah, Yeah, It's in the trunk.
All right, I'm gonna try to go get it, OK?
I'll be right back.
OK, Hurry, please!
Oh, God.
- Hello? Hello? No, no, I can't hear you.
- Shit, AT&&T...
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, stop! stop!
- Jesus, people, what's wrong with you?
- 911 emergency. Hello? Hello?
- Hello? Wait, wait, Can you hear me now?
- 911 emergency. Yes, I can, sir.
- All right, listen, there's been a wreck.
- Where, sir?
I'm on Mulholland Drive,
just east of Coldwater.
- Jesus.
- Hey, calm down, It's just me.
- I called for help.
- Oh, good.
What's going on out there?
I couldn't get the trunk open.
but help's on the way, OK?
Just hold on a few more minutes.
- Do you hear that?
- What?
I hear dripping, like leaking.
Do you smell gas? I smell gas.
Oh, God, The car's gonna blow up.
- No, no, no, The car is not gonna blow up.
- Uh, actually it could.
- Jesus Christ, get me the fuck out of here!
- OK, all right, all right.
Let me try.
Uh, hi.
- If I could get up, underneath...
- Just do it!
OK, OK. All right.
- Wait, All right, I think I'm getting it.
- Oh, God. Please, please.
Wait,
can you be still for a second?
You try flipping your car down a mountain
and then being fucking still.
Maybe you guys should hurry up.
-  All right. Calm down.
-  I am calm!
-  I think I'm getting it.
All right. OK.
- OK, I got it.
- Oh, my God. Thank you.
Oh, help me with the seat belt.
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit, OK.
- OK, OK.
- Oh.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah.
- My legs... There's help. They hurt.
The police are coming.
Yeah, well.
I hope you guys have insurance.
What? No, no, it was an accident. We hit
an animal, or it hit us. I'm not even sure.
- It wasn't a dog, was it?
- Actually, it was...
Ellie! Hold on to me.
Jimmy!
No!
Ellie.
Go! Go!
- Do you think she...?
- No, No, go, Go, go, go,
Oh, Jimmy.
Shit, look at your arm.
The police.
No!.
- They're ready for us now.
- They said it was pretty nasty.
Let me get this straight. It took a bite
out of your arm, but you didn't see it at all?
Well, it all happened so fast
and it was dark.
Well, I saw it, It was a wolf, but bigger.
It was like a monster wolf.
Yeah, Jimmy,
I have your statement already.
Fine, don't believe me.
I know what I saw.
What happened to her...
What kind of an animal could do that?
A mountain lion, a bear, maybe.
There hasn't been a wolf sighting
in southern California in over 70 years.
- Mountain lion, my ass.
- Jimmy.
Please.
Why don't you go check on Zipper?
Don't worry.
Whatever it was, we'll find it.
Hey, buddy, are you OK?
Zipper?
- What's wrong?
Hey, smell, It's just me.
Hey! Hey, look what you did.
That's enough with the biting.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Hey, you guys be safe.
-  All right, come on. Let's go.
Hey.
- Hey, Zipper. Come on in.
Hey, Zipper, come on in.
Hey. Whoa.
Freak.
- Well, good night.
- Hey.
What?
Don't you wanna talk
about what happened tonight?
- What's there to talk about?
- Jimmy, we were attacked.
We saw a girl get torn apart.
You wanna talk about the bear
or the mountain lion?
Look, I know you're mad at me,
but I didn't see what you saw.
I'm sorry,
but I don't know what else to say.
OK, well, uh, thanks for the talk.
Good night.
Oh, come on, Jimmy.
I'm trying here.
'Unsolved...'
OK.
Jesus, '1600 animal attacks...'
'...large wolf-like animals...'
Oh, my God.
Jesus.
- Oh, sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
- What are you doing here?
I just... I needed to talk to you.
I found the extra key under the mat.
I'm really sorry.
I just, I feel so terrible
about how we left things tonight.
- Jake, what's going on?
- I'm just scared, Ellie.
I'm scared.
I never expected
to meet a woman like you.
Jake, you're the only good thing
that's happened in my life in a long time.
I'm scared too.
I'm terrified,
because all the good things
keep going away.
I'm not going anywhere.
Here in Los Angeles,
a young woman was attacked and killed
by an unidentified wild animal
when her car ran off the road last night,
high in the Hollywood hills.
the victim's name has yet to be released.
It happened on a remote stretch of
Mulholland Drive, shortly before midnight.
Animal control officers speculate
that it might have been a bear
that wandered into the area
in search of water.
It is the first such fatal attack
in Los Angeles...
- Hey.
- How are you doing? Did you sleep OK?
I woke up in the bushes.
You woke up where?
Are you feeling OK?
I'm calling Dr, Steinberg.
No, no, I'm fine. Really.
Actually... I feel kinda great.
OK.
But I'm gonna make an appointment. They
said we should follow up with another shot.
For all we know,
that wolf could've had rabies.
Oh. Oh, so now it's a wolf.
Jimmy, I never said it wasn't.
I just said I didn't see it.
It was more like a werewolf.
And I found this website last night
and according to legend.
a werewolf feeds during the lunar cycle -
that's the three nights around the full moon.
Last night was the first moon
of the lunar cycle.
Why can't you just download porn
like other teenage boys?
Excuse me for trying
to make conversation.
OK, so what would a werewolf
be doing in LA?
shouldn't it be off in the countryside
somewhere, terrorizing helpless maidens?
Maybe it's a hip werewolf, Maidens come
here with the perfectly implanted breasts.
- You should get to school,
- Hey, I was bitten by a werewolf.
If that's not good enough for a sick day...
I could be cursed.
Everybody's cursed, Jimmy.
It's called life.
No, I mean by the mark of the beast.
Is that what the kids
are calling it these days?
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
-  Whoa, Hey, Ellie.
- Hey, Kyle.
Hey, '70s retro week is booking up, Do we
want Keith Partridge or Marcia Brady?
- Only one slot left.
- Marcia, Marcia, Marcia.
You look different today,
saucy, I like it.
- Yeah, it's new, Gauze look.
- Nice, What happened?
- Oh, you don't wanna know.
- Hey, are you OK?
Yeah. Actually, I'm fine.
Incoming psycho publicist, one o'clock.
...no trades, Oh, I have to go.
Yeah, OK, Goodbye.
Hi,
I didn't recognize you
with your hair down.
I just wanted to drop by to make sure we
were set for Scott’s pre-interview tonight.
- Absolutely, Nine o'clock.
- Great, Is that what you're gonna wear?
Hey, I heard that you're dating
Jake Taylor, Is that true?
- I hope it's nothing serious.
- Why not?
I guess it was only a matter of time
before he got to you.
- He always did prefer the vulnerable ones.
- OK, well, I'll see you tonight, Joannie.
I'm only saying this because I care.
Is there anything else, Joannie?
No, Tonight, Don't be late.
- OK, Thank you.
- OK.
Putting on weight, Kyle?
- What a piece of work.
- I do not like that woman.
- No, Apparently Jake didn't either.
- I didn't even know that she knew him.
- Do you think she's right about him?
- No, The woman's cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs.
But I'm not the one dating him.
I just know he's not the only guy in town.
What smells so good?
I... I don't smell anything.
I get these.
It's nothing, I'll live.
The blood freaking you out?
- Hey, Brooke, you need some change?
- Hey, Jimmy.
That'd be great.
Stupid thing won't take my dollar.
Oh, yeah, OK, Actually...
- I'll hold those.
- Thanks.
Werewolves, huh?
Oh, it's just a stupid report I'm doing.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
No, keep your money.
It's on me, Thanks.
- Geek juice.
- Trying out for the wrestling team, Jimmy?
- Oh, no, I don't wrestle.
Oh, I'd think all that male-to-male contact
would be right up your alley.
Is, uh... Is that the appeal for you?
Oh, Back talk.
Haven't you been team captain
for, like, two years now?
Nicely done, Jimmy.
Did you just attempt a confrontation?
- Yeah, maybe.
- Let me know when you're sure.
Just ignore him, Jimmy.
Let's get out of here
before we get homo-stained.
Hey, Hey.
(# ''freaks come Out At Night''
by Whodini)
# Now the party's jumping,
the place is packed
# But when the crowd's like this
I'm ready to rap
# But before I could
bust a thyme on the mic
# freaks are all over me
like white on rice
# freaks come in all shapes
and sizes and colors
# But what I like about them most
is that they're real good lovers
# they do it in the park,
they do it in the dark
# But most freaks are known
for breaking hearts
Joannie.
- Joannie.
- There you are.
What is this? Come as
your favorite endangered species?
Obnoxious, isn't it?
I just feel a little underdressed
without a tail.
Well, that's part of your charm,
Take this, I will tell Scott that you're here.
Well, I think you look fantastic.
- What are you doing here?
- I needed to see you.
What about the opening?
Disappearing for a few days.
- That didn't go over so well, did it?
- You know what? It's fine.
We've only been seeing each other
a couple of months, you need your space.
I get it, It's fine.
Please don't do that. Don't try
to make everything OK when it's not.
Can I talk to you in private for a second?
Ellie.
That was my MO for a long time. When
anything would get too close or too serious.
I would just run away.
For...
For a variety of reasons
that I can't even begin to go into.
I don't want to do that with us. This thing,
you and me, this is special, Ellie.
and I just don't want to lose you,
so I was hoping that, maybe,
you could just bear with me
for a little while longer.
I guess I'm learning about these things
as we go along.
Well, maybe I'll finish up here
and we can go someplace to talk.
OK. Thank you, Ellie.
Well, hi, there, Remember me?
Uh...
- Jenny Tate, Becky Morton's friend.
- Right. Of course, Jenny.
- It's good to see you again, I was actually...
- Jake.
- Hi.
- Hi. Long time no see.
Sorry to interrupt an awkward moment,
but we're ready for you.
I have to go.
- Ellie.
- I'm working.
So, Becky cannot stop talking about you.
She's gonna die
when she finds out you were here.
Excuse me, I have to go.
I know it was only a couple of dates, but
Becky is really bummed you haven't called.
Next time you speak with her, tell her I'm
sorry, but I've taken myself off the market.
Now I'm nummed.
Thanks for coming,
I appreciate it, see you later.
Scott, this is Ellie Myers
from the Craig Kilborn show.
- Oh, hi, How are you?
- Hi, It's a pleasure to meet you.
I've been a huge fan of yours
ever since happy Days.
Thank you. Listen, I appreciate you
meeting me here, I couldn't bail on tonight.
It's fine.
You guys have a nice chat.
I'll be over here if you need me.
OK.
- Have a seat.
- Thank you.
Craig is so excited
to have you on his show.
I think it's gonna be
just a fabulous line-up.
You'll be going on third,
after Ashton Kutcher and Carrot Top.
- Third?
- Uh...
I thought that we would start
with a Chachi clip,
and then move on
to something from Charles in charge.
- Original.
- And, uh...
and then we could...
segue into what you're doing now.
What are you doing now?
You know, you're a beautiful girl.
I mean, you've got this aura thing
happening, l...
I just can't quite put my finger on it.
Not when you can use your whole hand.
Thank you, I think that's really
all we needed to discuss
and I'll see you in the studio.
- OK, You got it.
- OK.
Wanna finish your drink?
No, Bye.
Okey-doke.
Excuse me.
-  Hey, where are you going?
-  Call us!
Ellie.
Ellie, wait up.
Jake, I really don't feel well tonight,
I just wanna get home.
Be careful with this one.
He's trouble.
- Who's the leopard?
- Someone I met before I met you.
- They keep popping up, don't they?
- Ellie, that was a previous life.
Please, you gotta trust me on this.
You know what?
I think it's my turn to be weird.
I'm gonna take a cue from you
and disappear for a few days.
Ellie, people can change.
I really don't wanna get into it right now.
Close, close, close, close!
Oh, my God.
Hello? Hello? Anybody there?
Hello? Hello?
Get me the fuck out of here!
Open up!
- Hey.
- Hi.
Are you doing homework?
I'm just reading up
on how you kill a werewolf.
Silver, right?
No, you actually have to separate the head
from the heart, silver just hurts a lot.
It might not be such a bad deal.
Think about it.
increased strength, heightened senses,
an unnatural sexual allure.
When do we sprout hair and pointy ears?
It's all a little sketchy,
but maybe never, maybe tomorrow.
The experts can't really agree
on that one.
You're starting to freak me out, Jimmy.
This is fiction, Myth.
We live in reality.
Come back to the other side.
I know, I know, but the line between
fiction and fact has always been a thin one.
Don't we have enough problems? Do you
really wanna add this one to the list?
OK, here.
Check this out. Here.
It's a five-pointed star.
It's a pentagram.
It's the mark of the beast.
Jimmy, this is ridiculous.
You need...
Whoa, Jesus.
Wait, is this for real?
Last night was difficult, OK?
The wreck, the girl dying,
it brought up a lot of stuff.
- No, no, no, Ellie, don't start with that.
- I know we don't talk about it enough.
- It has nothing to do with Mom and Dad.
- I miss them too.
Your hand.
It's a creepy coincidence.
This is some pretty freaky shit.
Admit it.
OK, OK.
Let's put it to the test.
I bought this frame myself,
three years ago.
It's from Tiffany's.
It's sterling silver.
Now, if I'm a werewolf.
I shouldn't be able to pick it up, right?
- It should hurt me, right?
- According to chapter four, yeah.
Go to bed, Jimmy.
It's late.
shut up!
shut up
Don't forget.
I'm working the opening of Tinsel tonight.
- I've gotta take Craig down the red carpet.
- OK.
Hello?
Hey, Jake's been calling all morning,
says he needs to talk.
Well, I don't need to talk to him,
What's with the gypsies?
Oh, it's auditions for Craig's séance
segment. What is with this new look?
- What are you talking about?
- I'm not complaining, I think you look hot.
- You're in danger.
- Excuse me?
It will come for you.
Don't let this getup fool you, I'm not a joke.
I've got the gift, I blame my mother.
Why are you talking to me?
You bear the markings of the beast.
Look, I'm not trying to freak you out,
but you've been infected. You're cursed.
You've got to sever the line of the beast.
It's the only way to break the curse.
OK, all psychics
back in their seats, please.
The beast is human too.
Don't forget that.
- And it's closer to you than you think.
- If you could just follow me.
Shouldn't you psychically know
when you're annoying someone?
Thank you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Excuse me, Miss, Get up and get out.
Look at him.
Yeah!
Oh, Brooke, hey.
- Are you stalking me?
- Maybe.
What's going on, Brooke?
You going fruit fly on me?
Actually, we were just talking,
but, if you don't mind... shoo.
Oh, you are asking for it, Abercrombie.
Come on, Bo.
You're really becoming transparent.
How about a little
identity intervention, OK?
'Cause all this internalized homophobia's
giving you away.
- You better watch your ass.
- What's going on?
I'm just giving Jimmy some pointers.
- He's here to try out for the team.
- Really? You?
Are you sure
you want to do that, Jimmy?
Oh, sure he does, coach.
I'll tell you what.
I'll wrestle him.
No, Louie, you and Jimmy take the mat.
Jimmy, suit up.
He's so dead.
- OK, limp wrist, stay away from my groin.
Take him down, Louie.
Take him down.
- Have you had enough?
- Uh-uh.
- Let him up.
- Watch his nails, Lou!
He might scratch your eyes out!
- You OK, Lou?
- All right.
- Let me take a crack, coach.
- Are you up for it, Jimmy?
Yeah.
Go for it, Bo.
- Come on, fairy, shake your dust.
- You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Come on, fag, What?
Do you like that? Huh?
Wait, no...
You know the best part about being a fairy?
You get to fly.
Jimmy! Jimmy! Jimmy! Jimmy! Jimmy!
- Ashton Kutcher's up first.
- God, he's so overexposed.
stick to his film career as talk points.
Don't linger on the TV stuff.
And if he doesn't mention the lnternet
sex scandal, just don't bring it up.
OK, you know what?
I've done this before.
- OK, I bump Baio.
- What?
I'm living dangerously.
Carrot Top's rehearsal was funny.
I'm gonna let the Top go long.
Randy's dealing with it.
- OK.
- My mouth's dry.
Thanks.
- You want me to do that?
- I got it. Ouch. Dammit! Look.
What happened?
- Do you have a tissue?
- Just stare at it.
It's the Late Late Show
with Craig Kilborn.
OK, Go, Go! You're on.
Mr Craig Kilborn.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, Ellie?
What the fuck do you mean.
'Scott’s been bumped?'
- I just heard, We'll reschedule.
- Reschedule, my ass.
- I'm sorry, The show was running long.
- Then bump Carrot Top.
It's Scott Baio, He shouldn't be
going after Carrot Top anyway.
- He should be first.
- I'll make it up to you.
- Listen to me, you little...
- Don't start with me!
Hi, Ellie.
Are you OK in there?
I'm fine.
You don't sound fine.
What's the matter?
Ellie?
No!
Ellie.
Ellie, your hand.
What's wrong?
I'm just having a really bad day.
Just leave.
Can I help?
Get the hell out of here! Get out!
Hey, Jake.
- Jimmy.
- Hey.
Cool place.
Are all clubs like this?
I sure hope not or I'm in nig trouble.
So what's up, Jimmy?
What are you doing here?
Yeah, l... I kind of need someone
to talk to. Is that OK?
Yeah, of course it is,
step inside.
OK, look, Ellie won't admit it, but ever since
the other night things have been different.
- We're different.
- What night? What are you talking about?
- Didn't Ellie tell you?
- No, Tell me what?
We were in a wreck in the canyon.
A girl was killed.
she was ripped apart.
By...
I don't know, by some kind of animal.
Whatever it was bit me and now
things have been happening to me.
Things I can't explain.
Jake, I know it sounds crazy.
nut I think it was a...
a werewolf.
Hm,
- What does your sister say about all this?
- You know Ellie.
Deny and avoid. It's her thing. But it got
her too and now I think we're cursed.
Look, I almost
took a guy's head off in gym.
I'm not the kind of guy to take
another guy's head off, I mean, look at me.
What if it comes back?
I mean, I know enough to know that it's
a who, not a what, so it could be pissed off.
It may want to finish what it started.
Jimmy, I think
you just need to calm down.
I think the best thing we can do
is just call your sister.
Get her down here and maybe the three
of us should just sit down and discuss it.
I don't want to discuss this, I've been
cursed, something bad is gonna happen.
I can... Look, I can feel it.
Jimmy, listen to yourself.
Werewolves?
- This was a mistake, sorry I bothered you.
- Jimmy.
No, no, Thanks.
Jesus Christ.
- Bo, What are you doing here?
- I just wanted to, kind of, talk.
About that stuff you said today.
What stuff?
About me,
I was just wondering how you knew.
No one else did, just you.
And I've been so shitty to you,
And then I thought,
why wouldn't you know?
It takes one to know one, right?
- Of course, you would know.
- Know what?
Whoa, Whoa,
What are you doing?
I'm gay.
I just can't keep it in anymore, I had to tell
you, you're the only other gay guy I know.
Whoa, OK, stop. No, I'm not gay.
Not that there's anything wrong with it.
- This is hard for me. Don't be like this.
- Trust me, Bo. I'm not gay. I'm cursed.
I know, sure feels like that, doesn't it?
Not being able to tell anyone.
- Talk to anyone about it.
- No, I'm cursed by the mark of the beast.
Bo.
I'm a werewolf.
Come on, Jimmy. You don't
have to pretend anymore. Not with me.
No, it's part of the curse. I'm appealing.
I have an unnatural sexual allure.
Yeah, yeah, you do, I know.
Look, dude, I'm happy for you.
You be gay. It's a good thing.
Unfortunately, I got my own shit
to take care of, so best of luck. Yay, go gay.
And I'll see you.
Hey, Jimmy, wait.
Jimmy.
- Liar.
Hey, Zipper.
Hey.
Hey, that's mine.
Hey, Hey, Zipper. Drop it.
Hey, No, drop it.
Zip.
Hey, Hey, come on.
Get out of it. Let's go.
No, Zipper!
Zipper.
- Zipper.
- Bo, what are you doing here?
- We're not through yet.
No, no, no.
We gotta go. Now.
- Holy shit.
- Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Go! Come on.
Fuck me.
- What the fuck was that?
- That was my dog.
- What kind of dog do you have?
- I have a regular dog.
Or he was, until he bit me.
I infected him.
- I told you. I'm a werewolf.
- Oh, yeah. Right.
- You're fucking serious.
- Yeah.
Look, I gotta find my sister.
Give me your cellphone.
Thanks, I know. Just keep your eyes on the
road, all right? Animals, they sometimes...
shit, stupid canyons. Look,
she's going to a club opening, at Tinsel.
- Oh, on the strip. Got it, I'm with you.
- OK, All right, settle down.
...killed 23 people
and wounded more than 100 on Saturday.
In breaking news,
is a wild beast terrorizing the Southland?
Another woman,
Jenny rate of Studio city,
was torn to pieces
at a charity benefit last night.
Authorities have linked the incident
to a similar attack on Mulholland Drive
just two nights ago, where Becky Morton
was mauled to death by an animal...
I'll drink, you can drive.
Ready?
Kyle, can you cover for me tonight?
I've gotta get home.
You're gonna miss Jake's big opening?
- Ellie?
- I guess.
- Good night, Ellie.
- Oh, good night.
Ellie.
Ellie, please.
You scared me.
I'm sorry,
but I needed to talk to you, Ellie.
You haven't been returning my calls.
You knew those girls, Becky and Jenny.
They're both dead.
I know, but, Ellie,
I can explain everything.
Ellie!
Ellie, Ellie!
Get out of the car, Ellie.
Please.
Look, I'm sorry about your window.
I didn't mean to do that.
but I have a lot of things
that I have to explain to you
and they're all going to sound a little crazy
so I just need you to hear me out.
Give me back my keys first.
What attacked you in the canyon
wasn't just an animal.
- What was it?
- You already know the answer to that.
You can feel the changes, can't you?
Ellie!
How's it going? These are my plus-ones
right here, all the way to the end, there.
Hey, man.
- Hey, Bo, can I use your cell?
- Uh, yeah, sure.
Hey, I'm gonna go look.
see if anybody's seen your sister,
- Hello?
- Ellie?
- Jimmy, thank God. Where are you?
- I'm at Tinsel.
- What?
- No, it's OK.
What are you doing there?
I'm on my way home.
Ellie, don't go home. Look,
I infected Zipper and he's gone werewolf.
- You gotta believe me. Look, it's all true.
- I believe you, OK?
I'd believe anything at this point.
- Jimmy, it's Jake.
- What? Jake?
he's the one who attacked us.
he's the werewolf.
- Ellie, I'm freaking out.
- Kyle should be there, OK? Just find him.
stay low.
Jake is definitely gonna be there.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Jimmy. Have you seen Ellie?
I just really need to find her, right away.
- Jake, Hi.
- Hi.
- The place looks amazing.
- Thank you.
- lncredible. Congratulations. Excuse me.
- Wait, Jimmy, I really need to...
Did I introduce you to Scott?
Scott, this is Jake.
- Hey, man. How are you doing?
- Good, thanks, Thanks for coming.
Can I excuse myself for one second?
- Jimmy?
- What am I doing here?
Do you have any idea who I had to blow
to get you in here tonight?
Who do I have to blow to get out of here?
- That thing looks real.
- I think it is.
- Find your sister?
- No, actually...
- Oh, shit, shit, shit.
- What? Is he a werewolf hunter?
No, no, He's trouble.
Tell the guys to look out for a young guy,
about yea tall, brown hair.
He's a little jumpy so be discreet.
Here, come on.
I think we can cut through here.
Come on. Come on.
We can get out the back way. Come on.
Kyle.
- Kyle, Have you seen my brother?
- Jimmy's here?
- I've gotta find him, it's an emergency.
- Ellie, you need to tell me what's going on.
- I wish I could.
- Hey, have you seen Kilborn?
He ditched me.
- ...out of here, baby.
-  Hold on. Find me...
-  Help!
-  Which way is out?
- I don't know. Here. Come on, come on.
-  Bo, over here,
- Jimmy?
Ellie.
- Please, Ellie. Don't be afraid.
- Stay away from me, Jake.
-  But it wasn't me.
- Bullshit, I saw your hands.
-  There's another one like me.
- Is that your sister?
-  I think so.
- I don't know who it is.
But that's who killed those girls.
It's trying to get to me.
Please, you have to believe me.
I'm telling you the truth.
- I don't know what to believe.
- Ellie, I was born with this curse.
I know how to control it.
I've learned to live with something terrible.
Just like you.
We're not that different.
- We can do this.
- How do you know that?
Because, Ellie.
- I love you.
- No!
- Please.
- Ellie. Come on.
Ellie.
I love you.
Please.
Jake!
Where is it?
Where are they?
-  Go! Go, go, go, go, go, go!
- Shit!
- OK, you go that way, I'll go this way.
- OK.
- Bo?
Bo?
No, don't go in there.
It's not safe.
No, Stop.
Randy, Randy, you gotta get everyone
out of there and you gotta radio for help.
Why?
Are you OK?
Come on, get up.
- Ellie!
- Jimmy.
Come on.
It's a fucking werewolf.
Jimmy!
- Have you seen my brother?
- He must be out front.
No, he's not, I've looked everywhere.
He's not out there.
- There's nobody left in there except for...
...that!
Jimmy!
Jimmy.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah.
- OK. We gotta get outta here.
- I know.
- Ellie.
- Kyle, what...
What the hell's happening?
I heard people screaming,
and then I lost Craig, I lost Craig.
- Stay away from us.
- What? Why?
Show me your hand.
- The other hand.
- Ellie.
We don't have time for this.
There's an animal on the loose.
It could be anywhere.
What? You guys hear something?
- Where the fuck did he go?
- I don't know.
Jimmy?
Come on.
- Come on, come on. Keep going.
- But it's closed.
- Shit, we can't get out. We're fucked.
- Where are we going?
I don't know, shit.
Where does this go? Come on.
- Shit,
- There should be doors. Look for a door.
- There's nothing. Look over there.
- OK.
No, they're not here.
- Weren't there three?
- What?
There's three microphones.
There's only two...
Jimmy!
- Showtime. lsn't that what they say?
- Joannie.
Just for the record, I didn't ask for this.
It was just a hot night
with the guy that every girl in town wanted.
Lucky me,
I should've been more careful though.
I got a little rough in bed and wound up
cursed by the mark of the fucking beast.
- That Jake, he's a catch.
- Oh, my God.
I thought he was the one, you know, but all
I got was a couple of dates, some hot sex,
and a 'I'm not ready for a relationship
right now, It's not you, it's me,'
Men, They're all beasts.
Jake didn't want me.
And if I can't have him...
- Well, you know how that line goes.
- Hey, l...
The funny thing is,
I never saw you as a threat.
I find you rather depressing myself.
Why do men always go for
the tortured ones? Poor damaged Ellie.
Fuck you.
Bitch!
Who's lost it now?
OK, Just the two of us, Fair fight, OK?
Just me and you, All right? Come on.
- OK,
- I'm right here.
OK, Let's go.
Fair fight?
This is Hollywood.
And you...
You get one taste of blood
and you freak out.
Jimmy, Jimmy.
Come on, run.
Jake? You bounce back quickly.
Hi.
- It's you?
- Yeah.
- How did this happen, Joannie?
- Well.
I guess there's no such thing
as safe sex with a werewolf.
Joannie, it doesn't have to be like this
for you, There are ways for you to control it.
Like what? Nibbling on coyotes
in the desert# No thanks.
I'm having too much fun
eliminating the competition.
Pretty soon I'll have you all to myself.
I won't let you kill her, Joannie.
Jake!
Honey, muffin.
I am not gonna kill her, I promise.
I'm just gonna rip her to shreds
and let her choke on her own blood.
Then...
maybe I'll eat her.
You have to kill me first.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Well, I've learned a few things about
this curse along the way, and I know better.
But that doesn't mean
I can't make it hurt a little.
- I don't see her.
- Sh.
Ellie?
Let's see how she deals with these.
I'm gonna get you.
Where are you, you bitch?
Get this off!
Where's your brother?
- Where'd she go?
- I don't know.
- Well, maybe she left.
Or maybe not.
- Did she see us?
- I don't think...
Run! Jimmy, get out of here.
Jimmy!
Ellie.
Ellie, wake up.
Wake up.
You're playing with us,
aren't you, Joannie?
Ellie.
Well, play this!
- Let's go!
- Move along, Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
Shit!
Move it.
- Freeze!.
- Don't shoot.
- Where's the animal?
- It's up there somewhere.
- What's it supposed to be?
- I don't know, stay alert, guys.
- What the hell is it, anyway?
- Oh, it's a werewolf. What?
- Did you say werewolf?
- Yeah.
she may have changed back
to her human form.
Her name is Joannie.
She's this hyper, skinny publicist.
- Any other description?
- Yeah, she's, what?! Like, five foot seven?
She's got a bony ass,
and fat thighs, and bad skin,
Liar!
Shoot!
Hold your fire!
- Man, that's ugly.
- Careful.
It's dead. All clear.
- That's fucked up.
- Yeah. OK.
- Stand down.
- What is this thing?
I told you, it's a werewolf.
You have to separate the head from the..
Repeat, all clear.
Call animal control.
- Get them out of here.
Is she dead?
Yeah. Her brain's on the floor.
That should do it.
- Jake.
- Bo.
Hey, I need a paramedic in here.
Bo, Bo, Bo.
- Yeah.
- Are you OK?
- Hey, Jimbo. How'd I do?
- You did good.
- I'm gonna go look for Jake, OK?
- Yeah.
Hey, you good?
Yeah. He sucker-punched me.
I was about to kick his ass.
OK.
Did you find him?
No.
- I'm telling you, we shot the shit out of this.
- Really?
You're gonna need a forklift.
This thing is...
huge.
I think we can handle it.
It looked a little bigger before.
Oh, shit!
- Are you OK?
- Are you all right?
- I think so.
- Yeah.
so, it's over, right?
And Joannie's dead, so we're OK now..
Well, that's subjective, We still have
to go back to our pathetic precurse lives.
- I'm personally OK with that.
- Well, you're not in high school.
What happened?
Zipper.
Are you OK?
I will be.
What's wrong?
Are you worried about Jake?
- His secret's out. He had to disappear.
- I don't want to talk about it, OK?
I know you think he's a good guy, Ellie,
but don't forget, all of this...
...everything we've been through,
is because of him.
When it comes down to it,
a monster is still a monster.
Jimmy. That's enough.
I guess some things never change.
- Do you think you can get us some light?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'll check the circuit breaker.
Zipper?
- How are you doing with those lights?
- Yeah, one second.
Shit.
Is everything OK down there?
Yeah, it's fine, I just...
Thank you.
Zipper?
It's OK, It's just me.
Sorry, I'm still working on the fuses. It's
a little dark in here, I'll be up in a minute.
Jake.
How are you, Ellie?
Jake, something's wrong, I'm...
- Sh.
It'll be OK. Just breathe.
You'll be OK.
- What's happening to me?
- It's starting, Ellie.
- It's almost midnight.
- Oh, no.
No.
- This can't happen, Jake.
- Ellie.
Ellie, sh. It's OK.
You're gonna be OK.
- I came back for you.
- I have to stop it.
- You have to help me stop it.
- Ellie, it's not really that simple.
But you have nothing to worry about.
This is how we can be together.
You need this, Ellie.
You need me.
- You said it could be controlled.
- You don't have to worry.
I can teach you how to live with this.
And we have years to figure it out.
So that's your answer?
We live happily ever after?
There's no reason why we can't now,
Think about it.
Your parents are dead.
Your brother is miserable,
your life is a mess.
Why do you think it is
that you fell for me so hard and so fast?
I gave you a reason to live again, Ellie.
And I can still do that for you.
- Jake, I don't want this.
- It's the only way we can be together, Ellie.
But I don't want you.
Tell me how to get rid of it. Tell me how!
The only way you can break the curse
is for the one who started it all to die.
And that’s me.
- I'm not ready to die just yet.
- I can't let my brother live like this.
You know I have to think of him first.
I know, I bet you promised your parents
that you'd give him a good life, didn't you?
But you know what, Ellie. You're
really not doing a very good job, are you?
- In fact, you're kind of a disaster.
- Get away from me.
I don't want you
to worry about your brother, OK?
After all,
there's only room for one alpha male.
And I really think we should put
the poor kid out of his misery, don't you?
Where is that brother of yours, anyway?
Now, where could he be?
In the basement?
These heightened senses
are a kick, huh?
No hard feelings, buddy.
I'll make it as quick as possible.
- Take it easy with the silver, Ellie.
- You're a monster.
Join the club.
That's only the beginning, Ellie.
I should've known
you couldn't handle this.
You're too weak to think you could
survive it. It only makes you stronger.
But you're too stupid, too timid.
It comes and goes at first.
I probably should've told you that.
- Unfortunately now you both have to die.
- Hey!
You'd better run, you little shit.
I am going to kill you.
Like you said, what doesn't kill you...
It's over.
Are you sure?! You were a little off on
that whole 'how to break the curse' thing.
Yeah, well, the books
kind of glossed over that part.
Uh-huh.
We're going to be OK.
Zipper.
Brooke.
- What are you doing here?
- Hey, Jimmy.
I found your dog.
He was wandering the streets.
- How'd you know where I lived?
- I told her.
-  Are you OK?
-  Yeah, you?
I'm good, thanks.
Uh...
- Can I walk you home?
- Sure.
- Are you coming?
- Yeah.
See you later.
- Nice moves.
- It's the new me.
I'm just gonna stay here.
And, uh... clean.
Come on, Zipper.
Zipper.
(# ''Better Now'' (cursed Mix)
by collective Soul)
# Yeah yeah
# Oh, I'm newly calibrated
# All shiny and clean
# Yeah yeah
# I'm your recent adaptation
# rime to redefine me
# Let the word out
# I've got to get out
# Whoa, I'm feeling better now
# Break the news out
# I've got to get out
# Whoa, I'm feeling better now
# Whoo
# Yeah yeah
# Oh, I'm happy as Christmas
# All wrapped to be seen
# Yeah yeah
# I'm your recent acquisition
# rime to celebrate me
# Let the word out
# I've got to get out
# Whoa, I'm feeling better now
# Break the news out
# I've got to get out
# Whoa, I'm feeling better now
# Let the word out
# I've got to get out
# Whoa, I'm feeling better now
# You break the news out
# I've got to get out
# Whoa, I'm feeling better now
(# ''Let Me Out'' by MBD)
# You're holy
# Not so holy
# running slowly
# running out
# You're hateful
# very hateful
# So unfaithful
# Giving up
# I'm fearless
# forever fearless
# Sick with weirdness
# So far gone
# I curse the day you fell on me
# Like a plague without a remedy
# Lost control of everything
# What's this all about?
# I can 't get used to this
# I tried, but I just reminisce
# close my eyes and make a wish
# You'd let me out
# Waiting
# All this waiting
# I'm still fading
# In the dark
# this bleeding
# can't stop bleeding
# I'm believing
# Who I am
# I curse the day you fell on me
# Like a plague without a remedy
# Lost control of everything
# What's this all about?
# I can't get used to this
# I tried, but I just reminisce
# close my eyes and make a wish
# You'd let me out
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org