Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Morning, Ms. Rita.
- Morning, Monty.
- Hey, Maya.
- Hey, Monty.
Hey, baby.
- What up, Willie?
- What's up, young blood?
- How are you?
- Old and tired, man.
- That woman say this engine won't start.
- Yeah. Well, it won't.
You know, Monty,
he was supposed to fix it.
He never did.
He don't know what he doing.
That fool can't even see.
I saw your mama the night you was made.
What you say to me?
Don't make me put this baby down.
And that ain't no way to talk to me.
I gave this car service
one of its best clients.
- Yeah. You never let me forget it, neither.
- That's right.
- Maya, I'll look at it for you, baby.
- Thank you.
Take a seat.
You all right?
And you better do something,
you know Chico quit.
You're gonna lose my boss as a client.
- Here you go, boy.
- How much is here?
Well, not enough, but I'll get it to you.
I promise, okay?
Hey, man, look,
I just lost one of my drivers.
He was the only one classy enough to drive
one of them corporate types, you know.
Now, listen to me.
No, no, no, Willie. You know
I can't stand them stuck-up types.
Hear me out. It pays good.
Oh, come on now.
It will help you make more
of a down payment for this place.
Man, Willie, you know
I'm better under the hood
than I am behind the wheel, man.
Do you really wanna buy this place?
Now this is a start.
Pay is good. Now she's a good client.
And she pays well. I don't want to lose her.
- I'll think about it.
- You'll think what?
- What?
- Watch it, old man.
- You watch it.
Maya, turn the key.
- Thank you, Monty.
- All right, baby.
You know, this should really be your place.
Oh, it will be soon, baby. All right.
- Hey, boy. How you been?
- What up, Kevin?
You all right?
Amen, amen.
Wilbert, get up.
- Hey, Monty.
- Hey, Ms. Rochelle.
You got people stepping all over you.
- Get up.
- He at it again?
Always. Always.
Hi, Monty.
Wilbert. Get up, boy.
Anybody home?
Sierra, get the door.
- Who is it?
- Who is it? It's your daddy. Open up.
- Hey, y'all. It's Daddy.
- Daddy.
Come on, y'all. Hurry up.
What up? Come here.
Come here. Come here.
What's going on? Can I get in?
Hey, Ms. Katheryn.
- Hey, Daddy. What did you bring us?
- Now, is that all I'm good for?
- No, Daddy.
- Can I get some love?
Daddy, you know
I got a B on my class project?
- Thanks for helping me.
- What did I tell you?
That I was gonna get a good grade
and I did.
Hey, Daddy, will you take us
to the movies this weekend?
No.
Okay.
I'll take you out to the movies.
You know Saturday
is Daddy-daughter day, so...
- Okay. So, Daddy, what did you bring us?
- Just some food, baby.
That always comes in handy.
You girls go in the room.
Let me to talk to your daddy.
Yeah, get in there.
Don't let me come in there.
What y'all doing? Playing checkers, huh?
Y'all been playing something.
Thanks, Katheryn.
$200, this week.
I'll bring the rest to you.
You know, Ms. Kat, you know
you got to take care of that cough.
I mean, it sounds like it's getting worse
every time I come up in here.
Yeah.
- Jenny been by?
- That daughter of mine?
No, only time I see her
is when she's driving by.
She ain't been here
to see these girls in months.
So happy you're here, or they wouldn't
know they had a daddy or a mama.
Monty, listen.
Sit down.
What's wrong?
I need you to go down
to family court with me right away
so you can tell them
that you're taking the girls.
I need you to raise them.
Ms. Kat, you know I love my kids,
but I can't take them full time.
Well, then they're gonna have to stay
with their mama.
- Now, you know I don't want that.
- Neither do I.
Especially since she living with that Joe,
the biggest drug dealer in the area.
Sitting up there in that window
staring down at all of us like he's God.
And she's right there with him.
She don't care about nobody but herself.
Do you know what'll happen to them girls
if they have to live with their mama, huh?
God forbid.
- Monty, please.
- Ms. Kat, I...
I have lung cancer.
I am dying, Monty.
I've been hanging in there for them girls
as long as I can, but I'm tired.
I'm tired.
Why didn't you say something?
Why didn't you tell me this?
Ms. Kat, it's gonna be all right.
It is not gonna be all right.
Why didn't y'all call me?
- Mommy!
- Don't look at her.
No, wait.
Wait, where do you think you're going?
These are my kids.
Stop. Stop. Get into the car, baby.
- Stop. Quit it.
- No, you get off of me.
Stop it, Jenny. Stop it.
- Everything all right, baby?
- No, you get my kids out of this car.
Jenny, stop it now. Jenny, stop. Stop.
You have not been
to see these kids in months.
- You want to come take them now?
- Get your hands off of me.
You got to be crazy. Get out of here.
- Now, you need back up, son.
- Yo, do me a favor, shut up.
- Do me a favor, dawg, just hold it.
- Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Go ahead, baby. Go ahead.
Put your seatbelt on. It's okay.
This is your mother's funeral.
And you know
she wanted these girls to go with him.
Jennifer, you know it.
You out whoring around with these thugs.
She didn't want these girls
around all of this foolishness.
Let me tell you something, Aunt Rita.
All right, these are my kids.
Do you hear me?
You ain't just gonna take them from me.
And let me tell you,
you go make your mechanic money,
you save it 'cause we going to court.
You hear me?
Give me my kids back.
You're gonna give them back to me.
You stay out of my way.
- What are you doing?
- Think you gonna let my mama die?
Calm down. Come on, calm down.
You gonna let them bury my mama
and you don't tell me, Wilbert?
- You should've been there for your mama.
- That's right.
- You know it ain't right.
- It's too late now.
Daddy, you know this place
is too small for all of us.
- We don't have anywhere else to go.
- We can go live with Mama.
China, Mama don't want us. She never did.
- That is not true.
- It is true.
- Is that true, Daddy?
- I'll tell you what is true.
I want you all to come stay with me.
Where are we gonna sleep?
Well, I'm gonna sleep on the couch
and you guys,
I mean girls,
are gonna sleep in the bedroom.
I fixed it up.
How bad was it before?
Daddy, China pees in the bed.
And I ain't sleeping with her.
I do not.
Why I got to put up
with being insulted like that?
- What's wrong with you?
- Whatever.
We need some separate beds
or some bunk beds or something
- 'cause this ain't gonna work.
- Well, I'll work on it, okay?
Well, while you work on it,
how about feeding us?
And getting all three of us some food?
'Cause all three of us are hungry.
You know what?
You got a mouth like your mama.
You need to put your clothes
in them drawers right here. Thank you.
I like this bedroom.
Lord, how am I gonna do this?
Man, I can't believe I'm doing this.
You waiting for Ms. Rossmore?
Yeah. Rossmore. Julia Rossmore.
Good luck.
What do you mean, "Good luck"?
- Good day, Ms. Rossmore.
- Good morning.
- You gonna open the door?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Can you close the door?
- Yeah.
What you laughing at?
Tell him to meet me there.
Tell him to wait then.
I'm surprised
the jury has returned so soon, myself.
No, it's a great thing. Yeah, definitely.
All right, see you in a second.
Did they tell you I need you to be on call?
- Oh, you talking to me?
- You're the only other person in the car.
Oh, no. You know what? I thought
you were still on the phone, you know.
Well, basically, all I need you to do
is get me to the office and get me to court.
Sometimes I work late.
And sometimes I entertain clients
after work, that sort of thing.
You know what, Ms. Rossmore? Right now
I need all the overtime I can get so...
- I'm sorry. What's your name?
- Monty.
Monty. Look, I don't like to fraternize so
let's keep this strictly professional. Okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Fabulous.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry about that.
Are you... Am I getting punked?
No, you're not getting punked, ma'am.
I just, you know,
thought you might want the radio on.
- No, I like silence.
- Yes, ma'am.
Silence.
You've missed your turn.
I asked you to take the freeway.
Well, you know what?
This way is much faster.
Excuse me?
Yeah. You seem like you're in a rush
and this way is faster, so...
Yeah, I am in a rush and I know this city!
The freeway would have bypassed
all of this lunchtime traffic.
I cannot believe this.
- Why are you stopping?
- Because we're here now.
- Next time follow my instructions, okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
Ms. Rossmore.
The jury has a question
that they need answered.
They want to know if
the damage award can be higher
- than what was previously requested.
- Well, Your Honor...
How's the driving going?
Oh, look, she is something else.
I know. I've worked for her four years.
She's good though. She wins every case.
And this is a big one.
Settlement.
That means she just won a grip of money.
She's that good?
My client's willing to talk.
Oh, and she's also impatient.
So you might want to get out to the car.
Sorry about that.
Your Honor, the people have no evidence.
- We have evidence.
- That is not admissible.
The search warrant gave them the right
to search the house not the car.
- He's right.
- Your Honor...
The evidence of the drugs is inadmissible.
In that case, Your Honor, we immediately
ask that all the charges be dropped
and that the case be dismissed
with prejudice.
Your Honor, we need to get him
out of the neighborhood.
Then your officers
should have been more careful.
- Where is your eyewitness?
- He has intimidated the entire community.
Then your office
has its work cut out for them.
I'm dismissing all the charges.
Adjourned.
They can't hold me, baby.
- You're the man.
- Thank you.
You want some pizza?
All right, I'm gonna bring some for you.
All right, I'll there soon.
I love you.
- Well, do you see this?
- Yeah, I see it.
I see it.
You looking like a little massa boy.
Wow. So, you had to get yourself
another job, huh?
Yeah, I know feeding them girls
ain't easy, huh?
Here. Let me help you out.
Let me see what I got in here.
Oh, look at that. Here. Take it.
- Stop it.
- Take it.
Oh, so, what, you Mr. Do the Right Thing?
Oh, so, you don't want this money.
It's okay. I'll take it back.
- You gonna leave me alone?
- What you gonna do, baby?
You see that brother right there?
If I even break a nail,
he will shut you down.
And I'm coming for my daughters.
You don't even want your kids. Huh?
Now, why would you do all this?
You tried to turn my mama against me,
huh?
You tried to turn my kids against me?
It ain't gonna happen, baby.
Yeah, I'm gonna make your life hell,
little punk.
Look at him, Joe. I think he getting mad.
He ain't gonna do nothing.
He's so scared to go back to jail.
Yeah. Go on, looking like a slave.
Go on, son. Mosey on down.
- Go on and drive the car.
- Come on, now, baby.
Let Stepin Fetchit get back to work now.
- Hey, man. Nice suit.
- Stepin Fetchit!
Look at you.
Looking just like a broke-down slave.
I must've been a fool
having three babies by you.
Oh, please. Yuck.
I'm just disgusted with myself.
- Do you think that's him?
- I think that's him.
- Hi.
- Excuse me.
Is this Ms. Rossmore's car?
- Who's asking?
- Yeah, this is it.
- Excuse us. It's okay.
- Excuse us.
- No, we got it.
- We know her.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Oh, goodness.
- Ms. Rossmore, you got somebody...
- You gonna open my door?
- You got...
- Are you going to open my door?
What are you doing in my car?
It's that time.
- No, no.
- Yes.
I just want to celebrate
winning this case, okay?
- 3rd and Peachtree, please.
- I'm gonna have to pass on the blind date.
I knew she was gonna say that.
Didn't I tell you that?
- You're going out.
- I can't.
Do you know what your associates
are saying about you at the office?
I don't care.
They're saying that you need a man, okay?
And that you're taking it out
on everyone at the office.
And they also say that you would be
a nicer person if you just got laid.
I agree.
I don't need to get laid,
as you so eloquently put it.
Yes, you do.
Look, we have been your friends
since college. We know what you need.
Well, if you know me so well,
you'd know that I don't like blind dates.
- They all end in disaster.
- Julia!
First of all, I have a very, very good feeling
about this one. I do.
Hey, so, Julia, I heard
you was like a lawyer and stuff.
- I am.
- Yeah, so you got this then?
- The bill?
- Yes.
No, I'm serious, though.
This is a nice place.
I like this environment.
You know, it's gangster.
I feel like, you know,
you could do some things in here.
You know what else is nice?
You got some sexy-ass lips.
I just wanna bite them.
Suck on them. Suck your lips off your face.
Yeah.
I'm gonna kill Cynthia.
You don't wanna mess
with your boy right here.
I mean, if you like pleasure.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Hey! Hey, come here, player.
Yes, sir.
What kind of fish is this filet mignon?
- I'm sorry.
- Y'all got Chinese food?
I'm sorry. We don't, sir,
but how can I help you?
You know what,
just give me some scrimps, man,
and some hot sauce and some fries with it.
- And for the lady?
- Yeah. You know what?
This water is gonna be just fine.
So we can just speed it along?
- I understand.
- I bet you do.
And your scrimps will come out
right away, sir.
Thank you.
Can we get some bread, man?
We're the only table without bread.
- All the white people got bread.
- I apologize, sir.
- I'll get that to you right away.
- Thank you.
That's a lot of hot sauce.
Well, what do you do for a living?
Well, right now, I'm between jobs.
So I decided I'm gonna be a rapper.
- A rapper?
- Yeah.
- That's something.
- Straight up. Check it out. Look.
You feel me?
Man, I be feeling that 'cause like I just...
- I'm sorry. How old are you?
- Forty, shorty.
- Forty?
- Yeah.
You don't think that's too old
to start a rap career?
Why everybody keep saying that?
I mean, yeah. But, you know, I'm good.
And I got a gimmick.
You got to have a gimmick in this game.
- You heard of 50 Cent?
- Yes.
They call me 40 Percent.
- Check, please. Check.
- They call me 40 P.
No, it's official.
No, this is my proclamation, Cynthia.
- I'm giving up on men.
- Why?
'Cause I'm 31. I've never been married.
I don't have any kids.
I don't even have a cat to curl up with.
And because I make six figures,
I can't find a decent man to save my life.
- What was wrong with this guy?
- Are you kidding me?
That man had no class, Cyn.
No, he had no class.
He was screaming across the restaurant
for some scrimps.
Yeah, scrimps.
I don't even know how to spell "scrimps."
Am I being unreasonable?
All I want is a man
who knows when to hold me,
and rub my feet, and make me feel safe.
Is that too much to ask?
No, sweetie, it's all possible if you
just relax your standards a little bit.
Girl, whatever.
And what's up with the black men
all trying to be down?
All of a sudden,
everybody's got to be down.
Like speaking correct English
is somehow uncool.
Like verb-noun agreement is just too much.
And if I see another black man over 30
in a throwback jersey,
girl, I'm gonna scream.
- What was that?
- I just saw one.
Julia, I just think you're too hard
on some of these guys, okay?
- You just need to relax a little bit.
- Excuse me.
I have standards.
Yeah. Well, the Pope
can't meet your standards, okay?
And I don't mean to be rude, sweetie,
but I got a man waiting for me.
I gots to go.
No, go. No, go. It's cool.
- Don't hate.
- I'm not hating, Cyn.
- All right. I'm just saying.
- No, my battery is dying anyway.
- Wait, I can't... I can't hear you.
- Hello?
- You got to be kidding me.
- I am so sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- You're gonna answer it?
- You know what? I got to get this one.
It's my neighbor and she got my kids.
Excuse me.
- Unbelievable.
- Hold on.
You're on company time.
You're not supposed
to be taking personal calls.
What happened? Yeah, I know where it is.
I'm on my way.
Whoa. Whoa. Where are you taking me?
- Lady.
- I'm being kidnapped.
- I'm being kidnapped! Somebody help!
- Lady, stop. Stop.
- You stop 'cause you're in big trouble, pal.
- Look, lady. Look, I'm sorry.
No, no, no. You're gonna be sorry.
You have a big problem
because you're fired. Fired.
I have a problem right now
and I am so tired of your stuck-up ass
giving me a hard time.
Now, do me a favor.
Sit back, shut up and ride, okay?
Thank you.
I do not believe this.
No way. No way. No. No, he didn't do this.
Excuse me. I'm Monty James.
You have my kids here?
Have a seat.
Someone will be with you in a minute.
- Yeah, I'm still here.
- Are they here?
Excuse me. Are they all right?
- Have a seat, sir.
- Where are they?
Excuse me. Excuse me. Where are they?
Have a seat, sir.
Did he take the keys?
He took the keys. He took the keys.
Fabulous. Fabulous.
I'm just gonna call... Who can I call?
My battery's dead. Great.
No, no. Julia, no. You're in control here.
And you're just gonna walk in there
and demand he take you home.
"Take me home, wodey."
No, do they say that?
No. "Take me home, brother."
Yes.
Hey. Look, I try to support
black-owned businesses,
but this is absolutely ridiculous.
Take me home now.
Monty.
- Ms. Rossmore.
- Maya, what are you doing here?
I live next door to Monty, your driver.
Well, he's not my driver after tonight.
Thank you very much.
The next time you wanna recommend
a little car service to me, Maya,
make sure it's not one of your buddies
from the hood, okay?
- Maya, what happened?
- Well, there was a fire and then...
- Jennifer Jackson, Monty James?
- Yeah.
- Laurie Bell, Department of Social Services.
- Are my kids all right? Where are they at?
They're fine. They're being looked after.
Mr. James, this could have been really bad.
I know. I know. I had to work tonight.
And the oldest one, she old enough
to look after the little ones.
- And I live right next door.
- This is my neighbor.
Well, your daughter started a fire.
Now, I'm sure it was an accident,
and the fire wasn't that bad,
but if your neighbor had not
broken down the door,
your daughters could have died
of smoke inhalation.
Now we're gonna have to look after
your daughters for a little while.
No, no, no. No, it's a mistake.
It's a mistake that could have
gotten them killed, Mr. James.
Now, you'll get a call about visitation,
but for now,
they're in custody of their mother.
No, ma'am. No, no. No.
Let me talk to the little one, please?
- Mr. James. Mr. James. I'm sorry.
- Look. All right. All right. Look.
- Go get my kids. Just go get my kids.
- Come on, Ms. Jackson.
Hold on. Ms. Bell.
And my mother had the nerve to think
that you would do a better job than me.
So I guess this, right here, is a better job?
- Almost killing my kids?
- Just go get them.
No, go get nothing.
You know we gonna get custody now,
right?
- I'm gonna enjoy raising your little girls.
- Monty!
- You wanna start with me, Monty?
- Give me a reason!
- Monty!
You picked the wrong person to mess with.
All right. Just let me get my kids, man.
Just let me get my kids, man.
Got you, player.
- What did you say?
- Monty.
Is he gonna take me home?
How old are your girls?
Five, seven and 12.
Look, I'm sorry about before.
Are they gonna be okay?
If you don't mind,
I don't want to talk about it.
I'm sorry.
Yeah. He's walking in right now.
I promise you I'll take care of it myself.
Please. Please, forgive him.
Thank you for your business.
What? I told you I couldn't do it.
I told you, man.
I'm glad she called and fired me.
You feel sorry for them girls.
- Did you get that court date yet?
- Custody hearing is in seven days.
I called like nine lawyers this morning.
They all said the same thing,
they need more money and more time.
Don't look at me.
I just feel like, you know,
I make two steps forward,
I gotta make four steps back.
All Ms. Kat asked me to do
was raise them kids
and I can't even do that.
You know, Jennifer and that crack dealer?
They got long money.
You gonna need some help from God
and two more white people to fight them.
So my assignment today is to encourage
your faith by using what Paul said.
He says, "And let us not grow weary
in well doing. "
He said, "For in due season you
shall reap, if you faint not. "
Now what I'm trying to tell you
is that God is faithful.
And in his faithfulness,
he reminds us that in doing good,
you shall get weary.
There's no sin in getting weary.
The sin is giving up.
Because I'm here to announce to you
you're so close to your due season,
you're about to taste it.
There's about to be
a manifestation of God in your life
and it's not time to throw in the towel.
It's time to lift up your head because
something's about to happen in your life,
and God's gonna ensure it.
The evidence that you're so close
to your breakthrough,
the evidence that you're so close
to your payday and your reward
for walking righteous,
is that you will feel like...
You better hear this,
I'm telling you something.
You will feel like you're about to faint.
And when you feel like
you're about to faint, don't faint.
Because that says
that I'm right there next to my miracle.
I'm right there,
right at the door of my due season.
I'm talking to those
that walked into this church today
with their head kind of hung down,
and just about to give up
and about to lose your faith.
I'm encouraging you, keep the faith.
Stay right there. Don't faint. Hold on.
God is about to bring your due season.
And you need to give him praise,
you need to bless his name,
you need to tell him, "I'm still holding on."
God bless you. God bless you.
And God bless you.
You know how you're working
my man's nerve with that whining?
You think I'm gonna let you
come in between me and my man
with all that mess? You're gonna stop that.
- I want my daddy.
- Well, you ain't going back to your daddy.
- Why?
- Because I said so, that's why.
You're gonna stay right here with me.
And you're going...
China, you gonna stop that whining.
China, get in there. Get in there.
You gonna stay here with me.
You ain't going back to your daddy.
Now you get in there
until you figure that out. Get in there.
Lauryn, go in there with her.
Go talk to your sister.
I gotta tell you something now.
Y'all better be glad I know Jesus.
How y'all get on my nerves.
Really beautiful.
Selling drugs right out here
in front of this holy place.
Oh, my goodness.
You know what, they need to be stopped.
Janice's son got caught selling at school,
he said he got it from him.
He comes to school and recruits the kids.
Babies, Monty.
And then he sends them to go sell it.
You know, Monty, you really need to come
to this community meeting.
Monty, a lot of people respect you
in this neighborhood.
And they still remember.
- You should come to one of the meetings.
- I know.
I'm praying for you,
and for you to get your girls back.
- I'll babysit any time I can.
- I'll babysit, too.
Honey, the Devil never wins,
unless you don't fight.
Yeah. You're right.
- All right, well, I'll see y'all later.
- Okay, baby.
I'm going back in for a piece of cake.
Now, you know, baby. You're old enough
to understand some things. Okay?
All right?
Now, you ain't gonna just be
sitting around here living off of me.
You got that?
Hey, look at me while I'm talking to you.
Look at me while I'm talking to you, I said.
Don't you dare not look at me.
- It's time for you to start your own hustle.
- No.
What do you mean, "No"?
- Are you telling me...
- I'm not a hustler.
No, you gonna be
whatever I tell you you gonna be.
I'm trying to teach you how never
to be broke another day in your life.
The number one rule to the game
is never get caught.
You got that?
Now, I'm about to go get a drink.
You want one?
Willie's Garage. Can I help you?
- Hold on. Monty, telephone.
- Yo.
Yeah.
What?
We called her mother
but no one answered.
This kind of thing is frowned upon,
Mr. James.
Yes, sir.
Sisi, where did you get this from? Huh?
- Go ahead and answer me.
- Joe.
Joe gave you this?
- Who is Joe?
- Joe's her mother's boyfriend.
What is wrong with you, Sisi?
- Did you lose your mind?
- I don't want you to die.
What are you talking about?
He said if I didn't do it, he was going
to get one of his boys to take you out.
And Joe crazy, Daddy.
He'll do it. I know he will.
It's okay.
Hey, didn't I tell you not to call him?
These are my kids.
- Please.
- He has no right to my kids.
Did you give this to my daughter to sell?
- Is this punk talking to me?
- No, I don't think so.
I'll take that as a yes. Look, man...
Daddy!
Look at him, you git.
- Security, get up here.
- You wanna play?
- Daddy!
- Now. Right away, to the Principal's office.
- Let him go!
- I run this, man.
Ain't nothing you can do about it.
These are my streets.
It's okay, baby.
Do yourself a favor, Monty, live.
'Cause if you keep coming at me
the way you coming at me,
we won't need a custody hearing.
You heard me?
- Stop it, Sierra.
- Let go. Come here.
Daddy's all right. Daddy's all right.
- Daddy, please, can we go with you?
- Sierra, come on.
- Sierra.
- Please.
It's gonna be all right.
- Sierra, come on.
- Let me go!
Stop it. Both of you.
- Stop grabbing her like that.
- What you doing, Sierra?
It's gonna be all right, Sisi. All right?
Why you gotta come up in here...
If you come up in front of me again,
I swear to God, you'll never see
another daylight in your life.
- Morning.
- Hi.
Excuse me.
...and your 8:00 appointment's all set.
- Okay.
Mr. Farnberg called.
Oh, and I was able to reschedule
your hair appointment for next Tuesday.
Also...
- Hey, what are you doing in here?
- I needed to talk to you.
That's what I was trying to tell you.
Mr. James is here.
Yeah, obviously.
Did you just let him in my office?
Well, he said he's here to drive you home.
- Call security.
- No, you ain't gotta call security.
I don't know what I was thinking
coming here talking to you.
I'll just leave. I'm going.
What do you want from me?
I gotta talk to you about my kids.
- Maya, can you give us a second, please?
- Yes, ma'am.
I gotta get my girls back.
Okay, what you need
is a family law attorney.
Okay? And if you can't afford one,
the court will appoint one.
I can't walk in there with a public lawyer.
Their mama's spending
a lot of money on a lawyer.
And I need a bulldog like you. No offense.
Look, our firm charges $500 an hour.
Can you afford that?
- I got $1,200 to my name.
- Look, Mr...
No, no, just call me Monty.
Look, sister, I'm trying to get...
Typical. Typical.
I thought more of you, but it's real
typical. I'm not your sister, okay?
I don't appreciate you coming
into my office asking for favors,
playing the race thing.
It's sad and it's pathetic.
- What are you getting out of this?
- What?
Why do you want your daughters back
so badly?
You getting a check for them
or some sort of government assistance?
Go to hell.
Well, that, my friend, is exactly
how you get what you want.
Insult me. Great strategy.
I see why you're so successful.
Get a man. Get a life.
Thank you.
Excuse me, are any of you ladies
named Julia?
- No.
Sorry to bother you.
Julia.
- Christopher?
- Yes.
- Please, call me Chris.
- Sure.
- May I?
- Oh, please. Sorry.
I'm sorry for staring.
It's just that you're more beautiful
than your friend said.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- So you're a lawyer?
- Yes, I am.
- Me, too.
- Really? Wow.
Mostly corporate stuff, tax stuff.
It's pretty boring. What about you?
Our firm handles some criminal, some civil.
- Okay. What firm?
- Rossmore & Blake.
Oh.
- What?
- I applied for a job there.
They turned me down.
Said that my resume
was a little bit shallow.
That's what the old fart said.
- What's he... How's he doing these days?
- He retired to Florida.
- Oh, you keep up with him?
- He's my father, the fart.
Check, please.
- I'm sorry. That was embarrassing.
- Don't worry about it.
He can be a little tough on people
he doesn't know that well.
Oh, it must be big wingtips to fill.
Actually I try to fill my own stilettos.
Touch. And I will try to keep
my foot out of my mouth
for the rest of this conversation.
It's cute. You should leave it there.
- Well, if it's what the lady likes, then I will.
- Oh, I like.
- Would you like anything to drink?
- A latte would be great.
Okay. Coming right up.
Thank you, Jesus.
So, I had an amazing time.
This was one of the best dates
I've ever been on.
Me, too.
- I would like to see you again.
- Yeah? I'd like that.
Who the hell is this, Chris?
This is...
Baby, you were supposed...
- Who are you?
- I was just saying goodbye, ma'am.
Yeah, you better go, slut.
You see, right now, this is his family.
- Get away from my daddy, tramp.
- Junior!
Excuse me, you're trying
to be playing player, huh?
Where is your wedding ring?
That is so tired. Get into the car.
- Where's your lawyer?
- Sir, I can't afford one.
But I do have all my paperwork,
Your Honor.
- Are you ready to begin?
- Yes, sir.
- My kids were taken for...
- The court is aware of that,
but first I'd like to hear about
the incident that happened at school.
Your Honor, he gave my daughter weed
to sell in school
so, you know, I had to handle that.
Mr. James has no evidence
to support that allegation.
However, we have documentation
that demonstrates
that Mr. James has a history
of violent behavior.
Your Honor, look, I'm caught between
a rock and a hard place here.
You know, the courts won't help me.
My daughters are living with this man.
You know,
what am I supposed to do right here?
Your Honor, not only are we requesting
full custody with no visitation,
but also a restraining order
against Mr. James.
He assaulted my client
and threatened bodily injury.
You Honor, this man
is giving drugs to my kids.
- What proof of that do you have?
- Absolutely none.
- Your Honor.
- Ms. Rossmore?
I'll be representing Mr. James.
I'd like to request a continuance
at this time
so I might be brought up to speed.
Your Honor, this has gone on long enough.
My client is ready to put this behind her.
Perhaps counsel might want
to remind his client
that in family court it's not
what's best for the parent,
but rather what's
in the best interest of the child.
That being said,
I think these children
need effective counsel.
Ms. Rossmore, you are appointed
by the court as guardian for the children.
When I hear this case on the reset date,
I want evidence,
not just accusations and speculation.
This case is continued for 30 days.
Your Honor,
during that time we'd like to request
full custody be granted to the father.
You're pushing your luck.
Full custody remains with the mother.
Father will have visitation one day a week.
Adjourned.
You have really interesting taste in women.
No, that's not the girl I met in high school.
Nope, she's changed.
I think the hood has a way of bringing out
the best and the worst in people.
That's not just the hood, Monty. That's life.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
We had big dreams, though. Big dreams.
Then I guess, you know, reality set in.
Really? What kind of dreams did you have?
I'm a mechanic and, you know,
I wanted to open my own shop.
I'm good with cars, you know.
So that's my hustle.
You should open that shop one day.
Well, I had to use the money
that I had saved on my kids.
- Oh.
- It was worth it, though.
You know, I think that parents sometimes,
they gotta give up their dreams
so their kids can have one.
Thank you.
- Thank you so much...
- All right.
...for giving me hope. Thank you.
Great. Cool. Okay.
Come by tomorrow evening after work. We're
gonna have to do all this after-hours.
- Okay.
- And if you could bring any receipt
that pertains to the kids' expenses
or anything else you can possibly think of
- that can help us win the case.
- Thank you.
No, no, no. This needs to be addressed.
He is the councilman.
He needs to know what the real issues are.
You the one we elected.
You supposed to do something.
- That's what.
- That's right.
Quiet, quiet, please.
One at a time. One at a time.
Yes, you, ma'am.
I'm scared to go to the mailbox on
the first because they be watching me.
Yes, sir.
That Joe boy's been selling drugs
on this block for years.
- Why haven't you called the police?
- What good would that do?
He's been arrested five times
and he keeps coming back.
- You gotta do something.
- That's right.
What did I miss?
More of the same. Still complaining.
Let me tell you why
he's gonna keep getting off.
Because none of you in this neighborhood
will testify against him.
What if we did?
I mean, what if we did testify?
Who's gonna protect us?
Police don't come when you call them
in this neighborhood half the time.
- May I say something, please?
- Yes, sir.
I've been in this neighborhood
for almost 67 years.
I've watched Dr. King walk this very street
to go to the barbershop.
I remember Billie Holiday
who checked into what used to be
the only hotel in the South
that would allow black people,
right here on Auburn Avenue.
What I remember most is we used to be a
people that would take care of ourselves.
Nobody never gave us nothing.
We all earned it.
We look at these politicians and ask
that they help. It ain't up to them.
It's up to us.
And if we all stand up together,
then maybe they'll come and help us.
That's the history of us as a people.
We have to get our neighborhood back.
I can see my whole neighborhood up here.
It ain't but five, ten blocks
but it's a whole different world out there.
- And the highway running right through it.
- Monty, I have a question.
Yeah.
When did you and their grandmother
file this with the family court?
Oh, pardon me.
It was like a month before the fire.
- There, see the date?
- Thank you.
So you've been supporting
these children their whole lives?
Yeah.
- What?
- Nothing, you should be proud of that.
That's all I'm saying,
you should be proud of that.
Judging from these past years' tax returns
and how much you spend on them,
- it's commendable.
- Don't be surprised.
I mean, I know the world
will have you thinking that,
you know, brothers in the hood
don't look after their kids but...
I know there are some that don't, but I do.
I love my kids. I want them back.
Oh, well, you know, I think...
I think we have enough info here to begin
preparing a really, really solid case.
You know, there is something
I have to ask, though.
Yeah.
Are there any surprises in your past
that I should know about?
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Yes.
Cynthia, no. No, no, no.
I know it's 6:30. I'm not going.
'Cause I don't want to go
on any more blind dates.
He was a 40-year-old rapper.
No, I didn't hear his demo tape.
Bye. Bye. Thank you, bye.
Sorry.
Why do you...
Why do you go on them dates?
- Why do you go on them blind dates?
- Excuse me.
When I was driving you, you know, you had
your homegirl set you up on a blind date.
And I'm like,
"Why you need that? You're so beautiful."
You really want to know?
I need... I mean, I need to know. I mean...
Because it's really hard
to meet a nice black man.
It is. It is.
And when you're in corporate America,
like me,
the people you work with
don't look like you.
And if you're a black woman
that wants to actually date a black man,
kind of difficult.
No, seriously, and if you want a black man
that has good credit,
actually wants to date a black woman
and doesn't play video games.
- Good luck.
- I love me some black women.
Where's my money?
- I don't have it.
- We can see that.
That's $700, kid.
See, now, the problem is
that comes from queen bee's account.
And as you can see,
she's a little pissed off about it.
Baby, you want to call this one?
- Oh, baby, you're going to let me do it?
- Oh, for sure.
Go do what you do.
Now, kick his ass.
$150.
$275.
- That's a good $350 right there.
- Stop it!
Stop it!
Get him up out of here.
Yo, light up my blowtorch.
I'll be down in about 20 minutes.
What you laughing for? That ain't funny.
I'm laughing at you 'cause...
Baby, he deserves to be beat, okay?
It's a tough world out here
and I'm getting you ready for it.
Ain't nothing given to you, girl.
No, you got to take it.
Now, I'm gonna wipe those
little sweet dreams out of your head,
okay, baby,
if it's not the last thing that I do.
Now, get your little black ass
back in that bedroom
before I have to smack it.
Oh, I'm about to come in there in a minute.
I got a big belt.
Okay, I think that's enough for tonight.
- So, how's it looking?
- Good, good. I think we're gonna do well.
- Come on, I'll walk you to your car.
- Thank you.
You know what?
I forgot, I let my driver go home early.
Oh, well, you know, I'll take you home.
Thank you.
- Is this how you're spending your birthday?
- It's just another day.
Wow, how old are you?
- You don't ask a woman that.
- I just did. How old are you?
- How old are you?
- Thirty-four.
Twenty-twelve.
Okay. Happy birthday.
What are you going home to do?
I got some paperwork
I got to catch up on, stuff like that.
I mean, that ain't how you're
supposed to spend your birthday.
You need to get out and have some fun.
What's fun? I don't even know what that is.
All I do is work.
Fun is where you make it.
Come on, I'll show you some fun.
You know, I don't think
this is gonna be a good idea.
Sure it is.
Is it safe?
You're always safe with me. Come on.
Come on.
What's up, man?
Hey, Karen.
- Did you buy that garage yet?
- I'm still working on it, you know that.
- This is my friend Julia. Julia, Karen.
- Hey.
- And she need a drink, okay?
You ain't lying.
I know just the thing.
You all right?
Y'all have a good time.
Monty.
- This is my friend Julia.
- Hello, pretty lady.
- How are you doing?
- Fine.
Good to see you. She looks scared.
No, I'm fine. No, really, I'm fine.
It's all right, baby.
We're gonna make you comfortable.
Karen, get us a couple
of them down South brews, please.
By the way, it's her birthday today.
Well, that's a reason to drink.
Happy birthday.
Yeah.
- Take that to you.
- What is it?
Oh, no, no.
Just hold your nose and swallow.
Unless you're scared.
If you're scared, let me take that for you.
No.
Sure?
- Wait now, wait a second. Wait.
- Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday, baby.
- Are you all right?
There's water right here.
Give me another one.
I'm trying to catch up with her.
- Please, do. Please, do.
- Seems like a nice girl.
Yeah, she a little too white bread for me.
- Where did you meet her?
- I was her driver.
Be careful.
- You all right?
- Dance with me.
Sure.
All right, have you got the keys?
No, let me help you with that.
Wait, wait, wait.
Are you sure you live here?
Who put this couch here?
It was a bad boy. It was a bad boy.
Okay, Julia, where the kitchen at?
That way?
Yeah.
What?
I told you
you was gonna have some fun, right?
I got something for you.
Julia.
Where's she go?
Oh, okay.
You knocked out, ain't you?
Hey.
You got some aspirin, something like that?
Okay.
Let me set you up.
Oh, man.
Here, baby.
- Come here.
I have to leave.
- Take that.
- It'll make you feel better, okay?
- You make me feel better.
- I do?
- You make me feel way better.
Stay the night.
- Stay with me.
- You're drunk.
- I know.
- You know?
- Oh.
Stay the night.
I don't need ibuprofen. I need you.
- You need me?
- I need you.
All right, come here.
Oh, wait. Wait a second. Yo.
You all right?
- Baby, you want... You need...
- No. Go home, please.
I'm okay.
Go home?
I'll see you tomorrow.
- Okay.
- I had a good time. It was great jazz.
- You had a good time? Okay.
- Great jazz.
Me, too.
Bye.
Okay, I'm gonna call you tomorrow.
I had a good time.
Hey, sorry I'm late.
Where have you been?
We've been calling you for days.
- I called you twice yesterday.
- I know, I've been busy.
- Excuse me. Coffee, ma'am?
- Yes, decaf, please. Thanks.
- What?
- Oh, hell, no.
What are you talking about?
Only good sex
can make you smile like that.
- Who is he?
- We did not have sex.
But there's someone.
- Who is it?
- She's glowing.
Come on. Give up the goods, girl.
No, no, no.
Because you're just gonna judge me.
- 'Cause you two are judgmental.
- Oh, God.
- Is he married?
- He's not married. I'm not a hooker.
- Oh, well, then who is he?
- Then tell us.
Come on.
- His name is Monty.
- Monty.
Oh! Oh, that guy you introduced us to.
He's the new associate. He was so fine.
- No, no, no. His name was Brian.
- How do you know his name?
You know, he's not an associate.
- Do we know him?
- Monty.
Monty. Come on.
We know him. We know Monty.
The driver?
- The driver?
Oh, hell, no. Are you out of your mind?
Okay, he's supposed to be driving you,
not you riding him.
Wasn't it you two ladies who told me,
"Relax your standards, Julia"?
Yeah, to relax them, honey,
not lay them down by the riverside.
- I don't know about this.
- Where does he live?
- Edgewood.
What does your lvy League background
know about Edgewood?
Nothing.
And what do you know about Edgewood?
What could you two
possibly have to talk about?
They ain't gonna be talking.
- Cynthia.
- What?
Your client's last settlement,
his baby-mama drama.
- How do you know he has kids?
- Because.
Are you kidding me?
It is not if he has kids, it's how many.
- Does he have kids?
- How many?
- Three.
- He has three children?
I'm so disappointed.
- Are they all by the same mother?
- Probably not.
Yes, they all have the same mother,
I think, but it doesn't matter.
Just be careful, don't fall for this guy.
I'm telling you, he will run up your credit,
have you in the SWATs wearing
knock-off Gucci before...
Brenda, relax, all right. She's not married.
She's just having fun.
Right? You're having fun,
you're not falling in love.
And she needs to have some fun.
Girl, you need to take the edge off.
You do.
- Hi.
- Whoa.
- Hey, hey.
- You all right?
- Feeling good?
- Yeah, yeah.
You had fun last night except for the...
Yeah, I'm fine.
What are you doing here?
Well, you know, I just thought
I'd come check up on you.
And I realized, you know, you're doing
all this work but you haven't met the girls.
I have them tonight so maybe
you want to come by and meet them?
- Great. Sounds good.
- My place ain't as fly as yours, but...
- How's 7:00?
- That sounds great.
That's great.
What's wrong with you? You still feel sick?
No. Maya, do you knock?
Well, I thought I did.
- I have the files you asked for.
- Great. Okay, thank you.
- I'll get those later. Thank you, Maya.
- Well, you just...
Thank you.
What is wrong with you?
I thought we agreed
that we would work after-hours.
Oh. Oh, I'm sorry.
You know,
you can't just come up to my office.
You know, it's a lot of nosey people and...
My bad. You know, I just
thought last night me and you...
- No, no, I hope you're not offended.
- No, I should have called you.
- You understand, right?
- Yeah.
- Great. Okay.
- All right, cool.
- Great.
- All right, so, yeah.
- Okay.
- You look good.
Thank you for that.
Damn it.
- So, your dad went to go get dinner?
- Yes.
Is it... Is it far?
Maybe.
- So, you have to be...
- Don't come up in here like you know us.
Oh, goodness.
I'm Lauryn and these are my sisters,
Sierra and China.
- Where did you meet my daddy at?
- We met at work.
I think you guys saw me in court
the other day. Remember?
- Oh, court? That was you?
- Yeah.
You look so much older.
- What did you say your name was again?
- Julia.
- Ain't that a white-girl name?
- Okay, now, we're supposed to be nice...
China.
...and say thank you for helping my daddy
try to get custody of us.
Oh, it's no problem, really.
Well, you could try a little harder.
I've been having migraines
since I've been living there.
- Migraines?
- Bad migraines.
- I'm sorry. I'm trying.
- Really bad migraines.
- Hey.
- Hey, you made it.
- Yeah.
- Hey, Daddy.
Yeah, your kids
are certainly gonna be lawyers
'cause they sure as heck
grilled the hell out of me.
I bet they did.
- Hi, girls. What you doing?
- Nothing.
And she's at school,
but she is not a nice girl at all.
- No?
- No.
- Are you a nice lady?
- I try to be.
I like your hair. Don't you, Sisi?
It's all right.
Looks like a weave to me.
- No, it's not.
- Sierra.
- What?
- So rude.
She's so rude. Are you okay, Daddy?
- I think it's time for y'all to go to bed.
- No, please.
- Not yet.
- Just five more minutes, not yet.
- Good night.
- No.
- Please, I want to talk to Ms. Julia.
- Say good night.
- Good night, Ms. Julia.
- Thank you.
Good night.
- Good night.
- Sierra.
Bye.
Tell me what you know.
You know what?
I'll tell you what I do know.
I know that you, you're feeling me,
but you won't let yourself go there
because you care more about what
people think than your own happiness.
Am I right?
We could both act like, you know,
the other night never happened.
- But we both know it did.
- I was drunk.
- No, no.
- No, I was drunk.
You was being yourself and like my
mama used to say, God rest her soul,
"A drunk man never tells no tales."
What?
- Touch.
- Yeah.
- So your mom passed?
- My mom passed.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- What about your dad?
- Who?
- Your dad?
- My dad, I don't know my dad.
I got a whole bunch of brothers and
sisters that I don't know, but that's cool.
It's funny how life works out.
You never knew your dad,
but my dad would have killed for a boy.
- For a boy?
- For a boy.
- Didn't get one.
- I know the feeling.
That man pushed me so hard, God.
I made partner in the firm before I was 28.
My parents have retired to South Beach.
I don't know, Ms. Julia. You know what?
You and I,
we come from two different worlds but...
Well, there is something
going on here, right?
- You want me to stop?
- No.
- No?
- Oh, you're on time today.
- Well, he's on time all right.
Oh, my God!
- What happened to you?
- Some thugs tried to break in here.
I fought them out.
Before that happened one of them cut me.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm all right.
Did you catch them?
No, it was just some crackhead
trying to get some stuff.
Yeah, I'm getting too old for this, man.
I'm tired of it.
They win!
You know, I was thinking.
I gotta get rid of this place.
I gotta leave this neighborhood.
So if you can get together what you can
for a down payment,
and then you hit me up once a month
until we reach 10, plus interest
you can have this place.
Would you do that?
I mean, sure. What are you saying?
Are you serious, man?
Yeah, this place is officially yours.
- I mean, I didn't want it like this.
- Me, neither.
But you gotta let me come back
and help you from time to time.
Any time you're ready, man.
All right.
Oh, man.
Congratulations.
- Is he gonna be all right?
- He'll be fine.
You see that?
I see it. Oh, look at that.
- Can you see it, Ms. Julia?
- I do. Wow.
So, you know, I'm mad excited.
I'm gonna get my sign for my new garage.
- I know.
- Sounds great.
- I know. I'm really excited about that.
Congratulations.
- Julia?
- Hey.
Hey. What are you doing here?
- Nothing, we were just...
- I'm Monty.
- I remember you.
- Okay.
- Can I talk to you for a sec?
- Yeah.
- What are you doing with this man?
- What? We're just hanging out.
Are you serious? You like him?
- He's a nice guy.
- Snap out of it, Julia.
You are a partner at your firm,
the only black woman at that level.
What do you think your partners
would think if they knew
you were sleeping around with the help?
Are you trying to ruin your life?
- Hey, Julia, how you doing?
- Good, how you doing?
- Hey, baby, you ready?
- Yeah.
Come on, guys.
I think there'll be some people
who are disappointed in me behind this.
I mean, you know who I am.
I'm from the streets.
- I can't change that.
- I'm not trying to change you.
- Do I embarrass you?
- No!
I mean, it's obvious that I do.
And that's okay. That's okay.
You just gotta tell me that.
Tell me the truth,
so that way I know how to deal with it.
Look, I don't know how I feel. Okay?
But I can't sit here and lie to you,
and say that I don't think about
who you are and what you have.
I do.
You have three daughters,
one of whom is almost as big as I am.
This is new for me, Monty,
and it's different, and I'm trying.
I am trying
and you gotta give me credit for that.
Can we finish this conversation? Come on.
- No.
- No? What are you... What...
I got my girls for like two more hours,
and I'm not gonna waste my time
dealing with this.
But I will tell you something.
You don't have three girls in your life.
- It's just you.
- Monty. Monty.
- Monty.
- Big guy, ain't he?
- He's so pretty.
- Pretty?
- Look at that one.
- That one's bigger than all of them.
Yeah.
I told him,
"Do not bring this chick to my house."
- Watch the seatbelt. Come on.
- I love you, Daddy.
- See you later.
- Come on, y'all. Hurry up.
- Bye, Ms. Julia.
- All right.
I love y'all. Okay? Y'all be good, okay?
- Little butterfly. Go ahead.
- Come on, y'all.
Come on, y'all. Hurry up.
Shoot, I've been standing out here
all night. I'm tired, too.
Y'all think y'all the only ones tired? Shoot.
Just let me explain, Monty.
The last man that I loved,
he hurt me to my soul.
We were together six years,
and he told me it was over
two days before his wedding.
I trusted him with everything.
And I've never felt so low
and stupid and humiliated in my life.
And so I told myself
not to think about you.
But I couldn't 'cause I do all the time.
So what are you saying?
I'm saying that I've been running
from something that already happened.
And I'm saying that
I fell in love with you, Monty James.
And I'm saying
that I hope I'm not in this alone.
You're not.
You're not alone.
Come here.
Your Honor,
the children's own grandmother,
their maternal grandmother at that,
went down to Child Welfare
and prepared a written statement
as to why the children
should be placed with their father.
Let me see that.
- Did you know about this?
- Look, I don't know nothing about this.
I don't know
what they're trying to pull now.
Your Honor, my client has the means
to take care of these girls.
And she wants to take care...
It says here that her mother thought
the means were ill-gotten.
- Well, that's pure...
- What do you do for a living, Ms. Jackson?
Well, I don't work, Your Honor,
but my boyfriend does.
What does he do?
You know, I mean,
he owns his own businesses.
And where are the tax returns?
Well, you know,
we was working on getting them.
And you know what, Your Honor,
you keep asking me about my stuff,
you need to be asking Monty
about some of his secrets
'cause he got a whole lot of them.
What is she talking about?
Your Honor, Mr. James was convicted of the
rape of a 16-year-old girl 16 years ago.
And we're afraid
for the safety of the children.
Counselor,
what do you have to say about this?
I wasn't aware, Your Honor.
It's right here in black and white.
Yeah, he was sentenced to eight years.
He's been on probation
ever since his release.
I'll take this matter under advisement.
I need to review
the circumstances of this case.
Adjourned.
So how long has he been screwing you?
Huh? 'Cause I know he can't afford you.
- Move, move.
- Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'll have to tap that ass.
Let me explain. Let me explain something.
- Get away from me.
- Hold on.
- Let me...
- Get you hands off of me.
- Wait, let me explain.
- You know what, shut up.
Shut the hell up. I can't even
stand to look at you, right now.
I asked you if there were any surprises.
You said no.
You're a rapist.
You don't think that's something
that I should have known about?
- Let me explain.
- Don't you touch me.
Julia, look. Look. Look.
Let me ask you a question. Did you
or did you not go to jail for rape?
- Julia, look. Julia, look.
- Did you go to jail?
- Did you go to jail for rape, Monty?
- Yes.
That's all I need to know.
Do you know what, it doesn't even matter
'cause you're a liar, Monty.
You're a filthy... God, you're a filthy liar.
This case is over. Maya will call you and
tell you when to return for the ruling.
You don't need me anymore, Monty,
and I certainly don't need you.
So, you like him that much?
- I fell in love with him.
- Oh, Julia.
Sweetie, this was supposed to be
a fun thing, not a love thing.
I know.
Go ahead, Bren, tell me, "I told you so."
Oh, girl, you know I'm not gonna do that.
It's just good that you found out now.
I'm with Brenda on this.
Julia, this guy was probably
just after your money.
He wasn't even like that.
You know, you guys, he was a hard worker.
And he treated...
God, he treats those girls
like they are princesses.
Well, let's not forget he has a record.
How did I not know he was lying?
Because he's probably really good at it.
They all are.
It's like I'm hearing it, you guys,
and I'm trying to understand, but I just...
It doesn't make sense.
You know?
And I can't make my brain believe
that it was all a lie.
Is it as bad as it sounds?
Honey, it's as bad as it sounds.
Jules, just do yourself a favor.
Forget about this guy.
He just sounds like a lot of trouble.
Okay?
I just want to say...
It was like that.
Hi, this is Julia. Leave a message.
Who that?
What y'all doing here?
Where your mama at?
What happened, Sisi? What happened?
Daddy, we don't really care
what the judge says.
We just want to be with you.
I'm staying here.
- How did y'all get here?
- We walked.
Y'all walked at 3:00 in the morning?
We can't stay there anymore, Daddy.
I'm sorry.
- What you talking about?
- Daddy.
- What happened?
- Joe...
Joe what? Sisi you can talk to me.
You tell me, what happened?
- Joe keeps...
- He keeps what?
Joe keeps hitting China.
What?
- Where? Come here. Where?
- On my back.
On your back?
Mama was sitting right there.
She didn't even say anything.
Hold on. Hold on a second.
Come here. He hit you?
He hit me because I wouldn't stop crying.
- Daddy, I was so sad.
- Okay.
Okay, come here. Come here.
Grandma told me.
Grandma told me to look after y'all.
I got to look after y'all.
So y'all gonna stay with me now.
Y'all gonna stay with me now. Okay?
Okay?
Sisi, I'm so sorry. I am so sorry.
Okay, you gotta stay with me.
It's gonna be all right.
Wait, hold up.
Monty, Monty. Man, come on.
Some girls up in here, man.
Monty, what are you doing, man?
Come on. What's taking you so long?
- I'm Monty.
- We know who you are.
You beat our team.
- How old are you?
- Eighteen.
You know, this sure is a nice place
you have here.
You want to see my room?
- So you gonna call me?
- Probably not.
You're just like all the other guys.
Mandy, what are you doing?
Did he force you?
- No way. Tell him.
- Mandy.
- Yes, Daddy.
- What?
- Sir, I didn't do anything.
- Shut up.
- I didn't do anything. It was her idea.
- Shut up, superstar.
- Tell him, I didn't do anything.
- Call the police.
Tell him, Amanda.
If you don't tell the truth, I'm going to jail.
- Tell him the truth.
- You're ball days are over.
- You got me?
- I didn't do nothing.
- Shut up!
- I didn't do...
Get you hands off of me.
I can't even stand to look at you.
You're a rapist.
I bet you
he won't ever take our money again.
I know, that's right.
Got to keep it straight, Jen.
You know I got your back, right, baby?
That's why you my girl.
You know, I want to go see that movie
with the dude with the ax.
No, no, no, it's the chain saw.
Baby, you know
if we went to see that movie...
Check it out.
Oh, snap. Load up. Load up.
Stop it!
There was a near riot today
in the Edgewood community.
Police officers were called in
to break up a fight
between local gang members
and residents who had had enough.
Among those arrested was Monty James.
You may remember Monty James,
a high school basketball star,
who was falsely convicted in 1990
for allegedly having non-consensual sex
with a 17-year-old girl.
I'm assuming you have
admissible evidence this time.
Yes, Your Honor.
The police seized
several pounds of marijuana,
hidden in the defendant's vehicle.
Subsequent search of the residence
turned up several kilograms
of crack cocaine.
This time, Your Honor,
we have a valid warrant.
Your Honor, even though
they served a search warrant,
they still have no witnesses.
Your Honor, I'll testify.
Congratulations,
it looks like you have a case.
Take them into custody.
There will be no bond.
- Next case.
- Wait, get your hands off of me.
The State of Georgia versus Monty James.
Order. Order in this court! All of
you, quiet, or I'll have you removed.
I will have order.
Order.
I said order!
- Who's here for the defense?
- I am, Your Honor.
Ms. Rossmore.
May I take a second, please?
What you doing here?
I'm sorry, I didn't give
you a chance to explain,
and if you don't ever want to speak
to me again, I completely understand.
Let me help you.
Monty, just let me help you.
Just get me back to my kids.
Ms. Rossmore?
Your Honor, there's no evidence
my client committed any criminal act.
The State has no case against him.
We demand a preliminary hearing
and request the State be required
to show probable cause.
Your Honor, I'm sure that one of these
witnesses can attest to the fact
that Mr. James drove his vehicle
into the previous defendant's vehicle.
It was an accident.
I'm sure that the subsequent fistfight
was an accident also there, Counselor.
Where are the witnesses?
Your Honor,
the entire neighborhood saw this.
I'm sure we have a witness.
May I have one of the witnesses
please stand at this time?
- Your Honor...
- I'm dismissing the case.
I love you,
and I'm sorry for everything.
Oh, man. Come on, man.
I can't believe this.
The whole neighborhood remembered.
- Daddy!
Come here, baby.
- It's all on you now, boy.
- I love you, man. I appreciate it.
Bye, babies.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org