Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
number in case of an emergency.
He was with Cecilia for a few minutes.
He said hi, he looked at the room.
Is there some problem?
Is he not allowed to?
Is there some restraining order
against him?
No. No.
I was just... wondering if Ceci was...
Still imagining things?
Actually, I'm glad you brought that up.
Her imaginary friend hasn't gone away.
In fact, she threw somewhat of a tantrum
during circle time
when we wouldn't let her "friend"
sing along.
I had to have her take a time-out.
I'm sorry. I'll certainly
talk to Ceci about that.
You know, the PTA provides
a psychologist, Katie Shoettle.
She's very nice. She comes every
Wednesday. It's absolutely no charge.
I'll talk to Ceci about it. It'll stop.
I'm really sorry about that.
You'll see. Couple of days, blend right in.
You won't see the difference.
I'm sure you're right. Thank you.
You know, those kids were up there
again last night, running around,
and I could hear them running water. So...
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna speak with Murray
about changing the lock on 10F.
You know what he told me?
Rimsky paid no rent this month.
- He's probably not coming back anyway.
- OK.
Well, that would be great
if you could change the lock.
Starting to have nightmares
about what's going on up there.
- Really? You gotta relax, huh?
- Can I get you something before you go?
Yeah. Get me a reward
for all this hard work I've been doing.
Yeah? I think I have beer.
- You want a beer?
- I don't drink beer.
Coffee? I could make a pot of coffee
if you want.
Oh, forget it. I've been working hard today.
I'm tired. I'm going.
OK. Well, thank you.
What about Hello Kitty? Can I have it now?
Oh, so sorry, kid.
Somebody came by for it today.
They were visiting town,
left it there by accident.
Oh, that little girl,
she was so happy to have it back.
- You're lying.
- Ceci.
He's lying, Mommy. Nobody came.
You want to teach that goddamn brat
some manners, lady.
Sorry.
What is the matter with you?
Mm.
Mac and cheese. My favourite.
I love you, Mommy.
I love you too, sweetheart.
I love you very much.
But, you know, it was very wrong of you
to call Mr Veeck a liar.
- You know that, don't you?
- He is a liar.
Ceci. You don't know that he's a liar.
- Yes, I do.
- How? How do you know that?
Natasha told me he still had
the Hello Kitty backpack in his desk.
I want to talk to you
about your imaginary friend, OK?
- She's not imaginary.
- She's not?
She's lost. Her mommy forgot about her
and now she's lost.
Like you.
- What are you talking about?
- Your mommy forgot about you, right?
Did someone tell you that?
- You did.
- No.
I didn't tell you that, Ceci.
Who told you that?
Are you gonna answer me?
I'm asking you a question.
- Who told you?
- Natasha told me.
Stop it. You stop lying to me.
Who told you?
- Hello?
- Hi, I'm just calling to arrange...
What are you trying to do? Sneaking into
her school, telling her it isn't any good?
Talking to her about my mother?
How dare you talk to her about my mother.
Look, I don't know who or what pressed
your wacko button today, and I don't care,
I'm calling to tell you I'm picking up Ceci
Saturday at nine.
I'll bring her back Sunday at six.
Don't play any games.
Have her there, 9am sharp.
- I tell you punks. No skating in here.
- Yeah, yeah.
She's cute.
Daddy's here!
Hey!
Look at you.
You shouldn't be smoking, Daddy.
I'm gonna quit real soon, honey. I promise.
- Thank you, Daddy.
- Satisfied?
As far as I'm concerned,
you can smoke as much as you like, Kyle.
Honey.
- I'll bring her back tomorrow at six.
- OK.
- Bye, Mommy.
- Bye, honey.
Hey, pretty lady. What's happening?
Laundry. Excuse me.
I got some dirty things I'd like you to clean.
Sorry.
I forgot my smokes.
Help!
Smart-ass kids.
Steve and Billy. They did this.
You'll see. Monday, the plumbers come.
They'll find something stuck in there.
They gum 'em up. Brats.
- Who's Natasha?
- What?
Who's Natasha Rimsky?
Little girl. 10F.
- Where is she now?
- How do I know? With her mother, I guess.
Couldrt stand living
with that crazy Russian husband of hers.
Took the little girl with her.
That Russki, he was a piece of work.
Always "blyad".
Look, there's a Laundromat
down the block.
I'll get you some garbage bags
so you don't get wet carrying them there.
The ítsy-bítsy spíder
clímbed up the vvater spout
Hi, Mommy.
Glad you like spaghetti and meatballs.
- It's my favourite.
- Your favourite?
I love them, Mommy.
I'm glad.
Mm.
I love you, Mommy.
You haven't said anything
about what your dad's new place is like.
- I don't like it.
- Really?
Yeah.
Well, maybe it's just new
and you need to get used to it.
But I don't wanna get used to it.
I don't wanna stay with Daddy.
I only wanna stay with you.
Well, your dad loves you. He'll be happy
that you spent this time with him.
Itsy-bítsy spíder
clímbed up the vvater spout
Dovvn came the raín
- Honey, can you stop singing that?
- Why? It happened.
I want to go to bed now, Mommy. I'm tired.
- Mommy?
- Mm?
I'm scared, Mommy.
I want to sleep with you.
Yeah.
I love you, Mommy.
Thank you for taking care of me.
Ceci?
- Hello?
- Mommy, where were you?
- I was napping.
- No, not now. Last night.
Where were you last night? I called
two times for you to say goodnight to me.
- Where were you?
- Last night?
OK, Daddy. Daddy says he's bringing
me home a half an hour early.
OK, Daddy. 5:30.
He says to be there in the lobby at 5:30.
- Don't fall asleep again, Mommy.
- OK.
I gotta go. I'm getting chocolate cake.
- Bye.
Dahlia, where have you been?
I left two messages.
I lost a day, Mary.
I took a pill, just one pill,
and it knocked me out for 24 hours.
That's never happened before.
And I'm tired, really tired.
It's like I haven't slept at all.
Dahlia, are you OK? Are you really OK?
My headache's gone. But the leak is back.
It's back?
I thought they were gonna fix that thing.
- Dahlia?
- Yeah?
- Are you OK?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
You have five new messages.
First new message.
Long nap, huh? Call me.
Message erased.
Next message.
Hi, Jeff Platzer here. I got the preliminaries
from your husband's lawyer
and I need to touch base with you about
his accusations as soon as possible.
Believe it or not I'm actually available
on Sunday afternoon until five.
If you are, would you call my cell?
OK. Bye.
- Mrs Williams?
- Yeah.
Hi. I'm your lawyer.
- Hi.
- I'm sorry it's such a mess.
- No, it's OK.
I just moved into a new office
and they've painted it.
I can't stand the smell so I'm improvising.
OK.
- Hi.
- So...
- OK.
Your husband's claiming
you're mentally unstable
because your father
was physically abusive
and your mother was an alcoholic
who abandoned you.
That's...
unbelievable.
- What do my parents have to do with this?
- That's my question exactly.
What's more relevant is that your husband
says you suffer from crippling migraines
and paranoid delusions.
He says he'll submit school reports
that show your daughter
is beginning to share your fantasy life.
"Cecilia is now having trouble
distinguishing between
what is real and what is not."
It's a lie. It's a lie.
In child custody briefs, it's standard
to make these kinds of accusations.
Don't take it too seriously.
But I do need to know what, if anything,
in your husband's narrative
has some semblance, some shred of fact
that he might produce in court.
Well, I get migraines.
Yeah. That's true.
But they've never interfered
with my ability to do anything.
You can talk to my doctor about that. He'll
tell you they've certainly never crippled me.
Um...
As for Ceci, I think
she's a little bit Ionely right now.
Her father's abandoned her and she was
forced to move from her neighbourhood.
So...
she's developed an imaginary friend.
But that's normal.
That's fine. But for future reference, when
you're talking to, for example, a judge,
I would stay away from phrases like,
"her father's abandoned her".
It's important, when the other side
is being so melodramatic,
- to sound like we're the sane ones.
- Right.
- That's all I'm saying.
- OK.
- I'd like to notch that.
- Oh, yeah, man.
Hey, sweetheart.
- Mommy?
- Yeah.
- Look what Daddy gave me.
- Wow.
- That's great, You're so lucky.
- Listen, next Saturday's a problem.
Can we do Sunday and I'll bring her
first thing in the morning
for school on Monday?
Yeah. Yeah, that's fine.
- Come on, honey. Say bye to Daddy.
- Bye, Daddy. Thanks for the Barbie.
- Did you do that ponytail by yourself?
- Yeah.
- It's a good one.
- Thanks.
- I like the collar.
Honey, you know what,
I forgot to do something.
I'm gonna be right back.
Will you wait right here for me?
- Don't go anywhere, OK?
- OK.
Be right back.
Two... one.
Ceci?
Ceci? Stay in the elevator.
I'm bringing you down.
Ceci, can you hear me?
Bake me a cake as fast as you can.
Roll it, pat it and mark it with a B.
- No more pretending to play with Natasha.
- She won't let me.
Well, then you stop talking to her.
You tell her I said so.
You tell her your mommy said
you can't play with her any more.
OK, Mommy.
- Hello?
- Hi, Mr Platzer.
I'm sorry to call you late,
but I think my husband...
Mrs Williams, it's Sunday night.
I can't talk.
Yeah, I know. I'm sorry. I just need
to tell you this as soon as possible.
I think my husband
is trying to drive me crazy.
Either that or he's hoping
that I'm gonna act crazy.
- Hang on. Let me call you right back.
- OK.
You say neither of the Rimskys
are living there?
No, no one's there.
So Kyle's paying these kids.
I mean, he must be paying these kids
to mess around with the water
and the backpack. And the elevator.
I went into the elevator the other day
and the buttons were burned off.
Mrs Williams, it's Sunday night
and I'm at the movies with my family.
If I don't want to be handling
my own divorce, I gotta get back. So...
I'll call you tomorrow
and we'll sort this out. All right?
Yeah. Absolutely.
Get down!
This time make sure
you put it in the garbage truck.
- Where did you...
- Those kids have been playing games,
moving it around the building.
And they were upstairs again so now
there's water all over my bedroom floor.
- They're running the water again?
- Mm-hm.
I thought you were gonna
change the lock on 10F.
Murray didn't authorise it.
He has to send me a 112B form.
- Look, is the plumber here yet?
- No, no. It's only 8:15.
OK, look. I left a message for Mr Murray.
I told him I need my problem fixed first.
So when the plumber gets here,
send him up to my apartment
or you and Murray
can both talk to my lawyer. OK?
Do you remember
what we talked about last night?
- Yes, Mommy.
- OK.
See you later, OK?
- Hello.
- Hi. Jeff Platzer here.
- Hi, Mr Platzer.
- Listen, I did a little homework on Rimsky
and I think I turned up the missing mother
in a hospital in San Diego.
Why are you looking for her?
I figured the Rimskys might want to know
their apartment's being used by strangers.
Mrs Williams, we're never gonna prove
your husband's behind this harassment.
And trying to do that is just playing
his game. He wants you to look paranoid.
We gotta deal with this straight,
as if it's all on the level.
So that's what we'll do,
we'll play it straight.
I'm due in court, I'll call you
when I get ahold of Mrs Rimsky.
In the meantime, just sit tight.
- I will. Thanks so much.
- OK.
- Bye.
- Abigail's making a storm, sweetheart.
- Done!
Done? You remember you have
to sign your name so you know whose it is.
You don't want me to take that home
and say I did it, do you?
I like that. Pirates?
Stop it.
Stop it, I told you, leave me alone.
- We've got rainbows...
- Stop it!
Stop it!
You're gonna get cleaned up
and when you're done
you're gonna come back and sit with me
and we'll read a story together.
Then maybe we'll talk about your friend.
Go on.
Ceci!
Go away!
- Where is she?
- She passed out in the bathroom.
We don't know what happened.
There was water all over the place.
- We took her to the hospital.
- Hospital?
We just wanted to check her out.
It's school policy. We couldn't reach you.
I had an emergency at work,
I didn't get my messages for two hours.
We called her father
and he's gonna meet her at the hospital.
- OK. Which hospital?
- It's the one right here on the island.
Kyle took her.
They released her and he took her.
- Did they say what was wrong?
- They said, you know, it's nothing serious.
She fainted but...
I'm trying to find him. I called his home
number, I called his cell phone number,
I called his office number,
and he's avoiding me
so I need to know what to do.
Can I go to his apartment?
Mrs Williams, I need you to calm down.
I need it, your daughter needs it.
Just calm down, OK?
I'm sorry. I know you don't know me,
but you have to believe me.
I'm not crazy, I'm really not.
- I believe you, Mrs Williams.
- I'm really not.
Just go home. Your husband and your
daughter are probably waiting for you.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Ceci.
- No new messages.
- Oh, God.
- Hello?
- Hello? It's Jeff. Are they there?
- No.
- They're not there?
No. There's no message.
There's water everywhere.
Mrs Williams, Mrs Williams, calm down.
Calm down.
- She can't be here.
- What do you want me to do?
Oh, God.
I can't be her mother,
I don't know how to be myself.
Ceci!
I hate you.
Get away from me, you little bitch.
Fuck!
I hate you! I hate you!
Bitch!
Sorry about this. I really had no idea.
I would've come down myself
a long time ago.
Better open it.
Hello?
Jesus.
Look at this. This is appalling.
This is appalling.
The plumber's on his way. I'm paying him
double overtime so he can get here tonight.
Hello?
- I'll get some of these lights on.
- Mrs Williams?
- You OK?
- I'm awake.
The plumber will be here in 15 minutes.
- Mr Murray?
- This is just a big misunderstanding. OK?
Mr Veeck did not keep me informed.
This will be fixed tonight.
- Or she's staying at the Plaza, right?
- It will definitely be fixed tonight.
- And I want to talk to Veeck.
- I will get him.
You OK?
- Migraine, huh?
- Yeah.
- I'll keep my voice low.
- Thanks.
I spoke with your husband's lawyer
and Ceci's fine.
Kyle will bring her to school in the morning.
OK.
Now, this part is gonna piss you off.
They want Ceci to see a psychologist
to be evaluated.
There's nothing we can do about that
but say yes. So we're saying yes.
OK.
- Here we are.
- Mr Veeck.
I had an interesting conversation
with Mrs Rimsky today.
She was very surprised to hear
her daughter isn't living upstairs.
- In 10F?
- Mm-hm.
- You said they left together.
- That's what the Russian said.
No, she left without her daughter.
She didn't think she could take care of her.
Mrs Rimsky's an alcoholic.
She claimed she was going for treatment,
and had to leave the girl behind
with the father.
You knew that, didn't you?
Only Mr Rimsky didn't take Natasha
with him.
I spoke with Grandma Rimsky
in Moscow today
and she said her son
is living with her alone.
- So he lied to me. What do I know?
- You had to know.
Well, we'll find out tomorrow. I have
a phone appointment with Mr Rimsky.
- Why did you lie about the little girl?
- I didn't want to get involved, that's all.
Did you see Natasha after her mother left?
It's a simple question, Veeck.
Yeah. I see her. I see her that afternoon.
I see her playing on the stairs.
Then the next day the father tells me she
leave with the mother. I ask no questions.
- Well, if he killed her, it's not my business.
- "Killed her"?
"If he killed her"?
Plumber!
You got a lot more than a leak to fix,
Mr Murray.
Mr Veeck.
- If you could just...
- Come on in, just right inside.
Thank you.
Some kind of pipe or something.
Yeah, well, see, that is a brand-new pipe.
So, this will all be patched tomorrow.
- By professionals.
- By professionals. Good as new.
It better be. I'm calling NYPD
to report a child is missing.
OK. I mean, I'm sure there's
a simple explanation for that, but...
So, goodnight.
And, again, I am so sorry about all this.
- Goodnight.
- You gonna be OK?
- Yeah. I'll be fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm feeling much better, actually.
- I gotta go. Family.
- OK. Mm.
I'll keep my cell on all night
and if you need me just call.
- Any hour.
- Thanks.
- Thanks again. Bye.
- OK. Bye.
She left you behind.
They both left you behind.
Help me.
Wait!
I told Murray, I told him a million times.
It's not my job. I'm not a goddamn plumber.
How you feeling? You OK?
- You warmed up?
- I'm OK.
Cops think Veeck probably
left the tank open and somehow she fell in.
They even think he might have discovered
she'd fallen in weeks ago.
That's why he hadrt cleaned it in so long.
They might have enough to charge him
with criminal negligence.
They'd arrest the parents, but they're out
of state and there are no witnesses, so...
The truth is, they'll probably
never know what happened.
Her mother left her.
The father assumed
that she was with her mom,
and the mother assumed
she was with her father.
Guess everyone just assumed.
No one really cared what happened to her.
That's what it looks like.
I'll tell Mary you've been a prince.
You just accomplished the impossible,
Mrs Williams.
You actually made me glad
I went to law school.
- Thank you.
- It's OK.
I can probably get you
a year's free rent out of Murray.
Oh! No, it's OK.
I'm moving.
- Call me in the morning, OK?
- Yeah.
- Come on, princess.
- Bye, Daddy.
Bye.
- How are you feeling?
- Good.
Yeah?
OK. I'll be here after school to pick you up.
See you after school.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Thank you for taking care
of Ceci yesterday.
It's OK. I'm really worried
about her mental state.
- I am too.
- You are?
Yeah.
So, I've been thinking...
I don't want her
to have to choose between us.
- What do you mean?
- I want to look for a place in Jersey City
so that shared custody
will be easier for both of us.
And we can do, you know,
one week with me, and one week with you.
Or maybe split the week.
We can see what works best.
- You serious?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, you know, you were right about the
school here. I checked it out. It's good.
- Maybe I could get a place...
- No, it's fine.
After this, we'll get a...
a place in Jersey City.
I'll see you later.
- When are we moving?
- Not until next week, sweetheart.
This is winter stuff though
so we can pack it up now.
You OK? Are you feeling OK?
What are you thinking about?
Why did her mommy forget about her?
Do you know how much I love you?
- You sure?
- Mm-hm.
- Do you know I would do anything for you?
- Yes.
That's a promise.
- Honey, do you want bubbles tonight?
- Uh-huh.
There you are.
- That's so great, Dahlia.
- Well, I think it's gonna be for the best.
And moving out of here,
that is definitely for the best.
What do you want to do? Be a chef? OK.
Let's see if we can make you a chef hat.
There.
Now, what are you going to cook?
Mac and cheese?
Look, I should go get Ceci out of the tub
before she turns into a prune.
- She's so cute.
- So... Oh!
Here she is now.
Yeah. So I will talk to you tomorrow.
- OK. Take care. Bye.
- OK. You too.
Goodnight.
- Mommy, can you read me a story?
- Course I can, honey.
Let's see which one you picked.
We haven't read this one
in a long time, have we?
"There were once a man and a woman
who had long in vain wished for a child."
We need more snow, don't you think?
Then let's get some more snow.
...beautiful Rapunzel.
Don't leave me.
I want you to be my mommy.
- Don't leave me.
- Ceci!
You can't leave me.
Ceci!
No!
Oh, God.
Let her go! You let her go!
No!
No! Please!
Natasha! Let her go! Please.
We'll stay. We'll stay here with you.
What do you want?
I'll be your mother.
- Please.
- Forever?
Forever.
Forever. Yes.
I'll be your mother forever.
Take me. Please, take me.
Yeah, OK. So we got an 11-46,
Caucasian female, aged 30,
no apparent cause of death,
and a six-year-old girl with shock.
Trying to locate the father.
Ceci.
Let's go home, honey.
Would you get the door?
We did a whole bunch of them.
A whole neighbourhood.
What was this one about?
Do you remember?
That was me and then that was you.
- That was a tree.
- A tree.
- And then that's a little angel.
- Beautiful gold wings on the angel.
Come on.
OK, honey, let's walk.
What's wrong with you?
Come on.
Ceci.
Ceci?
Open the door.
Push the button, Ceci.
Open it. Open the door. Ceci!
My beautiful girl.
Whenever you need me, I'm here.
OK, Daddy. Let's go.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org