Joseph, you're a genius.
That's my job. I'm a surgeon.
But I'm no genius.
Oh, my God.
It's Mitch.
I was just telling
your uncle here he's a genius.
Now he's arguing with me.
Well, you know us doctors,
very famous for our humility.
- How you feeling?
- Like a man who can't wait to tee off.
How long till I can
start playing again?
Well, let's see how you heal first.
Could be four to six weeks,
Really? That long?
We only want to
do this once.
Okay.
That's good.
It was great to see
Ellie and the baby.
When are they heading
back to New York?
Beth and Grace are taking them
to the airport right now.
Bet Beth hates to see them go.
She's fine.
Ethan, Ethan, we must say good-bye.
I know it's gonna be hard, but.
We just gotta suck it up
and not let our emotions get the best of us.
Is that okay?
Is that okay with you?
Because I know you're
thinking hard.
Well, when you finish your thesis,
you should come to New York.
We'll invite Jeff’s friend for dinner.
I don't think he's my type.
You haven't even met him.
- Could you cover your mouth?
- Sorry.
Maybe you're right.
All right, Mom, you gotta hand him over.
Give Grandma a kiss.
Give Mi-Mi a kiss good-bye.
Give Mi-Mi kisses.
- No...
- Hey, buddy.
Now, call me if it looks like
he's about to take his first step.
I'll fly to New York.
Okay, we'll keep him off
the floor till you get there.
- All right, honey. Bye-bye, love.
- I love you.
How can a person not cover
his mouth when he sneezes,
especially around a baby?
Yeah, especially around you.
Babies are exhausting.
It's different when they're yours.
You're great with Ethan.
Were you that patient with us?
Still am.
What did I do with my keys? There.
Do you think he'll remember us
next time he sees us?
- God, I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- That's okay, honey.
- He won't forget you.
- I know. I know. I know.
- I'm sorry. I'm an idiot.
No, you're not an idiot.
Oh, God.
Please.
Hi, Dad.
I thought I called your mom.
You did. She's busy.
Did they get off all right?
They're on the plane.
Ask Mom if she remembered
to pick up my stuff at the cleaners.
Did you get Dad's stuff?
Yes, she did.
Put her on.
I have to ask her something.
She'll call you back.
Well, she can't.
I'm going into surgery.
Wait a minute. She's upset.
Of course. Is she crying?
A little, we all cried.
Okay, you can do this.
Tell her to please calm down.
Okay.
Thank you, sweetie.
- I'll drive.
- No.
Okay.
Dad can be kind of
a prick sometimes.
He thinks I overreact.
When you do what he does,
you gotta have a thick skin.
Honey, he's not a prick.
You always defend him.
Oh, my God.
- Turn around!
- What?
- Oh, my God!
- What? We're on the freeway.
We got to go back,
I saw something.
What... Like a body?
- Take that exit right there!
- I'm taking it!
- God, take it easy, Miss Daisy.
- Turn around!
I can't turn around.
We're on the freeway!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Mom, are you sure about this?
Get out on this side.
No shit.
Here.
Hey! Hey, fella!
Here, boy.
Hey!
- Don't touch him!
- Okay.
He's filthy.
- He could have rabies.
- I know.
- It's okay.
- Why isn't he standing up?
Is this like one of those
subway accidents,
where you lift him up
and all his guts fall out?
Honey, he's terrified.
What can we feed him
to make friends?
I know. All right, I got it.
Yes, hello, 9-1-1?
Listen, this isn't
a life-and-death emergency, exactly.
No one has a gun or anything.
No, I said no gun!
- I got it!
- Hello?
- Here we go!
- Damn it.
- Look, look, look, look.
Ethan loves these.
He loves these.
I think you will too.
Watch it!
Hey, buddy. That's a boy.
Good boy!
There. Oh, my God, he took it.
9-1-1?
Thank God, I am on I-70
near Chambers Road.
And this is a life-and-death
emergency.
Never mind. We're cool.
Mom, look.
We're just not allowed
to deal with animals of an unknown threat.
I mean, this...
- Durley.
- Yeah?
- We gotta go.
- What do you mean?
I talked to Animal Control.
They'll be here sometime
in the next two hours.
Two hours!
That's all you're gonna do for us?
Well, no, in this circumstance,
we are authorized to
put the animal down.
I think you'd better go.
I'm sorry, folks.
Them's the rules.
Good luck.
Do you think we
can move him?
You mean, touch him?
This is one of those rare occasions
when I wish I had a man I could call.
Me too.
Honey, there really are
a lot of great men out there.
You have to make some effort.
Mom, let's keep our eye on the ball.
How are we supposed to move him?
Where is it?
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay.
Here is a giraffe.
What kind of assholes left you
out here all alone, huh?
Silk. Good idea.
Good boy. Good boy.
Now, nobody's gonna hurt you.
Get ready for him to go crazy.
Just get ready. Here we go.
There you go. Okay.
Okay. There you go.
Now, here we go. Okay.
Come on. Come on, darling.
- Come on, boy.
- Come on.
- Take a right.
- Look! No broken bones!
Look at that! Yeah.
It's gonna be so warm in there.
Now, on the count of three,
we're gonna throw this shirt over his head
and lift him in, okay?
Don't you want to use
one of Dad's suits to protect the seat?
Pay attention.
Ready?
Okay!
One, two...
There.
Three.
Thank you.
Hello, I'm Dr. Bhoola.
So, Mrs. Winter, you saved this dog's life?
I don't know about that.
Not many people would have stopped
in this weather.
You must have
a dog of your own.
No, no.
Then you must be a dog person.
Well, I don't know.
How about you?
Are you a dog person?
Yeah, I can't keep my hands off 'em.
Well, there's no chip in him.
There's no way to trace the owner.
He's a little nicked up.
He has a cut on his muzzle,
a few hot spots.
We'll get the blood panel back tomorrow.
But if I had to guess,
there's nothing wrong with this dog
a few good meals and a bath won't fix.
That's great.
I hope one of you
will take him home.
I just can't.
I have my thesis,
and it's time-consuming,
and I don't even know
why I'm doing it.
It just goes on and on.
And I can't have pets
in my building, so...
Mrs. Winter?
Me? No, no, no.
No, the last thing my husband
wants right now is a dog, so...
That's too bad.
His teeth are worn down,
if you'd just like to have a look.
Yeah? No.
Yeah, it looks like he was left alone a lot
and spent his time chewing on a chain.
He's about seven.
And the chances of a dog like him
being adopted from the shelter are minimal.
So in about a week,
he's likely to be put down.
Mom?
- Good dog.
- Beth?
Hi, honey.
Dad, we're in here.
Hello.
Hey, it's okay, boy. It's okay.
Stay calm. Stay calm.
You know, I think he's just startled by you.
That's all. Easy.
Hey! No!
No barking!
What's going on?
Whose dog is this?
Mom's. She saved his life.
He's not mine.
I'm just gonna find him a home.
Why is he here?
I just couldn't let them
take him to the pound.
So what I'm gonna do is,
I'm gonna call
a few rescue societies tomorrow,
and somebody's going to want him.
Yeah, but not us, right?
We're not getting a dog, right?
I think you should keep him. I'll help.
You're at school.
She's not gonna come back
every morning and walk a dog,
- and neither am I.
- I wouldn't mind doing that.
Beth, I don't want a dog.
I told you, I'm gonna find him a home.
Yeah, I know you.
And what's that supposed to mean?
- That was Dr. Bhoola.
- Who?
The veterinarian.
He's gonna stop by.
What is he...
He's coming here now?
Yeah, he has some
medicine or something.
I'm gonna use your shower,
'cause it's filthy in here.
The veterinarian makes house calls?
He's very attractive.
Did you see that?
- He's an amazing dog.
- I know.
- You did a great thing by picking him up.
- I couldn't leave him.
A lot of people just don't care.
Joseph, I want you
to meet Dr. Bhoola.
Sam, please.
- It's nice to meet you, Dr. Winter.
- And you.
Is this enough paper?
Yeah, that's great.
You don't want to get this stuff
on the floor.
Come on, buddy.
Okay, so...
There's the irritation, right there.
So you give it a little spritz, like so.
- What are you naming him?
- Freeway.
You've named him?
Freeway, I bet you didn't think
you were going to a spa today, did you?
Looks like you lucked out, buddy.
Well, we're not keeping him.
So says the pharaoh.
If you keep him,
you'll be getting a great dog.
Well, thanks for coming by.
I hope my patients don't hear
that you make house calls.
Do you think I could
take him for a walk?
Yeah, let's see how
he does on a leash.
I'll go with you, if you like.
That'd be great. I'll get my coat.
Would you like to come?
No, no, not at all. No.
I'm going to clean that bathroom.
- Okay.
Come, Freeway.
Let's go.
Come on, boy.
- Should I go with them?
- God, no.
Come on.
Hey, wait for us! Freeway!
Hey, where do you
think you're going, huh?
Hurry up, honey.
I'm here. I'm behind you.
Look what I found. Look at that.
Yeah. Come on.
How did you two meet?
- Don't ask.
- Don't... yeah.
- No.
- I don't want to talk about it.
- Why not?
- Let's just say.
Well, it was embarrassing.
There you go.
That's his choice.
He can get as many
opinions as he wants.
Morning!
Carmen, I'm out of basil.
Can you save me?
There's extra in the shelf
behind the spice rack.
Good.
- Carmen, we can't find
the big ladder.
- Don't talk to me, I
have to get this right.
The ladder.
In the shed, left side,
under the tarp.
- The ceremony is starting
- Okay.
Aunt Grace is so pretty!
Dad.
Namaste.
Welcome, everyone. I'm Todd.
Grace and Sam have foolishly asked me
to officiate today.
I recently was ordained
on the Internet, about last Wednesday,
so feel confident,
I know what I'm doing.
If the disk is massively herniated,
it's either got to be a laminectomy
or it'd be microdiscectomy.
It's unavoidable.
Have Ruthie send the MRI up here,
would you?
- Right now.
- Come on, Ethan.
I'll see you Monday.
Dad, everyone's leaving.
Grandma's waiting.
We have to go. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Listen, I know he calls your mother "Mi-Mi,"
but does he have to call me "Pee-Pee"?
He's trying to say "Poppy. "
He just can't say it yet,
We're working on it,
though, right? Poppy?
You're doing a great job with him.
Thank you.
Did you see Sam playing with him?
I think he's going to be
a pretty amazing father.
- Yeah. Hope so.
- Hope so,
Speaking of amazing,
you girls looked amazing today.
I've never seen
Gracie look so happy
Yeah.
Bride.
- Hi!
- Here's the pretty bride.
Hi, honey.
- All right, we're loading up.
- Okay,
Gracie, you know, it's not too late
if you want to change your mind.
Maybe after the honeymoon.
I want to see Bora-Bora.
Fine. Just don't sleep with him.
Dad, you know how when your daughter
asks for something on her wedding day,
you have to do it?
What, is that from The Godfather?
These next few weeks may be hard on Mom.
I'm sure, she'll be fine.
Will you make an effort?
Well, I always do.
More?
Will you try harder?
Promise?
Of course I will.
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
- Get home safe.
- Thanks.
So why didn't Joseph invite me
to stay tonight
since you're going to be here?
Did you want to stay?
No, I can't sleep in this altitude.
Where's your new boyfriend?
I want to say good-bye.
- Really?
- I'm right here, darling girl.
Let go of me, you sexy minx.
We don't want everybody
to know, do we?
Muriel, it's a delight.
I should have known
Penny's mom would be a fox.
Stop it, please.
Mom? Mom?
I can't sit in the back. I'll get carsick.
Especially on these horrible roads
you've got here.
I know, Mom.
That's why I'm putting you in the front.
I'll probably get sick anyway.
Well, that's the spirit, Mom.
Here, you know,
that's why I gave you that Tigan,
to help with the carsickness.
I didn't take it.
I don't know what's in that stuff.
You know what's best for you, Mom.
Bye.
Jeff, thanks for sacrificing your sanity
for the good of the family.
No problem. I'll get her to the airport.
Sam, you got a lot to live up to.
Wait till you get to know my family.
- Say it? Say it?
- Bye, Ethan.
- Say "Poppy "
- Poppy
- Pee-Pee.
- We're trying!
That'll do. Love you.
- Bye, I love you.
- Bye.
I love you! See you soon!
- Bye-bye!
- Bye, Mom.
Bye!
You shouldn't have told
her we were staying.
Bye!
- Bye!
Bye-bye!
Have a wonderful lime!
Bye!
It was really nice, actually.
Everybody was in a good mood.
No, Penny didn't say anything.
Violet, no one was insulted.
Don't worry about it.
I told them it was important
for you to be at your thing. it's fine.
Russell?
No one will mistake him
for a rocket scientist.
Except for my grandmother, who loved him.
Kind of wish she'd marry him.
Okay.
Yeah, go ahead.
All right. I love you.
Hi.
Why didn't your wife come?
I'm not married. You're Carmen, right?
I'm Bryan. I'm Joseph and Beth's nephew.
So, what, you live here?
You take care of this place?
Caretaker a hard job?
My other two jobs are harder.
What's going on with your neck?
It's killing me.
- Maybe I can help.
- Are you a masseur?
No, I'm a surgeon.
Maybe you can help me slit my throat.
Wow, tough day.
Wait, let me get it. I got it.
All right, where to?
- Out there.
- Okay.
You guys really rocked. You didn't rock.
You were blue grassing. I'm sorry.
- Had a good time.
- Thank you. Okay.
Oh, God.
Sweetie. Hello, sweetie.
- Cheers.
We've unloaded both girls.
That just leaves Freeway.
No, he's not going anywhere.
He's a real mama's boy.
What do you think about Russell?
Penny has outdone herself this time.
I don't know. It could be serious.
She said she wanted to tell us something.
Maybe they're getting married.
- To that idiot?
- Hey...
Come on.
He's got the personality
of a used car salesman.
Penny is a bright woman.
He charmed your mother at the reception.
Exactly my point.
Russell, Penny tells me
you're in demolition.
Twenty-two years, eight in London.
Really? I love London.
Greatest city in the world,
aside from Omaha.
We should all go there.
Well...
So you're no longer in demolition?
- What happened?
- The business blew up.
Completely collapsed. Demolished.
What are you doing now?
You know,
I got something pretty good brewin'.
I'm so glad you sat us with,
you know, Sam's parents.
Was that Pramilla's sister in the pink sari?
I know. Gorgeous.
What have you got "brewin'"?
Well, we don't want
to steal your thunder today,
you know, 'cause that was
one heck of a wedding you put on,
but since you're family
I gotta spill the beans.
No, I thought we'd wait until tomorrow.
We're opening an English pub.
Where... Who's opening a pub?
In England, is that.
In Omaha! Me and Penny.
I'm sorry. What?
Wait a minute. Penny.
You're not leaving the newspaper?
Well, [was about to be laid off,
and so I took the buyout.
At least they'll pay me for a year.
How could you not tell me this?
Do you know there's not one English pub
in Omaha?
If you want bangers and mash,
you got to go all the way to Des Moines.
Really? Who's financing this?
You know, finally, you'll be able
to get a decent pint in Nebraska,
and fish and chips, I mean, the real thing,
in newspaper, soaked with grease.
And...
- Excuse me.
- I'm sorry.
No, it's okay. Don't worry.
This is genius, if I do say so myself.
It'll be the only place in the Midwest,
that I know of,
where you can have... Are you ready?
Warm beer.
Wow. Warm beer.
Yeah.
Where's the money coming from?
Bottom-line guy, Bryan.
You got that from your mother.
First thing Penny asked me.
Good. What'd you tell her?
Well, I got some money saved,
and I sold my condo.
And I got a friend whose brother
wants to put up half the money,
after we raise the first half.
And, you know,
we're talking to other investors.
Okay, what are you contributing to this?
Not one cent, if Russell has his way.
- Nothing?
- That's right. Nothing.
Look, I mean, of course,
we may dip into my buyout
until we have some cash flow.
And Russell's moving in,
so we won't have that expense.
Penny's enrolled in a bartending class.
Mom.
We want to give all of you the opportunity
to get in on the ground floor.
How would you like to all be par!- owners
of the Partridge and the Plough?
Mom, are you serious?
Yeah?
Wait, wait. He's canceling on me
so that he can have
the surgery done by Ed Ritter?
Does he know I trained Ed Ritten?
Ruthie, tell me his exact words.
Really?
"Surgeons reach their peak at 45"?
Who told him that?
Freeway! Shit!
I got to go, Ruthie. I'll see you Monday.
Freeway!
Hi, Ellie called.
They got your mother on her plane.
And you know what? Ethan asked about you.
You know what he said? He is so cute.
He said, "Where's Pee-Pee?"
Honey, what are we going to do
about the Partridge and the Plough?
- What are we going to do about Russell?
- I don't know.
Has Freeway been in here?
I thought he was with you.
He was, but he took off on me.
What? Wait a minute. Where's the dog?
I told you. He took off.
When was this?
About 20 minutes ago.
He chased a deer and wouldn't come back.
Did you use the whistle?
I whistled.
I didn't have the whistle, per se.
You were on the phone, right?
It was an emergency.
God.
He's probably right outside.
Freeway! Come on, boy!
Freeway!
Where are you, sweetheart?
You lost the dog
while you were talking on the phone!
Freeway!
He's not lost, believe me.
- He knows how to get home.
- Freeway!
Is something wrong?
The dog's run off.
Shit. We'll be right there.
Yeah, be right there.
Dogs find their way across the country
all the time. Haven't you read that?
Freeway!
Is Freeway missing?
Yes, we've got to spread out
and search before it's too dark.
I'll get the keys.
- Freeway!
- You're panicking.
Don't you know how much
that dog means to me?
Yes, of course I do. I like him too.
I'm just not obsessed with him.
How could you be,
when you're obsessed with yourself?
- Where'd you see him last?
- On the back trail.
- Wait, the dog's gone?
- Yeah'
Come on, let's go.
I'm with you. Where should we start looking?
Okay, we'll go this way.
I'm gonna go out to the road
and look around.
I got a light. I'll come with you.
Wait, wait, wait, wait! Use your whistle!
Hi!
Okay.
Here, boy!
- Careful.
- Shoot.
Bryan thinks I should have my knee scoped.
Yeah, I've been begging you
to do that for years,
You can't fix a torn meniscus
with herbal enemas.
You know, Bryan's much more open
to Eastern approaches.
And it's colonics, not enemas.
You should try one.
It might dislodge that enormous bug.
- What?
- You're so negative about Russell.
Don't you think we've given
the pub a lot of thought?
The Pig and the Poke? No.
What are you doing with this guy?
Just because
your first husband was a genius
and he turned out to be a dick
doesn't mean you can never trust
another man with half a brain.
You're the dumb one.
Have you ever heard
of emotional intelligence?
You know, Russell makes you
look like a five-year-old.
Plus, he's the most generous lover
I've ever known.
Stop. Spare me that image.
Freeway, come back,
you son of a bitch bastard!
Your girlfriend,
she didn't come to the wedding.
Doesn't she like Grace?
Violet likes Grace just fine.
She had to go on a retreat with her firm.
A retreat?
Yeah, they all go away somewhere
and talk about IPOs, government regulations.
- To avoid the regulations?
- Yeah.
No, how to comply with them, sort of.
Anyway, it's my mother
that is hard on Violet.
She says you can't trust a woman
who wears four inch heels all the time.
All the time?
She looks good in them.
My mother says, "What's she selling?"
I have an idea. Wait.
- Come on, boy.
- Hey, buddy!
I'm just so pissed
he didn't take the whistle.
Joseph's got a lot on his mind
with the wedding
and then our news
about the Partridge and the Plough.
Trust me, he wasn't thinking about you
or the wedding.
If you want his attention,
herniate your disk.
- Hey, buddy!
- Hey, guys, stop talking about Joseph!
We can hear you!
We could use a little help here.
- Wait a second.
- Her knee, her knee.
- Get some ice on this
- Don't. Your back...
- It's nothing. It's nothing.
- This way.
- What did you do...
- Honey, it's my knee.
What are you looking at?
It's 10:00,
and you are deep
in Possum's Burrow on KGO-FM.
Coming up, we have Blue
by the Living Sisters.
Hello, big bear!
Oh, my God.
Woof!
Possum!
Wow.
You know, I had a dream last night
that you were gonna come down here.
I need a favor.
Anything, darling.
What's this, fresh meat?
I'm Bryan.
Bryan.
Are you ready to have your heart broke, man?
She's legendary.
Possum, my boss lost her dog.
I'm on it.
All right, everybody,
I got a friend who needs our help.
She's looking for a lost dog,
big brown-white mutt,
means about as much to his people as...
Carmen means to me.
Get to the point, Possum.
Dog's name is Freeway.
So everybody step outside
and give a big shout-out for Freeway.
There's a cash reward, if that matters.
Here you go.
Now, you need to keep that elevated.
And I want you to take these.
What are they?
It's a mild anti-inflammatory
and a muscle relaxant
They're organic.
Made from the hearts of endangered species.
You know I don't take chemicals
into my body.
You want to be laid up here
by yourself tomorrow
while we're all out looking for the dog?
Say, "Aah. "
Thank you.
New remember, everybody,
if you see Freeway, call this number...
He dedicated Searching to you.
Which one?
Erykah Badu.
Nice.
It's gonna be fine.
He'll probably show up in the morning.
He's out there with coyotes
and bears and porcupines.
But he's a dog. He can take care of himself.
But he has no wilderness experience.
Beth, I think you're overreacting.
I think you're under-reacting,
for somebody who actually lost the dog.
You know, I'm so sick of you
judging my feelings all the time!
Wouldn't want to be sleeping
with her tonight.
They are out of alignment.
No, the dog is definitely not black.
No, I do not want to come and check him out.
Possum had to mention my name.
Well, maybe we'll find him at the shelter.
It's a wasted trip.
Freeway is not there.
How do you know?
I know things.
You know things?
Like, what do you know?
I know Russell would like to be your friend.
Well, yeah, of course he would. He's
trying to close the deal with my mother.
And I know you were glad
Violet did not come to the wedding.
Excuse me. We've lost our dog.
Is there a report we can fill out?
Well, how long's the dog been missing?
Since last night.
Well, old Pipe here,
he'll take off for three days
anytime some bitch goes into heat.
He can smell 'em from five miles out.
That's really fascinating.
Our dog is neutered.
Yeah, could you put word out
to your deputies?
You'd have to talk to
the Sheriff about that.
And how could we reach him?
- The Sheriff?
- Yeah!
He's probably fishing down by Slater's.
Hey, what's going on?
This is where I found Django.
Django died last year.
Your dog?
And spirit-mate.
Passed over in my arms.
I'm sorry.
He was 24 years old.
It's unusual for a dog to live that long.
What?
Good-bye, little boy.
I know.
Good-bye, beautiful boy.
I know someone will come for you.
A spirit-mate?
No. He's waiting for a man.
Joseph, you're a doctor.
Is it my imagination,
or does your dick shrink
when you get older?
When you say "your dick"...
No, mature dicks, in general, dicks.
I think I see him.
Hey! Sheriff!
- Joseph Winter. Could we talk?
- Who?
Joseph Winter.
Well, look, tomorrow's Monday.
I'll be in the office all day, Joe.
Yeah, no, I understand.
I'm sorry about that, but it's an emergency.
You're the doctor, right? Who's that?
- Future brother-in-law.
- Nobody.
Well, what's the emergency, Joe?
We lost our dog.
Yeah, actually, they call me Joseph,
which I prefer.
His wife talked to your deputy,
but she didn't get too far.
Yeah, that'd be Chaz.
He wants my job, you know,
if it didn't interfere with ski season
or hunting season
or getting drunk season.
What kind of dog did you lose?
A mutt. My wife rescued him.
A what?
A mutt!
Look, let me come over there,
and you can talk to me
on my good ear, okay?
This is my day off!
Yeah, yeah, I realize that.
This all happened on the freeway, did it?
In the snow?
In January.
Well, your wife must have some brass balls
I'm telling you.
And your daughter,
she married the veterinarian, did she?
Yesterday, at our place.
Well, congratulations.
Thank you.
Hope they're happy.
What is it? Where does it hurt?
Kidney stone.
Okay, let's get you to a clinic.
No, I can move. I can...
Okay, you get this side.
Okay.
I can make it! I can make it I can make it.
Don't get hung up on the hook here.
Come on, boy. Come on.
- Bring my dogs.
- Come on. I got 'em.
- Bring my dogs!
- I will.
Gettin' old really sucks, Joe.
You're not old. What are you, 60?
63.
My fifth goddamn stone.
Maybe this one will pass quickly.
Maybe it'll be over in time
for my colonoscopy next week.
You wouldn't want to miss that.
You're a doctor.
Why don't you come up
with a better way to do that?
I'd make a fortune.
I don't want to be insulting,
but just... Man, you just...
What's your PSA?
1.2.
You're lucky.
How's your good cholesterol?
I only have bad.
What kind of doctor are you?
Spine surgeon.
When do they start
pushing you out of that deal?
- Let's boogie, Joe.
- Okay.
Clinic!
- Got you.
- Hammer down.
Hey.
Come on, Beth, let's go inside.
Come on.
It's getting chilly.
Well, the dog.
There's a place for you if you're hungry.
Beth, you should eat something.
Freeway is gonna show up, Beth.
He has the microchip. He has the collar.
We've got flyers everywhere.
It's about the only thing
playing on the radio.
They're getting complaints from people
who'd like to hear a little music.
We've done everything we can.
Someone will find him and call.
Let's talk about tomorrow.
My first appointments at 11:00
and Bryan has rounds starting at noon.
So that means Beth, Bryan and I
have to leave for the airport
no later than 6:30.
Penny, Carmen can drive you guys
to the airport later on.
I'm not leaving.
Honey, what are you gonna do?
You can't walk around all day
calling his name.
I'm up for another day.
We're not leaving Beth up here alone.
I'm not saying to leave Beth alone.
Look, I think that's great.
If you guys feel you can stay, that's cool.
That's fine. Yeah.
It's very nice of you.
The world goes on, though. Bryan and I,
we do have responsibilities to get back to.
I'm trying to be realistic.
What, that makes me the insensitive clod?
Yes,
Would you be leaving if I were missing?
That's ridiculous. It's nothing like that.
- Would you?
- I'm not even gonna dignify that.
- Dignify it.
- Beth, everything is a crisis with you.
There's no sense of proportion.
You just don't get it, do you?
What? What is it I don't get?
We haven't lost a person. We've lost a dog.
Love is love.
It doesn't matter if it's a dog.
Yeah, I know you love the dog
You don't think I've noticed
that you care more about him
than you do about me?
Jesus, Joseph, I don't believe
you're making this about you.
Mom.
When I rescued Freeway,
I made a promise to him and to myself
that I was gonna take care of him.
He'd suffered enough already,
and I wanted to make it up to him.
But now I've let him down.
How? How have you let him down?
I never should have let you take him out.
I have walked that dog 100 times.
I know.
On a leash, around the block, in the city,
while you were talking on your phone.
I thought Freeway was our dog.
You never paid attention to him.
You know more about your patients
than you do about your own family.
I'm not having this conversation now.
You're irrational.
I would have had that whistle,
and he would have come back to me.
But now he's gone.
And for all I know,
he may be suffering somewhere.
He's probably terrified.
I don't know. He may be dead.
He's not dead.
- Freeway is alive.
- What?
What are you talking about?
I am certain he's alive.
You're certain?
I never told you this, but I find things.
What kind of things?
Missing things. Sometimes living things.
You mean like a detective?
My great-great-grandmother was
Madame Luminitsa.
You've probably heard of her.
I am of the Romany people.
Gypsies?
On my mother's side.
My father is a yogi.
The women in my family, they have a gift.
We see things.
You find it hard to believe.
Gadje always do.
But I can help you find Freeway.
Gadje?
How?
When I realized Django was my spirit-mate,
the animal world became visible to me.
As opposed to the vegetable
and mineral worlds?
Now, who's Django?
That was Carmen's dog. He lived to be 24.
It was then that the gift blossomed in me.
My third eye truly opened.
What Django felt, I felt.
I traveled through the world with him,
seeing what he saw.
And what did he see?
He saw things for what they are.
He was connected to the prana.
The prana.
Shut up, Joseph. You're such a tight ass.
Do you have to be so one-dimensional?
Excuse me for living in this dimension.
Carmen.
Do you see him? is he all right?
Beth, are you kidding me?
Can you see what he sees?
- Yes.
- What do you see?
I see trees
and a shed with construction equipment in it
and mountains.
Wow. That really pinpoints it.
I see a redheaded woman.
What, Freeway's looking
at a redheaded woman?
She may have fed him.
He had some kind of interaction with her.
What should we do?
Yeah.
Go to bed.
What, are you closing for the night?
In the morning,
everything will be much clearer.
I need rest. And so do you.
Wail,
How long are we supposed to wait?
This is Freeway's hair.
Keep this close to your heart.
Freeway will feel our concern.
Are we supposed to sleep with this?
Makes sense to me.
Could I have mine in a baggie?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Carmen, why are you getting her hopes up?
Gypsy trick.
So you're leaving in the morning,
aren't you?
I have to. I'd stay if I could.
Violet is expecting you.
No, not Violet. I have patients to see.
My people have a saying.
"Those who don't push the caravan
from the muck
"become one with the muck,"
Thank you. That's very understanding.
Good-bye.
Beth, what are you doing?
I'm looking for those night-vision glasses
I got you for Christmas,
They're probably still in the same box.
Beth, you have to get some rest.
You heard Miss Luminitska.
Let me get you a Xanax.
You think it's impossible
Carmen might actually know
something you don't?
About Freeway? Doubtful.
Unless she kidnapped him.
She's given me hope. Maybe she has a gift.
And unlike you,
I don't think
I know everything about everything.
Why are you turning on me?
I didn't commit a crime.
There are a few pivotal moments
in a person's life,
where one reacts
exactly right or completely wrong.
I forgot the whistle.
But that's not what I'm talking about.
This is a difficult time for you.
For both of us.
And especially for a woman,
there are physical changes
that affect everything.
Tell me about being a woman.
I think that the anger you're feeling
is not actually about me. It's hormonal.
No, it's not menopause.
It actually is about you.
Zee men in my family have a gift.
They find things
that no one else can find, Gadje.
Gadje.
- Hello?
- Dad'
Grace. Gracie, you surprised me.
- What do you mean?
- Well, it's 5:00 in the morning here.
- It is?
- Yeah.
Oh, God, you're right.
I counted wrong. Go back to sleep.
No, no, no, no. I was up.
Tell me about Bora-Bora.
Amazing.
You've got to come here someday.
Dad, Sam and I can't stop talking
about the wedding.
It was just what we hoped.
And I know you didn't want Freeway
in the ceremony,
but you have to admit, it was sweet.
How's Mom?
She's great. She's fine.
Really? Is she doing okay? No big letdown?
She's relieved
that Sam took you off our hands.
When are you going back?
Later on.
Okay, well, we're going to dinner,
but! want to talk to Mom.
Call her when you wake up.
- Okay, give her a hug for me.
- Sure.
And give Freeway some of that salmon
that fell on the floor' He's earned it.
You got it, cookie. You just have fun.
Okay, love you.
I love you. Bye.
Hello?
I thought so.
Thanks.
This is good.
I was picturing a waterfall.
Now a hiker saw a dog
above Bear Creek Falls.
There's a reason you stayed,
but it's not the one you think.
No, I stayed to help find the dog.
Good.
Russell will need your help
finding the redheaded woman.
I'm supposed to find the redheaded woman?
Yes, it will take both of you to do it.
Okay. Where are we supposed to look?
I'm seeing a green house.
No, yellow. It's unclear.
- On a street named for a tree.
- Okay.
A tree.
Well, yeah, I'm gonna head up to Bear Creek.
Yeah, I'm gonna go with you.
Well, not with that knee.
No, you, please, come with me.
I need your help,
Well, I could go with Beth.
Or I could stick with Russell.
I don't mind going alone.
No.
Hey, Joseph.
Freeway!
I don't understand
why you're not talking to me.
I came back
because I wanted to be here for you.
I understand searching for Freeway.
But this Carmen crap?
It's voodoo.
But if another day of searching
is gonna make you feel better,
I'm here to support you.
Could we just not talk for a while?
I don't need to talk.
I think it's good for two people
to have quiet time together,
to heal, to smooth out the feathers
or whatever.
Grace called.
- What?
- Yeah.
- When?
- This morning. You were sleeping.
You didn't tell her about Freeway, did you?
Of course not.
- What did she say?
- They're having a great time.
They loved the wedding.
Anything else?
She asked how you're doing.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Oh, hey!
You didn't happen
to see a dog up there, did you?
- Yeah.
- You did?
Like that?
Yeah, could be.
Where exactly does this trail go?
It heads up towards Purgatory,
then loops back.
- Come on.
- It loops back? How is it?
It's radical.
Do you think you'll ever get married?
Perhaps.
I'm sure you have no trouble attracting men.
They swarm like flies,
but who wants a fly?
I'm a passionate woman.
It's not easy to find a man
who can keep up with me sexually.
- Yeah, it's tough for women like us.
- Yeah.
There was one, But he was a pickpocket.
My family would not tolerate that.
- No, of course not.
- It's not steady work.
Russell is very cheerful.
Can he keep up with you?
Why do you think he's so cheerful?
Do you want me to get that?
I got it.
Okay.
- Yeah?
- What are you doing?
Right now?
We're way the hell up toward Purgatory.
Where's that?
Above Bear Creek.
Yeah, we met a guy who saw a dog.
Okay, you sound
like you're having a heart attack.
- Let me talk to Beth.
- Hold on.
- Beth.
- What?
- Penny, for you.
- Okay.
- Hi, Penny.
- He sounds terrible.
No matter what you're feeling,
don't kill him.
Where are you, anyway?
I'm underneath the gondola.
Carmen had a vision
about porta-potties and took off.
I think she's coming back.
Don't worry,
I'll check in with you in an hour.
Don't drink that so fast.
That's drinking too much.
God, really.
Careful.
I love this.
We're on the job, like those cop partners.
I'm the grizzled old guy,
and you're the young kid
who thinks he knows everything.
You mean the one the older one resents
cause the younger one's actually smarter?
Yeah, until you save my life.
You know, Carmen said there was...
The house was either yellow or green.
I don't know. Maybe she's confused.
Yeah, maybe she's really a Gypsy.
You think she's faking?
Beautiful women get away with a lot of shit.
Hello?
Carmen?
I am not sure about the color of the house.
I'm getting mixed messages.
Something about blue.
Blue, okay.
Don't lose faith.
Hello? Carmen?
- What?
- She's getting mixed messages,
something about blue.
Okay.
God, maybe we should have just taken...
I don't know, the other trail.
- The one that went up? No, no, no.
- No, because...
If we'd done that,
we'd be sleeping out here tonight.
No, we've got to get down.
But we don't know where we are,
so maybe we should backtrack or...
I don't know.
No, no, no, no, no.
Dear, we've been out here
for about five hours.
- Yeah.
- It'll take at least that long
to get back by backtracking.
- How do you know?
- It's almost 4:00 now. it's gonna be dark
- in a couple of hours...
- I know it's gonna be dark,
but how do you know this is going down
and not just deeper into the woods?
- We're following the creek.
- I think we should call someone.
Creeks always run downhill.
I think we should call someone.
What? And say what?
- And say that we're lost.
- We're not lost.
- Oh, God.
- Honey, look, look.
- See over there?
- What? Yeah.
There. That's Mount Wilson.
Yeah, which means what?
You can see Mount Wilson from Utah.
Oh, shit.
My battery is way down.
Please, come on, come on.
- What are you gonna say?
- Well, I'm just gonna tell them
that if they haven't
heard from us in an hour,
they should call Search and Rescue.
That's embarrassing. You're panicking.
- Penny!
- Hi.
Penny, oh, God. Thank God.
No, I'm so happy.
Listen, I just didn't think
this phone was gonna work.
- Where are you guys?
- I don't know. I think we're lost.
Listen, if you don't hear
from us in an hour...
Penny?
Penny? Oh, shoot!
Beth?
Lost...
The phone is dead, honey.
Can you please turn yours on, quick?
Shoot.
Damn. It's already on.
I forgot to turn it off.
- Yeah?
- Joseph, what happened?
Penny, listen, listen,
I've got to talk fast.
There's no reason to panic,
but we got Mount Wilson on our left,
and we started out from Bear Creek,
so that means that right now,
we are somewhere between those two...
Penny?
Joseph?
Joseph!
Shit, shit,
shit!
You're panicking.
What made her call right then,
right when we were talking about her?
Gypsy shit.
It's weird.
Hi. How are you?
Did Hector send you guys?
No, no, we lost our dog.
And we heard you might
have seen him, you know?
Blue, behave. Blue.
I seen this poster,
but I don't recall seeing Freeway his self.
Let me think. You know what?
Ever heard of Christus Bonheur?
No, ma'am.
Your dad's a charmer. Watch and learn.
Yes, ma'am.
I could tell you two was father and son
right away.
You're so much alike.
- Christus...
- Christus Bonheur,
a stone-cold psycho, if you want to know.
That degenerate's always got a bunch
of loose dogs hanging around.
Seen him in town the other day,
which is unusual.
Now, where could we find him, ma'am?
He's got a filthy shack halfway to nowhere.
You know where you turn off
North Fork to Rattlesnake Trail?
Up behind 17 Heifers?
17 Heifers? Yeah, I know where that is.
Much obliged, ma'am.
Blue.
All right, thank you, ma'am.
Hey, if you hit Squirrel Head,
you gone too far.
Okay.
All right.
You know how to lay on the charm, Russell.
I just all of a sudden had a
Southern accent.
Did you ever hear of floaters?
Yeah, in your eye?
I never heard of them till last week.
Now I got 'em for the rest of my life.
It's no big deal. Older people get them.
It's fine. Your brain will adjust.
You won't even notice them.
You know, I'm not sure
this is such a good idea.
You think maybe we should
get a deputy or something?
No, we're just gonna go up there
and talk to old Christus, man-to-man.
You mean, stone-cold-psycho-to-man?
Well, my experience...
And I've been around quite a bit, Bryan...
Is that most people don't want trouble.
In fact, old Christus will probably be happy
to have some company.
Maybe.
My father left us for one of his students,
never lifted a finger for Penny or me.
And the guy is an ethics professor.
Hadn't been for Joseph,
I couldn't have gone to medical school.
I bet you wish
your mom was dating a millionaire, huh?
Not a millionaire, Russell, okay?
Just someone who's making a living.
I mean, Mom worked hard
for that buyout money.
She shouldn't have to support you with it.
What happens if the Pigeon and the Truck
doesn't make any money, huh?
Do you actually know anyone
who likes warm beer?
It'll all work out. I'll Always.
No, it doesn't!
I love your mother,
and I'm gonna take care of her.
And I've been working since I was 15
so I can always find a job.
And the pub is gonna do just great,
but you shouldn't feel
any pressure to buy in.
Well, I don't.
Yeah, well, I think everybody who invests
is gonna make a lot of money.
Why? Why? 'Cause anything's possible?
That's my motto. Anything's possible.
Snake!
He's leaving. Don't piss him off.
You got to relax.
We've got no flashlight.
We've got no clothes. We've got nothing.
It was hot and sunny when we left.
You said we were only gonna be gone
a couple of hours...
Right, it's my fault.
Look, we both screwed up, okay?
Why can't you ever admit
you've made a mistake?
No, I guess it's genetically impossible,
given your father.
- I'm not like him.
- Well, then name one mistake you've made.
Besides coming out here with you?
I don't think in terms of mistakes.
I take responsibility for everything.
That's what doctors do.
That's right. I forgot. You're a doctor.
You hadn't mentioned
it in the last eight minutes.
Here we go. "Doctors think they're gods
"Doctors are self-absorbed egomaniacs. "
- And full of shit.
- Doctors are full of shit?
No, I am not talking about doctors.
I am talking about you.
Have I ever put my work
before you or the girls?
Okay, sometimes.
When I'm doing surgery on someone's spine
to relieve them of a life of pain,
I have put my work first.
The girls always understood,
and they never complained.
Were we living in the same house?
- You see Freeway?
- No.
Wait, wait. The dogs are coming.
They're right there.
Stand slowly.
Don't move too fast.
- Hey, buddies!
- Hi, buddies.
- Hey-
- Hi, guys.
- Beautiful. What a sweetheart.
- Yep.
Shut Up!
Mr. Bonheur, I'm Bryan. This is Russell.
Yeah, we don't mean to bother you,
but we're looking for a dog.
These is my dogs.
And a handsome bunch they are, too.
Yeah, we thought maybe our dog
had wandered up here and fallen in love.
- He didn't.
- Okay, well, we knew we'd be intruding,
so we got you a little something
in the hopes that you might show us around.
Now, we didn't know what you drink,
but most men enjoy
a good scotch whiskey, so...
Get off my land.
It's not a single malt,
because people who drink that
don't do it for the taste.
They do it to make a statement
about who they are.
But for you, sir, that is not an issue.
Shut Up!
Now get the hell out of here.
Hold it, ass-wipe.
Don't make me get out my shotgun.
Don't make me get out my Glock.
Freeway!
- Get off me!
- Jeez, you stink!
Freeway!
Shit.
There are two things
that I won't allow in my pub,
and that's a troublemaker
and a man who stinks.
So if you're ever in Omaha,
you stay away
from the Partridge and the Plough!
I don't think
I can be this close to you much longer.
Shut Up!
Russell!
Let's go! Come on!
Shit. Russell?
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Get me to a shower.
Come on.
Man, figures the son of a bitch
went to Harvard.
They always got to let you know
about it too, don't they?
Look at that.
- Look at that.
- Holy shit.
What are they?
Those are rams, and they can be nasty.
But aren't they goats? Goats are small.
- No, they're sheep.
- Do they bite?
- No, they ram.
- Oh, my God.
But they can be controlled.
Little dogs control them just by yapping.
- Really?
- Yeah, yeah.
I'll scare them off. You go back and hide.
- Right now?
- Stay hidden, yes.
- Okay, but are you all right?
- I'll be fine.
Okay, all right.
Oh, God! Be careful!
I'll take care of it.
Go away!
Hey, go on with you! Go!
Go back!
Go back to your friends!
Flock!
Flock! Go back to your flock!
Go back!
Are they leaving?
Not yet.
Honey, did it work?
- Honey?
- Oh, shit!
No!
Oh, careful!
Thank God you're all right!
Of course we're okay.
Hi, sweetheart.
Oh, my God. What happened?
It's a long story. What's wrong?
Beth and Joseph are lost.
Search and Rescue is looking for them.
I'm sure Beth and Joseph are fine.
- Was I right about these two?
- Yes.
Beth and Joseph are cold and wet,
but they'll be back here shortly.
I made soup. Go in.
- Thank you.
- Get some.
I know. I'll tell you about it.
Hold on! Let's head back up!
We got to be well past the rams by now!
All right. Honey, watch your step.
It's slippery here!
Hold on!
Will you slow down a little bit?
Oh, God.
- I don't want to lose you.
- No.
Let's head back up! Back to the trail!
Okay. But, here, wait.
Just grab hold of this branch right here
before you step!
Right this way.
Right here!
Okay, okay, okay. Yeah, yeah.
Oh, God! No, Joseph, are you okay?
Where are you?
God!
Joseph, I'm coming!
Joe! I'm coming!
What is it? What's wrong?
Tell me!
I'm sorry!
My shoulder.
- You're gonna have to put it back.
- Put it back?
- It's dislocated.
- What?
You have to put the humerus
back into the glenoid socket.
No, no, no, really, I cannot do that.
Let's just get you to the hospital,
all right?
No, you have to do it now,
before the muscles tighten.
All right, just, what about your arm?
What if it ruins it?
What if you never operate again, Joe?
- Honey...
- You can do it.
You just have to do exactly what I say.
- All right?
- Yes'
First, get me sitting.
Okay.
All right, honey.
All right, now I need you to bend this arm
until it's in a right angle.
Are you sure about this?
Now, pay attention.
I'm going to help you, all right?
Now hold one hand there.
Lift into the right angle
with the other hand, all right?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Beth, I want you to ignore me
no matter how much I scream, all right?
Ignore your screams?
Yes, yes. Just go ahead.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Stop, stop! You're killing me!
- Okay, okay! I'm sorry!
- I told you to ignore me!
- I know!
So ignore when you say stop, right?
Yes, ignore me. Keep going.
- All right, I'm going!
- All right, that's it, That a girl!
Okay, okay, okay, okay,
all right, all right.
There. Now, now, yes, {got it.
All right, now I want you to push the arm
into my side, okay,
till it's flush with my body.
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
Shit, Shit, shit, shit!
- There?
- Yeah.
That's good. That's good.
- All right, Is it back in?
- No.
Now is the hard part.
That wasn't the hard part?
Honey, take my wrist here.
Rotate the arm
away from my body until I say stop.
Wail,
So ignore...
Don't ignore you what you say this time?
No, yes. Yes, don't... Don't ignore.
Yes, I understand. I understand.
- Okay, here we go.
- Go.
- Yes?
- Stop, all right.
- Okay, stop.
- All right.
Now you're going to put my arm
back in the socket, all right?
So what do... I'm gonna do that.
- Yeah. Good girl.
- Just tell me what it is, exactly.
- I want you to put all your weight...
- I'm gonna put...
Yeah, yeah.
- Put all your weight...
- I'm trying, yes.
...In the crook of my arm,
Push down. Lean in to me.
It's gonna take all you've got, all right?
- But you can do it.
- Yes, I can.
All right, until it pops back in.
Okay, Joe.
Now lean. Go ahead. Go.
Is that.
I got it, Joe?
That was it, wasn't it?
Okay, hon, I got it, right?
Joe, honey, Joe?
Oh, my God, Joe.
Joe?
That worked.
- How are you doing?
- I'm fine.
- Really?
- Sure.
Are you cold?
No, no, I'm fine.
Are you worried?
A little.
You?
As you know, I'm a doctor.
Is that a house?
It is. Yeah.
Okay, honey.
Hello?
- Hello!
It's nice in there.
It looks like a good place.
Please! Hello!
Hello! Help! Help!
Okay, okay. I got it.
Should I do that?
- Should I really do this?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, honey, okay, this is a bigger rock.
I think this should do it.
Back off! Back away!
I'd tell you to watch out for flying glass,
if I thought there'd be any.
Never mind!
I can't believe it!
I can't believe that I'm not strong enough
to break a window.
No, no, you're strong enough.
I think this has to be tempered glass
that's why...
What is it?
Are all the windows here tempered?
So wait a second now. Wait.
Okay, should I do this?
Yeah, but be careful. Watch your hand.
Okay, here I go!
- Oh, God.
- Hello?
- Careful of your hand!
- Okay, okay, all right.
Oh, my God, honey. Are you all right?
All right, now...
Oh, my God. Hello?
Hello?
Oh, my God.
Nothing, nothing, nothing.
Okay.
I like their wine.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
Let's keep the label.
Should we?
Okay?
Yeah?
Delicious.
- How come we never have these?
- We have.
Really? I have no recollection.
That's because you're in shock.
Your shoulder, honey.
- I know we haven't...
- Oh, my God!
Lower that weapon, deputy dog.
I had a feeling it'd be you guys.
You know the whole damn county
has been out looking for you?
How did you find us?
Silent alarm.
Would you let me through?
Damn it. God.
We got 'em! We got.
No, they look great.
They're in their pajamas.
Are you guys Okay?
Yeah, they're okay. Yeah, okay.
No, I have to go. Yeah, I'll tell 'em!
You scared the shit out of us.
- Buddy...
- No, no, don't touch him. No.
You know, he fell down.
Poor guy
He hurt his shoulder.
Well...
Okay, here we go.
Look at that.
French toast.
Clear!
Nourishment. That's what we need.
And a side of Lipitor, please.
Come on. Eat, Beth, eat.
- I can't...
- Last day.
Last day, right, your last day.
Sweetie, we've got to get back.
You guys have been
more than generous already.
We all have to get back to our lives.
I think we're gonna find Freeway today.
I don't know. Maybe.
Well, honey, you found him once.
Yeah, but that storm last night,
it was just so bad.
So what's the plan?
Carmen, what do you got for us?
Only one thing.
When I put the bacon in this pan,
I saw Freeway come out
of Lawson's Hill at Pioneer's Turn.
He wanted to cross the highway.
Cut the crap.
Beth.
Your visions sent us
all over hell yesterday.
Joseph got hurl.
And what about Bryan and Russell
risking their lives
because of some ridiculous
redheaded woman who knew nothing.
Not one thing you've said has been right.
Some were close.
I understand you don't believe me.
But you must believe
Freeway is out there somewhere.
Is this a Gypsy thing,
manipulating people
when they're at their most vulnerable?
- Come on, Beth. She's trying to help.
- Don't defend me'
You have to stay focused.
The moment you lose hope
is the moment your chances
of getting him back disappear.
- You have to have hope.
- That's all we've got.
That's all you need.
Don't you think Freeway wants to find you
as much as you want to find him?
I hope he's better at it than we are.
We can't get discouraged, guys.
We got to stay positive.
Hi? Hello?
Carol.
No, we haven't found him.
Where?
The gas station?
That's near Pioneer Turn.
Oh, my God, okay. So, 10 minutes ago?
You saw him in the frying pan?
You are one freaky caretaker.
Listen, I lost a pair of really nice
horn-rimmed reading glasses last February.
Maybe you could check the French toast?
Just get the whistles! Grab a whistle!
Thank you, Carol.
Thank you so much for calling, really.
Oh, my God.
Carmen, oh, look. 1 really... I'm sorry.
Let's go up to Pioneer Turn.
Sorry, bumpy.
Mom called last night
when everyone was lost in the storm.
I told her you were hiking.
I'll call her today.
Did she say anything about the wedding?
She thought it was lovely.
She said the food gave her gout.
That's your mother.
- Hey, she's your grandmother.
- Meaning what?
Meaning the dark side is
strong in all of us.
By the way, Joseph,
it's your turn to go to Phoenix.
Don't I get credit for the wedding?
No, because you put her at my table
with Sam's parents.
She asked Numendra
what he was in his last life.
All right, Mom.
I will go with you next time.
Nobody should have to go
through that alone.
Thank you.
Russell offered to go with me.
He's good with difficult people.
I've noticed.
The guy's pretty fearless.
No luck.
You want to come with me?
You take a knife
and you cut into people's backs.
How can you do that?
They're asleep.
That must take large cojones.
Well, they trained me to do it.
But, yes, I have large cojones.
How long did it take?
It's four years of medical school,
five-year residency,
- and a two-year fellowship.
- Eleven years?
Yeah, after college.
What?
When did they start calling you doctor?
About 10 years ago, after med school.
Maybe I should call you doctor.
I just hate
the thought of leaving Beth up here alone.
Hold her,
come home for a few days, recharge,
and we'll come back on the weekend.
She's afraid the search
will end if she leaves.
But everyone's on the lookout.
If he's out there, somebody will spot him.
If he's out there.
Okay, I'll go home with you tomorrow.
I will.
Anyway.
Hi, sweetie.
We're just having coffee
before we head out again.
Okay, look, Carmen says, don't give up hope.
Wait, I'm gonna put you on the speaker.
Okay.
Okay. We're all here.
Carmen says Freeway
really wants to come in,
but he's got to hear a friendly voice.
Okay, what... Don't laugh. Wait a second.
- Okay.
- So...
Carmen has a strong feeling
about a basketball court.
Okay, okay.
Now, there are two basketball courts
in town. We're going to the high school.
Can you guys cover the one in Town Park?
- Town Park.
- Town Park, okay, okay.
- All right, we're going to Town Pam.
- Town Park.
He's been gone two days,
so if you see a dog like this...
Okay, well, no, your hands are full.
Okay, well, thanks anyway. I appreciate it.
- Thank you so much.
- Okay, bye-bye, guys.
- Have a good picnic now.
- Smells good.
Come on, darling.
Freeway!
Freeway, come on in!
I can hardly remember the wedding.
- Everyone loved it.
- They did?
Especially my mother. It gave her gout.
I'll bet you remember
how beautiful Grace looked.
Yeah, and Ellie.
Ellie, too.
We're gonna have another doctor
in the family.
Wow.
Ethan could use a cousin.
They should get right on that.
Yeah, so to speak.
I told Grace to throw away her pills
two months ago.
I'm sorry I forgot the dog whistle.
That wasn't it.
No, I know.
I'm gonna try to be better.
I can't promise you I'll be much different.
It may be a little late for that.
I'm gonna try to calm down.
You can't help it.
It's a jolt finding ourselves like this.
Like what?
Not young.
Oh, my God.
Have you noticed the ages
of the people in the obits?
- It's not funny.
- No, it is funny.
I was thinking,
maybe we ought to invest in the pub.
Yeah, I was thinking that, too.
The Partridge and the Plough?
It's growing on me.
Doesn't mean I'm gonna drink warm beer.
- Here, Freeway!
- Hey, buddy!
Come on! Come on, Freeway!
- Careful, baby. Careful.
- No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I was so scared last night.
Everybody I care about
was out in that storm.
We all made it.
I'm never letting you out of my sight again.
Get used to it.
You would make a fine husband.
- For you?
- No. Not for me.
Why not?
It would never work.
I could see the whole thing.
Tell me.
The wedding would be very strange
but funny.
We would have to keep an eye
on my father around Penny,
My mother would disapprove of everything,
but Russell will melt her heart.
Yeah.
The sex will be fantastic.
You will have no problem
keeping up with me.
You've got good hands.
They will make me want to devour you.
Okay, this is all really good.
What's the problem?
You will take me to your world
of hospitals and cocktail parties.
You will introduce me
to all your educated friends,
and they will think,
"Bryan has let his dick make this decision,"
I will know what they're thinking
but that will not bother me.
What will bother me
is being in the wrong place.
You and I will become out of alignment.
Disaster will follow.
Tell me about the sex again.
What?
- Okay.
- Vision?
I was thinking,
in case one of us drops dead,
we shouldn't leave anything unsaid.
I don't want to be in cardiac arrest
thinking I forgot to tell you something.
Okay, go ahead.
Okay.
The girls were really lucky
when they got you for a mother.
While it's true that every so often,
you get on my nerves,
I just want to say
that the things that bug me about you
have never meant anything
compared with how much I love you.
Your turn.
Hey, GUYS.
We've reached a conclusion.
This is nuts.
We've spent three days running around
on the word of a Gypsy psychic.
Alleged Gypsy psychic.
Well, it's all we had to go on,
so why not?
I know. I'm tired of it. I am.
I'm tired of it, too.
Hello?
Okay.
Carmen's had another vision.
9:30, Freeway,
between the ice cream parlor and the church.
- Can we do this?
- Let's go.
Thank you.
Okay, okay.
I really thought he'd be there.
What dog goes to church at 9:30?
He didn't say where he was going?
Sneaked out before I woke up.
And he just took your car?
Stole it.
Well, don't worry, He won't get far.
I got his plane ticket right here.
You all right?
No, I got it. I got it.
Here's Bryan now.
Hi, honey, You made it.
- Hey, Bryan.
- Thanks for everything.
- There he is.
- He's got a dog!
- Hey, guys.
- Oh, my God.
- I wasn't sure I'd make it.
- Oh, look.
You're one lucky dog.
- Carmen, thank you.
- Don't worry. Bye.
- I will keep looking.
- I'll see you on the plane.
Sorry about the car.
But I had to get to Norwood.
It was supposed to be his last day.
And you were right.
He was waiting for a man.
But I think he's your dog.
He doesn't have a name.
What do you think? Django junior?
I think I will call him DOC.
It's gonna be a little bumpy
till we get over the mountains.
I will never forgive you for this.
This isn't even a real airport.
There he is! Freeway!
He's down there! Oh, my God! I can see him!
- You see him? - Yes, he's down there.
We've got to go back.
- What are you doing?
- I'm gonna tell them!
No, no, no.
They're not gonna tum the plane around
because you think you saw a dog.
They'll have you arrested!
Joseph, I saw him.
What? You saw Freeway?
You saw Freeway!
Oh. my God!
I knew it! We're crashing! We're crashing!
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, God.
Wait, are you okay?
- Don't overdo it.
- Good plan, right?
Okay. I got it.
On three. One, two...
Oh, God! Help us!
Oh, please, help him!
Hurry, please!
I got it! I got it!
Hold him. I got him.
It's a hijacking!
What the hell is going on back there?
Something happened to my friend!
Shut Up!
I don't know.
- It's the appendix.
- Or it could be a kidney stone!
Are we gonna die? Tell me the truth!
No, ma'am, I've got a passenger in distress.
We have to get this man
to a hospital immediately.
Turn this plane around right now.
- Are you a doctor?
- Yes!
Look down. Look down.
Watch your stairs. There we go.
Watch your stairs.
There you go. Nice, deep breaths.
Okay, guys, yeah. Thanks.
All right, here we go.
Arm around me. Arm around me.
Come on. Come on.
What's the problem here?
This one said
that one's appendix was bursting.
No, no, I said I thought it was his appendix,
but now I think more it's a kidney stone,
You a doctor?
Yeah, yeah. Well.
You in a lot of pain, Joe?
Well, no question it hurls.
Or rather, it was hurting.
I feel you, brother.
Let's get you to the clinic.
Okay, okay, yeah. Thank you.
Watch your head now.
Nice work. What do we do now?
Here! Right here is where I saw him!
Okay, stop!
No, no, Beth!
Come on!
Freeway!
Here, Freeway!
- Freeway...
- Freeway!
Come on, Freeway!
- Freeway?
- Here, Freeway!
There! Right there! There they are!
Here's good. Yeah, thanks a million,
Sheriff. We'll never forget this.
Hope it doesn't cause you any problems.
No one's ever gonna know about it.
Hey, Carmen, wait up!
Freeway!
- Carmen?
- Bryan?
Freeway?
Come on, Freeway.
Freeway!
You see him?
I don't know.
Freeway!
Hello, Look at you.
Freeway, you're back!
I missed you.
Thank God.
- Gracie?
- Dad!
Are you guys still in the mountains?
What's going on?
Well, you know, we're having so much fun.
I'm so glad you guys
took a few days to unwind.
We've been having the best time.
I love being married.
Dad, how's Freeway?
Freeway?
Freeway's fine.
You're back!
You're back, I knew it, I knew it.
Beth, I'm so happy for you.
Shut up!