Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
[ Muffled Rhythmic Pounding ]
[ Pounding Resumes ]
[ Fades ]
[ Water Gurgling ]
[ Water Rushing ]
[ Roaring, Squealing ]
[ Indicators Beep ]
- How we doin' out there, Leila ?
- Fuck you !
Aw, come on now, I pay you
two bucks a day, don't I ?
Get off your lazy ass
and come and help me !
Cut me some slack, will ya ?
I'm workin' hard too, you know.
Now what ?
[ n Headset ] I'm flyin' blind up here,
Brainiac. I thought you fixed the radar.
- Killed off by your negative vibes.
- No doubt.
No.
You know, where is it written
that I have to go out there and work ?
I mean, you know, Finnegan, why don't
you get your ass out there sometime ?
I love you too, Leila.
- Everything all right ?
-Just peachy.
[ Man ]
We are on schedule, are we not ?
- [ Finnegan ] You didn't
hire me for my social graces.
- That's right.
We hired you for your reputation.
You better live up to it.
there.
Yeah, I heard of you.
But I thought you'd be older.
Like a fine wine, I'm aging gracefully.
Thank you.
[ Laughs ]
Any questions,
Mr Finnegan ?
Nope. I get paid to shut up
and do my job.
So I shut up and do my job.
You're not the least bit curious
as to where we're going ?
Like the sign says,
''If the cash is there, we do not care.''
Very good.
- [ Door Closes ]
- Where the hell are we goin' ?
[ Loud Dance Band ]
Everyone drops
what they're doin'
When Lady Luck
walks into the room
- I'm so broke that it's a shame
- [ Gamblers hattering ]
Lady Luck don't even know
my name
Bartender, pour a double
When Lady Luck
walks into the room
[ Yelling ]
Ladies and gentlemen.
Mesdames et messieurs.
If I could have your attention
for just one moment, please.
welcome to the maiden voyage
of the Argonautica !
[ heering ]
Each and every one of
the hundreds of men and women...
has but one objective:
As for myself, my entire life...
And tonight,
seeing all of you here...
so beautiful, so elegant,
I realize that my dream
has come true,
and I thank all of you from the bottom
of my heart for making it so.
To the Argonautica !
Good times forever !
[ All Shouting ]
Forever !
[ Percussion Resumes ]
[ Passengers Laughing,
hattering ]
[ Skipped item nr. 59 ]
This ship is so smooth
we can't believe it!
[ Man ] She's state-of-the-art.
Not another ship like her, ma'am.
She can hit a 40-foot swell and not
even put a ripple across your martini.
It's been very nice meeting you people.
I hope you enjoy the rest of the cruise.
[ Thunder ]
[ Scoffs ]
Nice picture.
[ Distant Wailing ]
[ Australian Accent ]
I hate this bloody water stuff.
- That reminds me, I'm hungry.
- You're always hungry.
Yeah. So ?
I'm a growing boy, you know.
- You're still growing ?
- You got a problem with that ?
- Be happy I don't eat you.
- So what you realizing, Mamooli ?
Uh, well, that my goal in life
before I die...
Like, countries acknowledged by the
U.N. ? Or like, made-up countries too ?
- What the hell does that mean ?
- Like T. Ray's country.
Shut your face, Billy.
Australia's a country.
- Australia's an island.
- Well, technically, it's a continent.
Ah, shit, man. Island, country,
continent. If there's women there,
well, I'm interested.
Does he ever talk about
anything else but women ?
Nah, not that I recall. The only way
to shut him up is to shoot him.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Yeah ?
- [ Gun ocking ]
You ever thought about it ?
- [ Man ] Every day.
- [ Knife Unsheathing ] oh, ooh, ooh.
- [ Man ] Come on, boys.
- Sit down, right ?
- oh, ooh. [ huckling ]
- [ Belches ]
- You know what I want to eat ?
I'll take a couple of
nice, greasy pig's feet,
some pickled monkey brains
and one of them big elephant eyeballs.
- [ Men Laugh ]
- [ Blowing Smoke ]
- Yummy. [ huckles ]
- [ Vomiting ]
- [ Men Laughing ]
- You like that ?
- Oh, man, that's disgusting.
- T. Ray, you stinking up the place.
Hey, knock it off.
You're not getting paid to party.
[ Finnegan n Headset ]
Pantucci ! Pantucci !
You're not where I think
you are, are ya ?
Hola.
Listen, this radar's still funky. I can
feel it, and it's a very bad feeling.
You know how many uncharted
islands are out here ?
What is this, a talk show ?
I need some quiet time.
ver and out.
- [ Hydraulic Lift Hissing ]
- Whoa.
Hit you.
''h, shit.''
- I'm feelin' a real lack of love here.
- Get in there !
- [ Billy ] hh.
- Well, what do we have here, fellas ?
If there's anything I can do to make
your trip more comfortable, come to me.
- G'day, mate.
- [ Men Shouting,
Pantucci Grunting And Groaning ]
[ Fighting Sounds
n Headset ]
Well, don't just sit there !
Go help him !
- You've got to do something.
- I find you live longer if you don't.
Finnegan !
[ Punches Landing,
Men Laughing ]
[ Pantucci Moaning, Panting ]
Twenty hours out and back.
You beat my engine man to death,
it's gonna take a hell of a lot longer.
Which is okay by me,
since overtime will run you double rate.
He was nosin' around in my cargo.
kay, so he's nosey.
we kick this little
piece of shit overboard.
- [ Grunts ]
- Well, I vote we kill him.
I vote vwe kill him.
the vwe thovw him oveboad
Well, we don't vote here.
See, it's not a democracy.
kay. I'll say it one more time
for the hearing impaired.
- [ Billy Grunts ]
- [ Guns ocking ]
[ Knife Unsheathing ]
This could be messy.
Vivo.
Everypody okay ?
Anybody gonna shoot anybody ?
That's a year off my life.
[ Thunder, Lightning Crashing ]
Please enter your security key card.
Good evening,
aptain Atherton.
- Good evening to you.
- The vault is now open.
oh, you're a big, bad boy,
aren't ya ?
[ learing Throat ]
Good evening, mademoiselle.
- Hello.
- Red-handed. My God, what a
cheeky little trollop you are.
- r maybe not.
- A good decision.
There's no place to run. The nearest
land is-- What, 600 miles, aptain ?
- Nearer 800, sir.
- According to this fax we received--
- h, that's not a very flattering
photograph, is it ?
- Let me see.
You're wanted for burglary,
robbery, forgery.
My ex-boyfriend.
What ?
amass such an incredible record ?
- Trust me, it wasn't easy.
- I think it's because you're
not very good at what you do.
- h !
- Steady on, anton. No need for that.
Uh-uh !
I believe that's my card.
- Thank you.
- Do we have a brig on this ship ?
Yes, we do, sir.
But it's not finished yet.
- Can't put a lady in the brig !
- True.
But you, mademoiselle,
are no lady.
Hey, watch it !
[ Sighs ]
Hmm. And you, Mr anton,
are no gentleman.
w. w !
They must be 30 feet long, man.
You ever pull that shit again,
I'll kill you myself.
Hold still,
you big dummy.
I'm sorry. It stings !
Hey, do you think we could pull over ?
h, yes, my little love bug,
- I think I need a higher dosage.
- You always need a higher dosage.
- How many of those things are there ?
- Huh ?
I don't know. Eight or nine of'em.
Enough to sink a damn aircraft carrier.
This is just great.
Now I got bombs in my basement.
Maybe it's just me, but if you'd ask a
question or two before accepting a job--
[ Pantucci ] If the cash is there,
we do not care.
What kind of life philosophy
is that, man ?
Torpedoes. What the hell
are they gonna do with torpedoes ?
[ Soft Beeps ]
Yes !
Gentlemen.
Say hello to the hinese...
M 1 -L1 triple-pulse
assault rifle.
Rotating barrel,
thousand-round capacity.
- Auto cooling, watertight.
- Yeah !
heers, babe.
Mmm.
[ Electronic Whirring,
Beeping ]
[ Beeping ontinues ]
- [ Crew Members Chattering ]
- What ?
[ Captain ]
What's happening here, gentlemen ?
Communications,
what's your status ?
All thermal and laser imaging generating
a negative white screen response, sir.
Right. Switch to
auxiliary power, Mr Lewis.
Let's do a circuit check.
No response, sir. We have
a complete mainframe meltdown.
- Maybe it's the storm, sir.
- No, no. That's nonsense.
- This ship is impervious to weather.
- an we still send ?
This equipment is state-of- the-art !
Top of the line !
Mr anton, please !
without radar or any form of imaging;
we are sailing blind.
- No way to communicate our situation.
- I have something here, sir.
- What is it, olin ?
- I don't know, sir,
Probably just
a pod of whales.
Moving at 31 knots, sir ?
I don't think so.
- Where's it coming from ?
- Directly beneath us, sir.
1 60 metres directly beneath us
and rising very quickly.
1 50 metres.
1 40.
1 30. 1 20.
1 1 0. 1 00 metres.
Ninety, eighty.
- Seventy, sixty.
- What are they ?
Fifty metres.
[ Crashing ]
[ Passengers Screaming ]
- [ Man ] Open up !
- [ Sobbing ]
[ Metal Screeching,
Ship Rumbling ]
[ Squishing Sound ]
I didn't say you could put holes in
my boat! That's gonna cost you extra !
- What the hell is that ?
- I don't know.
[ Man ]
Let's go !
Looks like some kind of--
It's a torpedo launcher.
- I-- I don't like this.
- Yeah, I know. Neither do I.
- How much longer ?
-Another 22 minutes,
we'll be right on top of,
uh,
- whatever's out there.
- [ Radar Pinging ]
Hang on !
[ Screams ]
- [ Alarm Beeping ]
-Joey! Joey, talk to me! Damage ?
- Taking water?
- A little, but it's
Just above the water line.
I got no power coming from Jezebel.
She's out cold.
[ Leila ] Something's wrong with
Hercules. He's not getting any petrol.
Shit !
What the hell did we hit ?
Get it off the cases !
What the hell was that ?
Whatever it was,
it nearly took my bloody head off !
- [ Laughing ]
- [ Mamooli ] What are you laughing at ?
A direct hit on any of these warheads
and pfft ! We'd be history, mate.
We got a hole in the starboard
bow the size of Nebraska !
[ Finnegan ]
You got me.
We're hell and gone
from the nearest land.
There's no way a speedboat
gets out this far. No way.
w ! Shit, man ! Finnegan, nothing
works ! Hercules is shot to shit.
His gears are all mangled.
His cylinder head seized up, I think.
[ Skipped item nr. 235 ]
We have a job to finish,
a schedule to maintain.
- Man, would you listen to this crap ?
- Shut up, grease monkey !
Hey, get your asses up here !
Whoa. It's a--
It's a cruise ship.
[ Together ]
Absolutely.
- [ Finnegan ] What the hell--
- [ Guns ocking ]
We'll take over from here.
Not any more.
If I can get into
the Love Boat's machine shop,
yeah, maybe I can fix
this hunk of junk.
She ain't gonna run pretty,
but she'll run.
[ Softly ] They've armed all
the bombs, man. They're alive.
All right.
- Finnegan and the grease monkey
will come with us.
- Wait a minute.
-The three of us stick together.
-From now on, you'll be
sticking with me.
- Billy!
- Yeah, Chief.
Finish the torpedo launcher
and watch the lady.
Hey, Mr Comedy,
leave my girlfriend out of this.
This is worse
than high school.
ruise ship's not movin'.
Why ain't it movin' ?
I don't know.
All right, gentlemen.
- You know the drill.
- kay, let's move out !
[ Alarm Beeping ]
Bingo.
[ Finnegan ] Relax, Hanover.
This is a cruise ship.
- You're not gonna need your guns.
- What if they attack us, man ?
This place is a mess.
You want me
to call housekeeping ?
Use any and all force necessary.
The intimidation factor must be high.
There's a lot of passengers
on this ship.
That was kind of fun.
Well, it was.
Everybody's in the atrium.
We'll pin 'em down there, then split up
and finish the job. Sound off !
- Bridge !
- Bow, top level.
[ All Yelling ]
Everybody down ! Nobody move !
Shit.
We got blood here.
We got blood everywhere.
[ Bell Dings, Machinery Whirs ]
[ Level Indicator Beeping ]
I got a really bad feelin'
about this.
The doors are closing.
Where the hell is everybody ?
Well, the lifeboats,
they're all still here.
Where the hell is everybody ?
Let's go !
[ Thunder Crashes ]
This place looks post evac, man.
Total spooky town.
Looks like somebody
beat you to the punch.
- Where the hell is everyone ?
- Who cares? Let's hit the vault and go.
[ Fizzing ]
Whoa ! Whoa !
Shh.
- [ huckles ]
- Fuck me, man.
- [ Both Yell ]
- [ Gunfire Barrage Resumes ]
[ Hanover ]
All right, knock it off!
I don't know what the hell's going on
around here, but we've got a job to do.
- Machine shop.
- Sublevel nine.
- T. Ray, Mamooli,
take Finnegan and the grease monkey.
- Take the freight elevators.
They're the only ones that go
all the way to the bottom.
[ Moans ]
[ Groaning Sound ]
What the hell was that ?
[ Sighs ]
[ Whispers ]
Yes. Not bad.
lear.
[ Soft Beeps, Static ]
The man did a good Job
of shutting everything down.
Yeah. But he wasn't
supposed to stop the ship.
It's like-- It's like
everyone just... vanished.
[ Metallic Rumble ]
[ Water Moving, Gurgling ]
Turn up the pump, you idiot !
We're sinking.
I'm the one supposed to be
in charge around here.
[ Water Lapping, Gurgling ]
[ Soft Snorting Sound ]
[ Leila Screams ]
[ Gasping, Shrieking ]
- [ Hanover n Headset ]
Billy, Billy, are you there ?
- What ?
[ Skipped item nr. 316 ]
What do you mean no passengers ?
How could there be no passengers ?
nly an idiot
would be out in this rain.
[ Screaming ]
The hulls on these ships
are supposed to be impregnable.
[ Mamooli ]
So what are you sayin' ?
If the hull's impregnable,
why are my feet wet ?
h, my God. He's right.
You're right. Yeah.
You got a real big mouth
on you, you know that ?
Yeah, I know that.
I don't like you.
Hey, check it out.
It's my future ex-wives.
[ T. Ray ] Mamooli, you bloody pervert,
get your mind out of the gutter.
- ome on, hurry it up.
- Whoa, man ! What stinks ?
[ Mamooli ]
Man, this water's freezing !
- [ Growling Sound Nearby ]
- oh-ee, whoo. Mm-mmm.
Hey, stay close.
- I didn't know you cared.
- I care about your gun.
Mamooli, keep an eye on 'em.
Mmm.
What you got there ?
- Peanut.
- Peanut ?
- kay. Peanut.
- [ Plop ]
- Shit !
[ Soft Growl ]
[ Growl ]
- Hey !
- [ Soft Growl ]
Who's in there ?
[ Growls Continue ]
You come out now,
or I'm gonna kick your ass.
[ Mamooli n Headset ]
T. Ray, what the hell are you doin' ?
[ Growling ]
[ Splashing ]
[ Growl ]
[ T. Ray Screaming ]
T. Ray ?
- Huh ?
- Hey ! What did you do ?
- Don't shoot !
- Well, what happened to T. Ray ?
What did you do to him ?
We didn't do anything !
[ Loud Growling, Wailing ]
What the hell happened here ?
[ Beeps ]
- Please enter your security key card.
- Hey!
- Well, what do you know ? Sign of life.
- With curves.
As the assistant to the purser,
I'm afraid I'll have to report you.
You tell me what happened here,
or I pull the trigger.
Name's Trillian.
And you are ?
Thank you.
Makes my Job a lot easier.
- Glad to be of assistance.
- So again, tell me what happened here.
- Where is everybody ?
- I thought you liked to blow things up.
- [ Recording ]
Good evening. The vault is now open.
- I do.
- [ Trillian Screaming ]
- [ Hanover ] Vivo !
-Jesus hrist !
- Son of a bitch !
- No, no, no, no !
- ome on !
Get outta here!
Come on, get outta here!
You just killed
one of my best men !
I didn't mean to. I-I-I thought
it was one of them ! I didn't know.
- Those are innocent people in there !
- [ Hanover ] Shut up !
- ne of who ?
What are you talkin' about ?
- ne of those things !
- Haven't you seen them ?
- [ Mamooli n Headset ]
What's that ?
Speak up, Mamooli !
- [ Hanover n Headset ]
You're cutting out. Repeat that !
- Yeah, yeah.
Shut up, man. Listen !
I think T. Ray's dead.
There's nothin' down here
but you and me. Hmm ?
[ Growling, Splashing ]
Go on ! Get the parts now !
Get the parts ! ome on !
[ Growling ]
Mamooli ! T. Ray !
They're everywhere. You hear me ?
We've got to get off this ship.
- What about the vault ?
- It'll be here. Grab Vivo's gun. Go !
What the hell was that,
Finnegan ?
I don't know !
I didn't get a good look !
If I don't,
I ain't goin' back to get 'em.
[ Growling, Wailing ]
[ Growling Increases ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Slams ]
Fifth level.
Fourth level.
Third level.
Second level.
- [ Moans ]
- [ Alarm Rings ]
- Second level.
- [ Growling, Metal Crashing ]
[ Crash ]
- [ Elevator Dings ]
- First level.
- This corridor! Hey, hey, hey!
- What are you doing ?
- I'm not staying in here !
- Trust me, lady,
it ain't any better out there !
- I don't care ! I'm outta here !
- Will you relax !
- [ Operator ] The door is closing.
- Who the hell are you ?
- I think she broke my nose.
Give me a chance,
I'll break the rest of your face.
- Not that anyone would notice.
- What is this about ?
- [ Operator ] First level.
- That's what I've been trying
to tell you.
- Third level. Fourth level.
- [ Squishing, Growling ]
Please stand clear
of the door.
- [ Elevator Dings ]
- Drop it ! [ Weapons ocking ]
- Now !
- Drop it ! Drop it !
Do it.
Where's Mamooli ?
T. Ray ?
- They didn't make it.
- What the hell happened ?
- I didn't kill anybody.
There's somethin' on this ship.
- [ Hanover ] Bullshit!
No ! It's not bullshit, Mr Hanover.
There are things on this ship !
- Please stand clear of the door.
- T. Ray was my-- You killed him.
[ Grunt ]
- I heard you the first time.
- Stand down, you !
And you, tell me what happened.
- Infested with what ?
- I don't know ! How do I know ?
- [ Exhales ]
- [ Growling, Crashing ]
- [ Growling, Roaring ]
- [ Operator Continues ]
- [ Roaring Ends Abruptly ]
- Second level.
Third level, fourth level,
fifth level.
Sixth level.
- [ Growling Resumes ]
- [ anton Yells ]
- [ Roaring Stops ]
- [ Trillian Gasping ]
What the hell is that ?
Hey, guys, you don't mind if we
get off this thing now, do you ?
That's a good idea.
[ Growling ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
[ Operator ]
This elevator is out of service.
[ All Shrieking, Yelling ]
You back off, Finnegan.
[ Metal Creaking ]
Holy shit.
Look at that.
Now what ?
[ Rumbling, Creaking ]
[ Rumbling Stops ]
[ Body Parts Squishing ]
[ Muttering ]
- [ Yelling ]
- [ Roaring ]
[ Loud Wail Ends Abruptly ]
ome on.
There's nowhere to hide.
[ Thunder, Lightning Crashing ]
[ Canton ] It was almost as if the ship
had struck a reef or something.
And then suddenly they were everywhere.
Th-The passengers all panicked.
Trouble is, nobody knows we're
in trouble. ouldn't send an S..S.
Well, then,
mon capitaine,
- Yeah, man, call in the Marines.
- Yeah, let's do it now.
[ Captain ]
Look, you don't seem to understand.
- Something has jammed the systems.
- Not something.
Someone.
Who are you ?
Hanover had a connection
on this ship,
somebody to knock out
all the communications.
Very quick, Mr Finnegan.
- Is this true, anton ?
- [ Finnegan ] How do we fix it ?
[ Gun ocking ]
Answer him.
- Answer him, you son of a bitch !
- [ Muttering ]
[ Gasping ]
- For God's sake, man, why ?
- Damn it !
Four hundred eighty-seven
point six million dollars.
The insurance.
That's what
the torpedoes are for.
You loot the ship, and then
you sink it for the insurance.
I spent my whole life,
my entire fortune, building this ship.
I'll be damned if I'm gonna lose it
to a bunch of pencil-necked bankers.
is a hell of a lot more than
we're ever gonna take in.
You mean, we're all gonna die
because you screwed up on the math ?
What about the passengers ?
Were they insured ?
I may be a crook,
but I'm not a savage.
- You despicable, lousy bastard !
- [ Grunting ]
- You sold us out
to the bloody insurance!
-All right, knock it off!
Do you realize how many innocent
people you've killed on this ship ?
- Hey, hey, break this up !
- Innocent passengers!
- [ Hanover ] That's enough !
- [ Canton ] Nobody was gonna get hurt!
- What ?
- I like it.
[ Metallic Rumbling ]
[ Soft Growling ]
[ Pipes Clanging,
Wailing Sound ]
- [ Screaming ]
- [ Roaring ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Roaring ]
- h,Jesus hrist !
- [ Screaming ]
- Good God, it's Billy !
- [ Moaning ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Moaning Continues ]
Jesus no ! no !
[ Screaming ]
- ver here now !
- Right here ! Right here !
[ Yelling ]
- [ Distant Gunfire ]
- [ Panting ]
Jeez Louise, lady, give a guy
a heart attack, why don't you ?
- [ Distant Wailing ]
- [ Trillian Gasps ]
[ Hanover ]
Over this way! Go ! Go !
What are these things ?
So, um, you got a boat waiting outside. Is that right ?
- Yeah.
- kay. Let's make a deal here.
You get me to your boat,
and, uh--
And I can have
whatever I want.
Yeah, whatever you want.
an you get me
a cold beer ?
Funny.
- [ Roaring ]
- [ Screaming ]
[ Growling ]
- [ Steam Hissing ]
- [ Growling ]
[ Snarling ]
[ Low Growling ]
- [ Roaring ]
- [ Gasps ]
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Roaring ]
- [ Gunshot ]
[ Screams, Pants ]
Time to go !
[ Distant Wailing ]
- I owe you one.
- Damn right, you do.
[ Both Panting ]
Get me off this boat alive
and we'll call it even. Deal ?
Deal.
Please tell me
you're a man of your word.
[ Panting ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Grunting, Screaming ]
- [ Growling ]
- anton, get me-- Aah !
[ Screaming ]
- Come on ! Pull!
- [ Captain Screaming ]
[ Growling ]
Eat this, you wankers !
[ Wailing Recedes ]
I'm beginning to fear
that our friends here...
the ttoia are about
as long as a pencil...
with bodies about
the size of a golf ball.
But those at 20,000 feet...
have been found to eat
full-grown sharks.
At thirty
or forty thousand feet--
Well, you do the math.
This, uh--
This is not good.
Are we talkin' some kind of
mutated sea monsters here ?
The ttoia
are very crafty.
[ Canton ]
They hide in burrows...
and catch their victims
with spiny tentacles,
and then they-they crush them
between massive jaws.
Yeah, and then they
eat you, right ?
They drink you alive,
sucking all the fluids out of a body
before excreting the skeletal remains.
I'm still givin'the orders
around here, mister!
You stay here and give
all the orders you want.
I'm gettin'back to my boat, cuttin'it
loose and gettin'the hell outta here.
Yeah, man.
I second that motion.
[ Finnegan ]
Which way now ?
At the end of this passageway,
there should be an underpass
on the port side...
- that'll take us to the upper levels.
- The starboard.
- Who do you think gave
you those blueprints ?
- [ Electrical Shorting Sound ]
I ask you, man,
could it get any worse ?
[ Power Surging Sound ]
[ Finnegan ]
Thanks,Joey.
They must have ripped a hole through
the hull. That's how they got in.
The power of these things,
it's-it's awesome.
- I'm glad you're so impressed.
- Shit !
- There's no way out through this door.
- It's buckled right to the frame.
- We can't go back the way we came.
- Okay, Canton, it's your ship.
Any ideas ?
[ Beeps ]
- He's right.
- How far ?
- [ Beeps ]
- [ Sighs ] It's 20 metres.
- Somebody's gonna have to go and check.
- I volunteer to wait here.
- Me too.
- No way.
I'll go.
But you're comin' with me.
If we make it through,
I'll fire two rounds.
- That means it's safe to come through.
- kay.
Hey ! It's mine.
Let's give the lady
a real gun, shall we ?
You know how
to use that ?
Yeah. If something comes at me, I'll
just pull the trigger till it goes away.
Careful with that.
It's got a hell of a kick.
I can handle it.
I think it's your turn
to carry the parts.
This is turnin' out to be
one hell of a day.
[ Gasping, hoking ]
ome on. Up.
I don't mean
to sound like a pussy,
an you just get asthma ?
- [ Gasps ]
- [ Thundering Explosion ]
- h, my God !
- [ Roaring ]
[ Wailing, Pounding ]
Jump !
- Fuck !
- [ Wailing ]
- [ Panting ]
- [ Pounding ]
[ Wailing ]
ome on, you son of a bitch !
ome on ! ome on !
[ Gun Rattling,
Pantucci Panting ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Screaming ]
- [ Yelling ]
- [ Shrieking ]
h ! Aah ! I'm outta here !
I'm outta here !
[ Wailing ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Moaning, Shrieking ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Gasping ]
ome on, buddy.
There you go.
[ Gasping ]
- Where's Mason ?
- It got him.
- Shit ! Not Mason !
- Grabbed him.
[ Mulligan ]
No way this is happening!
This isn't bloody happening!
- There are more elevators
through that hatchway over there.
- Fuck elevators.
I ain't goin' up
in no more elevators, man.
I agree with these gentlemen.
How much longer before
we can expect a rescue ?
- I'm not waitin' on any rescue party.
- We checked in Just before sunset.
It'll be another 24 hours before
they start searching for us.
Are you saying they're not even
gonna start looking for this ship...
all ove: killi us off left ad ight
Makes for a bit of a tight jam,
don't you think ?
- Are you insane ?
- No. No, man. He's right.
There's plenty of food here.
We can hold out until they rescue us.
They're right.
This is the galley for the crew.
With these hatches closed, there's
no way those things can get in here.
You wanna wind up in jail,
Mulligan ?
I don't care what you do, but I'm gonna
keep on goin'. It's our only chance.
Back on !
They're wiping us out one at a time.
I say we make a stand.
Right here, right now.
I'm not stayin' down here,
and that's a fact.
- Now, back off that hatch.
- I'll do it.
I'll do it.
I swear to God, I'll kill you.
- I'm not mucking about here.
- Whoa, whoa.
- Don't get hasty, man.
- We're not staying here, Mulligan !
- I say we are !
- [ Weapons ocking ]
You back off right now,
soldier,
before I put you down.
[ Finnegan ] I once saw a guy
put a fish in a bottle.
And then he corked it
and sealed it tight...
and threw it
to a baby octopus.
Now, the octopus,
he felt his way
all around that bottle.
he got the cork off,
slid inside...
and ate the fish.
And the moral
of this story is ?
We'r e th e fish .
The ship's already starting to sink.
What if they don't get here in time ?
- [ Trillian ] I-I don't want to drown.
- [ Pantucci ] Yeah.
Look, Mulligan,
you can do whatever you want,
but I am gonna
get my ass to the surface,
pray to God that my boat
is still there...
and those things
aren't crawlin' all over it,
and then I am gonna
bail the hell outta here.
[ Panting ]
What ?
[ Yelling ]
[ Rapid Gunfire ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Shrieking ]
[ huckles ]
You want some ?
You're nothin'!
[ Panting ]
[ Roaring ]
- [ Growling ]
- [ Gasping ]
You see that ?
Did you see that ?
- [ anton Whimpering ]
- Shit !
They're closin' the damn hatches, man !
They're closin' the hatches !
- [ Growling ]
- [ Trillian Shrieking ]
[ Electrical Shorting Sound ]
They're herding us !
They're forcin'us to go
where they want us to go.
Wait, wait. Now you're tellin' me these things can think ?
They're pushing us
toward the bow of the ship.
[ Canton ]
That's the way up, through there.
[ Panting ]
- Are you comin', or what ?
- Yeah.
I'm right behind you.
[ Panting ]
[ Steam Hissing ]
What the hell is this ?
Looks like some kind
of feeding ground.
Where's anton ?
[ Metallic Groaning ]
[ Groaning Intensifies ]
Now what ?
[ Growling ]
[ Trillian ] Oh, my God.
They're breaking through the hull.
[ Roaring ]
Go ! Go ! Go !
What is this ?
pen up, anton !
pen the door !
[ Screaming ]
[ Wailing ]
Do you hear that ?
They're comin', man !
- They're comin' ! [ Screams ]
- [ Grunts ]
- Son of a bitch !
- I'm sorry !
Where's my gun ?
[ Water Gurgling ]
Hey, give me one of those !
- [ Grunts ]
- You idiot !
- [ Beeping ]
- Well, you didn't tell me to do that.
- [ Water Splashes ]
- You didn't tell me to do that.
[ Growling ]
[ Screaming ]
- Son of a bitch !
- Hey!
No, no, no, no !
What are you doing ? ome on !
I lost the backpack !
It's got the engine parts to my boat !
We're not goin' anywhere
without 'em !
- Damn !
- [ Water Rushing ]
- h, shit.
- [ Trillian Gasps ]
- [ Roaring ]
- They're catchin' up !
All I got is a wet stick of gum
and a breath mint !
-kay !
All right !
What do we feed 'em ?
What are we gonna feed 'em ?
[ Gunshot ]
- [ Screaming ]
- [ Roaring ]
[ Gasps ] h, my God !
It's gonna sink !
[ huckles ]
It's going to sink.
- [ Thunder rashes ]
-An island!
Hey !
Hey, did you see that ?
Yeah, I see it !
We gotta get to it ! ome on !
- That heap of junk is your boat ?
- You got a better one ?
[ Laughing ]
Wait a minute.
What if those goddam things
are crawling inside it ?
We'll have to
take our chances !
Then what are we doing ?
Trust me !
I got a plan !
[ Skipped item nr. 729 ]
[ Electrical Buzzing ]
[ Gasping, Groaning ]
[ Panting ]
[ Screams ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Snarling ]
[ Skipped item nr. 736 ]
Don't say I never
gave you nothin'.
You asshole !
[ Growling ]
[ Trigger licks ]
[ Screaming ]
-And find the keys!
- Yeah ! Yeah !
[ Skipped item nr. 744 ]
- [ Thunder Crashes ]
- [ Grunts ]
kay, okay.
The key's gotta
be around here somewhere.
[ Beeping ]
[ rashing Sound ]
[ Skipped item nr. 750 ]
Get to the engine room and
get me any power you can, fast.
[ Skipped item nr. 752 ]
''Joey, what happened
to your leg ?''
-Joey, you wanna be
the appetizer or the entree ?
- Right, right, right.
I'm on it.
Give me the parts.
[ Mutters ]
- [ Mocks Muttering ]
- I lost 'em !
- You what ?
- I lost 'em, okay ? I lost 'em !
Go with the flow, will you,Joey ?
I got a plan.
- more than about a city block!
- Well, that's all I'm gonna need.
Now get movin', will you ?
I don't think she made it.
Right.
I'll, uh--
I'll go see what I can do.
[ Beeping ]
And kaboom.
- That oughta do it.
- All set.
[ Skipped item nr. 768 ]
Then she's runnin'on fumes.
[ Skipped item nr. 770 ]
- ome on ! ome on ! ome on !
- [ Engine Sputters ]
[ Panting ]
Come on ! Come on ! Come on !
- [ Engine Sputters ]
- Damn !
[ Skipped item nr. 775 ]
[ Skipped item nr. 776 ]
[ Skipped item nr. 777 ]
[ Skipped item nr. 778 ]
[ Engine Idling ]
Bye-bye, baby.
- Hello.
- [ Gasps ]
- Shit !
- I'll bet. It's nice
to see you again too.
Ah-ha-ha ! No !
- Now, give me that key.
- [ Thunder Crashes ]
- I'll-- I'll take you with me.
- Yeah, what about the others ?
Fuck 'em. They have to go down
with the ship. That's how it works.
Give me that key.
[ Grunts ]
[ Shouts ]
- [ Trillian Screams ]
- Son of a bitch !
Just cut the engines, Tucc !
Do it now !
Wait ! Wait !
Shit !
Give me that key,
you bitch !
[ Grunts ]
Goddam it!
[ Screams ]
[ Panting ]
I've never actually
killed anybody before.
[ huckles ]
I don't think so.
No witnesses allowed.
I don't think this'll be quick,
but... it'll be interesting.
[ Skipped item nr. 801 ]
No ! No !
[ Skipped item nr. 803 ]
[ Shouting ]
[ Metallic Groaning, Rumbling ]
- [ Gasps ]
- [ rashing ]
h, now what ?
[ Metallic Creaking ]
[ Hysterical Wailing ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Skipped item nr. 811 ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Fierce Roaring ]
[ Skipped item nr. 815 ]
Now there's somethin'
you don't see every day.
- Time to go.
- Good idea.
- [ Screams ]
- [ Grunts ]
[ Growling ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Skipped item nr. 821 ]
Finnegan !
Aah !
[ Skipped item nr. 824 ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Growling, Roaring ]
What are you lookin' at ?
[ Weapon Unsheathing ]
[ Shrieking ]
[ Grunting ]
Look out !
[ Weapon ocking ]
Get to the cargo bay !
Go ! Go !
[ Roaring ]
Pantucci!
Come on !
Let's get the hell outta--
[ Skipped item nr. 837 ]
[ Skipped item nr. 838 ]
[ Gasps ]
God. Finnegan,
where are you ?
[ Thunder Crashing ]
[ Screams ]
[ Skipped item nr. 843 ]
Shit. I'm sorry.
Thank God you're alive.
Damn straight I am.
Let's keep it that way, huh ?
[ Skipped item nr. 846 ]
- [ Engine Idling ]
- [ huckles ]
[ Skipped item nr. 848 ]
[ Skipped item nr. 849 ]
No !
[ Skipped item nr. 851 ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Groaning ontinues ]
[ Finnegan ] Well, that's a hell
of a Jump. Let's get up some speed.
Hang on.
Whoa !
h, shit !
Finnegan !
Faster ! Faster !
[ Roaring, Snarling ]
- [ Shrieking ]
- ock it !
[ Shrieking ]
- [ Grunting ]
- [ Beeping ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Canton Groaning ]
[ Screams ]
[ Finnegan Grunting ]
We gotta get outta here !
This thing's gonna blow !
- [ Growling ]
- Whoa !
[ Snarling ]
[ Skipped item nr. 870 ]
[ Skipped item nr. 871 ]
- ock it !
- [ ocking ]
[ Shrieking ]
Whoo-hoo !
[ Groaning ]
[ Beeping ]
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Beeping ]
[ Panicked Groaning ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Shrieking ]
Shot to shit.
Where are you
when I need you,Joey ?
Well, I guess we're
stuck on this island.
[ Surf Crashing ]
Well, I guess we're
stuck on this island.
Better than
a cold beer, huh ?
Finnegan !
Hey, guys !
Joey !
-Joey !
- Are you all right ?
- Watch the leg !
- I thought you said he was dead.
- I thought he was dead !
- It-It almost had me, man.
It came crashin' right
through the windshield.
I ran out the hatch.
The thing was snappin' at my ass.
Next thing I know,
kabloowie.
And your damn surrfoard
almost cut me in half, man.
[ Laughing ]
Hey, was it the water
in my eyes,
-Joey--
- You know, I could always go
for a stroll down the beach...
-Joey.
- or go for a little swim.
kay, cool. I'll stick around.
You don't have to beg me.
[ Beastly Roaring ]
[ Snarling ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Finnegan ]
Now what ?
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org