Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
There it goes again.
That's the seventh time
in the last two hours.
Still no idea what's causing it?
It seems to be
opening and closing
completely at random.
No unusual readings.
No ships coming through.
For all we know,
the Bajorans are right.
Maybe it is a message
from the Prophets.
Emissary.
Hmm. If it is,
they didn't tell me.
Maybe the Prophets
don't recognize you
with the new beard.
There must be a scientific
explanation for this.
Here we go.
Something funny, old man?
Hmm? No, nothing.
Ops to Captain Sisko.
Sisko here.
Captain, we are receiving
a priority one message
from Starfleet Security.
On my way.
Then the Andorian says,
"That's not my antenna."
Why do I bother?
Quark!
What can I do for you,
Constable?
Dax... where is she?
She's not here.
Is there anything else
I can do for you?
You find all this very funny,
don't you?
You and Dax
probably planned it together.
Planned what?
Moving my furniture.
Is that what this is all about?
Someone moved your furniture?
Not someone-- Commander Dax.
It's the fourth time
she's done it this past year.
She breaks into my quarters
while I'm regenerating
and moves all my furniture
out of alignment.
Shifts one piece
three centimeters to the right
the next
four centimeters to the left.
Not one object in my quarters
is where it's supposed to be.
And... is that a bad thing?
Everything I own is carefully
and painstakingly arranged.
Dax knows this
and yet she takes
a perverse delight
in throwing
my quarters into chaos.
I'd hardly call
three centimeters "chaos."
Maybe you wouldn't, but I do.
You humanoids are all alike.
You have no sense of order
and Dax is the most
humanoid person I know.
Sisko to Constable Odo.
Odo here.
Please report to Ops mmediately.
Acknowledged.
Uh, when you see Dax
say hello to her for me.
How many people were
at the conference?
27, including
the Tholian observer.
27... it's unbelievable.
Federation President
Jaresh-lnyo has declared
a planet-wide day of mourning.
Constable, take a seat.
Of course.
Ten minutes ago,
we received a recording
of a high-level
diplomatic conference
that took place
between the Federation
and the Romulan Empire
on Earth two days ago.
Computer, begin replay
at time index 5-9-1 1.
A bomb.
Of unknown composition.
A crime like this hasn't
been committed on Earth
in over a hundred years.
Go back and show him
what you showed us.
Computer, restart recording
at time index 5-9-1-6.
One-tenth normal speed.
Freeze picture.
Enlarge section F-3 and enhance.
Keep your eye
on the piece of pottery.
Computer,
resume at one-tenth speed.
That's a changeling.
No sign of a changeling
was found in the aftermath.
We must assume
that it escaped unharmed.
I was hoping that this
would never happen
but it finally has.
The changelings
have reached Earth.
How's that?
Another centimeter to the left.
Shouldn't you be on the Lakota?
The Lakota won't depart
for another hour.
Which gives us plenty of time
to repair the damage
you've done to my room.
And while I'm gone, I want
your solemn word that you'll
stay out of my quarters.
You've got it.
So, how long do you think
you and Captain Sisko
will be on Earth?
I have no idea.
I just hope this trip
isn't a waste of time.
I'm not sure
what Captain Sisko and I
can tell Starfleet
about my people
that hasn't already
been in our reports.
Believe me, Odo,
with changelings on Earth
Starfleet's going to need
all the help it can get.
There. How's that?
A little more to the left.
Whatever you say, Constable.
Wait till you see
the size of the eggplant
I'm getting out
of my garden this year.
As big as Crenshaw melons
and twice as heavy.
So, how is Judith?
She still helping out
in the restaurant?
I sent her home to Portland.
Your sister's got
her own life to worry about.
Besides, she never puts enough
cayenne pepper in the jambalaya.
Just like Mom.
Which means she has
no business in the kitchen.
It'll be good to have you
home again, Benjamin.
Jake, too.
Dad, you know that this
isn't exactly a vacation.
I'll be spending most
of my time in San Francisco
at Starfleet Headquarters.
Whatever you do during the day
is your business.
But at dinner time
you better get yourself
down to New Orleans.
No son of mine is going
to eat that replicated slop
Starfleet calls food.
Not if I have anything
to say about it.
You won't get
any argument from me.
So, Dad...
you feeling okay?
Oh, let's not start that again.
It's just a question.
You look a little tired.
How's the new aorta holding up?
The doctors say
I am a medical marvel.
At the rate things are going,
in a year or two
I won't have an original organ
left in my body.
They'll write me up
in the medical books.
Well, but you're feeling okay?
Just point me in the direction
of a party and a pretty girl
and I'll show you
how good I feel.
Make sure you call me
as soon as you and Jake get in.
Your rooms are always waiting
and ready for you.
I know that, Dad.
We'll be there
before you know it.
Jake-o.
Dad.
You just missed Grandpa Joe.
Did you tell him we're
staying in San Francisco?
Uh, I didn't quite
get around to it.
Ah. Dad.
You know
if we stay with Grandpa
he's going to put me
to work in the kitchen.
Is that so bad?
Well, chopping vegetables
for nine hours a day
isn't exactly my idea
of a vacation.
Well, Jake, you're
not a child anymore.
Grandpa will not expect you
to chop vegetables.
He'll want you to wait tables.
Oh!
Barkeep.
So, what can I get
you two flyboys?
A Scotch, neat
and a pint of your finest
bitter for my mate.
Make it quick.
The cabbage crates
will be coming back
over the briny any minute now.
All right, all right.
I'd hate to let the Jerries
strafe that green
and pleasant land of yours
while the two of you
were taking time out
to get a drink.
No choice, man.
Ritual, you know.
To Clive, the best bloke
ever to prang his kite
into the Channel.
Ah, got to keep
a stiff upper lip.
Hear, hear.
Down the hatch.
Ah-ah!
Now, remember what I said
about throwing glasses.
So, you want to go back up
and have another crack
at the Jerries?
Oh, I don't know.
To tell you the truth,
my heart isn't in it.
Aren't you taking Clive's death
a little seriously?
After all, he was just
a holosuite character.
It's not Clive.
It's Earth.
You probably wouldn't
understand this, Quark
but when you care
about a place
and it's in trouble
and you want to do
something about it
and you can't
it's very frustrating.
I know exactly what you mean.
When the Great Monetary Collapse
hit Ferenginar
I was hundreds
of light-years away
serving as a ship's cook
on a long-haul freighter.
I can't tell you
the heartbreak I suffered
knowing that rampant inflation
and currency devaluation
were burning like wildfires
through the lush financial
foliage of my home.
It still depresses me
even today.
I remember thinking
my accounts needed me
and there was nothing
I could do.
I-l-l felt so... so helpless.
So you see...
I do understand.
Somehow, you telling me that
doesn't make me feel
the least bit better.
Hu-mans.
All you care about
is yourselves.
Odo!
Hang on a second.
Well, I take it
the Battle of Britain
has been won yet again.
There's a Spitfire
with your name on it
waiting in the hangar.
When you get back from Earth
you can take Clive's
place in the squadron.
Somehow I doubt it.
Look, Odo, do me a favor.
If you get a chance
stop by and visit
my folks in Dublin.
Just make sure
they're okay, you know?
I'll try to find the time.
Good. I'll let them know
you might drop by.
Anyone I can look up
for you, Doctor?
Uh, no, no, that'll be fine.
Um, just wish I was
coming with you.
Well, to be quite honest, Doctor
I wish both of you
were going with me.
I could use the company.
I... I doubt
that a shape-shifter
will be welcome on Earth
at the moment.
No one can hold you responsible
for what your people are doing.
Oh, really?
Well, I'd better get
over to the Lakota.
We'll be leaving shortly.
Good luck.
I don't believe in luck.
But I appreciate the sentiment.
Well, we better get
out of these uniforms.
Ah.
The Lakota 's gone to warp.
When was the last time
the wormhole opened?
12 hours ago.
Perhaps it has
returned to normal.
I suppose so.
You sound disappointed, Major.
I guess I am.
Part of me was hoping
that the Prophets were behind it
that they were finally
going to show themselves
to the Bajoran people.
I prefer Klingon beliefs.
I supposed your Gods
aren't as cryptic as ours.
Our Gods are dead.
Ancient Klingon warriors
slew them a millennia ago.
They were more trouble
than they were worth.
I don't think I'll ever
understand Klingons.
Don't worry about it, Major.
Nobody does.
That's the way they like it.
Ben.
Admiral Leyton.
Good to see you again, sir.
Captain Sisko.
This is my adjutant,
Commander Benteen.
Benjamin was
my executive officer
aboard the Okinawa
and a damn fine one, too.
I did all right.
Ah, don't be modest.
Admiral Leyton has had his
share of executive officers
and you're the only one
he ever speaks fondly of.
Present company excluded.
Admiral Leyton is the one
who recommended me
for the job on Deep Space 9.
One of my better ideas.
You must be Odo.
That's right.
Forgive me for staring
but you're the first
changeling I've ever met.
That you know of.
I sympathize with your problem.
Uncovering changeling
infiltrators is no easy task.
Well, with the help
of the two of you
I trust it'll be
a little easier.
What exactly do you
want us to do?
We'd like to confer
with you and Odo.
See if there's anything
about the Founders
you left out
of your official reports.
I'll help in any way I can
but I think you'll find my
reports were quite thorough.
Admiral, I doubt you brought us
all this way
just for a debriefing.
Of course not.
Ben, Earth is in danger--
maybe the greatest
danger it's faced
since the last World War.
Something has to be done
about these shape-shifters
which is why you're here.
You know more about the Dominion
than anyone in Starfleet.
And so, effective immediately,
I'm making you acting head
of Starfleet Security
here on Earth.
Congratulations, Captain.
This is one beautiful fish.
Seems a shame
to eat a trout this pretty.
Why, you should thank me
for the privilege
of simply looking at it.
Well, go on, take a bite.
It won't bite you back.
Now, I don't want to see
anybody studying
the dessert menu.
If you order anything
but the bread pudding soufflé
you'll be making a mistake
you will regret
the rest of your lives.
You should listen to him.
The man knows his bread pudding.
Benjamin!
Dad.
Jake-o.
Hey.
When are you going
to stop growing?
If you keep this up,
you'll be bumping your head
on that alligator
before too long.
I remember when
you used to tell me
that alligator
was just in stasis
and you let it out every night
to guard the restaurant.
Oh, I had to stop doing that.
It got to be too much trouble
wrestling it back up
to the ceiling every morning.
Come on, I'll get Nathan
to bring you both
something to eat,
and we can catch up.
Nathan, some gumbo
for these fine, young men.
Yes, sir.
So... where's
this shape-shifting fellow
you were coming with?
With things the way they are,
Odo thought it would be better
if he stayed
at Starfleet Headquarters.
I don't blame him.
I haven't seen people so nervous
since the Borg scare.
Me, personally,
I'd like to meet him.
Though I have to admit
I-l'm a little suspicious
about anyone who doesn't eat.
Grandpa.
Well, aren't you going
to eat anything?
I ate before you got here.
Son, don't look at me that way.
You've lost weight.
You think so?
The doctors said you have
to keep your weight up.
Don't you start, too.
I have a vat of crayfish
in the back
that needs cleaning
and it's got your name on it.
Now, I'm going to say this
one time and one time only.
I am fine.
I'm happy, I'm healthy
and I'm planning on celebrating
at least 50 more birthdays.
Satisfied?
Mmm. Gumbo is as good
as I remember.
Starfleet must be taking
the shape-shifters
pretty seriously
to have you come
all the way back here.
It is serious, Dad.
27 people murdered
right here on Earth.
Never thought I'd see the day.
But now that my son's
on the case
I feel a lot better.
Jake!
Nog?
Captain Sisko.
What do you think?
You look good, Cadet.
You think so?
Nog, I thought
I was going to see you
tomorrow at the Academy.
You are.
I'm just here for dinner.
Nathan, the usual.
I didn't know
you liked Creole food.
I don't.
I like tube grubs.
And your father is
the only person on this planet
who can get me live ones.
I've been thinking
of adding them to our menu.
Of course, I'll have
to cook them
for our human customers
serve them
with a nice remoulade.
Cook them?
What good are tube grubs
if they don't wiggle
on the way down?
So, how's everything
at the Academy?
Jake, they call it the Academy
but what it really is,
is school.
Well, I want to hear about it.
It's a lot of work--
Iots of classes,
lots of studying--
I'm doing okay.
Now, where are those tube grubs?
Good night.
You come back soon.
Come on, Ben.
I've got a nice bottle of cognac
I've been saving
for a special occasion
and I think this qualifies.
I think you're right.
Ah, there's nothing like
a full stomach
to make life worth living.
So, you going to tell me
what's on your mind or not?
What do you mean?
I mean, you didn't
stay here until closing
just to get one more root beer.
Something's up.
My friend, the writer...
always looking for a good story.
If you don't want to tell me,
fine, don't tell me.
It's nothing.
It's stupid.
All right.
Forget about it.
It's just...
the Academy's different
than I thought it would be.
Different how?
Some of the cadets--
they're kind of standoffish
especially the upperclassmen.
Because you're a Ferengi?
That's what I thought at first
but then I heard
some of the other freshmen
complaining
about the same thing.
Complaining about what?
Little things.
For instance, there's this group
called Red Squad
made up of all the top students.
They're always
going off on trips
getting special training.
None of them
will even talk to me.
You've only been in the Academy
for a month.
You can't expect
to fit in right away.
Who knows? One of these days,
you might even be in Red Squad.
I'm sure if you let them
get to know you
show them you're
a really good guy to be around
everything'll work out.
I am a good guy to be around,
aren't l?
I always thought so.
Mr. President, I'd like
to introduce Captain Sisko.
Captain, I've seen your record
most exemplary.
Thank you, sir.
Captain Sisko has
several suggestions
on how to combat
Dominion infiltration.
I think you'll find them
very interesting.
Hmm...
I understand the need
for increased security, but...
blood screenings, phaser sweeps?
They've proven very effective
on Deep Space 9.
I'm sure they have
but I hope you'll keep in mind
that this is Earth
and not a military installation.
Which means it's a
lot more vulnerable.
We have to take precautions.
Precautions may be advisable
but I will not disrupt the lives
of the population
despite what happened
at Antwerp.
I believe the changeling threat
to be somewhat less serious
than Starfleet does.
Mr. President, I assure you,
the threat is real.
For all we know, there was
only one changeling on Earth
and he may not
even be here anymore.
But, if he is here,
we have a problem.
There's no telling
how much damage
one changeling can do.
Forgive me
for saying so, Captain
but you sound a little paranoid.
Do l?
Forgive the intrusion,
Mr. President
but as you can see
Starfleet has every right
to be concerned.
Allow me to introduce Odo,
my Chief of Security.
A very effective entrance,
Mr. Odo.
One that never should
have been allowed to take place.
Admiral Leyton and Captain Sisko
walked in here
without being searched,
without being blood-tested
and without having
their possessions
subjected to phaser sweeps.
If Odo was
a Dominion infiltrator,
he could've killed you.
Or replaced you--
the way security is now
a changeling could
get anywhere on Earth
replace anyone, even you.
Mr. President
all we want is your permission
to increase security
at Federation and Starfleet
installations here on Earth.
Blood tests will be limited
to high-ranking
Federation officials
Starfleet officers
and their families.
The average citizen
won't even notice
the difference.
I wish these security measures
were not necessary
but the safety of Earth
and the entire Federation
depends on them.
You present
a convincing argument, Captain.
It seems I have no choice
but to accept your proposals.
Thank you, sir.
Don't thank me.
If I could think
of another solution
I would use it.
It took centuries
for Earth to evolve
into the peaceful haven
it is today.
I would hate to be remembered
as the Federation President
who destroyed paradise.
We're not looking to destroy
paradise, Mr. President.
We're looking to save it.
Activate the phaser.
That's enough.
How do you feel?
Well...
that time I definitely
experienced discomfort.
What was the setting?
Three point one.
If we set
the phasers at 3.4
we should be able to stun
any changeling we hit
and force them back
into a gelatinous state.
I'd push it to 3.5,
just to be on the safe side.
But, if you want to do
any more tests
you'll have to get
another guinea pig.
I've been shot quite enough
for one day.
3.5 it is.
I want these units installed
in every room at Starfleet
and Federation Headquarters.
Then start working
on the orbital stations.
We'll have them in place
by tomorrow night.
I want to thank you, Captain.
Thank me? For what?
For convincing the President
to implement
these security measures.
It feels like we're
finally on the right track.
Ha. You'd think she
would have thanked me as well.
I'm the one who got shot
13 times today.
Captain Sisko.
I hope I'm not
interrupting anything.
We were just about finished.
Can I speak to you for a minute?
In private?
Captain, I just want to say
I appreciate everything you've
done for me so far, and...
Jake says you're having
difficulty in school.
He told you that?!
He tells me everything.
I don't want you
to get the wrong idea!
Nog, you and I both knew
that it was going
to take a while
for you to adjust to the Academy
and for the Academy
to adjust to you.
I know, but it turned out to be
even more difficult
than I expected.
You're just going to
have to stick with it.
And I intend to.
In fact, I think I've come up
with something
to help me make
some new friends.
-Good.
-But I need your help.
I want to join Red Squad.
Red Squad?
What do you think?
I don't know what to think,
I've never heard of it.
It's an elite squad
of cadets at the Academy.
You know, the best of the best.
They get special classes,
simulated missions
off-campus training sessions,
all kinds of things.
A group of elite cadets?
They never had anything like
that when I was at the Academy.
Oh, it's pretty new.
It's a way of rewarding
excellence among the cadets.
I have the grades to qualify
but I need to be sponsored
by a high-ranking officer.
Ah, and you want me
to put your name in
for consideration?
All I'm asking for
is a chance to prove myself.
I... I'm kind of busy
right now, Nog.
But if I get the chance,
I'll see what I can do.
Thank you, sir!
This means a lot to me.
I can see that.
Dismissed, Cadet.
Yes, sir.
Well, look who's here.
Come in, stranger.
Sorry.
I haven't been around
much lately.
Oh, things have gotten
a little busy.
You want to tell me about it?
I'm afraid I can't.
You'd think that Admiral
could spare you
for a few hours a day
to visit your father.
With you in San Francisco
and Jake off visiting
that school in New Zealand
it's like the two of you
aren't even here.
You know, Dad, you
could come and visit us
at the station once in a while.
Don't start that again.
Earth's my home,
it's where I belong.
Besides, what would happen
to the restaurant
if I went gallivanting
around the galaxy?
You think Nathan can handle
this place on his own?
Nathan will be running
things around here
sooner than you think
if you don't take
better care of yourself.
I had a talk with your doctor.
And he tells me that you
haven't been in to see him
for eight months.
The man's an idiot.
He's lived in New Orleans
20 years
and can't tell the difference
between Creole food
and Cajun food.
Maybe not, but he can
tell the difference
between a healthy body
and one with progressive
atherosclerosis.
He says that if you
don't come in
for vascular
regeneration therapy
that this restaurant will
be looking for a new owner.
Ben, at my age, staying
healthy is a full-time job
and I am too old
to work two jobs.
Now, how long
until you're due back
at Starfleet Headquarters?
I've got about an hour.
Just enough time to take a walk
to Audubon Park.
You up for a stroll
with your old man?
I can't think of anything
I'd rather do.
Nathan, don't forget
to stir the gumbo.
Odo.
That was really something.
I've never seen you
imitate a life-form before.
Well, I was just taking
a little aerial tour
of San Francisco.
It's quite nice.
Not as ancient
as the cities on Bajor
but almost as impressive.
Makes me wonder
how many other changelings
might be flying around
up there.
If all they're doing is flying
around imitating sea gulls
we don't have much
to worry about.
I doubt that other changelings
are wasting their time
imitating birds.
They don't all share
Odo's lack of skill
when it comes
to mimicking humans.
That's right, they don't.
I'm glad
you're keeping that in mind.
Well, if you ask me
that was a pretty
convincing sea gull.
Thank you.
Though I'm not sure
the gulls would agree.
Commander, I think we've taken
up enough of Mr. Odo's time.
Keep practicing.
You'll have those birds
fooled in no time.
-Admiral?
-Yes.
I know that Starfleet Command
has always been a little uneasy
about a changeling
working in their midst.
I just wanted to say
how much I appreciate
the trust you've shown in me.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Well done, Odo.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
How did you know he wasn't me?
Oh, I'm not sure exactly.
It's as if I could feel
the changeling's
hostility toward me.
You're the only changeling
who's ever harmed
one of his own people.
I'm sure that hasn't
made you many friends.
What I'd like to know is
why was he imitating me.
You have access to all
our security procedures
all our protocols,
that makes you
a logical target.
I suppose so.
The bottom line is,
a changeling infiltrated
the grounds
of Starfleet Headquarters
imitated the Admiral,
and got away scot-free.
Our security measures
aren't working.
We're doing everything
the President will let us do.
Maybe that's not enough.
We could talk
to the President again.
I'm afraid that would
be a waste of time.
Jaresh-lnyo would be
a fine President in peacetime
but we have a war on our hands
and he doesn't seem
to understand that.
All he cares about
is not upsetting people.
But humans are tougher
than he thinks.
We've created a paradise here
and we're willing to fight
to protect it.
And you think the President
isn't willing to fight.
I think the President
is a long way from home.
This isn't his world.
We can't expect him to care
about it the way we do.
Sisko here.
Captain, your son's trying
to contact you.
He says it's urgent.
Put him through.
Dad, you'd better get down here
right away.
What's wrong?
It's Grandpa.
He's been arrested.
What's going on here?
Captain, we never meant for
things to get out of hand.
What did you think
would happen--
storming in here
and accusing me and my grandson
of being a couple
of shape-shifters?
We never accused you of being
a shape-shifter, Mr. Sisko.
We were just carrying out
our orders.
All family members
of Starfleet personnel
are required to submit
to blood screenings.
No exceptions.
That's the most ridiculous thing
I ever heard of.
Do you believe that?
I should.
I signed the orders myself.
Now why would you go and do
a stupid thing like that?
Dad, it has to be done.
Grandpa, look.
I'll take the test first.
Go ahead.
Now me.
Sir, that's not necessary.
Do it anyway.
It's your turn.
Jake, do you think
I'm a shape-shifter?
Come on, Grandpa.
Answer the question.
No, I don't think
you're a shape-shifter.
At least somebody in my family
has some sense.
Dad!
I don't want to hear about it.
You take these two vampires
and tell them
to either sit down
and grab a menu
or get out of my restaurant.
Jake, get them a menu.
But, sir...
I would recommend
the shrimp creole.
Look, Dad...
I don't want to hear it.
Listen to me...
you have got to take the test.
Why should l?
If I was an enemy spy
Iooking to replace someone,
I think I could
come up with better choices
than an old chef.
Yeah, you're probably right,
but this isn't about you.
We've got civilian families
living on starships
and Starfleet installations
all over the Federation.
The only way we can
secure those facilities
is to test everyone there
whether they wear
a uniform or not.
I'm not living
on a Starfleet installation.
Dad, if we test
the family members
of one Starfleet officer,
we must test them all.
You may want to test everyone
but that doesn't mean
we all have to cooperate.
I didn't take
an oath to Starfleet.
Neither did Jake or your sister
or anyone in your family.
We have rights, Ben,
including the right
to be as stubborn
or thickheaded as we want.
Damn it, Dad!
Can't you cooperate
just one time?
You don't take your medication.
You don't go to the doctor.
You won't let Judith help
you in the restaurant.
Just one time, please
do what you're asked.
I wish I could
but what you're
asking me to do is wrong.
You can't go around
making people prove they are
who they say they are.
That's no way to live
and I'm not going
to go along with it.
Now, if you want
to make yourself useful
start some water boiling
for the shrimp.
Come on, Dad.
Don't be this way.
If I have to,
I will get a warrant...
And what?
Hold me down and force me
to give you my blood?
Because that's the only way
you'll get...
Damn it!
Now look what I've done.
Jake?
Yeah?
I've got a dermal regenerator
under the...
Benjamin Lafayette Sisko.
What the hell
has gotten into your head?
You actually thought
I was one of them, didn't you?
I don't know.
I wasn't sure.
This business has got you
so twisted around
you, you can't think straight.
You're seeing shape-shifters
everywhere.
Maybe you ought to think
about something for a minute.
If I was
a smart shape-shifter--
a really good one--
the first thing I would do
would be to grab
some poor soul off the street
absorb every ounce of his blood
and let it out on cue
whenever someone like you
tried to test me.
Don't you see?
There isn't a test
that's been created
a smart man
can't find his way around.
You aren't going
to catch shape-shifters
using some gadget.
The only thing
you can count on in this life...
Grandpa!
The EMTs said he'd be okay
and they were right.
It turns out
it was just a mild stroke
brought on
by his atherosclerosis.
How's Jake handling it?
He is very upset.
He knows as well as I do
that if my father doesn't
take better care of himself...
I've found that when it comes
to doing what's best for you
you humanoids
have the distressing habit
of doing the exact opposite.
I can't argue with that.
But what bothers me is
that for a few moments there,
I really believed
that my own father
was a changeling.
A reasonable assumption
considering the circumstances.
I don't care
if it's reasonable or not...
but when a son
can't trust his own father...
That's why my people
came here--
to undermine the trust
and mutual understanding
the Federation is built on.
But what if my father's right?
What if all our precautions
turn out to be useless?
Maybe they will, but that
doesn't mean you should give up.
My people are here
and you've got to fight them
with whatever you've got.
I hope you don't take this
the wrong way, Constable
but there are times I wish
you'd never found your people.
Believe me, Captain...
sometimes I feel the same way.
Grandpa, would you
please sit down?
Enjoy your meal.
Your food will be right out.
What's that look
supposed to mean?
You sat down.
Damn right I sat down.
I feel terrible.
You should be in bed.
Jake, the only time
you should be in bed
is if you're sleeping, dying
or making love
to a beautiful woman.
I'm not tired, I'm not dying
and the truth is,
I'm too old for beautiful women
so I might as well be here.
Your father's the one
you should be worried about.
Dad? Why?
I've never seen him so tense.
It's like he's carrying
the weight of the world
on his shoulders.
He is.
I suppose he is, at that.
What happened?
I don't know.
The whole block's dark.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Admiral, what's going on?
From what we can tell, Earth's
entire power relay system's
been knocked off line.
Even Starfleet's emergency
backup's been affected.
How could that happen?
I don't know
but if you ask me, there's only
one possible explanation...
Sabotage.
The changelings.
Take out the power relays
and you neutralize
sensors, transporters
surface-based defense
installations...
In other words,
Earth is defenseless.
If the Dominion attacks now,
we don't stand a chance.
I'm not interested in excuses.
It is imperative
we get the power relay system
functioning again.
Mr. President.
How did you people get here?
We contacted the Lakota
and used their transporters.
Mr. President,
as acting head of Earth Security
I must advise you
to declare a state of emergency.
You're serious.
With the exception
of the Borg incident
there hasn't been
a state of emergency
declared on Earth in a century.
I am aware of that
but I have reason to believe
that a Dominion war fleet
may be in the Alpha Quadrant
headed for Earth.
Do you have evidence
to back this up?
Just before we left Deep Space 9
the wormhole was exhibiting
some unusual behavior--
opening and closing
for no apparent reason.
We didn't detect any ships
coming through at the time
but the Dominion
might have been using
some kind
of cloaking technology.
I wasn't aware the Dominion
had cloaking technology.
The combined Cardassian
and Romulan fleet
that the Dominion destroyed
in the Gamma Quadrant
was equipped
with cloaking devices.
Who knows what my people might
have taken from the wreckage.
How long
till the power relays are fixed?
From what we can tell,
the changelings
infected the system
with some kind
of self-replicating
computer protocol.
It jumped from one
power relay to the next
disrupting every system
it came in contact with.
The only way
to correct the problem
is to shut down the entire grid,
purge all the operating systems
and restart the relays.
And that could take days.
Which is why it is imperative
that you declare
a state of emergency.
What good will that do
when we have no way
to defend ourselves?
Mr. President, we can use
the Lakota 's transporters
and communications system
to mobilize
every Starfleet officer on Earth
in less than 12 hours.
We've been preparing
for something like this
for a long time.
We have stockpiles
of phaser rifles
personal force fields,
photon grenades--
enough to equip an entire army.
I can start getting men
on the streets immediately.
What you're asking me to do
is declare martial law.
What I'm asking you to do is
let us defend this planet.
We don't know what
the changelings will do next
but we have to be
ready for them.
Ben, tell him.
Sir, the thought of filling
the streets with armed troops
is as disturbing to me
as it is to you
but not as disturbing
as the thought
of a Jem'Hadar army
Ianding on Earth
without opposition.
The Jem'Hadar are
the most brutal
and efficient soldiers
I've ever encountered.
They don't care about
the conventions of war
or protecting civilians.
They will not limit themselves
to military targets.
They'll be waging
the kind of war
Earth hasn't seen since
the founding of the Federation.
At the same time,
my people will continue
to undermine Earth's defenses
in any way they can.
This power outage
is only the beginning.
I never sought this job.
I was content
to simply represent my people
on the Federation Council.
When they asked me
to submit my name for election
I almost said no.
Today, I wish I had.
We appreciate your feelings,
Mr. President
but we don't have time
for regrets.
You accepted the job
and now it's yours.
Mr. President
there are people
all over this planet right now
huddled in the dark, terrified
about what might happen next.
They're waiting for a sign,
something to reassure them
that everything
will be all right
but they won't wait long.
Fear is a powerful
and dangerous thing
and if you don't act
if you don't show them
that they're not alone
then fear will surely take over.
Give us the authority
we need, Mr. President
and we will take
care of the rest.
Earth is in your hands,
gentlemen.
Do what needs to be done.
Thank you, sir.
You've made the right decision.
I hope you're right...
for all our sakes.
Grandpa?
Grandpa, wake up!
I'm not sleeping.
I'm checking
my eyelids for holes.
You'd better come
take a look at this.
Take a look at what?
Come on.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org