Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
March 11.
Dear diary,
my husband of 18 years...
this week is being honored
by the city of Atlanta...
as the Jacob Frienstein
Attorney of the Year.
I am so proud of him.
He has worked so hard.
I wanna swing
Swing till daylight
with you
I wanna dance
Dance the whole night through
Where the beat-beat-beat
is jumping
And the crowd is feeling fine
Where the dance-dance-dances
are popping
Theirs are flowing like wine
I wanna swing
Swing till daylight with you
I wanna dance...
To look at us...
you would think
that we've got it all together.
But looks can be deceiving.
Some days are good
and I think he loves me.
Then other days...
I think he doesn't care.
Dancing till daylight
Just us two
Kicking up my heels...
I never thought
I'd see this day.
I was just saying
to my wife this morning...
that if I died and came back...
that I would want
to come back as me.
No, truly it is an honor...
to receive the Jacob Frienstein
Attorney of the Year Award.
It's especially
an honor because...
He is so into appearances.
What looks one way
on the outside...
can be a totally different
matter on the inside.
There is no way...
no way...
that I could have done
any of this...
without my wonderful wife
of 18 years.
I don't know this stranger
I sit next to.
All I know is that with
every dime and every case...
he has changed.
How about l...
run us a hot bath?
I left something at the office.
I have to go.
Who is she?
When you get a job
and pay one of these bills...
then you can ask me questions.
I am still your wife.
That's cute.
Charles...
I don't want to fight.
This is your night.
Let's just enjoy it.
Tell me what I need to do,
and I will do it.
You really want to know
what you ought to do?
Get the hell out of my car.
What a way
to start our anniversary.
Tell me...why do I love
that man so much?
Maybe if I could stop
thinking about...
how good things used to be...
I might be able to find
the strength to leave.
Hi, Sarah. How are you?
Hi, Mrs. McCarter.
Hey, Mrs. McCarter.
Kalvin, how are you?
How is Joanne?
-She's doing great.
-That's great.
-You doing all right?
-I'm wonderful. Thank you.
Listen, is he in?
Because I brought him, uh...
lunch.
Actually, I'm headed that way--
No, no. Please.
Thank you, though. Thank you.
Helen.
What, um...
Um...hi.
I'm Brenda Marcos.
How do you do?
Um...we got to go.
You ready, little fella?
It was nice to meet you.
Is that her?
Don't play games with me.
Tell me, Charles.
Is that her?
Thank you.
I'll see you at home.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
What?
-What are you doing?
-Working.
Where are you going
with my things?
Lady, look...I'm just filling in
for my cousin because he's sick.
Somebody named Charles McCarter
or something like that...
rented this truck,
told me to load it up and wait.
So that's what I'm doing.
No. Wait. Wait.
Christina?
Christina.
Christina, there--
there is a man out there
putting my things in a truck.
What is going on?
Mr. McCarter asked me to pack
all your things this morning.
And all these clothes
are from the boutique.
I wish I had a man to do
something like this for me.
Happy anniversary.
-I have something to tell you.
-Your gift first.
Aren't you going to open it?
Charles, I have to admit...
I thought you forgot,
but I saw all the clothes...
in the closet
and...ta-da! Ha ha!
It's not exactly my taste,
but I love it.
Helen--
This one, it doesn't really
fit quite right, though.
I think I'm going to have
to get some alterations--
Helen.
You see how I keep
interrupting you?
Charles, I only want
to hear the good tonight.
OK?
I need to tell you something.
What is she doing here?
I asked her to come.
Charles, what is going on?
Is she wearing the dress
that I just picked out?
What?!
There's no easy way
to say this...
but our marriage
has run its course.
It's over.
What? What are you
trying to say?
I'm saying...
it's over.
Charles!
Helen,
don't act so surprised.
I mean, I haven't
touched you in a year.
I haven't...well...
I haven't been happy for years.
18 years, and you think
you can just come in here...
and end it like this?
Charles, what am I supposed
to do without you?
You're a bright girl.
You'll figure it out.
Charles...please.
-Oh, my God.
-Don't do this.
Please tell me you're not one of
those weak begging sisters.
Brenda, let me handle this.
You are not leaving.
No...I'm not leaving.
But you are.
There's a truck outside.
It's full of gas,
and I hired some guy...
to take you
anywhere you want to go.
I can't keep treating her
like this. And my children...
not seeing their daddy
every night.
I'm staying here and there--
Children?
Two boys. They need me.
Charles.
It's me.
How can you say this to me?
How can you do this to me?
Good-bye, Helen. Now,
be a lady and leave quietly.
-No.
-No?
You would've never had
any of this without me.
Now, you better
get up out of here...
-before I lose my temper.
-No!
No, I am not leaving!
-You what?
-No!
You're leaving, all right.
You're leaving. Go on.
Any way you want to do it.
Get up! Get up!
Aah! No! Charles! No!
Come on.
Huh? Come on.
What you doin'?
Get out of here! Get out!
Charles! Charles!
Charles!
Oh, what the hell
have they got me into?
Hey, look...
we've been driving
around for hours now.
I do have another job that
I have to be at in a few hours.
So there's got to be
someplace I can take you.
Take me where?
He has alienated me
from my entire family.
He made me put my mother
in a home bec--
Because she didn't fit
into his "American dream."
I don't have anyplace to go.
Lady, I'm really sorry
to hear about that...
but it's the middle
of the night--
-Just stop the truck!
-I'm trying to help you out.
-I'm not stopping the truck.
All you men are just alike!
You just think about yourselves!
You don't think about
anybody else but yourself!
Just stop the truck,
and I will drive myself...
where I have to!
Pull the truck over!
Hey! Don't grab the wheel!
Hey. Don't touch the wheel.
I'm stopping. I'm stopping.
-Then get out!
-We're in the middle of nowhere.
I don't care!
Get out of the car!
I'll drive myself!
You know what? Now I see
why you're going through...
what you're going through.
Oh, you go to hell!
Have a nice life.
Yeah, you're welcome!
Don't shoot! It's Helen...
your granddaughter!
Don't shoot!
What the hell? Girl!
I always open the door
this time of night shooting...
'cause there ain't nothing
but a crackhead...
or the police knocking
on your door this time of night.
What you doing here this late?
I was in the neighborhood and--
You were in the neighborhood?
I thought I'd come by
and say hi.
You live in a mansion
on the other side of town.
What the hell you doing
in the ghetto?
You ain't on that stuff, is you?
Is you over here trying
to buy some stuff?
I missed you.
Come by in the daylight here.
Don't come by--
Madea, please.
Come on in here.
Who that is at the door?
Shut up, Joe. I got this.
...I'm gonna have
to put my foot down.
Kunta Kinte put his foot down,
and it got chopped off.
Now shut the hell up
and go back to sleep.
I know I had some
cigarettes in this--
Harpo.
Harpo, who this woman?
Joe, go in that room
and take your medicine.
You know you crazy as hell
when you don't take it.
I say hell...no.
What the hell?
Look what you
done made me do!
Oh, hell!
Get the hell up.
You didn't come by yesterday.
You got to eat something
out there on them streets.
You got to be careful,
you hear?
Look at you. Lord help me.
You ain't got
no regular clothes, do you?
What?
Helen...hey.
Debrah?
Yeah, girl.
You gonna hug me?
Yeah.
So, how are you doing?
You look good. You look good.
Marrying that rich lawyer.
When we were kids, we both said
we'd get a rich man, right?
We both got lawyers.
Deb, what--
what's going on?
Don't. Don't do that.
Don't judge me.
Thank you. I got to go.
You take care of yourself
out there.
Lord.
You hungry?
I can't eat anything.
You need to eat something.
What happened to her?
Life.
Brian and the kids must
really be going through it.
They're doing all right.
But I want to talk about you.
I called Charles this morning...
and he told me,
before he hung up...
that you and him
is getting a divorce.
But what I can't seem
to figure out is why you here.
He put me out of the house.
-Who house?
-Our house.
Exactly. How the hell
a man gonna put a woman...
out of her own house?
He might've put me out...
but he was gonna
put me out of half.
I'm gonna go in
the other half of the house.
He wasn't puttin' me
out of all of it.
The house is in his name, Madea.
Lord have mercy.
That's how women get messed up.
Too busy out shopping when you
need to be checking the deed.
Whoo! That makes me mad, girl.
I don't have any rights
to the money.
No right?
I signed a prenup.
What the hell
you sign a prenup--
I ought to punch you
in the face.
Who the hell told you
to sign a renup?
He didn't have nothin'
when you married him!
Charles always knew
he'd be successful.
And he said to me...
"l want to know that
you're here for love."
And I didn't have a job.
So it's his money.
Is it? What was you doing
while he was working, honey?
Taking care of the house,
cooking and cleaning.
Exactly.
That sounds like a job to me.
Cooking and cleaning--
how long you do that?
18 years.
All right. OK.
18 years...
let's see how much he owes you.
you've been cooking...
cleaning...
having sex with him
when he wanted.
-Was it good?
-No.
Major deduction.
And I didn't tell you
that he hit me.
Girl, that man
owes you 64 billion...
283 million, 974 trillion...
5 thousand...
and 20 dollars and 82 cents.
Now, you need to get your money.
-That'll never happen.
-You want to bet?
I can happen
one of two ways, honey.
You can get it from his
checking account voluntarily...
or his insurance policy.
Involuntary manslaughter.
Which one it's gonna be?
-Madea.
-Mm-mm.
I ain't gonna have this.
Come on.
-What? Where are we going?
-To your house.
Oh, no. The guard
will never let us in.
I said come on!
Mayday! Mayday!
Lord have mercy.
Get your stuff.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
These your clothes?
They're hers.
Oh, they're hers?
Who is, uh...
"Dol...say & Gab-anna?"
Who that is?
Dolce and Gabbana.
They're designers.
Oh. She a label ho.
$700 for a damn rag?
Just a rag.
Madea, no, no, no.
Don't do that.
This man left you...
for some old floozy.
Madea, what's wrong?
A wire hanger!
Rip it.
Rip it?
-Rip it.
-No, no.
Rip it!
-Rip it? Rip it!
-Rip it!
Rip it!
What the hell are you doing?
Rip it like this!
Get mad at it!
It'll make you feel better!
Rip it!
Rip it! Rip it!
Rip something!
-Rip it!
Rip it real good. Rip it.
Wait a minute.
What's this gonna solve?
Nothing. It's just gonna
make you feel better.
-Rip it! Ha ha ha!
-Rip it!
This is for every black woman...
who ever had a problem
with a black man!
Goodness.
Calm down, girl.
I'm tired as hell.
OK.
I'm gonna go down
to the office.
I forgot some things.
OK...you go down
in the office...
because you forgot something.
Find me some oxygen.
And bring me some oxygen!
What are you doing in here?
Charles.
Are you stealing from me?
No. No, I just--
How did you get in here?
I changed the locks.
What the--who are you?
Who are you?
I'm the owner of this house.
Wrong answer.
My granddaughter Helen...
is the owner of this house.
You're the ho. You ain't
got no power or no deed.
Did you do this?
This is Vera Wang!
Who that is? She do nails?
I need to get my nails did.
That's it!
I'm calling the police!
I'm not scared of no popo.
Call the popo, ho.
Call the popo, ho!
Charles, please...
I don't have any money, and--
I tried to be nice to you,
didn't l?
Didn't l?
I'll just go.
You'll just go?
I'll just take it,
and I'll just go.
Oh, you'll just
take it and go, huh?
You're gonna take
my money and go?!
If I call the police, they're
gonna be here in ten minutes.
OK. Then that leaves me nine
to beat the hell out of you.
You think?
I know tae kwon do.
And I know whoop your ass.
Come on. Bring it on.
You don't know me.
I'm from the projects.
Come on.
What the hell is your problem?
Come on. Shut up. Shut up!
Oh, hell no. Watch out.
Yeah, you keep running!
What?
Now you asking me questions?!
You begging now?
Oh, please do it.
Please hit her.
Please!
I want to see you do it.
What the hell's wrong with you?
Here, now, you bastard.
Put your hands on her.
Oh, my God! Don't hurt him!
Oh, I'm not gonna hurt him.
I'm gonna kill him.
Putting his hand
on my granddaughter.
I'm calling the police.
You call the police, so they can
see how you done hit her.
No, just get out.
Charles, I have been nothing but
a good woman and wife to you.
I don't deserve this.
You will reap what you sow.
Keep your money.
You crazy as hell.
Just leave it.
I might leave some of it.
It was this that made you
the evil bastard that you are.
Get out.
Here, now, the way I see it...
half of everything in this house
belongs to her...
and I ain't leaving here
till she get it.
-She'll never see it.
-What did he say?
Come on, Madea. Let's go.
That's right. Go.
Give me 5 minutes with her
in the bathroom, please.
Madea, let's go.
OK. Oh, yeah. I'm leaving.
It's just a matter of time...
before he does
the same thing to you.
Never. I could never be you.
I'm a woman who knows
how to get and keep her man!
What's that?
Madea...
Half of everything
in here belongs to her.
Which half do you want?
Do you want this half...
or do you want this half?
Madea.
Your Honor,
case number 456790--
the People versus Mabel Simmons
and Helen McCarter.
Criminal trespassing,
reckless endangerment...
criminal possession
of a handgun...
assault with a deadly weapon...
What are you
walking so fast for?
Suspended license,
expired registration...
reckless driving,
and a broken taillight.
Girl, I know that ain't
who I think it is.
I know you didn't say
Mabel Simmons. Madea?
How are you doing,
Judge Mablean?
It's good to see you.
Your hair is pretty, girl.
Look at you.
You're looking good.
How you been?
You're still at it?
This ain't even my fault.
What had happened was--
Save it.
Who's here for the defense?
Brian Simmons here on behalf...
of Mrs. McCarter and
Mrs. Simmons, your Honor.
-Brian?
-How you doing, Judge Ephriam?
I'm getting tired
of seeing your aunt.
I'm tired of seeing you.
It won't happen again.
Yeah, I bet.
Bail is set at $5,000
for Miss McCarter...
property or cash.
But as for you, Madea...
I'm placing you
under house arrest.
You ain't putting me
on no house arrest, honey.
I ain't fi'n
to to deal with that.
It's either that or prison.
What's your choice?
I'll take the house arrest.
Bailiff, call the next case.
The city of Atlanta
versus Bobby Brown.
What is this,
repeat-offender day?
Bobby! Bobby, I love you!
Sit down, Miss Houston.
-OK, you like hot sauce?
-Put that lid down!
What the hell?
How the hell you do that?
You don't know
what we're playing?
Hey, Daddy.
I see you got Thelma and Louise
out of jail.
Yeah, I did. Hey, stop running.
Stop running.
Say hi to your aunt Helen.
-Hi.
That's your son. Tiffany.
-My God. How old is she now?
-She'll be twelve tomorrow.
Hey, baby. How you doing?
-Can l?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So...
I saw Debrah.
I didn't know she was so bad.
Yeah. She took it pretty hard
when you left.
Charles wanted us
to move away from anything...
that reminded him of the past,
and why I let him do that...
Debrah and I were thick
as thieves growing up, huh?
Yeah, you were.
I'll tell you what.
Y'all about to be set.
What you got? Oh, hell.
Y'all don't know nothing
about playing no cards.
I'm gonna take mine and git.
I could have spent my money
in a better place.
Did you hear me, John?
We gonna play, or we gonna talk?
Joe, let me get some.
That's some good stuff.
You want some, John?
I guess not.
Joe, let me get some.
Last time we gave you
some of this stuff, Mildred...
we had to call the popo on you.
We had to call the ambulance
and everything.
You went crazy as hell.
You ain't supposed to smoke this
when you're on lithium.
I'm all right.
All right. Don't wet up my butt,
get the lipstick all over it.
You act crazy if you want to.
Whose play is it?
Play something.
Brian, can you handle
my divorce?
You don't even have to ask.
I always thought that
if I did all I could...
God would bless my marriage.
It takes a lot more
than you doing all you can.
And who's to say that
this is not your blessing?
You know, sometimes
we hold onto the things...
that God himself
is trying to tear away.
It's not that easy.
You know women. We love hard.
-And men don't?
-Not like a woman.
I don't know
if I agree with that.
We don't love as easy...
but when we love,
we love just as hard.
You don't see men
getting themselves...
in situations like mine.
The mother of my kids
is a junkie...
and I love her.
That's a tough situation.
Yeah. I look at Tiff--
she is so much like her.
She wants to sing.
I can't let her do that.
She's not Debrah.
Tell that to my heart.
Orlando. O-dawg,
what's going on, man?
Big Brian, what's up, man?
Y'all got it smelling
real right around here.
That's my deal, man.
That's my deal.
Hey, I want to introduce
you to somebody.
This is my cousin Helen.
Helen, this is Orlando.
Did I miss something?
You two know each other?
This is the sweet young lady...
that threw me out
of a moving truck.
This is the crazy woman--
That's her.
This town is too small.
I think you owe me an apology.
I don't owe you anything.
I was just trying
to help you out the other night.
Oh, yeah, right.
You're no good Samaritan.
He paid it. It's not like
you're some savior or something.
I'm gonna go...
check--do something.
Just another bitter
black woman, huh?
Excuse me?
I called you bitter, because
now every man you meet...
is gonna have to pay
for what he did.
You don't know
anything about me.
I know I watched a man
drag you out of a house...
and treat you like dirt.
Now there's another story
you can tell my cousin.
And I'm not bitter.
I'm mad as hell!
Turn that off up there.
Turn it off.
Shut up up there, all that
music.
How you doing, Henry Lee?
It's good to see y'all.
See, I'm on house arrest.
What is that?
You don't even
want to know, baby.
You don't even want to know.
Get somewhere and sit down
over there, little boy...
before I knock the hell
out of you. Where's your mama?
There you go.
-Mildred, you all right?
-Mm-hmm.
Mildred, don't you start
acting crazy.
Give me, give me. Here.
I'm gonna put this out.
You acting like you crazy.
I'll save that for later.
Your play, Mildred.
Play something.
Help! Somebody help me!
I'm out.
What happened to my eyes?
Everything is dark!
Open your eyes, and you might
be able to see something, fool.
Crawling all over me!
The rabbits!
The rabbits
are crawling all over me!
You ain't supposed to be
smoking that stuff, Mildred.
Rabbits!
Brian, please take her home
to her house.
I don't know why the hell
you come over here...
to my yard with that.
Get on, rabbit. Go, rabbit.
Go. Go, rabbit. Go.
OK, the rabbit's gone. OK?
All right. No more rabbits.
Hey, Mildred,
you forgot your rabbit.
Don't come back over here
no more, Mildred!
Don't come back over here!
I don't see no rabbit.
That was good stuff we had.
Is that a rab--
that's a rabbit!
Here. Use this.
What's this,
your way of apologizing?
Because if it is,
I'm not accepting it.
I'm sorry, mister.
Hey, hey.
My name's Orlando.
Orlando.
Willie, put some music on.
Something we can dance to.
You got it.
Let's turn this party up.
Y'all, come on. Dance.
Come on. Everybody come on.
Come on, Helen.
You and that young man.
Come on, young man. Come on.
March 19.
Dear diary...
I look out at my family
having fun and laughing...
and everything in me
is screaming for help.
How do I get to that place?
How?
Go, Joe! Go, Joe!
Hello?
Chuck, this is Jamison.
Man, I need to talk to you.
You know what time it is?
I don't really care
what time it is.
I got a situation.
We need to talk now.
It went bad.
What are you talking about?
-I shot him.
-Who?
Some cop undercover
who was trying to sting me.
What does that
got to do with me?
Charles,
I need a lawyer and a judge.
Now, there is $300,000
in that bag.
That ought to
buy me both, right?
Look, I'm a legitimate
defense attorney...
and I would advise you
not to try and bribe a judge.
Look, man, I'm hot!
I don't have time for
all this legal stuff, man.
OK, look, you know I don't deal
with your kind anymore.
My kind? Brother,
before you started...
defending all
these rich white boys...
it was my kind
that got you down.
-I'm going home.
-Home?
Oh, how quickly we forget.
I ran so much coke
for you back in the day...
I paid for that house.
Now look here. I need you,
like you needed me...
back in the day
to get all you got.
No. What you need
is a lawyer...
and not to ever
call my house again.
You are my lawyer.
You know where to find me.
Lord Jesus. All of this
calamity in the world.
But I tell--
The paper's sad.
It's really sad.
You nasty as hell.
I don't know what
I'm gonna do with you.
Here.
What?
You need a job.
Oh, Madea, I don't--
I don't know
how to do anything.
I got a job for you...
as soon as I get
some more Vaseline.
Joe, that is your--
that's your family.
That's your dead husband's
side of the family.
She ain't no kin to me.
I could introduce you to Harvey.
Maybe he'll help you out.
She ain't selling no dope, Joe.
If I had a bottle
of battery acid...
I would give you
a chemical peel...
just scrub all of that ugly
off of your face.
I know you're my brother...
and the only reason I'm
letting you stay in my house...
is to get your check.
But I can still
get your check...
if you come up missing.
Keep trying me.
But you're gonna end up
in the Chattahoochee river.
What you looking at?!
You ain't moving in here.
Next thing you know,
she'll be getting mail here.
Joe, leave that baby alone.
If their name
comes on the envelope...
that means they move
right the hell in.
Get out.
Get--get out.
Baby, take that newspaper...
and go on in the kitchen
and look for you a job.
And an apartment.
Look for an apartment
while you're in there.
You always messing
with somebody.
What the hell's wrong with you?
You're just grouchy as hell.
You been grouchy.
That's why Mommy and Daddy
didn't like you.
She ain't moving in here.
Ain't enough room in this house
for all of us here.
This ain't "Roots." These rooms
are barely big enough...
for you to turn around in.
Man, but you know,
you're just huge.
You big as a Buick.
You just fat as hell.
I watched you walk
down the hall the other day.
I thought somebody had put
a refrigerator on your butt.
You're huge. You're big.
And that's something
you'll never...
in your life hear a woman say.
Yes!
Thank you, Mrs. McCarter.
She's in her room.
Hi, Mama.
Hi.
I brought you some things.
Hey, baby. How you doing?
Oh. I'm doing OK.
Yeah.
They talked to me
about the bill here yesterday.
They call you?
Yes.
I'm gonna get that paid.
You know Charles
don't care nothing about me.
What makes you think
he's gonna pay it?
I talked to Madea.
I know what's going on.
I think I'm...
losing my mind, Mama.
He hurt me so bad.
He was my everything.
God is your everything.
Don't you know
he's a jealous god?
He don't want no man before him.
I don't even know
where to begin...
to pick up the pieces
of my life.
Lord have mercy.
I was 39 years old
when you were born.
I never ever dreamed
I'd have children.
And then here you come...
sweet bundle of joy.
But what did I do?
I think I shielded you
way too much.
Now you got to get out there...
try to stand
on your own two feet.
Oh, no, Mama.
I can't do that.
I'm not strong like you.
Sure you are.
You got the strength
God gave us women to survive.
You just ain't
tapped into it yet.
Come here.
Come on.
Come on now.
Oh...
just let it go.
Nothing wrong with
shedding a few tears.
It cleanses the soul.
You know, you need
to stop thinking...
about what you think
you lost...
and look forward
to what there is to gain.
It's a new life, baby.
It's right in front of you.
All you got to do
is reach out and grab it.
How do I do that, Mama? How?
By waking up every morning...
and thanking God that you did.
And then ask him to help you.
Just ask the savior to help you.
April 18.
Dear diary,
every day I wake up...
I take my mother's advice.
Most days, I don't want
to get out of bed...
but I do.
Some people say,
"One day at a time."
Seems too long for me.
Most days, all I can do
is moment to moment.
The good thing
about being this low...
is that there's
nowhere to go but up.
Hi. Can I get your order?
Hi.
OK, I'm gonna kill Brian.
Did he tell you I work here?
Hey, easy. Easy.
A man's got to eat, right?
What can I get for you?
How about a coffee
and a number four?
We don't have number fours
in this restaurant.
OK. How about just a coffee?
Coffee.
OK.
I like the new haircut...
a lot.
Thank you.
Oh, no matter what
You may be going through
Take it to the master
He'll see you right on through
I know Jesus, whoo!
Take it to him
You can leave it there
He will work it out
No matter what
You may be going through...
April 25.
Dear diary,
today was a bad day.
I got up and came to church
because I was so angry.
When I think
about all the blood...
and sweat and tears
I put into my marriage...
it makes me want to hate him.
Let me tell you something, boss.
I paid you a lot of money,
and that judge, he ain't down.
The judge had no choice...
but to allow the videotape
into evidence.
I told you
to make this go away.
Say it wasn't me,
I wasn't there.
How the hell do you
use self-defense?
You're on videotape.
And it will be
very hard to explain...
you not being there
at the time of the murder.
Self-defense is our only option.
Then put me on the stand.
I'll say it wasn't me.
Then all your priors
come into play.
Look, Mr. Jackson,
you have to let me work here.
Look, man, you can get me off,
make this go away.
Look, I said
I would do all I can.
Well, that better be
a hell of a lot, brother.
Or I will do all I can.
Wait a minute.
Are you threatening--
Ain't nobody talking to you.
I done paid you a lot of money.
You know how it is
on the streets, Chuck.
Brother don't do what he say.
However you and your homeys
settle your disputes...
this has to play out in court.
-If I go down, man--
-If you go down?
Kalvin, walk away.
Walk away.
Don't let this suit fool you.
I don't take too kindly
to threats, Mr. Jackson.
And I don't make
idle threats, Mr. McCarter.
I better get off.
May 12.
Dear diary...
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org