Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Water! Come on!
- He found water.
That's it, Eema.
Come drink.
Kron, look.
All we had to do is dig, and...
Good. Now, get out of the way.
Wait! Wait!
There's enough for everyone!
Ah!
- Oh.
- Eema!
That's it. Keep pushing and shoving.
That's very helpful.
Bruton, we've been walking
in circles. There's no water here.
- I think we should get back.
- Shh. Keep it down.
Let's get out of here.
Now, you come out on three.
One, two, three!
Come on. Come on out.
No one's gonna hurt you.
Hey, hey.
What's going on?
The little Aladars haven't
had anything to drink.
I think they're scared of me.
Who wouldn't be?
You are pretty scary.
Come on over, guys.
- Take it easy. Don't worry.
She's just a hair ball.
- And proud of it.
Come on. He's gonna
find you some water.
Here. Now, you just
take a foot and press.
Whoa.
Hey, hey, hey.
Come on. Come on. Knock it off.
Let's work together here, huh?
A little teamwork. Ready?
One, two, three. Press!
Good job, Suri.
- Where are your parents, anyway?
- A lot of us are on our own now.
You like kids, I see.
- Well, the skinny ones
can be a little chewy.
I'm Aladar...
the "jerkasaurus."
Ohh. Sorry about that.
You're probably right.
- Dad, wake up.
- Huh?
Why did you
help that old one?
What else could we do?
Leave her behind?
Oh. You mean, you actually...
Well, that happens all the time.
- You don't survive
if you're not...
- Strong enough.
Well... yeah.
Is that you talking,
or your brother?
Everything's so different.
I-I don't know
what to think anymore.
Look, Neera...
we watch out for each other,
we all stand a chance of getting
to your nesting grounds.
- You sound so sure.
- I'm not,
but it's all I know.
So, um... Oh, water.
I'll, uh,
get you some water.
- Can I try it?
- Sure. Just press.
- Hmm.
- Oops.
- Sorry.
- No. You... You first.
One down... and,
well, one down.
Kron!
- Carnotaurs!
- What? They never come
this far north.
The fireball must've
driven them out.
You led them right to us!
Maybe you can feed them
with your hide!
Move the herd out,
double-time!
- What's happening?
- My brother's moving the herd.
Kron, what's going on?
Carnotaurs. If we don't keep moving,
they'll catch up to us.
But the others in the back...
They'll never make it.
They'll
slow down the predators.
You can't sacrifice them
like this!
- Hold it! That could be
you back there! Or you!
If you ever interfere again,
I'll kill you.
Stay away from him!
Ooh.
Aladar, no.
You just... just go. I'll be okay.
Let's go! Let's go!
Carnotaurs!
- Carno-what?
- Carnotaur.
A mouthful of teeth
with a bad attitude. Let's go.
Come on, you guys! Get on! Get on!
We're gonna get left behind.
Let's go! Hurry up!
We're losing them!
Aladar, slow down.
Oh, joy. Blisters.
I've got blisters
on my blisters.
You don't wanna know
where I got blisters.
- What was that?
- It came from up ahead.
- Okay,
what's the worst thing it could be?
- A carnotaur.
- What's the second-worst thing
it could be?
- Two carnotaurs! Oh!
- That's it. I'm gone.
- Oh, my goodness!
Everybody, we don't know for sure.
It could be the herd.
- Let's check it out.
- Oh, my goodness.
Goodness gracious.
Oh, it's Bruton.
It appears we weren't
the only ones left behind.
- What happened?
- Carnotaurs. We should keep moving.
- We can't just leave him here.
- We can if we move fast enough.
Hey, you don't look so good.
Let me help you.
Save your pity.
I just need some rest.
Now, get away from me.
Suit yourself.
Hmm?
If you change your mind,
we'll be in those caves.
Mm.
It's dark, but
at least it's dry.
I like dry. It's the dark part
I'm having trouble with.
Ouch!
Ooh. Sorry, Url.
Sturdy little thing,
ain't he?
Ahem. We appear to have a visitor.
You coming in or what?
What is it with you?
At least I know enough
to get in out of the rain.
Now, come on.
On your feet.
- Uh, you can lie down
with us. It's warmer.
May I remind you
that he's one of them?
Well, looks like
he's one of us now.
Ahh. Who booked
this trip, anyway?
Ah, you'll be at the nesting grounds
soon enough.
Well, when I get there, I'm gonna
give Kron a piece of my mind.
You tell him, Eema.
If I could sleep that deep,
I'd be in paradise.
If you could sleep
that deep, honey, you'd be dead.
This plant grew
on our island.
It will make you feel better.
Ahh.
Why is he doing this?
Pushing them on with false hope?
It's hope that's
gotten us this far.
But why doesn't he let them
accept their fate?
I've accepted mine.
- And what is your fate?
- To die here.
It's the way things are.
Only if you give up,
Bruton.
It's your choice,
not your fate.
Well, the plant will help.
- Shh.
Carnotaurs.
- What do we do?
- Wake the others.
Oh.
Ooh.
Go! Go!
Hurry!
Move it, Eema!
Oh!
Aladar!
Aladar! Oh, no!
- I'll hold them off!
You help the others!
Bruton!
Bruton! No!
You did what you could.
It's okay, little ones.
We're going to make it.
Okay, okay. Let's
do it again. Let's do it again.
- Uh, I spy with my little eye...
- A rock.
You got it again!
Ooh! You are good!
Well, I'll tell you what I spy.
A dead end.
- What do we do now?
- I guess we just go back.
Hold on a moment.
Zini, what is it?
- Do you smell that?
- Yeah.
Get a load of that.
- Good show.
Everybody stand back.
We're outta here!
Aladar, look out!
No!
Aladar, we'll go back.
Back to what?
It's gone.
We're not meant
to survive.
Oh, yes, we were.
We're here, aren't we?
And how dare you
waste that good fortune
by simply giving up?
Shame on you.
Shame on you! Shame on you!
The worst of it is,
you allowed an old fool like me
to believe I was needed...
that I still had a purpose...
and do you know what?
You were right.
And I'm going to go on believing it.
And I, for one,
am not willing to die here.
Oh, dear.
The nesting grounds.
It's... It's untouched.
Our new home.
And it comes with a pool!
Cannonball!
Whoo-hoo-ha-ha!
Ha. Amateur.
Look out below!
Not to mention Neera.
They'll get here...
Mm. Soon enough.
Oh, no.
Eema?
- I spoke too soon.
- What is it?
That is the way
we used to get in here.
They'll never make it
over that.
Aladar, wait! Wait!
Kron'll eat you alive.
Let him try.
Mm. I hope Kron's
in a listening mood.
Stay here.
We'll find a way
around it.
In the morning,
we'll climb it.
Our survival, our future,
is over these rocks.
Now, let's go home!
You'll make it,
won't you, boys?
- No.
- Watch them. They're tough!
If they can do it,
so can you!
- Kron!
Get the herd out of here!
A carnotaur is coming!
- Keep moving!
- Stop!
- I've been to the valley!
There's a safer way!
- Go on! Show 'em!
- Kron, listen to him.
- Look, we gotta go now!
- Go where, straight
to the carnotaurs?
If we hurry, we can get around them!
You can't get over those rocks!
There's a sheer drop
on the other side!
You're gonna kill the herd!
I know a way to the valley,
and everybody can make it!
Now, follow me!
Kron!
They're staying with me!
All right. Let's go!
Neera!
He's led that monster
right to us! This way!
No! Don't move!
If we scatter, he'll pick us off!
Stand together!
Kron!
No. No.
Kron.
Welcome home.
Move over. Bringing in
babies is what I do best.
I'd say it's been a few years
since you've hatched an egg.
- You're right, so let me
practice on your head.
Look! Somebody wants to meet you.
Ohh! Aren't you the sweetest
little small fry I ever did see?
Hey, little guy.
He looks just like me.
Meet your dad.
He's not as crazy as he looks.
- Ohh. Oh, happy day.
- Well done, little one.
Come here, you little rascal.
Let me get a good look at you.
Yep. You're your father's son,
all right.
- Hey!
Look what I found! New neighbors!
Any of you ladies up for a game
of "monkey in the middle"?
Easy, now! Easy! Hey!
None of us really know what changes,
big or small, lie ahead.
One thing is certain...
Our journey’s not over.
We can only hope
that in some small way...
our time here
will be remembered.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org