Fucking hell.
Well, you know,
this is Area 52.
We are filming
the "Sanchez" movie.
So I got this idea, right,
where we proper up the ante.
What we got to do is bollock
right down this field,
we got a massive
football pitch...
and just smash the car
straight for the caravan.
But if you get
in the corner--
If you laid down,
you'd be all right.
No, 'cause you're
the shortest, right?
- Oh yeah, great.
- No no no!
( both shouting )
What if it just goes "plop,"
and mows me over?
- Trust us.
- It's not going to mow you over.
- God.
- We've worked it out.
We've got a tape measure
and everything.
Short man, short life.
Fucking bye!
Go on, Daint,
fuck him up!
I'm tellin' you--
no, it's not happening.
It's not fucking--
end-off, no. Fuckin'...
- Oh, come on, Panch!
- Oh, come on!
Daint, I don't give
a fuck if you've got
a flux capacitor
in that fuckin' car.
I'm not going
in there, right?
Before he fuckin'
wakes up,
let's just bollock it
for the fuckin' caravan,
straight through--
well, off to the corner,
'cause if you go through it,
you'll probably fucking kill him.
Look at Pritch
with his seatbelt on.
( "All My Friends
Are Dead" playing )
- Go on!
- Come on!
# Where are your friends? #
# Where are your friends?! #
What?
Don't fuck around!
# What? What? #
# Where are my friends? #
# All my friends
are dead #
# All my
friends are dead #
# Got kicked
in the head #
# All my friends
are dead #
# All my
friends are dead #
# All my friends
are dead #
# They got smacked
in the head #
# All my friends are dead #
# I always knew that they
would end up like today #
# They bought
the bullets #
# And they played
with hand grenades #
# Hey! #
- You fuckin'...
- No, Dainton.
- ...knobber, knobber, knobber.
- Tough fucking shit.
I got fuckin' payback
for once in my fuckin' life.
I put chili sauce in your fuckin' eyes
while you were driving.
Payback? Look where
the fuck we are!
Payback?
We're fucking dead.
- Pritchard: Dead?
- Fuckin' monkeys.
Boys?
I have a little proposal
for you fellas.
I want you to go
on a mission
throughout the world
to wreak havoc,
inflict pain
and, most importantly of all,
commit the seven
deadly sins.
If you succeed,
I'll give you
your lives back.
Fail and I'm afraid
this is it, lads--
the end of the road.
So go forth and sin.
I'll see you on the flipside.
( farts )
( all laugh )
( rock music
playing )
- ( sheep bleats )
- ( man yells )
( choir singing )
Dainton:
According to Dante,
sloth deadens
the spiritual senses.
But according to "Dainto,"
sloth is the epitome
of man...
that is Pancho.
( heart monitor beeping )
Welcome to the "Sanchez"
sleep trials.
Step one...
( sucking )
...Superglue.
( snoring )
Number one.
His mouth.
( heart monitor
beeping )
Whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa-- whoa whoa.
As you can see,
he's quite agitated.
( beeping quickens )
Feels like
I've got fuckin'
serious shit
up my nose.
Joycey: Watch out,
you got stuff-- medicine--
you've got this stuff
on your head.
Watch out,
watch out, don't --
Proof that this man
can fall asleep anywhere in the world.
Someone's fuckin'
glued my nose up.
( laughing )
- My nose is fuckin'...
- Superglued shut.
- ( all laughing )
- Try to blow it out.
It is proper stuck on,
though, isn't it?
It's going
fuckin' nowhere.
That's reinforced, that is.
What happens if I get
a Never-Ending Gobstopper
stuck in the back of
my throat? I'm fucked.
Ooh.
( straining to exhale )
( groans )
It's coming, it's coming,
it's coming, it's coming.
- It's com-- it's coming.
- It's not.
- It's snot.
- It's coming.
- It's not!
- It's snot.
Give me that.
I'll fucking do it myself.
God, you kids will
do some stupid things.
- You'll soon find it's rock hard.
- Oh, he's in.
- Three, two, one.
- Ow!
Yes, it's gone!
Oh, you got snot on me.
Am I sorry of sloth?
Am I? Fuck.
( hard rock beat playing )
Joycey:
The rich.
Now they're a bunch
of funny fuckers.
- Oh!
- Get him, get him, get him.
What do they do
to get off their asses?
( all screaming )
Pull!
( all laughing )
I've gone fuckin' deaf.
I can't fuckin' hear nothing.
This is rabbits.
This is what the toffs like to do
when the peasants
step onto their land.
Go for the bollocks.
( screaming )
My fuckin' nuts!
- Oh, fuck!
- It's a go.
Run, rabbit,
run, rabbit, run run run!
- Let's have it.
- Ow!
- Ah!
- Oh! Oh!
- Oh!
- Ah!
Um, what the fuck
am I doing?
Aha! Ah!
- Ah!
- Ow!
Oh, right in
my bunny boobs!
Ah! Fuck!
Oh! I want no--
fuck that!
Fuck!
- Right on the ankle-- fuckin' boom.
- ( all laughing )
- Joycey: Go on, take another hit.
- I can't fuckin' walk, Dan.
( man scatting in rap song )
# You know what I mean? #
# Know what I mean? #
This is a challenge
to see who's the laziest,
who's the most stupid,
who can take
the most amount of pain
without leaving
their La-Z-Boy.
Let's see how lazy Pritchard is.
- Do it.
- Oh I can't, it's not working.
- Joking.
- ( pellet gun firing )
( grunting )
Dainton: Hey!
- ( laughing )
- Ah. It's fuckin' so much agony, man.
- Fuckin'- -
- Oh, Christ!
- Right, you ready?
- Yeah.
Ah! Cha cha cha
cha cha cha!
Cha-da da da da! Oh!
- ( men laughing )
- "Da da da!"
( groans )
I lost the La-Z-Boy challenge
so it's cock action time.
( all laughing )
- Oh, look at him!
- He's got grey hairs.
He's got grey hairs
on his pubes.
Oh, am I really
gonna do this?
- How am I going to perform?
- Get on with it!
- Just get on with it!
- All: Oh!
Three, two, one!
Oh, God!
I pressed the trigger,
it didn't go!
- Three, two, one.
- ( fires )
Another.
Do another one!
I'm not gonna--
I won't, I won't, I won't!
Boys, you want
to see it?
Oh, no no!
- ( shot fires )
- ( screams )
You're dead!
You're dead,
you're dead!
I'm dead.
Pritchard versus Dainton.
He is dead.
( laughing )
Three, oh...
two, one.
( laughing )
Ah!
I didn't think
it would hurt my skull.
# You know what I mean? #
# You know
what I mean? #
Ah!
Taught you then.
- Watch it.
- Hey!
Don't mess around!
- Rah!
- ( screams )
You freak!
- You pig!
- Keep crying, keep crying.
- Holy fuck!
- It went in. It went in my finger.
Right on my nail!
Daint, you fuckin' penis!
- Dainton: Jesus Christ.
- Fuckin' penis licker!
Knew I shouldn't have
fuckin' trusted you.
Oh, I'm gonna faint.
Don't play fuckin'
darts with Dainton.
( echoing )
Right in the fuckin' nail.
Right in
the fuckin' nail.
Twat!
# All you lovely ladies #
# You're lookin'
fuckin' fine #
# You're looking fuckin' fine. #
Joycey:
You can't drink that.
So what about
a rogue finger?
Here we go--
big or small, fuck 'em all.
( men laughing )
( Joycey's voice echoing )
So what about a rogue finger?
This is just
a quick example
of whether I'm proper
slothed out or not.
- Stretch it a bit more.
- Dainton: Come on!
# Kick back
recline... #
# Make her move
your waistline... #
But there's no way
I will fuck with him now.
Pancho:
#You're lookin' fuckin fine... #
I'm gonna shoot
sloth to anger
in one easy move.
( Joycey laughing )
Shh, he's going green.
Shh.
( growls )
Right, if we're gonna try and turn
Pancho into "The Incredible Hulk,"
we need to cut
his clothes up.
We've been trying to
do this for five years.
There's something
I draw the line at.
Jim Hickey: What?
- There's no way--
- ( men laughing )
Stop it, that's
fuckin' male-- stop it.
- Fucking stop it.
- Jim: What are they doing?
- Joycey: That's fuckin' funny, man.
- Not funny.
- Shut up.
- Jim: What are they doing?
- Shh.
I'm not gonna--
I'm not-- shh!
I'm not-- shut up!
I'm not gonna tell you
what they're doing.
But you never thought
the Incredible Hulk--
I leave it
to your imagination.
Pritchard: Panch!
The sloth to anger,
in one easy move.
- ( squirting )
- Dainton: My God.
Pritch,
you got his eyes.
What?
You got
his fuckin' eyes.
Yeah, but it's
watered down.
You're fucked now.
You've fucked it.
Oh, fuck off.
You're staying here.
That's bullshit.
Fuck off.
Is there a prob--
is there a problem here?
Don't fuckin' have
a go at me, mate.
It's naught
to do with me.
It's nothing
Pancho:
Jim, it's fuckin' all to do with you.
- It's not to do with me.
- Joycey: It's not Jim, it's not Jim.
Pritchard:
Leave Jim alone.
He doesn't even know
he looks like the Hulk.
I'm green-- great.
( roaring )
( dramatic music playing )
( film projector clicking )
- Ah!
- Oh!
- Ahhh!
- There he is-- Paul Weller.
- Jim: What's a Paul Weller?
It just wells up.
( Pancho snoring )
Dainton: Of all the things
that go bump in the night...
that's Daint.
Daddy's here!
( laughs )
( snoring )
( cries )
( high-pitched )
Ow!
( all laughing )
There's one thing that
really fuckin' makes me angry,
and that's his
fuckin' snoring.
( gasps )
Dainton:
Time for a sleep, Panch.
Come on, boy.
Come to Daddy.
Come on!
( buzzing )
My motto in life is
"Sleep when you're dead."
So I decided to come
to a tattooist in Russia
and have "Sleep when you're dead"
tattooed on my leg in Russian.
There's a thousand ways
to make Pritchard angry.
But sometimes it's the
most simplest of things
that can make a man
go fuckin' insane.
It takes a lot to
make me angry basically.
Somebody will really have
to keep tap-tap pushing
to make-- make...
Can Pritchard
spin that coin
for plus 19 and
a half seconds dead?
One--
oh, shit.
My relationship
with Dainton--
I think that's
the only thing that properly
drives me fuckin'
angry-- Dainton.
Pritchard is coming
tomorrow morning to get a tattoo--
"Sleep when you're dead" --
done on his leg.
Those words are gonna get lost
in translation with my translator.
Don't get me wrong,
I love it.
It's brilliant. That's the whole
Pritchard-versus-Dainton thing.
Let's wake
this little piggy up.
If there's anyone that properly
does make me angry, it's Dainton.
Not even himself makes me angry,
it's just the way he does things.
Daint,
you are a ring nut.
It's always a competition
between me and him,
but he always gets
the upper hand.
I want "Sleep
when I'm dead,"
but you need to say,
when you translate it...
( tattoo needle buzzes )
He knows-- he knows
where my breaking point is...
and when he knows he's reached
that breaking point with me,
he will--
he knows
to back off then.
- Fucking prick!
- ( laughs )
- Fuck you.
- You fuckin' punched me in the face.
"Sleep when you're dead"
in Russian.
Right on.
It must really mean "Beef Stroganoff
and a lovely vodka,
thank you very much," but there we go.
- Spasibo.
- Ne za chto.
This is
gonna fuck him up.
Pritchard: Well, we're in
a paintball shooting place.
I'm going to attempt--
and when I say attempt--
attempt to try and beat
the world record
of the amount of paintball hits
to a human body.
Right, this is a test
to show you how powerful
these guns are
that he's gonna be shot with
to break the world record.
Hit the bin.
( echoes )
From my experience of
being hit by a paintball--
naked, before,
in previous years--
it's absolutely
fuckin' painful as fuck.
103 of those to break
the world record.
But there isn't even
a world record.
( shot echoes )
Right, "Thank you for your interest
in the paintball hits record
featured in the 2004 edition
of 'T he Guinness World Records.'
The record is currently
held by Anthony Kelly" --
that's the man
you got to beat--
- "of New South Wales..."
- All: Oh!
Maybe there'll be a new record
from the New South Wales.
"...in Australia,
who took 102 hits
from a distance
of five meters.
I have enclosed
a record-attempt registration
from which our terms
and conditions..." blah blah blah.
"I wish you best of luck
in your record attempt
and look forward
to hearing from you soon.
Yours truly,
Gerald Davey."
I can actually properly be
in "The Guinness Book of Records."
- All: Yeah.
- I never knew it was that official.
- Yeah.
- Fuckin' hell.
Oh my God. I've fuckin'
made me even more nervous.
You ready to roll,
Pritchard?
- Yes, Daint!
- Come on!
( Joycey shouting)
- ( screams )
- Pancho: 10 down.
- Joycey: 10.
- Dainton: 92 to go!
Joycey:
Come on, Math, you can do it!
Dainton:
Feel the pain.
Oh, Jesus fuckin'- -
fuck a duck.
- Go!
- ( paintball gun firing )
( shooting stops )
- How many?
- 10, 10.
20!
Dainton:...two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, 10.
Ah!
Oh, that fuckin' Anthony Kelly's
a fucking right thick cunt.
...three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, 10.
Oh!
51, 52...
- Panch, you fuckin' missed.
- A lot of those missed.
- Fuck!
- Have you been drinking?
- I haven't.
- You said you missed three,
- but now you've missed two.
- Two or three.
Well, make your mind up.
This is a world record attempt
we're breaking, motherfucker.
- You can't have more miss.
- I got hit with three.
I felt three--
I was counting them.
- Ready? Three, two, one.
- Yeah.
- Ah!
- Shoot!
- Oh!
- Come on!
You look like fuckin'
King Kong spunked on you.
Ah!
Ay-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya!
Fuckin' 90!
- Ah!
- One, two, three, four, five, six,
- seven, eight, nine, 10!
- Ah!
I only need another three,
I've fuckin' done it.
Four.
The record's 102.
I only need 103.
Only three more and
I've fuckin' beaten it.
I'm in that fuckin'
great book, baby!
- Whoo! Yeah!
- ( all cheering )
For being
a right stupid twat!
Come on, Pritch!
Here we go, to victory!
Three, two, one!
( all cheer )
Fucking done it!
Yeah!
World record holder--
103 paintballs to the body.
Kelly, kiss my ass,
you did 102.
Jim:
Maybe it's gone too far?
Well, Jim, it's gone too far.
He looks like he's been hit--
he looks like he's been hit
by a fuckin' truck.
He's ecstatic. He said,
"I can't wait to phone my mom."
To tell you the truth...
when I realized
I'd broken the record,
I mean obviously I knew
in my head, I've broken a record,
I was really excited--
I was jumping around telling...
Crew, I've done it!
( mumbles )
Shit.
I mean, as a kid,
you always read
"The Guinness Book
of Records"
when you have it for Christmas
or something like that.
You immediately think,
"Oh, I'd love to be in this book."
But, now I'm finally
gonna make it in the book.
You all right, Math?
Pritchard: Boys, you wanna see
the state of my fuckin' body?
- Let's have a look.
- Pritchard: It's fucked.
- Give us a ganders.
- Fuckin' ready?
- Let's have a look.
- Oh my God!
Oh my fuckin' shit-flaps.
Oh my-- oh my God,
look at that.
Look at how savage it is.
They're all raised up.
Joycey:
Oh, it's fucking hell, man.
Look at that fucker!
Oh my God!
Fuck me!
Look at that.
That's fucked.
I can't even look at it.
That's the good thing
about skin, boys. It fuckin' heals.
I've always said, whoever invented it
was a fuckin' genius.
( Joycey laughs )
I've never seen
anything like that.
I've never seen so much
fuckin' carnage on one body
after paintballs.
And when he finds out that-- when
he finds out there's no world record--
I made it up on
the computer last night--
I'm seriously, seriously in some
seriously deep shit.
Pancho: Yeah, you know,
Pritchard's fuckin' shaved my hair off
fucking God knows
what so many times.
He deserves
to be tucked up.
That'll teach the fucker
to fuckin' snore.
( snoring )
( buzzing )
( snoring stops )
Breathe.
( snoring )
Both:
#Ay ay ay. #
Now we have
the peacemaker,
Mikhail Gorbachev.
( muttering )
Right, that is it.
Right-- fuck.
- Pancho.
- What?
- What's wrong with you?
- What do you mean,
"What's wrong with you?"
Look at his long johns
You-- you knew
it was gonna--
Don't punch me.
Oh, just punch me.
Go on, punch me.
- Right.
- Punch me. Go on, punch me.
Oh!
Whoa.
He's gonna have a shit on him.
He's having a shit on him!
You're fucking dead.
This is Russia,
this was anger.
He semi-knocked
me out then.
Fuck this place, right?
This place is so full of anger,
I need some love.
Let me...
Come in here, Dainton!
Oh ho!
I love-- whoa!
Get off me!
Take me to Thailand
for the ladyboys.
Girl:
Dirty boys!
Come inside.
( pop music playing )
( film projector clicking )
( buzzing )
Woman:
Dirty boys!
# Oooh! #
# Dirty boys! #
"I love Dainton."
He's gonna
go fuckin' nuts.
Right, we're in Bangkok.
Bit of a ghetto area.
Per pound, you can get
liposuction done here.
- The ping-pong lady...
- Oh!
( faux-ltalian accent )
...said me too chubby.
Me need
to lose weight.
Too chubby, too chubby.
If they can make those
ladyboys look fuckin' good...
then there might be hope
for me yet. You never know.
- Hello.
- I am Pancho.
- I'm Dr. Somsak.
Mm-hmm.
Would you say
I have a beer belly?
Yes, in compare to your height.
Yeah, I'm a bit overweight, yeah.
Uh-huh, yeah.
But it makes me
stronger to party.
This is the real deal, isn't it?
I don't think
he realizes how--
I don't think he realizes
what he's let himself in for.
How does it feel,
taking fat out?
- Oh, some pain.
- ( yelling )
Some pain?
- Some pain.
- ( both sucking )
This is the fat that come out
in the bottle after liposuction.
Ooh.
This is blood,
and this is fat.
This is like putting
pantyliners on your face.
( lisps )
New, with wings.
I've got to be honest--
I am proper shittin' it.
Time for your medication,
Mr. Locke.
Done some stupid,
silly stuff in my time,
but this takes
the biscuit.
Oh my God, I'm not gonna
be able to see what's happening.
( exhales )
The operation's
about to begin.
- See the size of that needle.
- Pancho: Oh shut up, man.
- Pancho: I can't feel anything yet.
- Oh shit.
Has he cut me open?
Pritchard: No.
Oh my God.
Fuckin' hell.
Look at the size
of that rod.
Ow! Jesus, man.
( yelling )
He gone right down
by my hipbone.
( yelling )
No more!
Ah. Fuckin' hell, man.
Ow!
Oh fuck!
I'm fuckin'- -
Squeeze my hand, man.
Panch, I can see the head.
I can see the head, keep pushing.
- Boys, I can't go through much more.
- Squeeze my hand, man.
I can't --
it fuckin' feels so bad.
He hasn't even
started yet.
- ( yelling )
- Panch, squeeze my hand,
squeeze my hand.
Ah! Fuckin' A.
Fingers are diggin' in.
It's all right, man.
It's all right, this is it.
That's it.
You're done.
( Dr. Somsak speaking )
Oh, they've just started.
"Not done, just start."
- Joycey: Keep your hands up.
- Oh no no.
They're about to start sucking
the fat out of Pancho's hips.
- Ah!
- Savage, man.
Oh whoa whoa whoa! Ow!
Pancho said "Ow."
( Dr. Somsak speaking )
No.
- Eww!
- Gosh!
Ow ow ow ow ow!
I told you "Ow" means "More,"
you fuckin' plonker.
Ah! Fuckin' hell, man!
Shut up! Get out,
you fucking bell-end!
Daint, I'm not finding
any amusement in this now, right?
I'm really starting
to spook out.
( screaming )
( Dr. Somsak speaks )
Ah. Yeah!
Done, Panch,
you're done.
That is your fat.
I will give you,
so you can take the fat home.
Oh my God, look how
much is there.
Oh! Oh my God.
- You're gonna love this.
- Oh!
Right, now we've got it.
I think we've got to think
of some way to get rid of it.
We're in Bangkok,
Thailand,
and it's time to play
"Guess the Ladyboy,"
but the thing is
I know myself
that all these girls
here are ladyboys.
A man or lady?
Um, guy.
- Pritchard: Nice ass on there.
- ( techno music playing )
Oh, fuck off,
that's a dude.
- That is definitely a bloke.
- No, that's definitely not.
He's a man, look. He's got
a fuckin' Desperate Dan chin.
- Joycey: Oh, look at that, yeah.
- Pritchard: That's a woman.
That's a fuckin' man.
- Look at her hands.
- Look at his hands.
- That's a man.
- Oh yeah!
That's a dude.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- Cheers, Roger.
( music stops )
- Jim: We've got to do it!
- Jim!
Jim! Are you
fuckin' listening?!
I am not
kissing a man!
Fuckin' end of story!
If it was a fuckin' woman
and I thought it was
a fucking woman and it was a man,
my tough shit.
I am not kissing a fucking man.
- Joycey: Is one a girl?
- Dainton: There's not.
Joycey: Tell him which one
it is then. Tell him then.
- Tell him which one it is.
- ( Jim speaking )
Dainton:
Jim, Jim, Jim...
Is it a woman?
All right, then, brilliant.
That's okay then.
Dainton:
She has to be a woman.
There's no way someone
like that can look like a man.
Which one do you
think is a woman?
The one with the stars
and stripes on.
- That's a woman?
- Yeah.
All right then.
- Oh, this is the one I choose.
- ( techno music playing )
I hope it's
a fucking woman.
# Kissing... #
Joycey: What do you reckon?
What do you reckon, Math?
- Kiss it, Math.
- All: Oh!
- Go on then, Dave.
- She's supposed to be a woman.
It ain't, is it?
Dainton: That's a man.
This is clearly a man.
I can't even look.
Oh!
Pancho: Go for the kiss.
Go for the kiss.
- All: Oh!
- He just tongued it.
That's it, finished.
Nice one, mate. Cheers.
No no!
I'm gonna be sick.
( coughing )
I can't --
( vomiting )
Please be a man. What am I saying?
Please be a woman.
- "Be a man"?
- She does look pretty good though.
It is a woman,
isn't it?
It is a woman, isn't it?
Pritchard: Oh, Dainton,
she's got wicked fuckin' knockers.
Oh! And the tongue
went in!
I've got a bit
of a boner coming.
- And he's got--
- ...in the valleys, Daint.
- They don't take too lightly--
- Whoa whoa! Just in case!
Hello.
Are you a man or are you
a woman? Let's have a look.
- Oh-- oh yeah, there's a cock.
- It's a man! Oh my God!
Oh Jesus! Fuck!
All right, mate.
Yep, let's see what you got.
What have you got?
Oh my God!
Reveal.
- Oh, it's a cock.
- It's a cock.
- Oh Jesus.
- Put it away, put it away!
I know she might be an ugly girl,
but it's not a pretty boy.
- Let's have a look at the crown jewels.
- There's a cock in there.
I think there's a cock. No no--
what have we got, what have we got?
- Cock!
- There's a cock!
Oh! Fuck!
Get off me!
He got himself one of them!
He even got a fuckin'
semi-hard-on and everything
and he fucking
used his tongue,
when everyone else just
kissed him on the lips.
I've got fuckin'- -
I've got a misses and kids at home.
What the fuck are they gonna do
when they see that?
The missus probably
won't kiss me-- oh fuck.
I actually went backstage
when you were outside,
and I knew that every
single one was a man.
- You're fuckin' dead!
- ( yells )
- You fuckin' cunt!
- Fuckin'- -!
You set me up with
a fuckin' woman-- man, you dick!
You got a boner
off a man. Payback.
Oh, fuck off.
"What have you been doing
in Thailand, Dainton?"
"Oh, just been hanging out
with some ladyboys, you know,
having lap dances.
Even got aroused."
( siren wails )
Okay, boys, this is called
a game of Bangkok Roulette.
Ning is gonna come in,
go under there,
do her business.
We've got to try and guess
who she's doing
the business on.
But if you get it wrong,
then you'll have to have
a bug and down a whiskey.
- And those bugs are fuckin' rank.
- Oh shit.
Oh, look at that one.
He's got a face.
Oh!
Right then, boys,
- this is my sexy assistant, Ning.
- Hello.
She's the one who's going
to be pleasuring us tonight.
Dainton: God, they don't
hang around, do they?
Right then, boys,
down with the pants.
Are you ready
to play Bangkok Roulette?
I'm fucking
smiling already.
All right then, after three.
Three, two, one.
( jingling )
Fuckin' hell, there's some good
poker faces here, boys.
Right, that's the 30 seconds up.
Now we've got to guess.
We'll start with Dainton.
Who do you think
was getting played with?
Boys, I can't tell you
because I am being played with.
I thought--
I thought it was you.
It's me!
Can you tell her to stop?
I might get a boner.
"Say hello to
my little friend."
Get it over
and done with. Come on.
Come on, Pritch.
It's not a spider.
I just-- sorry, boys,
that freaked me out then.
- Why?
- A bit of his leg was in my mouth.
Come on, stop stalling.
- These boys are gonna get--
- Go on, chew it.
I can't do it!
I don't like bugs!
I don't like fuckin'- -
I don't like ladyboys,
but you fuckin' tricked me.
He's fuckin'
freaking me out.
Payback, Pritch.
Payback.
- Don't be sick on Ning.
- Get the leg.
Own up, who was it?
There we go. Look.
- Come on!
- It's going in.
Oh, don't be sick now.
( vomiting )
Oh, Jesus!
- Oh!
- Ew!
- Don't want to spill.
- All: Oh!
- You.
- It was me and I got a raging boner.
- Oh no no no no!
- ( gags )
Quick quick quick.
Come on, Pancho!
( laughing )
Go on, get it down.
You what?
Boys, the bugs
ain't even that bad.
I could stay here drinking whiskey
and eating bugs all night.
It's like pork scratchings,
that's all it is.
Well, let's fuckin'
up the ante, then.
- Up the ante?
- Yeah, let's do it with something else.
( screaming )
I've got some
good stuff here, lads.
- ( all groaning )
- It's my man-fat.
Jesus--!
Probably about 90% proof.
I've set up a little game show.
You remember "Family Fortune"?
This is called
"Unfortunate Wank."
We'll do the same thing--
whoever gets wanked off
has to fuckin'
down the fat.
What, whichever one
she picks?
Yeah. So she's picking
who eats the fat.
No way.
Joycey: Whoever gets the wank
has to down the man-fat.
Without further ado,
Ming, do your thing!
Oh my God.
( all scream )
Sucker!
That looks fucking rank.
Look at it.
It's all like bits
of fuckin'- -
That's not--
that's not food, man.
That's proper fuckin'
Panch fat.
Look, the doctor
showed me, right...
This is blood,
and this is fat.
It's fucked up.
You-- you're in there.
- Dainton: Let's get on with it.
- This is fucking cannibalism,
for fuck's sake.
You get sent down for this shit.
Well, separate--
separate the blood from the fat.
Pour it in,
pour it in, pour it in.
This--
oh! Oh man!
Pritchard:
Oh, that is fucking wrong, man.
Pancho:
See, there's blood there.
( gagging )
Look-- don't -- there's a bucket there.
There's a bucket there.
Oh my God,
there's a stringy bit!
Look at it,
just dangling!
Pancho:
Oh man!
Oh!
Dainton: No shit.
This is without a doubt
the sickest, fucked-up stunt
we've ever-- we've ever done.
If you're in the cinema now
watching this,
pull your sick bag out,
because this is gonna be fucking needed.
Steak-- lovely,
very very rare steak.
It's a very rare steak.
All: Oh!
Oh! Fuck!
Oh my God.
Oh God!
All right, I'm gonna
fucking do this again
and I'm gonna
keep it down this time.
I don't want to be
a part of this anymore.
- This has gone too far.
- It's just smooth water.
It's just smooth water.
Relax, calm
calm calm.
Relax, swallow.
Dainton:
Gulp, gulp it.
Gulp.
Go on--
it's tomato juice.
- Yeah!
- I've just eaten a fuckin' man,
for fuck's sake!
- ( groans )
- If you haven't gone
for your doggy bag yet...
you're as equally fucked
as these bastards.
Welcome to "Dirty Sanchez."
I've just eaten a man.
Here we are!
Phi Phi!
We've just done lust,
now it's time for envy.
Ooh, don't.
That was nice.
All right, boys, you just
arrived in Phi Phi.
Nice, isn't it?
- Lovely, Dainton.
- It is.
There's a price to pay
for everything, though, isn't there?
Exactly, because
this is the deal, yeah?
- We're gonna have a little crab race.
- I don't like crabs!
Two crabs that are winners,
those guys get to stay in
the beautiful accommodation...
( speaks Thai )
Welcome to Zeavola.
This is
a five-stars property.
For those who stay here,
they can relax, enjoy and being lazy.
...and the guys with
the slowest crabs,
gotta go in-- the accommodation
is a rat-infested shithole
on the other side
of the island.
Luckily, Daint, I think
I picked up crabs in fucking Bangkok,
- and these are fast fuckers.
- Go on, Number Two.
- Come on, Number Four.
- Give me. Give me rock.
Come on, crab.
Come on!
Yes!
Mine's out first!
- Come on. Come on, boy.
- ( cheering )
I bloody spurred yours.
I made yours win!
I was given a fucking crab
that wasn't even alive,
that was never going anywhere. I was
always sleeping in the tin fucking-hut.
I'm gonna make you sick with envy
when you see my place. Come on.
Do you want to come
and have a look at my little pad?
I'd rather wank
my old man off, Panch.
Welcome to Zeavola.
Oh, boys, I do see
our swimming pool.
- Joycey: Oh, fuck off!
- Pritchard: Oh my God!
( laughs )
Well, it looks like
fucking shantytown to me already.
- ( groans )
- Oh, look at that.
Shoes off, Joyce.
Just look at this place.
Fit for a king.
Fit for a king!
( all laugh )
- Oh my God.
- Oh, dude.
Look at what I'll see
in the morning when I wake up.
Joycey:
This takes the piss.
There's cockroaches
on the bed!
- Where? Let's have a look.
- I can't sleep in here.
I told you. At least there's
a bit of porn on the wall.
Ooh, look. We've got
lights in here.
I thought they
were fairy lights.
They're just holes
in the ceiling. ( laughs )
I tell you what-- I think there's
a few fucking rats in the ground here.
- Oh what?
- You said rat-infested.
There's a fucking
red ants' nest up in the tree
- in that pair of old stinking pants.
- Joycey: There is as well.
I ain't fucking staying here.
I can tell you that now.
You've got to.
It's "Sanchez Rule."
"Sanchez Rule" has
always been the same:
You lose, you fucking
stick the consequence.
But Daint, there's
fucking bugs everywhere.
- I'm fucking not--
- Whoa, man!
- Fuck, look at the size--
- See what I mean?
We can't fucking sleep here.
He's carrying half a tree.
You've got to stay here.
You lost fair and square,
we won fair and square.
Yeah, but you're in
a seven-star fucking hotel.
Welcome to Zeavola.
If I'm staying in here,
I'm gonna make sure
you go back to that hotel
fucking pissed off.
Like how?
I'm going back to the hotel--
- Do you want to fucking see?
- I'm going back to the hotel
with the biggest grin on my face knowing
that you're stuck in this proper--
this is worse
than I described.
Yeah, but when you
go back to the hotel...
you're going to be
proper pissed off when you see this.
"I love Dainton."
- Dainton, are you not envious of that?
- You're fucking sick!
- Aren't you envious of that?
- "I heart Dainton."
Are you sure you don't want
to share your seven-star room
- with me now, love?
- Who's envious now, eh?
- Is that fucking real?
- Yeah.
Try and rub it off,
Dainton.
( needle buzzes )
Pritch, you can't have fucking
"I love Dainton" on your cock!
You don't fucking
love me, you hate me.
By the end of this I'm going
to make sure you really hate me.
You're going to want
to chop your own cock off.
I tell you-- I'm going
to fucking knock you out.
"I love Dainton"
What in God's name have I dont to you?
Oh, fucking hell!
It's never-fucking-ending!
( paintball gun firing )
There's no record
for the most paintballs to the body.
- Oh fucking God!
- ( guys laughing )
That fucking Anthony Kelly,
he's a right thick cunt.
- ( guys laughing )
- You fucking wanker!
Yes!
- Yes!
- The whole letter, it was fake.
103 fucking bullets to my fucking body
and there's no such thing?
I'm in that
fucking great book, baby!
Whoo! Yeah!
I've got 103 bullet holes
in my fucking body
for fucking
no reason at all!
( shrieks, laughs )
I'm sorry,
this is fucking amazing!
This is the funniest thing
I've ever seen.
103 fucking bullet holes--
what else are you gonna do to me?
- Knock you out!
- You're gonna catch malaria
- staying in this shithole tonight.
- I'll tell you what--
that's fucking it now.
You've pissed me off so fucking much,
- let's have a fight.
- You wanna fight?
Yeah, I'll fight you,
Thai boxing,
in the boxing ring.
Fucking yeah. Tomorrow.
Right. No shit.
I'll take you up on that.
This might be the last time
we fucking shake hands.
Don't take it to heart
if I knock you out
and I won't take it to heart
if you knock me out,
but I'm gonna come out
tomorrow night fucking swinging.
You had better be, because I'll be
swinging like a fucking windmill.
( siren blaring )
Pritchard:
I am fucking starving.
- I haven't eaten all fucking day.
- I'll eat anything.
They put us--
Pancho and Dainton
are sitting there,
champagne fucking dinner...
- Champagne, Panch?
- It's like cracking open an egg.
Crack on.
Joycey:
This place is a fucking shithole.
Take me
the fuck out of here!
Phi Phi, fuck me,
this place is
a fucking wankville!
Here's to happy days...
in Phi Phi.
- At least you shit--
- Ah! Look at that fucking spider!
- Stay there, stay there, stay there!
- No no no no, don't! Don't!
- Joycey: Stay there!
- There's a fucking--
Uh, grilled lobster.
Caught today, please.
- Joycey: Oh my God.
- ( groans )
Can I have my food sprinkled
with the magic of Thailand, please?
What's that,
chili sauce?
( Joycey mumbles )
Ah. Ah.
You fucking--
Ah! Crap!
( retches )
- Bonjour, monsieur. Enjoy the view.
- Tres bien.
- Spider. ( laughs )
- Ah!
Where?! Fuck off.
Where the-- hurry up, turn the light on!
Turn the light on!
- ( Pritchard yelps )
- Joycey: Fuck off!
- Watch! Watch!
- Pritchard: Fucking what's that?
Joycey:
Say it! Say it!
Oi, fucking get your arse--
oi, Pritch, it's fight day.
Come on, man.
You're the winner.
- ( thuds )
- He just whacked his head on that.
( laughs )
Shit. That's a good start
to a fucking training day.
497, 498,
499, 500!
You're fucking dead,
Pritchard!
Aww, look at
the little chicks.
( chicken clucks )
10 more!
Come on!
( grunts )
- Go on! Use him as a body bag!
- Ah!
I'm gonna get him.
- Say "I'm a tiger."
- I'm knackered.
This fucking fight
ain't gonna last two minutes.
( crowd yelling )
This is the deal. Pritchard versus
Dainton, battle of the dickheads.
- Do you wanna see my killer moves?
- Joycey: Yeah.
This time he's taken it
one step too far.
Whoo! Whoo! Bam!
I am going to fucking
unleash the beast.
Might get my cock out.
He'll be like "Oh, what you doing?"
- Boff.
- I'm not gonna fucking play with him.
I'm not gonna
be nice to him.
- ( bottle clatters )
- Oh! Oh.
It was a spider
or a rat.
There's no kissing,
there's no hugging
and there's no fucking
tickling tonight.
Oh, tickle-tickle.
The Finisher.
Dainton's gonna
kick his ass!
Ladies and gentlemen!
- Pritchard! Dainton!
- ( cheering )
( Crowd chanting )
Go go go go go go...
( crowd whistling )
Fucking get over there!
One more!
- ( bell dings )
- Whoo!
Yeah, man!
That's so hard, man.
It's not as easy as it looks.
I hit him with the first,
the first of the match.
He went down.
I thought he weren't gonna get back up.
But he ain't got the prize.
He stayed down--
fucked, gone, game over.
I'll regain my pride
through stupidity, I think.
Well, Pritchard,
we're off to Japan next,
a country that is
fucking driven by pride.
( all yell )
Let's get fucking bollixed!
Let's get
fucking bollixed!
( rock music playing )
Huh! Tokyo.
- You movie star!
- ( speaks Japanese )
This challenge is called
the Spunky Dunky Challenge.
We're all gonna go
to the toilets with a camera--
just to make sure
that no one's cheating--
and we're gonna spunk
in a dunky,
and the one with
the least amount of spunk...
has gotta wear
the spunky dunky.
( jazz music playing )
Fuck, here I am.
Made it to the toilet.
Now I've gotta have
a fucking wank.
I had a room
on my own last night
for the first time
in fucking three weeks,
and l-- and a fucking
powerful bidet jet that goes up my ass.
I took full advantage of it
and I had five wanks.
So I'm sure there's nothing even left.
You ain't seeing
my fucking come-face either.
Is he gonna come out
with a load in the condom?
with a poor show?
If he comes out with a load--
I don't wanna say this, but we're
gonna have to check the footage.
How much you got?
- Any good?
( Joycey laughs )
( jazz music plays )
Oh, there's some romantic music
in there while he's doing it.
Where's Dainton's glass?
Which one's
Dainton's glass?
Oh, this is wrong, man.
This is Dainton having a wank.
- Why is he saying "Pritch"?
- Shut up.
Fuck! Can't even get
a fucking hard-on!
Did you keep thinking
about us at any point?
I thought about Dainton
quite a bit, yeah.
Pritchard:
Oh, that's less than me!
Yes! I'm not getting it!
There he is boys.
Oh, fucking hell!
Damn, how can he do that?
The music was one of the big factors
in me having a hard time wanking.
This music is
really putting me off.
Panch has been
so long in the toilet with the camera
having a wank that Dan
has to go down with my camera.
Gays take these
into bog toilets,
right, so that when--
when he meets
another cottager,
he puts his feet into it
whilst the other one blows him off,
so when the attendant
looks under
he sees a bag
and one set of feet.
Daint--
Daint taught me that.
You've been dipping
your condom in there, haven't you?
You dipped it
in there, didn't you?
Because you knew
I'd go for that instead.
Yeah, I have been.
- Fucking twat!
- Don't --
There she is.
- Did you fucking do that?
- You should've drunk out of your glass.
- Did you do that?
- I put some cum in there.
Boys, that was
hard fucking work.
- You're sweating!
- He's sweating!
That was so fuck--
so much hard work.
Panch, if I was you,
I'd drink out of that,
because he put
a fucking jimmy in my pint.
That was-- that was a proper
under-pressure wank.
Look.
- Well, you drink out of that then.
- Pour some in there.
L-- I've just
fucking drunk two pints.
I don't trust
any fucker on this team.
I ain't drinking
out of it.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Jesus Christ.
- Yeah, it's your cock, it don't matter.
- No, l--
It ain't my fucking cock.
Just fucking drink it.
I've fucked
with people's glasses.
We've just had this argument.
There's fuck all wrong with it.
- ( gags )
- ( laughs )
You've tampered
with that.
I haven't tampered with it.
I'm just good
at fucking pulling my plonker.
That's a fucking
endurance test.
How fucking hard is that?
We've all been to the toilet,
we've done the fucking deed.
As embarrassing as it was,
it's fucking crunch time.
All:
Two, one.
- Joycey!
- Yeah!
Oh, yes!
- It's going all in his hair.
- ( yells )
Jim:
Oh, that looks good.
That's it, slow. Slower.
Blow it up!
Blow it up,
Dan, blow it up.
- Blow it till it pops!
- ( pops )
I may be the winner,
but I'm the--
I'm the loser,
aren't I?
( rock music playing )
We're in Japan.
We're about to meet
the Tokyo Shock Boys.
( yells )
Their stunts
and our stunts.
( all yelling )
- Welcome to Japan.
- Bummer, man.
( speaks Japanese )
- Hello.
We're in Japan,
it's your country.
Let's fucking see how
the Tokyo Shock Boys rock.
Okay, okay.
Here we go.
- This is beer.
- Okay.
Come on, come on,
come on. Okay.
Oh my God!
How the fuck do you do that!
Cheers.
Cigarette.
Well, I honestly haven't a fucking clue
what he's doing this time.
( yells )
Fucking hell!
I can give you...
good thing.
Oh, it better not
be your cock.
Next, you!
It's time to shock
the Shock Boys!
We've invented a new game.
This is called "Bum Drum."
- New game.
- Yeah, what we do is he sticks
one up his bum, I stick one
up mine and we drum sticks,
and the first one
to fall out gets a Dirty Sanchez.
Every man knows--
on a blind date,
you always use
the best lube there is-- a bit of spit.
Go!
It's a good fight!
Shit!
It's all right.
It's not that bad.
Don't know what
you're whingeing about.
Stop!
Smell bad!
The Japanese like their tea,
so I'm gonna brew them some up.
( speaks Japanese )
( guys yelling )
- Give it a swing now.
- Swing it.
I think
the kettle's boiled!
Daint! Dainton!
Dainton!
Fuck off, Dainton!
Right, now they're in
for a finale.
This stuff is
about to go down the pan.
Let the beer enema begin!
- Right, you ready?
- Ready.
Stop it! No more!
Don't do it.
- Stop it!
- Go on, Dan.
Right, boys.
Have you got
any more squirt in there?
No no no no! Ah!
You must come back
to Britain with us
and we'll do a show together
and party together.
No way!
Ta-ta, Daint.
- These Japanese wrestlers--
- They're hard as fuck.
- We're gonna take them out?
- What do Japanese wrestlers do?
Extreme
Japanese wrestlers.
Fight with glass
and barbed wire.
I know there's
one stunt they do
where they shove glass
into their fucking forehead like that.
No! No!
And I can tell you
which ones have had it done.
He's had it done,
he's had it done
- and he's had it done.
- We're out here laughing--
like laughing and shit--
and when we walk through the door,
they're gonna be
in there just going...
He looks quite mild, that one.
He looks fucking harmless.
( growls )
Check out
Mens there, though.
That's pain and pleasure.
That's his jizz face.
I was smiling like that last night
when I sat on the toilet
with this hot jet
of water spraying my cornhole.
Panch, I think
you're the closest one
resembling one
of those wrestlers.
- I think they're gonna--
- I probably look like numerous ones
seeing as I look like fucking everyone
under the sun anyway.
You've looked like--
you've looked like--
you've looked like
the Incredible Hulk,
fucking Gorbachev...
"I want the U.S.S.R.
To continue the way it is."
...and now you look
like every one of these on there.
All the baldies.
- Fucking Jesus Christ!
- That's fucking barbed wire.
- Hello.
- Oh my God.
I think we've got into
a bit of shit here, boys.
We've got our own costumes,
our own little funny costumes.
Yeah, we have.
Put our--
put our outfits on.
Watch it,
I'll knock you out, mate!
I got my--
I got my own--
whoa! Whoa!
Don't push--
don't push me in!
( laughing )
We was laughing earlier.
That's definitely
a nervous grin now.
He's pointing at me.
Ah! Ah!
Fucking hell!
Whoa whoa whoa!
Right, your fucking turn!
No no no.
No more.
- Oh! Look at that!
- That kick in the back is fucked.
Go on!
Get off me!
- Hey, you.
- Get in, get in, get in.
Oh, he's fucked.
He's pinned his dick!
- That looked fucking savage, that.
- Oh, it was horrible, man.
And they played
with your cock and all.
- They stretched it a bit, though.
- I know. I know.
There was
no thrill in that.
- Look at his tail.
- It's all in the tail, isn't it?
( choking )
- Pigsy!
- Pigsy! Me monkey!
Dainton: Look at them all!
Look at them all!
Right, let's go
get drunk, boys!
What are we doing inviting these boys
out on the piss with us in Japan?
- I don't know. Let's go.
- We're professional drinkers, though.
- Yeah.
- Time for some saki.
- Saki!
- Ah!
Son of a bitch.
The Japanese extreme wrestlers
have stripped us of our pride...
so we're gonna play
a good old, er--
a game that
we do back in Wales...
and we're gonna
flip the box.
Whichever end this lands on...
equals a forfeit.
- Good man.
- I reckon he's gonna get green.
- ( vocalizes tune )
- Ooh.
He's just picked the mallet
with the pins on it,
and he's chosen
to go for the shoulder.
And to tell you the truth,
I don't wanna fucking hit him,
because he's
bigger than me.
- Check out-- check out the scars.
- And look at the scars.
Check out the scars
on this guy.
We thought we had
a lot of fucking scars.
And do you think
that's gonna do fuck all to him?
Three, two--
oh, I don't wanna do it!
- Come on.
- That hurt my pride.
- You want more?
- I don't -- I don't like.
Eeny meeny miney moe...
( whispers )
Please have the nasty one.
It's only the fucking staple
to the tongue, isn't it?
Stay stay, Pancho.
Stay stay.
It's in!
This is
my first time in Japan.
I don't even
like mustard,
so let's taste wasabi.
Because if
I don't like this
and this is going
up Pritchard's nose, God forbid.
Let's have a taste.
Ooh, that's a selfish line.
I'm Welsh, Daniel,
I don't fuck around.
Oh Jesus.
Not only is it just wasabi,
it's mixed with saki.
Three, two, one,
in "Sanchez" style, goodbye!
( snorts )
( hacks )
( cheering )
( all chanting )
Wasabi, wasabi, wasabi...
All:
Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
( random people
speaking Japanese )
( knocks )
Found it, boyo.
It's the one with the fucking ring
round it and the blade.
How you feeling?
The best way to--
to slice one's finger off--
one, two, three,
four, five.
Fucking hell, Panch!
Just like
the Yakuza do, baby!
Put that fucking hand
down now.
We're here.
Are you ready?
I'm fucking shitting myself.
Panch, how many fucking drinks
have you had tonight?
Look, I'll even do the piss test.
I'm gonna fucking get my pride back
by chopping my finger off.
Pritch, you're not gonna chop it off,
though-- Pancho is.
- Pancho ain't fucking doing it.
- He fucking is.
- Fuck off, he's a fucking pisshead.
- Pritch, Pritch.
( Joycey laughing )
Whoa whoa whoa whoa!
- Whoa whoa!
- Felt like Dogtanian for a minute.
This is the tip of his finger, and this
is how far in we wanna go.
Right, here we go.
Pancho set the gauntlet.
Daint, he can't even fucking shoot
a gun fucking straight.
- I'll put my finger there, Jim.
- And I'm gonna go...
- Oh!
- If I manage to have
my finger chopped off
by Pancho...
you have to stand in the middle
of a Japanese street singing karaoke
- with a song of my choice.
- Well, that's a deal, Pritch.
You're too pissed,
you're too fucking clumsy.
- You ain't fucking doing my finger.
- I'm fine.
- Look, Panch, you're not doing it.
- Joycey: How you gonna do it?
I chose myself
the cigar cutter.
- That's a very classy way of doing it.
- I'm a posh man, Daniel.
Well, to tell you the truth,
I'm fucking...
shitting myself.
- Panch.
- I don't even wanna look.
I didn't want to be affiliated
with this anyway.
- Well, he's bats. Use your reason.
- Yeah.
Are you sure, Pritch,
are you sure?
- Time to moan.
- Definite?
- I can't even look.
- Right. Are you ready?
- Go.
- Three, two, one.
( "Do You Really Want
to Hurt Me?" playing )
# Do you really want
to hurt me? #
Fuck a duck!
Motherfucker!
- Fucking hell, man.
- Yeah, it's fucking right off, boys.
Boys, I've fucking
regained my pride!
# In my heart
the fire's burning... #
- Gaylord.
- Look at his cock!
# Choose my color,
find a star... #
Boys, I can see
the fucking bone.
- I can see the fucking bone.
- Fuck off!
- Oh, fuck. Fuck a duck!
Yeah, motherfucker!
I've regained my pride!
Who's fucking
pussy boy now?!
I may have lost the fight,
but I've regained my pride.
- Look, it's still in the end there!
- Oh, fucking hell.
- Math, can I eat it?!
- No no, don't fuck around!
- Eat it. Eat it.
- Can I eat it?
- No, don't fucking eat it!
- I wanted to--
No, you can't
fucking eat it!
- Eat it.
- No!
- Eat it!
- No, don't, don't!
Dan, don't fucking eat it!
- Go on, Dan!
- Don't eat it!
It tastes
fucking weird, man!
- Oh, you spat it out!
- Yeah, I couldn't do it, man.
It's all fleshy!
That's right, I'm pink.
And pink might mean pussy.
But this pink guy is
now a fucking superhero.
And this superhero is
called Pinky Dinky Dainty,
and he's gonna
fuck Pritchard's world.
Bring on Mexico, Pritch.
( mariachi music playing )
Today is the day
where we meet Myke Hawke.
He's gonna take us
into the desert,
and we're gonna spend two days
in this fucking soaring heat...
er, just living off the desert,
basically. And Myke Hawke...
is gonna teach us
how to fucking do it.
Like a bike.
Kick him, kick him over like a bike.
You don't kick
a bike over like that!
Where's the fucking Hawke?
- No, don't do that, man.
- Leave it there.
It's cursed.
It's like
you don't fucking go
and fuck with
Tutankhamen's tomb, do you?
Well, you just fisted
a fucking dead cow.
I'm fisting a cow!
Oh, that's a bit of love.
Oh my God.
What the fuck is that?!
- Who the fuck is this?
- Is this Myke Hawke?
- All right, Myke?
- You miserable,
gluttonous... maggots.
( chuckles )
You've been
feeding your faces...
- ( mariachi music plays )
- ( Joycey laughing )
You've been stuffing chow
down your pieholes...
throwing booze
down your throat.
And now you're gonna pay
for your sins.
- Oh, fuck.
- For your gluttony...
this is the reckoning.
And we're getting ready to get
downright primitive on your ass.
My name is Hawke...
and we're getting ready to have
what I call a come-to-Jesus party.
Look at that
fucking cock!
- What is that?
- You've got a big wart on yours.
- Daint.
- It's a dick, what do you think it is?
- You've been getting a bit of wind?
- No, there's no wind.
- That's how my dick is.
- That's a semi.
Joycey: So, Hawke,
are you scared of anything?
Hawke:
To be quite honest-- no.
I mean, the way
I look at it is...
everything that's alive can be killed.
And I'm pretty mean.
- Pritchard: Ever done dry bumming?
- Hawke: Dry bumming?
Okay, gents, now it's time
to do a little bit of hunting.
Okay, got a couple
of techniques for you.
One is a bola.
- Are you familiar with that?
- No.
- ( Joycey laughing )
- ( screams )
- My jones!
- Good old-fashioned slingshot.
Ready?
Now, the whole thing about
these little critters--
- they die easy.
- Hands out of the way!
Daint,
you're pulling back.
Bollocks!
You fucking try it!
So once you whack him,
go up there and stomp on his head
or club his head or something
to make sure you finish him off.
( guys laugh )
And then you gotta practice
a little bit with it
- so you get your aim down.
- Fat ass, are you ready?
- No, but carry on.
- That hit his plums!
That hit
his fucking plums!
You've smacked the plate
in my arm where my arm is broke.
How I fucking missed that ass,
I don't fucking know.
Lesson one:
Don't play with these.
( rock music playing )
All right, ladies--
it's that time.
( Hawke speaking )
That's a snake,
isn't it?
Hold out your hand
and receive your chow.
- Joycey: Oh, no!
- Dainton: Holy shit!
That's it.
You've got it.
I don't want it
going up my top.
Oh, man, I don't know
if I can do this.
- ( yelling )
- Just poke it--
Oh, fuck!
He stung you?
- Oh, you can't do that!
- Hawke: There you go.
- Now cook it.
- Oh, you can't do it.
- Hawke: Cook it.
- I just have.
Joycey: How the fuck
did Panch just do that, man?
- Fuck! Fucking hell!
- It's still alive.
- Oh, I'm starving.
- Put him back on the normal floor.
Oh my fucking God,
he's eating the fucking sting!
- Not much flavor to him...
- There you go.
- Just like that.
- ...but it's food,
and my stomach
is fucking loving it.
I can't believe
you fucking did that.
- I'm not doing that.
- I know what's coming to me,
- I think.
- You can't eat spiders though.
- Fuck.
- Oh my God! No no no!
Fucking no!
I'll fucking starve.
- But killing it--
- lamscaredoffuckingspiders.com
This is looking one
in the face--
that you're afraid of--
stabbing that fucker...
It will bite me.
...and eating it.
No, he won't.
That's a big, bad,
furry bastard right there.
Whack him.
Get your knife ready.
Oh! Daint!
Don't fuck around now!
I've got a fucking knife
in my hand!
I could easily
stab you and cook you!
Actually, that's --
I fucking almost span out.
- There it is.
- Fucking hell!
Put it on the fire.
Straight on the fire.
He's gonna cry.
- He's in tears.
- What's the matter, Math?
- Joycey: What's the matter?
- Dainton: Oh, that's fucking wrong.
Just rip off a limb,
stuff it down your throat.
( Dainton gags )
- There you go, you've done it.
- You're in, you're in.
- Chew chew chew.
- ( strained ) Oh, crikey.
- Way to lead.
- Cheers, Hawke, you fucking cunt.
( hip-hop music playing )
I know you boys are hungry,
I know you've worked hard...
and I promised you
some Kentucky Fried Chicken.
So, I am from Kentucky...
this is a chicken
and you're gonna fry it.
Boys, I'm not doing this
for the fun of it.
- Well then, let's get on with it.
- Pritch.
- Most humane way, please. I'm starving.
- Dan?
- Yeah, no, I'm --
- He's watching.
If you're ready to do it
your way, that's cool.
- Dan, do you wanna do it?
- I wanna go for the machete.
That's the only way
I wanna do it,
because I don't like
touching fucking birds.
We've gotta fucking eat
something, boys.
We have to eat something.
He's gotta--
- Which way do you want me to kill him?
- Would you do the boot?
I'm not-- I'm not--
I'm not doing it.
- I'm not even eating it.
- You're not eating it?
If I can't kill it,
I'm not eating it. No way.
- ( groans )
- Just pray for him,
send him to a happy place.
( clucking )
( melancholy music playing )
Pritchard:
I think the only fact I couldn't eat it
is because
it's more domesticated.
It actually looks like
it's got feelings and stuff.
You look at a fucking
tarantula and a scorpion...
to me, they haven't
got feelings.
They're just this thing
that walks along the floor
and just looks horrible and ugly.
But a chicken looks nice--
it's feathery,
looks like it's got
a bit of personality.
- It's, you know--
- Dainton: Pritch, what do you want--
- leg or breast?
- Breast.
He's actually quite nice.
- Dainton: What's his name?
- Derek.
- Derek?
- Derek. Derek the chicken.
What we have here
is a very simple...
case of mind over matter.
I don't mind
and they don't matter.
- ( guys laugh )
- But seriously,
once they've walked
across the fire...
then they've paid their penance
for their sin of gluttony
and they'll be free to relax
and enjoy themselves
until go on their way
to their next mission.
( Hawke speaking )
Joycey: Yes!
Ah! Eeh. Ooh.
- Whew.
- Joycey: How is it?
- Whoo!
- ( blues playing )
- That is some mean shit!
- ( Dainton laughs )
- Pritchard: Ready, boys?
- Pancho: Come on, Pritch.
Three, two, one.
( screams )
( belches )
Let's do it.
Hawke, have you enjoyed the time
you've spent with us?
- It's been better than masturbation.
- ( guys laughing )
- Oh, what?
- Oh, this is so fucking gay!
Are we ready
to leave the desert?
Almost.
You have
one more thing to do.
Oh, fuck off.
You've got one minute
to crack all
the Myke Hawke jokes...
that you can.
I'm holding the head
of Myke Hawke.
That's enough.
Thank you very much.
Gentlemen, you've paid
your full penance
for your sin
of gluttony...
and you are now
- free to leave the desert.
- ( both cheer )
Pritchard:
Party time, boys!
( "You Got to Leave" playing )
# Who'd have thought,
who'd have thought #
# You'd get the devil
down on his knee? #
# Holy smoke, holy smoke #
# Only if you will remain #
# Hot time
down on the ground #
# You're causing a crowd,
the trouble is pride #
# And you are pointing it wide,
when it's dark it's dark #
# And you will lose
your heart #
# Pick it up and go back
to the start... #
Dainton:
Right, simple. Dead easy.
Stuff as much of this
in your mouth as you can.
The person that takes the least amount
of money in their mouth
has gotta make a simple
phone call to their mom.
Yeah, but there's
a distinct disadvantage here.
I haven't played up
on the small-man thing.
You know, I've done fucking
all the stunts so far.
But look at my gob.
That's how far
I can open it.
The dentist has even told me
I've got a problem.
( laughing )
Go.
Oh God, he's being sick!
30 seconds, Panch.
25 seconds, Pritch.
Oh, that's semi-cheating that is.
It'll make you heave.
( gags )
Joycey:
Fucking what?
Well that's fucking--
that's fucking unfair.
Who had the least amount
of money in their mouth?
- It's a fix, Daint.
- It's always a fix.
Well, you said
get your money in your mouth.
Everyone has
just gone like that.
No, because there was no rules,
just "put the money in your mouth."
Well make it
more clear next time.
Well, it's too late now,
you've lost.
Did you or did you
not say that the winners
get to write
the loser's script?
- Yeah, I did, yeah.
- Dainton: Exactly. What are we doing?
We're writing
the loser's script.
Oh, no!
Joycey, don't be
too fucking sick, for fuck's sake.
Right.
( Pritchard's mom speaking )
Hiya, Mom.
How you doing?
Yeah, not bad. Just in
the Dominican Republic.
"Mom, from the moment
I was born
I have been thinking
of returning
to that special
heavenly place,
those lips parting
across my face
as you pushed me out...
of your heavenly
love hole.
I want-- I want
to return where I belong.
I want to put my lips
around your soft delicious
nipples once again."
- ( mother laughing )
- "The thoughts I have
for you are uncontrollable.
L-- I want--
I want--
I want
to dry bum you."
- Pritchard!
- Sorry I offended you.
Right, speak to you later.
- Ta-ta. Ta-ta.
- Ta-ta, love.
Wankers!
( Joycey imitating pirate )
Let me tell you about the angry pirate.
Bird is giving you a blow-job,
she is, see. Enjoying it down there.
You're about to reach
the point of climax, about to cum,
so you pull your cock out of her mouth
and spunk in her eye.
And then she's
all sore in her eye.
You kick the little bird
in the shin, she hobbles around
- like an angry pirate.
- ( guys laughing )
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're gonna give
the angry pirate a go.
We're gonna go with some rum.
Three, two, one.
Ar! Ar! Ar!
Fucking hell!
What the fuck is that?!
Fucking acid!
Three, two, one.
( yelling )
Open your eye, open your eye!
Open your eye!
( grunts, yelling )
Dainton:
Open your eye! Open it!
- ( yelling )
- Shin! Shin!
Open up.
- Oh my God, it's --
- You're not angry enough.
- Arr!
Pancho, last night
when you were asleep in the car,
we nicked your money
and spent it in a casino!
Right, over there
is a vehicle.
Who's inside it?
Well, someone is missing.
( snoring )
Is that a-- is that
a bifta in your hand?
( groans )
Get the fuck off.
I thought there's no way
I'd lost that money!
- It was in my shirt, wasn't it?
- We lost it!
Hang on a minute.
I've just found his money,
and I'm one greedy bastard.
I'm gonna spend it in a casino.
Ta-ta, Panch.
Right, Captain Panch.
Do you wanna win
that money back that we took
- and stole from you our greedy selves?
- Fucking right, bud.
Pirates of Pain-zance,
let the pain begin!
- Go on, Panch, get that money.
- Go on, go on.
Joycey:
It's one of them, isn't it?
It's the anticipation.
I don't know if I can
go through with it.
Here we go.
( bell rings )
Fucking stop it!
That got you going.
Dainton:
But he didn't take the money!
- He didn't get the money!
- It's impossible. Fuck off!
- That's mine!
- Your turn, Daint. What you having?
I've got a wicked plan up
my sleeve for you, Daint.
We get loads of money--
basically, on the bottom
there's gonna be
loads of pins-- drawing pins--
and we're gonna put
the money on top of it.
You've gotta
put your hand on it,
and we're gonna smash
your hand down,
and you've gotta get
your money that way.
What-- what about forehead?
Do it on the forehead again?
- Forehead?
- Yeah.
- Fuck right off!
- Three, two, one.
Fucking hell!
Oh my God,
look at that!
That's fucking graphic!
- Get a photo of that, man.
- Oh, Daint.
Fucking hell,
it's pulling out...
I'm willing to gamble
1,000 of this back
for you to take
a gob in the mouth.
- Oh, Daint.
- A gob in the mouth?
- No, it's fucking rank.
- Dainton: Come on.
- What do you mean?
- Spit in his mouth. He don't like spit.
He's got a phobia of spit.
Would you rather get run over by a car
- or someone spit in your mouth?
- Run over by a car.
( hawks )
Right, ready?
All in his mouth!
- He looks so green!
- ( gags )
- Man overboard!
- Quick, set the sails. Let's fuck off!
We're backstage in, er,
The Voodoo Lounge
in the Dominican Republic
about to do a pain auction.
Pain equals money.
What do we like? Money.
What does it equal? Greed.
Are you guys ready
- for some fun tonight?
- ( cheering )
Come on!
Okay, we've got
lot number one.
This is
the fishing rod ear.
Stick it in there!
So do we have anyone who wants
to pay some money for that?
- ( man yells )
- I have a lady there.
Lady with the big tits.
Whoa, sold for 150.
- Go! Come on!
- ( yells )
Come on, pull it!
Pull!
Joycey:
Who wants to start the bid off?
100 to see Panch get smashed
on the head with some pots.
Can we have 60? 80!
Shoeshine boy, 90!
All:
Five, four, three,
two, one. Go!
That sex pest over there,
number five. Yes, 50.
( grunts )
Dainton, voodoo therapy,
stick it in there!
Whoa!
( yelling )
For 30. Can I see
that 30? Yes.
All:
Five, four, three,
two, one!
- He's in fucking agony.
- It fucking kills!
Get it out!
It's fucking killing, you prick!
Ah! Ah!
No no no!
Stop it!
Fuck the cameras!
Get it fucking out.
( all chant )
Pancho, Pancho, Pancho, Pancho.
Closed.
Sold for 150.
Dainton:
Let's get fucking bollixed!
Ladies and gentlemen,
you've been watching
"Dirty Sanchez - Live"!
Make some noise!
- ( rewinding )
- ( all screaming )
The Devil:
Boys, boys, boys...
that was really
some performance out there.
Tattooed penises,
dismemberment,
cannibalism--
you boys
really blaze a trail.
Do you have anything
to say for yourselves?
I have got
something to admit.
Pancho hasn't got
any eyebrows left.
No, that ain't -- fuck.
- Better fucking not be.
- Gone.
Guys, knock
the fuck out now.
No, it is, isn't it?
I need a fucking wash.
Fuck it!
He obviously doesn't
want his life back.
I'm fucking serious, man.
That's fucking it.
Get that fucking thing
out of my face!
I'm fucking telling you--
fuck off!
- No no no no.
- Right!
The makeup people,
well, we told them,
"Tell Pancho his eyebrows
need sorting out."
And we put lmmac
on his eyebrows,
so his eyebrows
are falling out.
Right, gone.
You're fucking
happy now, are you?
He's probably got
all those wigs,
and he's trying to superglue
some eyebrows back on.
I'm likely to go and fucking
stab someone now.
Look at it.
I'm fucking telling you.
Cameraman:
No, don't do that.
Fucking always
at my fucking expense, right?
Oh, fuck,
we've pushed it this time.
What did he say all the way
through the movie?
( mimics )
"Do not fuck with my eyebrows!"
Cameraman:
Panch, stick around.
Get the fuck away
from me.
( cameraman speaking )
Go on, Panch!
Here comes the trouble.
Hello.
"I love Dainton"? No!
No. No way.
Is that real?
Yeah. I went through
absolute agony.
I'm not sitting
on that ever again.
Oh, Lis, I haven't had sex
for four weeks.
Never again.
No way. I don't care.
I'm not putting Dainton
in my mouth. No way.
Come on, fucking get
out the way!
Look at that bubble!
Look at that snot bubble!
Am I green
in the face?
- ( guys laughing )
- I am?
I've brought you
to this spa
for the ultimate
sports massage.
Well, it better
be proper special,
because I've got these
absolutely poxy pants.
( yelling )
Pritchard:
Rock and roll!
Yes. He's done it!
Fuck me, man!
It's the only way
to warm up.
Guess-- guess what
that little bad boy is.
That-- that's --
that's frozen shit.
Oh, hello. A little penguin,
little frozen penguin.
It still stinks!
I didn't think it would smell.
Get off,
get off, get off!
That's Joycey's frozen--
oh, it's on my lens. Oh!
There's dots and there's
a lump of poop.
( all yell )
Pritch, you know
that tattoo on your leg?
"Sleep when you're dead"
in Russian, guys. Whoo!
- Daint, fuck off!
- It doesn't even say--
it doesn't even say
"Sleep when you're dead."
- What does it say now?
- "I love Johnny Knoxville."
( laughing )