Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Whew!
Lfl want to shower
in the middle of the day,
it's OK?
Fuck Sal?
We love roll call, y'all?
Boogie Down Productions,
Rob Base, Dana Dane??
Marley Marl, Olatunji,
Chuck D., Ray Charles,
EPMD, EU, Alberta Hunter,
Run DMC, Stetsasonic,
Sugar Bear, John Coltrane,
Big Daddy Kane,
Salt 'n ' Pepa,
Luther Vandross,
McCoy Tyner,
Biz Markie,
New Edition, Otis Redding,
Anita Baker,
Thelonious Monk,
Marcus Miller,
Branford Marsalis,
James Brown, Wayne Shorter,
Tracy Chapman,
Miles Davis,
Force MD's,
Oliver Nelson,
Fred Wesley, Maceo,
JanetJackson,
Louis Armstrong,
Duke Ellington,
JimmyJam,
Terry Lewis,
George Clinton,
Count Basie, Mtume,
Stevie Wonder,
Bobby McFerrin,
Dexter Gordon,
Sam Cooke,
Parliament Funkadelic,
AIJarreau,
Teddy Pendergrass,
Joe Williams,
Wynton Marsalis,
Phyllis Hyman, Sade,
Sarah Vaughn,
Roland Kirk,
Keith Sweat,
Kool Moe D,
Prince,
Ella Fitzgerald,
Diana Reeves,
Aretha Franklin,
Bob Marley,
Bessie Smith,
Whitney Houston,
Dionne Warwick,
Steel Pulse,
Little Richard,
Mahalia Jackson,
Jackie Wilson,
Cannonball and Nat Adderly,
QuincyJones,
Marvin Gaye,
Charles Mingus,
and Mary Lou Williams.
We want to thank you all
for making our lives
just a little brighter
here on We-Love radio.
I t's hot as a motherfucker?
Fan me with your ears?
Stop playir!
Leave it alone?
Why don't he leave me alone?
Shut up?
It's too hot for that?
That's why I asked you?
We don't have money for anything?
I'm beat?
Daddy, you know,
I've been thinking?
Maybe we should sell this place?
Get out while we're still ahead??
And alive?
You really thinkyou know
what's best for us, Pino?
I mean, couldn't we sell this
and open up a new one
in our own neighborhood?
There's too many pizzerias
already there?
Maybe we could try
something different?
What am I going to do?
That's all I know?
I been here 25 years?
Where am I going?
I'm sick of niggers?
It's like I come to work??
It's "Planet of the Apes?"
I don't like being around them?
They're animals?
Whyyou got so much anger in you?
Why? I'll tell you why?
My friends...
They laugh at me?
They laugh right in my face?
They tell me,
"Go to Bed-Stuy?
Go feed the moulies?"
Doyour friends put money
in your pocket, Pino?
Food on your table?
They payyour rent,
a roof overyour head?
Huh?
They're not your friends?
Lftheywere your friends,
theywouldn't laugh atyou?
Pop, what can I say?
I don't want to be here?
They don't want us here?
We should stay
in our own neighborhood,
in Bensonurst,
and niggers in theirs?
I never had no trouble
with these people?
I sat in this window??
All I see is
little kids get old?
And I seen
the old people get older?
Yeah, sure,
some of them don't like us,
but most of them do?
I mean, for chrissake, Pino,
they grew up on my food?
On my food?
I'm very proud ofthat?
You may think it's funny,
but I'm very proud ofthat?
Look, what I'm trying
to say, son, is, uh??
Sal's Famous Pizzeria
is here to stay?
I'm sorry?
I'm your father,
and I loveyou?
I'm sorry, but??
But that's the way it is?
Hey, S-S-Sal?
How you doing?
These are $2? 00?
Get out?
Get the fuck out ofhere, man!
Get the fuck out ofhere!
$2? 00?
S-S-Sal?
Come on?
Get out ofhere?
Get the fuck out ofhere!
Every day it's the same shit?
Hey, leave that boy alone!
Get a fucking job?
Why don'tyou get a fucking job?
Go to fucking work!
S-S-Sal?
Get out? Get out!
See what I'm saying?
Leave that boy alone?
You know he ain't right!
Get a fucking job, man!
I'm sick ofthis shit?
You get a job!
I got a job?
Bring your ass here, punk!
I ain't going over there?
I ain't got no reason
to go over there?
F-F-F-Fuckyou!
Fuckyou!
Get the fuck out ofhere!
F-F-F-Fuckyou!
Go inside?
Smiley, here? Here?
Smiley, here?
Here's a couple of dollars?
Come on? Come on? Here?
Fuckir asshole!
Hey, Willie,
take it easy?
He didn't mean nothir?
[Door Slams]
OK?
Motherfucker!
This is what I'm talking about?
Whoo!
Let's go, Jade!
Da Mayor,
we need your leadership?
Doctor, what areyou talking about?
I'm organizing a boycott
ofSal's Famous?
Shit?
Keep walking, Doctor?
I don't want to hear
none ofyour damn black foolishness?
Damn? No juice?
No, man, no?
No!
Hell, no, goddamn it?
Sal ain't never
done nothir toyou before?
Whatyou ought to boycott
is that barber
that fucked upyour head?
Yeah!
Shit?
Come out here fuckir
with Sweet DickWillie?
Get the fuck away?
Would you sign a petition
to boycott Sal's Famous Pizzeria?
I ain't boycottir jack,
string-cheese
head motherfucker?
I'm going for a slice now?
I was raised on Sal's pizza?
Whatyou talkir about?
You crazy, man?
Good as them
motherfuckir pizzas is?
Black Panther eat pizza,
we eat pizza?
I'll do it withoutyour help?
That's 75 cents?
Thanks?
Thanks, honey?
Sal, we're going to boycott
your fat pasta ass?
You're going...
You're going to boycott me?
You haven't got the balls
to boycott me?
He's going to boycott me?
Are you kidding?
Here...
Here's your boycott?
Up your ass?
You're going to boycott?
Where you going?
I'm talking toyou, Pino!
I'm right here?
Go inside?
I can take care of myself?
Take it easy, OK?
No? Go inside?
Here's your boycott!
Messed up myJordans with muck?
Damn!
Get this thing
straightened out, man?
White guy/black man?
I can't believe this crap?
Ah, yourJordans are dogged?
Oh, man, you, too? Stop?
Yeah, me, too?
Hangir out with baby sis?
We're not hangir out?
She's escortir me back to Sal's?
I'm just goir to get a slice?
You can't? Not today?
I'm organizing a boycott
ofSal's Famous?
What did he do?
You know them pictures
he got on the wall offame?
So?
Notice somethir about them?
No, Buggir Out,
I haven't?
You're wasting my time?
Leave that shit alone?
You really should?
I'm gone?
I'll seeyou there?
Buggir Out, howyou been?
Every single one of them pictures
is somebody Italian?
And??
Wewant black people?
Did you ask Sal?
Yeah, I asked him?
Wewant nobody in there,
nobody spending
good money in Sal's,
until we get black pictures
on the wall?
What good will that do?
Lfyou tried hard,
you could direct
your energies more usefully?
You got to be down?
You ain't?
I'm down, but I'm down for something
positive in the community?
Areyou down for that?
Jade??
Jade, I still
loveyou anyway?
Yeah, I still loveyou,
too, Buggir Out?
Later?
Man?
You're pushing it, Mookie?
You're really pushing it?
I don't pay good money
to haveyou jerk me around?
Keep it up,
you'll be in the street
with your other homeboys?
About time, Pop?
Jade?
Howyou doir, Jade?
Whereyou been?
Just working hard?
Keeping busy?
How's business?
Business is great?
We were wondering
when you'd stop by?
How's Mookie doing?
He's, uh?? Mookie is??
He's great?
A good kid?
Hey, Pop?
Stop lying?
He's kidding?
I know?
What'll it be?
Regular slice?
No, I'm going to makeyou
something special,
ifyou don't mind?
No, that'll be great?
OK? What doyou
want to drink?
Cream soda?
Used to be root beer?
Tell me ifl'm wrong?
I want a change ofpace?
Vito, clean the table forJade?
All right, Pop?
Come here, Jade?
Sit here?
# Fight thepower#
[Music Slows]
# Fight the power #
# Fight the pow... ##
20 "D" Energizers?
20 "C" Energizers?
"D?" Not "C?" "D?"
"C" Energizers?
"D," motherfucker? "D!!"
Learn to speak English first,
all right? "D!"
How manyyou say?
20, motherfucker? 20?
[Speaking Korean]
Motherfuckyou!
Motherfuck??
Motherfucker, you,
you all right, man?
Just give me
the motherfuckir batteries?
20 "D" fuckir batteries?
Hey, yo? Yo, wait?
What's the date on them?
The date!
The fuckir date!
What?
Can you fuckir speak English?
The date!
The date?
Marcha!
Marcha?
Whatyou talkir about... Marcha?
1991?
Oh, March?
That's March, motherfucker,
March?
Yo, man,
you sure that's 20?
20?
No? No? Take them out?
Count them again?
Count the shits again, man?
Motherfucker?
May I helpyou?
I want some flowers?
The whole thing?
It's very expensive?
I know? I'll pay?
I thoughtyou might like these?
I guess not?
There is nothing
like the smell offresh flowers?
Don'tyou agree,
Mother Sister?
Summertime...
All you can smell is the garbage?
Smell overpowers everything,
especially the soft,
sweet smell offlowers?
You don't mind,
I'll sit right here,
catch a breeze or two,
then be on myway?
Thank the Lord,
the sun is going down?
It is hot as blazes?
Yes, Jesus?
Well, guess I'll be on myway?
[Boom Box Blares]
Oh!
Oh, goddamn, man!
Cut that shit down!
A person go deaf
or something?
Fucker!
Man, I don't know
how he does it?
Oh, man!
Goddamn?
That is shit?
ML, come here?
What?
Come hold this fucker, baby?
Hold what, sucker?
You know what I'm talkir about?
That's OK?
At least my moms
didn't name me??
Sweet DickWillie?
Uh-huh?
I told you about that mama shit?
Nobody talkir aboutyour moms?
I ain't say nobody?
I said you!
Just squash that shit?
I didn't mean it like that?
You did, too?
I justwanted to know
who named you
Sweet DickWillie?
Man, it's just a name?
Goddamn? Shit?
How'd you get the name ML?
ML stands for ML?
Now that's some stupid shit?
Hear me?
That's some stupid shit?
'Cause everybody know
why they call me
Sweet DickWillie?
You Negroes kill me?
Always holding on to??
Always talking
aboutyour dicks?
It's too hot to fuck?
Man, you out
your fuckir mind?
It ain't never too hot
or never too cold for fuckir?
I had my best piece ofwoman
on a humid day?
Over in the projects?
Close to yourwoman?
Get out!
Oh, Lord, have mercy?
I better not see her
naked on payday?
Piraguero!
Everybody out!
The icee, icee man is here?
Hey hey!
Looking good?
Here we are?
Look at these beautiful people?
The icee man is here?
I want coconut?
Give me lemon?
Tell me whatyou need?
Thereyou go, my love?
That's your color?
That's your flavor?
I want more syrup on mine?
He's always drinking, man?
[Ice Cream Truck
Music Chimes]
Hey, hey!
Where's everybody going?
Ice cream!
Doctor!
Doctor, don'tyou
know no better
than to run out
in front of a car?
You trying to kill yourself?
Come on?
Let's get up?
You gonna be all right?
You gonna be all right, my boy?
You gonna be just fine?
Eddie, what's wrong?
Mayor knocked me down?
You ought to be
shamed ofyourself?
Ha ha? That boy's
just scared to death?
What happened...
I was walking,
minding my business?
I seen your son
about to get hit by the car,
so I dashed out?
I knocked him down
to keep us both
from getting hit?
I saved two lives today...
his and mine?
Eddie, is that the truth?
Eddie, you hear me
talking to you?
I'm talking toyou, boy?
He gonna be fine, miss?
Mommy, Mommy!
I'm sorry!
Get upstairs now!
Your father gonna
wear outyour behind?
Miss, you didn't have
to hityour boy like that?
He's already scared to death?
I appreciateyou
helping my Eddie,
but I'll have nobody question
how I raise him?
You're right, miss?
You're right?
I don't want to sound like a jerk,
but can I say something, Jade?
Yeah, Sal?
You got the biggest eyes
I've ever seen?
Theyjump out ofyour head?
I feel embarrassed
even saying that?
Thanks, Sal?
Don't even mention it?
It was delicious?
I got to talk toyou?
Come on?
Let's go?
Jade, don't forget
to come back soon, OK?
Hey, Mookie?
Take it easy?
You're going to bust her arm?
I don't wantyou
in Sal's no more?
Mookie, what?
Stop tripping?
Read my lips?
Don't see Sal?
What areyou worked up about?
The way Sal looks atyou?
- He's being nice?
- Nice?
- He's completely innocent?
- Innocent?
You heard me?
Sal just wants
to hide the salami?
You're really crude, Mookie?
Do not come in Sal's anymore?
You are not welcome?
You got a lot of nerve?
I'll tell you one last time?
Stop playing
big brother to me?
I'm a grown woman!
You can't payyour rent,
and you're lecturing me?
That makes no sense?
Oh, it doesn't, huh?
You got $250 a week?
I'm getting paid?
Peanuts?
In a while,
I'll be making a move?
Yeah, when?
Don't worry?
When, Mookie?
Don't worry about it?
Don't come here no more?
We're not talking about that?
I'm tired ofsupporting
a grown woman, OK?
a grown man, OK?
When areyou going
to pack up and go?
Don't come in Sal's no more?
And no more pizza, either?
I don't care ifyou fire me
this exact fucking moment?
Lfyou're saying
what I'm thinking
you're saying,
you better not say it?
You hear this?
Do me a favor?
LeaveJade alone?
You know, Mookie,
not for nothir,
but ifyou were
just a little taller,
I'd kickyour ass
forwhatyou're thinking?
As a matter offact,
I should kickyour ass
on principle alone?
Here?
You got a delivery?
This the right address?
What is this??
Yeah? It's the right address?
That's the right address?
I wrote it myself?
Sometimes you make mistakes,
and I deliver fucking pizzas
to the wrong fucking address?
I don't make mistakes?
You don't make mistakes?
Hurry back, OK?
Don't get lost?
We're still open?
Make a pizza, huh?
Mr? Mayor?
I saw whatyou did?
That was foolish but brave?
That child owes you his life?
Wasrt trying to be a hero?
I just seen what was happening,
and I reacted... didn't even think?
Probablywouldn't have done it
ifl had thought?
Da Mayor's getting old?
Ain't run like that in years?
Went from first to home
on a bunt single?
Scored the winning run?
Two outs?
Bottom of the ninth?
August 1, 1939?
Snow Hill, Alabama?
Mud Cat Bones
was the pitcher?
He hated my guts?
He come down offthat mound,
and I took off
like white lightning
up a black snake's ass?
Maybe I, uh??
Maybe I ought to be
a hero more often?
Maybeyou shouldn't?
Don't get happy?
This changes nothing
between you and me?
You did a good thing?
Mother Sisterjust thanks you?
I want to thankyou?
You're welcome?
Delivery from
Sal's Famous Pizzeria?
Is it hot?
I've never delivered a cold pizza?
Come here?
You thinkyou're slick, Tina?
How else could
I getyou up here?
I haven't seen you all week?
I'm working?
Making money?
You forgot the ice cream again?
I forgot?
Your memory's getting ridiculous?
I got things on my mind?
I reallywanted some ice cream?
I'll run out and get some?
No, no? That's out?
You won't come back?
I can't be staying long?
How long?
Long enough to do the nasty?
Come on, Mookie?
That's out?
First of all, it's too hot?
Lfyou think
I'll letyou get some,
putyour clothes on and leave,
and I won't seeyou again,
you're bugging?
I'll seeyou tomorrow?
Yeah, right?
So no nasty, huh?
No?
Something else?
What?
Trust me?
Last time I trusted you,
we got a son?
Remember him?
His name's Hector?
You saying I'm a bad father?
On the strength?
Let me talk toyou?
What? What?
Over here?
Tina, takeyour clothes off?
I already told you
it's too fucking hot
to make love?
It's too fucking hot?
Why are you always cursing?
I don't fucking curse that much?
What the hell you mean?
All you do is curse?
Anyway, no rawness
is jumping offtonight?
All right?
That's it?
No rawness?
No? No rawness?
Why's it always like that
when you come over?
It's not always like that?
It's always...
What areyou doing?
I'm not cursing?
Mookie? Come on?
I mean it?
I'm not playing?
Don't be so anxious?
That's right?
Take it off?
You're sweating?
Of course I'm sweating?
It's only 100 degrees in here?
Look, freeze?
Don't move?
I'll be right back?
What doyou mean
you'll be right back?
Where areyou going?
I'll be right back?
Whyyou got me
standing on the bed?
Whereyou going?
How's my son, Hector?
Honey, doyou hear that?
He wants to know
howyou are doing?
And he has the straight face
of asking about it?
Sinverguenza.
Good for nothing?
Callejero.
Que se la pasa por la calle... -
English! English!
I want my son speaking English?
Get out of my kitchen?
Bad enough his name's Hector?
I don't want to hear anything?
Out, I said?
Yes, children?
This is the cool-out corner?
We're slowing it down
for all the lovers in the house?
I'll be giving you
all the helpyou need?
Musically, that is?
This shit is cold?
Supposed to be cold?
It's an ice cube?
Later foryour shit?
Mira.
What?
You don't got a forehead?
You got a eight-head?
Mookie, you're full of shit?
You got one of them
Sade foreheads?
Fuckyou?
Goddamn?
Big-ass forehead?
I need an iceberg??
Rather than this ice cube?
Thank God for lips?
Thank God for the neck?
Thank God for kneecaps?
Thank God for elbows?
Thank God for thighs?
Thank God
for the right nipple?
for the left nipple?
Feels good?
Ah? You likes?
You likes?
Amen?
I got to be going?
You better come back?
I'll be back tonight?
You better,
'cause I'll kickyour ass?
Oops? I got to be back then?
All right?
Get out ofhere?
I got to go?
Bye?
I'm not leaving yet?
Get out ofhere?
All right? Later?
Later?
Just out of curiosity,
how long you
sticking around here?
You mean tonight?
I mean the neighborhood?
I figure about 50 years?
'Cause I'm going into real estate?
I'll put up a high-rise
in the neighborhood?
Yeah? Lot ofpeople
want to move here?
Why not?
You want a condominium?
A couple ofstraws, Mr? Trump?
Trump's Pizza?
I heard ofthat?
That's Trump's Plaza?
Get out ofhere?
Take care, Salvatore?
Pino, take the soft drinks
from the back
and load up here?
OK, Pop?
You want me to deliver faster,
I need a rocket?? Something?
I can't be running?
The cheese lands on one side?
Mookie, I didn't say nothing?
You must have a guilty conscience?
I'm not guilty ofanything?
You're guilty ofsomething?
Otherwiseyou wouldn't be saying that?
Come on, Sal?
Wherewe going?
Oh, shit?
Vito, give me a hand?
Come on?
What the fuck's the matter?
Vito, I wantyou to listen to me?
I'm your brother?
I smackyou around
once in a while,
but I'm still?? Your brother?
So what, Pino?
So fucking what?
I loveyou, man?
I'm listening?
I wantyou to listen?
Jesus Christ, Pino?
I said I'm listening?
Vito, black?? White? No?
No, no, no? No?
What the hell
you talking about?
Areyou listening to me?
Stop busting my balls?
I said I'm listening?
Mookie's not to be trusted?
I trust him, Pino?
They can't be trusted?
First timeyou turn your back??
Boom? Aah!
The spear in the back?
How doyou know this?
How doyou know, man?
I know? I read?
I never seen you read nothing
in your fucking life?
Read your history?
It's historical?
He, them??
They're not to be trusted?
What do you want me to do?
Be on fucking guard?
Mookie has Pop conned,
so we got to look out for him?
You don't know
whatyou're saying?
That's exactlywhat I'm saying?
[Sal]
Vito! Pino! Let's go!
We'll be right there, Pop?
One minute?
You better listen to what I say?
I'll ripyou?
I'll fuckyou up?
You know something, Pino?
You don't know everything
you thinkyou know?
You thinkyou know,
butyou don't know?
Mookie, he listens to me?
You don't, man?
You fucking don't?
You'll fucking stab me
in the back, man?
[Rap Music Blares]
Radio!
Buggir, what's up?
Howyou been, man?
Living large, bro?
Yo, that the only tapeyou gots?
You don't like
Public Enemy, man?
The shit's dope?
I'm down, butyou don't be
playing nothing else?
I don't like nothing else?
Yo, check this?
You know Sal?
Yeah, I know
that motherfucker?
I've been trying
to organize a boycott
ofSal's Famous?
I almost had to bust him
in the head today?
Gonna tell me...
Tell me, Radio Raheem...
to turn down my box
and shit, man,
and didn't even say "please!"
Who the fuck he think
he is, Don Corleone?
He make much money
off us black people,
and all he got on the wall
is Italians...
Sylvester Stallone,
okey-doke-lookir motherfuckers?
On the strength?
We shouldn't buy one slice,
spend one penny in there
till he put folks of color
on that wall?
That's what I'm saying!
You got my back?
Your back is got?
My bro?
Yo, Smiley?
Come here, man?
Whatyou listening to?
M-M-M-Malcolm?
M-M-M-Malcolm, huh?
Cut offthat rap music!
I'm in here trying to get me
some motherfucking...
I'll fuckyou up quick!
Two times!
Th-Th-Th-Three t-times!
Th...
Sal, start counting
my money tonight
'cause I gots to get paid?
Come on, Vito?
Come on?
This is terrific?
I mean we had
a great, great day?
You know something?
There's nothing like a family
in business working together?
I'm going to rename the place?
I'm going to call it
Sal and Sons'
Famous Pizzeria?
Why not?
You guys are going to
take it over someday, right?
And, Mookie??
Mookie, I want to tell you
that there's always
going to be a place foryou
right here
at Sal's Famous Pizzeria
becauseyou've always
been like a son to me?
Sal! Can we get some pizza?
We're closed!
Shut up!
You shut up!
Shut the fuck up, man!
All right, let them in?
They love my pizza?
Four slices, and I'm gone?
Sal, we're trying to go home!
Shut up!
You're a delivery boy, bitch!
Man, you don't know shit!
Shut the fuck up!
Sityour black ass down!
Shut up! Fuckyou!
Yo, Sal?
Four slices, man, regular?
To go, all right?
Whyyou gotta curse?
Looking good?
Looking real good, man?
Come on?
Move it, man!
# Fight the power #
# We got to fight
the powers that be #
# Elvis was a hero to most#
# But he never meant shit to me #
# Ya see straight out
racist the sucka... ##
I told you about that noise!
What about them pictures?
What the fuck, are you deaf?
No! Are you?
Fuckyou!
We want some black people
on that motherfucking
wall offame now!
We're trying
to go fucking home!
We've been here all day!
Turn that jungle music off!?
This ain't Africa!
Why it got to be
about jungle music?
Why it got to be about Africa?
It's about them fucking pictures!
It's about turning that shit off
and getting out of my place!
Radio Raheem!
Fuckyou!
And fuckyou, too!
Kick ass, Sal!
Get in there, Pino!
This is music!
My music!
Fuckyour music!
Well, turn it off, then!
Get the fuck out ofhere!
We're closed!
Fuckyou!
We're closing you
guinea bastards for good!
For good, motherfucker!
Until you get some black people
on that motherfucking
wall offame!
You're gonna fucking close me?
You're goddamn right!
You black cocksucker!
I'll fucking tear
your fucking nigger ass!
Oh, we're niggers now?
We niggers now?
Fuck them up!
You fucking white trash!
I'll fuckyou up!
Sal, put the fucking bat down!
Come on,
you fucking guinea trash!
Open the motherfucking counter!
You black cocksucker!
You nigger motherfucker!
[Music Stops]
I just killed your fucking radio?
My music!
You motherfucking...
Aah!
Get offhim!
Get the fuck offhim!
Get off!?
You fucked up my eye!
Ahmad, stop!
Please, stop it!
Stop it!
You fucked with my box, man!
Get the fuck up!
I'll kickyour ass some more!
Come on!
Somebody got it at Sal's, brother!
Fight!
Mookie!
Hey!
Break it up!
Hey! Hey!
You're gonna kill him!
- Stop it!
- Break it up!
Stop it!
Stop! Break it up!
You're gonna kill him!
Let me at 'em?
Let me at 'em!
Get...
Get the fuck out
of the way, man!
Move it!
Get off!?
Let me through!
Get the big guy!
Get off me!
I'll kill you, you motherfucker!
Just take him off me!
Get away!
What are you doing? Sal!
Get the fuck off me!
Get off of me!
You're taking me to jail, huh?
You're not taking Vito
or Pino or Sal out!
Get the fuck off me!
Aah!
Get his other arm!
Take him down!
Just take him down, man!
Let him go, goddamn it!
You're killing him!
Give it up, asshole!
Aah! Aah!
Just take him down!
Come on!
Aah!
Let him go!
Stop it, goddamn it!
Stop it!
Aah!
Get his arm!
Gary, that's enough!
Shut up?
Gary, that's enough, man!
[Chokes]
Gary, that's enough!
Shut the fuck up!
Radio Raheem!
No!
Radio!
Radio Raheem!
Get up!
You ain't dead!
Get up, asshole!
Qit faking it!
Get the fuck up!
Let's get him out ofhere?
Goddamn it!
I'm a black man!
You can't kill us all!
You can't fucking
kill us all, goddamn it!
Motherfucker!
Let's get him out ofhere!
Come on!
Get him to the car?
Let's go?
Back off, assholes!
You pig-fucking murderers!
You can't kill us all, man!
You can't fucking kill us all!
Back off!?
Back off!? Back off!?
Everybody, back off!?
Get back!
Fucking bastards!
Shut up, man?
Fuck off, you fucking...
Damn it!
I told you to shut up!
Back off!?
Radio!
[Sobbing]
Mookie, they killed him?
They killed Radio Raheem!
It's murder?
They did it again,
just like Michael Stewart?
Murder!
Eleanor Bumpers! Murder!
Damn, man!
It ain't safe
in our own fucking neighborhood!
Neverwas?
Neverwill be?
We ain't gonna stand
for this shit no more, Sal?
Ain't gonna stand for
no fucking police, punk!
It's as plain as day?
They didn't have
to kill the boy?
[Smiley Sobbing]
You do whatyou gotta do?
Fuck that, man!
Listen, listen, listen?
Good people, please?
Let's all go home?
Somebody's gonna get hurt?
Yeah? You, boy!
Lfwe don't stop this now,
we gonna do something
we're gonna regret
for the rest of our lives?
Sal had nothing to do
with what the cops did?
One of the police was black!
Leave him alone?
We'll getyou
and them three stooges, Sal?
Go on, Mr? Sal?
You see how they had him
in a choke hold?
I knew that choke hold
would kill him!
You might have saved him!
A fucking radio!
He died because ofa fucking radio!
He wanted pictures
on the wall, and he died!
Whatyou got to say, Sal?
Your son called the cops!
Get the fuck out ofhere, man!
Somebody's getting hurt!
Fuck that, man!
Hate!
Ohh!
Whoo!
What are they doing?
Sal, come on?
Come on, quick?
Get them out of there!
Get...
That's my place!
That's my fucking place!
Sal!
Fucking niggers?
Radio! Radio!
Burn it down!
Come on?
Let's clean house?
Shit? Come on?
I no white?
I no white!
It's your turn, sucker!
I'm black!
What?
I black!
Me black!
Whereyou black at?
I'm black!
You, me... same!
We same?
Same?
Me black!
Open your eyes, motherfucker!
ML, leave the Korean alone, man?
He's all right?
Yeah? He's all right?
He's black?
Shit?
[Sirens Blaring]
Oh, fuckyou, man!
Howard Beach!
People, please disperse!
Please disperse!
Howard Beach!
We're giving you
one more warning
to please go home!
This is our home!
OK, you've had yourwarning!
Hose that black sucker down!
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Get off of me!
Yo!
Well, come on! Come on!
Come on, asshole?
Come on!
Come on? Move it?
Motherfucker, come on!
What you think this is, Birmingham?
Fucking Alabama?
Yo, where's Bull Connor?
Son ofa bitch!
Oh, no!
No!
# Fight the power #
- # Fight the power #
#We got to fight
the powers that be #
- # Fight the power #
# Fight the power #
#We got to fight
the powers that be ##
My people, my people??
What can I say?
Saywhat I can?
I saw it, but I didn't believe it?
I didn't believe it, what I saw?
Are we going to live together?
Together are we going to live?
This is your
Mister Seor Love Daddy
talking toyou
from We-Love radio,
108 FM on your dial,
and that's the triple truth, Ruth?
Today's weather?
Hot!
Wake up!
Fuck!
My money? Shit!
Where are you going?
To get my money?
Don't try that shit, OK?
You're going to run out,
and I won't see your ass
for anotherweek?
It's not like that?
You don't give
a fucking shit about me,
and you don't
give a shit aboutyour son?
I care aboutyou and my son?
Why don'tyou be a man?
I am a man?
Then act like a man?
Why don'tyou be
a fucking man, Mookie?
I'm so tired ofyour shit?
Why do we have to
go over this again?
Becauseyou don't
fucking listen, Mookie!
Lfyou listen to me,
I wouldn't have to repeat myself
like a fucking radio!
What kind of motheryou are
using fucking language like that?
What kind of mother am I?
Your ass isn't even here!
Get anothervocabulary, right?
Get a fucking life?
Yeah? Look??
Lookwhat?
I'll be back?
Don't leave, Mookie?
Don't leave?
I'm tired ofthis shit?
You walk out that door, that's it?
All right?
I have to get my money from Sal?
I'll be back?
Your shit's to the curb,
and I'm tired ofit?
You need to step off
with your stupid-ass self?
You need to get
a fucking life, Mookie,
because the oneyou got
is not working!
I ain't going to deal
with this shit no more!
Shit?
Fucking ass, stupid ass,
fucking pendejo.
Shit? Fuck?
Fucking shit?
Good morning?
Is it a good morning?
Yes, indeed?
You almost gotyourself
killed last night?
I've done that before?
Where did you sleep?
I didn't?
I hope the block is still standing?
We're still standing?
What doyou want?
I want my money?
I want to get paid?
You don't work here no more?
I want my money?
Your money couldn't begin to pay
for the windowyou broke?
Motherfuck a window?
Radio Raheem is dead?
I know he's dead?
I was here, remember?
He's dead because ofhis buddy?
That cocksucker started this shit?
He's responsible
for that kid's death?
He wanted to close me,
and you stood there like a fuck
and watched them
burn me down!
I also watched the cops
murder Radio Raheem?
You'll get it all
from the insurance anyway, Sal?
What the fuck's
wrong with you?
This ain't about money?
I could give a fuck
about money?
You see this place?
I built this fucking place!
With my bare fucking hands!
Every light socket,
every piece oftile?
Me! With these fucking hands!
You know what that means?
It means pay me
my motherfucking money?
That's what it means, Sal?
OK, Mookie?
How much do I oweyou?
My salary is 250?
250 a week?
1??
That's 2??
That's 3??
That's 4??
And that's 5?
You got $500?
You're a rich fucking man?
Are you happy?
You happy?
He's got 500 fucking dollars!
He's a big man!
He's a rich fucking man!
He's never going to have
any more trouble!
Not Mookie!
He's fucking rich!
Who the fuckyou yelling at?
You're wealthy, Mookie?
You're a real fucking Rockefeller?
You gotyour fucking pay?
Now leave me alone?
Sal, my salary's 250 a week,
all right?
I oweyou 50 bucks?
Keep it?
You keep it?
No, you keep it?
I don't believe this shit?
Believe it?
Areyou sick?
I'm hot as a motherfucker?
I'm all right, though?
Well, they say it's even going
to get hotter today?
What areyou going
to do with yourself?
Make that money?
Get paid?
Sal, I got to go see my son
ifit's all right with you?
Hey, Mook.
It's the Mook man.
I seeyou walking.
Go home toyour kid.
Now the news and weather.
Our mayor has commissioned
a blue-ribbon panel...
"to get to the bottom
oflast night's disturbance.
The City ofNew York
will not let property
be destroyed by anyone."
His Honor plans to visit
our block today.
He should hook up
with our own Da Mayor,
buy him a beer.
Your Love Daddy
says register to vote.
The election is coming up.
There 's no end in sight
from this heat wave,
so today,
the cash money word is chill.
That's right. C-h-i-l-I.
When you hear "chill,"
call in at 555-L OVE,
andyou'll win
cash money, honey.
This is Mister Seor Love Daddy
coming atyou from
what's last on your dial
but first in your hearts,
and that's
the quintessential truth, Ruth.
The next record goes out
to Radio Raheem.
We love you, brother.
# From the heart ofBed-Stuy #
# W-e-L -o-v-e ##
# I was looki ng through
a wi ndow at my I ife today #
# And for the first time #
# I saw things in a different way #
# I n the middle of my mind #
# It was there all the time #
# Never explain love #
# It's not like anything
you've ever done #
# lfit is there,
it's yours to keep #
# And the boundaries, they grow deep #
# Never explain love #
# Let the experience take overyou #
# And when you do #
# Never explain love #
# I was looking for an answer #
# And I was searching for a sign #
#To try and understand
this relationship of mine #
# But I didn't need to go far #
# I was reading it all wrong #
# Never explain love #
# It's not like anything
you've ever done #
# lfit is there, it's yours to keep #
# And the boundaries, they grow deep #
# Never explain love #
# Let the experience take overyou #
# And when you do #
# Never explain love #
# Before I knew #
# I almost knew it all #
#Who needs to be rational #
#When love isn't practical #
# Oh, I knew this was inside #
# And it's so wrong #
# It's so right #
#Whoa-oh-ho ahh #
# Never explain love #
# It's not like anything
you've ever done #
# lfit is there,
it's yours to keep #
# And the boundaries, they grow deep #
# Never explain love #
# Let the experience take overyou #
# And when you do #
# Never explain love #
# It's not like anything
you've ever done #
# If it is there, it's yours to keep #
# And the boundaries, they grow deep #
# Never explain love #
# Let the experience take overyou #
# Forwhen you do #
#Yeah, yeah #
# Never explain love #
# Never explain love ##
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org