Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
You were right.
This is definitely better
than being at work.
One thing you didn't warn us
about though, bloody midges.
You are a big
girl's blouse.
Anyway, now that
you've mentioned work,
and seeing that I bullied you to come all
the way out here to celebrate the fact,
here.
Congratulations.
No knight should be
without his sword.
I don't know
what to say.
My writer
lost for words?
It's perfect.
Yeah, and it's also solid
silver, so don't lose it.
Nice try, Private Cooper.
You evaded capture
for 22 hours
and 47 minutes.
You're straight to
the head of the class.
Of course the real
trick to survival
lies not from
running and hiding,
but in removing your enemy's
capacity to hunt you down.
Here. Shoot the dog.
I'm sorry, sir, what?
Take the weapon
and use it.
During the selection process,
you are under my command.
That's a direct
order, Cooper.
You're taking
a piss, right?
He thinks I'm pulling his leg. Do I
look like a sodding comedian, shit?
No, sir.
I still won't do it.
You don't have a choice.
Finish the job. Shoot the dog.
Shoot it!
No, sir!
What use are you
to my team
if you can't
even kill a dog?
I didn't say I couldn't kill a dog, sir.
I just will not kill
that dog for no reason.
You're bent, Cooper. I don't
need a man of conscience.
You're failing me
for this?
You failed yourself.
We're on a different
level here, Cooper.
For that, I need
men of action.
Not deeds.
No!
You sick
fucking bastard.
It was just a dog.
That's all.
Maybe one day when that's
sunk into your thick skull,
you'll be ready
for us.
Until then, you
live and learn.
Yeah. You don't.
I don't do second
chances, Cooper.
And I never forget.
Owe to you this
pathetic piece of shit.
Send him back
to his squad.
I want a good
clean dispersal
and a secure
landing zone.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Joe, get out
of the chopper.
I'm not missing the footy
for this, it's totally bone!
I'm not going.
They're up.
Cooper. I want a position and
bearing. Wanna move in three minutes.
On it.
Spoon, Terry,
you're on stag.
Joe, for fuck sake.
Get off your big fat lardy
ass and make like a soldier.
Right then.
Time sync.
I've got 07:30.
Coming up in three,
two, one.
Check.
Bollocks. I don't
believe this.
What is it now,
Witherspoon?
Left me watch at
the barracks, Sarge.
Take a breather every
once in a while.
Nice work, Spoon,
you tosser.
Took the words
right off my mouth.
You will take my boot out
of your mouth, Joe, you twat.
Piss now.
This shit is
totally bone.
The most important football match
of my life is playing tonight
and I'm stuck at the back side of
beyond without a six pack or a telly.
That's the army for you.
It's England v. Germany,
man. Full on footy war.
Well, it's nothing like
this at all, isn't, Joe?
It's just an exercise.
Hardly life or death.
Don't bet on it, Joe.
You're fucking slaying me.
If you'd paid any attention at
all during the briefing, Kirkley,
you'd know exactly who we're up
against on this harmless exercise.
Who's that then?
Special Forces, you plunker.
Bollocks to them.
All right. All right. Listen up.
I'm gonna make this
quick and to the point.
All I wanna do is get
home, jump into a warm bed
with a nice hot woman
and watch the footy.
Planning on scoring, Sarge?
Mind you don't foul her
in the penalty box.
All right. Ban it,
private parts.
As for this moment
as far as we're concerned,
we are 50k behind enemy lines. Now,
if we do happen to make a contact,
I expect nothing less than gratuitous
violence from the lot of you.
As we're firing blanks, it doesn't mean
we have to be thinking nice thoughts.
So, you remember,
you put five down.
You get stuck in, you kick their fucking
teeth out or I guarantee you, Joe,
they will be having your
bollocks for breakfast.
Hard boiled
or fried, Sarge?
Scrambled.
Here, Spoonie.
Oh, smart.
That's nice and new and shinny doesn't mean
it's worth shit. Remember I want that back.
What about you, Sarge?
Well, I'll count.
Right then, Coop,
what we got?
We're here. The front
line is here.
AWAK reports enemy positions
here, here and here,
with sweeping patrols
between each of these bunkers.
Have all the whole sector wrapped
tighter than an Eskimo's nutsack.
With one exception
right here.
A river crosses the line through
a gorge 30 or 40 feet deep.
It's certain to have a patrol
on it but if we go at night,
tread careful and don't
mind getting our feet wet,
I reckon we can
make it through.
What the fuck is
all this about then?
More likely I'll need
all the help I can get.
Hey, listen. I know you think
it was a piss pool cooled you.
Failing selection and all that,
but I got to say I'm not sorry.
This squad would be
a lot worse without you.
Something I had
to do, you know.
For myself, get it
out the system.
The only people going
into trouble are Kamikazes.
Glory boys and full
on fucking fatwits.
Take my advice, son.
Be patient.
Right then, ladies.
Pack up your troubles,
put your brains in first
gear and start tabbing.
Spoonie, you're on point.
Terry, Joe, tail in Charlie.
Over here, Cooper.
On me head.
Twater.
I can't believe I'm missing
the footy for this party.
Joe, if you don't shut up, I swear to
God I'm gonna shut you myself. Now, move.
Didn't say a word, Sarge.
Where the hell
are we now?
I heard a cracking
story about this place.
You what?
People disappear out here.
It happens all the time.
Come on, Cooper.
Give it some bollocks.
It's true. Just last month a young
couple were hiking through these woods.
They set up camp somewhere near here.
During the night, something happened.
A rescue team found the remains
of the camp a couple of days later.
The tent was ripped to threads
and there was blood everywhere.
The papers said it was a monster,
like the beast of Bodmin Moor.
The locals claimed
it was an escaped lunatic.
But no one's been caught, so
nothing could be proved either way.
Every year, more and more
people come through here.
Every once in a while they don't
come back. No trace, no bodies.
Just disappear and
never seen again.
Oh!
Contact camp.
Tell them the flock is
heading for the fold.
Then, Bruce,
what scares you?
The self-destructive nature
of the human condition.
Just taking a piss now.
You think so?
What about you, Spoon?
Castration.
There's no argument
there. Joe?
Only one thing that puts the
shit at me. A penalty shoot-out.
That figures. Terry?
Watching a penalty
shoot-out... with Joe.
What about you, Coop?
Spiders.
And women.
And, uh, spider women.
I want to know
what scares the Sarge.
Piss of, man. Nothing
scares the Sarge.
I don't know
about that.
The thought of never seeing my wife
again scares the shit out of me.
That and those little things
that make your skin crawl
and the hairs stand up
at the back of your neck.
You mean like Spoon?
There's one thing actually in particular
that I'll remember until the day I die.
It's back in '91, just before
my unit was flying out to Kuwait
to mop up the last
pockets of resistance.
Me and this young fellow
called Eddie Oswald
decided to go and get a tattoo done to
commemorate our first trip into the desert.
I remember Ed. He was a stocky hard case
with a broken nose
and a bone eye, eh?
Yeah, that's him. Good-looking
fellow. Big hit with the ladies.
Anyway, me and Eddie,
we had a few drinks.
We had a lot of drinks.
And we went down to the tattoo
parlor, and I got a desert rat done.
And Eddie being Eddie wanted
something a bit more meaning.
And being a bit
of a believer,
he said that his soul
still belonged to God.
But his flesh was way
beyond redemption.
It was up to Satan
to save his skin.
So he got this fucking great laughing
devil tattoo right on his ass.
Anyway, about six days later, we were making
a regular sweep along the, uh, Iraqi border.
And, uh, Eddie, poor fucker,
triggered an antitank mine.
Yeah. We all saw it
happen. He was on point.
A white, blinding
lightning flash
and a fucking deafening crack. By the
time we picked ourselves up of the deck,
Eddie was-
He was gone.
Just bits and
pieces of him.
It's all that remained. This big
fucking red circle a hundred meters.
I'll tell you something, lads. It
really puts things in perspective
when you have to scoop your mate up
with a shovel and stick him in a bin bag.
Anyway, the thing that really
did our nuts in that day
was when you, uh, came
across the bit you recognized.
A bit of an ear, a toe, a nose, a tooth.
The thing that really
freaked us out that day
was when left-hand Charlie found
a bit of Eddie with the tattoo on.
I mean, everything else was burned
to a crisp covered in claret.
All mushed up,
pocked up.
Not this bit.
This bit was perfect.
And there's old Nick chalking
his fucking ass all over us.
So you could say
that Eddie was right.
That Satan did indeed save
his skin, just not all of it.
Or you could say that
Eddie was just unlucky.
Either way.
It taught me to keep
a very open mind.
Boom, boom.
Anyway.
Eddie Oswald.
To Eddie.
So, this bloke
walks into a pub
with a dog under his arm. Puts his
arm on the bar, goes and sits down.
The bartender is looking and
thinking, "What is going on here?"
He looks back at the
dog and the dog turns on-
Fucking cow!
Ceasefire, Terry.
Ceasefire.
Terry, what the hell
are you doing?
You're firing
blanks, man.
Is everyone all right?
Is everyone okay?
No. I think
I've shit meself.
Is it dead?
Oh, yeah, it's dead.
Look at the state of it.
Look at the state
of Terry.
These aren't entry wounds.
More like teeth marks.
What are you
saying, Cooper?
What he's saying, Terry, is
that it died of natural causes.
Don't you think we should
call this in, Sarge?
Aye. Go on
the radio, Bruce.
There's no way I'm about
to break radio silence
'cause you lot got spooked
by a dead flying fucking cow.
We have this position. We keep
it secure 'til the morning.
Then we reassess
the situation.
Right. I want
a watch posted.
Two on. Four off. Brucie,
Spoon. You're up first.
Cooper an I relieve at 0100 hours.
I n the meantime, Terry,
sort your kit out.
The rest of you
get your edge done.
Unbelievable.
Sarge?
Cow came in from this
direction, straight off the edge.
From the frying pan
into the fire.
Bleeding to death, it could've wandered
around for miles before it got here.
It's good of it to leave some
breadcrumbs for us to follow.
Looking for trouble?
No, Cooper.
Just looking.
Sarge, shouldn't we report
this when we get back?
You're right, Terry, but in the meantime
I'm curious, and it's on the way.
Come on, lads.
Natural causes
my ass.
Oh, now what?
Christ.
What the fucking hell
happened here, Sarge?
This is getting all
bone by the minute.
Jesus Christ, Sarge.
All right, lads.
Get a grip.
We've got casualties.
Ditch your bargains.
Salvage whatever weapons
you can find, and stand to.
We are now up against
live, hostile targets.
If Little Red Riding Hood should show
up with a bazooka and a bad attitude,
I'd expect you
to chin the bitch.
Looks like they got hit hard. Every magazine
is full. Nobody got up a single round.
If they're lost, then
where are the bodies?
Yeah. All right, Corporal.
Get on the net. Call in.
I want an emergency
air lift immediately.
Help me.
Captain?
Ryan? What
happened here?
Do not tell me
you know him.
Captain Ryan,
Special Ops.
No fucking dog lover.
Spearhead patrol. This is
spearhead patrol. Receiving?
He looks like he took on
Jack the Ripper and came last.
I can patch him up, but
he needs a medic right now.
This is an
emergency. Code 64.
You gotta get me out of
here. Do you understand?
There was only
supposed to be one.
We're working
on it, Captain.
Sarge.
Not now, Spoon.
You're receiving?
Shit.
What's wrong, Bruce?
I can't find a signal.
Did you check it?
Of course, and I double
checked it and it worked fine!
All right, Bruce, stay on
it. See what you can do.
Terry? They must've
had their own comms kit.
Have a look round. See
if you can find it. Go.
Sarge.
Spoon, have a shift on the camp.
See if you can find anything else.
Not now, Spoon.
This is spearhead patrol,
are you receiving me?
There was only
supposed to be one.
Jesus! Charnel House
is compromised to fuck!
How is he doing here?
All I know is
he's special forces.
If this is part of our exercise,
it's been not advertised.
No cap badge, no insignia. Just tags.
Some kind of
a covert action?
Covert action or not, they're
packing all kinds of weird shit.
Tranquilizer darts,
nets, you name it.
It's a special ops mission,
not a fucking safari.
Sarge? We found
that radio.
Shit, I don't believe it.
There was only
supposed to be one!
What's he on about?
Terry, get back
on stag now.
You got to get me out of
here before they come back.
Who, Captain? Who is going to come back?
They tore them to pieces
in front of my eyes.
If we don't get him somewhere warm
soon, he's gonna die of hypothermia.
Stay with me, Captain.
Captain Ryan, stay with me.
Sarge.
Not now, Spoon.
I n about half an hour
it's gonna be dark.
Does anybody copy?
Any joy?
The fuses are blown.
Can you fix it?
Maybe it was faulty or maybe
some damp got in the casing,
but it's fried
the circuits.
Well, if it's
useless, bin it.
I also found this.
It's attached inside. Not part of
the radio. Looks like a transmitter.
Why would they put
a bug in our radio?
It's the Kobayashi Maru test. They
fixed it so we can't fucking win.
Ban it, Spoon. Terry,
it's probably some joke.
He didn't want Joe to
hear the footy results.
An early shot.
Anything useful?
Weapons, ammunition. A
couple of magnesium flares.
That's about it.
All right, lads. Ditch
your ITs. From here on in
the exercise is well
and truly over.
Anyone not carrying
life rounds, better do.
Bruce.
It won't make
any difference.
They won't die.
This gives me a better
peace of mind, sir.
You want peace of mind? Run for your
lives before they tear your legs.
You just shut up
like a good gentleman.
You are scaring my lads.
Oh, shit.
All right, lads,
grab what you can.
Head to the tree line.
We're moving. Let's go.
Right. I need a volunteer
for rear guard action.
I'll do it.
When we clear, you fall back.
We're gonna be there to cover you.
Off you go.
Bruce, no heroics.
Spoonie, you're on point. Joe,
help Ryan. Terry, you're up next.
Coop, you and me. All right,
lads, in front the long grass.
Double time. Go!
Come on, sunshine,
fucking shift it.
Come on!
Bruce. Bruce!
Jesus!
Cooper, get out of here!
Jesus, I'm bit, mate.
You said no heroics, you
bloody hypocrite. Where's Bruce?
He's all over there. They
fucking tore him apart.
You piss off.
That is an order!
They're coming!
Fuck off.
You can take your orders
and shovel them up your ass.
Oh, Jesus,
my guts are out.
We'll just put them
back in again.
They're not gonna
fucking fit!
Of course
they'll fit, man.
Here.
Come on.
Come out of the fog.
God.
To your rear!
A target!
Target.
Keep moving.
Covering fire.
Backing guard.
Coming through!
Target.
Reload!
Bloody hell!
Just fucking lie down!
Lads.
On me.
On me!
Stop!
Get in.
Everybody on me!
Hurry.
Fire!
Oh, shit!
Just drive.
Now!
They're fucking coming!
Come on, stab it!
Go reverse.
Stab it!
Go forward.
Fuck!
Everything okay back there?
Any more casualties? Spoon?
No, I'm all right. What
about Bruce? Where's Bruce?
Bruce is, Bruce
is gone. He's gone.
Fuck it!
Just hang on back there.
Thank you.
It's okay.
What happened?
What happened? We were attacked by huge
fucking howling things. That's what.
You were lucky I found you.
I was about to give up hope.
And you were here?
I heard gunfire last night.
I knew someone was out there.
If you weren't already in
trouble, then you soon would be.
We are. Two men are down.
Both need medical attention.
We need to dress the Sergeant's
wounds before we can take him too far.
There's only one
farm in this glen.
The owners are friends.
We can take him in there.
Hello?
Nobody home?
I don't know
where they could be.
Nice.
Stand back.
Little pigs. Little pigs.
We've come to nick your video.
Hey. Sit.
Hey. Sit, sit.
You stay. Hm?
All clear.
What the fuck happened
back there, Cooper?
I don't know, mate.
She might have
some answers.
All clear upstairs.
Where the hell
are we now?
Home sweet home.
Sit him down.
Spoon, get a field
dressing on that wound.
Terry, keep an
eye out front.
Is there a
telephone here?
What? No.
It's still hot, lads.
You can't just
help yourself!
I'm chinstrapped and I'm bloody
starving. I can't help meself.
It's the training, miss. Never
waits an opportunity to eat. Come on.
Now look what
I'm doing.
Get it down
your necks, lads.
Hold it, hold it.
Top grub.
What is it?
Don't know, mate.
Looks like pork.
Leave some for us,
you greedy mongrels.
Miss, where is
the nearest phone?
Fifty miles as
a crow flies.
What about the nearest
population center?
You mean a town?
Well, Fort William,
but it's at least a four-hour
drive back the way we just came.
Do you think your
wounded can make it?
The Sarge is in serious
trouble if we don't.
You seem to know these
roads. Will you take us?
Right now?
Unless your friends are just gone.
This place may be compromised.
Fine. The sooner
the better. Let's go.
All right.
Spoon, on me.
Everyone else hang by until
we bring the car about.
Joe, help the Sarge.
Terry, watch him.
The safeties off.
Spoon.
Don't stare back.
I can't help it.
Go.
Move on!
That puts a kibosh
on that plan.
That was my car!
Sam, no!
Oh.
Piss off.
Fuck that!
Step back!
Bloody hell!
Get the dog off me.
No.
Pull the dog off me.
Sam.
Shut the dog up!
Sam, come here.
Terry, right flank.
Cover the window.
Christ.
That's bloody
charming, that is.
You incompetent moron!
Do you wanna have
a fucking go like?
Bathroom?
Upstairs. Far
end of passage.
We need to talk, Ryan.
It doesn't look like I'm going anywhere.
Joe, Spoon. Looks like we're
staying. You know what to do.
I want a secure perimeter
with a clear field of fire.
We'll give them something
inviting, right?
I'm on it.
Terry, are you okay?
I'm real craving
for a kebab.
I'll take that
as a yes.
We've got limited ammunition. I want you
to get as many pots and pan as you can.
Fill them with water and keep
them on the boil, all right?
Terry, set
the kettle on.
We'll all do
with a brew.
Terry, give us
a hand with this.
To the side.
You fool.
You came here because
of them, right?
I don't have a clue what they are,
and right now I don't really care.
What are you
doing here?
This was supposed to be a routine
training exercise, and that's all.
So this wasn't a rescue
mission? No, I guess not.
Back door is secure.
What's happening
here, Spoon?
They're still moving around out
there. They're keeping their distance.
Maybe they've had
enough for one night.
Not likely. They're smart.
You've seen what they can do.
My guess is they're doing exactly
what you'd be doing in their shoes.
Working as a team. Looking
for a weakness. A way in.
I'm not about to second-guess these things.
They're the enemy. As simple as that.
This is no
ordinary enemy.
You know what this reminds
me of? Rorke's Drift.
A hundred men
of Harlech
making a desperate stand against
ten thousand Zulu warriors.
Outnumbered,
surrounded.
Staring death in the face.
No flinching for a moment.
Balls of British steel.
You're bloody
loving this, aren't you?
It's totally bone.
That's all there
is to say.
What are we talking
about here? Wolves?
Not entirely wolf, nor human,
but something in between.
Wolf men?
And a laugh, right?
I may be nuts
but I'm no fruitcake.
Fine. Stay here
and drink tea.
I thought you might be here
because of them. But I guess not.
Just don't be
an asshole.
I like your new
girlfriend, Coop.
How're you feeling?
A touch of gas.
And the fact the various body parts
are trying to evacuate the premises.
Fucking awful.
Ta.
Cheers.
Attention!
For crying out
loud, man.
Short, controlled bursts.
Do you have
a name, soldier?
Cooper.
Gonna need your
help here, miss.
My name is Megan.
And I know
how to kill-
Shit, Sarge, you're
leaking like a sieve.
I need you to get some
Superglue and some whiskey.
I'll see what
I can do.
Come on.
I'm sorry about the asshole thing.
I've got a mean streak of mine across.
It's all right. It's the
least of my worries right now.
Can you pass me
my gun, please?
Thank you.
Come on, Coop.
Up the wooden hill.
Where are we
going, Coop?
You don't want
to know, mate.
What's the glue for?
Never wondered why the best thing that
Superglue sticks together is your fingers?
Give it. Give it.
Forget your grandma's
China cups.
This stuff was developed for the
Vietnam war to patch up broken soldiers.
How are you
feeling, Sarge?
Absolutely fucking top,
fucking bollocks.
Give us.
Give, give, give.
Are you sure he should be
taking painkillers with whiskey?
He's earned it.
Is it your
birthday, Coop?
No, mate.
Is it my birthday? Hey!
No. You're gonna thank us
for this in the morning.
I'll tell you something.
I'm gonna fucking thank you.
Right now I'm gonna thank you because you
saved my life. You got me out of there.
You would've done
the same.
If I'd done the same fucking thing,
I would've saved Bruce, wouldn't I?
Yeah! Fuck!
Fuck.
Jesus!
Sausages.
I'll tell you
something, miss.
This guy here
is my best mate.
He's the salt of
the fucking Earth.
Don't get me wrong. The rest of the
guys in the squad are lovely fellows.
Anyone of them
could marry my-
marry my sister
if I had one.
I'll tell you what.
I love him I love you.
Like the mate
that I, that I love.
Would you like
to be alone?
You fucker!
Here.
It's the adrenaline.
I'll stick
and you bond.
I'll tell you something.
Something better get fucking stuck
'cause this is really
starting to hurt.
Cooper.
Knock me out.
Hit me!
You fucking
pussy. Hit me!
How long have you
lived around here?
Two years. Came here
for the wildlife.
I'm a zoologist.
So you've heard those
stories as well then.
Yeah. I heard the stories. I
went looking. I found evidence.
I was fascinated
by the possibility-
You can't seriously
believe in werewolves.
Straight out of college, I'd have
loved to the suggestion, but now
I know they are
as real as you and me.
Before tonight is over, you will, too.
There.
I think that'll hold.
You've done this before?
Oh, yeah. We glue people's guts
together all the time out here.
Everyone tooled up?
To the nines.
Keep a fucking eye
over that one.
Right, Terry,
you look sharp.
The rest of you.
We know things are going from shit
to bone to worse in the last 24 hours.
But if we pull our way and do the
job, we still have a fighting chance.
No more running. We
stand here. We fight.
Right?
Any questions?
Just one, Coop. Exactly, what
is it we're fighting against?
Megan, you wanna
run it pass the boys?
Lycanthropes.
That's werewolves
to you and me.
Are you taking a piss?
Makes perfect
sense to me.
Full moons, silver bullets and
eyebrows that join in the middle?
Before you dismiss it off hand, think
about what you've seen and heard.
The full moon, the teeth,
the claws, the howling.
Is it so difficult
to believe?
For a whole year now
I've tracked these things.
I've studied them.
Try to understand them.
Every month when the moon
is full, they hunt as a team
dedicated to the kill.
During that time at least
15 people have vanished.
Hikers mostly, in small groups or alone.
They're caught out in the open,
hunted down, torn apart, and devoured.
I've never witnessed the actual
slaughter, but the next day
no bodies,
no werewolves.
Just blood.
The eyebrows thing is nonsense.
It's just Dark Age paranoia.
And silver bullets, no one's
ever got close enough to try.
I'm sold.
Slow down, Spoon.
Megan might have a point.
I'm still not convinced that these things
didn't escape from the local nuthouse
and forget to shave or trim their nails.
But they're out there and we're in here.
What they may or may not be does not
affect our immediate situation one bit.
This is bone. This is so fucking bone!
Anything else?
Yeah. What
does "bone" mean?
Bone. Bollocks.
Not very good.
Right. Anything else
I should know?
Call signs.
You need to be specific.
Upstairs you've got Sergeant Wells,
who you seem to know inside and out.
You got Spoon over there.
The vomiting cavalier, Terry.
The big guy
with the ax is Joe.
Didn't you
forget someone?
Ryan.
Captain Ryan is not
one of our team.
His being here
is hazy at best.
If I could tell
you, I would.
But I'm just a
soldier like you.
No stripes.
No insignia.
A suit and a uniform does not make
a soldier. He's with Special Ops.
His team were wiped out last
night. He was the only survivor.
I'd advise you against pursuing the
line of questioning, Private Cooper.
You're pulling rank
on me now, Captain.
You can shove that
right up your arse.
I'm saying my being
here is a moot point
since I'm now in as
much shit as you are.
We're on the same fucking
shit. And we need each other.
I doubt
I need you.
You bloody did
two hours ago.
The Uaths.
Crying like
a baby you were.
That was then.
Circumstances change.
What?
Uath is Celtic. The family's
lived in this glen for centuries.
So, what was he
doing out there?
I have an idea.
I wanna hear it
from the horse's mouth.
Think of it Ryan.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
When we found you, you could barely
open your eyes, let alone walk.
And then later you manage
to run. And now look at you.
Fine and fit
and sitting pretty.
Hardly the behavior of a man who until
recently was knocking on death's door.
I have a strong
constitution.
You bloody kidding.
You won't mind if I have a
look at that wound of yours.
I just assumed
you didn't.
I have a responsibility
to my patient.
I'm warning you, Cooper,
don't touch me.
Get back!
Tie him up.
I want him to talk.
What are you gonna do?
Torture him?
I don't know.
What would you do?
I'd torture him.
What now?
They shut down
the generator.
Why would
they do that?
Because they can
see in the dark.
And you're all
afraid of it.
This is a pile
of rancid shit!
Now what do you believe?
I'm beginning to believe you. I
think Joe might've worded it better.
They're on the move.
All right.
This is it.
Mark your targets
and preserve your ammo.
Three-round busts.
We only got one
stun grenade apiece.
So only use them
if absolutely necessary.
Stand to.
What can I do?
What do you
want to do?
Run and hide.
I know what's coming.
Take care of Sam.
Keep an eye on Ryan.
If he tries
anything, pan him.
Chasing that first
kiss, are we, Cooper?
It's as simple as this.
You're not there for us,
we're not here for you.
Contact!
Die!
Spoon, get down.
Fuck!
Fire in the hole!
Ah!
Cooper!
Hurry!
Cheers, mate.
The Sarge.
Cooper.
Sarge?
Sarge!
Sarge? Sarge, wake up.
Wake up, you fuck.
Sarge!
You fucker.
Wake up.
Sarge!
Fuck off!
Dogs.
More like pussies.
You all right?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I'm peachy, mate.
Coop.
The squad's yours, mate.
They took Terry.
Then we go
and get him back.
You're right.
Forget about him.
What did you say?
He's dead, Cooper,
and you know it.
Shit!
Somebody must've heard
some gunfire.
Somebody must've
heard something.
Who? The only other house within 50
miles of here is mine, and I'm not there.
What about the road,
passers by?
Do you have any idea what kind of
luck you had running into me tonight?
I thought you
ran into us.
Joe, check upstairs.
Even if anyone did come by, they'd
only end up with a slaughter like you.
Our really hope
is daylight.
Sunrise is
in six hours.
We did the best
we could.
But if the Sarge's condition
deteriorates, he'll have less than four.
And the only thing holding them back, is they
don't know how much ammunition we have left.
Let's give it a look.
Tell me, honestly,
what are our chances?
The morale seems
good, considering.
It'll only last as long
as the ammunition holds it.
High spirits it's no substitute
for 800 rounds a minute,
but I don't think that's
what you want to hear.
Think about it, Cooper.
Up until today you believed there
was a line between myth and reality.
A very fine line sometimes,
but at least it was a line.
Those things out
there are real.
If they're real,
what else is real?
You know what lives
in the shadows now.
You may never get another
night sleep as long as you live.
So why worry, Cooper? You
may not live that long.
Shut your mouth.
I'm gonna make it through
this. You know why?
I don't scare
that easy.
Here.
It's supposed
to be lucky.
For me or the rest
of the rabbit?
You'll need a lot more
than luck this time.
Shut up, Ryan.
Listen to me, Cooper.
Ignore him.
We can survive 'til sunrise. That's all
that matters. It's just a few more hours.
Wait a minute. Am I
missing something here?
I know him.
I was seconded to his team
during their first visit here.
First visit? What first visit?
What the fuck are you talking about?
They came to check out the
stories. They needed an expert.
It's just a few more hours,
Cooper. That's all there is.
All clear?
Yeah.
You wanna
kill them all?
Yes.
Good. Keep it up.
What's the damage, Spoon?
We might've pissed
on our chips.
We've only got two full
mags for the MP5,
six rounds for the shotgun,
and one spare. Just in case.
Stay sharp, everyone.
We're putting fire
down all over.
We fill those things with lead, and
they just kept coming back at us.
Sixty rounds won't
last two minutes.
So, either we all
fight our way clear,
or the rest of us keep them
occupied but one of us goes for help.
By the time the cavalry get here, they'll
have what's left of us between their teeth.
Fucking brilliant.
We either stay and
snuff it, or we all go.
And snuff it.
Decisions, decisions.
Laugh.
I nearly died.
Who stopped you?
That's it! We'll
fucking have him!
Take it easy, big man.
Calm down.
Do any of you know
how to hot-wire a car?
They keep an old
Land Rover in the barn.
I don't know where the keys are, but if
one of you could break in and start it.
I can do that.
Are you sure?
A piece of piss.
The further I am from this
wanker, the happier I'll be.
All right. You're
gonna need a decoy.
Something fast
and loud.
What?
You what?
You, sit.
Stay.
You're serious about this
werewolf thing, aren't you?
Afraid so.
Shit.
Don't suppose you know
who won the match.
Didn't even know
there was a game on.
It's not a game.
All right, this is it.
Everyone get ready.
Bollocks.
Joe. Good luck, man.
You don't get off
the hook that easy.
All right, you bastards.
Come on and have a go if you
think you're naughty enough.
Come on, you beauties!
They took the bait.
Come on!
Spoon, run!
Move your fucking
arse, soldier.
Come on.
I'm trying.
I love it when a
posh bear talks dirty.
Jesus! What's fucking
going on, Cooper?
Cut it.
Fuck this.
Shit.
He's done it. Ryan, up. Everyone
else downstairs. Come on, move it.
Move. Move.
You're behind
me, aren't you?
I'm gonna
fucking have you!
Right? Go. Go.
Well?
She's in a bad way.
A few pumps gone.
Fan belt is bugging.
She's pissing out petrol.
The word "bone"
springs to mind.
Joe's body?
It's gone.
What's the damage, Spoon?
We're down
to 48 rounds.
Check the right.
Well, Ryan,
you heard the score.
Maybe one or two of us are
gonna make it through this.
I don't care much
for our chances.
Do you like football?
What? They think it's all over
and all that crap? No, I don't.
Don't you remember Joe? He liked
football. Fucking lived for it.
Is this relevant?
He missed the most important match of
his life for this bullshit exercise.
And now he's dead along with two other
mates. I'd give them my right arm.
To fucking right
it's relevant!
You just can't get
pass the dog, can you?
We're losing, Ryan.
We're three now down,
and we're close to the final whistle.
At the very least I wanna even score.
I understand
your resentment.
But you failed because you weren't
prepared to take that extra step.
If you'd passed, you
would've been on my team.
And if you were on
my team, you'd be dead.
Yeah, I failed.
I'm bloody glad of it.
If I was given the choice of
taking orders from a twat like you
and slogging it out at these guys,
I'll take the underdogs anytime.
So you can take your precious
selection, shove it up your arse
and stop trying to change
the fucking subject!
Fair enough.
But you won't like
what I have to tell you.
There are some places
you really shouldn't go.
We'll be the judge
of that, Ryan.
Ever heard of Special
Weapons Division?
They're the men in white coats who train
dolphins to stick mines on submarines.
And cute furry animals to
tear your head off at the neck.
They saw an opportunity
and called me in.
To do what? Catch
one of these things?
And to bring it back.
Alive if possible.
Only "it" turned out
to be "them. "
We underestimated
the enemy numbers.
Underestimated? I would have a serious word
with your heads about their intelligence.
It may have been their
invitation, but it was my party.
I planned it
and executed it.
And you loused it up.
We lost good men, Ryan.
Yours and mine.
I wanna know
where we fit in.
The reality is
you're expendable.
And I had approval
to put you at risk.
Get to the fucking
point, Ryan.
I made a gap
in enemy lines.
You were good enough to spot it
and predictable enough to go for it.
That was your bait.
You were mine.
You bastard.
I had to choose somebody.
I remembered you.
Monkey see,
monkey do.
They were my men!
Get up, you shit. You know what we
can do. Give us a fighting chance.
Live and learn, Cooper.
I didn't hit him hard.
You tricked
something lose.
Bad dog.
Fetch.
Make the shot.
Clear.
Cooper, get down.
I got target.
Werewolves spend most of their
time in human form, right?
And the only people from
miles around live right here.
So these things aren't about to
give up the fight and go home.
They are home.
That makes perfect
sense, don't it?
We bust into their house. We eat all
their porridge. We sleep in their beds.
No wonder
they're pissed off.
But they're good people.
They're kind people.
More is the pity.
Why?
We're gonna have
to kill them all.
He's right.
What self-respecting werewolf would
have anything silver in a house anyway?
Fuck the folklore.
Let's just burn them.
If we knew
where to find them.
Maybe we do.
Everything we've seen so far
suggests the behavior of a pack.
Six to eight members. An Alpha
pair leading the subordinates,
and a young male, the Beta wolf,
second in command. Makes sense.
You lost me.
A wolf pack sticks together, generally
somewhere close to its food supply.
Somewhere safe,
sheltered, and warm.
You're gonna have to move like
shit off the shovel on this one.
You wanna get
your own shit.
When we blow that fuse up, that place
is gonna look like Zabriskie Point.
Yeah, it's easy peesy.
My lime's squeezy.
Listen, Coop.
What about the Sarge?
You know what I mean.
The Sarge is with us.
Yeah, yeah.
I just didn't want him to go
out without his watch back.
And you stay
out of trouble.
You all right?
Oh, yeah,
I am fine, Cooper.
I mean, I feel
absolutely fantastic.
That's a problem, isn't it?
Hey?
What if she's wrong?
What if they're not
all in there?
Then we'll get
some of them.
It's a shit lot better
than none of them,
and a marked improvement
on all of us.
No, you listen to me.
You get the fuck out now.
I'll hold them back, keep
them occupied. You get out.
We've lost enough men for
one night, don't you think?
Let me show you something.
Do not tell me that
that is fucking normal.
What happened to Ryan
is happening to me.
It's just a matter
of time, mate.
Stop wasting time
with this hara-kiri crap.
This fight isn't
lost, yet.
With Ryan it only took a
couple of hours. It's full moon.
Maybe it's like when you need to take
a piss or something. I don't know.
When you gotta go,
you gotta fucking go.
Maybe it's more than
needing a shite.
Just 'cause you need one, it doesn't
mean you drop your kegs and pinch one off.
Fucking Ryan, shifty bastard could've
been one of those things from the start.
You know, Coop, there's one more thing
you gotta learn about command, mate.
Sometimes the people that
you kill, are your own men.
So, I'm asking you.
Let me take care
of myself.
And at least spare you the unfortunate
business of trying to expla-
explain to Annie why
you had to incinerate me.
We're gonna knock seven colors of
shit out of these fuckers. We need you.
It's all right,
you know, mate.
It's okay.
I just didn't make it
out this time. That's all.
Because of the job,
you know what I mean?
When I signed my life away on that
doted line, I fucking meant it.
I am a professional soldier.
So, what do you
want me to do?
Roast their
bollocks off.
All clear.
Good luck.
Light it!
Shit.
Sarge.
I'm sorry.
When I found you
out there tonight,
I truly believed you were the
best chance I had of getting out.
But now we have
no chance.
There is no out.
There never was.
I came here to be one with
nature. Well, I got what I wanted.
Now I have
to live with it.
There is no house
in the next glen.
No.
And there were no werewolves
in the barn when it blew.
Not one.
The reason you're not in the
photograph is 'cause you took it.
I never meant to-
You women.
Same old shite.
Being nice to women
will get you nowhere, Cooper.
Being nice to me
will get you killed.
You may think they're
all bitches, but
I'm the real thing.
Do you think I like being
part of this fucked up family?
Do you think I chose
to run with the pack?
No.
I chose you.
But now you're out of
luck, and I'm out of time.
And all we can do is let
nature take its course.
They were always here.
I just unlocked the door.
It's that time
of the month.
Somebody has to put it
out of his misery.
Spoon. Clear.
Go now!
Spoonie, stop fucking.
It's an order!
Come on!
Sarge?
I'm in the closet.
Open the closet.
Come on!
You fucking mother!
You're not killing me,
you bastard.
How do you like the
tomatoes, you fucking bastard?
Come on.
I'm running out, Coop.
I'm running out.
You're a fucking bastard.
Come on!
I hope I give you the
shits, you fucking wimp.
You fucker.
Come on, Coop.
Beat it!
Here.
Go away.
Go on, Coop! Get stuck in mate!
Get out of it! Come on, you fucker!
Go away, you
fucking ass.
Come on!
Cooper, let's get
in the wardrobe, son.
What?
Let's get
in the wardrobe.
All right.
What's that smell?
I don't know.
Fucking hell.
Give me that.
Open your mouth. Watch
the ears. Mind your toes.
Go.
Where's Spoon?
There is no Spoon.
No, you fucking bastards!
Help me, Cooper.
Get in there.
Get in there!
What are you doing?
Take this. There's one in
the chamber. I'm fucking bent.
We go together or
we don't fucking go.
It's my last order. Do not
fuck about. Do not disobey me.
Fuck! Listen.
You have got
to make it alive.
Prove what happened. Not
just for me or my lads.
For her!
Here.
Prove it happened, mate.
Go! Go!
Sam. Fuck.
What the fuck?
Ryan, have you tried
licking your own balls, yet?
I forgot. You don't
fucking have any.
Ha!
You think it's all over? It is now.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org