Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Warrior representation. Yes.
No means no! No means no!
No means no!
I'm a freshman.
And....
I was raped.
No, we didn't.
We'll have to think about
what we're doing next week.
-You look cute.
-Do I?
Happy Halloween, brother!
Be sure and stay away from the white
girls from now on. I know you will.
What are you doing?
Let's go get some fucking candy!
-That was awesome.
-It was good.
There are things
we could've done better...
...but I was proud of you.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
-I feel so much better now.
-Good.
Look, you know, I could just--
Why don't I just stay
with you tonight?
We could stay up and talk or....
What do you think?
Are you sure you're ready for that?
Don't do it just because
you're fascinated.
I want you to be sure.
Good night.
So...
...what's up with your friend?
-She's weird.
-She's not weird. She's just different.
Yeah, and I bet she wants to show you
just how different she can be, huh?
I'm tired of running and studying.
It's too hard to do both.
I feel like a slave.
They wouldn't give a fuck about me
if I wasn't running for this school.
I'm tired of feeling
like a thoroughbred.
Why you always gotta
take stuff so far?
People would die to be where you are,
and you tripping.
You have the opportunity to go
to school, and it's here. So take it.
I don't see security stopping you
on campus to see your I.D.
You're all hunky-dory
with your scholarship.
They'll let that harmless black woman
through easier than a man.
-So you think I got it easy?
-Hell, yeah.
-Easier than me.
-You know them girls I stay with?
Every time something comes up missing,
who you think they look at?
-And?
-I feel like fighting.
-I feel like beating people up.
-Why don't you?
It's a waste of time.
lnstead, I fight with this:
And I'm getting mine.
You gotta stop doing this all the time:
And start doing this:
Quit worrying about
what people are thinking.
Yeah, but it still ain't the same.
Listen.
You a woman.
I'm a black man.
You're safe.
I'm a threat, educated or not.
You ain't educated yet.
Crazy!
Hey. Kristen.
-Can we talk?
-Sure. Here?
-Don't put too much lipstick on.
-Why not?
You don't want to look like a tramp.
You'll look desperate.
Here, blot it some.
-Is that better?
-Yeah, yeah. Yeah, like that.
Is that him?
Well, all right, Kristen.
I was getting worried about you.
-Where'd you get these, man?
-A buddy of mine in law enforcement.
Fucking gun-control department.
These guns all suck.
It don't matter as long as
they do the job.
-Do you want a beer?
-Yeah.
Check this out, man.
This is a gun, man.
-Glock 9 mm.
-Shut up.
Pumped gas two years
to buy this. Laser sighting.
Fucking Rambo, man!
No way I can miss.
-This is power.
-Don't point that fucking shit at me!
I know how to handle guns, man.
I been shooting since I was 9.
Don't ever point a gun at me
ever again. You'll be sorry.
Who taught you how to shoot?
-My pa.
-Your pa?
My pa's a survivalist.
Used to kick my ass every day.
He's always talking about
the world coming to an end.
Do you like to hike?
I've never really tried it.
Yeah? You should go.
Around here there's beautiful hills.
I try and go everyday. I was there
this morning. The light was beautiful.
What if there's snakes?
Hey, Monet.
Hey.
-How's it going?
-Cool. You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
-Hi, Taryn.
-Hi, Monet. How you doing?
-See you later.
-Yeah, see you guys later. Bye.
Girl!
I like it that you understand me.
There are things that...
...I don't have to say because...
...you just know how I feel.
That was nice.
I think you're nice.
You're trembling.
Are you afraid?
Yes.
Why?
I won't hurt you.
I don't want you to do anything
that you don't wanna do.
I know.
I want to.
Are you ready?
Just a second.
As a black man in America,
my stress comes from everywhere.
Recognize.
Take a look around you.
Look at this.
Columbus disgusts me.
Fool wasn't nothing but a thief,
mass murderer.
Slaughtered Native Americans, we got a
holiday and a university named for him?
We're supposed to be learning their
westernised thoughts...
...only to learn that in their eyes,
we're lower class. Always.
Class is a state of mind.
History's proven you can be
the smartest, run the fastest...
...they still think we inferior.
What's that shirt, man?
You support the Black Panthers?
-Yeah. And?
-That's reverse racism, man.
1995, coon.
-What?
-Malik, come on--
-Stop.
I'm gonna kick your ass,
whatever ass you got left, fool!
Yeah, all right.
You can run, but you can't hide!
"The sharp separating wall
between master and slave fell.
The Aryan gave up the purity of his
blood and, therefore, he also lost...
... the place in the paradise
he had created for himself.
He became submerged in the
race mixture. He gradually lost--"
What's up, man?
Man, I gotta admit, you've been real
polite about staying out of my way.
But you ain't been honest.
I figure, it ain't what a person say,
it's what they think.
So in my mind...
...you been walking around calling me
a nigger in your head.
Am I right?
-I don't have nothing to say to you.
-I think you do.
Say what you feel.
You think I'm a nigger?
Then be a man and call me one
to my face.
You're just a punk-ass white boy
with a fucked-up haircut.
Bitch.
Fuck!
Fuck you!
You don't fucking scare me!
This is fucked-up.
This is really fucked-up.
What's wrong with you?
I don't give a shit
what you do with your stuff...
...but this is my stuff, man!
-Know how selfish that is?
-What are you gonna do?
Jeez, I don't know. I'm gonna
kick your ass. What does that mean?
Why don't you get your shit
and move out, man?
Excuse me?
Why don't I get my shit and move out?
-You moved in here.
-What are you gonna do?
Look, why don't we just sit down?
Why don't we just fucking
stop this and talk about it?
I don't wanna talk to you.
I don't need to talk.
Don't you know I'm superior to you?
Don't you know I came
from the master race?
-You're nothing. Don't tell me what--
-Get off, crazy motherfucker!
All right, motherfucker?
Go to sleep.
Calm your ass down. Calm down.
What is wrong with you, man?
-What's going on?
-I gotta get out of here.
-Fuck you!
-What the fuck?
You damn Jews and niggers
stick together.
You all work against me,
the pure, white, Christian man.
Don't you know he controls you, nigger?
You ain't nothing without them.
You're nothing!
You're a slave.
I'll take my fucking belt off, man.
I'll make you my fucking monkey.
-Get on the floor.
-Relax.
Get on the floor!
You're not white.
You're Jewish. You're nothing.
You're not me!
What are you gonna do?
Dirty nigger.
Got something to say now?
I'm not fooling.
You got something to say now?
-Jesus Christ! Fucking relax!
-Who's the man now, big man?
Fucking hotshot ape.
You're nothing, Malik! You're nothing!
You're dead. You're dead.
Don't move, fucker.
You're all gonna die.
You're gonna die, monkey!
He had a fucking gun!
A fucking gun!
I'm gonna call secur-- He broke the
phone. We gotta call security.
-I'm gonna get this fool!
-Where are you going?
-Stop. Not so fast.
-Get out of my way.
I'm trying to catch this dude
who just pulled a gun on me!
-Let's see I.D.
-You don't need no I.D.! Out of my way!
No! That's the wrong guy!
That's the wrong guy!
-Who are you?
-Get the fuck out of here!
Charlie, look what I found
in the kid's room.
You believe this?
Do me a favour, will you?
See if you can find a name or a picture
or an I.D. in his room.
You bet.
All right, let's break it up.
Everything is fine now.
What do you mean, " Break it up"?
Look at those white folks there.
You ain't telling them to go.
White boy pull a gun out in his face
and you ask us to break it up?
Y'all got some nerves.
Fuck you! We ain't going nowhere.
If they can stand over there together,
we can stand here together.
Now you go find the asshole
that pulled a gun on this man's face.
Get those kids to move out
so we can clear this area.
Okay, let's go.
Break it up. Come on.
Show's over. Back to your rooms.
Nothing to see here.
What do you think
happened here?
-What's going on?
-I don't know.
It's Malik.
What happened?
-He doesn't feel like talking now.
-Can I help?
What's that all about?
I don't know.
Hey, man. Malik, wait up.
What's up, man?
Why'd you move all your stuff out?
I'm staying with some homies now.
I thought you and David
might want to live together.
David doesn't even know
if he's going to school next semester.
He's all depressed. His parents
have him going to a shrink.
-I think he's lost it, myself.
-Listen, Wayne.
I think you're cool, man.
We ain't never had no beef,
outside of your dirty clothes...
...and opposite taste in music.
But I'm just--
I'm at the point where...
...l feel safer and more comfortable
with my own people.
I ain't come here to have
no white boy pull a gun in my face.
I could have got that in the ghetto.
Seems like this system is setup
towards maintaining white supremacy.
I didn't come here to learn that--
I understand you're pissed.
But I'm not like that, Malik.
You treat me like I'm Remy.
I'm not like that.
I'm no white supremacist!
Is that what you see?
I'm different.
So are you. You know?
No, I'm not. Neither are you.
That's the problem.
Peace.
What are you two doing
sitting there? Plotting?
Yeah, we're plotting.
Plotting to steal.
To steal what?
-To steal the information. All of it.
-Yeah, but whose information is it?
The more you learn about this system,
the more upset you get.
Oh, my dear Mr. Williams.
Peppermint?
Information is power.
If you don't have the information,
one cannot seize power.
You need to think about
becoming mentally competitive.
Being black does not free you
from being a responsible individual.
But being a responsible individual
don't free you from being black.
-That's right.
-Poor, misguided soul.
You have yet to learn
the rules of this game.
-He will.
-I don't want to.
See, I'm smart enough to know
it's not my game to play.
I'm just a pawn like everybody else.
Used intelligently, a pawn can create
a checkmate, Mr. Williams.
Or become a very
powerful player himself.
Don't you understand?
This is all a game. All of this.
Like basketball, football,
Mr. Big-Time Track Star, a game.
You play it to win.
Because in the real world, no one wants
to hear excuses or empty rhetoric.
They want to know
if you have a plan.
Right.
Mr. Williams, Mr. White,
good afternoon.
All right.
Mr. White?
-You had his class before?
-Yeah, I had his class once.
Maybe twice.
Let's roll.
" Mr. Williams, do you have a plan?
Nobody wants to hear that bullshit."
Somebody's got to do something
about how tense it is.
We can't let the campus go crazy
because of the actions of some psycho.
What do you mean, "we"?
"We" don't have to do anything.
Just because you and I get along
doesn't mean everybody else has to.
Get that "We Are the World"
stuff out of your head...
...'cause it is not gonna happen,
not on this campus.
Hi, here's a flyer for the Peace Fest.
Take a flyer.
Come to the Peace Fest.
-Faggot.
-Suck my ass.
-Fuck.
-Fuck you.
-Fuck me? Why don't you shut up?
-Don't start that.
Why did you drop out of school?
I never really wanted
to go anyway, man.
All's it was was an excuse
to get out of ldaho.
You know?
What's the point? The gooks and
towelheads get the engineering jobs.
Leave the white man in the cold.
Goddamn affirmative action shit. Right?
You really should not have dropped out
of school. You hear me?
We need more people like you
to become doctors, lawyers, engineers.
You listen, you get it together and
you do something for your own people.
Your own country.
If you don't, you ain't nothing
but a race traitor yourself, you hear?
Fuck you, you big-eared faggot!
No, you know what?
You are worse than a fucking nigger!
-What's up?
-Is Malik here?
Yeah. You didn't bring no homies?
Got any sisters?
-What's up?
-You got crazy friends.
What happened?
Skinhead fool who
pulled a gun on me....
I beat him.
I'm the man. I'm God!
Put something cold on it.
-I don't need no ice.
-Put the ice on it!
I had his ass like this:
Why you fighting like some thug?
This is college.
I don't know about that no more.
About to take a semester off,
let the shit cool.
It's about this, nigger! See this?
Yo, it's about this black fist, nigger!
We gonna pound
their motherfucking ass...
...until they give in, motherfucker!
You're gonna drop out.
-Did I say that?
-I see it in your eyes.
I said I'm gonna take me a break.
Look at me!
-Look what they did to my fucking face!
-What's wrong with you?
It's a war, man.
This is the first battle in the war.
I'm telling you, man. Remy's right,
man. It's their gang against our gang.
Fucking Malik.
I'm gonna get him. Fuck him!
Fuck all those fucking niggers.
They're all gonna fucking die.
Fucking Malik's a piece of shit.
It's all right. We're coming back, man.
We're coming back. Niggers, spics,
the fucking mud people, they'll get it.
-Fucking idiots.
-Fuck all those niggers, man!
Hey, yo, trooper.
What's up, man?
What's up with your girl?
She out there looking kinda bugged.
It ain't nothing.
She's just tripping, I guess.
It's all good, though.
Them fools.
They so lucky they called security.
I was fit to kill one of them white
boys. You know what I'm saying?
Whoa, shit!
Fucking white boy.
See how he swole my shit up?
Knuckles all fat and shit.
It's all right, though.
Whipped his ass so bad...
...his stepmom's gonna feel me
for the next three birthdays.
Look what his homeboy did
to your head.
What you talking about? This shit?
He ain't fading nothing over here.
-One ass-whooping, but they still won.
-How you figure that?
Look around you, man.
They own this shit.
They own this couch you sitting on,
them shoes on your feet...
...this building, this school,
this country, you!
We're behind enemy lines, dog.
One beat-down will never compare
to 439 years of captivity. Never.
You don't know shit, freshman.
This is a war. This is the opening
stages of World War lll.
I said, shut the fuck up!
I'm tired of hearing your bullshit. I'm
tired of you trying to rev everybody up.
What are you gonna do, college boy?
And you don't even got your GED.
-Two fucking dumb-asses together.
-I'm gonna make war.
That's right, man. A race war.
-On who?
-On the fucking niggers.
On the fucking race traitors.
On the fucking everybody.
Why you testing me?
Remy, you ever shot somebody before?
Actually, better yet,
you ever shoot a piece of meat?
Seen what bullets do to flesh?
Them fucking niggers out there,
them fucking little monkeys...
...those gangbangers...
...are training every fucking day
and every night shooting each other.
They're ready for war.
But are you?
If it all went down today...
...which one of you would have
the balls to shoot a nigger?
-I would.
-You would?
Would you?
I have.
-I'd do it.
-Yeah?
That's right. I'd do it.
All right, then.
-What's his problem?
-My fucking head's killing me.
Everybody says things one way,
and you talk to me that way?
This is my blood, man.
It's white blood.
What you got there, Scott?
Go on and kill one of them, man.
Big shot.
-Are you really gonna do it?
-Yeah, he's gonna!
I'll do it.
You do it.
You do this shit, Remy!
Right between the nigger's
fucking eyes!
-I'll do it, man.
-All right, Remy!
Come here. Hey! Hey!
There are many ways to fight a battle.
Different fronts for different people.
Some people use their mind,
some use words...
-...some use fists.
-This is my front.
-For real?
-That's right. This is my front.
-You're full of shit.
-I'm for real.
Go ahead, then.
What is high?
What is higher?
What is learn?
What is learning?
What is higher learning?
What it is?
I mean, what is it?
What is higher learning?
Promise me you won't drop out.
I ain't going nowhere without you.
Viking Two to Viking One.
-Yeah, Viking One.
-Let's do it, man.
I'm gonna kill communication.
This looks suspicious. All right?
For Eurocentric indoctrination...
...is learning in an environment
that is mostly white.
If the Dred Scott decision
was retried in a contemporary court...
... the decision would be the same...
...meaning that a black man
would still have no rights...
... that a white man, by law,
would be bound to respect.
The result would be the same
no matter what the law states...
...because it was not written by and
for the benefit of African-Americans.
The credo
"And liberty and justice for all"...
... is a falsehood that has been widely
ignored and needs to be addressed.
That was great.
Let's give a big round of applause
for Eve's Plum.
The purpose of this gathering
is to bring together everyone...
...so we can have fun
despite our differences...
...whether they be racial,
cultural or sexual.
This is a celebration of the
commonality of these differences.
There are people in this country who
have profited from keeping us apart.
Do you feel better?
I'll feel better tonight.
Shoot, Remy, shoot!
Remy, brother,
you gotta do it now!
Come on, Remy!
Do it for the Aryan Nation!
White power, Remy!
White power!
-I know what that was. Come on.
-It was probably a car.
Shit!
Somebody's got a gun!
Everybody, stay calm.
Don't panic.
Come on!
Why?!
We have to get her to the hospital.
Go get some help, boy!
Mr. Williams?
Mr. Williams, please....
Malik, what are you
standing there for?
You must go now!
Do you hear me, Mr. Williams?
Do you hear me?
White motherfucker!
You're dead!
It's my world. It's my country.
It's my world.
You're nothing but a monkey.
Look at me.
I'm a man. I'm the man.
I'm a man! You're nothing!
-You're nothing! You can't beat me.
-Fuck you.
I fucking hate you!
You gonna die!
She's dead!
I'm gonna kill you!
You're gonna die now!
-You all right?
-Get off me!
Hey, kid. What are you doing, kid?
Take it easy. Come on.
It's gonna be all right. Settle down.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Take it easy. Just relax.
What are you doing? No!
-Don't shoot.
-Get away!
-We can't get back, kid, we can't.
-You wanna shoot me.
No, we don't. Put the gun down.
-Get away from me.
-We're not coming any closer.
-You're lying.
-I'm not. Nobody's hurt yet.
-I'm not lying. Look at my eyes.
Phoney.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. We know. Put it down.
-It's over.
-No.
Don't do this. Put it down.
I wanted to build things.
I wanted to be an engineer.
-You still can.
-Stop lying!
Please, put the gun down. It's okay.
It hurts.
I know.
-It hurts.
-I know, kid. It's okay.
-It's okay.
-It's not.
It is.
This is Columbus University,
a great centre of higher learning.
But the lesson taught here today...
...was one in how good things
can go tragically wrong.
A multicultural peace fest organized
in the interest of campus unity...
...has ended with three people dead.
One of them was a gunman who took his
own life after killing two students.
The mayor...
... is on his way to the campus
as we speak.
University administration
has had nothing whatsoever to say.
Wow. You know what that is?
Remy's fucking dead.
No, man. That's white power.
Yeah, you're right.
White power. White fucking power!
-White power!
-Sieg heil.
What do you think I should do?
What do I think?
You're right.
That's my job.
Man....
Man, I don't know, you know?
Maybe if I hadn't....
It's just....
Man, I don't know what to do.
Mr. Williams...
...in spite of the recent tragedy here,
you have persevered.
You have overcome many obstacles
this semester.
For those reasons,
you have my utmost respect...
...and every confidence...
...that you will make a wise decision
concerning your future.
Got to think.
Got to get my head straight.
I'm gonna go now.
Without struggle,
there is no progress.
Frederick Douglass.
Right.
I lost my girl here.
I feel like this is all my fault.
I helped put this whole thing together.
I'm responsible for all of this.
Oh, God.
Hey.
You can't blame yourself, you know?
My name's Kristen.
Malik.
Nice to meet you.
I seen you around.
Phipps' class, huh?
It's funny we never spoke before.
Yeah.
It's funny.
Well...
...I gotta get going.
-Take care.
-You too.
All right. Give us a big smile now.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org