Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
So how long
were you gonna keep me waiting?
Excuse me?
- I'm dying over there.
- Where?
There, by the Ben Franklin
potato salad pavilion.
I'm sorry.
Are we supposed to know each other?
Definitely. I mean, we're supposed to.
We don't, but we should.
- Ray. Ray Koval.
- Theresa Corrado.
- Nice to meet you.
- Okay.
- Happy Independence Day.
- And to you.
Look, I'm sorry. I don't know if it's the
knee or something, but I'm a little confused.
I thought we were checking each other out.
No. Sorry. Maybe you're drunk.
No, no, no.
If I was drunk, I'd be coming on to you.
That's a relief.
If I was drunk,
I'd be saying how amazing you look...
...and how crazy it is
that you're standing here on your own.
Wow. Are you always like this?
No. I sometimes sound like this,
but this is definitely different.
- What's so different?
- I don't know.
I guess that's what I came over to find out.
You're kidding, right?
I'm dead serious.
Behind me?
He made the turn with us on 6th.
Hey, if this is some kind of game
you guys play to keep things exciting...
I gotta tell you, it's a little sad.
This is no game, Ray.
This is real.
Like I told you, man,
this is old-school espionage.
Moscow rules. Street spies.
How far behind me?
He's about three meters back.
He must have picked us up downtown.
And you know this guy?
I've seen him around.
He's definitely Burkett & Randle.
I keep telling you, man. These people
take soap and shaving cream very seriously.
So I guess that means we're going to plan B.
Let's do it.
- What's he wearing?
- Navy turtleneck, gray jacket.
That was sweet, man.
It's all good. It's all good.
There's no way this guy is working solo,
so if we want to bust you out...
...we're gonna have to make a little noise
up here at the corner.
You wanna box him out of here
or leapfrog? What do you wanna do?
I still think you're messing with me.
Call it, Ray. Box or leapfrog?
Or maybe you just want to find out
if I'm worth the money.
Come on, man.
- Leapfrog.
Jesus!
Watch where you go. It's New York, okay?
Let me help.
Open the eyes!
- Hey, you there?
What are you doing?
Problem.
I thought you were in position.
- I am. I was.
We're two minutes away.
- We're blown.
- What are you talking about?
Reschedule the meet.
No. No can do.
We're blown. Just walk away.
Listen to me. I know what it's like.
New guy on the team, big game...
...you wanna make a good impression.
Hello? Ray?
Remember me?
- Sure. Of course. We...
- Long time, huh?
- Yes!
- Gotcha.
- I'm sorry, I just...
- Just what?
I'm drawing a blank.
- Nice try.
- Excuse me?
A little professional courtesy
would make this a lot less awkward.
- How do I know you?
- How do you know me?
Wow! That's tough.
That's a strong play.
Believe me, I've spent a lot of time
thinking what this would be like...
...where we'd be, what
I'd say, what you'd say.
- But I never thought that you'd...
- I'm terribly sorry.
You really want to go this way?
You clearly have me confused
with someone else.
I don't know.
I mean, I'm not great on names.
I should be. I try.
Faces, I'm definitely better.
Faces, I'm like a B, B minus.
Where I'm good, where I really excel,
people I've slept with.
That's been a traditional area of strength
for me.
Look, seriously,
I don't know who you think I am, but...
You charm me, you seduce me,
you screw me...
...then you drug me
and ransack my hotel room.
And how sick is this? You know, the last
thing I remember before I passed out...
...was how much I liked you.
All right. You don't look crazy...
...which is the only reason
why I'm not screaming...
- For a security guard right now, but...
- I can't believe you're going this way.
Wait. Is this a joke?
Is that what it is?
Do you have any idea how far my ass
was hanging out because of you?
Did I win something?
I woke up the next morning,
I went back to the consul.
I practically crawled over glass
to get a copy of the guest list.
I spent the next 24 hours
trying to figure out...
...if you were working for Mossad,
the Syrians or the Russians.
- And which was it?
- Still working for the CIA?
Okay, I think we're done now.
American Consulate, Dubai,
you and me, Fourth of July, 2003.
Find someone else to bother.
- Red, white and blue margaritas.
- Stay away from me.
I had a knee brace, you had toe rings.
First toe ring I ever saw, by the way.
You follow me, I'll scream.
I took vacation time
to find you! Five years.
And every time I walked
into an evaluation...
- I'm warning you for the last time.
... I was waiting for them...
...to throw your picture
on the screen and say...
"So, Ray, anything you care to tell us
about Dubai?"
- You are harassing me!
- So who the hell are you?
Oh, no. You?
- You're the drop.
- You're my contact?
You're acting like
I owe you an apology.
Knock yourself out.
You were an assignment. You're a big boy.
You knew what you were doing.
I can see it's really been eating at you.
An Ml6 case officer takes a strange girl
from an embassy party...
...back to his hotel room
where he has an unsecured briefcase...
- Full of Egyptian Air Defense codes.
- Did they tell you to sleep with me?
I needed the codes. I thought the less time
I spent with you, the better.
- Oh, Jesus.
- How did you get on this project?
- And you're the mole.
- And who the hell hired you anyway?
- I can't believe it.
- How did you get this job?
I got news for you, okay?
The day I left Ml6...
I had 15 major companies
begging for my services.
Well, I guess you picked wrong.
But you must be used to that.
- You know, I've got a meeting in 12
minutes. - Where's the drop? Hand it over.
- Forget it. I'm not working with you.
- Excuse me?
You think I'm gonna let you
be my contact officer?
- This is way over your head.
- Over my head?
Lady, I worked Yemen, Athens and Cairo.
I've been promoted and decorated
every place I served.
Tell Duke to send someone else.
Listen. I'm sure you know your way
around a shoe store...
...but I did 12 years in the field.
And how long have you been working
for Equikrom?
- Long enough.
- How long?
Three weeks.
Three whole weeks? Like every day?
Well, I've spent the last 14 months
undercover inside Burkett & Randle.
I'm an Assistant Director
of Counterintelligence. I am all the way in.
So let's get this straight.
I'm the asset here. You're a delivery boy.
And the only thing I'm gonna give you
is a message.
Tell Duke I don't ever wanna see you again.
I run field agents for a living.
There's only two ways to do it.
Either you bring them flowers...
...or you hang them by their heels
out of the window.
Now, maybe you're so used to having
your legs in the air you don't realize it...
...but you're upside down, sister.
I own you.
- You've 10 seconds to get your hand off me.
- Or what? You won't be my friend anymore?
I like this gig.
I like the money. I like the hours.
So I'm not going anywhere,
and you're gonna get over it...
...because if you ever mention again
that you don't wanna work with me...
...or that we've met before or that you
think someone else might do a better job...
...if I get replaced
for any reason at all...
I'm gonna call those suckers
over at Burkett & Randle...
...and tell them they have an Equikrom spy
in the heart of their security team.
Be a shame to let the last 14 months
go down the drain, wouldn't it?
So where's my package?
Tell Duke this is the one
he's been waiting for.
- You screw this up, I'll ruin your life.
- I thought you tried that already.
You wanna take one last shot
at that apology?
Okay. Thank you.
What'd she say exactly?
I mean, her exact words.
She said, "Tell Duke
this is the one he's been waiting for. "
Do you wanna do it?
- Go ahead.
Easy. Just...
Just, you know, pull it out.
- Slowly. Slowly, slowly.
- Duke.
All right, go ahead.
Pam, Pam, easy, don't tear it.
Pam, Pam, Pam, Pam, just... Careful.
- For Christ's sake, Duke,
keep your shirt on. - Just...
Do something useful.
Punch up Tully's fingerprints.
Wow. Look at this.
So is this the big one?
- I gotta call Garsik right away.
Yeah.
Come on.
I need a secure line at Equikrom.
- How are you?
- Good. How are you?
Houston.
This was over the weekend.
Who are they?
Researchers at the fragrance lab down there,
when they're not dealing ecstasy.
Track it.
West Coast Market Coordinator
of the Floor Wax Division.
Came back from lunch on Friday,
handed in his resignation.
- Unexpected?
- Very.
Three kids in private school,
he just remortgaged his house...
- And the wife has a heart condition.
- All right.
Well, get his financials, phone, e-mail,
and get the wife's prognosis.
Senior V.P., Medical Disposables.
He called in Sunday...
...lost his laptop in the Denver Airport.
Why does this guy look familiar?
He had a briefcase
full of sales projections stolen last year.
- Is this the guy who bought the boat?
- Same guy.
- All right. Get a team up his ass tonight.
- I sent them this morning.
We're in a meeting.
Now? Everyone?
Well, did they say why?
It's Tully. Mr. Tully's coming down.
He wants the entire floor gathered
in five minutes.
Dick, it's just that you have
a very busy schedule today.
Yeah, well, something's come up.
There's the dandruff shampoo
marketing presentation at 3:00.
- Cancel.
- They're in the building.
Make it tomorrow.
The nail polish R&D group from Germany
is at 3:45.
Reschedule.
You've got a premium
diaper teleconference...
- At 4:15.
- Tape it.
The nasal decongestant
rebranding numbers are in.
- They wanted 15 minutes at around...
- Cancel!
And the toothpaste. And the car wax dinner.
Cancel it all.
All right, let's have a look at me.
There should be another vehicle.
Yeah. Change of plans.
You're going with them.
Everybody's going. Let's go, come on.
Get out there and sell it, folks!
Go, go, go! Come on!
Get the hell out of here!
Get out! Leave it running.
Leave it running. I'm driving.
This is starting to look pretty good.
I can't even tell them apart.
Which one is the new one?
Right here.
- This is 16.
- That's a match.
Boris, handwriting?
Hundred percent. It's Howard Tully.
All right.
Burkett & Randle, here we come!
Guys?
Duke? I'm locked out. Again.
Yeah, I'm standing right outside.
Of course it's me!
Who the hell else has this number?
Yeah, okay. Duke, you know, for all
the money that I'm spending on this...
...you could've given me a code
that I can remember.
Sir!
What the hell is this?
Why are we here?
We are here today
because the rules have changed.
We're here because the fabric of integrity
has been so abused and mangled...
...that it is little more
than a threadbare memory.
We're here because it's no longer enough
to have the best ideas...
...or the best manufacturing, or the
best pipeline to deliver your product.
"We're here today because we find ourselves
in a world where duplicity and theft...
"are tested daily as replacements
for innovation and perseverance. "
"Tested daily. " What a bunch of crap.
Can you believe this?
This from a guy who bought a dump
so he could go through our garbage.
I believe the history
of all successful endeavors...
...can be reduced to a series
of decisive moments.
"There are moments in the history
of all things...
"where the placement of a single... "
...where the placement of a single molecule
can make the difference...
...between triumph and catastrophe.
I mean, who the hell writes
with a fountain pen anymore?
For Christ's sake.
How fricking pretentious is that?
This room we're in now,
this entire program...
...was created in anticipation
of just such a moment.
You people are the very best at what you do.
You were chosen by that standard.
You've been paid and treated accordingly.
And you have never been tested
as you are about to be tested.
"Burkett & Randle will be rolling out
a new product...
"in the very near future. "
And while I cannot reveal
the nature of this product...
...believe me when I tell you that simply
by announcing its development...
"... B&R will be dramatically repositioned
at the summit of the global marketplace. "
I don't need to explain to anybody
in this room...
...why the scope, the details,
the very existence of this project...
...must be so carefully protected.
I expect your best in days to come...
...and I promise you,
if we stay focused and vigilant...
...we will, all of us...
"... Prosper. "
What the hell does he have over there?
Dick? Dick? Don't go dark on me now.
Dick!
We gotta stay positive. Hey, look around.
This is why we're here.
When you came to me,
that first conversation, this is it.
This is why we built the unit.
- I know what he's doing.
- Dick. Dick!
Look at me.
This is a great team we've got here.
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah. We are so prepped.
We are so ready to deploy.
You say the word,
you unleash the beast, Dick.
- We will tear this thing apart.
- He's just timing the blow, Duke.
- No. Wrong. We caught a break here.
- We caught a break? You call this a break?
I got a shareholders' convention
in nine days.
Hey, man, he's not thinking about that.
Oh!
Are you out of your fricking mind?
That is all that he thinks about.
And believe you me, if he has got a knife,
that is when he's gonna use it...
...because that's what I'd do! Yeah.
No, I would wait till he is right in
the middle of a big old standing ovation.
I would wait till he is just so overwhelmed
with beloved waves of adoration...
...he couldn't even hear the sound
of his own cojones...
...as they hit the goddamn floor!
Oh, my God, he is gonna crush me.
Tell your people not to make vacation plans.
- They're gonna wanna know why.
- Then they're in the wrong business.
How are we supposed to work it up
if we don't know what we're protecting?
Look, I don't know. Assume it's everything.
B&R's mainframe network is a beast.
I mean, we've spent
the last 10 months probing.
We got nowhere.
I mean, the encryption
and system awareness codes...
...are tactically equivalent
to anything we had at the Pentagon.
The good news is 200 photocopiers
that B&R purchased last month.
We paid a little visit down to the vendor...
...and we made a few adjustments
to one of the units before it shipped.
Call this the Ghost.
It's not fast, it's not easy,
but this device right here...
...allows us to hijack signal traffic...
...without leaving
any electronic residue behind.
Here. Right now we're hacking a photocopier
in their Human Resources Department.
I mean, we're still mapping, but look,
we're tapped into 12 units already.
The B&R Research
and Development Unit in Westchester...
...hasn't brought a major new product
to market since 1997.
In spite of that,
we made it a surveillance priority.
Number one, we graph
the volume of traffic...
...and the quality of vehicles
in that parking lot.
Number two, we track the stock portfolios
and mortgage payments...
...of everybody on site.
And, number three, we monitor
the frequency of Internet shopping...
...and pornography searches
from inside that lab.
Stocks are down, porn is up
and there's plenty of free parking.
There's nothing going on here.
We're confident
that whatever this new product is...
...it comes from outside the company.
The moment this meeting breaks up...
...we'll be going over every acquisition
B&R has made in the past 18 months.
We'll find it.
This B&R building is very strong
with security.
Is the same for us like the computer.
We are all the time feeling our way
around this building...
...but not getting anywhere.
Then we make a big discovery. Travel
Department is not in the big building.
Travel Department is four blocks away
and this building is very different.
- Very simple and very basic.
- Yeah, it's a gold mine, Dick.
They basically handle
all of B&R's commercial travel...
...so every private jet, car, boat, hotel,
housing, everything goes through them.
The boys have got some great ideas
on how to get us on the inside.
Very simple and very basic.
I swear, she was that big.
No, I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding.
Don't start that again. Translate that?
- You're always kidding.
- I'm not. I'm a very serious guy.
I'll be right back.
Hi. Remember me?
- Yes, I...
- Gotcha.
- I'm sorry, I just...
- Just what?
- I'm drawing a blank.
- Don't even try it.
- Excuse me?
- Can I make a suggestion?
A little professional courtesy
would make this a lot less awkward.
- How do I know you?
- How do you know me?
Wow. That's a strong play.
Believe me, I've spent a lot of time
thinking what this would be like...
...where we'd be, what
I'd say, what you'd say...
- But I never thought that you'd...
- I'm sorry. I just...
You really wanna go this way?
Look, you clearly have me confused
with someone else.
I don't know, I'm not great on names.
I should be. I try.
Faces, I'm definitely better.
Faces I'm like a B, B minus.
Where I'm good, where I really excel,
people I've slept with.
That's been a traditional
area of strength for me.
Look, I don't know who
you think I am, but...
You talk me up, seduce me, screw me...
...then you drug me and ransack
my hotel room.
And how sick is this? The last thing
I remember before I passed out...
...was how much I liked you.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I can't...
- What? You think this is funny?
- I... No, I...
No, it's not. I'm sorry. It's just...
It's... Seduce you? You?
- You admit it?
- I...
- I just... No, I'm... No, I'm...
- No, you don't get to do this.
- You do not get to laugh about this.
- It's...
- This is unacceptable.
- No, you're right. You're right.
It's not funny. Seriously. Completely.
- And it's not you. It's not you.
- What the hell does that mean?
It's tension. Nerves.
Nervous laughter, obviously.
Your knee. Wow. All better, huh?
Yeah, with that brace and everything,
you really looked like you were hurting.
My knee is fine. Thanks.
Do you have any idea how far my ass
was hanging out because of you?
- Mmm. I can imagine.
- That's all you say?
And I'm sorry.
I can tell.
It's... I don't know. The laughter. I
don't know what that's about. It's about...
Nerves. Guilt. Lots of guilt. And regret.
Remorse. Just a lot of things.
I mean, I'm assuming you know
by now that I was...
...working for the Agency,
so, yeah, there's that.
- This sucks.
- Yeah.
I mean, we were under
a lot of pressure then.
This is totally unsatisfying.
Well, what did you have in mind?
I mean, in terms of vengeance.
Hey.
What's that?
The reckoning.
Bad?
We've been bad.
How bad?
We've been very bad.
We're very good at it.
Worth it?
Very.
Very worth it.
Oh, my God.
What?
It's...
It's noon. It's 12:15.
What happened to my wake-up call?
I left a wake-up call.
Oh, Jesus! This can't be happening. This
is not the day to not get a wake-up call.
Oh, God! I can't believe I
didn't get my wake-up call.
I had a 10:30 flight.
I'm supposed to be landing
in Geneva right now.
You probably told me all this.
I just don't remember it.
No. I couldn't. It's classified.
Yeah, I was supposed to be in Cairo
two days ago.
- You told me London.
- The point is, I blew it off.
And nobody called this morning?
- You were here.
- I'm a heavy sleeper.
So what are you saying?
I took the call and didn't tell you?
When did you set this up, anyway?
Last night.
Where was I?
In the bath.
- We were in there together.
- When I went for the ice.
While I was waiting?
I can't believe they didn't call.
You snuck out of the tub
to leave a wake-up call!
This is a five-star hotel.
How does that happen?
Welcome to Italy.
Look, I told you it was classified.
I shouldn't have to explain this to you.
Well, this beats the hell out of Dubai.
- What?
- I'm still standing, right?
There. See? There it is.
If you're looking
for Egyptian Air Defense codes...
- I'm keeping them in my socks these days.
- See, I knew it.
You'll never get over that, will you?
You couldn't.
I'm afraid that's classified.
- You actually think, what, I'm playing you?
- That's crazy, right?
This felt like an assignment to you?
Three days? All this?
What was the objective? Rug burn?
Who knows, maybe you didn't want me
in Cairo yesterday.
God, that's so sad.
Because that's exactly
what I was just thinking.
That maybe you're playing me,
that you canceled my call.
That this was just some revenge
to get back at me for Dubai.
Then I'm thinking how terrible it is
that I think that way.
Then I realize we both think that way.
Then I'm thinking...
...is that what makes this so worth it?
Is that it?
That I know you're thinking
exactly what I'm thinking?
Because then I'm thinking, do we both
think like that because of what we do?
Are we good at what we do
because we think like that?
Everybody thinks like that.
They just don't say it.
- Civilians don't think like that.
- Bullshit.
- Nobody trusts anybody. We just cop to it.
- Okay. So cop to it.
- Me? I think you better go first.
- Why? What am I hiding?
This wasn't an accident, was it?
Being here. Meeting like this.
You came looking for me, didn't you?
- You'd like that, wouldn't you?
- I'm right, though, aren't I?
Because you went looking for me, right?
But why? Just for this?
- Isn't that enough?
- Not for you.
What are we into, Claire?
Can you imagine living like this?
- How much fun we could have?
- Aren't we in enough trouble?
I mean, having the money.
- Keep going.
- How much do you think we'd need?
- $20 million?
- I was thinking 40.
So what do you have to do
to get $40 million?
Go private.
Be smart.
Get lucky.
How smart?
Smart enough to pick the right partner.
- Private, you mean...
- Corporate.
And lucky?
Be someplace when something's happening.
Be there first, hear it first.
- Something inside.
- Something big.
- But do it up right.
- Set it deep. Take your time.
Know your way out before you go in.
- You know what I think?
- I think you like the idea.
- I think you missed me.
- I think you canceled my call.
So, we're even.
Yeah, copy that.
Okay, so you hold tight.
No, we're just around the corner from you.
I'll be standing by.
He's moving?
- Yep.
So very simple, very basic, right?
The plan is good. It's up to him.
He's got a great reputation.
Look, Garsik says the sky is falling
in six days.
If you got a better idea, tell me now.
Right. So get to work.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Excuse me.
Look at this. I am so sorry.
Here I am, squeezing around,
making a complete pig of myself.
Look at this. Are you...
I'm fine. Really. It's nothing.
What was it before I got here?
Appletini.
Well, that sounds good. Was it good?
Yes, they're very good. They're great.
We'll have two of those, please.
You coming or going?
Well, I woke up in Knoxville,
I'm supposed to be sleeping in Belgium...
...and here I am in New York
waiting for an Appleteen.
So, I guess I'm just not sure.
- My daddy was from Tennessee.
- You're kidding. Where?
- Western part of the state.
- Where?
Just a little town.
It was actually named after our family.
You're not gonna make me guess, are you?
Bofferd.
- Get out of here!
- What?
- Is this some kind of joke?
- No. Not at all.
I used to go fishing in Bofferd.
I grew up in Darnum, next county over.
Well, that's my name! Bofferd.
Barbara Bofferd. Here, look.
Have a look.
Damn.
Well, it's nice to meet you, Barbara.
I'm Jimmy Tierney.
- You don't seem like a Jimmy.
- Well, actually it's James.
Well, actually, it's Dr. Tierney.
Would you excuse me?
Yeah, did you get them?
Nobody there can help me out?
What, and wait at the airport all night?
That's $26.
No, no, no, no, no, no. It's not your fault.
Okay, yeah. Thanks.
Travel problem?
Yep.
I'm a pediatric cardiologist.
We're opening a clinic in Ethiopia,
and my team's over there waiting for me.
I was supposed to fly to Brussels tonight
and then on to Nairobi...
...but my ticket got scrambled.
So, I got on a flight in the morning...
...but now they're telling me
it's too late to get ticketed now...
...so I'm gonna have to spend the night
at the airport...
...just to make sure I can get on the plane.
Now, all you need is a flight to Brussels
in the morning?
Honey, that's what I do for a living.
We have to be quiet, okay?
No peeking! You're peeking.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Back up.
I want to see that one more time.
Let's get it all in here.
Passport or permit?
Right there! What does it say?
Wait? Over here, or here?
Read this one.
What's that say?
I mean, why aren't we on three terminals?
- I don't understand why we only have two.
How many eyes do you have?
For Christ's sake, Duke!
- You're getting that to go, right?
- Why?
- Didn't you get the text?
- I don't know. I just stepped out.
- Did you read my memo last month?
- Which one?
Vulnerabilities at the travel office.
I don't remember.
See you upstairs.
Okay, so what are we looking at here?
Give me a ballpark figure.
- Around 10, 12 minutes.
- And then what, I get everything?
Six years of travel orders.
- Eight minutes. Eight minutes.
- Great.
All right.
Super job, Ray.
Really. Outstanding.
- Who is this guy?
We're not sure.
Jesus.
Is that the one
where they're on the desk?
Is he an Equikrom agent?
Yeah, if he is, he's new.
We don't have him logged.
We think they're running
some fresh players out there.
Wow. Get this woman over here.
I was thinking I should conduct
the interview at the travel office.
Rattle their cages. See if anybody...
No, I want her over here.
And don't tell her a damn thing.
- I was just thinking...
- And Claire's doing the interview.
- But, Ned, I wrote the memo.
- No.
I want her to talk to a woman.
Okay, assumption A,
Burkett & Randle has a new product.
Assumption B,
they didn't develop it internally.
I agree.
So, we took every company
B&R bought in the last 18 months.
They made 57 acquisitions.
We tossed out anything where the product
was known or already on the market.
- We ended up with...
- Twenty-eight, the 28 companies.
We can't dig deep on any of them.
We don't have time.
So we're scanning for patterns.
Last night, Dale ran a timeline,
and we found a day last March...
...when B&R bought seven companies
in one afternoon.
- Is that normal?
- No.
So they're hiding something.
- What are they hiding?
- I think it's Dunwoody, Georgia.
We just laid the travel office records
over our calendar.
You can't believe
the amount of traffic last summer...
...between New York City
and Dunwoody, Georgia.
Howard Tully made
at least six separate visits...
...none of which were reported
in his official schedule.
So what the hell's down there?
Something called Formavale Labs.
I think we need to get the boys down there
right away.
Where's he going?
It was the way, when he talked
about the children, you know.
Helping the little children
and mending their broken hearts.
And I know, I do,
how I should know better, and I'm not...
I'm really not a gullible person.
But... But the children
and their little hearts...
And... And, yes, I felt special, you know,
that I could help him and the children.
And, yes, he was cute, I'll admit it.
Everything falling out of his pockets,
and charming.
You know, I mean special.
Special, like there was no one
in the world but me.
Hasn't anyone ever made you feel special?
Maybe for you it happens all the time.
Yeah, you probably have someone
making you feel that way all the time.
You know what? I don't even care.
Do whatever you're gonna do.
'Cause you know what?
I loved it!
It was worth it.
It was so very worth it.
It was incredibly worth it.
- Hello?
Hey, it's me.
- You're so early. I just got in.
- I ran.
- It went okay?
- Not a hitch. God, you feel good.
I can't believe you got here so fast.
I'm sorry,
but two months is just too goddamn long.
What? Did you... Did you push
your appointment up? You go in early?
It was fine. There wasn't that much to it.
- You did it, right?
- What?
- You told them.
- Of course.
- And you're okay with it?
- I'd better be, right?
How?
How...
How did you do it? You just...
- You walked in and what, said, "I quit"?
- Basically.
- They must have tried to talk
you out of it. - Not really, no.
Well, they can't be happy to see you go.
It couldn't have been that easy.
What are you trying to tell me?
- You didn't do it, did you?
- Hang on.
There's no way
that they just let you just walk out.
- Wait.
- You just punched out? Just walked out?
No, no, no, no, no. Hang on.
- Answer the question.
- Did they ask you to stay?
- You're ducking the question.
- They did, didn't they?
- This is classic.
- They asked you to stay.
- I know this drill, okay.
- Did you quit or not?
Deny everything. Admit nothing.
- Make counter-accusations.
- That's what you're doing.
I asked you how it went and you evaded!
How it went?
I just terminated a 12-year career with Ml6.
I spent an hour
signing non-disclosure forms...
I did a quick outplacement polygraph,
I turned in my credentials...
...and I walked out
on the only job I've ever really had...
...and now, right now,
I'm getting the very distinct impression...
...that you changed your mind,
kept your job, and left me out in the cold.
They kind of begged me to stay.
And you don't call
to tell me that this morning?
I couldn't risk it.
You're unbelievable.
- I was completely surprised.
- I don't believe this.
I hope you kept your passports.
What am I supposed to do? I can't go back.
You have to turn in a couple
to make it look good, but...
I am totally cooked.
...we're gonna need decent passports.
What are you talking about?
I took everything I could get my hands on.
After they begged me.
You bitch.
Admit it.
You don't trust me, either.
So, the total footprint.
That's if you're interested in both buildings,
'cause they're both available right now.
It's about 22,000 square feet.
The ventilation, it's zoned.
And you've got separate filtration systems
for the lab, office, storage and loading.
- It's lovely and clean.
- Yes, indeed.
The last tenants left the place
in terrific shape. It's just spotless.
What kind of business were they in?
Formavale? Damned if I know.
Some kind of biotech.
They took the place, loaded in their gear
and that's about the last we saw of them.
Hell, they used to truck
out their own trash.
Cronin Partiz. Ronnie Partiz.
Dr. Ronald Partiz.
This is 10 years ago up in Albany.
He's graduating high school,
15 years old in that picture...
...but he's a smart kid.
He gets a free ride to Cornell.
He finds his way
into the biochemistry department.
Two years later, he's in med school.
He's 18, he's doing research
with some heavy hitters...
...he's getting good evaluations,
he's rolling along.
1999, he publishes an article in a magazine
called American Dermatologist.
- About?
- Something about a fungus.
What kind of fungus?
It doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter?
Everything matters.
He plagiarized it. He stole it.
He got caught immediately.
They bounced him out of Cornell.
He set up shop in his parents' garage...
...started working on
some kind of skin cream.
Yeah, something called...
- What?
Spring Skin.
He tried to sell it to health food stores
in the area up there.
Now, you're sure this is a cream
or was it a lotion?
- Because a lot of people confuse the two.
- I don't know.
Well, for Christ's sake, Duke, let's
have that! Let's have that! I mean, if...
If there is even a chance that this guy
is Tully's secret weapon...
...we're gonna need a hell of a lot more
than his goddamn grade point average!
You gotta get me his cream!
Show me the cream!
Dick, he went bankrupt overnight.
It was a bust, okay.
We don't think the cream
is the answer here.
So, Ronnie Partiz
now goes deep underground.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org