Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I will be truthful and mention
that before our rigid search...
... i had the opinion jewish people
were having shit between their brains.
Primarily, this is because all i knew
of jewish people...
... was that they paid father
very much currency...
... in order to make vacations
from america to ukraine.
I was of the opinion
that the past is past...
... and like all that is not now,
it should remain buried...
... along the side of our memories.
But this was before the commencement
of our very rigid search.
Before i encountered the collector...
... jonathan safran foer.
Your grandfather wanted you
to have this...
...for your collection.
Who is augustine?
Grandma?
Where did you get that hat?
Alex gave it to me.
Take it off.
Why?
Because i told you to, that's why.
I think he looks cool.
Who asked you to speak?
Did i ask you to speak?
Did mama ask you to speak?
Did grandfather ask you to speak?
Shut up!
Don't talk to her like that!
Papa, i already have one son
walking around odessa...
...looking like a raving lunatic.
I don't need another.
But papa...
my legal name is alexander perchov,
but all of my friends dub me alex...
... because this is much more flaccid
to utter.
That is father retrieving his fist
from the right side of my face.
Father is a first-rate puncher.
This is my miniature brother, igor.
I am tutoring him to be a man
of this world.
For an example, i exhibited him
a smutty magazine three days yore.
Why is it called sixty-nine?
I explain it to him that this is
because it was invented in the year 1969.
I know this because my friend grisha knows
a friend of the nephew of the inventor.
What did people do before 1969?
He is a genius, my miniature brother.
He will be made a vip
if i have a thing to do with it.
This is grandfather. Like my father
and myself, he too is dubbed alex.
My grandmother, anna, died two years
before of a cancer in her brain.
Precluding this,
grandfather became very melancholy...
... and also, he says, blind.
His most recent employment
was heritage tours...
... a business he started in 1950s...
... mostly for aiding rich jewish people
to search for their dead families.
It is a strange employment
for grandfather...
... as there is nothing he hates more than
rich jewish people or their dead families.
This is sammy davis jr. Jr.
She is grandfather's seeing eye bitch.
Father purchased her for him not
because he believes grandfather is blind...
... but because a seeing eye bitch
is also a good thing...
... for people who pine for
the opposite of loneliness.
In truth,
father did not purchase her at all...
... but merely retrieved her
from the home for forgetful dogs.
Because of this,
she is not a real seeing eye bitch...
... and is also mentally deranged.
Most of all, she relishes when i sing to her
her most beloved song...
..."billie jean" by michael jackson.
But now i must tell you more of myself.
I am unequivocally tall. I do not know
any women who are taller than me.
The women who are taller than me
are lesbians...
... for whom 1969
was a very momentous year.
For me, america is a first-rate place.
Kangol!!
Most of all, i am beloved
of american movies, muscular cars...
... and hip-hop music.
I also dig negroes.
Most of all, michael jackson.
He is a first-rate dancer, just like me.
Many girls want to be carnal with me
because i'm such a premium dancer.
You're taking a jew
to lutsk this weekend.
- I can't, i have plans.
- What plans?
With grisha at club zephyr.
Well, now you're taking
a jew to lutsk.
But we have vip passes.
Papa, i need you to drive them.
Go to hell!
I'm not driving anyone.
Papa,
they are paying $ 1200 american.
I don't care. I'm retired.
No more dead jews.
Papa, you drive him to this place...
...show him everyone is dead
and you come home.
It will be so simple.
He's looking for a woman
who saved his grandfather from the nazis.
Trust me,
there is no one there anymore.
She is from someplace called...
...trachimbrod.
It's near lutsk.
They said he has a map.
His name is jonathan s. Foer.
He is a writer.
He wants to write a book
about the place.
Okay, i'll go.
But sammy goes too.
Papa, please,
you know that is impossible.
She's demented!
You listen to me.
I'm supposed to be retired.
I am not supposed to
be dragging rich jews...
...all over the goddamn country.
I'm blind. Blind!
Understand?
My bitch is my eyes.
I'm not going anywhere without her.
Papa, i'm not saying
that i don't believe you're blind...
...but the american could have
a problem with this.
No bitch, no driver.
We could make a uniform for her...
...to make her seem more official.
Are you jonfen?
What?
Jonfen. Are you jonfen?
It's jonathan.
What?
My name. It's jonathan.
Jonfen.
Are you my translator?
Yes, i'm alexander perchov.
I'll be your humble translator.
I implore you to forgive my speaking
of english, jonfen...
...as i'm not so premium with it.
My name is jonathan.
This is our driver.
He is an expert at driving.
- Is he all right?
- What?
I mean, you know, is he healthy?
Of course. He's my grandfather.
Please, do not be distressed.
This is only driver's seeing eye bitch.
Okay, she's deranged, but so, so playful.
Wait, he's blind?
No, only he thinks this.
Please, do not be distressed.
Grandfather!
Grandfather, i've got jonfen.
We should go to lutsk.
Yes?
Are you sure he's okay?
- Grandfather!
- Shut up!
I'm blind, not deaf.
I heard you the first time!
What does he say?
He says, "okey-dokey, we will go now."
- Where will the dog be?
- What do you mean?
I have a phobia.
A fear.
I'm distressed by dogs.
He is afraid of dogs.
Bullshit,
no one is afraid of dogs.
Grandfather informs me
this is not possible.
What?
Get in the car.
The bitch and the jew
will share the back seat.
It is big enough for both of them.
No, wait. Wait.
You don't understand.
I have a very serious, serious problem
with dogs.
I can't sit in there. You...
were you able to manufacture the:
- What?
- The z's.
Were you able to make the:
- I don't understand.
- Repose.
Did you repose?
Yeah, i reposed.
Good. Sammy davis jr. Jr.
Is also in repose.
- Why do you call her that?
- What?
Sammy davis jr. Jr.
Because sammy davis jr.
Was grandfather's most beloved singer.
You know, the candy man.
The negro from the rat pack.
- And a jew.
- What?
Yeah, he was a jew.
You didn't know that?
Grandfather, the jew says that
sammy davis jr. Is jewish.
The bitch?
Not jr. Jr., jr. The singer.
That's bullshit!
Grandfather informs me
that this is not possible.
Of course it is. He converted. He's the most
famous black jew in america.
- Please tell me, is the shaq also the jew?
- Who?
- Shaquille o'neal, the los angeles laker.
- No.
- And michael jackson?
- No, definitely not a jew.
Father informs me you are writing a book
about this trip. You are a writer?
No.
Then what is this?
It's a catalog.
Catalog.
I don't know why they told you that.
I'm not a writer.
I mean, i write, but i'm more of...
...a collector, really.
And what do you collect?
Things.
Family things.
It is a good career, yes?
No, it's not a career.
It's just something i do.
Why?
I don't know. Why does anybody
do anything? It's just something to do.
I understand.
I also enjoy writing...
...but i truly feel i was born
to be accountant.
Are we close?
The jew wants to know
if we are close.
Tell him to shut the hell up!
Grandfather says we're very proximal.
He says it will not be long
until we get to the superway to lutsk.
And from there?
How long from here to lutsk?
Perhaps you would like me
to stop the car...
...and you two can
fuck yourselves to lutsk!
What did he say?
Grandfather says you should look out
the window at the premium countryside.
- Are you hungry?
- Yes.
- I just hope they have something i can eat.
- What do you mean?
I'm a vegetarian.
You're a what?
I don't eat meat.
How can you not eat meat?
I just don't.
He says he does not eat meat.
What?
- No meat?
- No meat.
- Steak?
- No.
- Chickens?
And what about the sausage?
No, no sausage. No meat.
He says he does not eat any meat.
Not even sausage?
I know.
What is wrong with him?
What is wrong with you?
Nothing. I just don't eat meat.
Hello.
Excuse me,
do you have anything without meat?
Why?
Our friend here is american...
i can see that.
Yes, of course,
but he does not eat meat.
What is wrong with him?
What did she say?
She says they do not have anything
without meat.
Don't they have potatoes or something?
Potatoes?
You only get
potato with the meat.
The potatoes come only with the meat.
But can't i have a potato
on a plate by itself?
Please, this american is deranged.
Would it be possible to have
a potato without the meat?
Welcome to ukraine.
- And these are your family?
- Yeah.
My grandmother gave me this.
That's my grandfather, safran.
It was taken during the war.
It's you.
I've heard that.
- And this is augustine?
- Yeah.
My mother said that he never would have
made it to america if it weren't for her.
And she's from trachimbrod?
Or somewhere near there.
This is kolki. My grandmother's shtetl.
"Shtetl"?
It's a village.
It's yiddish, it means "village."
It doesn't seem to be far from trachimbrod.
That's why i was thinking
it might be called sofiewka now.
Why do you make such a rigid search?
I guess i just wanted to see
where my grandfather grew up...
...where i would be now
if he hadn't come to america.
You would be ukrainian, like me.
Only not like me, because you would be
a farmer from some unimpressive town...
...and i am from odessa.
- I see.
And did your grandparents ever return
to ukraine?
God, no. My grandmother would go crazy
if she knew i was here.
Why?
She didn't think it was safe.
She said that before the war,
ukraine was just as bad as berlin.
Jews weren't exactly popular in ukraine.
When the nazis invaded, she actually
thought it would be an improvement.
Who told you this?
My grandmother.
Why did she say this?
I don't know. It's just how she felt.
Grandfather...
...he says ukrainians were
anti-semitic before the war.
Is it true?
Grandfather?
It's nice.
Really, it's just for sleeping.
- Jonfen?
- Yeah.
You were very proximal
with your grandfather, yes?
Yeah. Why?
Tomorrow we will make a search.
Good night.
Make sure to secure the door
when i am gone.
I do not want
to make you petrified person...
...but there are many dangerous people
who want to take things from americans...
...and also kidnap them. Okay?
Okay.
Good night.
Sammy davis jr. Jr.
Come on, let's go.
He seems like a good person.
Yes, he does.
We should try to help him.
How?
We should try to find her.
Who?
Augustine.
- What is it?
- Soviets.
What happened?
Independence.
Look.
We are looking for trachimbrod.
Do you know it?
You heard of trachimbrod?
Never heard of it!
Come here, please!
Come here!
It's a small village...
...trachimbrod.
Mention the other names to him.
Perhaps one will sound informal.
Kovel', kivertsy, sokirentsy.
Maybe kolki?
Yes, yes.
Could you direct us to them?
Of course.
They are not so far.
Go north on the superway.
Keep going north...
...until you see wheat fields...
...then head east
through the farmlands.
Thank you.
Here. Thank you.
- What is he doing?
- What are you doing?
- For helping us.
- What?
- I read in my guidebook...
...you can't find
marlboro cigarettes here...
...so you should take them everywhere
as tips.
He doesn't eat meat.
Thank you.
What is "tips"?
Tips are something you give someone
in exchange for help.
You are informed you will be paying
for this trip with currency, yes?
No, not like that. Tips are for small things,
like directions or the valet.
- Valet?
- You know, the guy who parks your car.
Why do you not park your own car?
How much currency would
a first-rate accountant receive in america?
I don't know.
A lot, probably, if he or she is good.
She?
Or he.
Are there negro accountants?
Yes, there are african-american
accountants...
...but you don't want to use that word.
- And homosexual accountants?
There are homosexual everythings.
There are homosexual garbage men.
And how much currency would
negro homosexual accountant receive?
You shouldn't use that word.
- Which word?
- The n-word.
- It's not the n-word, but...
- negro?
Yeah, that one.
But i dig them all the way.
They are premium people.
It's that word, though.
You're not supposed to use that word.
What is wrong with the negroes?
- Are you carnal very often?
- What?
With american girls, you make sex often?
Not really. Do you?
I inquired headmost. Do you?
Not really.
What do you intend by "not really"?
I'm not a priest,
but i'm not john holmes, either.
I've heard of this john holmes.
With a premium penis.
Yeah, that's the one.
In the ukraine,
everybody has a penis like that.
What about the women?
You make a joke, no?
Yeah.
Come, zlata, come.
Do you have any chewing gum?
Do you know where trachimbrod is?
What's in trachimbrod?
Nothing, it's just a place
we are trying to find.
If there's nothing there,
why are you trying to find it?
Why do you ask stupid questions?
Where are we?
I don't know.
Ask the jew.
- Where are we?
- I'm not sure.
He doesn't know.
What do you mean, he doesn't know?
We're driving! How can he not know!
- What do you mean, you don't know?
- None of the roads have names.
I thought you were a certified guide.
Grandfather is certified.
- Please, you're making this impossible.
- Shut up!
This is pointless!
We don't know where we are.
"Shut up" means shut up!
Grandfather, we should stop.
What are you doing?
Maybe we should stop and ask someone.
Go and ask them.
Leave the jew here.
I'm not a moron, you know.
I know what that word means.
What word?
It's russian for "jew," isn't it?
Wait! I'm coming too.
- What are you doing?
- I'm coming with you.
- You should not do this.
- Why not? I can help.
You cannot help. You cannot even speak.
It is bad enough that i am from odessa.
I won't speak.
I promise, i won't say a word.
Excuse me, could you tell me,
do you know where trachimbrod is?
Never heard of it.
Thank you.
Wait! What are you doing?
They do not know.
What about sofiewka?
Did you ask them about sofiewka?
I'm sorry, i forgot,
it's also called sofiewka.
What do you want?
I told you i never heard of it!
What's your problem, huh?
Maybe you've seen this woman?
What are you doing?
We are trying to find
the town of trachimbrod.
I told you, we don't know.
Do you want a marlboro cigarette?
Get lost! Go back to kiev!
I'm not from kiev,
i'm from odessa.
Then go back to odessa!
- What did they say?
- Nothing.
They said nothing.
Hey, odessa! You forgot your dog!
Sammy davis jr. Jr., come here!
Hey! Don't do that!
Why were you speaking english?
I commanded you not to speak!
You understanded me, yes?
- Yes.
- Then why did you speak?
- I don't know.
- Now they all think...
...l'm stupid american tourist, like you!
- I'm sorry.
- Why do you not listen?
This is not your country!
You little piece of shit!
Don't you put your
filthy hands on her!
If you ever hit her again...
...i swear to god,
i'll cut your hands off!
Do you understand,
you piece of shit?
Grandfather?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org