Operator. May I help you?
Operator, I've been trying
to get 555-8129. 212?
- Recording says it's been disconnected.
- Just a moment, please.
I'm sorry, the number's been
changed to an unlisted number.
Operator, this is a real emergency.
You need to give me that number.
I'm sorry. We're not allowed
to give out that information.
- Well, fuck you!
- My place or yours?
- I like it. I like it a lot.
- Well, we've been very happy here.
I'd definitely like
to think about it, if I could.
- It's so clean.
- Yes.
We have a cleaning lady who comes in
a couple times a week.
- I can certainly give you her name.
- I'd love that.
And there's baby-sitters galore.
The whole works.
Whatever information you would need.
You know, they have...
Hi, darling.
Darling, this is Alex.
- I've forgotten your last name.
- Alex Forest.
Hi. Glad to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Haven't we met somewhere before?
I don't think so, no.
We have.
Weren't you at that party...
at the Japanese place
a few weeks ago?
Honey, the exercise book.
Oh, yeah.
You're a lawyer and you work
for the firm of...
What's the name?
Well, anyway, we've definitely met.
Well, you have a good memory.
I never forget a face.
It's a small world.
It certainly is.
So, I gather
you're going to the country?
- Moving to the country?
- Yes.
- Have you found a place yet?
- We found a place in Bedford.
- Do you know it up there?
- Oh, it's beautiful, yes.
I guess you'll be moving
out of here almost immediately?
Actually, we wanted to do
some remodeling first.
I guess you're looking for a place
right away, aren't you?
Well, yeah,
I'd kind of like to settle in.
Alex is expecting a baby.
Oh, that's...
Will you excuse me?
I have some work I've got to do.
I better run too.
Thank you for the tea
and showing me the apartment.
- You're very welcome.
- I like it.
- I really like it.
- We've been very happy here.
I'd like to think about it,
if I could.
Let me give you our number
so you can call us direct.
Thank you.
- I'll keep in touch.
- Great.
- Bye-bye.
- Good-bye.
She seemed really interested.
It's funny.
She didn't mention a husband.
I get the feeling
that she's on her own.
- What is it? You seem down.
- No, I'm just tired.
- Hello?
- Hi, it's me.
Who?
You know damn well who it is.
Let me in. I wanna talk.
So now you wanna talk?
So, what can I get you?
I've got scotch, vodka.
- I've got a nice chablis...
- Cut the shit, will you?
Just cut it!
I don't know what you're up to...
but I'm gonna tell you
it's gonna stop right now.
No, it's not gonna stop.
It's gonna go on and on...
until you face up
to your responsibilities.
What responsibilities?
I'm pregnant.
I'm going to have our child.
That's your choice, honey.
That has nothing to do with me.
I just wanna be
a part of your life.
This is the way you do it, huh?
Showing up at my apartment?
What am I supposed to do?
You won't answer my calls.
You change your number.
I'm not going to be ignored!
You don't get it.
You just... You don't get it.
Don't you remember our weekend?
I mean, wasn't that wonderful?
Why can't we just
be like that again?
I know you feel it too.
I mean, what are you so afraid of?
Hey, don't flatter yourself.
Go ahead, hit me.
If you can't fuck me, just hit me.
You're so sad. Do you know that?
You're lonely and very sad.
Don't you ever pity me,
you smug bastard.
I'll pity you,
because you're sick.
Why? Because I won't allow you
to treat me like some slut...
you can just bang a couple times
and throw in the garbage?
I'm gonna be
the mother of your child.
I want a little respect.
You want respect?
- Respect.
- What are you doing?
Please don't go.
I didn't mean it. I'm sorry.
I'll tell your wife.
You tell my wife, I'll kill you.
It only takes a phone call!
Hello? Hello?
Guys, that's on the second door
to the left all the way in the landing.
Thank you.
You could have stayed
in the apartment.
Dan was in such a hurry
to get out of New York.
Mama, that's you, isn't it?
Oh, Lord, put it away.
All right, easy on that door frame.
Nice, nice.
Just like a glove.
I got it. Sorry.
Hello? Martha.
It's Martha.
Hi, honey. How you doing?
Did the plumber come yet?
Did he ever.
I don't really wanna know about it.
Guess what I'm looking at.
- You got it?
- Yeah, I got it right here.
Or I should say, I got her.
What's she like?
Well, she's cute.
She looks like a rabbit.
She's white, long ears,
little pink eyes.
Ellen doesn't know
anything about it?
No, she doesn't think
she's gonna get one.
See what happens if
you work here too long, Eunice?
- Isn't she cute.
- Thank you.
Oh, I forgot.
This arrived for you.
- Good night, Eunice.
- Good night, Mr. Gallagher.
Hey, Joaquin!
Jesus fucking Christ!
Fucking bitch!
Jesus Christ.
It had something to do
with the electrical system.
The whole goddamn thing blew up.
A lot of smoke.
All right, honey,
I'll see you in a little while.
Mr. Gallagher?
You forgot your contract.
Hello, Dan.
Are you surprised?
This is what you've reduced me to.
I guess you thought
you'd get away with it.
Well, you can't.
Because part of you
is growing inside of me...
and that's a fact, Dan,
and you'd better start...
learning how to deal with it.
'Cause, you know, I feel you.
I taste you.
I think you.
I touch you.
Can you understand?
Can you?
I'm just asking you...
to acknowledge
your responsibilities.
Is that so bad?
I don't think so.
I don't think it's unreasonable.
And, you know,
another thing is that...
you thought you could just
walk into my life...
and turn it upside down...
without a thought
for anyone but yourself.
You know what you are, Dan?
You're a cock-sucking
son of a bitch.
I hate you. I bet
you don't even like girls, do you?
You flaming, fucking faggot.
Daddy! Thank you!
Like it?
You thought you could just
walk into my life...
and turn it upside down...
without a thought
for anyone but yourself.
You know what you are, Dan?
You're a cock-sucking
son of a bitch.
You are.
I bet you don't
even like girls, do you?
They probably scare you.
I know I do.
So you're scared of me, aren't you?
You're fucking frightened of me.
You're afraid.
You're afraid, aren't you?
You gutless, heartless...
spineless fucking son of a bitch.
I hate you.
You deserve everything you get...
Sorry.
I was wondering what you
were doing up so late.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
It's okay. I was just listening
to a deposition and couldn't sleep.
Come on.
I'm gonna give you a back rub.
- A back rub?
- Brandy, a back rub.
You won't know what hit you.
Sounds good.
My client wants it stopped.
Hejust wants an end
to the harassment.
He's positive it was this woman
who trashed the car?
Yes, of course.
- Any witnesses?
- No.
He's welcome to file a complaint,
if it'd make him feel better.
There's not a lot you can do
without proof.
Look, Lieutenant, this woman
is completely irrational.
There's no telling
what she could do.
We can't go around arresting people
for what they might do. You know that.
I'm not asking you to arrest her.
He simply...
He wants her warned.
Well, we could talk to her.
It may make things public.
He's not gonna like that.
It may even aggravate
the situation with the girl.
How's that?
Whatever resentment she's feeling,
she probably got it out of her system.
And any action we take
could provoke her.
What if she didn't get it
out of her system? What then?
You have to catch her in the act.
Then we can bring charges.
Well, you say he just has to
sit there and take it?
It's his bed. Afraid
he's gonna have to lie in it.
Come on.
Come on, Ellen.
We're going to Grandma's.
Come on, Quince.
Quincy, come on. Hurry up.
Come on. Get on in.
Hurry up.
Watch his tail, sweetie.
Make him sit down.
See you didn't get your car back.
No, it's a total write-off.
The electrical system's just shot.
Extraordinary, those foreign cars.
- Here you are, dear.
- Oh, thank you.
- Wanna try again, sweetie?
- Okay.
Okay. So?
Dear Priscilla, Miles asked me
to ask you to marry him.
Very good.
You wanna do it one more time.
Do it with your hat and do the bow.
So when you actually do it,
you know what you're doing.
Let me see your bow.
And what do you say?
Dear Priscilla, Miles asked me
to ask you to marry him.
Very good.
Come here.
That was good.
- Thank you.
- That was really good.
That was so good.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Thank you, darling.
Come on, Quincy.
Daddy!
What?
Whitey's gone!
It's all right, darling.
It's gonna be okay, sweetie.
You should try to get some sleep.
- She okay?
- She's asleep.
- Did you call the police?
- Not yet, no.
Why not?
Honey, we gotta talk.
What is it?
I know who did this.
You do?
Who?
Remember the girl who...
came to the apartment?
The one I met
in the Japanese restaurant?
The one with the blond hair.
You're scaring me.
What is it?
Did you have an affair with her?
Yes.
I am so sorry.
The last thing I ever wanted to do
was to hurt you.
Are you in love with her?
No, it was one night.
It didn't mean anything.
What has it got to do
with what's happened?
She's pregnant.
She's... It's yours?
I don't know. That's what she says.
Honey, listen to me.
Get out!
I want you out of here!
I want you out of this house,
and I want you out now!
How could you do this?
I hate you!
- Honey, you don't understand.
- I don't wanna hear it!
- Please, just listen to me.
Please, please, listen.
What is the matter with you?
Dan. What a pleasant surprise.
It's over, Alex. It's all finished.
I told Beth. She knows all about it.
Sure.
You haven't got the balls.
Why don't you speak to her.
Why would I wanna talk to her?
This is Beth Gallagher.
If you ever come near my family again,
I'll kill you. You understand?
That's the last one.
I mean it.
Hello?
Hi, Daddy.
When are you coming home?
Honey, I don't know.
How are you doing?
Good.
Grandpa taught me a new card trick.
Oh, did he?
The one with the jacks?
No, the one with kings.
Good.
I won't.
How's Mommy?
Send her my love?
Okay. Good-bye.
Daddy?
Call me tomorrow.
I will. I promise.
You be sure
you tell Mommy I called?
I will.
Love you a lot too.
Hi, Mrs. Gallagher.
Did you forget something?
- I came to get Ellen.
- Ellen?
I thought you picked her up already.
Well, I'm sure
she's left already.
Betty, is Ellen in here with you?
- She's gone home already.
- Are you sure?
I'm positive. She's not inside
and she's not in the playground.
- I thought you picked her up.
- Who did pick her up?
Don't worry.
She can't have gone far.
- You don't understand.
- I'll check her locker.
Alicia, where's Ellen?
She's gone.
Call the police!
Please let her be all right.
Please.
Oh, Christ.
Where are you?
- Bye-bye, Ellen.
- Bye.
Can I have a kiss?
Excuse me. I'm looking
for a patient named Gallagher.
I'm her husband.
Room 22 at the end of the corridor.
- Is she gonna be okay?
- Yeah, she'll be fine.
She was very lucky.
It might've been a lot worse.
Thank you.
Hi, baby.
Oh, God, I missed you.
I missed you, honey.
Are you okay?
Did you see Mommy yet?
- Yeah.
- Oh, good.
You stay here with Granny.
I'm gonna go see Mommy.
You're gonna be okay.
I came in before.
I tried to explain the situation.
You didn't wanna listen to me.
Now, the woman took my kid.
That's kidnapping, right?
Am I right?
My wife's in the hospital.
She could've been killed.
- If you're not gonna do something...
- Take it easy. You don't have to shout.
Okay, what are you gonna do?
We'll tell New York to pick her up
and bring her in for questioning.
Okay, then I'm...
I'm gonna go to the hospital
tomorrow, pick my wife up.
And hopefully...
I'll be home for the weekend
if you need to talk to me.
Thank you, Lieutenant.
You're welcome.
How's that feel?
Good and warm?
- You all cozy?
- Is Mommy gonna be all right?
Mommy's gonna be fine, honey.
She's gonna be fine.
Are you going to stay with us?
I'm gonna stay with you, honey.
Now, you go to sleep, okay?
Good night, doll.
Forever?
I promise, honey.
You mean the detectives in Manhattan
have no idea where she's gone?
They don't know where she is?
No, I see.
If you get any more information,
be sure and let me know, Lieutenant.
Thank you very much, sir.
Good night.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
- How does the arm feel?
- It hurts.
I'll get you some more painkillers.
Thanks.
Now, you just holler if
you need anything else, all right?
I'd love a cup of tea.
You got it.
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
He tried...
to say good-bye to me last night.
But he couldn't because...
he and I feel
the same way about each other.
Do you know how it is when you
meet somebody for the first time?
And you get this instant attraction.
And don't you think
I understand what you're doing?
You're trying to move him
into the country...
and you're keeping him
away from me.
And you're playing happy family.
Aren't you?
You wouldn't understand that
because you're so selfish.
He told me about you.
He was very honest.
If you weren't so stupid,
you'd know that.
But you're so stupid.
You're a stupid, selfish bitch!