Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Felon
You have not touched your cereal yet.
Are you not hungry?
What is there for today?
We must give the meal service
the last check.
decoration of the church and I must
see what clothing.
I told them what he wanted ...
- ¿Cuánto?
$ 650.
- Do you $ 650? It's a lot of money.
Come here.
What do you think of that? ¿Estás insurance?
- Yes.
The man said that you do.
- ¿De truth?
It is a wedding dress.
And I want to see you well.
And the groom as well.
Thank you.
What we have 4/ 30?
- On why we Wade.
Come boys,
time to recover.
¿Nena?
- Dime.
We have the loan for the business.
- Do not tell me. ¿Estás playing?
That's great.
- I have to find 5more men.
I have to form a second team
of 30men.
I'm so proud of you my love.
You've built the entire business.
- No, we did.
There is someone in the house.
Let's look for Mickey,
do not say anything.
Stay close to me.
Everything is fine.
Stay in this room.
¿Wade?
Stand, ¡ What are you doing?!
- Backs.
¡ I said to you!
Devils.
What is happening Wade?
-- ¡ Stay at home!
¡ Stay at home!
My God.
I will call 911Wade.
¿Podemos lead to child
to bed?
We did not find any weapons
nowhere.
He had his wallet in his hand,
perhaps you thought ...
No, what I saw was that he was looking
something I thought was a gun or a weapon.
I told him to stop and not
is vires.
So went the bat
the shoulder and fell.
Look, if I was at home when it happened
and was armed at least ....
We can make a case
for self-defense.
The problem is that it was no longer
a threat when he left the house.
And he chased out with a bat
and killed him in a coup.
Wait a moment, please.
I did not want ...
Sorry, we will arrest him
for murder.
¿Asesinato?
¿Están crazy?
The rate was robbing us.
I was in a room with my child.
Mrs., I understand.
- What was supposed to make Wade ...
Wait for the kind he fired first.
No, what we had to do was stay
inside and call 911.
Look at the wall hands on their heads.
¿Alguna membership?
- No.
Press this button in case
emergency.
I have you son of a whore.
You were you son of a whore.
Son of a bitch.
¿Quieres Jodo?
You are going to have to clean it.
Fighting in the courtroom.
¡ Leave go!
Cloudy place.
Suélteme.
Did nothing.
You're dead son of a whore.
You're more than dead.
Central Prison for men.
¿Estás long?
Do not you are a skinhead?
We draw on Wednesdays and Saturdays.
You must look after your bones.
Time in prison:
one day.
Hello.
- Hello.
What happened in your face?
- I attacked.
We need to talk to someone.
That is not going to help Laura.
¿Tú you all right?
How is Mickey?
It frightened. Just a question
and you do not know what more to say.
I told him that departure.
If it does not help me stay with my mother.
Grandioso.
- I do not feel safe at home.
Everything will be fine.
I promise you.
I have to help you out of here.
I will put to a public attorney.
Let me see what I said.
Mara and what I am going to represent.
Taste-in know it.
For mere formality put a bond
one million dollars.
If you have a million dollars
can afford it now.
No, I do not have.
- ¿Alguien that can help?
¿Sus parents?
- Died 9years ago.
I will do what it can
for out of this.
State Prison
San Quentin.
Come inside.
Do not breathe smoke.
¿Dijeron why the mutiny?
- No, we all calm.
With John there is always a reason.
You destroy ...
Do not you stop advertising?
- I know Gordon.
Just looking for entertainment.
We are talking about business John.
They want to let you in the hole forever.
And both do not want that.
had been 26years yesterday.
¿De that is what all this?
You have to stop living in the past John.
- I am the past.
I wish you were a dead man
walk instead of get in these walls.
They're gonna transfer to start over;
but after that there are no more favors.
¿Me understand?
I think it's another place Gordon,
maybe not.
Only portate bien, ¿lo you do?
What the hell is going on?
The hearing should have been premilinar
Indeed weeks.
I need more time to
build the case.
But you have good news.
The prosecutor has agreed to make a deal.
Wait, what does that mean?
What you pleaded guilty to
reduce the sentence.
means that you still have two
years and start to comply immediately.
If not for you just dilo.
Already have completed 97days,
you would just 15months.
What other options do I have?
- We are going to trial with a jury.
You can take a year and you get processed
for second-degree murder.
You can give 15years to life imprisonment.
Look, accepts the deal.
It's the best offer.
His señoría the defendant is considered
guilty of murder, involuntary.
We legacy to the agreement of 3years
sentencing in a state prison,
The 97days that Mr. Porter has fulfilled
in the county jail ...
will be taken into account.
Mr. Porter understands that this conviction can
be used against them for violations or convictions
that will result in additional time it add
his judgement.
Yes, your señoría.
¿Entiende which will be punishable by bear
Firearms and during his sentence
Three years can not
vote or leave the country without permission.
¿Entiende terms?
- Yes its señoría.
Then Mr. Porter will meet
3years in state prison
and have already served 97days.
Good luck.
Partner, we must change the cursed house.
This place is like.
My name is Jake but
I say Snowman.
How your name?
- Wade.
¿Wade? Watch the one there.
The kind of mustache.
Is Dennis Samson.
Do not you want to stick with him.
It should be locked up while ago,
but the mad dog is a genius.
Fly under the radar with
like a bird.
Neither cards, or passes, nothing.
The police did not find anything.
- ¿Cuál is the plan?
You and I are brothers,
you better decide quickly.
¿A what time is this game?
- At 5.
What are you doing?
- Escondido that Santos.
He wants to fight with me
but it's a girl.
¿Cuál? ¿La white?
She is great.
- Yes, it is huge.
Well, the flames and tell that you will not peel
and endpoint.
Just leave it.
Failing that, you know
you give a kick.
Come on, and salt here.
Come on.
See you later.
Recalls that the weak are the
they can not avoid problems.
I know Dad.
- Okay, we are after.
¿Y why these here?
I had a fight in the county
and made a deal with the prosecutor.
That's shit partner.
Everything is being very dirty.
Find someone who protects you.
Become a favor.
When lowering the courtyard ...
looking for your race and stay away
the cursed monkeys.
It is going to start.
- What?
We have a great fight
at the bottom of the bus.
There are many convicts involved
there is a wounded.
You put something on the seat did not say anything.
- What are you doing?
¡ Sit down and Callens now!
Stay seated ¡
and silent!
Or putting together a disaster in this bus in which
committed a crime.
Is Dennis Samson, put the other in
the gap until we finish.
¡ Bájenlos bus!
¡ Get out of the bus!
¡ Vamos! ¡ Get out!
It was not my weapon, I swear.
- Let shit.
I was in my seat.
Administrative segregation.
¡ Oh my God!
¡ Listen! ¡ Guard!
Shit.
Guard, please.
¡ A telephone call evil!
A call evil.
Shit.
Please God ...
¡ should not even be here!
Raise your head above the ground.
Look at the eyes when you speak.
We know that the man did not apuñaleaste
in the dime who did it.
I do not know.
I found the gun under my seat.
Someone must have left
on the floor.
¡ Lie!
We know that Dennis was Samson, admit.
If you already know, ¿para do I need?
- Son of a bitch, you will ...
Come on.
hole-in until you're old!
¿Me hear?
- Wait a moment.
Let me tell you that piece
shit you're covering.
You think you will love this
or that will give you some protection.
He is a murderer does not care a bledo
someone like you.
Look what they did to one of their own race ...
Do not you have anything. ¡ Look at me!
When the time comes,
you kill to protect themselves.
The man she apuñalearon
is in a critical condition.
If he dies going down
an accomplice to murder.
I do not know guys,
I do not know what I feel.
It has no case.
- Leave.
Porter Congratulations, you're going to Shu (solitary).
My evil house.
Come on.
We bitch.
Pegale hard.
Opens section 80.
Security Unit.
- Start.
Welcome home.
Watch that you're lucky.
- Go to the wall.
Open 13
Do not you move you have a gun in your head.
Move to the right, falls.
- Close the 13.
Put your hands behind.
You hold a hand and climbs
Foot, ¿entendido?
When you loose the other hand
away from the door, ¿entendiste?
¿Me understand?
- Yes.
Stay away.
One hour a day of yard,
3showers a week.
That's it.
Welcome to Shu.
17, 18, 19.
Time in prison:
111days.
It has a very good record.
He did well, a true example.
The army enseñó me a lot.
¿Ranger?
- Mr Lo lost.
It changed my career in DC.
¿Alguna-action?
See paint dry and when
we look at the fingers.
That is not going to serve in the Shu (solitary).
¿Estamos well then?
Give me a minute with the mayor
and you see it in a few minutes.
Sure.
What you have in mind Bill?
- Give a chance here.
That starts tomorrow.
- ¿Lo put in custody?
No, put it here in the Shu.
It has caused the problem in each house that has been
why in isolation?
I am not looking for a celebrity.
What will other difficult cases.
For this is the Shu.
Yes-Mr.
Porter, your time.
Remove clothes and shoes
and Get to Know the door.
¿Tienes something?
- No.
If you've got hurt.
- Check your fingers through your head.
Open your mouth.
Move the tongue.
He spends his finger on the gums.
Let me see your left ear.
And right now.
Raise your arms.
Pump up the penis.
Virata.
The right foot.
The fingers.
Your left foot.
Listen, I want you to stay on board
three times.
At the third stop.
For. For.
I want to get off three times
when you hear my voice.
In the third you Doblas
and coughs.
Okay.
Dress.
Come on.
As the delay damned.
At the wall.
I-Ya, let me finish.
Apartat.
Open 13.
Come on.
Close the 13.
Close the 44.
Come to the door, now drop your hand.
When you release the other hand
Stay away from the door.
Go to the courtyard.
I told you.
He started the activity.
I'm going with Gonzalez.
Look-action, is a damned son of a whore.
Come on, Dale.
No effort, will fight anyway.
¿Con who are you?
I'm with you lieutenant. Gonzalez.
- ¿Y you sergeant?
By William.
- Insurance.
Of course.
Come on.
Crap.
- Ya see.
Let's go for them.
Cursed you're black,
yes, you Jackson.
You should not shoot and you know.
- Leave William in the yard, alone.
Kill you if you were in the hole.
Who says that you go to the hole?
Get in the room for revision.
Quítenle wives.
Lieutenant.
¡ What will you say now?!
¡ ¿Dijiste black, is not it?!
For this wine.
¡ Come on, tell me!
¿Lo took his cell?
Get where we all see.
It is still the champion.
¿Todos see this?
Put your things in the cabin.
I'm using a bra.
- We'll have to revisarte.
Please remove the shirt.
Also remove her bra.
Raise your arms.
Thank you.
Hello cariño.
What's happening?
- It's nothing, I'm fine.
Why not let me speak
you or see you for three months?
I called and told me that
were in a security unit.
What is happening?
Only me into something.
- ¿En what?
¿Te did something?
- Yes, I took 90days for good behaviour.
Why Wade, what did you do?
- Did nothing, I swear you.
For something must be castigadote.
- It is not so simple here.
Do not explain what I can,
you're gonna have to trust me.
Please.
How is Mickey?
Okay.
Tra-¿Lo next time?
I have to see it.
- I'll do, you extraña.
Wade we are without money, I have tried
to seek work but can not find.
¿Trabajo? ¿Y Mickey?
- My mother cared for me during the day.
We were 9months in advance.
- What were the wedding and, ¿lo remember?
Okay, used cheques
of the loan.
Use it until you see something.
It is your business, I do not want ...
Al-devil with my business.
I can not think of that now.
Only USA cheques.
Opens section 80.
It's good to see Smith,
you need only Dimelo.
I know you have a partner.
Porter, the floor
looked at the wall.
From knees, hands over his head.
I'm talking about you.
Open-13.
Letters of John Smith.
Any student of philosophy you
I would say that the truth of human behavior
you're in the ability to deal with things
as survivors ...
understand human behavior
is, blah, blah, blah.
¿Alguien buy this shit?
I remember when I heard talk
you the first time.
¿Mataste to those 16, 17people?
Personally, I think
you're a damned hypocrite.
Write shits hoping that people
take something from it.
Cursed imbecile.
Looking for a religion to change the world
to the children and now you.
They found it in your pocket.
The family is everything, ¿cierto?
I'm going to save this,
for cuidártelo.
Meter some shit in my house ...
and that is what you enseñaré
the real revenge.
¿Estamos clear?
Close the 13.
Therein lies your compañero.
Porter and you can lift.
Already have a compañero.
Do not you are a rapist, is not it?
How good will.
I love this part.
- Okay.
Already have it.
If Virata coughs into the wall.
A but, towards dirígelo
the door.
Urine on the tin.
Do this and we will be fine.
Smith, Porter,
Time courtyard.
34, below,
35down below 36, 37.
Who's this fool?
- Do not know.
Hello Mr. Smith,
what you need.
Smith ¿Conocen this?
- Oyeron that history was among the jackals.
This is who you spoke, Wade.
It was good what you did.
- I was in San Quentin.
¿Te goals in a problem?
It really was not a joke.
- Yes, thank you.
He said the man who you are solid.
¿Ustedes both have a brotherhood?
No, we are in what
really important.
Why did that on the bus?
- It was a damned.
He said the man who you need
count with him.
Thank you.
I heard you had one day bad.
- Yes.
I was supposed to get married
four months ago.
How is your son?
- Michael.
It looks like you,
in the eyes and mouth.
Fortunately mine
resembles her mother.
¿Tienes a picture of them?
Jackson took me when I arrived.
Sorry.
- On 24.
I remember everything as
if this morning. Everything.
The smell of your perfume leaving
through the door
and I looked as if it were
the only man for her.
I married couple, she was sleeping in my
chest, he liked to listen to breathe.
I can not forget.
I can not drop.
- What will. Saldrás here.
But you were in the car, ¿cierto?
- ¿En the car?
In the courtyard you'll find yourself with someone,
a gang.
You think all you have to
cruzarte do is not a black.
How you do?
The perception is the reality
cree makes the mind and accept it.
¿Con who were speaking
in the courtyard?
What is this "24questions"?
His name is Bear,
is a leader, a colleague
has the keys of the house.
It means that none of their
Soldiers made no movement
until he tells you.
I do not know, as you know who is
with whom.
Watch "Fish "....
You enseñaré the politics of prison
but you have to do something for me.
Yes, what?
- Stay away from me in the yard.
I understand.
- Not so.
This is my world until
death separates us.
You're just a tourist.
- Okay.
The first lesson for rates
like you and me:
what is white is not right.
The prison are not games
the street is about race.
Bands: the northern and southern,
believe me there's always war.
Blacks have many bands,
do not forget their biceps.
Asians are and the Pacific Islands,
not bother to know who's who.
All you hate.
And you have the color of your skin,
all whites are in a brotherhood ...
are the ones who make the show
and seek to reclutarte ...
increase their numbers, metiéndote
in drugs.
Watch out for callers
to strike with whites.
If you do not do not have business
Iran on you.
How andas partner?
¿Ves to the moño, this son of a bitch?
- Yes.
Patéalo for me.
- You Blanquita.
No, do not do anything.
Dale in the face.
Get up.
Come on, hard.
¿Los going to stop now Lieutenant?
Yes, the dispárale of 14.
But Mr. the're missing.
Shoot-you are in the 14.
Come on, paste it.
- Come on.
If you do not obey the ordenes you are commanded
a message.
I can not do this.
Do not let adjournment.
- No adjournment none.
That is the official enemy down there.
Les enseñas some weakness
and you send a message to you.
Do this and you're dead man.
We treated as a shit.
¿es that what you want?
- No.
That's right, that's not what you want.
It is very simple.
¿Estás in the car or not?
¿cuál is?
Because I transferirte ...
- I'm in the car.
What was your experience there?
Now clean the courtyard.
Call the doctor.
I'll do the report.
Well done, you have to limpiarte head.
Why he was shot with a rifle?
The question is why do not you fired
to you that you were kicking the rear.
¿Alguien said something?
Ten-something very clear in your head.
When you leave the room trial and
laws are there,
the rules of the game are here
they do whatever they want.
This place is very fucked.
The prison will disintegrate.
The first time you see as you cut
face a man vomiting.
The second worry.
Then you go and no longer matter.
There is no difference for
them, pull the triggers,
not make mistakes,
we are all prisoners.
Time in prison:
231days.
There is a lot of activity here.
Not in vain to end what drew the army.
We are working together.
Believe me. I got everything
under control.
I know that is true.
Thank you very much.
Hello papito.
Well done.
What noqueaste.
Hello boys.
- What was that?
You can not survive here by yourself.
You can not.
¿Ahora you're a Nazi skinhead?
- I do not expect it understand.
How are we going to the accounts?
- Good ...
the loan business
was completed.
I am late with the payment of the house y. ..
we do not have to cover
all that.
If I tell you the truth I do not know what to do.
- Okay.
Sell the house, sold my truck,
everything you can.
We are talking about our house.
- I know.
You and Michael are the most important thing now
venda the house, buy another later.
Laura mírame, as you leave here
All this is history, I promise you.
¿Entonces protect you?
¿a exchange for what?
Let me worry about me
why. ¿O.K?
Dale drive.
Just the chest.
Good shot.
- Well done boy.
Come on, strip.
¿Estás well?
- Yes.
¿Ves that tomato there?
- Why do not you go to Shu?
¿Ahora you think hard is that? Te
I will put the ass against that.
What if I want.
We are going to beat this son of a whore.
Hey.
They are hitting one.
I do not want to see this again.
Below or I lose.
Down.
¿Quieres you sink your damn head?
Back to his cell, put
their hands behind their heads.
If you move you shoot.
Open 13.
Come on.
Close the 13.
You can stop.
We warned,
and now I have along with you.
¿Crees not make anything?
We are both. Should
I scrounge around the rear.
It is hard.
Thanks, John.
¿Sabes how to survive?
You have to have a good friend.
¿Ya arranger everything with the house?
Yes, yes, I'm just reviewing.
¿Estás you're safe
well with all this?
As soon as you can fix it
Michael look elsewhere ...
Laura, of course that there is no problem.
You and Michael can be
be as much as they want.
Lieutenant.
¿Estás purchase?
Yes, I was eating too much
pizza and fast food.
My wife and I
Divorced recently.
Yes.
Sorry, she is my wife Kelly.
And he is Lieutenant Jackson.
Bill, call me Bill.
Nice to meet you, Bill.
Pleased to meet you.
Oh, congratulations.
¿Ya know whether it was male or female?
It is female.
Oh, I remember those days, but grow
so fast, you will know what I mean.
Oh, it is already ready
all for what lies ahead.
No, not everything. We
to buy a house.
We need fourth extra now.
Please tell me what you
I can do to help.
And do not be afraid to tell people
from here you're part of the family ...
... one of the employees of the
imprisonment. We take care of everything.
Okay, I'll do, thank you.
See you, James.
See you, Lieutenant.
It seems a very friendly.
Back.
Virata.
Two steps back.
Close the 13.
¿Sabes you what will happen today?
What's important to you?
I'll give you something else to shoot.
Okay, you know.
Time rules.
That is my bitch, Do not?
Cursed lamb.
Doing so after
everything they did because of you.
¿Nosotros?
Surely you do not.
As far as I am
Concerning you are fucked.
I feel you've tried it dammit.
Weapon in the toilet, Sergeant, I saw him.
Nobody is going to touching.
If you want to ride with
we look to see me.
If you do not, you're on your own.
I can not believe that
is gaining more friends.
Métanlo in the hole.
Wait, what's Samson?
What there with him?
When you do something, I will give you with a stick.
why such hate so much?
Samson the Jodo him 5years ago.
He gave a cartabón in the face.
He told you to JOD
cursed his wife and children.
We all have a Samson here.
If you stay in this work as
enough, so you'll need.
What kind of work.
There is nothing better to think here.
Do not tamper with dangerous types,
And when you are convinced that
quite right, Patience, Pender.
What these represent?
It's my timetable.
That is its cumpleaños,
this was their first date.
Our anniversary,
The cumpleaños my daughter.
The first day he walked.
And the day I took off.
And that vacuum, what is?
This is
the day we meet.
You say you have a girl.
Yes, but I do not have much to say.
No,
dijiste
who were 6years together
and not yet married.
I just ...
... I want to be well first.
Let me give you ...
... stability.
Something to pass this.
Now you're good fucking, Do not?
Yes, it ...
Hey, John.
¿Crees that Samson kept his word?
Oh, you just do not want a
reason not to do so.
You and I are now
in a sea of sharks.
I only know you're on your own.
Come on, Mike. End your work, come on.
Come on.
Yes.
Watch that you're well, arbitrator.
Come on.
God, is impressive.
Come on, big.
I was thinking that perhaps
we should cool it a bit.
Why?
You know,
these rates are going to
fuck with lawyers.
Treaty with gentle hand does not work,
all people, you should know.
I know, is that those bastards are going to
Making talk about that among all of them,
we took the only person who ...
They are not going to be more convincing
we with the police,
they will not check anything.
Nothing.
¿De what is this?
It's just that I do not want to lose everything
the work I've done, Bill ...
... I'm too close to my pension
and I do not want to lose by an imbecile ....
Hear a moment,
¿cuánto money did last year?
¿Cuánto hiciste?
68thousand.
-- We have a good salary
-- Yes, yes.
Come on.
¿Sabes? there is a reason that
the state has prisons.
Because all they care a carajo
the lives of those pieces of shit.
The outside of society they want.
Nobody's going to Jodo anything.
Nobody, ¿está well?
-- Continue to do so.
-- Agreed.
Trust me, ¿de agreement?
Come on, Tom.
Dale hard, we partner.
Do impressive.
Venda
Stay at home.
I said to you.
¿Una nightmare?
Yes, I was thinking about
people who kill.
¿Y then?
I can not remove the face
This kind of my head.
He stays inside, I quit going.
Not ...
... you did what you had to do.
Protect your family, that
The only thing that matters.
¿Te I ask something?
Why not kill those two guys?
why the others?
Sorry.
No.
... You do not have to tell me.
If you are going to be next to a
rate, breathing the same air,
need to know things about him.
And when your life is ...
defined forever ...
by a single action,
changes over time.
It feels like 1000years in
my body, but in my mind ...
... it seems that happened yesterday.
You know the feeling when ...
... get home and
you see your wife and son.
Yes.
Try to imagine the other party.
When I arrived home y. ..
... I saw the bleeding ...
... exposed.
Covers blood.
My little Mary had the
broken legs and was on the floor.
He dislocated his hip.
He was 7years.
I wanted these two imbeciles ...
... feel the experience I had.
I wanted them to know
how I had felt.
Kill every member of their families.
One by one, limpide.
I became crazy.
And I purifies.
Before killing them,
I knew the loss.
He wanted me to death
return, but it did not.
I wanted to be with my and my Mary Anne.
These sons of whores did not have the right
of Jodo
They say the law that
I see full of blood.
Hello.
What happens?
¿Estás well?
Yes, I'm just tired.
¿Estás safe?
Yes.
I can not believe that
have already spent 11months.
Anything that I thought
is a new life.
How is Mike?
Yes, that's okay but with nightmares
since the last visit, so ...
I thought it was better ...
to stay at home.
Yes, you're right.
Probably should not
see this place anymore.
Yes.
Venda home.
Agreed.
In 24or 25thousand, Do not?
No, we sold in 3800.
What?
3800a shit, Laura.
With everything on the house, the
'd asked least 10thousand U.S. dollars.
How will you survive with that?
If you think I have not thought of that, if
not what you think should have done,
maybe what you should have done.
Hey, I'm which stands
over time, ¿te remember?
¿Crees I'm not so well?
You're on your cage with many types.
I have had to cope with the disaster
to continue with life.
Your tools are gone.
Your truck, he left.
The whole house was.
Meanwhile am
Work sucks ...
... and rarely see Michael,
I have to deal with my mother and listen
say all shits all day.
All we know
We are rejecting.
OK, calm down.
¿De agreement?
Sorry, I know you're
dealing with many things.
But have no idea
what happens here.
What I have to do to survive.
No, Dímelo.
Because I do not know.
I can not.
Jódete, Wade.
Do not you, Laura, please.
please sit again.
Please.
¿Ves someone Jodo here?
Your team, how outdoors.
And in the morning,
you break, you destroy.
Rather than exercise, go to work.
Everything you do,
to the last detail
This is the only prisoner.
¿Viste your girl?
I saw his face, but.
I could not do anything to be better.
You're in a mess with many types.
It seems everything has remained unchanged.
More moves,
She is everything to me.
If you do not have it or Michael ...
I'm so bored of this shit.
Here we go, going to see a bronze.
I will not fight with you, man.
What the hell you doing?
¿Me called for this?
Clear the courtroom.
Vamonos here.
¿Quieres fuck with me?
Get in the infirmary.
I want to be in peace
rest of my time here.
I do not want a death.
Dímelo everything.
Everything.
And you will be protected at night.
Talk.
Neither keep thinking.
19years I have grappled with you.
Under pressure, tested.
Never has anyone done anything to me
I know personally.
My image is destroying every time
we talk about why you got.
And people like to buy
the prison guards
This always happens, 55years ago.
But that will not be me.
I do not let pressure.
I inflicts.
Jesus Christ.
Please, please.
-- We will implore.
-- Dime.
-- Please lieutenant.
-- If you do not let this lie ...
... you will pay cagándote.
I think I put more
fear in you, son of a whore.
-- Sorry.
-- You are empty.
Sorry.
please do not.
¿Sabes what?
I think I have a better way.
¿Sabes what happened to
Samson friend of the Bus?
Yes
Died
Now I import a shit.
But whether it should be important to you.
She went to see the people
indicated that works for me,
and a witness who did know that Samson
the conviction for murder in 1st grade.
Contigo I make an exception.
Okay, look, I'm sorry.
I should haberte told the truth.
I thought it was going to kill me, never
I have been in prison, ¿de agreement?
That is already sold, Porter.
Except you and I are going to
spend much more time together.
Listen, Lieutenant only
I have left 4months.
I will do what he wants.
Please.
Time served: 427days.
Lord Samson,
when the jury sentenced him by the
charge of first degree murder,
what gets life
with the possibility of change.
This term is not consistent
with his initial judgement.
Lord Porter,
when the jury what
sentenced for murder
the maximum sentenced to 3years.
And because the testimony
Lieutenant Jackson was so bad
I will give you another 3years to
reconsider its allegations.
These are 6consecutive years
his initial judgement.
I hope that his life back on track.
What I heard.
Sorry.
What coño did to deserve this?
No, what I must
face, we must ...
Look at what has become Wade.
It happens just happens. Some
people become ...
What mom want me to do?
Just want to flee, Do not?
Just want to leave it.
Sorry, but he has left you
you, I'm trying to understand.
You have 33years, a single mother.
If you expect Athens 40before he
leaves, and if you do something else, ¿entonces what?
've Waited in vain.
He was 26when your father is long.
We left you and me with a ticket
for a swimming pool. ¿Recuerdas?
I do not regret a moment or that.
Working all these
years to support us.
Look at me well, Laura.
I have 50years and still single.
Do not want to see in this way.
You know.
She left me.
¿Lo to carry hollow?
Why?
You have to let go.
Piece of shit.
I have nothing to Alo
return, I have nothing.
Everyone must know what it feels like.
How you doing here, John?
¿Comparado with your fishing boat or
take your beautiful wife in your holidays?
In fact, I was in the boat this morning.
¿Necesitas a couple of
glasses? I can ...
No. Not me ... I have to go
used to be that way.
I've seen letters on the website.
What I think you should ...
... you did long ago.
¿Crees which is the only reason
by which I coming here?
No, has been a good friend to me.
But both know that never want
seeing the walls of prison
if it were not for me and it hurts.
So ...
... please, just
enjoy your life y. ..
-- Watch ...
-- Leave expenditure here.
John.
Guard.
Oye, oye.
We are now carrying surgery
same. We can not let pass.
, Everything is Dad.
It hurts.
I know, champion.
You have to be tough, ¿de agreement?
We are going to operate and you will come
to collect, ¿de agreement?
I'll be right here, ¿de agreement friend?
I'll be here when
leave. I promise.
Be tough, ¿de agreement, baby?
What happened?
I was in the garden and its
friend ran
wine and a type that the
crashed into the corner and
beat him before he
given time to do something.
It is this son of a bitch that did this.
How you know?
For the policemen.
We are now withholding
same in a room.
It looks like you're uncomfortable.
Yes.
It's very bad what happened.
I am very ...
... very embarrassed, How is he?
Do not talk shit.
I did not want to hit.
It is best read
that the judge thinks the same thing as you.
because there will be no jail or prison
where you can hide from me.
For you promise
I will find you
I will make you do
bleed to death.
But for now I have your license
lead, I took the report of the incident ...
perhaps you can hit again, wimp.
Perhaps passing through your property and
cursed shock to your children.
There'll fuck with
the son of a guard.
coño why it had to happen?
why? Hello, black, stay
in the cage, son of a whore.
What's going on, my black?
Jódete, red.
A bastard.
I'm going to fuck the ass,
see you, son of a whore.
Already Di keys
apartment, Do not?
Yes, just do not know where most
we will save more.
It is cheap, is what matters.
And this helps comic side of here.
Just stay here.
Thanks, cariño.
Thank you.
why are you giving
Papi clothes there?
Good,
baby,
Papi is not going to live
with us anymore.
But tell that to return home.
I know, I did.
But things changed.
-- Cariño, is just ...
-- Sometimes ...
... sometimes, Mike,
people change their lives.
And all we can
do is say goodbye.
¿Está Bravo with us?
No,
No, daddy wants us much.
¿Sabes what? We are going to be okay.
¿Está well?
We can talk about this
then why ...?
Why not looking for your coloring book
and you draw a picture to your grandmother?
¿Está well?
Mike.
¿Donde are you?
Porter.
You visit.
Take your time.
Thank you.
¿Anda everything OK? ¿Mike okay?
Yes, no, no, that's okay.
I thought that you would not again.
I do not.
I do not know what to do.
But the problem is that Mike will be
in the secondary when to leave.
But I know he does not want
spend the rest of his life without you.
And I either.
Not'm going to lie.
Your letter to me killed.
If you do not know that I have to you
and Michael when I get back ...
... not what I will achieve.
It's just that he needed time to
understand everything that was losing.
So Dime
¿Espero for you?
That's what I want.
But if you can not understand.
Well, I will.
No matter how much I cost.
Only when I need to leave home
're you.
Love is the force more
powerful on Earth.
It was Laura.
Look, John.
I know that never wanted
getting into trouble.
I do not need any disrespect.
But this kind I have been robbed 7
years of my life with my family.
I can not let this happen.
The last time checkup, he
does this because it gives the wins.
Unless you have
something with which to negotiate.
What you mean?
What I mean?
Expose to operate.
True, but nobody is going
to risk against Jackson.
Not even Collins.
You can not think outside these walls.
Look at the people who
really is involved.
Fuérzalos to pay attention.
How?
Please,
just tell me how.
How is your son?
Sorry.
Porter has been asking for you.
I do not know what they want.
I'm ready to give you what you want.
¿Dime again?
The nuts of the cell 19
this son of a whore is one of the
why I am here.
Want to pay, Do not?
Yes.
Ponna in the yard, kill it.
I'm so tired of you all.
You say one thing.
If you want to handle this
as a soldier, you'll need.
But with my rules, you go for everything.
What you mean?
¿Quieres or not go to this yard?
I wish you the ride
life of this son of a whore.
I will not finish my work until
that ends with you one by one.
¿Me listening?
I did not expect that this will happen.
-- ¯Tienes address you di?
-- Yes.
Just make sure you go
when working.
Why risk? Te
I expect that.
¿Otros 7years?
No, baby.
This type will not cease,
not in this way.
If something happens, he will learn
and you'll never leave here.
Back home.
Just make sure it does not do anything wrong.
We do not know whom to trust.
¿Puedo help?
¿Señor Cameros?
Yes.
Time served: 457days.
Open 13.
That same, right here for.
Come on.
Ponte backs.
What is what happens? Do not do.
Even if you win,
lie to lose your life.
Why you care? You are like them.
I'm not like them.
Then do something.
Wade said that insurance ¿Estás
that this will happen this morning?
He said that what iban a
extricate the patio at 8:00.
If we can finally take,
we will have circumstantial evidence.
We have to look at this yard with the fight.
Anything that happens,
do not leave this place.
We copy.
Life is defined by
individual actions.
Return the concept over time.
Come, son of a whore.
¿Crees that we must stop
that happen in the yard?
When you are finished with those by comemierdas
myself, get ready to finish the fight.
Porter seems to be
better than it looks.
Agreed. I think
it's time to stop.
No.
Now.
Forward.
You do not fail or next.
Come on, salt there.
What is jodan, if they want blood between
brothers, as dale, we will give you blood.
Leave move, Bill.
None of them deserve this and what you know.
Leave pass.
Clear the yard.
Move.
Cell 13, quit the courtyard.
¿Crees that worked?
Now that your absence
girl reaches the Guard.
I can not believe who do not want to stop.
Quiet.
You do not want you to hate them more than
. For the police, especially Jackson.
The two, returning to the yard now.
Move their hind screwed.
Everything will be fine, cariño.
¿Me have, Diaz?
If they move, jodo complete.
Oh, shit, Bill.
I'm going to the infirmary.
I pass something in the knee.
That is what I am going to bring.
Open the door of the courtyard.
Damn now.
¿Crees that someone
matter if they do this ...
Nobody cares a
carajo what they happen.
What happens is that I have the two
Gaza front of the camera.
So if someone looks at my report
will see that this old man here
fired them to colleagues in the room
and you break your head against
floor, of course you had to draw
with the team on duty.
And the shit that's happening now is ...
That sent me to two bastards
to me it can ....
13.
You, accursed.
Okay.
Listen, my friend ...
¿Sí?
You ...
¿John?
coño What we want to go?
Guess one thing, Diaz,
just hit the car.
I heard the shots, reviews all
sections. I'm going there for now.
Cameros, ... What you doing here?
I am the agent of Skiletti
FBI, we must speak.
Sorry, I have an emergency
in prison and I need ...
This is a federal review, has
to tell me what kind of emergency is.
I am a lieutenant and died a prisoner.
¿Cuáles are the names?
Lt. Bill Jackson
and John Smith.
I want to see the surveillance tape
before anyone touch them.
How knows that happened in the courtyard?
Collins.
There were with them.
We all know it.
¿Crees that matter?
Nobody in the prison system
will be able to play.
Not with what I do.
¿Y did not do anything about it?
I was in the infirmary,
just like my report said.
Look, I do not know why the FBI has to
involved before they finish my people.
After what I see,
we are involved.
And let me make this clear, Wade Porter is now a witness
Federal and want this in custody until the release.
Cameros, How knew that this
happen before the fact?
Sorry, he does not have
to answer that.
It's part of our investigation.
He knows that is what you jode, Frank.
It's not what you know.
Wade is being transferred to custody.
Nothing will happen there, I will also put pressure
for the benefit because of their testimony.
What does that mean?
It means as ends
his original sentence.
That will be within three months, Do not?
Oh, God.
That you stayed in the cell.
Thank you.
Gordon Cameros, a friend of John.
Hello Gordon.
Pleased to meet you.
-- Thank you for getting involved.
-- Oh, sure.
I heard that I was captain.
Yes, caring for John for 20years.
I spent more time with him that the
I spent with my own family.
The
I saved a puñalada.
a few years ago that.
Yes.
Was dead sure.
That is one reason why the ...
... I came out of these things.
We were true friends.
Mine too.
The not told me anything about this,
When I last saw ¿sabes?
Y. ..
... your girlfriend wine ...
Oh, she wanted to tell you
she wanted to give you a message,
was postponing the wedding for when you leave.
Thank you.
Try to relax.
John wanted this happen.
That broke it.
No, he did not.
Usually, he recorded the words of others.
If the original John
would not be poetic,
but it would be the truth.
Close 13.
Oh, let man,
I wanted to be in peace the rest
my judgement, Jackson ...
Jackson is dead.
Please close it.
Yes, you synthesizes prison.
But they also force you to
see what is most important.
The family.
And loyalty.
Because a convicted as
you do not exist in this place.
So who did not flee
you becoming a criminal.
Abrázala grows.
To see what is
what you really matter.
This is my last council, Wade Porter.
And to protect your family
at any cost.
Even if you are forced
to kill again.
Because if I had to do
what would have everything planned
to bring across my rear.
So, my friend,
Until 2008, there are over 2.3million
people imprisoned in North America
That number increases
more than 1000per week.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org