Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Taken? Taken where?
A boat, sire. From the north gate
into the forest.
l have scouts and dogs out already.
Give me a battalion of guards.
- Give me the men.
- No, that압 exactly what he wants.
- Take one brigade, now!
- Sire.
He앏l not harm her. sire.
She압 too vaIuable.
- He앏l try to trade her first.
- That압 what l앐 afraid of.
l앇 give my life for her.
But what if he asks for more?
Welcome to my palace ... My Lady.
l think we can release the lady
from her bonds.
lf she so wishes.
What압 this?
Your dress is torn. Ralph ...
l gave orders that the lady
was not to be harmed.
Your dress is quite spoiled.
You ...
... almost ...
... a queen.
RaIph. Did you do this?
- Yes, My Prince.
- You see?
This is
what Arthur doesn앖 understand.
Men don앖 want brotherhood.
they want leadership.
Shall we?
This was once
the greatest castle ever built.
Now grass grows in the halls
where kings once feasted, -
- and peasants cart away the walls
to make shelters for their pigs.
- Such is glory.
- What do you mean to do with me?
Keep you
till Arthur becomes reasonable.
He won앖 trade Leonesse for my life.
l앇 rather die. Arthur knows that.
Self-sacrifice is very easy.
But sacrificing someone you love
puts your convictions to the test.
l앐 sure Arthur will come round
to the merits of compromise.
This is called an oubliette.
That압 French
for a place of forgetting.
Your quarters, My Lady.
No gates, no bars, no locks.
Just walls of air.
You can come out!
l앐 unarmed and alone!
- Who are you?
- A messenger from the King.
- He came alone?
- Yes, My Prince.
- What is your message?
- ls Lady Guinevere unharmed?
She압 unharmed. l give you my word.
- l need to see it with my own eyes.
- My word isn앖 good enough?
l앐 a common man.
l don앖 have much use for words.
He does have a message.
Take him to the pit, then bring him back Here.
give me a chance to finish my food.
- You았e seen her. Let압 go.
- No.
- l still have a message to deliver.
- AlI right. We앏l drag you back.
Jump on! Jump!
Come on! Jump!
lf the water can get out,
so can we. Come on.
No! Hold on!
Shoot!
Why have we stopped?
- l앐 tired.
- Never.
You battle in your dreams.
- What are you doing?
- You앏l see.
Now. drink.
Again.
- Where did you learn to do that?
- l lived most of my life outdoors.
Don앖 you have a home?
No. l don앖 have a home.
Not for a long time.
- That must be hard.
- Why must it be?
I앐 my own master.
l go where l please.
Why build a house
for the warlords to burn?
ls that how it happened?
God save you from such a day.
How old were you?
Mother!
Father!
lt was long ago.
- God save us all from such a day.
- He didn앖 save me.
- Ah. but he did.
- For what?
lt압 made you who you are.
A man who fears nothing and no one.
You can use that gift.
lf not, you might as welI have died.
You don앖 know how many times
l았e wished for that.
But you didn앖 die. You lived.
- Tell me what to do.
- Your life is your own.
l give it to you.
You forget l앐 to be married.
lf you could freely do as you
pleased, would you marry Arthur?
- l am free. As free as you are.
- Prove it.
- How?
- Forget who you are.
Let all the world go away ...
and all the people in it, but us.
Do what you want to do.
Here. Now.
There she is!
Thank you, God.
Thank you.
Thank you. You can go.
You must have better things to do.
You have given me back my life.
l can at least give you your shirt.
- Tell me what you want. lt압 yours.
- l did what any man would do.
You risked your life for another.
There is no greater love.
You have deceived me.
But now ... l know the truth.
You care nothing for yourself.
No wealth, no home, no goal, -
-just the passionate spirit
that drives you on.
God uses people like you.
Because your heart is open,
you give all of yourself.
lf you knew me better,
you wouldn앖 say such things.
l take the good with the bad.
I can앖 love people in slices.
Now, no more protests.
Let me thank you in my own way.
They are welcoming you back.
We owe Lady Guinevere압 life
to one man.
Lancelot.
l believe he comes to Camelot
for a purpose, -
- even though
he doesn앖 know it himself.
What l앐 about to offer this man
is already his.
One seat stands empty.
- You앇 make him a knight, sire?
- l offer no life of priviIege.
lt압 a life of service.
lf you want it, it압 yours.
- We don앖 know anything about him.
- Perhaps we should discuss ...
Enough! What do you say?
Will you join us?
My Lord, if l may speak?
l owe this man
more than anyone here.
He deserves any honour
you can give him.
But he doesn앖 belong in Camelot.
He압 a man who goes his way alone.
ln that freedom and solitude
is his strength.
lf you wish to honour him,
as l do, with alI my heart, -
- Iet압 honour him as he is.
Let him go, alone and free ...
and with our love.
Well ... Lancelot?
Lady Guinevere understands me well.
But here, among you, -
- l have found something
that l want more than freedom.
lt would break my heart
to leave you.
Bravo! Then you앏l join us?
- Yes.
- Welcome.
This is only the beginning.
Go pass this night in prayer, -
- for tomorrow you앏l be born again,
into a new life.
- Why?
- You know why.
- Please leave Camelot.
- l want to be where you are.
You must not say such things to me.
Say nothing.
l will leave Camelot now.
if you come with me.
- No.
- Then tell me you don앖 love me.
l don앖 love you.
Arise. Sir Lancelot.
Brother to brother.
yours in life and death.
yours in life and death ...
l swear to love and serve Guinevere.
my true and rightful queen.
and to protect her honour as my own.
Jacob ...
Forgive me, milady.
Black Malagant has taken Leonesse.
Leonesse ...
The gates are open.
- Make camp for the night.
- Where. sire?
There.
lt압 too exposed. sire.
We could never possibly defend it.
Sire.
Theyre not here.
There압 no one here!
Draw!
Loose!
Charge!
Attack!
- Archers in position, sire.
- Hold position.
- Their left wing is falling back.
- Second battalion to the left!
ls our centre holding?
Charge!
- Theyre breaking, sire.
- Do not give chase.
- First battalion regrouped, sire.
- Sound the advance.
- Theyre running. Do we follow?
- No. Let them go.
On to Leonesse!
Well done.
Your sword ... Sir Lancelot.
No!
- Come out.
- Theyre alive.
Youre safe. Don앖 be afraid.
Were glad youre safe.
There압 a step. Be careful.
God bless you, sir.
l앐 so old now ...
Can l go home now?
Yes.
Yes, you can go home now.
Bless you, milady.
Elise ...
l았e come to say goodbye,
and wish you well.
lt압 been a long night.
You았e not slept.
- Where will you go?
- Wherever the road leads.
When shall we see you again?
l don앖 think l앏l be coming back.
Never?
Never.
I know what l must do now.
l never believed in anything before.
But l do believe in Camelot.
And l will serve it best by leaving.
Tell the King, l앏l always remember
that he saw the best in me.
And what shall l tell myself?
There was once a man who loved you
too much to change you.
l앏l not forget him.
l sheltered under a tree
with him once ... in the rain.
Lancelot ...
- My Queen.
- l owe you a kiss.
l앐 asking you.
Why?
The King asks for you, milady.
l ask you not to lie to me,
even if you think you앏l hurt me.
- Have you given yourself to him?
- No, My Lord.
Do you love him?
Yes.
- How did l fail you?
- You았e never failed me, My Lord.
l saw your face as you kissed him.
Love has many faces. l look on you
differentIy, but not with less love.
When a woman loves tWo men.
she must choose betWeen them.
- l choose you.
- Your will chooses me.
- Your heart chooses him.
- My will is stronger than my heart.
Do you think l put so high a price
on my feelings? They앏I pass.
My will holds me
to my course through life.
As mine does me, and yet,
all l have to do is look at you -
- and everything l ever believed in
fades to nothing.
- All l want is your love.
- You have it.
Do l? Then look on me
as you looked on him.
l gave one moment to Lancelot.
Yes, youre innocent.
But you love him!
Any more of this innocence
and l앏l go mad.
- l앏l do whatever you tell me to.
- l don앖 know what to think.
l no longer see my way ahead.
Only fools dream of the one thing
they can앖 have.
Forgive me.
What압 to forgive?
l dreamed the dream of you.
lt was a sweet dream ...
... while it lasted.
- Unlock the door.
- Sire.
- My Lord?
- l앏l ask the questions.
Did you come to Camelot
to betray me?
- No, My Lord.
- You desired her. You pursued her.
- The Queen is innocent.
- lnnocent?
l saw her in your arms.
l trusted you, and you betrayed me.
- l never meant to hurt you.
- You leave me nothing! Nothing!
You will be charged with treason.
Defend yourself in court.
The law will judge you!
May God grant us the wisdom
to discover the right, -
- and the strength
to make it endure.
Amen.
l was mistaken in Lancelot.
As a man, l may forgive ...
As a king, l must see justice done.
There will be a trial tomorrow.
in the great square.
- ln the great square?
- Let압 settle the matter privately.
You think the honour of Camelot
is a private matter?
Am l to hide in dark corners
as if l앐 ashamed?
Open the gates.
l want everyone there.
Let every citizen see
that the law rules in Camelot.
Guinevere, Lady of Leonesse,
Queen of Camelot. -
- and Lancelot.
Knight of the High Council, -
- are charged in their own persons,
and in collusion. -
- with dishonour to the realm.
and violation of the King압 rights.
These crimes constitute
an act of treason against Camelot, -
- and the penalty under law
is death.
- Sir Lancelot may speak.
- My words are for the King alone.
My Lord.
The Queen is innocent.
But if my life, or my death, -
- serves Camelot. Take it.
Do what you like with me.
Brother to brother.
yours in life and death.
ls it the King압 wish
that the Queen be questioned?
May God forgive me.
Is it the King압 wish
that the Queen be questioned?
- Who goes there?
Guards!
Close the gates!
Nobody move or Arthur dies!
My men control the city gates.
On every roof,
l have men with burning torches!
l have only to lift my arm,
and your golden city burns to ashes.
l am the law now!
You obeyed Arthur. Now, obey me.
My people are unarmed, Malagant.
lf it압 me you want,
here l am.
Look at him! Look at the great
King Arthur of Camelot.
He압 a man waking up from a dream.
The strong rule the weak!
That압 how your God made the world.
He makes us strong only for a while,
so we can help each other.
My God makes me strong
so I can live my life!
Arthur says, 얎Serve one another.얎
When will you live your own lives?
This is the freedom l bring you!
Freedom from his tyrannical dream!
Freedom from his tyrannical law!
Freedom from his tyrannical God!
l want your people
to see you kneel before me here.
Kneel before me. or die.
Too proud, Arthur? Do you think
you serve your people better dead?
l have no pride left in me.
What l do now.
l do for my people, and for Camelot.
And may they forgive me.
This is my last act as your king.
Do not be afraid.
All things change.
l am Arthur of Camelot.
l command you now, all ...
... to fight! Fight!
Like you았e never fought before!
No!
- Camelot lives!
- Burn everything!
No! Be careful!
Come on!
Sword!
Camelot will never fall
to the tyranny of Malagant!
- ls there no more we can do?
- l앐 sorry.
- Lancelot ...
- Yes, My Lord?
- Where압 my sword?
- Here.
My truest ... my First Knight.
Camelot is your home now.
You are the future ...
The future of Camelot.
You take care of her for me.
Take care of her.
l feel it now, my love.
The sunlight.
lt압 in your eyes.
English subtitles - lFT
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org