Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- I'll miss you.
- Yeah?
Of course.
I wish I could go with.
It's okay.
- Peek-a-boo.
Hey.
Ernst!
- Gavin?
- Yeah, in the flesh, mate.
Nice to finally meet you.
You all set then? Ready to go?
-Ja.
- It's over here.
Gavin, I want to thank you
for looking after Martijn while he's away.
No trouble.
I'm just a glorified tour guide, really.
Yeah, but he couldn't do it without you.
Oh, his food programme?
I'm a bit clueless about that, I'm afraid.
It's for the malnourished kids
in the Rif Mountains.
The Rif Mountains, right.
Get him in, get him out, that's my bit.
Gavin, can you give me a second?
- Oh, yeah, okay. Bye-bye.
- Bye.
- I'm really gonna miss you.
- I'm gonna miss you, too.
It's a shame Saadia's not coming with us,
isn't it?
Ja,  she can't leave the country
at the moment,
but hopefully she'll get her passport
in time for my next trip.
I didn't know
there was such a famine in Morocco.
They're malnourished, not starving.
So you really do go for all this
"save the children" bollocks, then?
Of course. What did you think?
I don't know.
Might've been for Saadia's benefit,
mightn't it?
Hello.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
You know, when I leave home,
my missus won't even stand on the porch,
let alone the observation deck at Heathrow.
- You're married?
- Why do you think I do all this travelling?
Come on.
You all right?
Rif Mountains. I'll check this bus.
He's got it, okay?
Hey! Hey!
What's going on? What's all the fuss?
Get your fucking hands off me!
Marhaba.
Mr Fikri, please.
There is no Mr Fikri here.
Hassan Fikri?
I'm trying to reach Hassan Fikri.
There is no Hassan Fikri here.
Martijn, is that you?
Martijn! Martijn, it's me!
It's me, Gavin.
- Gavin?
- Yeah.
What happened?
Last thing I remember was on the bus.
Hey, when did they come onboard?
- Who?
- The blokes who jumped us.
I don't know.
Yeah, well, don't worry, mate.
I'm right behind you.
I've got your back, you've got mine. Right?
Where are we?
I'm wearing a blindfold, for fuck's sake.
Yes, but on the bus,
did you recognise anything?
Oh. I was getting a bit of kip, actually.
But why did they take us?
Maybe they thought we were Americans.
Why would they think that?
Maybe they heard us speaking English.
But I'm from Holland.
They don't know the difference.
So that's why they took us?
Yeah, you and me, both.
Maybe we should ask them.
- What's that?
- I don't know.
Hello?
- Is somebody else here?
- Hello?
Hello?
- Is someone else here?
- Hello?
Hello!
Just relax, will you?
They'll let us go as soon as they realise
they've made a mistake.
It is a mistake, right, Gavin?
These things usually get sorted
in the first 24 hours.
- This has happened to you before?
- Sure it has.
- Really?
- Well, not quite like this.
Then like what?
You know, seminars.
- Seminars?
- Security seminars.
You know, with the experts.
So you've never actually been held hostage?
No. But the company I used to work for,
they had ops in lots of dodgy places.
So they made us role-play this type of thing.
When you were here before,
what were you busy with?
Business.
Yes, but what kind of business?
I worked for a chemical company.
Oh, shit!
Here, those gits
made a lot of dosh off the deal.
Which gits?
Those Moroccan geezers.
Fuck me, if I can't even remember
their bloody names.
It looks like they remember yours.
Easy with the blame game, all right?
All right, mate?
Just how many villages
did your company rape and pillage?
You just shut the fuck up.
We did not rape anyone.
They were all proper business transactions.
Then why, Gavin, would they kidnap us?
For the publicity.
- Publicity?
- Yeah.
Yeah, you'll see.
Pretty soon they'll be parading us
in front of the cameras
trying to get us to make speeches
denouncing the West,
or some sort of bollocks.
But I'll tell you, mate,
I'm not gonna say a bloody word.
No, I'm not gonna give them
the satisfaction.
Maybe we should try and talk with them
or something like that.
No, fuck them! Goddamn savages.
- They're not savages.
- Sure they are.
Stupid wankers.
Listen, you've got to drop all this
PC bullshit and steel yourself, mate.
- Fuck them! Treat them like animals.
- They're not animals.
The thing is don't let them
fuck with you psychologically.
As soon as you realise that they don't
really have the guts to kill you, it's easy.
Well, yeah, they'll threaten us,
they'll act like they want to kill us,
but really they want to keep us alive.
Really, it's just a bluff
because we're worth nothing to them dead.
Gavin, what if these guys
don't want a ransom?
- What else could they want?
- I don't know.
Shit! Someone's there.
He's been watching us this whole time.
Hello?
Sir, you have the wrong guys.
Yeah, we're not American.
- I didn't even vote for Tony Blair!
- And I'm Dutch.
So you could just let us go
and we'll forget the whole thing.
We haven't even seen your faces!
Hello?
Hello? Hello!
Whatever it is you want from us,
you can forget about it, you understand?
You have made a massive mistake.
I don't think yelling at them
is such a good idea.
Fuck them!
They wouldn't dare kill us,
not if they want sympathy.
What if they don't want sympathy?
What else could they want?
It's a publicity stunt, isn't it?
For Christ sakes.
Our photos are plastered all over
every paper in Europe right now.
What if they aren't? Should we...
We should, Gavin, try and start a dialogue.
No, they're fucking fanatics.
I don't know why you even agreed
to come here in the first place.
To help the people, to make a difference.
Oh, well, congratulations.
Oh, true idealist, you are.
Maybe you and old Omar over there
really do have something to chat about.
Maybe we do.
Maybe this is all one big misunderstanding.
Jesus! What's happening?
What's happening?
Hey, hey, here!
Hey, don't go soft on me now, mate.
You just remember what I told you,
remember my advice.
Fuck them, goddamn savages!
They're just bluffing, they are.
Yeah, just bluffing.
- They don't really have the balls to hurt us!
- Shut up, Gavin.
They can go fuck themselves!
Now don't go mental on me now.
Remember what I told you, hold your nerve.
Please, let me explain.
I've got you.
You really know your way around here.
I take my youth group to the beach
every weekend.
- You should join us sometime.
- You're right.
I should do more.
Yeah, you should.
I have been spending all my time
on the food programme.
It's going to change the world.
I would like that.
Mate.
Good. Very good.
I am impressed. We play another game.
I... I can't.
It is not a request.
And I give to you the first move.
I'm tired. I can't... I can't play.
Voila!
If you don't move soon, you will lose.
Smart move.
Choosing to play, I mean.
Not your pawn.
Are Muslims allowed to smoke?
I thought you said you are not American.
I'm not.
- Spent time in California?
- No.
- Would you like one, then?
- I don't smoke.
Afraid it's going to ruin your health?
Why is that funny?
Nothing. Just you.
Worried about your health.
There are other things
that you should be worried about, Martijn.
Like making your next move.
I have to tell you
it is a pleasure to play with you, Martijn.
Most Westerners cannot play chess
to save their own lives.
I have a theory about that.
Westerners cannot play chess
because they play too much poker.
What do you think?
I don't gamble.
If more Westerners played chess,
they would understand.
There are no bluffs, only calculations.
I think Gavin played poker.
Don't know. Maybe.
I thought you were good friends.
I barely knew him.
How were you introduced?
Me and Gavin?
- On the Internet.
- Not by the woman?
What woman?
The Moroccan woman at Schiphol.
She's my girlfriend.
So you are not married yet?
No, not yet.
But you are thinking about it.
- When the time is right.
- Yes, yes, of course. Life can be short.
Twenty-five seconds.
Fifteen.
- Ten.
- Do you mind? I...
Forgive me, Martijn.
I only want to help.
You are running out of time.
I wonder,
perhaps you do not like women?
What?
Perhaps you are preferring boys.
No. Definitely not.
- You live in Amsterdam.
- Not anymore.
But you often go to Amsterdam.
- Why is this?
- To visit my friends.
- Friends. Gay friends?
- Not everyone in Amsterdam is gay.
Then who do you visit there?
Just because I go to Amsterdam
doesn't mean I'm gay.
It's like saying every Muslim is a terrorist.
- Is every Muslim a terrorist?
- No.
Are you?
What do you think?
You could be gay.
What makes you say that?
I saw Lawrence of Arabia.
And using your logic...
I could be just like
one of the Muslims in that film.
Yes. And look what they did to Lawrence.
- What did they do to him?
- They fucked him, to humiliate him.
You think I want to fuck you, Martijn?
I hope not.
I could do it. Right here.
In front of the camera.
Would you like that?
Your move.
You know, Martijn,
you speak very good English.
I'm Dutch. We all speak good English.
Yes, but yours is better than most.
And so is yours.
Thank you. I studied in Nigeria.
So you're not Moroccan.
Tell me about your friends in America.
I don't have any friends in America.
Yes, yes,
but you speak their language perfectly.
I used to have some clients there.
- Tell me about that.
- There's nothing to tell.
- You are hiding something.
- No.
I'm not.
You are lying.
Get out of my face!
I'm not lying.
We shall see.
Check.
- Can't we... Can't we take a break?
- There are no breaks.
Then can't we quit?
You are willing to concede defeat?
No.
- Then we must continue until you lose or...
- Or what?
- You know what.
- No, I don't.
You will tell me when you are ready.
- What will I tell you?
- Eight seconds, Martijn.
- Help me a little.
- Six.
- Just say it and I'll confirm it.
- Four.
- Please.
- Two.
You've got to tell me.
Martijn, your flag has fallen.
- I should not allow that.
- What do you want me to tell you?
Technically speaking, it is cheating.
The game should be over.
I just need to hear it from you.
What is so important
that you would cheat, eh?
We were talking. We were talking.
What's the matter? You sound upset.
Relax. Relax, Martijn.
It's all right.
Let me see your hand.
- You are a dentist?
- No.
- A doctor?
- A writer?
- No!
No, wait.
A musician?
- No.
- You are lying.
I'm not. I'm not lying.
Martijn, you have to understand,
I hate it when people lie to me.
I have enormous respect for artists.
- Why is that?
- You play guitar?
No, wait.
Piano. Yes?
Yes, piano.
Jazz or classical?
- Mostly jazz.
- There you are.
Straight ahead or fusion?
Free jazz.
- You a fan?
- In a way, yes.
What way?
Jazz is American.
But it has its roots here, in Africa.
Where exactly in Africa are you from?
I thought you were a banker.
That's my job, not my passion.
I thought the Moroccan woman
was your passion.
She knows how important
my music is to me.
And now, Martijn, so do I.
Then you don't mind if we quit?
If we do something else.
Of course I mind, very much.
- Please.
- You know you are a very deep man, Martijn.
First I discover your skill at chess,
which certainly surprised me.
I had no intention of playing this long.
And now I learn you are a jazz pianist.
It makes me wonder,
when did you have the time?
- For what?
- You know what.
No, I don't! I don't know!
Check. Your move again.
Just say it and I will confirm it.
I will tell you whatever you want.
Quite obviously you will not.
Just tell me who you are.
I am a savage.
I am an animal.
Please.
I can't tell you anything
unless I know what you want me to say!
Everything.
I want you to tell me everything.
- You want to know my birthday?
- April 5.
My passport number?
C4538H49.
My bank account numbers?
1 79654384H.
- Then you know everything.
- Not everything.
There's nothing left I can say.
- You and I both know that is a lie.
- I am not lying! I am not!
- Why have you come here?
- To set up my food programme.
Did Saadia put you up to this?
She... She...
She has nothing to do with this.
- I find that hard to believe.
- It's true.
Martijn, when are you
going to tell me the truth?
Why don't you tell me the truth?
Just who the hell you are
and what the fuck do you want from me?
This is your last chance.
There's nothing else I can say.
All right.
- Mate.
- No.
I am so sorry, Martijn.
- Please, another game.
- I thought you were tired.
- Just... Just one more try.
- The game is over.
I need another chance.
I need another chance!
You should have concentrated more.
Your last moves were very hasty.
Please. Please. Please.
Another game, please.
- Give me your hand.
- No! No! No! No!
Give me your hand, Martijn.
No!
Please, no.
No! No, don't, please!
This is your last chance.
I don't know what you want me to say.
You'll make a good father.
Someday, ja.
- So you want to have a family?
- Of course.
Don't you ever want some kids of your own?
If I could, I would.
But these kids,
and a few back home in the Rif Mountains,
I sort of see them as my own.
Then I guess they're mine, too.
Jesus.
Who are you?
Do you speak English?
Francais?
Arabic?
Answer me!
I'm sorry.
Please.
Just... Just say something.
Anything.
They told me not to.
How many are there?
You can whisper.
- About 10.
- Are you part of their group?
No.
Then how do you know them?
They hired me to bandage your finger.
They're going... They're going to kill me.
Then why would they hire me
to bandage your wound?
When did they hire you?
- Yesterday.
- Until when?
Tomorrow.
And when tomorrow comes,
do you think they will just pay you
and let you go?
- Yes.
- No. You've seen my face.
- No.
- You can see me.
No, I cannot.
Then how can you see my hand?
It is very difficult.
I know.
You're hurting me.
But I am trying to help you.
Well, then please,
take off your veil and bandage it properly.
Did they blindfold you
before they brought you here?
No.
So... So you know where we are?
- Yes.
- Are we still in Morocco?
- They've told me not to tell you.
- Or did we move south, to Nigeria?
- I said I cannot tell you.
- They're going to kill you anyway.
- I will not listen to you.
- You have to.
I don't want to die like this.
Then tell them.
- Tell them what?
- Where the money came from.
How do you know that?
I heard them talking.
And they said they want the money?
Yes. That is what they said.
Did they say how much money?
The million dollars.
I'll give you half.
Half?
- For what?
- Lf you... If you get me out of here.
- Half a million dollars?
- That's right.
Half a million dollars.
- What is all this money for?
- My food programme.
- Have you heard of it?
- No.
I'm here to help your people.
There is nothing I can do.
- Are you hungry?
- Yes.
I haven't eaten for...
- How long have I been here?
- I don't know.
I brought this for lunch.
Perhaps this is my food programme.
Thanks. Thanks.
I am sorry.
I could not help you.
No, no, no. Don't. Wait.
- You still can.
- How?
When you leave here,
you can tell someone you saw me.
Tell them where I am.
People around here, they will not
risk their lives for a Dutch tourist.
What about the police? Or the Embassy?
You could tell the Dutch Embassy.
There is no Embassy.
- What do you mean?
- Just what I said.
Then we must have gone south,
at least to the Sahel.
- I did not tell you that.
- I'm a supporter.
My girlfriend is Moroccan.
I never said we were in Morocco.
Then where are we?
Even if you knew, what good would that do?
What about your friends?
- My friends?
- I could try to call them.
No.
- Why not?
- The police. Call the police.
The police are corrupt.
- My friends can't help.
- Well, neither can the police.
It is better to call your friends.
If you just give me their names...
Why do you want to know their names?
To call them. So they can help you.
No.
That isn't it.
I can't believe I almost fell for it.
- Fell for what?
- You almost had me!
You almost had me!
Who are you talking to?
You're good, you know that?
You're fucking good!
What are you talking about?
You're not here to bandage my hand.
You're here to talk to me.
No, they told me not to talk to you.
That's what they told you to say.
Well, it won't work!
Tell me who your friends are.
Tell me where the money came from.
- Tell me where the money came from.
- I embezzled it.
- From who?
- The bank!
- With your friends?
- I did it alone!
You are lying.
My new best friend.
I brought you something.
- You have a request?
- Perhaps you can teach me how to play.
Okay. Meet me at my flat
every Thursday at 4:00.
Good, very good.
I thought you might be getting homesick,
so I also brought you
some reading material.
You mind reading them out loud?
I'm a bit tied up at the moment.
I am very happy to see that
you have not lost your sense of humour.
Serves me well in times of torture.
The real Martijn emerges.
Glib. Strong.
Defiant in the face of extreme pain.
I like that.
Shall we see what everyone else
is saying about you?
"Germany and Poland seek labour deal
to ease EU enlargement."
"Six Palestinians killed in Israeli air strike."
Here is something.
"Two Europeans missing in North Africa."
I am sorry, Martijn.
No, not you.
These men are French.
Totally separate incident.
What's your point?
Come, come, Martijn.
You are a perceptive man.
Don't you have a grieving mother?
Or sister?
What about your Moroccan girlfriend?
Has she noticed that you are missing?
My mother died six years ago.
My sister is living in Spain.
My girlfriend thinks I'm in the Rif Mountains,
helping her people.
You expect me to believe that?
What do you believe?
I believe that the press knows everything.
In fact, I know
that the press knows everything
because we have told them everything.
Then why hasn't it been reported?
That, my friend, is the question.
They are pretending that you don't exist.
What kind of people
does this happen to, Martijn?
I don't know.
- What are you doing in Morocco?
- Setting up a food programme.
Then why could our sources
not confirm this?
Because it hasn't been set up yet.
Please, explain.
Shouldn't need to be told.
If you're working with the people,
you'd know about my food programme.
It's been in development for months.
With such careful planning,
perhaps more people would be aware of it.
The right people know.
They have forgotten you, Martijn.
I think we are the only ones
that remember you now, eh?
Make it easy on yourself.
Don't be foolish.
Tell us who your friends are.
Tell me who you are.
Are you with the movement?
It is more appropriate to say
that the movement is with us.
Then why do you want to know
the names of my friends?
You know why.
- Someone gave you my name?
- We have our sources.
- What sources?
- Does it matter?
Yes! Of course it matters.
Don't you see? This mistrust has to end.
Mistrust. Between who?
Between people like you and people like me.
We're both working for the same goal.
- You are Muslim?
- No.
Just a servant to the cause.
- What cause?
- The cause of the people.
What people are you talking about, Martijn?
Just let me go.
- They lied about me.
- They lied about you?
Who lied about you? For what reason, eh?
Some person, ja.
The one that gave you my name.
They never knew me,
they just pretended to know me.
You know, Martijn,
it is an interesting theory.
It's the truth!
Yes, but it does not explain one thing.
It fails to explain the money
in your bank account.
- I told you how I got that money!
- Yes.
You expect me to believe
that a low-level private banker in Amsterdam
embezzled $1 million
without anyone discovering it.
I risked everything.
Everything to get that money
to fund my food programme!
We told the bank about your capture.
We have had no response.
Don't you find that odd?
If you had stolen that much money,
they would want you back.
They would want the money back.
I'll sign it over to you.
- The money?
- Yes. Yes, the money.
How did you get it?
I said I'd give it to you, all of it.
- We don't want your money, Martijn.
- Then what do you want?
Why did you call Hassan Fikri?
- I... What is Hassan Fikri?
- One of your friends.
I don't... I don't...
Marhaba.
Mr Fikri, please.
There is no Mr Fikri here.
Hassan Fikri?
I'm trying to reach Hassan Fikri.
There is no Hassan Fikri here.
You have been misinformed.
- Why did you make that phone call, Martijn?
- That's not me.
- Stop lying.
- I don't... I don't even know who he is.
- Then who gave you his number?
- No one.
- How did you know to call him?
- I never called him!
He is a jazz musician, eh?
No, no.
He is the one who gave you my name,
and he made that tape to...
Stop this fantasy, Martijn.
No one gave us your name.
You know why you are here.
Ja!  Do you?
Understand, Martijn, there is a reason
for all of this, a very good one!
Then tell me the reason.
Tell me who you are, who you are with.
- You know who we are.
- No, I don't!
But you have your suspicions, yes?
That is why you came to Morocco?
To find Hassan Fikri?
But finding this man
is like finding a needle in the ear of a camel.
So you found a guide,
someone who said he knew the area,
someone who could protect you.
But Gavin did not protect you.
- Not well enough.
- Not well at all.
You have to admit,
hiring Gavin was a big mistake.
I don't know what happened.
You have been fucked, Martijn.
Just call me Lawrence of Morocco.
That is a good one.
Your best one yet, in fact.
Why are you doing this to me?
Because I know Hassan Fikri.
He is a retired chemist.
So?
He has been working on a form of bacteria.
What kind of bacteria?
You already know!
That is why you called him.
I didn't call him.
You called to find out about this bacteria.
About how it can be
disseminated through food.
- I don't know what your business...
- This bacteria is fatal.
- Why would I call about something like that?
- Because you were paid to.
I stole that money!
You were paid that money
to call Hassan Fikri,
to find out what you could!
That is why you came to Morocco.
- I'm a banker.
- That is just your cover.
- For what?
- You are paid in US dollars
to collect evidence on Hassan Fikri.
- You're wrong.
- I would like to believe you.
- Then believe me.
- How can I, when I know the evidence?
What evidence?
That tape was fake.
The money in your account,
why is it not in euros?
I told you so many times.
Who has that kind of power
to make that kind of money appear
- From nowhere?
- Nobody.
Who has that kind of power
to stop the papers from running a story?
I don't... I don't know!
- Who gave you the name of Hassan Fikri?
- I didn't call him.
The Agency!
What agency?
It is not a travel agency.
You think I work for the CIA?
We know you work for the CIA. Yes, yes.
- It's crazy.
- Is it?
I'm not even American.
But you sympathize with the Americans.
I am from Holland.
Why would I sympathize with America?
Because they paid you $1 million.
You think I got that money from the CIA?
What else could we think?
I'd laugh.
If it wasn't so horrible, I'd fucking laugh.
Tell us who your friends are. Your contacts.
- There are no contacts.
- What about your girlfriend?
- What about her?
- Did she recruit you?
Saadia has nothing to do with this.
- Is she your handler?
- She does not work for the CIA!
No, not again.
No, not again. Please.
Please. Please. Please.
It's a gift.
What kind of gift?
For the children.
But why all the secrecy?
Because some donors
prefer to remain anonymous.
Yes. But why?
As long as they help my kids, I don't care.
As simple as that.
It's never that simple.
Can you set up a numbered account?
It's really a little bit tricky
without a passport.
- Euros or dollars?
- Dollars.
- Maybe I should meet this friend.
- Maybe you should.
You're actually a lot alike.
- Is he Dutch?
- No, he's American.
Wow!
An American that thinks the way that I do.
- That is someone I have to meet.
- Okay.
Can you hear me?
I know you can hear me!
Relax. I am just here to remove your clothes.
Why?
You have soiled your pants,
and you have not had a bath for days.
Now, please cooperate.
Now your pants.
Are you going to wash me?
You are going to wash yourself.
Can't.
There's a lot you don't know about me.
- Like what?
- My beliefs.
You are a banker.
You believe in making money.
I was a banker.
And now?
I'm here to help.
Why don't you just go back to Holland
and leave us alone?
- I can't.
- Why not?
You may approach it differently.
For you, it's spiritual.
For me, it's ideologue.
But in the end we're the same.
We support the people
for the same basic reason.
And what reason is that?
Because we both know
there is more to life than money.
Then why did you steal $1 million?
It isn't for me.
Then who is it for?
Not who, but what.
You think this is going
to make a difference?
- Your food programme?
- Yes, I do.
Suppose it works. Then what?
Then I'll keep on fighting
until everyone is forced to start over.
No more Western World.
No more Third World.
No more rich, no more poor.
No more debts, no more creditors.
A worldwide social system.
You are still a banker.
I was fired.
And why is that?
Did they find out about the money?
No. They saw pictures of me.
- Doing what?
- Protesting.
Protesting. Against who?
Dutch immigration policy and our
government's support of the World Bank.
You honestly believe
that to protest against the World Bank
would accomplish something?
I did.
I used to think it could accomplish a lot.
But not anymore?
- Not that way, no.
- Of course not.
Because you are a child, Martijn.
An idealistic, stupid child
who is playing a very dangerous game.
You go away for a weekend,
throw a few stones,
swallow a little tear gas
and tell your girlfriend how risky it was.
And while she is sucking on your cock,
your government expels
40,000 asylum seekers.
You have no idea what it would really take
to change the world.
You're wrong.
Then tell me.
A series of devastating events,
events that would destroy
the world's richest companies,
that would crush the world's economy.
A dozen 9l11s all over the world.
Like what?
Like targeted direct action
against Halliburton.
Against Dow Chemical, against McDonald's.
And not just American companies.
Against Airbus, against British Petroleum.
Against any company
that promotes global capitalism
and destroys lives and cultures
in order to increase its profits.
The Agency has trained you well.
I am not with the CIA.
You are clean.
It's an insult, what you think of me.
There is no other explanation.
I hate the CIA.
I hate everything they stand for.
So you claim.
What about you?
What about me?
Are you a good Muslim?
Yes.
Then why aren't you wearing your veil?
You are right.
I never should have taken it off.
I'm glad you did.
This is why we wear veils.
So men are not distracted.
Are you distracted by me?
You are pale and weak.
You know I'm not weak.
It is true.
It takes a strong man
to hold out for so long.
To keep lying
through your clean, white teeth.
I've told you the truth.
- That you came here to help us?
- And the rest of the world.
Through catastrophic events.
At the moment, just one.
Which you already have planned?
Yes.
With your help.
- But I know nothing of it.
- But you know Hassan Fikri.
That's why this is so wrong.
So that is why you raised $1 million?
- To fund this event?
- Yes.
Then what is it?
I cannot tell you.
Because even if I'm killed
over some stupid mistake,
there are others
who may still make it happen.
- Yes. Your friends.
- Our friends.
If they were our friends, Martijn,
I would know who they are.
Not necessarily.
You are lying.
I've only said this much
to convince you I'm not CIA.
- Then why did you not tell this to Ahmat?
- Because he'd never believe me.
- And I would?
- At least I can try.
I have taken your fingers.
I will do it again.
I have convictions, too.
Tell me what you have planned.
Tell me about your food programme.
Do it.
They have trained you well.
- Is that your friend?
- Yeah. What's wrong?
- You think he'll fund it?
- Your food programme?
Our food programme.
But I don't know nothing
about your food programme.
You know me.
And that's all I need to know.
We're gonna change the world.
I love you.
I love you, too.
What's that?
They can still be sewn back on.
It will require a fine surgeon,
but it is possible.
Why are you showing me this?
Because Aicha seems to think
that we are wrong about you.
So I made some inquiries.
She may be right.
Oh, thank God.
I thought you were an atheist.
It's only an expression.
If she is mistaken, I still have this.
I already told her the truth.
Protesting against the World Bank
proves nothing.
It could just be a part of your cover.
You're right, you're right.
Doesn't prove anything.
So tell me, Martijn,
why did you try to contact Hassan Fikri?
I can't tell you that.
I can only confirm what you already know.
What if I were to tell you
my own little secret?
What secret?
That I am Hassan Fikri.
Ja.  Makes perfect sense.
- What do you mean?
- It's... It's safer to use an alias.
Yes, much safer.
And I'd heard rumours
that you were from Nigeria.
Rumours?
From who?
People in the network.
They suggested I call you,
but you weren't expecting my call.
No, I was not.
You didn't know who I was
so you needed to find out why I was calling.
Yes. Why were you calling me?
- You don't know? Not even now?
- Perhaps I do.
- You've made inquiries?
- Yes.
- Then you know who I am.
- I know who you might be.
- He needs confirmation.
- What kind of confirmation?
He needs to know
you are really who you claim to be.
There is a terrorist cell in Holland
that our network agreed to finance.
- Then you know how I got the money?
- No.
There was a miscommunication.
Yes, but now you know.
We know that it is possible.
Of course it's possible.
It's the fucking truth.
- Convince us.
- Convince you of what?
That you are a part of the Dutch cell.
Okay.
What were you recruited to do?
I have friends in food distribution centres
across the EU.
They are willing to take action,
and the security is weak.
You have identified a target?
I'm going to poison fast food products.
American hamburgers, milkshakes,
French fries.
From the Leidseplein
to the Champs Elysees,
anyone who eats a Big Mac or a Happy Meal
will die within 24 hours.
So a few fat Americans
will have their potbellies incinerated.
A few? Try thousands if not
hundreds of thousands in one single day.
By the time they shut us down,
we will have killed
a hundred times more people
than Osama bin Laden!
How do you intend to poison the food?
With the bacteria that you're developing.
How did you learn about the bacteria?
From the network.
Why did you need $1 million?
To cover the lab costs,
to cover the materials.
- What materials?
- You're the fucking chemist. You tell me.
No, no, no, it must have been
a miscommunication.
I thought you did not speak Arabic.
I picked up a few words from my girlfriend.
- A miscommunication.
- Yes. Yes.
One that's already cost me four fingers.
- The system is not perfect.
- It's not supposed to be.
- No. I am not convinced.
- What...
- What would convince you?
- The money. Where did it come from?
From someone who believed
in the value of the operation.
- Someone outside the network?
- Yes, yes, that is correct.
But how do you know they are your friend?
Who else would give me
that kind of money?
The CIA.
How would the CIA know about you?
That is exactly
what I am trying to find out, Martijn.
This is going nowhere.
Convince us the money
did not come from the CIA.
- How?
- Trace it back to your friend.
- The money is untraceable.
- Why?
Because I designed it that way.
I used to work for a fucking bank.
Here. Drink that.
I am sorry, Martijn.
But we cannot afford
to risk the entire network
for the sake of one operation.
An important operation.
Yes, but imagine if we trusted you
and we were wrong.
What then, eh?
I am sorry it had to happen this way.
I am sorry about your fingers.
But you are prepared
to die for the cause, no?
- Yes, but...
- But what?
- I understand. I do, but...
I just wish there was some way
I could convince you.
- So do I.
- After all, I am a rarity.
What do you mean?
I have blonde hair, blue eyes
and a Dutch passport.
How many dedicated sympathizers
do you know that look like me?
We could do great things.
What about the names?
We have the names.
What names?
Last night,
the network gave us the names,
the names of the members of the Dutch cell.
- So... So, you have my name.
- Unfortunately not.
That's not possible.
- I'm new... I'm new to the network.
- Or perhaps you are lying.
If Martijn knows the names, Ahmat,
he must be a part of the network.
- The Agency might also have those names.
-La.
If the Agency had the names, they
would have already arrested the entire cell.
She's right. The CIA can't know.
The only one
who knows those names is me.
- It is the only way to prove it.
- There is a hole in the logic.
- No, Ahmat.
- There must be.
Let him do it. Let him prove it.
For the sake of his food programme.
All right.
You're doing the right thing.
We shall see.
My food programme is a big operation.
It's important.
Something to write with.
You are very lucky.
If not for her, you would be dead.
You will write the names of the Dutch cell
and the person that gave you that money.
- You first.
- Me?
- Why me?
- How else do I know that you're not lying?
You will only copy what I write.
We can write them at the same time.
All right.
One problem.
Thank you.
Thank you, Martijn.
You have been most cooperative.
All right, everybody. Nice job. Nice job.
Come on, let's go. Let's shut it down.
Shut it down.
Time to clean up.
What about the body?
Come on, come on.
This is not our first barbecue, people.
We all know the drill here.
Yeah, we know the drill.
He wouldn't have given us anything else.
How do you know?
Because I know.
- How do you feel?
- Like shite.
You know, you were supposed
to stand 10 feet away.
- I had to make it look convincing.
- Yeah.
I had powder burns all over my face,
for fuck's sake.
- Squibs hurt, huh?
- Yeah. My spine's still sore.
You'll live, baby.
Listen, get back out on the Net.
See who else you can rope in.
You all right?
You did great in there.
Thanks.
What do you say we go get a drink, huh?
Yeah.
Let's do that.
Marhaba.
Mr Fikri, please.
There is no Mr Fikri here.
Hassan Fikri?
I'm trying to reach Hassan Fikri.
There is no Hassan Fikri here.
You have been misinformed.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org