Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
RiPPED BY
~ADOMAX~
SEPTiCEMiA TEAM
It is time.
A little mas, we go.
If.
That does it happen?
He is that drinks fat mas that I have seen in my life.
Mio God.
Which does not he cry by? Ho Ho .
That said?
Ho Ho.
Perfecto in each sense.
Like him will we call?
I call my father Nicolas.
If.
Nicolas Claus.
Nicolas St.
Frederick?
Do you want to come to know your brother?
Come.
I love Fred for the first moment
That knew it.
In fact that day, he did him a promise.
I promise you to be the best brother
All world major.
Ho.
And Fred is himself the beginning of the story.
Sometimes doing a promise is easy.
That keep her.
If!
Ayudenme to cut the cake.
Hello Nicolas. I did this for you
Happy birthday.
Gracias Frederick.
That is very kind Frederick.
Nicolas ¿, to where you go?
There is a young poor called Henry
Crossing the track
I will donate him all my presents.
Mas needs them that myself.
That is charming. - Do you believe that Henry needs a diary with Nicolas name?
Frederick, lets be to your brother
If that is a saint.
And so it was for Fred.
Whenever towards proud to his parents.
You are seen Frederick, adorable.
Nicolas one arranged them to do mas
Proud to his parents.
The door was closed so I decided
Enter by the chimney, that amusing!
Nicolas.
The door not this closed.
Because that invents.
Myself did this garb, mother.
I would not tell that people.
In serious Frederick ¿, by that you can not be mas
Like your brother?
I do not want to hate him.
He has good intentions.
And I promised him to be the best brother
Of the world.
Your you are the only one that me Jo Jo understands.
Frederick, notes as much as you liked the tree
So we will put it inside of the house now
With a lot of trimmingses.
Is not that wonderful?
Jo Jo, never return.
Frederick?
Our poor friend.
That tree was her he finalizes drop.
He began to feel resentment by his brother
And his parents
And until himself.
And as a lot of unhappy children.
That put one furious.
Like a devil.
That passes Nicolas?
Nothing.
He stops well or Nicolas stops badly
He grew being generous mas and contingently.
..lleno la profesia de su mamá.
For humanity he turned into a saint.
It is a little hardly to accept that now when
You turn into holy
You remain frozen in the time
And you become eternal.
Everything applies the saint's family, I eat
His friends
You probably already must suspect now
Into which kind of holy turned
The world grew and I eat it maybe
Saint Claus.
But as I said to them before this he is
The story of Fred.
And in the following part of the story he happens
In a time and in a place that can be familiar mas for you.
He can not remove me my television
I see it in my bed.
These crazy?
You can not come like that and kick someone
I seized.
As many years do you have? - Nine.
And you have a 30 inch TV your room? Holy gave it to me by Christmas last year.
If, but the kind of the red coat
I did not take care your future ¿, truth?
That not vera by you, him I can see now
Afterwards chetoos 60 000 bags
You wake up you have 35, you have overweight and
tves novels with your wife
I did a favor, you you can go out to play
Outside, do friend.
Do atelticas things, you go to the school
You play sports, to have scholarships
Do you like some sport?
I bet that if, he finds out such as he is and put that
In your application for university.
Now, in a time the tio Sam
Leaning rot you
With that money you can buy one
Motorcycle.
Maybe know to a kind when east in
The school, you remained pregnant later
If he works with a boy, if not
To whom matter him!
These blessed of having that boy
In your life.
Athletic Seras, good girl, and you will have
To a boy before you graduate of university
Who will you have to him thank?
Not to the kind of the red dress.
But to your friend if.
It is bad grow.
He hears boys, you have strange children
Is it by you or by the television that you use as nursemaid?
If you do not pay your bills of new, the next one
Time sell by your wife.
The television goes to my home, asegurenlo
Either for which he does not get scratched.
"Ho ho Ho, is Christmas "
"Everybody
Atrapalo if want once.
We go, we go, that is
Slowly.
Podrias change the radio station friend?
Sera a friend dollar.
Can you change her new please? We Go, I like, that one, it is good.
Can he stop please?
We go, are not like that.
Stop the cart, by favor.
Wanda I have never seen you as attractive.
Freddy I am annoyed with you
I talk seriously, very annoyed.
Two complete days.
Me you must, I try to have a conversation
With you about changing us together
And you disappear later.
Fondness, not disappeared. I was in
A business selling kids of the India opportunity.
There are not kids in the India.
Being honest stops my kid
It is very strong now.
Freddy ¿, you know that day is tomorrow? - Tomorrow?
If, one that day is tomorrow.
Seriously? Tomorrow is tomorrow.
And today it is today.
We should not waste it discussing.
Freddy what is significant of morning. - Is this conversation on the dia after today?
If... Me these asking.
Freddy what I am about saying is that when
Arrive at a minute after the midnight
He tomorrow starts and that one is my birthday.
That? Ho not.
That the se. ¿, you do not believe that not the one?
Clear that the one.
Freddy. - That?
Do not do that, one you forgot that of my birthday
I know you very well.
Do not forget your birthday. - Did you forget?
I have a surprise for you in fact.
But you ruined it now.
You remember your he finalizes surprise, after ours
1er year of anniversary
You took me to types of Frances, you took me
To the top of a tower
And you led me to bet in a can
To Indiana.
Because I did the first to get you out
Hence.
But he went productive, study by
Three weeks.
That part of your life nobody you her can
Remove.
Do you have time?
Do I bring you a cafe cup?
I can not be upset with you.
Will you tell me on the surprise?
If I tell it to you not serious join surprise.
The one, but... you have razon
But maybe you mention.
Do you know that?
You dire on the surprise.
It is not a surprise you already know that he is, it is alone a moment
For a such as special occasion that you already know, he is.
It is a supper. If.
In a place very good here in the city
Called Palace Bonsai.
He rings relative, Palace Bonsai.
Not these inventing this?
If we go to the Palace Bonsai, is going to exist ¿, will be there?
In the absolute, it is an impressive place. This well one.
Her it will happen well.
Can you do that? If.
We will see Bambi videos.
This well one?
This well one.
Do you have to go by behind the sofa?
He looks at your feet, they are dirty and you put them on my bed.
I establish it. - Does he want milk?
Fred, I asked for saint an east pup
I will call year, Macarroni.
Not to where Saint must send my present
Because not one where be in the morning of the 25.
If my mom gets sick one, I will be in the hospital
Or I will finish passing with my Ma's boyfriend.
That you think Fred?
Did I send it?
Bundle thought on Saint Claus?
Not in reality. The kind this of I brought red because he does not like it the light.
The kind is a clown, is a maclomaniaco.
One presents with a good boy, I give things
But there are a lot of things below that.
¿ You know that statues sell mas
Of saint. That of them Buddha?
The big kind that you have big nails
I eat.
Do not believe in Saint Claus, a lot
This well one?
Piensalo, look it in other angles, you are not
Credulous, your you are better than that.
I like Saint. If, but not much.
I assume that your you do not believe in him.
I get what I want Saint's help
He grasps the glass with two hands, by favor.
With the two hands, the truth is that I have
A small business
I have my money working for him
It is a new class business.
Of class? Class .
Are not repetitive, you are better than that.
He owes slightly best credit please. You Have To have the all the 50 thousand for the 20.
It is the only way as I can separate it for you
I have respirandome people the neck.
I have the money.
Maybe I do not have us... the money.
It is not on the money
What passes is that I have to do I eliminate that money
I have to have the money a situation he eliminates
For power have it.
Such as is she the big mas industry of America?
Betting ¿ is true?
This empty place at this moment, sera the
Put mas request of the city in 3 months.
We are in charge of the change building
Of the state.
I seized that each dia when the market closes
He is here where they will come
This place means all give birth my
Please.
I have to have it. Listens, I do not want to listen to mas
Him I need for the 22 and that is the best
I can do.
24, 25, as I am, we will do it work. I Want to listen to saying the 22.
The 22, 23 perfect sera. The 22, has to be.
The 23, maybe ... The 22, and that is everything.
Not dire mas, this well ones.
But if you say the 23.
Event.
¡ This well one, ladies and gentlemen, want
That people helps each other between them!
Give me an embrace!
Who is the jungle queen? Your it are!
Do we see what you have?
We go, I like it as you are.
Give me something of paper, and others 20.
I will take all. - Everything?
Hear lady! If he wants true salvation
For the children, come here.
Bring his ashes here, you demolish, help
People do.
He can do it, by yourself give me a second
Please.
He forgives my action.
That either that I help this people
That I have a cute Christmas.
Go of here.
I want to see his permission, he needs
An east permission for which in the street.
I do not answer you to you, I answer people.
Ocupate of your things by favor.
This is my business. - That this passing?
This kind this working without papers
And speech on the salvation.
I am not talking about salvation. They See here.
Nobody this talking to it to nobody
He stops being unpleasant.
Muestrame your papers, clown.
We are in the XXI, century, I am in her
Internet, if they enter there
They will see a photo of mine, dinosaur. This well, calls the police.
There is a police there!
Hear!
Agarrenlo!
Grasp to that kind!
Come!
¡ By himself a man will go out thereof
And I promise him
That sera the kind that has the things yellow
In the hands!
Can he listen to me?
It is Fred.
This in the restaurant?
Digale that calls me so soon
As this well one can? ¿
We will talk soon.
Her not this telephone fence.
It is Christmas.
He walks, do other call.
There is not not a black hair
All this white.
Fondness ¿, you believe that he sees me silly if I shave myself? You Have a cute head fondness.
But this very white. You do not have to let you take by the appearance.
One that I am stressed, has
A lot in my head.
You are seen annoyed.
Fondness, we are 2 late % mas that
Last year. Not one if him we will achieve.
You must not cause stress you.
Verificandome Estan now, we have not been
As deficient suedes, the one.
Nick. Fred.
As these do I join? Is good listen to your voice.
How are they any the things? Either, the business this as crazy
But we go well
As these your?
That is impressive, I am very happy by you
That good by you.
If, we are putting to the dia
That passes Fred? Is there something that can do by you?
If you want to send a present, really
I suppose that you can send 5 thousand
To the police with my name.
Five thousand dolares?
I am well by the way
I am well.
Wait a second, waits. I do Not want to say nothing, but Fred.
This in a difficult situation fondness.
One that it is difficult but you have to practice
Be strong fondness.
I am a saint, strong fondness, be is
Something difficult one give birth my.
Hello Fred. Hello.
This well one, will send it to the season.
Happy Christmas Frank.
Really the appreciation.
Do you know that? Myself you dare something, you dare
An east present year.
You dare 10 thousand in cash this Christmas.
As that establishes one?
I do not understand, I am giving five Fred.
Nicolas you have to accept what people you offers
We are honest people.
Sent then 50 thousand mas the 5
And wait for me by a month
dejemoslo in 60 ¿, this well ones?
Then you 10 thousand mas of what dare
You gave me, with the 50 on the way back
Of that way I will give you 5 thousand
By Christmas.
He waits for a second Fred.
Fifty thousand besides the five? - That?
That is in UK, Nick do me a favor little
Do not make this complicated
Let me give to feel me other present
Good.
This well Fred, sight.
You dire that... will pay the five thousand stops you
But if you want the rest
You will have to come here.
Not!
If, you have to win you that money!
We are honest, I do not believe that I am a bad one
He devises work for you
Do you know something? Never do come
Here, not even once.
That is what I have to do?
Put rubber stamps to her biscuits
Putting the stars, to where the dwarfs do not arrive sew easily.
I have to have the money for the 22. This well one.
The I need that dia. This well one.
The 22.
¿ This sera does not join ambush
With my mom?
We go, he not ire run to mom.
I do not have idea because you do not give me
The fifties to give you sixty.
Him I establish, I go to practice love hard
With you friend.
This well one?
And I tell you right now whether not these of agreement
I establish it, but I can not pay your surety.
We go it is Fred!
Fondness one that these in house!
¡ Freddy walks home, I do not want
Talk with you!
By myself I want an opportunity give birth
Explain you.
¿ You want to explain me my romantic supper
Of birthday?
I was working for solidary people
They pursued me as 30 Saint Claus!
Callate, people slave trade of sleeping!
I tell you the truth! - She does not believe you so he vetos!
He hears Garcia I am being about talking with. - Callate!
You are the worst one.
Freddy walks home at this moment.
Wanda there was an unexpected situation and I have
That to be going to work tonight.
In which these?
One is business that I have my brother.
Freddy, when I knew you you said me
That not taeniae a brother!
Tecnicamente I have her brother
Mother, but I do not feel that him I have.
Escuchame. - Already get tired of this relation!
I not. I do Not stand it.
I have not ended. I can Not mas.
I can stand him even. Freddy I believe that I will come back London
Good luck with your brother, if
It is that he exists.
I am happy to your side!
Wanda!
Hello.
I am not, hurried now.
They come to see my father. - Which do you talk about?
Come here.
Who is you?
I am the boy's father
We are social services, we come to see
East young person's home.
According to our you report his father
He died a year ago.
Pense that you said that your father was.
They see a second here.
You can not count in nobody, son.
You have to always take care of you.
You know as do that ¿, truth?
If.
Lighten something.
If he hopes it to stay in an orphanage
These wasting his time.
Vamonos.
Are you Fred?
If.
Can I see an identification, by favor?
A taste know Fred.
My name is Willy I am the assistant
Of Saint.
I had not guessed it.
Is that one his bag? If.
I take it. - These insurance?
If I can.
Her attracted.
We are well.
I had done it if you gave me an opportunity
mas.
Come.
Escuchame, I am not as good in this
Of flying.
We will go to the north pole, he tastes when he travels like that
But if I would like if we talked.
This sera
Seriously?
A stop at Hokey.
There one are passenger behind, in case
That I do not remember it.
I establish it, I do not vomit at least.
He take cares of your steps.
Good, here this.
The elves' city
I adjoint ¿, truth?
The workshop this behind your.
Is it Fred? Hello, welcome to that
Pole north, is very nice to have it here.
I am Charlene, the little assistant to Saint
I feel hustle, him but we have to comply with the timetable
Because we are 439 hours, 22 minutes and 30 seconds
He stops the crucial dia.
It is good with the numeros and it is beautiful.
Thanks
Wlliy. - Willy!
Gracias Willy.
I wait to Holy in 26 seconds.
Display the point where we are
I repeat, revise the meeting point.
Allergies.
You have a weapon!
That it happens?
Not, boys, slowly!
Fred.
That was a madness!
That devils he passes here?
Not taeniae dwarfs when I arrive ¿, that you do with them?
You have to excuse the boys, it is Christmas
It is a tense period.
One they put gamboling, they have to assure one that nothing passes me.
Maybe must give him a lesson!
Not, by himself forgetting it, did not pass of new
They will not make it of new.
Give them a rest. The hare immediately .
Do you remember to Annete?
Say to him hello.
Annete ¿, that I pass with my bill?
That one finalizes night in the carcel you he has he put
Very funny.
That is impressive, because he notes one
A lot of him that work here.
Seriously? Because myself pense that consents
To ask him for a loan to your brother from new.
This well one.
The family this assembly of new
That amusing.
Fred, already arranges a room for you.
I will put you with Willy.
Good, here we are.
Care with the head.
It happens.
Aqui this.
That do you think?
Warm, very warm.
To be honest they do not do a lot
Homes for huespedes.
I do not believe that someone has slept in
That bed per years.
Either Willy, thanks for having me.
Good Fred night.
These better insurance that you will not be here down?
I do not believe that he will do a lot of difference.
This well one.
Good night.
Willy, himself for which he knows it
I am not a morning person.
Good, Holy that told me you of an orientation
Of the process of giving presents.
Better Sera than we start.
This Fred Aqui ... Saint's workshop.
Everything starts with a boy
And a letter.
All around the world, the children are
Writing the same
And it is what they want for Christmas.
Wanted Holy. Only him I love that
It is an orange bike with hearts.
The children all letters
They enter here, in the postal office of the north pole.
They come of all the world.
Once received they go straight to the distributor
Of presents.
Each made toy that a boy asks for, this
To hand by the elves.
It is important that each boy is manned.
Once built, they pack up it and
Finally
The toys are ready for Christmas
And they are delivered by Saint.
Aqui comes Holy Claus.
You are going to love this.
We have our own DJ.
Hello Donny DJ, Donny.
Good, the man is known mas
Of the north pole.
DJ Donny tell it my brother hello
Freddy major.
Can you give me a ho Ho?
Not.
If you do not say it these fried.
Of all the departments.
...este es el rey de todos los procesos, el
All operation sympathetic nervous system.
Do you have a list of the rud mas?
If, we have to Johnny Rollins now in
Nova Scotia, this in the place I number one.
Last month bit his father and
To his dentist.
Which did he bite them by?
I assume that they put his hands very
He encloses to his mouth.
Opening that sometimes the children are
Naughty and kind.
In that case. We do the determination
Putting the hands on the snowballs.
I will show you as he works.
Jimmy Jackson, New York's city.
Do not do me damage!
That seems to be very aggressive.
Not one that does. Fred Good Morning.
Fondness ¿, I can talk with you? Clear that if.
Fred remain there, do not move you. Ire to see the girls that they move their feet
I wait are filthy.
Fred this very motivated, sera of a lot of
He helps here.
Do I eat any these Fred?
That good work with you.
The train will come in 15 minutes.
Everything will be well. The one.
Give me a kiss. If, the hare.-
Aqui we go.
This either, pongamoste to work!
I will explain you this in terms very
Simple ¿, this well ones?
Do you see any those files?
I want you to revise them.
If the boy is seen slightly naughty.
We put it as naughty.
But if the boy seems kind to you.
You put him kind.
I am a good judge, that is what I am. Well
I have to drain me, I have to go
To know that someone ¿, this well one?
This well captain.
Do good work, brother. immediate Delivery.
Hare the best than I can.
Is that everything? If, opening.
That is himself the beginning.
This either everybody, mio here God, comes
Saint Claus.
Aqui comes Holy Claus.
Not taenia that come in helicopter
Gentleman Norca
I had sent a sleigh.
I do not like deer.
Did I want to settle down?
We have his room ready.
Maybe want to take a nap. I do not take any naps.
He sounds like to which mortal sera.
How 6096 can see in the picture.
The estimate of the list of children
He has grown in last a hundred years substantially.
In the 1800, the children that did not ask for mas
An item and they were common interests
Something as helping that a member of the family
Or the end of war.
I remember that, try to go down by those chimneys.
The I match 345 LB, he shows that today a young one
He asks for 50 presents by letter.
This wants to say that his operations must go down
Every year.
And this is not enough gentleman Claus.
We are not here to give to each boy
Each present that quieran.-
Part of Christmas is to thank the things
That can not have.
If I were that simple.
Is not it? No, deplorably.
Vera
Her puts this together thinking seriously.
..en cerrarlo.
That?
We are going to close?
We will consolidate a support, a new
Operation, improved
And one that this sera hardly listen
For you
Put on the south pole.
But by himself he is not you, we will put the elves
In an adoption system.
He will do it a year, but he must later
Forget them.
We are going to throw out the rabbit also from Easter.
this does not yet have sense; Easter; rabbit;
Eggs and all that.
It is one lost of energy.
Now, follow with the proximo
Problem
All feeds the elves?
Wanda McAllister.
Chicago, Ilinois.
Is someone special? If.
She is my girl.
Forget completely
I have a coin here.
If, him I feel, but he is two minutes late.
Seriously?
If, seriously.
You must not feel good that people discusses
With you all the time.
If, but it is part of my work.
That how if one do I compensate it?
Dejeme lead her to have dinner.
Have dinner with you?
Considerelo joins supper and one
Good conversation.
I can, not thanks
But no.
Seeing to a kind bounce is always painful.
Does boyfriend have?
Not.
That is something good one.
That do you say?
Him a ticket dare. And myself him dare my card.
A taste know it. Is the best ticket that have given me.
Have a good dia.
"The Step "
Certain.
They are not going to consider this, other request
Of "Aqui Saint Claus comes "
Of Beth, there Beth goes.
These bromeandome?
With the same song?
Hear DJ.
DJ Donny!
That there is Fred?
¡ You have to stop touching the same one
Song because me this boring!
But Fred is very good.
This well one, is a song that is touched
Again and again
And instead of shouting the same song
You must put something different one.
I said that not. Donny changes the song.
Not!
Change the song! - Not!
I will change the song you.
You do not get like that, her puts to music one slave trade
Of love.
That do you do?
Tab.
Do you want to arrest you?
Better Sera than you calm down, socket
A bath, stops disturbing me.
You are going to calm?
Do you know that?
I will put you on the cabin of naughty
There you the truths.
Hold, he walks with the elves.
He uses your words.
When you go out you will give bill that
You must change song.
Do not do it!
Haras that them Elves you feel offended!
Dejame go out! - That is!
This feels different, they touched it
Same song all the time
It is time of changing, they begin to dance
And diviertanse.
Do not do you fondness, he begins to move you. Mio God .
RiPPED BY
~ADOMAX~
SEPTiCEMiA TEAM
He sounds ugly. The one.
I like it.
To continue life in the pole north
We have done it in three not fulfilled rules
How is it that?
If you arrive at Christmas without three warnings
One I sented an I settle homewards.
However if he does not fulfil the three you regulate
This operation sera closed permanently.
And a thing, absolutely nobody.
..necesita saber por que estoy aqui,
In special the elves.
Opening, gentleman Clyde, the elves
With extremely polite
I became impressed gentleman.
Devils.
Put that out.
Everybody, this is the gentleman Nortec.
That will be with us until Christmas
Give him the welcome and let that I observe please.
Get back to work.
Suedes have never behaved like that.
One the insurance.
There is not discipline with the elves, they show
A complete lack of control.
That one is a big disappointment and that sera
Broken first rule.
I establish it, do not listen to his name.
It is Fred, he is my older brother hello.
This helping the season.
Not wise that taeniae a brother.
Gentleman Nortec, him dire to someone who shows him
The place.
Willy.
He takes a tour, by favor.
That devils bundles?
Nick let me be honest you here
The DJ is a true problem.
But it is the specified one.
Nicky puts the same song again and again.
I understand you.
Decidio put me the hands above
And put physical.
This well one?
I have one destiny that to take.
He lowers a little your voice.
And to be honest if you decide to punish him
I will not be annoyed with you.
I will not worry me with you to the concerning
If you want to pass him the hammer in his DJ hands
By yourself do it. This well one.
That is a thought and I will have bill.
But what I am about saying you is
That you must keep you peaceful
It now, is very important
This well one?
You must not bring in to DJ meeting room mas.
I understand, we are two brothers talking now.
And we are good at where we come. That is what he counts.
Now that you told me that, it is not going to get back to happen
Because from now on kind sere
You not do not, have to do that.
Love and the goodness flows of you
I eat a radiation or something.
Not, your you stayed in your season.
Correct. Like a sailor ¿, truth?
Freddy me brightens up a lot who have accepted
My invitation to have dinner.
I loved it happen between brothers. You Have razon.
Nick. - By which?
Nick.
That?
That do they do at your home?
I want you to be honest
Does she know that I am here?
You know, call me crazy, but my Ma comes
And me he visits by the parties every year ¿, this well one?
I am not going to bring in because I do not visit my Ma
In the parties and by a good razon.
Serious very nice if this time
The things are well and calm
By himself he enters to have dinner with us.
This is a trap
I am not going to go.
We go, I do not want to listen to one not.
This went on, we will not be going to have dinner
You will open the book and truths that in her finalizes paginates
I am not going to have dinner, that is everything.
It is similar, the sequence starts now
Do you know as he calls one?
Ding dong ¿, who this there?
It is Fred
I am not going to go! We Go.
Not ire to have dinner!
Hello, I expect not to be inconvenient, me hit
With your parents and me they invited to have dinner.
He does not, stop anything, welcome.
Aqui has.
Frederick ¿, as bundle state?
I have been well mom
Very well.
You inspired dire that Fred has done a work
In this apartment.
Not always inspired, I had some complications
In one that other place.
I do the best than I can.
Not, these doing good work.
Good, I imagine that he must be a good one
Hard worker considering.
Considering that?
Considering that you did not have time of coming
To our anniversary party.
Your I join if I accompany us.
But I send a charming present.
We go, he is perfume one saw very dear.
Him he went surely.
This well one.
These out.
That enjoys the letter inclusive wine with that.
Do you remember what you wrote in the Frederick card?
We see, I was something I eat.
Happy anniversary, I hope you to hang yourself
With the bun.
He eats something fondness, the potatoes
They are delicious.
Prefiriria that does not do that, Nicolas
It is allergic.
Perfecto, these seeing a man that he travels
The world in an alone night.
That is incredible. This either, mom.
Forgetting that never rots Nicolas
You amaze me.
Is not it amazing? I Believe that it is
Think that he flies to million of houses
In a night, I eat theft.
During the children they sleep that this eating
His biscuits, it is something fantastic one and he amazes me a lot
By yourself you think all those laws broken
Do not they feel it?
Frederick ¿, by which these so I am unpleasant?
We go mom. Not.
Alone wish that you were mas like your brother
That is everything.
Impressive, I believe that I will feel me mas comfortable
With the elves
With some mouthfuls and a milk. We Go, you are not like that Fred.
The relatives love know.
He is so
Revealing.
Fred, hello!
Advance my friend one.
Do I eat any these Willy? I Am well.
A drink stops Fred hello.
Make it double. Thanks.
Fred
Charlene. If.
You know, you see this people after the work
And they are good with you
Opening that are German. If.
Fred good night.
Charlene good night.
Good night.
Willy.
Fred, not the one.
I do not understand it Fred
She does not know my name?
That passes Fred?
I am I!
You can tell it to me Fred
This either, your you are my friend
Is it by that he thinks that I am a strange one?
I love her.
Willy, you have to be fence his.
Fred, I can not nor tell him one joke
Last night pense that was going to stop listening to me.
The thing is easy. Let it know that these I list give birth
Entertain and you are not going to excuse you.
You know, in the last year party
I ask him to dance with me almost.
Despues I remembered that I can not dance.
Even.
That?
You can not dance even.
Fred, I feel ridiculous
Not one how dance.
This is very I am inconvenient.
Give birth my.
We go, go out from your head by a second
And he moves your body.
I either, I do not believe that I do that, not
I can do that.
Do you know that? He stops talking with this
By himself he dances.
He brings all that goodness that you have.
We go, you are a green angel.
Put your hand here.
We go, are not shy.
By yourself you will do a small movement.
That is, by yourself you inclined side by side.
As you are small it is something good one
Because you have to bring closer ¿ you, certain?
Asi that further, by himself approach to my.
That is good.
The proximo that you will, do is to put
Your hand in my back.
That one is not my back.
You have to lift a little your hand.
Slave trade remembers, dancing not one of
Dancing, is about connecting.
Mirame to the eyes.
Impressive, if you went join woman
I would have the goose bumps.
The impressive of dancing is that is
A bridge stops a kiss.
Only him you have to do it is to entertain
And see that she also does it.
And when I arrive the correct moment
You do your set-to, with the blood
Flowing that him I feel, that the
Heart beats and we make it to happen.
We go, you turned and he proves what you have.
Asi is, is a way of seeing it.
Baby goes on moving you.
He is still like that, you make it well.
That this well one but not him this
So he must be well.
Do it!
Me he likes, do it strong mas
That is.
Forget my gloves.
This well, by himself raise slowly.
Everything this well one.
Willy!
You fell down, big thing.
Everyone does not fall down opposite
Opposite to the girl who love.
I was seen like a total idiot.
As showing rots in do I publish?
It is ridiculous.
Thanks to God, Blitzen did not feel
I seized when he learned to dance.
When Blitzen
One her does not chronicle me.
We go, everyone knows it.
-¿Cuando Blitzen aprendio a volar?
-Se cayo de cara.
-¿Asi fue?
-Si.
Corrio stops give boost and one key
But I raise and one he went on trying.
I stop thinking and he flew contingently.
It is common knowledge.
-Vamos, Fred.
-Es cierto.
-No soy Blitzen.
-No estoy de acuerdo.
One that you have Blitzen mas inside
Yours of what you give bill.
Love is as complicated.
If, it can be him.
He hurts.
I am proud of you, Willy.
-Buenas noches.
-Buenas noches, Fred.
Maldicion.
To where were all the letters?
That cute, Lucy wants a kitchen Sep
Good, so one her fondness graces, ago.
The small Kenan Adams
He wants a bike.
I assume that angers the bus to the school.
Fredy, you have been very bad.
Never get the letters, out
Bequeath to the S not even.
I do not need to tell you it important
That are those files.
Without them we do not have idea
Of what the children want.
Or if they are good or bad.
And your responsibility was to have them sight.
Already I said to you, do not take anything.
That this passing?
Which do you judge me with your crossed arms by?
You I am not judging, I am nervous.
I also it would be if I were
Charging someone mas.
Can you believe to this kind?
You I have my sight Bob.
If? When you want.
If you talk as elf at some moment
You will have to act as one.
-Si.
-Habla bien.
He has mas that reaches your Bob.
-¿Problemas?
-No, no.
Nobody in Winscosin will receive presents this year!
Mio God, young beggars.
Do not you have any lists of backing?
I had never passed something like that one but
Insurance they will, appear after all
Where could they go to?
Not have any lists of backing
That one is the second miss.
One that is not mio business but
I am something worried about Fred.
And I appreciate his worry
Clyde Mr but that this well one.
That I have seen this is suedes, the children
Lies, annoyance shows.
I can assure him that the this well one.
But one can put much more worse.
Digame ¿, has been begging
Big money sums?
That must the problems?
Has some caused?
-Si, asi es, Sr.
-Por supuesto.
This asking for help to shouts and
If someone does not help it
I fear that he will get ugly.
That can I do?
It is all what I have.
If in something but no he liked pense.
Which type of party is this?
Haganlo now!
Dance!
These crazy? pense that
They were extraterrestrial.
You have to pay something to compensate
The damage that I have had.
And not sera cheap, I have a lawyer
That has a lot of vowels his surname.
And you I got in touch and he will make you feel
The ache that myself senti.
It is a familiar intervention.
Your behavior is unacceptable.
-Bueno, hola.
-Hola, ¿estas bien?
I feel very well
How have you been your?
-He estado trabajando.
-Es grandioso.
The work is something good one give birth
Do when bundles things.
I do not work a lot, I have been
Quarrelling by my life.
But my brother is Saint Claus.
If, him I can see.
It is different.
If, everything has been something unusual one.
Your brother brought to someone that
We believe that he can help you
The Doctor Goldfarb, is your erratic behavior
Him a lot of stress brings your brother.
-Por Dios, no estoy estresado.
-Te caes por pedazos.
-No es asi.
-Si, asi es.
-Y tienes mucho sobrepeso.
-No es asi.
He does not have idea what
This passing his son.
It is a compulsory dining room and he has
Developed reflex acids
-y apneas al dormir.
-Solo ronco.
He is me awake all the night
And this affecting his health.
Without mentioning other marriage aspects.
Sometimes he does not detach the sleigh ¿ not?
Please, we go to the grain, he is
Very simple, it is always the same.
Your you cause problems and you give excuses then
That you were take caring of to someone mas.
From which I was small.
Does he know that? I can not have him
Said more good, that is what you do Fredie.
Impressive, by yourself do me that
Favor of not involving ¿ if?
I came by the intervention
They asked me to come.
Do not you have an appointment an elder now?
-¿Me has estado espiando?
-Si.
-¿No tienes nada mejor que hacer?
-No me gusta lo que veo.
If you had spied me well
You could that not go out with that kind.
Dejame telling you something, does not favour you
It be seen with a man who seems
Your grandfather, it is a bad election.
You I can such as saying is your problem, you do not leave
That nobody you loves because you do not think you deserve it.
If you could answer
You do I invite to go out a old man?
-Si.
-¡Eso es todo!
-No lo volvi a ver.
-Salio con el.
He stops going out, loose the telephone.
That is all, enough, I excuse
Santa Claus Mr was very good
If
There an elf is outside, salt with that.
I hope everything to go you well.
There are many ugly outside
You liked me.
-Creo que estamos progresando
-¿Quieren saber las buenas noticias?
He tomorrow is my I finalize dia
We do not have to have therapy.
The therapy is for people
That wants to be in your life
We do not have that problem.
I will finish my work and
Me ire of always give birth here
-Linda noche.
-Pierdete.
You are Santa Claus brother
That must be complicated.
I have a brother who is a Doger
And it is as if I did not exist.
The way like you tries all your family.
-¿Cual es tu historia?
-¿Perdon?
What is that east trying, not I worked.
-¿Y que es eso?
-No lo se.
But there is something gloomy one on you
And himself one that from which you arrived
-mi hermano esta nervioso y algo agitado.
-Eso es maravilloso.
That is wonderful?
That you are you interested in your brother's well being.
Clear that insurance that makes the same by you.
¿ You have seen to a tree sometimes
That grows in the shadow of other?
Everything without way is twisted by trying
Arrive at the sun light desperately.
If someone cut a little that one
Big, east tree would grow hard.
But life is not like that.
Everyone loves to that big tree
Everyone is proud of that
It does not matter them of the next door one.
From the small tree that one rehusa to grow.
While nobody cuts that big tree
The child the light will never give him.
Never!
The I establish, not one of where wine that.
Christmas, good night.
That rays was it that?
It seems that other boy has just
Occupy the first place of bad.
Slam?
Illinois Chicago Samuel Gibbons?
-¿Que le estas pidiendo a Santa?
-Una familia.
I also.
Saint will not give them families, Saint
He is a clown, he likes the fame
He has a big sleigh and he walks one
By the city with his reindeers.
That is the man this despaired by attention
He needs to be in center of attention.
That is what mas him costs that
Do not consider all that silly.
Callate, never you they adopted because you are bad.
Sueltalo!
Wanted Holy: I would like a pup
He stops Christmas Thanks. Slam.
GOOD.
Saint, the numeros three times lei.
Do not mention this anyone.
In special not to Clyde.
If, Mr
¿ That hiciste? rays, you marked to
All the bad children as good.
These crazy?
None seemed bad to me.
You never see the nothing consequences.
We can not do many presents in 3 days
Nor we neither will be able to deliver them.
Do you see it? I end one. Congratulations.
You cost Christmas to all the planet.
Everybody, by every Africa.
Everything went by the odorless one.
Culpamelo all to my.
How can I arrange it?
Annette and Ma had razon you.
Guardatelo! You should maybe
Look you to you to vary.
You follow atragantandote with bread
Of ginger, chubby boy.
You are a silly one!
You know that I have that problem
Per years, it is not funny.
Do you know that? tragatelo red thigh.
Me I get tired, to east tree fell down him light
Someone cut that fat tree.
-No tengo que aceptar tus abusos.
-No hay manera de no darte, gordo.
You seem a girl with leather frock coat.
We go, Nick.
How did you come to work?
Rolling?
Your did you steal a boy some sleigh?
Good night, princesita.
You seem a gigantic snowball.
Did you want to kill me perhaps?
Bill had not given me
You hate me.
I you do not hate Nick.
By myself I would want that you were never born.
Clyde Nortcut is not of
Human resources
He is an expert in efficiency.
And this to one fails of closing me.
Permanently.
I wait that east happy.
I want my money, a relation is a relation.
The despite you win and you do not deserve a cent.
Queria that you had this, also.
Happy Christmas, Fred.
We go, Willie.
Nortcut ¿ Mr, I wanted to see Mr?
If, then he is, put to Fred Claus, in the morning.
That the we can correct.
If one can.
We have time enough even.
They remain less than 3 days
You know that there is not way of achieving it.
I believe that you know what he means.
Third class fails.
Saying this does not give me pleasure but
Who do I deceive? It is wonderful.
Layoff Notificacion.
These seen off.
Fred, is Leon, 20 seconds. It is your big dia
I have 20 big in the hand.
Llamame, do.
It is not that that does not love my brother
I am successful, we are very joint.
Of children we shared it all.
My mother always said to me from which was small
That taenia that to support to my brother.
And Rocky Salian and the things changed then.
I was the first in knowing it
And then when Rocky 3 Salian.
I wanted to know mas about my brother.
It was like an identity theft
Rocky quarrelled and tried
Of making it all well
I want to thank them by listening to me
I sit down either here, it is wonderful.
Thanks for sharing, Frank.
I believe that he touches Roger now.
I have some things that I want to say.
Tendras that wait for your turn.
Roger has been waiting
He finalizes it time could not talk.
I wanted to share.
I am roger a brother in recovery.
Hello Roger.
My brother is Bill Clinton
He was the president of the EUA.
I was changing with the TV canals
And there was a speech in the story canal
Of 1993 when I leave the White House
Wise person that serious the first step to the recovery
But I did not, get back to cry.
And now not one if he rots recover completely.
Ahi I can enter and saying what passes me.
-¿Quien eres?
-Soy Fred.
Hello Fred.
Further ¿, you wanted to talk now?
-Me llamo Frank Claus.
-Hola Frank.
I am
I am Santa Claus brother.
I have mind, always a lot
There is a lot of juice in the tank.
-Y...
-¿Esto es una broma para ti?
-De por cierto, soy Steven.
-Hola Steven.
By which this is not funny for all us.
That is very serious for us.
Me I feel very I am inconvenient by what you say.
Steven, maybe in serious
His brother is Santa Claus.
I feel that my brother is Santa Claus.
I also but because if it is in reality.
Enough! We have a problem.
Peaceful Steven, sedative.
That is not Alec, you do not look me to my but to that.
-No es Alec.
I am not Alec.
-Bien, continuemos.
-No es Alec.
-Steven, Alec no escuchara eso.
-¿Como lo oira?
-No es Alec.
-¡No es Alec!
It is not Alec!
Now that you have that attention
Of Alec ¿ that you want to tell him?
Steven.
I believe that I understand what you want.
By which I used to be very annoyed with my brother.
I did not want to be the First Brother.
Not by the my life rest.
Not podia control be brother
Of the president of the EUA.
But if I could control be the brother
Of Bill Clinton and take the decision
Though I could destroy the house.
That takes the decision by love of my brother
And by my family's name
That was going to do what was needed
Because I loved my brother.
And I was always going to be there for that.
And him I have been and ¿ you know that?
Your also you can do it.
Agency? I need to arrive at that
North Pole immediately
I have 50 dolares effective
That say that I do not mention.
-Polo norte.
-¿Aca es?
Thanks, you take cared.
Willy puts all the elves together
And he finds in the workshop.
Walking.
Boys look, we have to do many presents
As one can in the next 10 hours.
It is the eve of Christmas, it is impossible.
Many one can not build
Toys in this time.
The rule tells each boy to receive a toy
Such as is it the mas easy to do?
One for children and one for girls.
-Un bate de baseball.
-Un Ula Ula.
You beat of baseball and ula them.
Charlene ¿ you believe that achieving it am possible?
If, it is possible.
It is but he is not what the children asked for.
Only him that costs is that the
Children receive a present.
That everyone has something that to open
When one wake up in the morning.
The important mas that they know that he is
Someone over there outside who thinks of them.
Uds. They were never absent no Christmas.
Uds. They would go out this year
Saldran to try it.
This either, us will order.
His back this hurt.
Hello Annette ¿, as these?
Fred.
Hello friend, I believe that we will, achieve it
All the workshop this doing presents.
I believe that him we will be able to achieve
Even you rot save Christmas
-tienes que levantarte y motivarte.
-Eso es imposible.
He can hardly load his own weight.
I can not move, me
I can not fly.
Clearly that you can, is Christmas.
The children count on us.
Desearia power.
Willy this is your big night
You delivered the presents, that can do it.
I can not Fred.
Clear that you can, you are impressive in the sleigh.
You do not understand, I can not. There is a rule.
By himself a Claus can deliver the presents.
Would they mind leaving us alone?
I can not do it, I believe that you know it.
I am not able, I do not feel comfortable flying.
I do not believe that that improves doing it in a reindeer.
Fred
This well one.
That someone waits for that is ridiculous.
You can not do it.
Believing me is huge. The one.
I could not ask you you to do that.
This well one.
The world is as you do it.
But everything starts by as you do it your.
I want you to believe in yourself.
Because you have which to believe in a lot.
The rest fell on his place.
-¿Esta bien?
-Esta bien.
-Feliz Navidad, amigo.
-Feliz navidad, Santa.
If?
He takes your notecase.
It is a good beginning
For the next one by yourself you do not do it.
This well one.
I believe that we will achieve it.
Christmas 1 ¿ listens to me?
North Pole, further.
Good luck advance in her
Darkness without candles, Fredie.
And from now on all Uds
Dwarfs are seen off.
Go home, bale his stockings.
They came back to the Elf's small town or of where are.
North Pole?
North Pole, is Christmas 1.
Further.
Boys!
I believe that we are to blind here.
He stops when the sun goes out, everything will have ended.
I see you in the morning.
Archibal Nortcut Clyde.
422 street Dashwood
Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
If, you managed to be the bad mas in the 68.
That one was a bad year.
You can not remember that
You asked me for a superman cape
But her do ¿ not say you truth?
-¿siempre usaste lentes?
-Si crees que esto cambiara algo...
Clyde 4 eyes, apposed which I seized called you.
Not one of that you talk.
Despues of all that you got angry a little maybe.
Quizas you started a quarrel or two
Maybe 10 or mas.
Asi that you asked me for castrates it of superman
Because you thought that that the exchange everything.
This is ridiculous.
If, but when that turns one into superman
That does not yet need those glasseses ¿ truth?
It was bad of my not give you that present
I fear that I made a very serious mistake
There are not bad children.
I establish it.
Quizas is something late.
Do you want to put her to you?
I am a 45 years old man, I will not put me
We go!
By my.
-Esta bien.
-Asi es.
Out the glasseses.
I need your help now.
Do you know what any bundles?
They are the 2 am.
Turn on the left!
I need your help seriously
I need you to enchant the light, Superman.
One him you can do that.
Already I deliver my report, it is final.
If Fred does not deliver all the presents
Until the dawn in North Pole
Closed sera always stops
That I understand it.
But that you say whether we give him an opportunity?
He is not a bad boy.
I believe that we are well.
That seems to be the big canyon.
Rays.
Fred 4:15.
I try to go the rapido mas that I can.
We need mas speed to this altitude.
-Solo dime cuando volteo.
-Ahora.
-Fred.
-Lo se, Willy, lo se.
I have a bad premonition.
We did it.
-¡Si!
To the globe of nine.
You are the best older brother
That someone can have.
Fred?
-Te traje un regalo de navidad.
-¿Como entraste?
Go down by the chimney.
You can not enter simply to my
Home by the chimney in Christmas.
In fact, it was doing all the night.
I am slightly worried about you now
Because these unemployed in my room
Using red and most of times
This finishes in caution command.
I am very tired so that
You call mas evening maybe.
He by himself sees home now
He walks home.
-Estoy en casa.
-¿Como?
I let my apartment, I will move with you here.
One that you need time for trying this.
Insurance you need to sleep, I will be down
In our breakfast area.
If you want to call it like that.
This is not good, we can not go to her
Bed made angry now that we live together.
I have a big surprise planned for you.
Nothing of surprises by favor.
I believe that you changed idea when you see this.
This either that do this?
It is the company's cart, it is the benefit.
-Fred, es increible.
-Estamos en Paris.
We are in Paris.
I bet that it ask them I happen to the other ones.
That Christmas I turn out to be the successful mas.
People felt everywhere
mas satisfied and complete that never
Good I work, you learned rapido.
Cute work.
RiPPED BY
~ADOMAX~
SEPTiCEMiA TEAM
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org