Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Buenos dias, buenos dias.
You coming early today.
I'm almost not finish.
But don't worry,
I'm finish.
I gotta get to school.
Come in, come in.
Always with you young boys,
always in a rush, always in a rush.
Marisol already
leave for school.
She has not missed one day
of school in three year.
Sit down, sit down.
You like some milk?
Some milk and cookie?
I have some nice
chocolate chip.
You like Marisol?
Marisol, she always
asking about you:
Why he don't talk to me
at the school?"
You have a girlfriend?
Ahhh, you already
liking somebody.
You are young.
Is plenty of time.
Soon you get tired of her,
and then you talk to my Marisol.
And I'm always telling her,
So take your time.
It's okay. "
Because I always tell her a word
- Half a brick means 20,
- Yes, yes, of course, 20.
- It ain't 20.
Esteban said I gotta take this to
Chillie's store. I gotta take 20.
If I don't give him 20, he gonna
get mad. You want me to count 'em?
No, no, no, no.
Wait, wait.
I- I-I check for you.
I- I check again.
Oh, look, look.
This one was stuck in back here.
I don't understand.
It's my eyes, you know?
So old, not seeing
so good no more.
And that's why I buy Marisol
her glasses right away.
So she don't have no trouble
with her eyes like me.
But Marisol is a pretty girl.
Just think about my Marisol...
because I want her to have a clever
boy like you, so you think about it,
Yeah, yeah,
they already called.
Then why they ain't
ready yet?
Relax. It's 8:00 in the morning.
We ain't hardly woke up yet.
I'm late for school,
Oh, for joy! It's little Fresh,
our messenger to the gods.
My tag is for my friends.
You can call me Michael.
You know,
it's embarrassing...
Esteban using this ugly
little maricon for man's work.
It makes me sick.
What's embarrassing is,
all the work there is to do...
Esteban got you workin' up here with
the bitches, that's what's embarrassing.
Damn! Ugly spotted little
motherfucker. I'll fuck you up.
I'm all over these bitches, nigger. Got me
a harem here like Arabian motherfuckin' shit.
You ain't all over me,
motherfucker.
You be dead before you touch
this good thing, fucking monkey.
You tripping on
your own shit, motherfucker,
Only harem you playin' is them five
fingers on your own fuckin' hand.
- That's right,
I need five bricks, Five,
Everybody know
the only reason he here...
is 'cause Esteban skied
on his freakin' sister.
Don't be talkin' about my sister.
Word, Esteban clockin'out
on that chocolate freak,
He doggin'her
every chance he get...
and she ain't nothing but a hop-head
freak riding the white horse-
Say one more word
about my sister, bitch.
You know, maricon,
I'm gonna fuck you right up.
Do it. Come on, bitch.
Fuck me up.
You know you ain't
fuckin'nobody up, Herbie...
so shut the fuck up,
I need five bricks. Five.
Chillie, man, they're all there,
I already counted 'em,
You know
I got to count 'em.
You don't get paid 'til they're
all counted and accounted for.
What, you got ants
in your pants?
Chill, homes.
Esteban wants to talk to you anyway.
I gotta get to school, Chillie.
I'm stupid late.
It's gonna be my second
late day this week.
Man, Miss Coleman's
gonna kill me.
Don't worry. I'll write you
a doctor's note.
Yo, it ain't funny, man.
Esteban comin' here
just to talk to me?
He's making the rounds.
But he said he wants you to wait
for him 'til he gets here, okay?
Kick it, Chillie.
Pay me later.
I'm crazy late.
Tell him I had to get to school.
Yo, yo, Fresh.
Come back here, crimey.
Here. Here, homes.
If there's anything missing,
I'll kill you later.
Well?
Did you bring a late pass
or didn't you?
Boy, who's talking to you,
me or that floor?
Is this a comedy act, Chuckie?
You find this funny?
Then shut up and wipe
that stupid-looking thing...
which you probably think
is some kind of charming expression...
right off your face, boy,
Put your things away
and find a seat,
Go on!
This is not over,
do you hear me?
Now, what I was saying
before that interruption...
was that Mr, Hill told you what
the words "manifest destiny"means...
but not what it was,
So don't come into my classroom
with that ignorant nonsense...
about the heroes of the Alamo
and Davy Crockett...
and how bad they were...
because all
they were really doing...
was robbing another people
of their land...
so that they could keep opening up
new territories for legal slavery,
The papers that I gave you
have a series of quotes...
from some antislavery writers
of that time period,
You read the first quote, Rosie,
It's from an antislavery writer
by the name of David Child...
written to
the Mexican government...
warning them about his own
United States government,
Read it to the class,
"Dear Sirs, There is
an impatient and almost ir-
"irresistible desire
in the South and Southwest...
to lay hold on Texas-"
Excuse me,
Where do you think you are,
the land of Oz?
You must be trippin'if you two
think you're gonna sit together,
Boy, move over there,
Go on, Rosie,
All right, Curtis, you're
hogging the ball again. Pass it.
Power!
That's it.
Yo, that shit's mine.
Not with a prayer, nigger.
That's it.
- That shit's mine This is mine.
- Look, look, nigger.
- Yeah, that's mine. That's right.
- Shit.
Step right up,
step right up.
One more, my good man.
One more.
Only if you flip
Willie Randolph.
- Uh-uh. Sorry, G.
- Yo, forget it, then.
Yo, I gave my last Willie Randolph
double to Fresh in class, man.
- I only got one left.
- Flip Willie Randolph!
No! N-O spells no.
No one never flips him.
And it be costing me
six bucks of packs 'til I get him.
You a chump buyin'
them shits, man.
I ain't never bought me
no baseball card.
- Been stealin' them shits all day.
- Stealin' them shits all day.
Yo, shut up, Tarleak. You ain't
never stole shit, so shut up!
- Yes, I did.
- Why you ain't got nothin'? Show me your cards.
I ain't bring 'em with me. Niggers be
always jumpin' me for my baseball cards.
- Yo, shut up, retard.
- My old man got every series of baseball cards since 1900,
He got Willie Mays,
Jackie Robinson, all of them,
They didn't even have baseball
cards back then, stupid,
- Uh-huh, I seen 'em,
- Yeah, where?
At my old man's,
He got all them cards where he at,
Where he be keepin' 'em at?
In his, like, how many limos?
Six, Nigger got six limos,
Word, six of'em,
Stupid big limos,
You haven't even met
your father, motherfucker.
- I did!
- You haven't even seen the motherfucker...
so shut the fuck up before I kick
your bucktooth, nappy-head ass!
- Look at this.
- He be lookin' at her like this.
- Shut up, nigger.
- I don't be likin' them bitches.
Always be trippin', Walkin' with
their nose up, like they all that,
Word, always hittin'me and shit,
- Like that girl Shanice, She don't stop 'til I smack her,
- Word, right,
They be hittin'you
'til you smack 'em,
Then they cry,
but they like that shit,
Word, they think they all that, but
they just want you to smack they head,
Oh.
Where you goin', man?
Watchin'girls,
- That's cold, man.
- Leavin' his best friend for a girl, man.
Yo, Rosie, stop looking at me, all right?
Why you always lookin' at me?
- 'Cause you look at me so much, I can't help it.
- I don't look at you.
- You do. You're always lookin' at me.
- You trippin'.
You drag all your friends into our cheerleading
practice like it's all their idea...
but you bring 'em
so you can look at me.
- You stupid trippin'.
- It's all right. I think it's cute.
Girls always be sayin', "Mikey got
them spotty white spots on him. "
But I think it's cute, I do.
I think it's real cute.
- Damn, you be lookin' almost white yourself.
- I am.
- Damn, why you buggin' out?
- My mother is white.
- Get outta here.
- She is. Straight up white.
Why she never come
to school, then?
She don't want you
'cause you're black, right?
- Why don't you live with your mother?
- I do.
You live with your aunt, with Hilary
and Jewel and all them others...
- so you can stop fronting any time now.
- Shut up.
My mother's married
to a millionaire.
Word, she live with Tarleak's old
man, with all them limos and shit.
She lives in Scarsdale.
She's got a big house.
Near as big
as this whole school.
You gotta go through a gate and drive
through a whole forest just to get to it.
- What kind of car she drive?
- A sports car.
- What kind of sports car?
- I don't know. AJaguar.
If I had me a million dollars,
I'd get me a Porsche 959.
I'd get me a sports car.
AJaguar.
Damn, I'd get me
a Ferrari Testarosa, V-12 engine...
get me a Porsche 930,
straight six turbo engine...
get me a Vector B-12,
twin turbo...
go from zero to 60 in 7.8
seconds, so don't even talk.
Yeah, well, who cares, 'cause you ain't
never gonna have a million dollars anyway.
- I will too!
- Who's trippin' now?
Ain't nobody trippin'.
I'm gonna have it.
Someday, I'm gonna have it.
Hi, Grandma.
Yo, what up?
Why is everybody out here?
We just here.
What a place to spend
our last night on earth,
What up, y'all?
Hey.
Where Aunt Francis at?
She home.
Yo, why everybody
around here illin'?
Yo, I got winners.
Michael?
You're home,
Look, Nichole,
Your brother's here,
Hey, Nicky.
I know Michael wants you to come
back and stay with us for a while.
Look, Aunt Francis, I just came
to get a few of my things.
I'm not staying.
Michael, you want Nicky
to stay with us, don't you?
Can't sleep here no more,
There's like a thousand little girls
running in and out of here.
Like my feet are hanging off
the edge of the bed already.
I know it.
I know it's crowded in here.
And you being a grown woman
and all. Nicky, take my bed.
Doesn't matter to me. I can sleep
in here with the girls for a while.
Aunt Francis,
I don't want your bed.
Well...
I guess I'll leave you alone
with your brother for a while.
Maybe he can talk to you about
staying with us a little longer,
Michael ain't no one
to talk to nobody about nothin'.
I gotta go,
- Michael?
- What?
Why you come home so late?
You know Aunt Francis be gettin'
worried when you come home so late.
It's hard enough on her without
you be worryin' her all the time.
If she gets too fed up and gives
all of us up, I'm gonna kill you.
'Cause ain't none of us
can go back to our parents...
and I ain't goin' back to
no group home, you hear me?
You my cousin and all,
we all cousins here...
but if you ruin it
for the rest of us, I'm gonna kill you.
- What up, G?
- I got ten bucks.
- Get you two bottle, homes.
- It's good stuff, right?
You tried all the rest;
now try the best.
Are you sure? I mean,
you know it for a fact, right?
Bust it, you don't like it,
you come back.
Jake give you back your ten
dollars, send you on your way.
Just don't be comin' back here
again, understand what I'm sayin'?
No way five dollars, man. Last time
I bought from Jake, I was illin'.
That stuff be stupid cut, man. Jake should
throw me a freebie, and just on principle.
Yo, Consuelo,
this is the dope.
Live kickin'jumbo crack.
You don't like it...
bum rush Stringbean
or Howard or Lenny.
Then you be ill on that
stupid baking soda, word.
What you got for me there,
little buddy? What's the deal?
Five dollars a pop,
Tell you what. I'll throw you 20
bucks for five. What do ya say, homes?
Five times five is 25.
Five dollars a pop, man.
Look, maybe I better talk
toJake myself, you know?
You know you don't be talkin'
toJake. You know that.
Look, you tellJake that
I'll suck his dick good, okay?
You tell him
I'll suck him off real nice.
Damn, you know Jake down with them
fine bitches. Why he want that from you?
All right, listen,
how about you and me, baby?
We get in that car, I'll suck
your sweet little dick for ten bucks.
Get out of my face, bitch.
Okay, how about
I let you fuck me?
Okay? I let you bang this good thing
if you just askJake to talk to me-
Get out of here!
Go over to Lenny.
He be likin' them no-tooth,
old bitches like you!
Yo, man,
we outta here, nigger.
No, man,
Kermit ain't showed up yet.
Let me tell ya, that nigger set his watch
for yesterday, the motherfucker still late.
- Yeah, word up.
- I got them bitches waiting, G,
And you said you gonna
be with me, right?
Come on, man, You're makin'me look
bad, man, Let me tell you somethin',
That nigger, Kermit, he is skied. You
hear me? That motherfucker is gone.
- You stand here waitin', you trippin'
worse than he is. - Um,Jake, I gotta-
- Nigger owe me $50.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- That's twice his money he ain't showin', G.
- Yeah, he owe me $50.
- Yo, I hear you, man. Come on.
- Word up.
Look, man, look, look.
Motherfucker still ain't comin', man.
Oh, you don't think so?
Let me tell you somethin'.
Nigger don't show up with
my money, I'm gonna dead him.
- I'm your boy, man, why you beefin' with me?
- Yeah, okay.
I'm gonna grease that
motherfucker like Sunday bacon!
I'm gonna cold drop
that motherfucker!
I'm gonna drop him, man!
I'm gonna cold drop him!
Now you know better than to always be
in my face with this silly ass nonsense.
I wouldn't ifJake paid me. But he like
always gettin' mad about somethin'.
And you know I ain't gonna be gettin'
all up in his face when he like that.
- So instead, you get in mine.
- 'Cause you ain't like that.
My man Fresh.
My stand-up little G.
You see, homes, this-
Hey, what the fuck you doin'?
I was pickin' up.
Don't be doin' shit behind my back!
Why the fuck you gonna be doin' that?
Corky, it was my turn. Man, we
just playin'. It's just me, baby.
I don't give a fuck who you is! Be my
mother, motherfucker, I don't play that shit!
- Sorry, all right?
- Yeah, you be sorry.
You do that shit,
just do it in front of my face.
Now, am I free to finish my
little transaction here...
without every nigger be doin'
some shit behind my back?
Niggers be dissin' you
at every turn, homes.
It's all right, 'cause
you my stand-up little G.
Yeah.
And, uh, I'll be talkin' toJake
about his temper too.
It's one hundred dollars.
Niggers be gettin'
$50 for lookout.
I be runnin' that rock all day.
One hundred dollars.
- You one bad
motherfucker, crimey.
Only reason you ain't the man
is you still too goddamn little.
But you get bigger,
you gonna be the man.
Oh, man!
I shake on a game, Fishcake.
That wasn't no game.
All right.
Who's next, who's next?
Come on. I heard there was
players in this shit hole.
All I see is chumps.
Come on. Who's gonna
give me a game?
Come on.
Get outta here.
I ain't got time
for this shit,
All right.
Play.
Check,
Mate in four.
Fuck you. Ain't no mate
in no four. Fuck you.
Would've been four
if you were smart. Mate.
Shit.
That shit over there
was a waste of time.
Fished me a twenty, Dad. You don't
be pulling 'em in for no twenties.
Said it was a waste of time.
Time ain't money...
no matter what those morons who eat that
kind of shit up may try and tell you.
Anything lost can be found again,
except for time wasted.
- It was fun, Dad, stupid fun. You seen
that nigger- - Chess ain't fun, boy.
How many times I gotta tell you that?
Don't you listen to a word I say?
- Maybe if I seen you more.
- Well, you don't, so you'd be well served...
to retain some of the knowledge
I'm impartin' to you...
rather than giving me all your
hard-ass street-attitude bullshit.
Ain't so much fun now, is it?
Gettin' to be less and less fun
every second here.
Uh-uh, think about it,
Forget the clock
for a second, Michael.
What kind of player am I? Am I an
offensive man or a defensive man?
That's right; I'm neither.
I play my opponent.
If he likes to attack,
I force him to defend himself.
If he's a cautious man,
I draw him into dangerous waters.
See, you get so frustrated
playing defensive positions...
you make stupid moves you'd
never make if you were thinkin'.
When you come here, boy,
check that shit at the door.
That's good.
That's better.
I'm still gonna kick your ass,
but that's better.
You been playin'
on the team?
No, huh?
Just watchin' the world
pass you by.
Figure as long as you ain't drownin',
everything's all right.
I don't need
no punk school team.
Mate.
And he got Hulk number one
and all them Thors.
My old man
got all them comic books.
He showed 'em to me, and they
were like all stupid number ones.
- Yo, he got Superman number one?
- Yeah, he got that.
He got Action Comics
number one?
Word, he got that too.
He got all them number ones.
Where he be keepin' 'em at?
In his garage with all them limos?
- You know you ain't got no old man.
- I do so.
Then we'll call him up when we get to
my house. We be givin' the nigger a call.
- He don't answer no phones.
- And why not?
He don't want no po' niggers
wastin' his time.
Bam, Spiderman goes down.
Bam, Daredevil goes down.
All them niggers is goin' down.
Punisher be takin' they ass out.
- X-Men take out the Punisher.
- X-Man baby stuff, homes.
All their costumes and powers ain't
shit. Punisher the real dope, homie.
Word, I seen a seven-foot-tall
White Terminator nigger...
with 20 guns on my roof
just the other day.
Punisher be takin' out
all your stupid heroes.
He be sayin', Bam! Bam! Bam!
Bam! Take out that nigger!
Bam! Bam! Bam! Bam!
Yo, Fresh, I been training him.
Watch this.
Good boy, Roscoe.
Good boy.
Good boy? That dog
ain't nothin' but badness.
Ain't nothin' but badness.
What up, Roscoe? You miss me?
You miss your homie?
Okay, okay, Mama,
I'll be in in a minute, all right?
I'm gonna fight him
on Sunday.
- You gonna do what?
- Roscoe's gonna take on Ricardo's pit,
Roscoe ain't fightin'
nobody's nothin'.
My dog fight
when I say he fight,
He ain't your dog.
He's our dog; I found him.
Ain't nobody askin' you, homes.
I'm gonna get paid, bust it.
You already gettin' stupid paid,
workin' them jobs for Esteban and shit.
Yo, we see y'all later.
We gotta go.
Well, I ain't gotta go.
You always be lookin'
all ratty and shit...
but everybody know
you gettin' paid.
Yo, why you always
be lookin' nappy like that?
What you be doin'
with all that jack?
You be hidin'
that shit away, right?
Damn, when I get paid, I'm gonna get
me those dope new Nikes, like ten pairs.
And I'm gonna get me some
stupid gold, homes, crazy gold.
Like this tooth right here
and a five-finger gold ring...
- with my tag bustin' all out that motherfucker.
- You ain't got no tag.
- I will when I get paid.
- He ain't fightin'.
Then you gonna take me to get a
job for Esteban? Yo, man, why not?
'Cause you be actin' like a
stupid little kid, that's why not.
Yo, why you dissin' me, man? I'm crazy,
homie. I'll bust those dope moves.
Come on, Rudy, Get it in your
mouth, Don't be such a spaz,
- Don't be talkin' like that to your son, Esteban.
- Hey, chill, woman.
He knows I'm only messin' with him.
Right, baby?
You know Daddy's
messin' with you.
Sure you don't want
no eats?
My grandma
be cookin' at home.
You're a good boy, Fresh.
You be eating at home.
And you be running to school
when I want to talk to you.
That's okay, little homie.
I like me a smart G. I really do.
You seem to have
enough time on your hands...
to be runnin' those rocks
for Corky's boys, though.
What, you think I got no eyes
but these two in my own head?
I know where you be at.
Corky got that work.
I be runnin' for you once a week,
maybe twice if somebody else gets sick.
Corky got them jobs.
Hey, let me tell you
something, Fresh.
Now, you're a smart kid, so you
hear these words of wisdom.
You know,
that rock is a bad move.
You start messin' with that
shit- sellin', dealin'-
I guarantee inside three,
five years, you'll be dead.
Or you'll have
a bullet in your head.
Or that pipe in your mouth.
Either way, you're dead.
Smack is the way to go.
This is a gentleman's operation.
The clientele is stable,
peace-loving.
The competition
is unconfrontational.
And the heat,
they mostly let it slide...
'cause there's little hassle
all the way around.
You find your niche,
you stay there, you stay cool...
and you be the man
into your 50's and 60's.
And then you retire your old ass
to a nice condo someplace hot...
with a lot of
niceJewish people.
Leave the business for your kids.
Hey, it's like banking,
only it's more secure.
And you don't pay no taxes.
Hey, what are you doing? You ain't
holding her right. Come here, come here.
I'm trying to feed her,
in case you haven't noticed.
No, you ain't holding her right.
She ain't hungry.
Hey, come on,
I'm gonna put her to bed.
You know, I ain't never sold no
rock, and no kind of coke whatsoever.
I never even tried it. Don't come near
that shit, not even from curiosity.
Close the door, okay?
It got loose on my last run.
I didn't want to give it
to no one but you.
Hey, my little money man.
Hey, you just lost Chillie
a hundred bucks on a bet, G...
'cause he don't know you
like I do,
Hey, you my solid little man.
Most niggers, they be givin'
their bitches rocks, you know?
Watchin' them pop off.
Bang!
They got theyself
a Action Jackson bitch.
Jumpin'around like a rabbit,
Divin'for that dick...
like it's gold at the end of the
rainbow, you know what I mean?
Hey, not me, little homie.
No, no, no, no, not me.
No, I love me a straight bitch.
Maybe she like to slide
into the land of"H"...
every once in a while,
a regular bitch.
Maybe she fine, like a-
Ay carajo,
like your sister.
Hey,your sister, she fine,
And then she take her hit...
and, like,
her eyes they roll back...
and she get suddenly soft.
Oh, so soft and pure.
And I am holding
my very own virgin.
My Madonna.
Hey, I take that.
You know I take that,
Is your sister a freak?
Hey, come here.
Hey, sit down.
Now, I'm askin' you a question.
Is she a freak?
Man, you married.
Hey, I know you're just a kid,
Fresh, even though you're smart.
So I let you talk to me
like that just this one time.
But you tell me- You better
tell me who she's runnin' with.
- Nobody.
- Don't fuck with me, little homie!
Serious, my aunt won't
let her out with nobody.
You know,
I find that hard to believe.
Bitch as fine as that.
She always has somebody.
Word, but my aunt won't
let her out with nobody.
I hope you're right, little homie.
I hope you're right.
Okay, come on, Let's go,
I gotta see Nichole.
Yeah?
Who the fuck are you?
Her brother.
I gotta see her.
I got a kid down here
say he Nichole's brother.
Send him up.
- One flight up.
Use the stairway at the back of
the store. There's only one door.
So, you Michael.
I guess you used up
all the ugly in the family.
Keep hearin' you the little man
runnin' the street.
You the little man
runnin' the street?
Shit, next thing I know
niggers in diapers...
packin' tech-nines be tryin'
to take over my business.
I said put me down!
Put me down!
She's in there.
Esteban looking for you.
Good for Esteban.
Yo, why you stay with James?
You know why, Fresh.
Why?
'Cause his smack is the dope
and he got plenty of it.
You happy now?
Why you don't go
to Esteban, then?
I don't like the way
he looks at me.
I don't need no spic pimp motherfucker
lookin' at me like I'm no fucking queen.
I'm just a sorry-ass
nigger ho'.
James here, he looks at me like
I'm nothing, so I'm down withJames,
You ain't
ain't nothin'.
Michael, fuck off,
all right?
Don't Aunt Francis think you ain't
nothin'. She think you somethin'.
Aunt Francis
is a fuckin' saint.
Aunt Francis loves every damn dog in
the street the same as she loves me.
Ain't no shit to be loved
by no fuckin' saint.
I love you.
I got him.
Come on now.
What's up, what's up?
Ain't got nothin', homes.
- Yo, what's up, nigger?
- He ain't got nothin'.
Watch him, watch him,
Aw, shit, he finally
got one in there!
Curtis bad, homes.
He be bustin' out those moves!
Word, as long as I ain't
playin' that nigger.
He ain't doin'shit,
Come on,
What's up, shorty?
Come on, come on.
- Damn!
- Yo, Red, man, pick him up, man.
Man, you pick him up,
motherfucker!
Yo, Fresh, other court's open.
Let's shoot some hoops.
No, not right now, man.
You just don't want me
embarrassin' your ass...
in front of none
of them bitches, huh?
Yo, don't be
callin' her that, nigger.
What, now you Mr. Tough Guy Nigger,
huh? Now you Mr. Tough Guy Nigger?
Hey, hey,
what's up, what's up?
Shit, Here, here,
take that motherfucker,
- Right here, right here.
- Foul ball,
Foul, motherfucker!
That's a flagrant fuckin'foul!
Hey, man,you okay?
Man, fuck you, nigger! Little
motherfucker gonna take that shit up...
- I'm gonna challenge him every time.
- What? Challenge?
Yo, don't be jumpin' on my boy like
you're the fuckin' New York Knicks!
Just forget about it, man.
Your ball.
Yeah,yeah, nigger,
you know you ain't shit,
Come on, man. Give me
the ball. A shot, a shot!
My man! Point game,
motherfuckers, we up!
Take the shot,
Yo,Jake,
what's up, man?
Why you let that motherfucker play
with you like that? What's up, man?
Oooh!
In your eye, whoa!
Damn, she comin' over, man.
- Yo, she be likin'you, man, What you say to her?
- Shut up, man,
Man, she in love with you, man, Yo,
man, she wanna get with you, man,
She like you, man,
Come on, man.
Let's go, man!
Let's go!
Yeah, go ahead, run,
motherfuckers! Run!
Y'all punk, pussy-ass,
motherfuckers! That's right!
Go tell somebody
you saw somethin'!
I come back for all of you
monkey motherfuckers!
You pussy-ass punks!
That's right.
Punk ass.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org