Am I responsible for this?
I'm afraid you are.
Previously on Fringe...
Our universe
is starting to break down.
What we've seen happening
on the other side
is starting
to happen here.
I destroyed their world
to save ours.
May God have mercy
on us.
The machine came on
by itself.
Without Peter.
You think that Walternate
turned the machine on
over there?
It's triggered
on a sympathetic response
from the one over here;
Yes, it makes sense.
How could he do that
without Peter?
We all thought
that I could turn
the machine on.
Maybe I can turn it off.
Dear God.
All civilians proceed
to evacuation route
immediately.
Agent Bishop,
take cover!
Where the hell
am I?
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Peter Bishop.
47 years old.
Shrapnel wound
in the abdomen.
BP is 110 over 70.
Start an IV.
Where am I?
Peter, you were injured
in a fringe event.
You're in good hands.
It's okay, I'm right here.
Lie back.
Just relax.
He's bleeding
pretty bad here.
Get me some units
of his reserve blood.
Start transfusion now.
Agent Bishop,
please just lie still.
Get me the U.V. cauterizer.
It's all right, Peter.
You're going to be fine.
I'd like to find out
how Peter Bishop is doing.
May I see your badge?
I don't have a badge...
Yet.
I was just promoted
last week.
I have a temporary barcode.
Can I show you that?
Sure.
Thank you, Agent Dunham.
Agent Bishop has been
in recovery for an hour now.
He should be out soon.
Ella.
Peter's fine,
Aunt Liv.
He's in recovery.
I mean, uh,
Agent Dunham, ma'am.
You can just call me boss
like everybody else.
Now, how are you?
I'm fine.
I remember
being in my SUV.
And the next thing I knew,
I was on the ground
and there was vortex
shrapnel everywhere.
People are saying that
it's the end-of-dayers.
That's what we think,
yeah.
We think it's Moreau.
Hey.
Peter.
How are you feeling?
Ah... Just like new.
- So what'd the doctor say?
- Doctor says I'm fine.
No. They said to stay
off his feet for a few days.
See? You're pushing
yourself.
Moreau's out there.
Peter, you got to
stay off your feet.
This is gonna be
one of those times
when you say,
"you were right. "
I'm not gonna say
that you were right
because I got state-of-the-art
science on my side.
I feel fine, hon.
Do you remember what
you were saying in the field
about the machine
and being from the past?
Well, I didn't say
I didn't get my bell rung,
but I'm doing better now.
Two eggs over-easy,
bacon, and grapefruit juice.
That's what I made you
for breakfast on Sunday.
Hey, guys. Look.
There's a stage three tear.
We've initiated
Amber Protocol.
Psst.
Okay.
Hey.
The security firm
just emailed this video.
We think they gained entrance
from the side fire door.
Okay, so how come they didn't
trigger the alarm?
It was disabled.
But that's not all.
We think we found
an electrilight.
It must have been a dud.
I believe so.
We finally get to see one.
"The End of Days. "
Ha.
That's one of my father's
favorite sermons.
When the world dies
and a savior arrives
to end the suffering
and usher all the worthy
into heaven.
Pass me those
alligator clips?
Of course, if my father
ever met one of the kooks
who's actually attempting
to end the world,
he'd probably
kill them himself.
Agent.
Eyewitness
statements.
I'll let you know if
any of this is worthwhile.
- Anything?
- No.
Not only can I not
tell you how the thing works,
according to all the readings,
it shouldn't be working at all.
You know, there's probably
only one person on Earth
who can tell us
how this thing functions.
Walter.
Got any markers
you can call in?
You think now's the time?
I think it might be
past time.
Hello, Walter.
Must be bad if they're
letting you see me.
It is.
I heard a rumor
that the Sun was burning out.
They don't
tell me much in here.
The Sun is still shining.
I also hear
there's been a massive
increase in Kappa radiation.
That one's true.
A wormhole opened
in Central Park,
right in the center
of Sheep's Meadow.
Took us months but...
We were finally able
to amber it over.
A wormhole shouldn't emit
that type of radiation.
Not unless it's a wormhole
through time.
Exactly right.
The carbon levels
were consistent
with the late Paleozoic era.
250 million years ago.
Paleozoic.
Theropods!
My old self would have been
fascinated with that.
How's Olivia?
She's fine.
Thank you.
I need your help.
What is it?
We're not exactly sure.
Some kind of light bomb.
It's made by
a terrorist group.
They call themselves
the end-of-dayers.
They use them on soft spots,
trying to rip holes
in the fabric of the universe.
Trying to accelerate
the end of days.
I'm hoping if we can
figure out how it's made
and maybe trace the parts...
We can stop them
before it's too late.
Even if I could help you...
I can't do it from here.
I... would need my tools.
My special instruments.
We both know
that's not going to happen.
Senator.
Hello, Peter.
Thank you for your time.
No need for formality
in here.
It's good to see you.
Have a seat.
You said it was urgent.
It is.
I assume you've been
briefed
about the end of days
organization?
I'm well aware
of the situation, yes.
We recovered this device
from what's left of
the opera house.
Science Division's been
trying to crack the technology,
but without much luck.
What do you need?
I need Walter.
I want you to grant him
a temporary furlough
so he can help us
on the case.
That's out of the question.
I'm sorry.
If we can understand
this technology,
we might be able
to prevent future attacks.
Consult with him
in prison if you need to.
That's all I can offer.
Why? You worried about
your reelection prospects?
You know me better
than that.
I'm worried about that.
The entire globe
is disintegrating.
We're running around
putting on band-aids,
and every day more people
are lost because of it,
and Walter is responsible.
I know him.
And I know his intentions
weren't this.
But there's not
a single person out there
who hasn't lost someone
they love because of him.
You can't begrudge the anger
they feel towards him.
I don't.
I'm out there in the streets
with them every day.
And, yeah, maybe I am
running around
putting band-aids on it
until we can figure out
how to reverse the damage
that's already been done.
But at least it's something.
And if we can figure out
this technology,
I guarantee you we will
prevent future casualties.
Phillip.
If what we lost in Detroit
still means anything to you...
Just give me one chance.
That's all I'm asking.
Where are my things?
They're all still
in evidence, Walter.
Don't worry.
Olivia's on it.
Your equipment
will be here shortly.
Mm.
Will Astrid be here?
No. Astrid's
a Fringe Agent now.
- We need her out in the field.
- Oh.
I suppose since she's
no longer caring for me,
she's able to-
spread her wings.
May I take
a look out back?
My old office.
Just leave him there for now.
I'm not sure
where he wants him.
Walter.
I didn't realize how much
I've missed swivel chairs.
I've also missed swiveling.
There's someone here
to see you.
A visitor?
Walter.
Olivia!
Congratulations
are in order, my dear.
What for?
The wedding, of course.
Oh.
That was a while ago now.
This is the first
opportunity I've had
to give you an appropriate
welcome to our family.
I always did want
a daughter.
Thank you, Walter.
For goodness' sake!
Doesn't the word fragile
mean anything to you?
Was that you?
I learned to control it
a few years ago.
I'm impressed.
So... What's the next
target?
The wormhole
in Central Park.
Considering your world
was destroyed by a wormhole,
I suppose it's fitting.
Is this it?
Followed your specifications
to the letter.
More than twice the yield
of the device
we used last night.
It won't be long...
Till this world joins mine.
Boys.
Any luck?
Afraid not.
Can't make any sense
of this technology.
I'll continue to run
diagnostics on the canister,
but even if I am successful,
our world is still ending.
You may stop this group,
but you cannot
stop the inevitable.
Our destiny was set the day
we triggered the machine.
I didn't understand
until it was too late
that our... two worlds
were inextricably linked.
Without one, the other
simply cannot exist.
When their world
was destroyed,
that was the day
we sealed our fate.
For all intent
and purposes...
that was the day we died.
We don't know that
for sure.
Have you seen him?
Walternate?
No.
Nobody has.
He's become a recluse.
Imagine coming over here
to try to save the world...
Only to be stuck here
when your world was destroyed.
Not to mention
having the same face
as the most reviled man
in the universe.
I just wanted to say...
At the trial,
you spoke on my behalf-
Walter, I'm the one
who got in the machine.
I'm the one who destroyed
the other universe.
The courts perceived
that you did it...
to defend our universe.
And so do I.
This all began with me,
my... hubris.
Walter-
and I just wanted
to say thank you.
No matter who's at fault,
you are my dad.
That smells
insanely good.
After the day we had,
I figured we deserved
better than takeout.
Hey.
How you holding up?
Ha. I'm doing fine.
Why?
Well... you know Walter
would always cook
when he was worried
about you, so...
Well, of all the bad habits
I could pick up from him,
that's the least of them.
Amanda from across the street
gave it to us.
That's you and me
and the little baby
that we're gonna have
that she is planning on
babysitting.
Oh...
Well, I think we should
get started on that right away.
You're really gonna use
a drawing from a little girl
to get lucky?
It sounds so dirty
when you say it like that.
She's a sweet
little girl.
You know, hon, if you
wanted to reconsider...
I can't say that I don't
think about it.
And that I don't wish
things were different.
Honey, people still
have families.
Look at Amanda.
She was born
into this world,
and she's still happy.
And the world
could get better.
So I still think
we're gonna have a kid.
I hope you're right.
In fact, I think
we're gonna have several.
Two, maybe three.
Little tribe of Bishops.
Hello?
I understand now.
They're splitting atoms...
not as an outcome goal
but as a means to an end.
Slow down, Walter.
The diagnostics
on the canister-
they show residual traces
of strontium 90.
That's a radioactive
isotope.
That's how they're making
the electrilights.
Which means
it would leave a signature.
Yes! Like radioactive
breadcrumbs.
They'll lead us
to whoever's doing this.
We need Science Division
to monitor current
radiation tracking maps.
It'll be faster
if you exclude
readings inconsistent
with strontium 90.
Look for spikes
in the remaining data.
This is a campground.
Do you think it's even possible
to split atoms here?
I can see 'em making s'mores,
maybe,
but weapons
of mass destruction? No.
Is this the right
place?
The tracking system
is detecting
the same radioactive signature
that registered on the canister.
So then where's the lab?
Okay.
You keep searching.
I'm gonna call this in.
If you find anything
out of the ordinary,
I want to know.
Yes, ma'am.
Sir. We found this
sitting on top of a rock.
I don't know
if it means anything.
- Thank you, Agent.
- Sure.
Peter.
Maybe Walter was wrong
about the radioactive signature.
Yeah.
I'll go back
to Science Division,
see if maybe
something's wrong
with the radiation
detection sensors.
Okay, well, let me know
if you find anything.
Yeah. Will do.
How come no one
respects my desk?
You're too nice.
Team one, get ready to deploy.
Perimeter breach.
Sector eight.
This technology's 10,
maybe 15 years
ahead of its time.
I don't mind saying
it's something I would like
to have invented.
I mean for peaceful
purposes,
mining, maybe.
Walter. What about
the components?
Where were these parts
made?
I haven't the foggiest.
Dunham.
I'm on my way.
What's wrong?
There's been a security
breach at the wormhole.
Someone in the park
I.D.'d Moreau.
Come on.
Hello?
Hello, Peter.
Why'd you leave me
the key, Walter?
I knew you'd recognize it.
I couldn't just call you.
Yes, you could have.
No, no, no, no.
Not if I wanted
the proper reunion
that we both
so richly deserve.
So letting me know
that Moreau works for you-
that was your way
of getting my attention?
Among other things.
I should have known that
the electrilight came from you.
After all, Walter was
the only one brilliant enough
to figure out how it worked.
Stands to reason
that you were the only one
brilliant enough
to invent it.
Yin and Yang.
That's interesting.
Interesting
that you should say that-
Yin and Yang.
Why are you doing this?
One man broke the universe.
The other man did nothing...
But have his son stolen,
his life stolen, ruined.
I came over here
at the end
on a mission of mercy
to ask for help
for my side.
The race was lost,
a race I didn't initiate.
But still, I came.
And you destroyed us,
Peter...
My son.
You destroyed
your own-
you activated the machine
on your side.
You were going to use it
to destroy this universe.
I only acted
in self-defense.
Do you know what
it's like...
to wake up and just
for a moment...
Think that everything
is as it was?
And then to realize
it's not...
That the nightmare you had
was real.
Soon everyone here
will experience loss
the way that all those
over there did.
Air, water...
Light, even.
But you...
You will experience loss
the way I did.
What does that mean?
You destroyed
my universe, son,
and I'm going to
destroy yours.
And not all at once.
Peter's still not
picking up.
Agent Dunham.
We spotted a vehicle parked
near the perimeter breach.
- What kind of vehicle?
- A bus.
Okay. I want
all tactical teams
to enter
the restricted area-
I came here alone,
Walter.
To make a personal plea
to you.
I'm sorry for the suffering
that I've caused you.
I'm sorry...
For destroying your people.
Our people.
I'm sorry
for destroying our world.
And if I could
take back that choice...
I would.
But it's no excuse
for what you're doing now.
And it has to stop.
I don't want to have
to use these.
But you're going to
come with me now, father.
You know, Peter,
if I was really there,
I might not be able
to resist killing you.
I think this is
the better way,
so you can learn
about loss.
Let's start by killing
someone you love.
We're gonna evacuate
the area,
try and contain
the wormhole.
So can you move everyone
back to sector three?
Olivia Dunham...
My wife...
was everything to me.
Why have we stopped?
What is this,
some kind of protest?
No. It's the wormhole.
They're still trying
to seal it up.
Sergeant, when we start
moving again,
can we cut over
and take Columbus, then we can-
Wait. No.
Turn the car around.
Please...
I need to get back
to my lab.
Diagnostics
are almost complete.
You used to call me
"Uncle Walter"
do you remember?
I don't remember much
from before it got bad.
I'm so sorry...
Ella.
I understand...
Words can't come close
to mitigating your loss.
Truly, if I could go back
in time and change things,
I would.
I would give anything
to be able to go back
and make different choices.
But you can't.
There aren't any happy endings
nowadays, are there?
No. I suppose not.
I remember the cow
that stayed over there.
She had kind eyes.
She did, didn't she?
My gene.
I do miss her.
Oh...
That's it.
Peter, I was wrong.
It's not too late.
You can save both worlds.
We can do it all over again.
This time, you-you simply need
to make a different choice,
and should
something go wrong,
then Olivia will be
our fail-safe.
Walter, stop.
Olivia is dead.
But she won't be...
Not then.
The machine?
I turned that on
15 years ago.
And all the time
I sat in prison,
I- I-I couldn't figure out
where it came from.
I knew the pieces were buried
millions of years ago,
but how did they get there,
so deep in the past?
But now I understand.
I sent them there.
The wormhole
in Central Park-
I sent them back
through time.
Peter, you can stop
the destruction
before it occurs!
If that's the case, just
don't send the machine back.
Then we'll never
discover it,
and I'll never destroy
the other universe.
No, no, no.
It doesn't work that way.
I have already done it.
Therefore, I have no choice
but to do it again.
Walter, that doesn't make
any sense.
It does.
It's a paradox.
I can't change
what happens
because
it's already happened.
But you can make
a different choice
within what happened.
I simply need to find a way
to bring your consciousness
forward to now
so that you can witness
what will happen
if you make
the same choice.
Peter, for all I know,
it could be happening already.
Don't you see?
We can fix everything.
We can cheat
the rules of time.
Imagine the repercussions.
There's no way of telling
what the cost might be.
But it can't be
worse than this.
It can't be
What would I need to do?
Walter?
What's happening to him?
His heart rate's
going up-
156 and climbing!
What's it doing to him?
I don't know.
It's been 60 seconds now.
How much longer are we gonna let
him stay inside that thing?
Peter has interfaced
with the machine
at a biological level.
If we take him out
prematurely,
I'm afraid we'll harm him.
What is it?
Sir, it just started
60 seconds ago.
What started exactly?
The machine-
something is happening.
The diagnostics
are through the roof.
Look at this-
the soft spots-
they're not closing.
They're getting worse.
Bring me
Olivia Dunham, now.
I don't understand
what you're asking me to do.
The drawing suggests
that you have a connection
with the machine...
That you can stop it,
that you can turn it off.
They outsmarted you,
didn't they?
They know you turned
the machine on.
So they put Peter
in theirs...
And now we're the ones
that are gonna get destroyed.
Something's wrong!
Help me, quick!
Come on,
let's move it!
Peter.
Olivia...
You're alive.
Are you doing that?
I understand now.
Walter? Walter!
I understand
what the machine does.
I know what it's capable of,
and I know where it came from.
The first people?
Yes, the first people,
Walter,
but the first people
are us-
you, most specifically
and maybe Ella and Astrid-
I don't know.
I don't know who it was
that took the machine
back through time.
But I know something else.
I've seen doomsday,
and it is worse than anything
you could possibly imagine.
This isn't a war
that can be won.
Our two worlds
are inextricable.
If one side dies,
we all die.
So I've torn holes
in both the universes
and they lead here,
to this room.
A bridge so that we can
begin to work together to fix-
you shattered my universe.
You have any idea
how many deaths you've caused?
That was an accident.
What you have tried to do
you've done on purpose!
Whatever
you've both done,
we're here now.
So maybe it's time
we start to fix it.
You were right.
They don't remember Peter.
How could they?
He never existed.
He served his purpose.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player