Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
It's almost like a spy film
in the intrigue...
of this romantic encounter...
between this guy
that Calvin plays...
I'm sorry, there's a...
Uh, and this woman.
And anyway,
I think it's a neat story.
And I think it's a great cast.
Um, uh, but, uh...
Yeah. I'm sorry,
I have some... it's weird.
I'm really happy about
the project. I really am.
I got... you know, there's...
I've got issues with some of...
Actually, Calvin. Calvin is,
I think, I don't know...
You know, other people...
get more excited about him
than I do.
It's not to say I'm not happy
having him on the movie.
I think that's great, and
I'm sure he's very good in it.
I just don't get what
the big thing is with Calvin.
I think... you know, you picture
a role in a certain way...
And sometimes it's...
I'm not always right, either.
I know, you know, certainly
my wife thinks he's great.
FRANCESCA:
I'm starving to death.
- Well, I've got it right here,
- I might actually faint,
OK, tuna, No celery,
No celery and no,
- Onion,
- Right,
Uh, so listen...
you know that thing
that we were talking about?
Um, I can't keep...
OK, I mean...
Come on, come on,
I'm uncomfortable dealing
with this aspect of your life.
I don't want to talk to them,
Well, I don't want
to talk to them, either.
I don't even want to talk
to the guys I'm dating,
Uh-huh.
Well, I'm not dating anyone.
A date is not dating.
Well, you know,
someone buys you dinner,
you owe them a phone call,
in my opinion,
See, dinner...
that's where I fucked up.
It should have been lunch,
They all seem pretty nice
to me.
Well, they don't strike you as,
like, networky, freaky,
actress-dating
executive types,
with their water bottles
in, like, a mesh tote bag?
This is really...
this is disgusting,
I can't eat this,
That arugula is so bitter,
It's like
my algebra teacher on bread,
- OK,
- Ugh,
I'm truly, I'm... look at me,
I'm gonna faint,
I might actually faint,
We all know how you get
when your blood sugar's low.
All right. I'll be right back.
OK. Thank you.
- You're welcome,
- I need some wet naps, too,
- OK,
- Tuna fingers,
- Don't want tuna fingers,
- No, we don't,
- You're an angel, Thank you,
- Oh, you're welcome,
Oh, post-its!
LEE: See, I knew
something was wrong, I just...
I didn't know it was that.
I had that one this morning,
CALVIN: Hey,
I need to talk to you
about something,
- Lee...
- Don't,
Why did you even pursue this?
What? Wait a minute.
You came over and spoke to me.
Now, all of this began
because of you,
Are you saying
you weren't attracted to me?
No...
Gus told me
to watch out for you,
I'm forty-one tomorrow,
Calvin...
the age where
I could have a stroke,
in the middle of the night,
If you think I'm not going
to Gus', you're,
OK, I have a meeting,
Go fuck somebody else,
- Hey,
- Hi,
- You're still here?
- Yeah, I was just upstairs,
I was shopping
for my friend Gus,
- Oh,
- Yeah,
- Are you OK?
- Oh, yeah, I'm good,
I've just had really some
sad cases today, so I'm just...
- I'm sorry,
- I'm emotional,
Yeah.
What did you get him?
- Who?
- What did you get Gus?
Oh, They didn't have it,
- What was it?
- Yeah,
- Are you,
- It was a thing,
He's... he's, uh,
It was... they didn't... you know,
'cause he's forty today,
and I was just gonna get him
some, I don't know, this...
- Are you OK?
- Yeah,
I just have to go,
I'm really late, so...
- Are you sure?
- Yeah,
I'll call you later.
Oh, OK,
Thank you.
Um, you need to find him,
I don't know if he knows
I'm here at the office,
so I have to have a contact
name in order to transfer you.
Um, Harvey's not here
at the office right now.
He sees on the TV a murder,
and as he listens to the murder,
His whole face
just goes white...
and he bolts
from his apartment.
Now, we follow him.
The murders... they deviate
at this key point...
for reasons nobody can
understand, because...
T ell Trevors I'm not gonna
do it, I'm not gonna do it,
Good, good, Go, Sorry, Go ahead,
Aah,
My brother Bob
should look at this,
Yeah, Good, Good!
- Great,
- Good,
CALVIN: Motherfuckers,
Did you see their faces
looking at us?
Yes,
It was like a labrador
staring at a Picasso,
Right,
Ed, we walked in there
- They want beer mugs,
- Yeah, right?
I could so see myself
in that part,
Right?
Fuck!
- It's all right,
- All right, I gotta go,
- See you later,
- See you,
Hey, Ed, keep the faith,
It was good. It was good.
- Mr, Liveright,
- Hey, hey, Bill,
- Come on in,
- Thanks,
- Ann?
- Yeah,
My massage is here,
I'll call you back in an hour,
- How about in back? Good?
- OK, sure,
Um, what do you think
about the lighting?
A little light... too bright?
Whatever you're comfortable
with is fine, Yeah,
I think a little darker,
- Like so,
- Sure,
- Need some help?
- No,
Done it before, huh?
"Bill Liveright"... great name,
Well, a name with a message
is a good name, right?
I don't know,
It just always eluded me,
Mmm,
Money is just feminine energy,
Huh, It always seems so male,
I don't get it,
Money: Mater, The Latin,
You connect with that,
You make it sound pretty simple,
- It is,
- Just connecting with it,
You're catching on, Ann,
Look, don't be
If you have purpose,
you can just wade right through,
It's like running past
people who are asleep,
OK,
you can turn over now,
I think I kind of drooled
a little bit,
Just scoot your head down,
so you're not in the hole.
OK,
You're from L, A,?
No, Miami, actually, You?
- New York,
- Oh,
Do you find me attractive?
What?
Yes,
In what sort of way?
In a human sort of way,
- Ann,
- Bill,
It's my birthday, Ann,
- Really?
- Yeah,
Happy birthday,
What's your philosophy
on release?
You know what, Bill, I know
and the thing is,
I don't do it, so,
Right, Not even
for a little extra money?
Mm-mmm, It's not
the kind of massage I do,
Right,
I offer a release
of tension and toxins,
and sometimes emotion, but,
Yes, well,
Well, I don't do it, so...
Oh, yeah,
You can come in thirty seconds?
- Do you have a second-hand?
- Look, I can't do it,
You could stop
after thirty seconds,
Five hundred dollars,
When was the last time,
you made five hundred dollars
for thirty seconds of work?
- You're cruel,
- I'm not cruel, I'm practical,
You need the cash,
This is crazy,
Five hundred dollars, Ann,
You can't make any noise,
- The place is noisy,
- No, You can audibly exhale,
You can't moan or grunt or sigh,
I can't moan or grunt or sigh,
just audible exhale only?
- Yes,
- Ahh!
No, Too loud, And if
you do it... it's too much,
I'll be quiet,
OK, Ann, I'll be quiet,
Are you ready?
Fuck.
Will you just hand me
that plastic bag right there?
Well, why?
No reason,
Oh,
Oh, my God,
Ahem,
- Here,
- Thank you,
GUS: Shit.
- Hey, Ann?
- What?
I'm sorry,
I thought I had more cash on me,
That's OK, Bill,
You know what? There's a limit.
There's a limit.
To the machine, You can only
get three hundred dollars out,
Could you move that, please?
That bag,
- You're kidding,
- No, I'm not kidding,
- I feel bad,
- You should,
You should feel
really bad and ashamed,
It's,
- Hold on,
- Forget it,
- Just hold on a second,
- You know what? Forget it,
It's pathetic.
"Mater equals money. " I mean,
give me a fucking break.
All the world loves a winner,
You know why
they love the winner?
Because they think
he knows something,
I mean, he had to know
So, we admire him,
But the winner doesn't
learn anything from winning,
No, the loser... the loser
Losing teaches you
about yourself.
So, the loser's the winner.
I don't know. I mean,
it's not in actual terms.
I'm speaking figuratively.
Sorry, Excuse me,
- Good night, Denny,
- May I see you, please?
The gentleman in 205
left this for you,
Oh, Huh,
Wow, That was nice,
GUS: Ann, thanks
for the happy ending. Bill.
Nice card,
Django?
Django? Hey, hey, hey!
Sweetie-pie?
Dja...
LEE:
I know what they say.
I know what they say
about me...
my colleagues...
and my family.
I don't... fucking movies.
OK, let's fucking go,
Fucking movies!
Fucking overpaid, fucking
unhappy childhood fuckers,
Fucking movie fucking fuckers,
Let's go! Somebody...
Jesus, buddy!
Uh, do you think somebody else
could go?
Maybe one of us could
fucking cross the street?
Fucking movie cop!
Hey, fucking movie cop!
Could I maybe
fucking cross the street?
Francesca Davis, Fuck,
Yes, He's gonna get... what?
Dehydrated? OK,
Yes, Yeah, I understand,
Hello, Yeah, hi,
I did that,
and... and I gave him
some water, yeah,
and I was just hoping
that Dr, Green could come by,
and, uh, and give him
a quick look,
Oh, he is?
Oh, I see, Uh,
Yeah?
Well, if... you know,
I just... I just, uh,
want to make sure
he's not gonna die,
you know, or anything,
Um, so if you could,
that would be great,
Right, heh heh, Yeah,
Uh, that's fantastic,
Yes, I will see you then,
Yes, What? The address?
Oh, Oh, my address, Oh, yeah,
I guess you'd need that,
wouldn't you? Heh heh,
Hi,
I know,
You know, I can't really talk,
I'm going into a store,
Can I call you back?
OK,
Oh, really?
Oh that'd be...
that's... that's great,
I'm... I'm glad,
You met Gus?
Where? Wow,
Yeah, well, there's a guy,
who could change your life,
you know?
So, I'm gonna get the dress,
- Oh, good, Great,
- Yeah,
LINDA: Mm-hmm. Sure.
Yeah. I was, um, fat...
overweight, and very short...
and, um, I hadn't
gone through puberty.
So, yeah, I mean, I looked,
you know... I did not look...
like I would've liked
to have looked in high school.
Yeah, surely I would've
changed my social status.
I still would. Heh heh. Yeah.
Treat myself,
So, that's five there,
Oh, great, Thank you very much,
- OK,
- Excellent, Thank you,
Hey, you came, I thought
you were coming later,
No,
Hey, How are you, man?
Good to see you,
The house is open, guys,
if you want to,
Oh, Hi, Dee,
Good to see you,
Thank you for coming,
Good,
That guy didn't pay,
Did you pay, sir?
MAN: I did, yes.
Would you like...
No, no, I just... I saw you
come the other way,
and most people were coming,
I'm sorry,
Right in here,
Right there on the sofa,
Oh, boy,
What else was in the brownies
besides chocolate?
Um,
- Hash?
- Yeah,
Aw, come on, man,
No, My wife
brought it back from London,
We made the brownies
for my friend's fortieth...
So, what'd you do,
leave it out for him to eat?
No, no, I know,
it was right here
on this counter,
I didn't think
he could jump that high,
He's got little legs like a,
All this... he ate all this,
It's so much better than pot,
right?
- Uh...
- Aw, no, no, no,
You don't understand,
I haven't smoked that in years,
so, you know what I'm saying?
Goddamn,
When I was in my twenties,
this guitar player and I,
would make up all these lyrics
while he played,
and our songs would end up,
with all these fucked-up
rhyme schemes,
Heather, Heather, I'm sorry,
Is he going to be all right?
Oh, he's going to be fine,
He's going to be fine,
So, uh,
you going to throw that out?
Look, you liked it,
and you've told me
you haven't liked things,
You liked it, Man, listen,
you're not going to pursue
any more meetings...
because
this is what I want to do.
I'm serious, OK?
Hey, listen. Could you, like...
It's better now,
It's a lot better now,
Ed and I,
We've been
beefing up the scenes,
And that whole thing
you mentioned...
I agree with you...
about me being in it.
I'm not going to do it.
Even if they ask about it,
we're not going to build it in.
I figure, you know,
in the long run...
it's probably a good thing,
me trying to establish myself
as a writer instead of an actor,
Like Pinter. You know, Pinter,
he was an actor.
He started off as an actor,
He still acts, occasionally.
All right, this shit
is cyclical, you know that?
All right, don't.
Don't, don't, don't.
I got it,
OK, Thank you,
If you stop telling me
that that letter makes sense,
you can throw up all you want,
How about that?
Tch, Yeah, Aw,
Do you know her?
- Ahem, Who?
- Carl's wife,
Nuh-uh,
That's kind of funny, because
I've heard things, actually,
Yeah. Yeah.
A couple of them.
- Hey, how are you doing?
- Uhh,
Hey, Fran, listen,
I want you to meet...
Frannie, It's Lucy Morgan,
L, A, Magazine,
- I'm sorry, I...
- The Sedona piece,
Oh, my God, Yes, Oh, wow,
Wow, You changed your hair
or something?
Yeah, How do you know Cal?
- Uh, we...
- It was a dinner.
Yeah.
Excuse me,
Hey,
Hi,
Is it... is it upstairs,
or is it in there?
God,
- Oh, this is wrong,
- No,
- I'm overdressed,
- You look,
- I wasn't sure what,
- It's on the roof,
Where's Carl?
He's not here yet,
I just, um,
- We should go up and,
- OK,
- Wow,
- You OK?
Yeah,
You know,
No, You look great,
Well,
You know, I have to admire you
for your belief,
in this project,
but the reality...
is a whole different thing
altogether.
It's all marketplace shit,
And I don't think that
this is a good role for you...
so don't even push that.
When does this article
come out?
In a couple of months,
Well, you call me,
if you can't get any answers
out of this guy,
Thank you.
Nice to meet you,
Nice seeing you,
Huh?
"Meltzin. "
Name kind of suits him,
Oh, Nicholas,
No, it looks good,
Where'd you get that dress?
- Seaver,
- Where?
On Third, Do you know it?
- Is it good?
- Yeah,
- It was on sale, I like it,
- No, it's,
Oh,
God,
All chromium is not bad,
because
I get Fitness magazine,
I need a drink,
No, I'm saying there's
a lot of good chromiums,
- I read it in a magazine,
- Hey,
Hey, I wouldn't go
to the lengths,
of bathing in bottled water,
that's all I'm saying,
I believe what you're saying,
- Franny Davis?
- Yeah,
Sam Osborne.
- I'm sorry,
- The Duchess of Malfi,
- Birchers,
- Yeah,
I was the lighting guy,
Mmm, Oh, my God, Oh, OK, Yeah,
- Sam Osborne,
- Osborne,
- How are you?
- Nice to see you again,
Oh, you, too, Wow, That's funny,
- Yeah,
- That's...
Do you remember when you said,
"I feel like a waitress
on vacation"?
Oh, God,
It was, like, just the cutest
thing I've ever heard, and,
I don't know why
that just stuck out,
I don't... yeah,
I just... um, well,
- I was going to go,
- OK,
Jesus, You remember that?
Yeah,
Yeah, I do,
- I got a funny memory that way,
- Oh,
Anyway, hey,
I... I don't want to bug you,
I know you got
lots of people to see,
I just wanted to say
how happy I am for you, and,
Oh, thanks, Thank you,
It's... I always thought
you had something special,
This,
You know, it's just amazing
what you've been able to do,
well, from,
Or, well, yeah,
No, I'm just... I'm... thank you,
Thank you,
Right, Good, Well, hey,
- Cheers, Good to see you,
- Thank you, Cheers,
I couldn't "Cheers" you,
I don't have a drink,
but, well, shit,
Ha ha!
Birchers lighting guy,
Birchers,
Get me a...
why don't you come with me?
- Yeah, OK,
- OK,
- Nicholas, Oh, my goodness,
- Oh, God,
- Uhh,
- Let's get you on the sofa,
- Oh, God, did I just...
- Yes, you did,
- Ohh,
- Go slowly,
Ah, Catherine, I'm sorry,
Are you all right?
- Here's some water,
- Oh, thank you so much,
- I feel a little light headed,
- Here, have some water,
- Yeah,
- Drink it,
Yeah?
Are you sure you're all right?
- Mm-hmm,
- Thank goodness,
- I need to ask you something,
- What?
I need you to come back
to New York with me,
Nicholas, I can't...
Catherine, it's that letter,
Well, but that was...
I've never had anybody
write me a love letter,
- Never,
- But I just...
No, listen,
You're here,
You there just makes sense,
You write the article,
Nicholas, these kind of things...
A moment of inspiration,
that's all
anybody ever really wants,
Mmm,
To have an original idea,
to fall in love,
It takes courage,
to surrender these things,
Especially when you have
control issues,
I get that a lot,
I know what
they're going to talk about,
when they talk about me,
They're going to talk
about the mustache,
People are so fucking petty,
People say,
"God, what's up with that?
"Like, didn't you know
that Chaplin had it first?"
Yeah! I knew, OK?
It's either the name
of your first pet,
and the first street
that you ever lived on,
or it's your middle name,
and the first street
that you lived on,
Well, which is it?
I think... is it pet?
- Pet,
- It's pet,
So, if it's pet...
all right.
WOMAN: I'm Daisy Bufane.
Daisy Bufane?
Jo Jo Mountainview,
I would be Peavey Meander.
- What?
- Peavey Meander,
Meander,
- Thurston Craddock.
- Hmm.
Uh, Baron Von Hugecock,
What?
That's... that was my street,
I lived on
Van Hugecock Avenue,
MAN: The little kid
who lives on Van Hugecock.
FRANCESCA:
Oh, God, where is Gus?
- Save us from this misery.
- Uhh.
CARL:
So, it's your middle name...
- Right.
- first.
CARL: And then... and then...
the name of the street
that you grew up on,
HEA THER: OK.
Lolita...
Honeysuckle.
CALVIN:
All right, I'll open it.
Obviously, everybody,
Gus is not here...
so I was thinking,
to pass the time,
why don't we all just kind of,
whoever wants to, stand up
and give our little Gus stories,
Uh, so, let me start off,
I think
my favorite Gus moment,
was when he called me
at 1:20 in the morning...
to ask what
I really thought about him.
WOMAN: What'd you say?
What did I say?
I said,"Well, Gus,
"I'm going to think the same
thing at 10. 00 in the morning,"
Then I hung up,
- Whatever.
- Calvin.
Aw,
It's all right, It's all right,
Listen,
let's get down to business.
If someone wants to stand up,
please, feel free.
The floor is open.
MAN, TAPPING GLASS:
All right. I got one, Calvin.
Yes,
that's right, that's right.
So, Gus and I... some of you
may not know this...
Gus and I used
to hunt together, all right?
And this one time, we're
and, uh, Gus climbs down,
to relieve himself
in the bushes, OK?
And, uh... it gets funnier.
It gets funnier.
So, uh...
Wow. Thank you, man.
I can't tell you
how much that means to me.
I really appreciate that,
you know?
Especially coming
from someone like you,
who writes and acts and directs
and plays the sax,
Originally,
I kind of felt like,
it was really coming after me,
you know?
Now I feel like
I'm coming after it,
Perfect,
It's not coming after me,
I'm going to get it,
- Can you grab that sword?
- I'm already on it, man,
It's weird, I was watching
this interview with Al,
- Pacino?
- Yeah,
And he was talking
about the differences,
between stage acting
and film acting,
and he was talking about
how being on stage,
is like being on this high wire,
like, a hundred feet up,
And if you fall,
you're fucked,
but acting in film is like
having the wire on the,
- Ground,
- On the Ground,
Oh, OK, you've heard that,
Yeah, man, working for guys
like you and Carl,
- the writing, just everything...
- Aw, come on, man,
Where is Carl, by the way?
Is he,
He had a party to go to,
Oh, that's right,
Is that that producer guy?
- Gus Delario,
- Oh, OK,
That's not too shabby,
Carl owns a tux, huh?
Mm-hmm,
Huh, Not just one of those
shirts with the design on it?
You know, he says
good luck and break a leg,
Thank you, Thank you,
Did I tell you about tomorrow?
Yeah, Fuck, man,
That should go really good,
Ann? Is that her name?
Yeah, It's a nice name,
I hope so, man,
I've been looking a long time,
Yeah, I hear you,
It's hard, I don't know,
You want to go for a beer
or something?
No, I got to teach a pilates
class, but thank you,
FRANCESCA:
Shouldn't we all say grace?
I think you're right,
Listen, it's been 45 minutes,
so let's eat,
Everybody dig in,
MAN: Thank you.
FRANCESCA:
Even at a party... bossy, bossy.
CALVIN: You know you love it.
You love it. You know you do.
- Oh!
FRANCESCA:
What are you doing? Shit.
" C-C-C-Calvin "
I'll get my ball,
CALVIN: Uh, everybody, this is
Lee Bright, Carl's wife.
Hi!
Our writer,
Gave us a beautiful script,
- Hi,
Hi, Thank you,
Lee, Lucy Morgan, L, A, Magazine,
I've worked with Carl,
Oh, yeah, That's right, Hi,
How are you? Nice to meet you,
Hi, I'm Lee,
Yeah, Hi, hi,
Hey, can you name all
the countries in Africa, Calvin?
What do you want from me?
- I'm not drunk,
- OK, Let's go,
I'm just...
you know, fuck you, man,
- Yeah, let's go,
- He needs to sober up,
All right, Sorry,
Sit down, Sit down,
He needs to fucking sober up,
I mean, come on,
LINDA:
You know what? Enough, No more,
No more drinks, all right?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
No more, Do not drink anything,
Carl's on his way, all right?
- Where are you going?
- I'll be right back,
Don't drink
and don't talk to anybody,
No one!
Tch,
Hey, Soledad, Do me a favor,
- You're beautiful,
- Oh, thank you,
- You working?
- No, I'm not,
You know,
I left something in here today.
Could you just let me in
for a second?
Of course,
Yeah, Thank you,
Thanks, Gus?
Hello?
Oh, my God,
Oh, my God.
LEE: I mean, I'm wearing
a linen suit, for God's sake...
and mascara's
running all over my face...
And I'm the only fucking car
in the parking lot.
It's, late,
Hey, where did you go?
Why?
He's what?
OK, OK, look, look, look,
We'll call down, and I'll say
I left something in here,
and I came up and I knocked
and he didn't answer, OK?
What? What?
Lee, I don't know what!
- Just wait,
- Fuck!
Wait for what? Oh, my God!
A few hours ago he was alive,
OK? He was really alive!
Oh, man!
Fuck, fuck! Do not touch him!
- Jesus Christ!
- Oh, my God!
Of course he's cold!
CARL: I don't know
ifyou can calculate...
I don't know
if you can quantify...
the effect that would have
on a ten-year-old girl.
I think Lee is like...
Have you ever seen
a dog get hit by a car...
but walk away?
And... there's this impact...
and you know
something terrible...
has happened to that dog...
but it walks away...
and it doesn't seem to even
realize the implications...
'cause it just goes on.
But you know
that something terrible...
has happened inside this dog.
LEE:
Why do you think he did it?
Oh, God, I don't know,
It's some weird sex thing,
I don't know,
LEE: No. Not this.
Ohh,
CARL: That's, I think,
what happened to Lee.
It's like... it's like...
She's a dog that got hit by
a car, and she walked away...
and she's still walking, but...
LINDA: I don't know.
I guess he was really sad.
CARL: Some very, very
important things...
inside her are damaged.
LEE: Oh.
Jesus.
CARL: So... my wife and I
were having trouble...
and I said I thought
maybe we were in a rut...
and that maybe
we should try something...
to liven things up,
and she said,"Like what?"
And I said like maybe we should
tape ourselves doing it.
And she was
completely shocked by this...
and she thought
it was beyond disgusting...
and that was that
for, like, four months.
And then one night,
out of the blue...
she says,"Let's do it. "
Ohh,
So, we get it all set up, and
I'm ready and she's ready,
and, uh, and she has gone out
and bought herself,
a little toy to use
in the video,
Really?
Well, it's not a little toy,
It's a... it's a huge,
Fucking, I mean, it was...
No one has a... you know, OK,
Well, anyway, I took one look
at this thing,
and I knew
I would not be able to...
I mean, it... I just couldn't...
I couldn't,
So we haven't,
And, you know,
you can't come back
from something like that,
I don't know whether
she lost respect for me,
or I lost respect for myself,
but something was lost,
HEATHER:
What are you going to do?
CARL: I have no idea.
I mean, I know professionally,
I'm gonna go back to teaching.
I always loved teaching.
- Really?
- Yeah.
CARL: Never learned a thing in
my life, but I love teaching.
The legacy of higher education.
HEATHER: What about your wife?
CARL: Tsk. I...
will hope
that we get over this.
HEATHER: Hmm,
CARL: Aside from loving her,
I just really like her.
A lot.
But...
I guess she thinks...
everyone and everything
is against her.
Somehow I just think...
it keeps her from being happy.
Is that your wife?
- Hey!
- Hi,
HEATHER: I'm with Dr, Green,
CARL:
This is... Heather, this is Lee,
- Django, he was sick,
- Django ate the brownies,
- Yeah,
- He's OK,
- He's fine now,
- We put him to bed,
CARL: Are you OK?
Um, the,
they found Gus
in his hotel room,
He's... he's dead,
He's...
HEATHER: I should go.
CARL: OK, OK, Thank you,
Thank you, Thank you for that,
HEATHER: Yeah.
Hey, OK?
OK, OK,
He... he's dead,
Oh,
Oh, sweetie pie, OK,
Um,
Well,
If you ever left me,
I would die,
I would die, Please don't,
OK,
I just want this day to be over,
Mmm,
Yeah, Let it out,
OK,
- Happy birthday,
- Thanks,
CARL: Mmm,
LEE: Hi,
Did you have any
interesting dreams last night?
CARL:
Um, no, Back to normal,
LEE: Oh,
CARL: I had an afro,
LEE: Huh?
LEE: I really don't know
what you should do...
when you're in love
with someone.
I know that you're thinking
about them all the time.
You want to be with them
and see things with them.
I think it's impossible.
It's an ideal to just think...
that you can actually
be kind all the time...
and never be disappointed
in them or by them.
It's hard. I mean, it's like
the dream is short-lived.
CARL: You've got
to keep hoping that...
that there's more.
FRANCESCA:
You know, you always...
It's when
you least expect it...
that something
kind of pops up, literally.
He just was...
appeared, kind of...
Um, so...
And nice that it's somebody...
that I knew
a really long time ago.
And, clearly, you know,
paid attention to me...
before I was, you know, blond.
So, that makes it nice...
but I think
that it's just fate...
and it's kind of, um...
I don't know. And today, just
negative ions in the air...
bringing good fortune
and... and, yeah.
Yeah.
Sam Osborne.
CAL VIN: I think,
you know, with Lucy...
she's a good listener,
like I said...
but she's also, you know,
she's teaching me stuff.
She comes from a nice family.
Her parents are still together.
She got three-four
brothers and sisters...
and they're
a real close-knit family.
It's just the opposite
of where I had come from.
I don't know. Honestly,
I don't know what it is.
I mean, I gotta just kinda go
off my gut right now...
and just see what feels right.
And right now,
when I'm with Lucy...
man, it just feels right.
Catherine,
Nicholas,
You're here,
I am,
I wasn't sure,
Neither was I...
until now,
Mmm,
- Mmm,
- Did you get that?
- The announcement? No,
- Where you going?
- Oh, Tucson,
Mmm! I'm going to Tucson,
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah,
- You ever been?
- No,
It's supposed to be beautiful,
That's what I hear,
I've never been, either,
- I'll see you on the plane,
- All right,
- Oh, are you Russian?
- No,
No, you're supposed to say,
"Am I rushin' where?"
- That's funny,
- Thanks,
Hi, I'm sorry,
Is this seat taken?
No, no,
Ohh,
Sorry,
I hope this isn't a full flight,
- Yeah, I hope so, too,
- Sorry,
LINDA:
You know, I was ready to go.
I was at the airport,
and I met...
like, in the food court,
I met this guy, um...
and then he sat next to me
on the plane...
and we just hit it off.
His name's Arty, and we just...
He just made me laugh.
He's really funny and sweet...
and, um, sort of open.
We just talked the whole time,
the whole flight.
ARTY:
She laughed in a way...
that made me feel like
she saw me.
I blew off
meeting... meeting Ann...
but we ended up spending
the weekend together.
And she's terrific.
LINDA: It was amazing.
We just had an amazing time.
It was definitely...
It was like out of a movie.
" Do something real "
" Sidewalks chasing,
citizens racing "
" Do something real "
" Bloodhounds closing in
on opposing men "
" Do something real "
" Crows like rats
like cats on vacation "
" Do something real "
" You've been scrapped,
I'm trapped at the station "
" Small claims courts,
community snorts "
" It's fine
when it's so concealed "
" Do something real "
" Extra special happiness "
" Defined
by an endless field "
" Of nothing real "
" Do something real "
" Crap stripe exits,
examiners expect it "
" Do something real "
" Plot of rockets,
holy ghost markets "
" Do something real "
" Small claims courts,
community snorts "
" It's fine
when it's so concealed "
" Extra special happiness "
" Defined
by an endless field "
" Of nothing real "
This is, like,
When we know
who the killer is,
I know,
The audience doesn't know yet,
But I know,
And this is where you see me
put the pieces together.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org