Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
-Come on! Come on!
-OK, all right.
Will you hurry up?
I'm home.
Afternoon, Miss Edna.
Penny, your mother called.
Tracy Turnblad, can't you say
hello to Mrs. Malinski?
Every day she's got to watch
that Corny Collins Show.
Delinquents, if you ask me.
It ain't right to be dancin'
on TV to that colored music.
She's just a teenager.
-Good-bye, Mrs. Malinski.
-Good-bye, Edna.
Come on, baby,
gonna teach it to you
Mashed potato
Feel that groovy beat now
Come on and move your feet
now, baby
-It's the latest
-Come on, honey
-It's the greatest
-Come on, baby
Mashed potato
Could you turn that racket down?
I'm tryin' to iron in here.
They found this dance
was so out of sight
To When the Lion Sleeps Tonight
-Mashed potato
-Mmm, yeah, mashed potato
Ladies and gentlemen,
Corny Collins!
Good afternoon, Baltimore ...
and welcome
to The Corny Collins Show.
That was Dee Dee Sharp ...
and today's bull's-eye hit,
Mashed Potato Time ...
and, hey, we've got
our first telegram of the day.
Thank you very much, Tammy.
"Please have Lou Ann Levorowski
and I.Q. Jones lead a dance."
Signed, "Your number one fan
in West Baltimore."
Here they come now.
Come on up here, kids.
-Hi, Corny.
-Hi, West Baltimore.
Lou Ann, you're
a pretty darn groovy chick.
How long have you been a regular
on the show?
I've been on the council
for five months.
-And you, I.Q.?
-Two out-of-sight years.
Not bad.
God, he's gorgeous, Penny.
Look at her hair.
Gosh, I wish mine was that high.
And what's your favorite record
from the survey?
-Gravy!
All right. Here's I.Q. Jones
and Lou Ann Levorowski ...
leading our next dance, Give Me
Gravy on My Mashed Potatoes.
Come on, baby, I need gravy
Give me, give me, give me,
give me gravy tonight
I know you dance
the mashed potato fine
But that don't show me
that you're really mine
Once we're dancin',
we'll start romancin'
So put that somethin' extra
on the line
Give me gravy
On my mashed potatoes
Come on and treat me right
Give me gravy
Baby, you're the greatest
So give me, give me, give me,
give me gravy tonight
Link, why don't you
tell the home viewers ...
where we're gonna be tonight?
Well, Corny,
we'll be at the Parkville VFW ...
For the Corny Collins
record hop.
Stuck-up little spastic.
She's such a queer.
What do you want to hear, Amber?
Shake a Tail Feather,
by the Five Du-tones.
Here they are,
the Five Du-tones.
I heard about this fellow
you been dancin' with
All over the neighborhood
Well, why didn't you
ask me, baby
Or didn't you think I could?
I know that
the bossa nova's worth a shot
I've seen him do the bird
all night
But if that was you and me
out there, baby
I would have shown you
how to do it right
Do it right
Bend over, let me see you
shake a tail feather
Twist it
Shake it, shake it, shake it,
shake it, baby
You should be on that council,
not her.
I know I should, Penny.
Hey, I'm going to that hop
tonight.
Oh, let me come.
We'll lie and say we're going
to the library to study.
It's a deal.
We'll meet at eight o'clock,
up on the avenue.
OK, young ladies.
I've had just about enough
of this screeching music.
Mother, we're watching
The Corny Collins Show!
Penny,
your mother called all frantic.
She said you are punished.
I'm always punished.
And, Tracy, I have told you
about that hair ...
all ratted up
like a teen-age Jezebel.
Oh, mother, you're so fifties.
Tracy's flamboyant flip
is all the rage, Miss Edna.
Jackie Kennedy, our first lady,
even rats her hair.
But Tracy ain't no first lady,
are you, Tracy?
No, sirree, she's a hairhopper.
That's what she is.
Now I've got nothin'
but hampers of ironing to do ...
and my diet pill is wearing off.
Tracy, I want you to go
to your room and study ...
and, Penny,
don't you be listening ...
to every bit of nonsense
that my daughter tells you.
lf I didn't know better,
I'd swear she was mental.
Now what? More soiled laundry
for mommy, I suppose.
Come in.
Edna, have you seen Penny?
Good lord, Prudy,
she's right over there.
Hi, mom.
Penny Pingleton,
you know you were punished.
From now on, you're wearing
a giant "P" on your blouse ...
every day to school ...
so that the whole world
knows that Penny Pingleton ...
is permanently, positively
punished!
-Eight o-clock.
-Bye, Miss Edna.
Bye, honey.
Oh, stop! Stop!
What is it?
Oh! Oh, my God!
-What's the matter?
-No, get off of me!
Don't look at me!
What's the matter?
I happen to have a blemish!
You had three good close-ups
today, period.
Why can't you dance up front
where the voters can see you?
Leave me alone, mother.
I have a pimple.
Ugh. And you had to choose
a colored record ...
as your favorite song,
didn't you?
That's nice for the neighbors.
You got something against
Connie Francis?
Shelley Fabares?
I love Shelley Fabares.
Amber, are you listening to me?
We have to have a little talk.
You know,
if your father is forced ...
to integrate Tilted Acres,
we're out of business ...
so, at least act white
on television.
Leave me alone, mother.
Shake a Tail Feather
is a wild song.
It's got a good beat,
and you can dance to it.
Oh, God, of all nights!
A Corny Collins record hop,
and I've got craters.
Oh, just pop it! Pop it!
Just relax. Relax.
Don't be ridiculous.
Take it easy.
Tension is the worst thing
for a complexion.
Come on. Lie down. Lie down.
No moping.
Mother is here.
You have beautiful skin, Amber.
There ... it's gone.
Now it's time for you know what
Mother, I know all the dances.
Come on. Get up. Get up!
Practice makes perfect.
I ought to know.
Don't forget,
I was Miss Soft Crab in 1945 ...
and that title wasn't handed
to me on a silver platter.
I worked for it.
Now come on. A-one, two ...
a-one, two, three, pony!
Mashed potatoes!
Faster!
Amber, l'd like to talk to you.
Yes, daddy?
-Don't stop. Cha-cha.
-I'm tired.
One, two, cha cha cha.
I had some new campaign fliers
made up today ...
all for daddy's little girl.
I want you to hand those out
at the hop tonight to everyone--
each and every one of those.
-Twist!
-Oh, daddy.
No lip from you, Miss lngrate.
This campaign is costing us
an arm and a leg.
New gowns,
hairdresser three times a week!
Why, your hairspray bill alone
is enough to eat up ...
all the profits
from the tilt-a-whirl.
You'll do as daddy says ...
or we'll send you
to catholic school ...
where you belong,
right, Franklin?
That's right. Catholic school.
Pass the macaroni and cheese ...
please.
Did you take that appetite
suppressant I gave you ...
on Dr. McKenzie's orders?
Mother, I'm a growing teenager.
I need food.
Let her eat, Edna.
Tracy, did you do your chores
around the house today?
Not Miss Tracy,
Cyd Charisse herself.
She's too busy ratting her hair
and doing the Ubangi stomp.
Tracy, we all have
responsibilities in life.
You may think owning
the Hardy Har joke shop ...
is all drudgery--
unwrapping dribble glasses,
checking doggie doo inventory--
but I wuv it.
You'll see. Work can be fun.
Can I please be excused
to go to the library to study?
Are you ready?
Let's have a ball
at the hall tonight
We'll groove and jerk
till the early light
Make the scene
with the record machine
And we'll dance and party
tonight
Come on ...
What's the problem, officer?
-This is a white establishment.
-Oh, come on.
Hey, listen,
we just came to dance.
-That's not fair.
-Open your purse, please.
And everything's all right
Go.
And every night
is Saturday night, yeah!
Let's go round,
bristol stompin', too
Hold me now
like it's all brand-new
Any dance that you want to do ...
Boys and girls,
stay on the dance floor.
Here comes
the hottest tune of the day ...
and it started
right here in Baltimore.
And where did you
see it first, kids?
The Corny Collins Show!
A big, strong line,
ladies and gentlemen.
It's Madison Time!
I can do that dance.
It's madison time. Hit it.
You're looking good.
A big, strong line.
When I say hit it, I want you
to go two up and two back ...
with a big, strong turn,
and back to the madison.
Hit it.
No. You dance better
than all of them.
Go ahead! Go!
You're looking good.
Now when I say hit it ...
I want you to go two up
and two back, double cross ...
come out of it
with The Rifleman.
Hit it.
Crazy.
Now when I say hit it ...
I want the big, strong "M",
erase it ...
and back to the madison.
Hit it.
Walk on. You're lookin' good.
Now, then, when I say hit it,
it'll be T-time.
Hit it.
Big, strong line.
Now when I say hit it ...
I want the big, strong
basketball ...
with a Wilt Chamberlain hook.
Hit it.
Two points.
Now this time
when I say hit it ...
I want the big, strong
Jackie Gleason ...
and back to the madison.
Hit it.
And away we go.
Crazy.
When I say hit it,
go two up and two back ...
double cross, and freeze.
Hit it.
And hold it right there.
All right. Hold on to your hats,
all you continental rockers ...
'cause
it's dance contest time ...
and we've got the wildest judge
in town.
You listen to her every night
on WEDD ...
and she hosts Negro Day
on The Corny Collins Show ...
the last Thursday
of every month.
A warm welcome for
the queen of Baltimore soul ...
Miss Motormouth Maybelle
herself, ladies and gentlemen!
Let's hear it, Baltimore--
Motormouth Maybelle!
All right, here she comes,
looking very fine.
Ooh whee! Tiddley papa!
I am a whopper!
Motormouth Maybelle
is my name ...
and, sweetheart,
dancin' is my game.
All right!
Chubby Checker and Pony Time!
It's pony time! Get up!
Hey, now, let's party
ln the Union Hall
It's pony time
When you hear this call
So get with it
Don't quit it
Get up
OK, fatso,
let's see what you're made of.
Or it'll make boss lines
But any way you're doin' it
You're gonna look real fine
So get with it
Don't quit it
Get up
Now you turn to the left
when I say gee
You turn to the right
when I say haw
Now gee, jam, jam, little baby
Now haw
Jam, oh, baby
Pony, baby
Do it, baby
Gonna see little Suzy
Who lives next door
She's doin' the pony
She's takin' the floor
Yeah, so get with it
Don't quit it
All right!
All right, Motormouth,
just three couples left.
Tammy,
bring on the applause meter.
Isit going to be
couple number one?
Or is it couple number two?
Or shall it be
couple number three?
All right.
I think we have a winner ...
and that winner is ...
I love 'em tender,
Tracy and Fender.
All right!
Tracy Turnblad and Fender.
Tracy Turnblad, you are
the queen of the hop tonight.
Listen, we're holding auditions
for the council tomorrow.
You ought to come down
and strut your stuff.
Oh, Corny, do you really think
I'm good enough?
What do you think, kids?
I hear ya.
Thanks for comin' down, Tracy.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Now, Motormouth,
I think it's time ...
we slowed things down a little
with Mr. Gene Pitney.
You can't hide your face
in this godforsaken place.
Here in your own city,
there's a town without pity.
Gene Pitney,
ladies and gentlemen.
When you're young
and so in love as we
And bewildered
by the world we see
Why do people hurt us so?
Only those in love would know
What a town without pity can do
Whore.
How can we keep love alive?
How can anything survive
When these little minds
tear you in two?
What a town without pity can do
No, it isn't very pretty
Thank you, girls.
And now it's time to move on
to a little something ...
we call the spotlight.
OK. First girl--Miss Pingleton?
I'm just a little nervous.
This is show business,
young lady.
lf you think
you're nervous now ...
Ha!
Wait till you're on the air.
OK, first question?
Are you now,
or have you ever gone steady?
Well, I'm not going
with anybody now ...
but l'd love to date
a council member.
Yeah, right.
Come on!
Exactly how many sweaters
do you have?
Gee, I never counted.
I guess about five.
-Five?
Next.
Nadine Carver,
Eastern High School.
Are you aware that Negro Day ...
is the last Thursday
of every month?
Yes.
I've been on it a few times.
I feel the show
should be integrated every day.
Yeah, right.
Can you relate
to Leslie Gore's music?
Look,
she ain't no James Brown ...
but I can dance to Lawrence Welk
if I have to.
-Lawrence Welk?
-Thank you, Nadine.
Tracy Turnblad.
Would you do a pimple cream
commercial on camera ...
if Corny asked you to?
I'd be proud to.
Luckily, I've never been cursed
with acne ...
like others ...
but I realize the devastating
effect of skin blemishes ...
on the social life of teenagers.
Would you ever swim ...
in an integrated swimming pool?
Oh, my God.
I certainly would, lggy.
I'm a modern kind of girl.
I'm all for integration.
Aren't you a little fat
for the show?
That's enough, Amber.
I would imagine
that many of the home viewers ...
are also pleasantly plump
or chunky.
Oh, come on. The show's
not filmed in cinemascope.
You're out of line, Amber.
Corny, Tammy, can't you see?
This girl's a trash can.
That's five demerit points.
You're suspended
from the show today.
Pack up your things and go home.
Oh, my God.
But I was supposed to lead
the ladies' choice.
I'm sure we can find
a replacement.
Please wait outside.
The council
will now meet in secret ...
debate your personality flaws,
and come to a final decision.
Miss Edna! Miss Edna!
Penny Pingleton,
you'll wake the dead.
Tracy's not home yet.
Plus, your mother called,
and she's on the warpath.
I know, Miss Edna.
Can I come in?
There's something
you've both got to see.
Well, yeah, come on up ...
but I've got ironing,
and Wilbur's working.
Mr. Turnblad!
It's not war with Cuba, is it?
-Or more negro problems?
-No. You'll see.
Did poor Debbie Reynolds
have a nervous breakdown?
This better be good.
Broad daylight, and
I'm sittin' in front of a TV.
I've seen The Corny Collins
Show, thank you, Penny.
Just watch.
I just lost
a $2.69 Silly Putty sale.
-This better be worth it.
-Wait, you'll see. Just watch.
-What's your name?
-I'm Ruby.
-And you?
-Dee Dee!
-And what about you?
-I'm Lucille.
Now, where are you gonna be
appearing tonight?
We'll be at the Royal Theater ...
-At Motormouth Maybelle's ...
-All Soul Review.
All right,
ladies and gentlemen ...
a big hand for Baltimore's own
Trinklettes.
I closed up shop for this?
Just wait.
All right,
let's keep the music playing ...
and the hits a-turning
with Mr. Gene Chandler ...
because the Duke of Earl
loves to cha-cha.
Duke, duke, duke of earl
There! There! Look! It's Tracy!
Oh, my God.
She's all peroxided up.
I'll be damned. Tracy's on TV.
With a triple process, yet.
But Tracy was accepted
on the Corny Collins Council.
Mr. and Mrs. Turnblad,
your daughter's a star.
Duke of earl
And you, you are my girl
And no one can hurt you
Oh, no
Oh, see?
She's already getting close-ups.
Does she get paid for this?
Big as a house!
I think she looks pretty, Edna.
'Cause I'm the duke of earl
Yes, I'm watching her now.
You are? Well, thank you.
Yes. Good-bye.
That was Hilda
from up Conklin Street.
She's going to send a telegram.
Oh, God! There she is!
Yes, l ...
Oh, I'm gonna love you
Nothing can stop me now
'Cause I'm the duke of earl
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's time to introduce ...
someone very special--
a brand-new council member ...
making her first appearance
on the show ...
and we already have telegrams.
Why don't you introduce
yourself?
Hi, Corny! I'm Tracy Turnblad,
and I go to Mervel High!
Well, Tracy,
someone out there likes you.
"Please have the new girl
lead a ladies' choice."
I was supposed to lead
the ladies' choice!
Tell me, Tracy,
are you going steady?
No, I'm not, Corny, but there is
somebody I've got a crush on.
Who, l'd like to know?
She's just a child.
Well, let's see
who the lucky guy is.
Ladies and gentlemen,
a ladies' choice.
Hi, Tracy! It's me, Penny!
She can't hear you.
Oh, she better hadn't dare!
lf you should lose me
Oh, yeah
You'll lose a good thing
lf you should lose me
Oh, yeah
You'll lose a good thing
You know I love you
Do anything for you
Oh, God!
He's violated the oath
of the friendship ring!
Aw, don't cry, honey.
You'll lose a good thing
I'm givin' you one more chance
For you to do right
lf you'll only straighten up
We'll have a good life
That fat girl's no competition!
White trash, plain and simple!
For all we know,
that girl could be high yellow.
Oh, mommy, daddy ...
I'll still be the queen
of the auto show, won't l?
Aw, honey.
No, she's not here.
Well, I'm sure
she loves you, too.
Yes, thank you. Good-bye.
This is amazing!
She's so popular already!
She could be one
of the June Taylor dancers.
Well, yes,
I am Tracy Turnblad's agent.
Give me a pencil! Quick! Quick!
How may I help you?
Oh, Tracy, you were wonderful!
Honey, we're real proud of you.
Oh, sweetie, listen.
Tomorrow, if you could get up
just a little bit closer ...
so we can see you better, OK?
And maybe even give
the Hardy Har a little p-p-plug.
Oh, mom, dad ...
Oh, Penny, my best friend ...
I'm so happy!
Finally,
all of Baltimore knows--
I'm big, blonde, and beautiful.
You're a teen leader now!
And the show biz offers
are pouring in.
Tonight, we have an audition ...
and, honey,
this is only the beginning.
Stick with me, and
we'll claw our way to the top!
Oh, God!
Fame, fortune, glamour ...
and to top it off ...
I'm in love!
Wow, Tracy, you're really tough!
Ooh, Tracy, what do you think
about this one?
I like it.
Wilbur would kill us
if we spent that much money.
You look gorgeous, Bertha,
simply exquisite!
Oh, I don't know, Pinky.
Have an eclair.
Eat up, girls, eat up.
Big is beautiful.
Tracy Turnblad!
Welcome to the Hefty Hideaway
house of fashion ...
for the ample woman.
Hi, I'm Mr. Pinky.
Mr. Pinky, I'm Tracy's business
manager, Edna Turnblad.
Well, it's a pleasure to meet
the both of you.
Here, we cater to the big-boned
gals like yourself ...
who are stylish and
at the same time frustrated ...
by the lack of sizes
in the department stores today.
I saw you on TV.
I want you to be my model!
Would she be paid for this?
One free outfit a month.
You start tomorrow.
I hope there's no diets
in the works ...
because I want to design ...
your Miss Auto Show
coronation gown myself!
Could you throw in a pair ...
of complimentary pettipants
in the deal?
You drive a hard bargain,
Miss Edna, and rightfully so.
Pettipants, pettigirdle--
you just let Tracy
take her pick.
How about a fabulous frock
just for me?
Tracy'll have to work
one extra day for free.
It's a deal!
Thank you, Mr. Pinky.
I'm going to make you a star!
I hope your father likes this.
He's going to love it.
You look beautiful.
It's the new you.
Mom, come on! Come on!
Go in the beauty shop?
Yes!
You haven't done that in years.
Come on, mom. You deserve it.
-No. Wilbur will kill me.
-Come on!
Oh, OK.
You really think I should?
Come on, mom.
Mama, welcome to the sixties.
Listen, I'll talk to you
after biology.
See you after P.E., guys.
ln the figure shown ...
line segment AB
and line segment CD ...
are chords of the circle.
Line segment PA
and line segment PC--
What is the problem, Mr. Davis?
I can't see through her hair.
I can't help it if he's short.
Your ratted hair
is preventing ...
yet another student's
geometry education.
It's feathered, not ratted.
Whatever you call it,
it's a hair-don't.
You've been warned repeatedly.
I want you to take a little walk
down to the principal's office.
Let's see what he has to say.
Anyway,
she was right in the car ...
in plain sight of just everybody
at the hop.
She was nude.
-No.
-That fat thing?
Tracy Turnblad is a whore.
-Happy now?
-But, mom, I didn't do--
-Don't "But, mom" me.
-l didn't! He's lying!
Ow! What was that for?
I'll give you something
to whine about.
Might as well just forget
that TV.
Miss Turnblad?
Have a seat.
Yes, sir.
Once again, your hairdo
is getting you in hot water.
Didn't two weeks in hairdo
detention have any effect?
I happen to be
the height of teen fashion.
You're on a one-way ticket
to reform school.
I'm afraid we're just going
to have to change your homeroom.
Starting today, you report
to class 10-D, room 108.
Special ed?
Yes, Miss Turnblad,
special education.
But that's for retards ...
and the black kids
you try to hold back.
Here, you will be taught
by specialists ...
trained to deal
with hairdo scofflaws ...
in high school society.
Mr. Davidson!
That will be all, Miss Turnblad.
The city of Baltimore has
an interesting Catholic history.
It was named after
Lord Baltimore.
He founded the Maryland colony
for Catholics and others ...
who could not practice
their religion in England.
Hey, don't touch my stuff!
I'll kick your ass!
Take it back!
Teach us how to dance, honey.
Come on,
show us what you've got, honey.
Go! Go! Go!
Good morning, class.
Good morning, Mrs. Shipley.
Now let's all stand and say
the pledge of allegiance.
I pledge allegiance
to the flag ...
of the United States
of America--
And one and two ...
and three and four.
Let's warm it up.
Come on, Amber,
can't we just be friends?
You're acting like a child.
Here we go with jumping jacks.
Let's go and one ...
and two and three ...
Now, as you all know, today
is special education's turn ...
at the dodgeball tournament.
So let's get
into the locker room ...
put on those gym outfits ...
and show them
that special education ...
is nothing to laugh about.
And three and four--
Hey, look! It's special ed!
This is special ed?
Special ed in the red!
All right, ladies, let's go.
Let's play dodgeball.
Penny, they put me in special ed
just 'cause of my hair!
Hey, I saw you
on The Corny Collins Show.
Where'd a white girl
learn how to dance like that?
Just practicing.
Oh, and watching Negro Day
on Corny Collins.
Hey, thunder thighs,
this one's for you!
-Grow up, Amber.
-God, I love this game!
My mama says Negro Day
ain't nothin' but segregation.
-Your mama?
-Yeah.
None other than
Motormouth Maybelle herself.
I'm Seaweed.
Hey, Penny, see
the colored boy--the cute one?
His mother
is Motormouth Maybelle!
He's gorgeous!
I'll get the fat retard!
Game over!
Let's hit the showers!
Did you see that?
Aw, you're all right, girl.
Are you sure she's all right?
She'll be OK.
It's not who wins.
It's how you play the game.
Tracy,
would you go steady with me?
Come on, everybody
Clap your hands
Ah, you're lookin' good
I'm gonna sing my song
It won't take long
We're gonna do the twist,
and it goes like this
Come on, let's twist again
Like we did last summer
Yeah, let's twist again
Like we did last year
Do you remember when
Things were really hummin'?
Yeah, let's twist again
Twistin' time is here
Round and round and up and down
We go again
Oh, baby,
make me know you love me so
And then twist again
Like we did last summer
Girl, let's twist again
Like we did last year
Come on and twist again
Twistin' time is here
Five, four, three, two, one.
You're on the air.
Fatty, fatty, two by four.
Can't get through
the dressin' room door?
Hi, I'm Mr. Pinky,
owner of the Hefty Hideaway ...
3311 Eastern Avenue.
Are you big-boned,
got a glandular problem ...
but you still want the glamour?
Don't worry about it. The Hefty
Hideaway has got it all.
This beautiful ensemble, being
modeled by our lovely Tracy ...
is available
in sizes twelve to twenty-six.
You heard me right.
You need a girdle? We got 'em.
Even got large size shoes ...
for that continental
Clementine look.
Oh, my darlin'
All at prices you can afford.
Big is beautiful!
Hefty Hideaway, Eastern Avenue.
You come on in today.
You'll be awful glad you did.
That's our little baby!
She's prettier
than Elizabeth Taylor.
Thank you, Mr. Pinky.
It's a thrill to have you
as a new sponsor ...
and, Tracy, you keep this up ...
and you just may be crowned
Miss Auto Show 1963.
Remember,
tomorrow is preteen day ...
so bring your little brother
or your little sister ...
or your cousins or
your nieces or your nephews ...
and let those tykes
rock-and-roll on--
The Corny Collins Show!
I've never been to North Avenue.
Don't worry.
Seaweed gave me the directions.
Oh, my God! It's Tracy!
What's your name?
Oh, that's so sweet.
Thank you.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
I got to go. Thank you.
Taxi! Taxi!
Come here! Quick! Quick!
Follow that bus!
-Yeah, this is the place.
-Wow!
This is great!
Look at that!
Never been
to this part of town before.
There they are!
Stop the cab!
Come on, everybody,
gather around
Dig this dance
I'm gonna put down
Isit the watusi?
No, baby
-Isit the twist?
-Uh-uh
Flap your wings
While the music swings
Get with the beat now
Get with the beat
Ow! You're lookin' real neat
Come on and work it, babe
Work, work, work
Come on and work it now
Tracy Turnblad!
You're my favorite dancer
on Corny Collins.
I'm L'il lnez, Seaweed's sister.
Well, it's nice to meet you,
L'il lnez.
This is my best friend Penny ...
and Link
you probably know from the show.
Wow, you guys really came.
Hey, everybody, this is Tracy ...
the baddest white dancer
in town.
And this is Link ...
and this is Penny.
No matter what you heard ...
we are gonna teach
the white children ...
how to do the bird.
Right! Come on. Come on. Watch.
Come on and work it, babe
Work, work, work
Come on and work your body
Do the swim
Do the flea now
Hey, miss white lady.
Can you spare me a quarter ...
so I can buy me a taste?
Somebody, please help me!
Here! Here! Take it all!
Take it! Take it all!
Please, don't hurt me! Please!
Why, thank you.
Thank you kindly.
Help!
Officer!
Yes, ma'am? Can I help you?
Say, man,
let's get together tonight
And play some hide-and-go-seek
I said, let's get together
and play some hide-and-go-seek
Let's go, let's sing
Ooh, the dirty boogie!
Well, I have a lady
who love me, love me
Dig her
for her huggy, huggy, huggy
Move on ahead
lf she ain't a hit,
you better holler, let her know
Are you ready?
I'm a-gettin' ready
Aw, man,
let's holler it this time
I went down the road,
the road was muddy
I stubbed my toe,
my toe was hurtin'
Move on ahead
lf it ain't a hit,
you gotta holler till it go
Two bottles of washing powder,
two bars of soap
lf it ain't a hit,
you better holler till it go
I went down the road,
the road wasn't muddy
I stubbed my toe,
my toe wasn't hurtin'
Bullfrog jumped
to the bottom of the well
He swear by the devil that he--
I'm not gonna say that!
Move on ahead
lf he ain't a hit,
you better holler till he go
Don't anybody come near me!
I'm armed, and
I'm prepared to protect myself!
Oh, God, mother!
I know you were snatched, Penny,
and I've come to save you!
Ooh, papa tuney, we got a loony.
Don't you try any of your voodoo
spells on me, you native woman!
We're just dancing.
Mrs. Pingleton,
stop acting crazy!
These are our friends.
Don't act ignorant,
Tracy Turnblad.
-Come on, Penny.
-Mother!
Come on. Run! Run!
Run for your life!
Don't push, please. Don't push.
Settle down. It's hot. Please.
lf you'll just stay still,
you won't be so hot ...
You're gonna do terrific,
all right?
Oh, it's gonna be a lot of fun.
Come on, come on
And do the fly with me
Hey, come on, everybody
Well, if you don't know
how to do it
Just watch and see
You got to shake your hands
all around
Like a fly in the sky ...
What the hell?
What are they doin' here?
Look what she's wearing.
Hurry up, but watch your step.
-You all together?
-Yeah.
Well, I'm sorry, but preteen day
is a white only show.
Negro day
is the end of the month.
Now, you can come on in
or get out of line, all right?
You mean you're gonna
turn this little girl away?
Look, I don't make the rules,
all right?
Aren't you aware of the supreme
court ruling on segregation?
I just want you to either
come in or don't, all right?
I have a dream.
You heard the man.
You're holding up the line.
Segregation never!
lntegration now!
Cut it out! Knock it off!
Sarge, come here. Come here.
Hold 'em. All right.
Ok, all you little tykes.
We got a real treat
in store for you.
A local group
with a big hit record.
Let's have a warm welcome,
come on, for The Lafayettes.
-Mother.
-Go on.
What are you waitin' for?
Well, life's too short
And you're too sweet
Every day of your life, child
You gotta spend with me
Now let me tell you about Sally
She's really tough
Girl, you're no boss to me
Mr. Collins,
there's some trouble outside.
There's a little black girl
who wants to be on the show.
Well, let her in, for God sakes.
The station management says no.
She's with some agitators.
I'm afraid a demonstration's
in the works.
OK, I'll be there
as soon as I can.
-Stop. Where are you going?
-Wait, I gotta go. Mother!
Tracy, you're a teen helper.
You can't go.
You can't change
the world's problems in one day.
l--l keep a-tellin' you
I said I told you, baby
Two, four, six, eight.
TV's got to integrate!
Tracy, please sit down
and stop this, please.
Hey, you, can I ask you
a personal question?
No, you can't.
-Isyour daughter mulatto?
-Why, you!
Look at this!
How dare you call my daughter
a mulatto!
Tracy! Tracy, come back here!
Two, four, six, eight.
TV's got to integrate!
Now, kids, we're gonna get
real lovey-dovey.
I know this is
one of your favorite records ...
and it's one of mine, too.
Leslie Gore,
sing your heart out.
Can I have this dance?
Sure.
You don't own me
What difference does it make,
Mr. Hodgepile?
One little black girl?
Who are you--the N.A.A.C.P.?
But it's an easy way
to integrate without trouble.
Absolutely not!
Baltimore is not ready
for integrated dancing!
Who do they think they are?
Please, when I go out with you
Don't put me on display
'Cause you don't own me
Don't try to change me
in any way
Two, four, six, eight.
TV's got to integrate!
Aah! That's the fuzz!
Well, that's it for today, kids.
See you tomorrow at 3:00,
live at Tilted Acres.
I don't tell you what to say
I don't tell you what to do
I wanna tell all you people
I dropped a penny in the well
Hoping you would come back soon
I couldn't believe what I heard
My fortune teller told me
My love with you was doomed
I hope her reading was wrong
I hope she was wrong
'Cause you've been gone too long
Oh, come home
Black Baltimore, your mother
is ready to show her might ...
and fight, fight, fight!
All right, now.
After school,
you know where to go--
Tilted Acres, for the show.
Segregation?
All right, now. I want
to introduce you to my main man.
I'm his biggest fan.
All the way from Louisiana ...
just to see me,
the big mamma jamma.
Now, I want a ball in this hall,
because he's a real doll.
Talkin' about Toussaint McCall.
I moved your picture
From my wall
And I replaced them
Both large and small
And each new day
Finds me so blue
Nothing
Takes the place of you
And, oh, my darling
I'm so blue
Because nothing
Oh, nothing
Takes the place of you
As
I write this letter
It's raining
On my window pane
And
I feel the need of you
Because without you
Nothing seems the same
So I'll wait
Until you're home
Again I'll love you
But I'm all alone
And, oh, my darling
Oh, Link. This is so romantic.
I wish ...
I wish I was dark-skinned.
Our souls are black ...
even though our skin is white.
Oh, Seaweed,
will integration ever come?
Oh, Penny,
my little white lily ...
we're outcast from both
societies--black, white.
Our love is taboo.
Oh, go to second. Go to second.
Seaweed, look!
Tracy Turnblad, it's your mommy!
Oh, my God, it's my mother!
-She's gonna kill us!
-I'm gonna die!
Where are they?
Don't run, Tracy! You'll fall!
You have heels on!
You'll fall, honey!
Oh, thank God. Can we please
come in for a little while?
-Open up!
-Please!
Oh, come on. Open up!
Can we come in?
Come on, guys! Come on! Come on!
Like, hi, cats.
Sit down.
You got the fuzz chasin' you?
No, we were--
Wow, you cats are real beatniks.
Just like New York.
Day-o, day-o
Daylight's a-comin',
and he wanna go home
You two checkerboard chicks?
What?
You know, black and white,
salt and pepper.
Well, yes, I'm
a checkerboard chick, I guess.
I'm an integrationist.
We shall overcome someday.
Not with that hair, you won't.
You look like a hairhopper
to me.
I mean,
your hair is really uncool.
How do you get your hair
so straight and so flat?
With an iron, man.
I play my bongos,
listen to Odetta ...
and then I iron my hair, dig?
I think
we'd better get going now.
The coast looks clear.
Let's do some reefer.
We'll get high,
and I'll iron the chicks' hair.
Reefer?
Drugs?
Locoweed.
When I'm high, I am Odetta.
Let's get naked and smoke.
Cool.
Don't breathe it in.
You'll be addicted.
Later, sister, later ...
Much later.
"l saw the best minds
of my generation ...
"destroyed by madness,
starving, hysterical, naked ...
"dragging themselves
through the naked streets ...
"...burning up for the ancient,
heavenly connection..."
-Oh, hi, dad.
-Dad?
Don't "Hi, dad" me. The whole
world saw you on the news.
Penny, this is Dr. Frederickson.
He's a psychiatrist, and he's
going to make you all better.
Feeling depressed, Penny?
Want to talk about it?
Think of all the white boys
in school ...
and how much
you'd like to date one.
Be a good little girl
and slip this on.
I'm telling you,
shock treatments are the answer.
Come here, Penny.
What are you doing?
Good girl. Good girl.
I love you, Seaweed!
-Shut up!
-Get her in the car!
It's gonna be all right,
dumpling. Get her, doc, quick!
Prudy,
this is totally unnecessary.
Come on, honey. Time to go home.
You can see Link tomorrow.
Come on.
We've been worried sick
about you.
This neighborhood is
certainly no place for a star.
Now, get in that car
before someone sees you.
Tilted Acres is not fair--
racist people everywhere.
Get out of here!
Go back where you belong!
Well, personally,
I have nothing against them.
It's merely a matter
of economics.
Tilted acres
will never be integrated.
-Segregation today.
-Segregation tomorrow.
Segregation forever!
One black face gets on camera,
this show's off the air.
The kids don't care
if blacks dance on the show.
Can't you see
this is ripping the city apart?
Motormouth Maybelle is
out there, and she's our friend.
We've done hops together
for years. The kids love her.
Look, The Corny Collins Show
remains white ...
Or you're all fired!
Good afternoon, Baltimore ...
and welcome
to The Corny Collins Show.
Yes, we are live
from Tilted Acres ...
so hop in the car
and bring the whole family out.
Right now
I want to introduce to you ...
the top contenders
in the Miss Auto Show contest--
Amber Von Tussle
and Tracy Turnblad.
Now, I understand you're both
going to introduce ...
a brand-new dance
on the show today.
Yes, I am, Corny.
It's called the limbo rock ...
and I bet some people
will find it quite difficult.
Here it is--the limbo rock.
Every limbo boppin' girl
All around the limbo world
Isgonna do the limbo rock
All around the limbo clock
Jack be limber, Jack be quick
Jack go under limbo stick
All around the limbo clock
Hey, let's do the limbo rock
Limbo lower now
Good afternoon, Penny.
Feeling better?
Getting in touch
with your anger?
Go, Tracy! Go!
Limbo ankle, limbo knee
Bend back like a limber tree
Jack be limber, Jack be quick
Jack go under limbo stick
All around the limbo clock
Hey, let's do the limbo rock
I watch that tramp,
and I'm embarrassed to be white.
You know, Edna, I've been
readin' about these kids.
Maybe Tracy could be
some sort of campus leader.
Wilbur, it's the times.
They're a-changin'.
Something's blowin' in the wind.
Fetch me my diet pills,
would you, hon?
Get yourself a limbo girl
And then shoot the limbo whirl
Go back to Africa
where you came from !
Your kind's not wanted here!
Well, Baltimore,
you saw it here first.
The limbo rock.
Thank you very much, Amber.
I'm a winner, Corny.
Well, Amber,
you won the dance ...
but let's check
the election results ...
to see how you're doin'.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have an upset!
For the first time,
Tracy Turnblad ...
is number one with a bullet.
What do you have to say
for yourself, Tracy?
lf elected, I plan to represent
all of Baltimore ...
and today l'd like to
introduce a brand-new dance ...
and dedicate it
to some of my special friends ...
who, because
of small-minded people ...
can't be here with me today.
My dance is called the waddle.
That girl's got roaches
in her hair.
Roaches?
My little Tracy's a clean teen.
There's no bugs on our baby.
I'm not kidding. I just saw one.
Ha ha!
Amber, you're such a comedienne.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Tracy Turnblad and the waddle.
You all make me sick!
What is going on here?
Look,
we had nothing to do with it.
Seaweed! Come on!
Tracy, just keep dancing.
Move it around here.
What, are you crazy?
Come on! Move out!
That's why
I would like to humbly state--
Daddy! Mommy!
Daddy! Mommy! Daddy!
There's a riot going on!
-A riot?
-A race riot!
-Yo, I'm talkin' to you!
-Look, I have no--
Everybody just stay calm !
Stay calm--
You leave my boyfriend alone,
you witch!
-You scum !
-Stay back! Stay back!
Police brutality!
Negroes.
Black boys.
Police brutality!
Hey, let her go!
Good evening.
Friday, June 5, 1962.
Racially tense
Tilted Acres amusement park ...
long a tradition
of Baltimore fun ...
-Penny! How are you?
-What are you doing here?
What happened to your head?
It happened at Tilted Acres.
-Get me out of here!
-OK.
Come on.
Thanks for coming.
Come on!
Be careful!
Girl, they gonna flip
when they see the new you.
... including Link Larkin.
That's Link Larkin,
my boyfriend!
Ooh! Boyfriend!
... common-law boyfriend
of Miss Turnblad ...
was listed in fair condition ...
at Union Memorial Hospital
tonight ...
recovering from
two fractured kneecaps ...
received in one
of many incidents of violence ...
that erupted today.
I love you, Tracy.
Tracy Turnblad
is a human roach nest.
Is this
the caliber of teenager ...
we want representing Baltimore
at the auto show?
Amber will be so proud of us.
We're going to go down
in the history books ...
for this one, Velma.
Tracy's parents had an emotional
appeal for their daughter.
Tracy, honey,
we know you are innocent.
-It's Miss Edna.
-Has she always been that big?
We joined the N.A.A.C.P.
And we will fight in every way
possible to get you released ...
and back in front of the cameras
where you belong.
God! It's mother!
You've got to hide!
Where?
Under the bed! Under the bed!
It is time that black and white
take hands ...
-Hey, it's motormouth!
-Mom !
We will not stand for racism !
Free Tracy Turnblad!
Now, darling ...
aren't you glad
that you were punished ...
and under psychiatric care?
You could have been killed
today.
I wish I was at a hootenanny
in Harlem.
-What was that?
-Just the TV.
I heard somebody laugh.
Oh, my God! There are
colored people in my house!
I'm gonna make
a citizen's arrest!
Stop! Stop!
-Paddy, stop them !
-What the--
Come on, Penny!
Penny Pingleton,
I'm calling the cops!
You are no longer my daughter!
You are punished
even after you die!
Corny, it's a real pleasure
to be here today ...
in the city of Baltimore
at this wonderful auto show.
Thank you. I have my aide here
with the scissors ...
and we're going
to take this opportunity ...
to open the show here
in the city of Baltimore.
-There we are.
-Thank you, governor.
Wonderful to see you again.
How are you doing?
Well, how do you do, governor?
So nice meeting you.
You've got some spinach
on your tie.
Hardy har har!
Free Tracy Turnblad!
Segregation never!
lntegration now!
Free Tracy Turnblad!
Now, just remember ...
if Amber loses,
she walks off the set ...
and then you throw the bomb.
Who the hell is Tracy Turnblad?
She's
an upper lower-class teenager ...
who was arrested
in yesterday's demonstration ...
and is currently being held
at Montrose.
She is a hairhopper.
A what?
Free Tracy Turnblad!
Jesus Christ!
More integration pickets.
This is a political hot potato,
and I wasn't even warned!
This came out of nowhere.
We had no idea
of her grass roots support.
You keep
the goddamn cops away ...
before this makes
the national news.
Free Tracy Turnblad!
Governor, we must have
some answers right now ...
for our vast
television audience.
The voters
are demanding answers ...
from right here
at the governor's mansion.
This demonstration's
gonna turn nasty.
We've got to get answers.
Hey, no police. No police.
Good evening, governor.
May I speak with you?
How are you, my dear?
Nice to see you.
What are you doing?
What is this?
What's with the handcuffs?
Hi, honey. I'm - I'm home.
Well, Baltimore,
today's the big day.
We're here live
at the new armory ...
for the grand opening
of the 1963 auto show.
And who will be
the dancing princess ...
from our council
to be crowned queen?
We'll know right after this.
No cops. No cameras.
We're gonna work this thing out
ourselves, aren't we?
Madame,
you do have the key to these?
We'll talk about the key
after you release Tracy!
Stinky, stinky, stombo.
Tombo, tombo, tombo.
Alla, balla, basso.
Well, the moment of truth has
arrived, ladies and gentlemen.
-You the audience ...
-Excuse me.
... has made your decision ...
and here to announce the results
we have Mr. Arvin Hodgepile ...
president of WZZT studios,
ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you. Thank you.
We have a difficult situation
with the votes tabulation.
The results were quite close.
Technically, the winner
is Miss Tracy Turnblad.
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
Quiet!
Shut up,
or we're goin' off the air.
Now listen carefully.
Since Miss Turnblad
is in reform school ...
the judges
have found her ineligible.
I would like to announce,
on behalf of WZZT ...
the winner
of the Miss Auto Show 1963--
Amber Von Tussle!
Let's talk this over!
We can discuss this.
Oh, what!
-Let's talk it over!
-Leave him alone!
I'll call!
Well, Amber, like it or not ...
you're officially
Miss Auto Show 1963.
Any words for your opponent ...
who many feel
was the more popular winner?
I'd like to lead a dance
and dedicate it to that loser.
Tracy Turnblad,
I hope you're watching ...
because this one's for you.
It's a brand-new dance--
one that I'm sure
you'll know how to do.
It's called the roach.
Too bad you can't be here
to do it.
I'm the winner!
Leave me alone!
Amber Von Tussle and the roach.
There's a dance
They're callin' the roach
It's buggin' all the kids
from coast to coast
Well, now, form a big line
-To the floor,
-Ooh, roach, roach
Everybody now, squish
Ooh, squash
Kill that roach
Yes, there's a roach
upon my floor
For Christ's sakes,
pardon Tracy Turnblad!
All right!
Free Tracy Turnblad!
You stomp, step, skip, two,
three, four, five, six, seven
Squish
Ooh, squash
Kill that roach
Hey, hey, hey, hey, now
Squish
Ooh, squash
Kill that roach
Hey, hey, hey, hey, now
Squish
Ooh, squash
Kill that roach
Well, I was takin' a bath
the other night
Checked my hair,
it was lookin' a fright
Well, I went down to the store
To get some hair-on
Squish
Kill that roach
Let me at him
I'm gonna kill him
I got something for you.
Wait. Hold on.
Baltimore, you are seeing
history being made today!
White and black together
for the first time on local TV!
I hate you, Tracy Turnblad!
The Corny Collins Show
is now integrated!
Yes! All right!
Amber,
we're going home right now!
No, mommy! No!
Stop! Get away from me!
Get away!
Come on!
I'm a married man with a family!
Don't hurt me, please!
Thank you. Thank you.
I love you, Baltimore!
I don't know about you,
but I feel like dancing.
I've got the bug.
Everybody's jumpin',
movin' around
Nobody's standing still
or keeping their ground
You can't tell what'll happen
when they pass it around
It's the bug
You got it, you got it,
you're all on your own
Somehow it seems better
when you do it alone
What are you doing?
Give me that! Ow!
You little ... Oh!
Well, come on, baby,
let's do the bug
Come on, baby, and give me a hug
Come on, baby,
my turn's long due
I wanna bug, bug
A hole in my shoe
Real bugs bug me,
no matter what size
Come down! Come down!
Itching powder!
It's that old bug
Let's dance!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org