Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
(Man chants in distance)
(Chant continues)
(Chants again)
(Repeats chant)
You know what I mean, you know?
You know?
- You know?
- I know.
It's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's...
Isn't it just?
You know? You know, it's...
You know, they, they, they, they, they...
Do they?
They're not, they're not, they're not, they're not!
They're not, you know?
Oh.
Are you warm enough?
# I know, I said that I was leaving
- That's nice.
- He's, he's, he's...
- Is he?
- You know, he's...
Ah, now, and he's, he's... Oh, he's...
Oh, no.
He's, he's, he's...
- What is he?
- He's a prick.
Oh! I know a few.
(Grunting)
There you go.
That's it. Yeah.
- You know what I mean, you know?
- Yeah, yeah.
She's, she's, she's...
She's, she's, she's, you know. She's, she's...
You know. She's, she's, she's,
she was, she was...
She was, she was, she was, she was...
- She was so...
- Was she?
She wouldn't, you know.
She wouldn't. She wouldn't, you know.
She wouldn't, and I'm, I'm...
I'm not, you know.
I'm not, you know. I'm, I'm...
She's... you know. She's...
She's, you know. She's...
You know, they're,
they're, they're, they're...
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
I do.
What's your name?
Hey?
- Come on.
- Where are you going?
- Taxi!
- (Giggles) That'll be for me.
Come on, 'sake.
Keep your hair on.
I've only just met you. Mum warned me
about going with strangers.
- Where are you going?
- Longest way out, shortest way home.
Oh, sod's law.
- Is he gone?
- All right. What?
- Ease up.
- What?
- Is he gone?
You what?
- Is who gone?
- The rubber knocker man.
- You what?
- Oh! The rubber knocker man.
- Sssh.
- Why didn't you say?
- Is he gone?
- Yeah, yeah. No, he's gone, he's gone.
- 'Sake.
- I see him. He's a-running.
He's a-rubbing his knockers. He's gone.
Oh, he's gone. Hang about.
Oh, there you go.
Found the en suite, then.
Shake it all about.
What am I doing?
Oh, all done, then?
All right?
Have you had your dinner?
No.
- Here you are, take that.
- No.
- Something to eat.
- No, thank you.
- Where are you going to sleep tonight?
- In a bed.
Of course you are. Silly me.
What?
You know?
Yeah.
Next, please.
- Are you asleep?
- Yeah.
So what you been up to?
- This and that.
- Ducking and a-diving.
Wheeling and a-dealing.
- So where you been?
- Tooing and a-froing.
- Seriously.
I went for a walk.
Thought we were going out for a drink.
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
- Left you a message.
- My battery died on me.
- So how was your day?
- How was your day?
Fantastic, the earth moved.
- I've got a violent pupil in my flock.
- What's he doing?
- Being violent.
- What, is he hitting you?
- He's been hitting the other kids.
- What are you doing about it?
I spoke to Heather.
Poor little bugger.
You've got to love them, haven't you?
Yeah, otherwise you'd kill them.
So where did you go tonight?
The eternal question. Where have we been?
Where are we going?
What's the meaning of life?
I went to the moon and then back again.
- Wow, you walk quickly.
- I've got good legs.
Yeah, you've got great legs.
Not that you're my type.
- These are great legs.
- Ah, get off. Read your palm.
Oh, I see a very strong line.
It's your bullshit line,
and I see a tall, dark, handsome... turd.
- Next to it is a bloke.
- A bloke?
- Yeah.
- Let's see.
Oh, yeah, there he is. Isn't he gorgeous?
- Not my type.
- No.
Where have all the good men gone, eh?
Well, they're not hiding in here, are they?
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
We're ready and waiting.
They haven't got the balls.
- All right, Nick?
- Yeah.
- How you doing there?
- I'm reading.
- What you reading?
- "Yuck!"
- "Yuck!" That's nice, isn't it?
- Oh, it's a classic, that.
- Nick, this is Tim.
- Hi, Nick.
Hello.
Now, Nick, when I asked you the other day,
did you know what a social worker was,
can you remember what you said?
A social worker helps you on... hard things.
A social worker helps you with hard things, yes.
- That's true.
- Yeah, very good.
That's right. And I was thinking,
how could I help Tim
to get to know you a bit better?
I was thinking, because you've done
some very good learning this year...
POPPY: Oh, I'd say so, yes.
- He has, hasn't he?
And I was thinking, would you mind
showing Tim some of your work?
- No.
- That's a good idea.
I'd love to see it.
Is that, "No, you don't want to"
or "No, you don't mind"?
- No, I don't mind.
- I didn't think you would.
Well, that's good, isn't it? What's it going to be?
- You come and sit here. Have a look.
- Oh, thanks.
- We should show off your maths.
TIM: Are you good at maths, Nick?
- Are you all right, sweet? A bit tired?
- Let's have a look at this. Here.
- What's this, then?
- Look.
- This is last term.
TIM: Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick.
POPPY: Oh, he's good at his numbers.
- Very good.
- Yeah, smiley faces.
- I'm going to see you later, OK?
- See you.
- Thanks, Mrs Stockman. See you soon.
- Smiley face, big smiley face there.
- Smiley face, ticks everywhere.
- Very good.
- All last term this was.
Isn't it? Not bad.
Is it good this term as well?
Er... yes, it's a bit on and off. Isn't it?
- Oh, yeah.
- Not so good.
- We'll get around that, though.
- Of course.
You know you're not in trouble, don't you, Nick?
- Yeah.
POPPY: Yeah.
No-one could be angry with you. Not for long.
You've been a bit angry, though, haven't you?
Yeah.
- What's made you angry?
- I don't know.
You don't know?
What's it like at home?
Fine.
- Yeah, with you and your mum?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- You get on with your mum, don't you?
- Yeah.
- Does anybody else come to the house?
- No.
No? What about any of Mummy's friends?
Has she got a boyfriend?
Yeah, she does.
She does? What's his name?
Jason.
Is Jason nice?
No.
Has he been making you angry, Nick?
Yeah.
That's no good, is it?
Have you got a piece of paper, Miss Cross?
Yeah, sure we could rustle one up.
- You good at drawing, Nick?
- Yeah.
OK.
- Here we go.
- Let's get you a pencil.
There you go.
Take that, Nick, and what I'd like you to do,
is draw me a house.
Do you think you can do that?
- Yeah.
Thought so.
That's your mum, in her bedroom.
- And who else is there?
- Jason.
Jason's there. Where's he?
- He's in the living room.
- In the living room.
- You're all in different rooms, aren't you?
- Mm-hm.
Why are you in a different room to Jason?
- Because he's not nice to me.
- He's not nice. What does he do to you?
He hits me.
- He hits you.
- Yeah.
You know that's not right, don't you, Nick?
- It was lovely to meet you.
- Yeah, you too.
Thank you. I think he'll be all right.
- Of course.
- Yeah.
- He's got a good teacher.
- Has he? Where is she? I can't see her.
- I'm looking at her.
- Oh. Thank you very much.
- I wouldn't mind looking at her again.
- She wouldn't mind looking at you again.
Really? That's good.
- Give us your number.
- OK, I'll write it down.
That's a start.
There you go.
- Thank you very much.
- You're welcome.
- Goodbye.
- See you.
Are you all right? Had a good week?
- Yeah.
- Oh, that's a bonus.
Smells in here.
I didn't know you had a dog.
No, it isn't a dog. I just had a lesson.
- Bit stinky, was he?
- Could say that.
- You got a dog?
- No, I live in a flat.
Be cruel, wouldn't it? I'd love a dog.
Have you ever had a dog?
- Your mum and dad got a dog?
- My dad's dead.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
- How do you get on with your mum?
- I don't.
Oh.
You live with your mum and dad?
No. (Chuckles)
How old do you think I am, 12?
- 22, 23?
- Oh, I like you.
You can stay.
I'm 30.
Old maid, now.
So, do you live on your own?
No. I live with my flatmate.
Nearly 10 years now. She done well, bless her.
- That's a long time.
- She's gorgeous. I love her.
What do you mean, you love her?
I mean, I love her. She loves me.
We love each other.
What, so you're...
What?
Yeah, that's it. That's us.
- You got a problem with that, Scott?
- No, nothing to do with me.
I don't think it is.
- OK, check your mirrors. Enrahah.
- Yeah, checking, checking.
Indicate and knock on the door,
let them know you want to come in.
Knock on the door, OK. Put your foot
down on the clutch. Put it in first gear.
OK, find your biting point just before you go.
OK, stop.
- What?
- Put the car in neutral.
Put the car in neutral, the hand brake on.
Take your hand off the steering wheel,
foot off the pedal, turn off the ignition.
- I haven't started.
- I've stopped.
- Now you tell me why I've stopped.
- Got a headache?
No. Yes! I have got a headache
and you tell me why I've got one.
Erm... I don't know. Time of the month?
Oh, give me a clue.
Well, think. Top to toe. Top to toe.
- Boots, Poppy. Boots.
- Oh, here we go.
Every week I ask you,
"Please wear appropriate footwear."
And every week you insist
on wearing those stupid boots.
- Yeah, sorry about that.
- You know what this is?
- This is vanity before safety.
- Oh, right.
"I'm sorry, Mrs Jones. I'm sorry.
Poppy killed your child,
but don't worry, she looked really cool
in her sexy, seductive boots."
- Am I keeping you awake at night?
- No.
Are you sure about that?
Shall we get on with the lesson?
Will you do something about your boots?
I don't think so. They're fine. I'm comfy in these.
A lot of people drive in heels.
Very well, on your head be it.
Yeah, okey-dokey.
Keep to the left of the centre. Enrahah. Enrahah.
When we come to this bend, what do we do?
- Are you expecting the worst?
- We keep to the left.
We expect a juggernaut, OK?
- Expect the worst.
- Expecting the worst.
- More gas, more gas.
- More gas.
- There's a juggernaut, get down!
- Poppy, put both hands on the wheel
and keep your eyes on the road!
- There was a juggernaut, Scott.
- There wasn't a juggernaut.
- That was a stupid thing to do, Poppy.
- There was a little...
- Give me gas. Give me gas.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- I'm giving you gas.
- Away from the bend. Give me gas.
Right.
- Poppy.
- Yeah?
I am not going to allow you
to endanger both of us,
just for you to have your stupid little joke.
I mean, if you want to make jokes,
if that's what you want to do,
then I will gladly sit here
and you can take the mickey out of me
for £22.50 an hour - it's your money.
- I'm big enough. I can take it.
- Can you?
But I will not allow you
to endanger yourself, myself,
and other road users just for your amusement.
I wasn't taking the mickey, Scott.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't touch me! Don't you touch me!
Right, that's it. Get out!
- What's happening now?
- Get in the passenger seat.
- Why?
- The lesson is over. I'm taking you home.
Oh. So, that's that, then, is it?
All right, then.
Speak to the office and when they ask you,
tell them I can't teach you.
Fucking...!
Take it easy, Scott. It's all right. It's all right.
Well, come on, then. Let's go.
It's costing me enough money as it is.
All I ask is that you behave like an adult.
What? Like you, Scott?
It's like musical cars, this.
- What now?
- Get in the driver's seat, please.
I've never given up on a pupil.
Oh, so that bit's over, is it?
Oh, well, make your mind up.
Do you want to have a walk,
get a breath of fresh air or something?
No? All right, then.
Check your mirrors.
What about that guy you gave up on
the other week, eh?
He passed his test this morning.
- Oh, well, that's good.
- He didn't deserve to.
He was very rude.
He didn't even say thank you.
I don't know, some people.
Doesn't take much.
- It'sjust the little things.
- That's right.
Enrahah.
Keep to the left of the centre of the road.
You can make jokes while you're driving,
but you will crash and you will die laughing.
Well, if you're going to go,
it's the best way to go, I suppose.
- Are you scared of death?
- No, I'm not scared of death.
I'm scared of dying. That's why I woke up.
- Oh, when did you wake up?
- A long time ago.
- Who set the alarm?
- I did.
- I opened my eyes and I saw.
- And what did you see?
You can laugh while Rome is burning,
but believe you me, Poppy, it is burning.
And if you don't wake up,
then you will be burnt to a cinder.
I mean, look around you. What do you see?
Do you see happiness?
Do you see a policy of bringing
happiness to people? No. No.
You see ignorance and fear.
You see... You see the disease
of multiculturalism,
and what is multiculturalism?
Multiculturalism is non-culturalism.
And why do they want non-culturalism?
Because they want to reduce collective will.
The American Dream never happened.
The American nightmare is already here.
Look at the Washington Monument.
It is 555 feet above the ground
and 111 feet below the ground.
555 plus 111 is 666.
666, Poppy. 666.
Keep to the left of the centre of the road.
Are you an only child, Scott?
Enrahah. Use all your mirrors.
Watch your speed.
Same time next week?
- Of course.
Stay happy.
- Oh, come on, Suzy.
- Don't worry, she'll be here.
What time's Helen expecting us?
- She wanted us there by four.
- She's going to go nuts.
Not much I can do about that. Runs in the family.
How was your lesson?
I don't know. Dark.
- How do you mean, dark?
- Dark as the night.
He hasn't been feeling you up, has he?
I'd like to see him try.
Touching your knee instead of the gear stick,
that old chestnut.
No.
You all right, Poppy?
Yeah. I think I'm just worried about Helen.
Really, how do you mean?
- Should have gone to see her ages ago.
- Yeah, families, eh?
Oh, here's Suzy.
- (Squealing)
POPPY: Here we are.
- Hello!
- Are you all right?
- (Laughter)
- Look at this! Oh, mind the tree.
- It's nice to stand up.
- All right, Poppy?
- All right, Jamie?
- Suzy, mind your sister's new motor.
- You all right, Jamie?
- All right?
- Yeah.
- Long time no see.
- Yeah, long time no see.
- All right, Suzy?
- All right, Jamie?
- All right.
Ooh, these are for you.
- I got you a little bottle of bubbly.
- Oh, thank you very much. It's lovely.
- All right. I'll pop these upstairs for you.
- Lovely, Jamie. Thank you very much.
- Isn't that lovely?
- I'm guessing we're having a barbecue.
Whatever gave you that idea, Suze?
- Keep on running, Jamie.
- Yeah.
Better put these down now, shall I?
That's a good idea. Having fun yet?
- Yeah.
- Take your shoes off, Suzy.
- All right!
- And you too, Poppy.
I'll give you the grand tour.
This is the downstairs toilet.
- Oh, I thought it was the wine cellar.
- I wish.
Through here, this is the living room.
Ta-da! Yeah, went with
a blue and silver theme in here.
Did you, Jamie? It's very nice, isn't it, Suze?
- Here's our dining area.
- Lovely.
There's usually another chair here.
But we put it outside for later.
- For the foxes?
- Yeah!
- We only got it last weekend, didn't we?
- Yeah, flat pack.
Really?
It's beautiful, Helen.
Haven't you got green fingers, eh?
- Is it all right to smoke, Helen?
- I suppose so.
Can you get the ash in the ashtray, please?
I'll try not to miss the potty.
- You've been trained.
- Come and see my roses!
- Oh, lovely.
- I only planted these this time last year.
- You didn't.
- They've done really well.
I want to grow them into a big bush.
- They smell lovely.
- Don't they just.
My lavender. Put that by the compost.
- Best place for it, really.
- Hydrangeas need perking up a bit.
Bit down in the dumps, is he?
Hello there, cheer up. Might never happen.
Busy Lizzies are doing very well.
Beautiful flowers.
- Been a bit busy, has she?
- Going to plant more of these next year.
- That looks crap.
- Thanks, Suzy.
- Eucalyptus.
- Oh, Zoe.
BOTH: Gum tree!
- Brings back memories, doesn't it?
- Yeah, the smell.
POPPY: G'day, blue, how's it going?
- Drinks up.
- Cheers, Jamie. Let me give you a hand.
- Cheers, everyone.
- Cheers.
So, you've spoken to Mum, then?
Yeah, I spoke to her last Sunday. She's all right.
- Lovely. She coming down?
- Yes.
What's she coming down with? Syphilis?
- When did you last speak to her, Suzy?
- Oh, leave it out.
- You should give her a ring.
- I spoke to her.
- They're very excited.
- Course they are.
They'll come down when the baby's born.
- Get on with the in-laws, do you, Jamie?
- Yeah, I do, as it goes.
- Yeah, you get on with Dad, don't you?
- We have a nice chat from time to time.
- Do you?
- That's more than we ever do.
Does it seem funny,
your little sister having a baby?
- Yeah, it is a bit weird.
- No, it's perfectly natural.
- I'm an auntie.
- Oh, yeah?
- Got two nieces. My brothers' kids.
- They're lovely.
- Yeah, well, they're all right.
- Oh, he's kicking.
Oh, yeah, that's amazing. Hello,
little man in there. It's your auntie speaking.
There's your other auntie here, Auntie Suzy.
Does she want a word?
- What are you going to call it?
- Yeah, have you chosen a name yet?
- We weren't going to say, were we?
- We're not telling anyone yet.
- Go on, your secret's safe with us.
- No, it's bad luck.
It's Nathan.
Oops. It's lovely.
- Nathan?
- Yeah.
- It's a lovely name, Helen.
- Is there a Nathan in the family?
- No.
- No, just feels right to us.
Well, that's the important thing.
- Nathan Lightfoot.
- Yes, Suzy, Nathan Lightfoot.
Nathan Lightfoot Esquire.
- It's boring.
- Take no notice of her.
- I'm not.
- Cheers. Cheers, Nathan.
- Let me get you another top up. Suzy?
- Oh, yeah, thanks, Jamie.
I know, let's have a go on your PlayStation,
Jamie.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I'll start it up.
- No, Jamie.
- Zoe's favourite, isn't it?
- Yeah, I can't get enough.
- What games you got?
- Sonic The Hedgehog, Splinter Cell.
- Cool.
- We can't start with that now.
- Why not?
- It's too late.
Is it? What's the time?
- Oh, five minutes.
- No.
- Come on, let's play.
- Jamie, I said leave it.
- All right, lovely.
- Sit down.
Oh, for fuck sake.
Bane of my life, PlayStations.
- Oh, you got one?
- No, the kids at school.
They're like that under the desks, aren't they?
- I always confiscate them in my class.
- Do you?
- What a surprise.
- They must love that.
- Well, maybe in the morning, eh?
- Yeah, before we go for a walk.
It's incredible to think
I'm going to get even bigger.
- Only 10 more weeks.
- Exciting, strap yourself in.
Doesn't it make you both feel
a little bit broody, you girls?
- No, actually. How about you, Zoe?
- Afraid not. With all due respect.
You want a baby, though, don't you, Poppy?
- No, thanks. I've just had a kebab.
- I didn't mean that. Eventually.
Maybe. Who knows?
At 35, you're considered a high-risk mum.
- Give me a chance, I've just turned 30.
- It's only five years away.
- You've got to make plans.
- A five-year plan? Like Stalin?
- When are you getting on the property ladder?
- I need a step up first.
- You got to get yourself a mortgage.
- We don't want the hassle.
- You need to invest your savings.
- I just stuff mine under the mattress.
- Have you got a pension yet?
- You got to be joking.
- Have you got a pension?
- We've both got pensions, haven't we?
- Oh, yeah.
- Great. Where are your Zimmer frames?
- You've got to take life seriously.
- Have I?
You can't get drunk every night, partying,
however much fun it is.
I don't get drunk every night. Do we?
- No, she's an adult now, your big sister.
- Unfortunately.
- You have to take responsibility, Poppy.
- OK, take it easy.
I am taking it easy.
I just want you to be happy, that's all.
I am happy.
- I don't think you are.
- I am.
I love my life. Yeah, it can be tough at times.
That's part of it, isn't it?
I've got a great job, brilliant kids, lovely flat.
I've got her to look at.
I've got amazing friends. I love my freedom.
I'm a lucky lady, I know that.
- All right, no need to rub it in.
- What am I rubbing in?
- I know what you're saying.
- What?
- You think I've taken the easy option.
- Hey.
Hang on, Helen. She didn't say that.
- It's what she meant.
- No, you're insecure about your life.
- All right, Suze.
- That's not true.
- Why are you trying to control everyone?
- I'm not. I'm not.
- Whatever. You're boring me.
- Leave it out.
Why are you all attacking me? It's not fair.
- No-one's attacking you, Helen.
- They're not attacking you, Hel.
- Blimey.
- It's pathetic.
- Suzy!
- Sorry.
- She'll be all right in a minute.
- Yeah.
It's hormones.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- Do you want to play a game, Jamie?
- Yeah, yeah.
No, best leave it till the morning.
I think we should all go to bed, it's getting late.
All right, then.
Jamie, go upstairs
and get the bedding for Suzy.
- You're looking tired, Suzy.
- She always looks like that.
It's just my face.
Thanks for the barbecue, Helen. Jamie.
- Anytime.
- It was gorgeous.
Thanks.
We'll go for a walk by the sea tomorrow.
It'll be lovely.
Be nice.
SUZY: Move your arse.
Flap, flap, flap!
Careful, Poppy.
I'm worried about you in those shoes.
- Don't worry. They're not too high.
- Poppy, come off the wall.
Give us a piggy back?
Suzy, don't do that. Don't. Stop it.
You should have told me,
I wouldn't have got on your back.
I'm all right. How are you? Good weekend?
Oh, heavy night last night, was it?
That's what I like to hear. Good boy.
So, do you fancy going out sometime, then?
How's Friday looking for you?
Think you can squeeze me in?
Oh, go on, then. I don't drink.
But...
Yeah, maybe just the one.
Yeah, something like that.
All right, then.
See you then, then, then, then, then.
All right. See you, sailor. Bye.
Scott!
Suzy, wind your sister's window up.
What was that all about, then?
Search me.
Bit weird.
Isn't it just?
- Gives me the creeps, to be honest.
- Yeah.
So, what are we doing for tea, then?
- Takeaway. What do you reckon?
SUZY: Chinese?
Oh, hello, look who's here. Little piglet.
- Are you paying?
- No.
- Course she's not.
- Don't worry, we'll take care of it.
- Mum and Dad.
- Which one am I?
- Dad, of course.
- I hate being Dad.
- You love it.
- Oh, get off, Poppy.
It's a beautiful sky.
There you go.
Thanks.
So where were we?
What brings you here?
- I met a girl.
- Oh, very nice.
- Yeah.
- What's she like, then?
- I can't talk about it.
- Why not?
- It's a secret.
- I'm good with secrets.
- It's between me and her, though.
- Oh, fair enough. I won't pry.
- Who is she?
- I couldn't possibly.
Trust me.
She's a teacher.
- Is she?
- She's gorgeous.
Oh... I hate her already.
Haven't you got lovely eyes?
- Thanks.
- Beautiful colour.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Picked them myself.
- Did you?
- Yeah.
- Where from?
- Down the market.
- You're joking me?
- No.
I'd say you got yourself a bargain there.
- You've got one as well.
- Have I? Just the one? Which one?
- That one.
- This one?
- Particularly lovely, is he?
- He is.
But don't upset the other one.
- No, she's all right.
- Is she?
- Yeah, we've had a chat about it.
- Oh, good.
Yeah, she's over the worst now.
Yeah, anyway she's got other talents.
- Has she?
- Yeah.
- What are they?
- So many.
- She can juggle.
- Obviously.
Yeah, goes without saying.
She can wink on demand.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah.
- Let's see.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- It's pretty spooky.
- Go on.
- OK, are you ready?
Yeah.
She is good!
- This one tries to join in.
- Don't let him.
I won't. Anyway, he's lovely, so...
- Well, she's lovely, too.
- Don't try and claw your way out of it.
- Sorry.
- It's all right.
- Cheers.
Again.
This is nice.
It is nice.
Here we are.
Wow.
Welcome to my humble abode.
Thank you.
(Poppy giggles)
- Aren't you high up?
- Yeah.
Yeah. What's it like up there?
Hm. It's OK.
That's better.
- I think you must be too hot.
- Yeah, it does feel hot.
Yeah, I thought so.
Usually right.
- Though it's not really my job.
- No, you're very good at it.
I know. (Giggles)
Hidden talents.
Oh, wow.
Now, that's what I call a bargain.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
(Bangles jangle)
- One, two, three.
(Poppy giggles)
- I'm a bit hot, too.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
- Maybe this'll help.
- I think you might be right.
- What about if this...
- Oh, yeah, and that one. Go on, then.
OK.
- Ooh, I quite like it like that.
- (Chuckles)
- Oh!
- Lovely.
(Both laugh)
- What's it like in there?
- Oh, not bad.
I'll go and make that tea.
Great.
Going to be late for my lesson.
Hey-ho. There you go.
- I'll give you a lift.
- Will you?
- Yeah.
- Oh!
- Means I keep you for longer.
- Thank you very much.
It's OK.
- So when you coming back to school?
- Oh. Next week.
- I'll see how things go with his mum.
- Yeah, he'll be all right.
He'll be fine.
Hello.
Hi.
Are you happy... in your life?
That's a big question.
Isn't it just?
- So, you play football, then?
- Yeah, five-a-side every week.
- Right. Is that indoors or outdoors?
- No, outdoors.
- Oh, here she is.
- Made it. Just.
- Why aren't you wearing any jewellery?
- Oh, it's that kind of day.
So, you doing anything tonight?
Yeah, it's a mate's 30th.
We're all meeting in a bar.
- Great.
- What are you two up to?
- Oh, cinema.
- Yeah, see a film.
- Popcorn...
- Sit in the dark, hold hands.
Yeah, no necking.
She's only saying that cos you're here.
Normally I'm all over her like a rash.
- I don't blame you.
- He's a right smoothie.
- Isn't he just?
- (Doorbell)
- Here he is.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, Zoe.
- Yeah, whatever.
- Have a good time tonight.
(Poppy laughs)
POPPY: Come on, you.
Hiya, Scott. This is Tim.
He's coming with us today.
- Just joking.
- Hi.
- Ooh, can't win them all.
- Apparently not.
- See you later.
- I'll call you.
- Will you?
- Yeah.
Good.
What happened on Sunday, Scott?
You should've stopped to say hello.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I was in Stevenage on Sunday.
Stevenage? Funny, you must have a twin.
I was there all day. I was looking after
my mum. My aunt's dying.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- It's all right.
- Don't believe you, Scott.
- It's up to you, I was there till midnight.
Don't think so, gigolo.
(Engine starts)
Concentrate, Poppy.
Concentrate. Watch what I'm doing.
Now I'm going to indicate. I keep in lane.
In a roundabout, you keep in lane.
OK? You keep in lane, all right?
You take responsibility for other drivers
and for yourself and you keep in lane, OK?
This is a roundabout. Concentrate,
pay attention. Good. Thank you.
Are you... Was that a request
or was that a demand?
Did he bully me then? Did he just shove in then?
- Or did he ask?
- Did he?
No, he didn't ask.
You see what roundabouts do?
Roundabouts, if you keep in lane
and you keep going, you'll be fine.
You're following rules and keeping
everything the way it should be.
Everything in check.
But if you get selfish and if you
step out of it, then it goes wrong.
And it gets dangerous.
Do you see what I mean?
- Waa-aaah...
- (Car horn blares)
I'm not waiting for somebody
who can't keep in lane on a roundabout.
I'm not waiting.
Everywhere you see, look at the cameras.
Everywhere you go, they're watching you.
They're seeing you. They're watching.
Everywhere you go.
Look at this place, it stinks.
Come on. What are you waiting for?
- All right.
- Jesus Christ! Look, another camera...
Speed camera. Why do you need them?
There's two guys at the back of the road
selling drugs
and you have a speed camera.
Why do you need a speed camera?
You can wait.
- You can wait!
- Easy.
(Car horn)
Come on! Drive the car.
You're not driving a camel.
OK? This is not a bazaar.
We have rules in this country.
We have regulations. Keep to them.
Fucking morons!
(Tyres screech)
Check your mirrors, your seat,
make yourself comfortable.
- No, I don't think so.
- Seat belt on.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- What do you mean?
You are in no fit state to take this lesson.
I am the instructor. You are the pupil.
- You need to calm down.
- I am calm.
- You can't drive like this.
- You can't comment on my driving!
I think I can when you're putting yourself
in danger, putting me in danger,
- and putting other people in danger.
- It's them.
That's bullshit. It's all bullshit.
That's it, I don't want it.
- You want this lesson to stop?
- Yes, I do.
I don't want you to teach me any more. I'm sorry.
OK. Fantastic. Get in the passenger seat
and I'll drive you home.
No, I don't think so. I'm driving.
- No, you're not.
- I am.
Poppy, if this isn't a lesson, you can't drive.
You're not driving anywhere.
You got two choices,
either I drive you home or you walk.
I don't mind walking, but you can't drive this car.
- You can't stop me.
- Yes, I can.
- Poppy, give me the keys.
- No.
- Give me the keys to my car.
- No, I don't think so.
I'm going to ask you one more time.
Please give me the keys to my car.
- I'm sorry, I can't.
- Give me the fucking keys to my car,
- you fucking bitch!
- Get off me!
- Give me the... fuck...
- Get off me. Get off me!
- Give me the fucking...
- Get off me. You get away from me!
- Give me the fucking keys!
- You can't touch me, Scott.
- You can't touch me. You're out of order.
- Give me those fucking keys!
- You're out of order.
- Give me the...
I'm calling the police.
Do you want me to call the police?
Do you?
Right. So let's just calm down, shall we?
OK, we're disturbing the peace here.
I just want to get in my car and drive away.
- That's not going to happen.
- Jesus!
You're doing it again. You never give in
for fuck's sake, you fucking bitch!
- You need help.
- Don't patronise me.
- I'm not patronising you.
- Yes, you are always patronising me.
This is what you always wanted,
what you set out to achieve.
This is the game you play.
You prodded me. You poked me.
You stroked me. You teased me.
You flirted with me. You sucked me in.
You wore your high-heel boots,
your short skirt, your low-cut top
and you flashed your tits, you tossed your hair.
You played with the gear stick. You lied to me!
This is all about you.
The world has to revolve around you.
I'm a driving instructor.
I just wanted to do my job.
You had no intention of learning how to drive.
You had one thing in mind.
To reel me in. And why?
Because you have to be adored.
You've got to be wanted. And you drink it in.
And you leave me with a spring in your step
and you go off and you fuck your boyfriend
and you fuck your girlfriend.
And you all drive around
in that stupid, little yellow car.
Scott...
Come on, now.
I just want to go home.
I'm sure you do.
Don't we all, eh?
Tell you what.
Why don't we have a talk about it?
We'll sit in the car.
We'll have a chat, OK?
All right?
And then I'll give you your keys.
I'm sorry if I upset you, Scott.
I wish I could make you happy.
I was happy.
OK.
And I was in Stevenage last Sunday.
- Sure.
- You can ask my mum.
So, same time next week?
I'm sorry, Scott.
There you go.
I'll just get my bag, all right?
I'm a good driving instructor.
Yeah, I know you are.
Take care, Scott.
Was that your boyfriend?
Before?
Was it?
(Starts engine)
I think I should give up smoking.
That's a good idea.
What can I give up?
You could give up being too nice.
Seriously, you can't make everyone happy.
There's no harm in trying, though, is there?
Bring a smile to the world.
- Come on, Poppy.
- I know. I know.
I still think we should call the police.
No, that's not going to help him, is it?
I don't know.
- You know what?
- What?
- We're lucky, aren't we?
- Yeah, we are.
Well... well, you make your own luck in life,
don't you?
Well, some of us do.
Some of us miss the boat completely.
It's hard work being a grown-up, isn't it?
Yeah, it is. It's a long trip.
Yeah, tell me when we get there.
Don't worry, I'll let you know.
You keep on rowing and I'll keep on smiling.
Hm. Are we there yet?
We've got a hell of a way to go.
POPPY: We're getting good at this, aren't we?
Nothing to it.
(Mobile rings)
POPPY: Hello, you. Missing me already?
Oh...
That's nice to hear.
A nightmare. Yeah.
I'm still alive... just.
Well... it's a long story.
I'm on the lake, with Zoe.
(Laughs) Yeah.
The bathroom flooded, yeah.
It's all right now. We've found a boat.
(Laughs) You're funny.
No. (Laughs)
(Poppy continues laughing)
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org