Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Keep the change
- What are you waiting on?
- Four cappuccinos
- Four cappuccinos. Let's go.
- There you go
- Thanks.
- l've got a break
- You can't smoke in here.
Hey, buddy, you forgot your change.
- Makes the world go round
- What's that?
Gold.
Some people say love.
They're right too. lt is love.
Love of gold.
Hold on.
Thank God you're there
There's been an explosion.
Pick up the phone and dial 911.
l'm burnt.
''18.36.7. Pound.''
What are you doing?
Find the security tape!
Enough.
Hey, thanks.
Hey, how'd it go?
Finest kind.
- Where'd you get that?
- Here you go.
- You fixed it
- l made a new one.
- You're a pretty smart fella
- Not that smart.
- How'd you figure it out?
- l imagined someone smarter than me.
Then l tried to think
''What would he do?''
- That's one hell of a boat
- Sign up, l'll build you one.
- l wanna buy that one
- Well, that's my boat.
Come up with a down payment
and l'll have it in 18 months.
- We're good at this conversation
- Then close the deal.
- There you go
- What is it?
Open it up. lt's yours.
lt's shaped like an arrow
Freccia means arrow.
- So you told me
- lt looks like gold.
- That's because l gilded it
- Why?
l wanted to sell you a boat.
Good try, though
l want that boat.
Sell me that boat, and l'll come
down with a laundry bag of cash.
Take the money, take your little girl
cruise down to a tropic isle.
- How will you get the cash?
- Don't be coy.
You know who l am. Sell me your boat
you'll be under my wing.
That's my private number.
l can't do it. l'm working on
your boat. Take mine out.
Does that girl go with it?
Call me, l'll have five guys here
Monday laying out the hull.
You decide to sell me your boat...
...let's do something, huh?
- l'd have Ked to build him that boat
- Walk away from it.
Well, let's start getting
the gear on board.
- You got the charts?
- Oh, yeah.
Why so many?
Wouldn't want somebody to look
at them and follow us.
- How'd l get so lucky?
- You're the law west of the Pecos.
Yeah, l used to be
the law west of the Pecos.
Now l'm cashing out.
- You got your picture took
- ls that why l'm cashing out?
lf you say it, it's right.
You're the brass ring, babe.
Glad you Like me.
Off you go.
See you tonight.
Stay in the shadows.
Everyone's gonna be looking there.
- Where's the place to be?
- Place to be is in the sun.
Beautiful.
Just gorgeous.
Nobody gets the goods like you.
Anybody can get the goods
The hard part's getting away.
Plan a good getaway
you can steal Ebbets Field.
- Ebbets Field is gone
- What'd l tell you?
My nephew, Jimmy Silk.
Yep, that's who he is.
- He don't say hello?
- He must have things on his mind.
Anything you want while you're here?
Something for that pretty lady?
- What's she see in you anyway?
- l'm resilient.
- So's Gumby
- l got a better profile.
You're gonna leave that
down south in Argentina.
- How you doing, Bobby?
- l think you're looking at it.
You go down south, sit in the sun.
Pull down your bathing suit
stick your ass out at the world.
You think the world's ready for that?
The other thing
We got the go-ahead.
We got a firm date on the Swiss thing.
l'm burnt. They got my picture.
Of you in drag
with your war paint on.
lt's a blessing
lt's time to check out.
What do we got?
- lt's higher than the estimate
- Half is yours.
We're on for the Swiss thing.
Why did he tell me that half is mine?
l know half of it's mine
Me and my crew got it.
l went in hock
and set it up on your say-so.
Let's review. You let me
walk in there with my crew...
...and now you're stiffing me?
- lf it was me..
- Yeah. l owe my crew.
l gotta get out of town
l gotta go.
- Should have shot the girl
- Should have been there.
This Swiss thing. lf l was
a publisher, l'd publish the plans.
Why don't you?
lf l was a publisher. But l'm a thief
so l have to do that thing.
Give me our cut
We'll do the Swiss job.
You know that's bullshit
You're going traveling.
You gonna play me for a sucker?
l give you the money and you're gone.
The job's set up, you understand?
We did the job, my partners and me.
Hey, fuck you and fuck your partners.
l'm your partner. Without me
you've got, what? Little Lambsy Divy.
- l bankroll this job on your say-so
- l drove here, l didn't take the bus.
- Fuck you, go back to prison
- What'd l tell you?
l don't think so.
- Guess again
- You stay the fuck down.
Want to play OK Corral?
Wanna dress up and play?
ls that the thing?
ls that it?
Give me that fucking bag!
Your weight and your fate right here.
- Bag's empty, Bobby
- What?
The bag is empty.
Put the bag down, it's empty.
Want me to pull up a chair
while you rape me?
lf you'd pause in your
headstrong progress...
Joe, l'm in hock for all the toys.
All the toys you said go out
and buy. Two trucks, the plane.
- You said spend the money
- What do you want?
l want you to do the other thing.
You screwed me
Now my face is on a cereal box.
You got no money!
You're burnt and busted.
What the fuck does it take
to get you to do the other thing?
Excuse me, Mr. Bergman
asked you a question.
Excuse me
my uncle asked you a question.
- Fuck your uncle
- Fuck my uncle? You're the help.
Yeah, l'm the help, motherfucker
Why'd the chicken cross the road?
Because the road crossed the chicken.
- Walk away
- Hey, you! Hold on!
Situation is pristine.
Cut him off.
l didn't see him.
Oh, my God!
How is he?
lt's his road game.
- Your man does good work
- That's why l use him.
Yeah, these will pass anywhere.
Why don't you take advantage of it?
No.
l need somebody to throw me
in the briar patch.
Yeah, give the gentleman a call.
- l need some walking-around money
- That's reasonable.
And l'm gonna need my men's share
on the lastjob.
- Give it to me
- Now?
You got it in your pocket.
You're ahead of me every turn.
Stunning.
The plan holds
you get your shipment on the 14th.
The plan has changed
We split it 50/50 on the site.
50/50.
So be it.
- Now what's your surprise?
- My boy comes with you on the job.
- He's got terrible manners
- Which of us is perfect?
So be it.
Wait a sec. lf it's about
your wife, why didn't you...?
Will you wait? lf the whole thing
is about your wife...?
You know what?
The hell with it!
Not a happy camper, huh?
l'm not a camper at all, stud
Pour it.
See anything you like?
l'm busy.
- Pour it!
- Hope you're not driving.
l hope l am, and l run into
some fucked abutment.
- Take me off, will you?
- That'll rot your stomach lining.
Yeah, but l get to drink it first.
- That's all l need
- What?
There goes my job
You see his badge?
Do you know where that guy is from?
And he caught me drinking on shift.
End of a perfect day.
- That's Betty Croft
- What's her problem?
- She's a drunk
- She's a drunk.
You bet she is.
- Why is she important?
- She gets us in the door.
She gets us in the door, how?
l want you to leave the uniforms
on the porch 3 or 4 days.
Get the dry-cleaning smell
out of them.
When we do the switch, the highway...
- Nobody can hear
- lf you don't say it.
l'm as quiet as
an ant pissing on cotton.
l don't want you as quiet as that ant.
l want you as quiet as an ant not
even thinking about pissing on cotton.
Hello. l gotta report
a breakdown here.
l got one of your rentals
l need a tow truck.
Oh, come on, don't tell me that.
- Yeah, all right
- What's the story on your pal?
He was born, he suffered, he died.
- Can he do the thing?
- He was doing it before you were born.
See, that's what troubles me.
Maybe you want to pray about it?
- No, l'm not a religious man
- That's a shame.
- How's the leg?
- Never better.
- How long has he been with that girl?
- Who?
- His wife
- How long is a Chinaman's name?
How long is a Chinaman's name?
You ever notice that?
Got the uniforms?
Yeah, l got them
l got them all aired out.
- Rental trucks?
- Yeah.
What do we got?
Gotta redo some of these figures.
- l gotta start from scratch
- Worked out on the plan. Why now?
When things start to go sour
someone's gonna be pissing.
Looking to shoot somebody
l want an alternate idea.
Why should it go sour?
- You timing the wrecker?
- Yeah.
Why should it go sour?
Was that such a stupid question?
You ever cheat on a woman? Something
stand her up, step out on her?
What?
- Ever do that?
- Yeah.
- Did you have an excuse?
What if she didn't ask?
Was your alibi a waste of time?
ls he gonna hold up?
He's only gotta hold it together
till the thing.
- Okay. All right
- ls he backing up?
Here he comes.
Ain't that pretty.
Don't start the car
lt's just a routine stop.
Don't start the car.
Good morning.
- Can l see some identification?
- Good of you to come.
You were supposed
to be here an hour ago.
Just forget about this.
lt's no big deal. But we're
out here without protection.
- Who'd you talk to?
- lt burns my butt!
- l understand
- We're out working for the city!
- Who did you talk to?
- l know it's not your fault.
Who did you talk to?
Who did you talk to, sir?
- Keep it together
- Can he cool the guy out?
- Pretend to write in your clipboard
- ls he gonna be cool?
My motherfucker's so cool
when he goes to bed, sheep count him.
Appreciate that
Why are you mad at him?
He's right. He's right
Beg your pardon.
- Get off
- Get in the car.
- Get back in the car
- You know....
Give Pinky the piece
Put your hands on the wheel.
And keep them there
Just keep it right there.
We got it taken care of
lt's all right.
- Thanks so much
- All right.
Chuck! You got a phone call
right here.
Excuse me.
lt's Mr. Smith at the office.
- Yeah. Yeah
- Thank you, officer.
Well, it's one of those days
Got it.
- You son of a bitch
- Oh, that was real good.
You fucking lame! Leave me dead
and the crew on the road.
- l saw..
- You fucking cowboy!
- Tell me why don't l kill him?
- How about we do?
l'll put you down
Like the dog you are.
- You gonna shoot your way to stardom?
- l only...
l don't want you
to do anything unless...
We hit the city, you burn the car.
- l'll take the..
- No, you do it!
Car's filthy. Whole fucking job's
in the car. You do it, Pinky!
Get me the fuck out of here.
Listen, it's very simple
lt's several elements.
You got the tow truck
You got the roadblock.
l can do it, okay? l know the job
l got the job cold.
You can't cut me loose.
Please, guys. We got a deal here!
Why should we bet on you?
Young, dumb, full of cum.
Leave me bleeding on the side
of the road. ''He's just impetuous''.
Joe, security truck to the garage
We beat the tow truck...
What's so fucking funny?
You got no job without me!
You got nothing without this job.
You want to go down south?
You want to go broke?
Without me, you got nothing
You need the job. You need me!
- You can't take him
- Okay, l got loose, but...
You cannot take this lame
on the job, Joe!
Can we just go calm here
for a minute?
Go calm?
So, what happened to you now?
l'll tell you what happened to me.
l need a fucking minute
to make a decision.
- Fine
- Joe, can l talk to you?
- What the hell is it?
- They found the car.
- What car?
- The station wagon. The cops found it.
How could they find it?
l told you to ditch the car.
l stopped off to see my niece.
- Did you wipe it down?
- You saw your niece?
Did you wipe it down?
- l left my clipboard in the car
- What does this do to the job?
- You left your clipboard?
- My leg was troubling me.
- The job is on the clipboard
- What about the job?
- The job's on the clipboard!
- Job stands.
- Are you crazy?
- The job stands?
- The job is bust. This place is burnt
- What does this mean?
Job stands.
You're out of your fucking mind
We can't sink with the job!
Tell you what
You want to run the show?
lt's fun to play pretend
Come on!
You're gonna roll over
for these guys?
- l gotta go away
- You took this lame on the job.
Can't leave with nothing.
You're drawing dead
You want a fucking telegram?
The job is dead.
You put your man in the street
you lamed up the job.
- Wait, wait, wait. Bobby!
- l can't sink with the job!
Wait a second. Wait a second!
Baby, you got old.
l'm gone, l'm out
That's it.
l don't see how
they could have found the car.
Fuck the car, Pink!
You're a stupid lame
l'm out of here.
- l gotta get on with my life
- Bobby, wait!
- Fran, what are you doing?
- Place is burnt.
Hold it, hold it.
For chrissake!
You gotta move your car.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
What's going on?
What's the shot?
You got someplace to go? Some shade?
You best get to it
And move your car. l gotta go.
Shit, where's my piece?
- l'll get it to you later
- Now.
What am l telling you?
Just follow me!
Bobby, hold on! Just a minute!
For God's sake!
Walking away, Bobby?
You walking out on me?
Are you walking out on me
you weak son of a bitch?
Joe, l'm sorry.
Gonna get in your car?
After all this time!
What the hell?
Come back here, you fucking coward!
You're a fucking coward!
Go on, get the fuck out of here!
Little prick.
- And there they go!
- That's right.
You get gone too.
- l would've loved to do the Swiss job
- lt's a good plan.
Never Ked the Swiss
Their clocks...
...two guys come out with hammers
and hit each other.
What kind of sick mentality is that?
You take care, pally.
Get Bobby's share to him.
- What'll you do for cash?
- We're taking down the boat guy.
You're gonna take his cash?
- l'm selling him my boat
- And then?
Then we'll take my boat back.
- Well, baby, then aloha
- See you later, Pinky.
lt's a shame we didn't get to do
the Swiss job. lt's a beautiful plan.
- Cute
- Cute as a pail of kittens.
- Say goodbye to your niece for me
- You bet, pal.
You might want to put that out, sir.
- Put it out. Put the cigar out
- l told him.
We got a fuel leak
trying to put your cleat in.
- Your arrow cleat
- Her idea.
- To put your stamp on it
- Damned if l didn't cut the fuel line.
l wanted to take her out tonight.
l know you did, sir
and l'm sorry as hell.
l'm gonna work all night and
l'll have it ready for sunup, okay?
All right, l want to re-ballast her.
Put her a bit by the stern.
l have the change of title, coast
guard certification and bill of sale.
Let me show you something pretty.
That's a lot of cash
to be carrying around.
- l brought a friend
- Nice friend to have for a rainy day.
Yes, sir.
- l'm sorry about that leak
- Forget about it.
We got forms, certifications....
Fran.
- Would you Like a cup of coffee?
- Yeah.
l want you to do something for me
Look at this.
l did this myself
You're gonna love it.
This is what l want for a figurehead.
Robin Hood
What do you think?
l Like it because
it puts a twist on my name.
Freccia is ltalian for ''arrow''
so you see the thing?
To personalize the boat.
Robin Hood, robbing from the rich
but who wants to rob from the poor?
Let's see. Bill of sale.
We got certificate of title.
1400 hours on the engine.
My people will contact you
Here's what we're thinking...
Easy!
Wait, wait, wait! Hold on!
Are you alone? Are you alone?
Are you alone?
- What the fuck are you doing here?
- l left my copy of the plans.
Hey, hold on.
Call Freccia.
You said the joint was burnt
l don't understand.
- l didn't want..
- To what?
l'm looking out for you two.
He won't answer.
What does she see in you?
You must be hung Like man-of-war.
You want to play the dozens?
Here we go.
There was an error at the hospital
You died at birth.
Cat got your tongue?
Don't you want to play?
Joe, leave him.
You going somewhere?
What are you
the social service lady?
- Going somewhere?
- Taking the baby back?
You can't run
You gotta do the job.
You know that you got to
You know you do.
Can you shoot me and walk away?
They'll hunt you down.
- Shoot him
- l can't go down there with nothing!
Well...
...that's the thing.
- What'll you do?
- Out!
And what? You owe them money
Think you can just sail away?
- They'll never let you walk away
- Get out!
What are we gonna do?
That's what everybody wants to know.
How do we get the gold home?
What's the difference?
They'll never trust you.
They need me to do the job.
How can they trust you
not to walk over?
- The kid came back?
- Yeah.
- All right. Let's start again
- Why'd the kid come back?
Listen.
He don't come back
you're on some island.
- l got an idea
- You should've left him on the road.
You shouldn't have left him
with the plans!
What plans?
He forgot his cheat sheet
That's why he came back.
He didn't forget it
because l got it right here!
What, am l gonna leave my papers
in the hands of some fucking lame?
- That's why he came back
- He came for me.
What?
He came back to make sure l was okay.
- He came back for you?
- That's right.
l know how to get the gold.
- Suit up
- Sure you want to do that?
- She's the go-getter
- Tell me what you want me to go get.
l need you to suit up
ls that all right?
You say it, it's right.
All right.
- We'll put the job off for a month
- For a month?
l need dates for next month's shipment
and the name of a freight forwarder.
Freight forwarder
and a customs broker.
- Good
- Where are you going with this?
You just listen.
We're gonna stand this thing
on its head.
Are you fucking with me?
Or are you done fucking with me?
l've financialized the problem, and
you're more trouble than you're worth.
The girl says you'll do it
You said that before.
Why now?
What is it, all of a sudden?
Everybody needs money
That's why they call it ''money''.
Let me add this sweetener.
Do the fucking job
or l'll turn you over.
l'll drop a Roosevelt dime on you
Finita la Commedia.
ls that strict, you fucking vonce?
Sorry to use such language
in front of a woman...
...were it not for who
l'd waste your fucking ass.
lf you say you'll do the job, do it
No more charades.
Save the bold moves
for the brilliant players.
- Sorry for the language
- How generous.
And fuck you too! Save the bullshit
He wants the job.
ls that a question?
You came begging to me, doxy
l didn't come to you.
He'll do the job next month
He needs a month.
- ls that the thing?
- ls that what l just told you?
- Ain't you a piece of work
- l came from China in a matchbox.
Thank you.
Fill up her drink
she seems to enjoy it.
What do you think?
- He's scared
- He's never scared.
- He's getting old
- She said that?
He's broke, he's tired
She says he wants to play ball.
Why should we believe her?
Why did he send her?
- She came to me
- To you?
- He put her up to it
- She came to me on her own.
Yeah, but as rational men
don't we have to doubt her?
She thinks he's weak
She's scared, she's sincere.
Let me put a question to you:
lf you had the job
how would you test her sincerity?
Okay, we're all on one team
all arrayed against a common enemy?
Thanks for coming
l'm going to bed.
- l'll see you back
- l'm all right.
- You're all right now
- Am l?
You just need somebody to lean on.
- Adrenaline gives you the shakes
- l'm okay.
l'm just saying
adrenaline gives people the shakes.
Some mistake it for cowardice
You could pray.
l'm not a religious man.
- There's nothing wrong with prayer
- Think so?
l knew this trooper who always
carried a Bible next to his heart.
- lt stopped a bullet
- No shit?
Hand to God, it stopped a bullet
Would've ruined his heart.
Had he had another Bible in front
of his face, he'd be alive today.
- What time you got?
- 5:18.
Make the call.
Hello? l got one of your rental
trucks. The engine quit on me.
- Nobody lives forever
- Frank Sinatra gave it a shot.
You'll do.
Good morning.
lt's the acid.
lt isn't the acid, it's the asphalt
lt's making me sick.
How can they work in that
all day long?
- Got any Rolaids?
- Want an Alka Seltzer?
- Doctor said not to drink
- You shouldn't then.
Same old story everywhere you go.
You know....
Oh, no.
- Do l know you?
- No. Please, please.
- What?
- Don't fire me. Please.
- What do you mean?
- Don't fire me.
l saw you in the bar
You're with the FAA.
Miss Croft, you're drinking
on the job. You're done.
l got two kids at home
Please, mister.
Give me your keys.
Mister, l need a break
l'm begging you.
l swear to you on my life that
l will never take another drink.
Don't fire me.
Did you ever ask anybody
for a break?
Do you have any kids?
Oh, Christ.
ln about three minutes
l'll be conducting a security check.
l'll be passing through your station
l will be, quote, armed.
l will have a tool kit...
...in which is hidden
three dangerous items.
lt's a test of
the personnel under you.
lf you tip them off
l'll have yourjob.
l wouldn't.
Go back to your station.
- l will
- Give me your keys.
Your alcohol.
- You will go into the program
- l will.
Thank you!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org