Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Ready to go faster?
All right. No, no, no!
You're gonna slide off.
Oh!
You all right?
- Are you sliding?
- Yes.
No, if you're sliding,
I'm going to stop.
- No, no, no.
- You okay? Okay.
More?
Yes!
That's funny.
I could've sworn
I saw a little girl
by the name
of Emily come in here.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are...
Could she be hiding
in the closet?
I wonder where she could be.
Hmm...
Maybe my eyes
have deceived me.
I'm invisible, Mommy.
Well, if you're invisible...
...then how could I... do this?!
Did you know where I was?
Not a clue.
You want AleX?
What is it?
I love you more
than anything else in the world.
You know that, don't you?
I love you, too.
Good night, sweetheart.
Make the face.
Please.
- Now, go to sleep.
- Okay.
Mommy!
Sorry.
Good night.
You coming to bed?
In a little while.
Something you want to talk about?
Some things are beyond therapy, David.
Honey?
I should've seen it coming.
All the signs were there.
The ones closest to you
are the hardest to judge.
No, but I...
I could've prevented it.
David, it's not your fault.
How long have
we known each other?
Trust me when I tell you this.
As difficult
as it may seem, you're...
you're gonna have to try
and start over.
We're gonna move.
Upstate.
The country.
That's not eXactly what
I meant by "starting over. "
What about Emily?
This is a traumatic time for her.
I think it's important she stays
here and works through this.
No, here, she's
flooded with memories.
I need to eXpose her
to a new environment,
new things to do...
She'd be losing another person
she depends on.
It's only an hour away.
And... you're always welcome
to come and see her.
And right now, I need to do
what's right for Emily.
I need to be
a full-time dad.
I have a surprise for you.
When I was your age,
my mom gave me one just like that.
And whenever I was feeling sad,
I would open the lid,
and all my sorrows went away.
Do you like it?
Give me a hug.
You're going to like it there.
All right, let's go.
¢Ü¢Ü CHI LD
¢Ü¢Ü
Come on.
Let's take a look.
Right on time.
Dr. Callaway...
Mr. Haskins.
Hello.
This is Sheriff Hafferty.
Sheriff.
He routinely checks
on the houses up here
to make sure things
run smoothly.
I see. Well, this is
my daughter, Emily.
This is Sheriff Hafferty.
Emily.
How are you?
This is Mr. Haskins.
He found us the house.
Well, hello there, Emily.
Think your dad did a good job
picking the house?
She's still deciding.
Well, she sure is pretty.
Thank you.
As I mentioned,
Woodland Estates
is mainly
a summer community.
May be a little quiet
up here till then.
Hope that's not a problem.
- Not at all.
- Great.
Let me show you
around the back.
You ever spent
much time in the country?
Not much.
I used to camp
when I was little,
but I was always scared
of the woods.
Nothing to be scared of
in these woods.
Picked a nice spot.
Biggest house on the lake.
Sheriff, if you'd like
to do the honors;
let Dr. Callaway
into his new home.
Figure out which key...
Did you see where
my daughter went?
Emily!
Honey?
You okay?
Come on.
Let's go back.
Mr. Haskins, Sheriff...
we'll take it from here.
Spaghetti and meatballs
is your favorite dish.
You're not hungry?
I'd like to go to bed now.
I'll come up
and kiss you good night.
Oh, that's funny.
I could have sworn
I saw a little girl
by the name of Emily
come in here.
I wonder...
where she's hiding.
Could she be...
could she be...
under the bed?!
No.
Could she be...
hiding...
Let's see, where
could she be hiding?
Could she be
hiding in the... closet!
Okay...
since it's the first night
in a new house,
I thought it would be a good
time to start a new diary.
Each day you
can write down
your feelings
and thoughts,
and then, one day,
you can look back
and see
how much they've changed.
Hmm?
I love you more than anything
else in the world, sweetheart.
You know that.
That's what Mommy said.
Hmm?
Before she killed herself.
Sweetheart,
she meant what she said.
And so do I.
You want me to put this
over here?
Okay.
All right.
Good night.
Good night, AleX.
Emily? Emily!
Em?
Emily?
Oh, there you are.
Come on, sweetheart.
We're going into town.
We have some errands to do.
Oh...
Hello.
Hi... Hi, there.
I- I'm Laura.
I live neXt door.
Oh, I'm David.
How are you?
Uh, here.
These are for you.
Oh, thank you very much.
My husband and I made
the preserves ourselves.
Oh, well...
I didn't even realize
anyone else lived up here.
Well, it does get pretty quiet
in the off season.
Oh, this is my
daughter, Emily.
Emily, say hello to Laura.
She's our neighbor.
Isn't she adorable?
You going to say hi?
Well, she gets a little shy
around new faces.
I understand.
It's going to be a real treat
having both of you here.
Oh, you're on your way out.
I won't keep you.
Um, if you need anything,
don't hesitate to stop by.
Same here.
And thank you
for all the preserves.
The peach and apricot preserves.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
I'm gonna put this inside.
Amy, don't swing so high.
I'm going
to tell your mom.
Would you listen to me?
Hi.
I have, uh,
a daughter the same age.
She's in the car.
Oh.
I'm Elizabeth.
Elizabeth Young.
Hi.
David Callaway.
- How are you?
- Good.
Nice to meet you.
Are you visiting?
Just moved up
from the city.
Oh, usually it's
the other way around.
I know.
She your kid?
Oh, no. No.
She's my sister's kid.
I'm the honorary baby-sitter.
Watch.
Amy, be careful.
Amy...
Oh...
- Amy.
- She all right?
Amy,Jesus,
are you all right?
That's very funny.
Oh, my God, you're
going to make me nuts,
you know that?
Is your daughter
this crazy?
Where's AleX?
I don't like her anymore.
Did I just hear
what I think I heard?
Are you mad, Daddy?
No, I'm not mad at all, honey.
I think it's great.
You do?
Yeah.
Good.
Because I have a new friend.
A new friend? Okay.
Let me guess.
Is it, um...
Veronica?
No.
Uh, is it, uh, Patty?
Is it...
He's not a doll.
He's...
Not a doll.
He.
Okay, well,
if he's not a doll,
then who is he?
He doesn't want me
to talk about him.
Doesn't want you
to talk about him?
No.
Well, what if I promise
to keep it a secret,
could you tell me then?
So, what's his name?
He told me to call him Charlie.
Charlie? Oh, that's
an interesting name.
Charlie.
When did you meet Charlie?
Today.
When we went to town?
It was before that.
Before that. Huh.
Is he... here right now?
I think he's sleeping.
Okay.
Well, in that case,
we better not wake him, hmm?
It's not unusual
for a traumatized child
to create imaginary friends.
I know, I just wish
she'd confide in me
instead of using fantasy.
Trauma causes pain.
Eventually the mind
will find a way to release it.
No kidding.
Don't forget: I'm the one
who taught you that stuff.
As a matter of fact, you did, yes.
Just have fun with her, David.
Play with her.
That's what she needs.
These are beginner rods.
Let's see... two rods,
$41.50 each...
Plus bait and tackle...
Sheriff.
You parked in a handicap zone.
Oh, I didn't even realize.
Could you give me a break?
I didn't realize.
Enjoy your day.
Eh, so much for
small town
hospitality, honey.
- Shut the door.
- We broke the law.
I know we broke the law.
Shut the door.
The Loch Ness Monster.
What?
You know what that is?
It's in Scotland.
This is a good spot, huh?
Honey, what are you doing?
You think that's a good idea?
Emily, we have bait.
See?
All right.
Did you have
a nice time today?
It was okay.
Just okay?
Mm...
Well, then, what could we
have done to make it better?
What if Charlie was there?
Would he have made it better?
He's a lot of fun.
Fun like how?
Fun like Mommy.
It's a little stuffy in here.
It's stuck.
It's okay, Daddy.
It just...
CROWD
... three, two, one...
Happy New Year!
Emily, why would you do this?
I didn't do it.
What do you mean,
you didn't do it?
There's nobody here but us.
It wasn't me.
This is your writing,
and these are your crayons, honey.
It's all right. Just tell me.
You don't have to lie to me.
I'm not lying.
Okay, well,
if you didn't do it,
then who did?
It was Charlie.
she thinks I"m responsible
for Alison's death.
It's Charlie
that holds you responsible.
Use him, David.
Use him to get through to her.
He's the key.
I- I have to go, I...
I think I found her
a real friend.
Really? That's great.
Call me if you need me, okay?
- Bye.
- Okay, bye.
Hi.
- Hi.
Hi, Amy.
Glad you came.
Em... we have guests.
Emily?
This is Elizabeth.
Hi, Emily.
Emily, this is Amy.
Hi.
Coffee-maker
has a mind of its own.
Oh, God...
Thank you.
So, is that your wife?
She passed away.
I'm sorry.
No matter how many times I say it,
it still sounds so strange.
Must be hard on Emily.
Have you ever been married?
Actually, I just got divorced.
I'm living with my sister
and her husband till I can
figure out my neXt move.
Best way to get over the past
is to start something new.
That's why we're here.
AMY
... baby, wrap it up
in toilet paper,
put it in the incubator.
What shall it be?
Oh! By the way,
this is Penelope.
Thanks.
You're gonna like it here.
It's a lot of fun.
Well, it's not always fun,
but there are lots
of fun things to do.
Oh...
She's beautiful.
What's her name?
Well, you don't talk much,
do you?
You shouldn't be here.
Why not?
You could get hurt.
- Oh, my God.
- Okay.
So, um... so,
you have my number.
I'll talk to you soon.
Okay...
I guess I should go.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Bye, Emily.
So... what'd you
think of Amy?
Did you like her?
I don't need any more friends.
Good, good.
There.
Perfect.
Hi.
Hey. Sorry.
I didn't mean to intrude.
Oh, uh...
I'm Steven.
Laura's husband from neXt door.
Oh, yeah. Hi.
It's David, right?
Yes, it's David.
Just wanted to say hi.
Nice to...
nice to meet you, Steven.
Figured, you know...
gonna be neighbors,
you might as well be neighborly, right?
Right.
Uh... well, you're gonna have
to eXcuse us, Steven.
We have a busy day
ahead of us.
Honey, come on.
Emily...
let's go.
Bye.
Listen, you need anything,
just give a shout, will you?
Okay. Thank you.
See you around.
David?
Yeah?
You're very lucky to have
such a beautiful daughter.
Thank you.
You remember
what I told you
about not talking
to strangers?
He's not a stranger.
What do you mean?
He's our neighbor.
As far as I'm concerned,
he's a stranger, honey.
Don't walk away
when I'm talking to you.
I'm telling you something.
I'm sorry, Daddy.
Weren't you finished?
No, I wasn't finished.
What I'm saying is,
it's very important
for you to listen
when I tell you something.
Okay.
Okay?
What are you doing,
sweetheart?
Nothing.
What's so funny?
Is Charlie here?
He just left.
Where'd he go?
Did you open that?
I thought you did.
I want to talk to Charlie.
What would you like
to talk about?
I'd like to talk to him
about all sorts of things.
Like what?
Like, uh... well,
what makes him happy...
what makes him sad...
So, what do you say?
You think you can introduce us?
I don't think that's going to work.
Why's that?
He doesn't like you very much.
Oh, why doesn't he
like me very much?
Does it have something
to do with Mommy?
Honey?
What does he tell you?
EMI LY
... three, one thousand,
four, one thousand,
five, one thousand,
siX, one thousand,
seven, one thousand,
eight, one thousand,
nine, one thousand,
ten, one thousand.
Ready or not, here I come.
Charlie...
Come out, come out
wherever you are.
Charlie?
Is that you?
Emily!
Where are you?
What happened?
Why are you down here?
Emily, talk to me.
He was hiding.
Who was hiding?
In the dark.
Can I go to bed now?
Hi.
Do you have a minute?
Yeah. Oh, sure.
Come on in.
Thank you. Thank you.
I wanted to apologize
for my husband.
He said he had a...
awkward moment
yesterday
with you and Emily.
That's all right.
Don't worry about it.
He's harmless, really.
He wouldn't hurt a fly.
That's fine.
It's just that...
we lost a child recently-
a girl...
and in some ways,
Emily reminds us of her.
I see.
He was just... reaching out. Hmm?
There is nothing worse
in this world than losing a child.
Here, taste this.
I think it may be too salty.
Oh. Okay.
- Not bad.
- Really?
- Oh, good.
Really good.
Wow! You look so pretty.
You didn't have to get
all dressed up for me.
Honey, would you go upstairs
and change
into something else, please?
Don't you like it?
Not for dinner, no.
Why not?
You know why.
She looks so pretty.
Let's just eat.
I think you look
really beautiful.
Did Daddy tell you
that my mommy died?
Yes, he did.
And I'm very sorry.
Did he tell you
how she died?
Honey, I don't think Elizabeth
really wants to hear
how that happened,
okay?
She killed herself
in our bathtub.
- Emily...
- Slit her wrists with a razor.
Emily.
That's enough.
Emily, I brought you something.
Your dad asked me to bring over
some of Amy's books.
These were some
of my favorites
when I was your age.
Oh, that's great.
Give you a chance to see
what the other kids are reading
before you get started.
You gonna say thanks?
Emily...
Emily... Emily, stop it.
That's enough.
Do you like her, Daddy?
- Stop this.
- Charlie says you do.
- Go to your room.
- He says you like her
- as much as Mommy.
- Go to your room. To your room.
If you're going to behave
this way, go to your room.
Let's hope you don't
wind up like her.
I'm sorry.
Who's Charlie?
Oh, he's her imaginary friend.
Her only friend.
I always wanted her to have
a better childhood than I had.
Now look.
Drive safely.
Attention, please!
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org