Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
From the dawn of time we came,
moving silently among you...
down through the centuries...
immortals.
I'm Connor MacLeod
of the clan MacLeod, the Highlander.
After the death
of my friend Ramirez...
And my beloved wife Heather,
I left my home in the highlands
of Scotland...
and began to wander the world
searching for answers.
Finally, I came toJapan...
to the mountains of Niri
and the cave of the sorcerer Nakano.
Great danger lies ahead, Highlander.
From a faraway land
comes another,
the most feared
and evil among us.
He keeps growing
stronger everyday,
feeding on the power
of other immortals.
Soon, there will be none left
who can stop him.
If he wins,
the world will suffer
eternal damnation.
Who is he?
His name is Kane.
The mountain of Niri,
where is it?
What for?
Listen! Where is
the mountain of Niri?
Do you seek the power
of the sorcerer Nakano?
Maybe the old man
still can't hear me.
- Burn it down!
- Yeah!
- Hyah!
- No! Oh!
How do I kill him?
With heart, soul and steel.
I've heard that before.
I know. Ramirez.
Like him,
I have lived many lifetimes.
And like him,
my gift to you is my knowledge.
The knowledge does not come easy,
Highlander.
Nothing is what it seems,
First, you must be aware
and respect the power of illusion.
You have already lost.
Fight with your spirit...
and the sword will follow.
Well done, Highlander.
The sword wields the spirit
of its master.
It can be the gate
to either heaven or hell.
Just strike at my head
and you will take all my knowledge.
I will not.
Not even for the power
of illusion?
Not even.
- Where to now, Kane?
- There.
Oh, yes.
This is the place.
- Shh. You have to go now.
- What?
Shh. Trust me.
You must leave.
Nakano.
You have a long journey
ahead of you.
Why do I have to go?
This is not your time,
Highlander.
Remember...
they're both mine.
Now, go!
I won't forget you.
Ah, Nakano.
So good to see you again.
The pleasure is always mine!
Actually, the pleasure's all mine!
Where is the Highlander?
Huh?
You age badly, you old goat.
Aah.
I think this is the Highlander.
There can be only one!
Always in the way, old man, huh?
More than you know.
When I tell you to go, just go!
Go after the Highlander! Now!
So.
Your magic has improved, wizard.
Why don't you give it to me?
I didn't give it you 200 years ago.
- I'm not about to now!
- Yes.
But if I cut off your head,
I get your magic anyway.
So... we could do this
the easy way...
or we could do this...
the hard way.
My head doesn't come off that easy.
No? But it does come off, nonetheless.
You betrayed yourself, old man.
There can be...
only one.
Yes, only one!
But it will not be you!
Hi, Alex. Good to see you.
Hi, Takamura. How are you?
Fine, thank you.
The archaeological commission
is waiting.
The owner of the corporation
is threatening...
to shut us down so he can
continue his foundations.
They can't stop the excavation now.
TheJapanese government has respect
for a famous archaeologist as yourself,
but this is a delicate situation.
Well, from what you sent me to
authenticate, defýnitely 16th century.
But check the grid points.
Do you realize this spot is less
than a mile from the center of Niri?
What are you suggesting?
The cave of the sorcerer Nakano?
Alex-san, Nakano is a legend.
Oh, which reminds me.
- So's Babe Ruth... based on fact.
- Domo Arigato.
Oh, Alex.
The commission.
Highlander's out there somewhere.
And he owes me for all those years.
Find him!
Nothing more!
Just fýnd him.
Where are we?
What's happening?
Nothing really left for you
to worry about, my friend.
- There can be only one!
- Kane!
Ahhh.
Dad, is it okay?
Yeah.
I didn't think there could be lightning
without clouds.
Let's go.
How can this be happening?
They were all dead
and the prize was mine.
So who is out there?
And where is he?
If anything happens to me,
I want you to look afterJohn.
What are you talking about?
I have to leave, Jack.
Everything is taken care of.
Does the boy know
you're not his real father?
Oh, yeah. He knew he was adopted
before he could spell it.
I hope whatever's taking you
is worth what you're leaving.
I hope so too.
But I don't have a choice.
I know he's alive...
and I have to fýnd him.
Going back to New York
to the place of the gathering...
is not what I had in mind.
Once again, my life was about to change.
What are they doing?
I thought we got clearance last night.
You won't believe this, Alex-san.
Someone broke into the dig.
Oh, shit.
So what did they take?
- We don't know.
- What do you mean, you don't know?
I couldn't pass the police line.
They found two bodies.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
So this must be the inner chamber.
But how did they know it was here?
Look at this!
What, 1500s?
Remarkable copy.
- Alex.
- I just want a sample.
- Why?
- I don't think it's a copy.
John.
Hey. I'm not gonna be away long.
Well, you better call me.
Hey. You better call me.
You take care of the place.
You're in charge now.
Come here.
I love you, John.
Get out of the road!
Hey, pendejo. What are ya doin' here?
Stop the car!
Hey, Antonio.
Hey, vamos, carnales.
Yeah, that's a cold thing, my man.
Pretty late for a walk,
hey, motherfucker?
- Little boy lost his way.
- Cat got his tongue. Meow.
Hey, fuckhead, I'm talkin' to you.
Nice blade.
Gang beating! Malloy! Here!
- Clear the way! Come on, move!
- Severe trauma.
- Internal bleeding, two gunshot wounds.
- Vital signs?
- Stable.
- Lucky guy.
- Notify the police?
- Of course.
What the fuck are you talking about?
These aren't bullet wounds.
- Impossible.
- Stop wasting my time!
- This guy was shot!
- You can deal with it.
- Doctor! Malloy!
- Restrain him!
Grab hold of him!
Get me a sedative!
Let me go! You don't understand!
Let me go!
Take him up to ward seven right away.
- Ward seven?
- You got a problem with that?
This guy's a lunatic.
Well...
it's defýnitely not a fake.
It doesn't make any sense.
Alex-san, how do you explain this?
- Where'd you fýnd it?
- In the chamber.
It's old, maybe 300, 400 years.
But look at the pattern.
- The weave. Certainly notJapanese.
- Looks like some sort of tartan.
Scotland?
That's a long way from Japan.
Especially 400 years ago.
Waterloo, my greatest battle. If only
I'd used my left flank before dawn.
Wellington, you swine!
You are better prepared than me.
Me, the great emperor Napoleon.
Keep it down.
Who are you?
Martin. Remember?
- Your favorite soldier.
- Martin?
- Yes.
- Is it you?
- Yeah.
- My God, what are you doing here?
I had to warn you.
You're in great danger.
I know. It's not safe here.
Please help me.
Oh, great one.
My mission is not over yet.
What mission?
Wellington. Remember?
I have to kill him.
Nephew, make him suffer.
- Hey, how do I get out of here?
- Leave it to me.
Soldiers, I'm proud of you!
Finally the time has come
and the time is now!
Hip, hip, hooray!
Shut up!
- Yeah. Let's dump this stuff and go.
- Where you want to go eat?
Highlander!
I am your shadow!
Where is Kane?
Don't worry about Kane.
Worry about me.
You've already lost.
There can be only one.
So what do you got, Vorisek?
We got a body here
and we got a head over there.
Now, I suspect foul play.
Maybe you should've taken over
for Carson, you're so funny.
Lieutenant, we got a guy in a Halloween
costume gets his head sliced off.
- It's not your usual assassination.
- Where's the sword?
- How'd you know about that?
- I remember things.
You, you forget, but I remember.
Hey, Lieutenant, you know,
we checked for prints already.
Wasted your time.
You won't fýnd nothin'.
Somebody broke out of the psycho ward,
came down and did this hell of a mess.
Russell Nash.
- You see, he's a genius.
- Yeah? So you know the victim?
I know the killer.
Mr. Nash.
LieutenantJohn Stenn, N.Y.P.D.
- What do you want?
- Eight years ago, you got away with it.
But I'm not Detective Bedsoe.
I'm gonna nail you. That's a promise.
Have a good night, Lieutenant.
Whoop. Sorry, Charlie.
- Twenty bucks in my hand.
- Twenty in mine.
- All right.
- Yo, yo, the brother. The brother.
My brother, come on in, come on in.
Tell you what, you fýnd the red card,
I'll give you $20 now.
Easy as that. You do my magic.
Boom. You're on.
- I never seen that shit before.
- Hey, yo, how'd he do that?
Hey, yo! Yo, gimme back my money.
My glasses!
Fuck it, man.
You keep the money, all right?
Welcome back, MacLeod.
Get back in the car immediately, please!
My son...
I have with me American archaeologist,
Dr. Alex Johnson,
who's from the New York Museum
of Ancient History.
Dr. Johnson, what can you tell us
about the discovery,
and why is it so exciting?
Well, the artifacts
are clearly exceptional,
but only after
a much more detailed analysis...
- Sarah.
- Can we speculate the identities...
Do I know you?
No.
No. Hmm?
I thought not.
So, what are you doing here?
Well, I may be mistaken,
but I had the feeling...
that this was the house
of Mr. DeFernet.
Well, you're obviously not mistaken.
Ah, Connor MacLeod.
I see you've met
my rather spirited niece, Sarah.
- She's come here from England.
- It seems I'm in need of taming.
Pleasant challenge... I would imagine.
I invited him for the weekend
to join us at the card table.
- So you're a gambler, Mr. MacLeod?
- On occasion.
So am I.
On occasion.
Any chance of a preview?
Not at this point, but some
of the more unusual objects...
will be lent
to our existing exhibition...
However, is it not possible
to be stepping on the site...
of the legendary lost cave of
the greatJapanese sorcerer Nakano?
As I've said before, any speculation at
this point would be a little premature.
Well, is it not true that supported
by your own controversial studies,
that legends can be used
to identify archaeological sites?
It is true that we have seen parallels
between missing sites before.
What about the inscriptions?
Do they offer clues
or is this some cave-robbing graffýti?
It's probably just some ancient taggers.
Taggers. Well, Ms. Johnson,
so no idea what it means?
I know what it means.
As for the alphabet...
uh, early Russian.
"There can be only one. "
Only one what?
Alex-san, another fax from Tommy.
"A little something
to read on the flight home.
I thought this might interest you. "
Well, that's it for me.
I'm off to New York tonight.
Better document that last crate.
The man wants vinyl
when he can have the real thing?
I don't think so.
Come on.
Why don't you come here a little bit
and make yourself comfortable?
You nice, big boy.
Come on, you little devil.
Silent type, huh?
It fýne by me, baby.
But I'm telling you...
no glove...
no love.
What you waiting for, honey?
Come on, baby.
So after three days,
this better be good.
Well, it wasn't easy, but I fýnally
determined the cause of death.
All right, now that we've had
our little joke, what else you got?
Nothin'.
Besides havin' his head cut off,
he's in perfect health.
No broken bones, no cavities,
no organ deterioration.
Like a newborn baby.
Find out who he is?
He's nobody.
No prints, no dental, no nothin'.
It's like he never existed.
So what do you really think, Howard?
Mmm. I think you better not smoke
in here, Lieutenant.
What's this guy doin' in New York City?
What's he doin' on the planet?
Thanks, Howard!
MacLeods. I checked it.
Same pattern, didn't match up.
Apparently,
this alteration in the color...
denotes a branch of the clan
that broke away in, I think, 1536.
Some incident occurred that year...
involving a Connor MacLeod
who was driven from his home,
accused of wielding powers
thought to have been unnatural.
So in defýance, the father altered this
insignia to honor the son's lineage,
but there's been no record
of this branch ever since.
Except for a piece of cloth.
Which could now place one of them
in a Japanese cave a few years later.
Yeah, but what would
a Scot be doing there?
What if he was one of these
Gaelic mystics?
Nakano's initiates were said
to have been great sorcerers, right?
- Yeah.
- None of the legends refer to where they came from.
Interesting theory, but, Alex,
no records, no proof.
Once a year, the MacLeods meet
at Dunvegan Castle, Isle of Skye.
According to the registrar,
this entry was made in 1986,
some antique dealer claiming
to be a direct descendant...
of this particular branch.
So where's this guy from?
New York. They faxed me his address.
What? You're gonna harass
some poor guy about his ancestors?
- He's gonna think you're crazy.
- Perhaps.
Then again, at this point,
it may be my only link to Nakano.
Well... I'm off.
Bye, Tommy.
I'll tell security you're working late.
Thanks.
- What do you call this place?
- Excuse me?
This place, here.
What do you call it?
Uh... A museum, but we're closed.
Museum. Ah, no, please.
I'm your biggest fan.
You see, I saw you on television.
I'm a big historian myself really.
Ah, this looks familiar.
Oh, isn't it amazing how the present
just can't seem to escape the past?
C- Can I help you with something?
No, no, no. I'm just a...
Just doing a little research.
Ooh, look at this cave.
Little small, eh?
And what does your museum call it?
- A model.
And you?
Um, um,
a vision of a past reality, I suppose.
Oh, reality. No, not reality.
Reality is so boring.
I much prefer...
illusion or fantasy,
a little hocus pocus
and maybe a little...
Maybe a little bit of...
hanky-panky, huh?
Connor MacLeod.
Don't worry, my prissy, I'll fýnd him.
I'm gonna fýnd him.
Burn it down.
I'm outside theJapanese
Spiritual Center in Queens.
Hyah!
Ya!
- Good to have you back, Nash.
- Good to see you, Charlie.
Hyah!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Whooo-oh!
Come on. Come on.
Hyah!
I wish we could go on like this
for a thousand years.
What do you wish?
MacLeod?
That he had better timing.
What do you want, Pierre?
I have bad news.
They need you in Paris.
Why now?
The revolution has started.
You must leave the girl.
Come now, my friend.
If not for you, then do it for her.
You're not coming back, are you?
You have to get back to England.
- It won't be safe here.
- No one is safe now.
Connor.
Take this.
Russell Nash?
- Excuse me?
- Sorry. Are you Russell Nash?
- What if I am?
- I'm looking for the previous owner of your shop,
a Connor MacLeod.
You wouldn't happen to know
where I could fýnd him, would you?
Did you follow me?
Yes.
I haven't seen him in eight years.
Do... Do you know
if he's still in the area?
I wish I could help you, Miss Johnson.
How do you know my name?
Well, your, uh, discovery in Japan
has made you famous.
You're obviously...
interested in Japan yourself, Mr. Nash.
Strange food. Good cars.
Tough deals.
Listen, it's getting late.
Good night, Miss Johnson.
Look, Mr. Nash,
I don't mean to bother you,
but you're my only link
to this Connor MacLeod.
Try the phone book.
There's plenty of MacLeods in New York.
Well, thanks,
but I'm only looking for one.
So am I.
Four hundred years...
is a long time to hate.
Ohh. And you never wrote.
But hate feeds you.
It focuses the mind.
Keeps you warm.
Gives you hope. Eh, MacLeod?
Don't worry about the girl.
She's not really my type.
A little too... pale.
Then again, this being the 90s,
I could make an exception, huh?
After all, I've got so much
catching up to do.
This is a Buddhist shrine, Kane,
and we can't fýght on holy ground.
Oh, well... I guess
I'll be the judge of that.
Hyah!
Oooh.
Nothing!
There can be only...
One!
After 400 years, patience is a virtue.
Jesus Christ. I'm goin' in!
Listen!
Whatever you saw, you saw nothing.
You don't know
what you're getting yourself into.
Stay away.
Freeze! Police!
One more thing
I think you should know about...
There was a woman.
Worked with us once in a while.
Brenda.
Brenda Wyatt.
- What about her?
- Well, she was fascinated by it.
The murders, the swords...
the whole thing.
Lieutenant, it's what,
5:00 in the morning?
They scraped her off a highway
in Scotland seven years ago.
She was killed instantly,
but he walked away without a scratch.
Sad for him.
So, are you sure
you didn't see anything?
- Miss Johnson!
- Sorry. No.
Russell Nash is a dangerous man.
Now I suggest you stay away from him.
That's exactly what he said.
Please, my friend. For the revolution.
MacLeod!
Visitor!
Calm down, MacLeod. If you die,
we lose a great warrior against evil.
I'm here to take your place.
Go home and sleep it off.
Come on.
I'm tired of this eternal life.
Death would release me from my pain.
Come on, Pierre. Go home.
I'm not going anywhere.
It's time, Mr. MacLeod.
When he wakes up, throw him out.
God be with you.
For treason against the King of France.
Connor MacLeod.
Connor! Connor!
Connor!
Oh, Sarah.
Yes?
Well, it was a very interesting
evening last night,
but I didn't exactly have time to
check the phone book... Mr. MacLeod.
You wanna come in?
Come in.
I'll fýx you a drink.
Make yourself comfortable.
Thanks.
You've, uh, got quite a collection.
- Hello?
- Mr. MacLeod?
This is Janet at Super Travel.
I'm calling to confýrm your reservation
on the Newark-Glasgow flight.
Your ticket is prepaid
and waiting at the counter.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
Bye.
Lot of Connors in the family.
Her name was Sarah.
Come on, dear.
Ah, Papa.
Look, I don't know
what was going on last night,
but I think it's got something
to do with what I'm working on.
We found a piece of tartan
in the cave that was traced to...
an undocumented branch
of the MacLeods, of which...
you are apparently
the only member on record.
That cave was sealed 400 years ago.
Have you ever heard of the legend
of the sorcerer Nakano?
Don't you ever think about
anything else but business?
Do you have something
better to offer?
It seems I'm in need of taming.
Pleasant challenge...
I would imagine.
Well, I'm sure you'll let me know
if something comes to mind, huh?
Hm. What's this?
Looks familiar.
Death to the MacLeods!
My bonny Heather,
my fýrst wife, my fýrst love.
I came back here
because this is where it all started.
And I need some strength.
God.
Ahh. The last 400 years...
have been good to you, MacLeod.
Oh.
Oops-a-daisy.
Hi. Leave a message;
I'll call you back.
Uh, hi, it's me, John.
I miss you.
When are you coming home?
Uh, y-you said you were
gonna call me, remember?
Well, in case you forgot,
it's Marrakesh 1442.
Love you, Daddy. Bye.
Daddy.
Hey, MacLeod.
I thought you'd fýnd me.
Why did you come?
Nakano.
O bonny Portmore
I am sorry to see
Such a woeful destruction
Of your ornament tree
For it stood on your shore
For many's the long day
Till the long boats from Antrim
Came to float it away
O bonny Portmore
You shine where you stand
And the more I think on you
The more I think long
If I had you now
As I had once before
All the Lords in Old England
Would not purchase Portmore
All the birds in the forest
They bitterly weep
Saying, Where shall we shelter
Where shall we sleep
For the Oak and the Ash
They are all cutten down
And the walls of bonny Portmore
Are all down to the ground
You seem like you belong here.
Maybe I used to.
But that was a long time ago.
You spend a lot of time alone.
I'm used to it.
Nobody is.
You don't let people in, do you?
I can't.
- It hurts. Love and...
- And see them die?
Like the woman in the painting.
Yes. I loved her very much.
I know who you are.
You're Connor MacLeod.
Born into the clan MacLeod,
in Glen Finnan,
on the shores of Loch Shiel.
You were driven
from your home in 1536.
- And I cannot die.
- And have wandered the world ever since.
- Mr. MacLeod?
- Yeah?
There's a Jack Donovan
on the phone returning your call.
I'll be right back.
- Jack.
- What are you doing in Scotland?
- What do you mean?
- John's on the flight from Marrakesh.
He gets into Newark
tomorrow afternoon as planned.
- What are you saying, Jack?
- Is something wrong with your memory?
I've just dropped him at the airport.
Is there a problem?
No problem, Jack. I'll pick him up.
Bye, Jack. Thanks.
Passport, please.
You're traveling alone?
Um, yeah,
but my dad's picking me up.
Welcome to the United States,
Mr. MacLeod.
Thanks.
- Yeah.
- What?
- They got Nash.
- Where?
All right, we'll be right there.
Northwest Airlines. Flight 489.
Just landed in Newark.
Come on, move. Let's go!
It's over there.
The green bag. Grab it.
I know he's here somewhere.
I can feel him.
Excuse me.
- Excuse me.
- Did you see that?
Next.
- Dad!
- John.
- Freeze!
- Let me go!
John!
- Where's the Porsche?
- The Porsche. Get in the car.
Little punk.
Who... Who are you?
I'm a friend of your daddy's.
- He's got my son.
- What son, Nash?
There's nothing in your fýle
about a son. You're a fuckin' liar!
Nash, what son?
Please, stop the car! Please!
Let me outta here!
- "Let me out of here. Stop the car. "
- Stop!
Please! Look at the plane!
There's a plane!
No!
Whoo! I ain't missin' my plane!
Whoa! Whoa!
You take the wheel!
Watch out! Give it back!
Ohh! Mother!
Okay, guys, I'll take it from here.
Okay. Good luck, Lieutenant.
So, Nash, talk to me.
We've got plenty of time.
Whoo!
- Hey! Aaah!
- It's a truck! Stop!
Help!
This is fuckin' bullshit.
Without a confession,
we got nothin' on this guy.
So if we can't charge him,
he's gonna have to release him.
Pretty stuffy, eh?
Need a little ventilation, eh?
There goes!
Now, fýrst rule of safety:
Keep your eye on the road!
What's that? It's a wall!
Okay, Nash,
you're free to go... for now.
- Oh, yeah. One more thing.
- What?
One day you'll make a mistake,
and when you do, I'll nail ya.
I've heard that before.
Let the fucker go.
Your daddy can't save you now.
MacLeod... or Highlander...
whatever you're going by these days.
- It's your boy.
- Dad!
I hope I wasn't too hard on him.
I'm at the old mission.
Route 1.Jersey City. Do come.
Dad!
Ah, the importance of teaching young
people family values. Hah? Smoke.
- Don't touch him.
- Ha-ha! Little punk.
- Come here, John.
- Go see your father.
Ohh! Disappearance in the family.
It's funny. You know, I... I thought
immortals couldn't have children.
But it seems that while
I'm the master of illusion,
you are turning out to be
the master of deception, Highlander.
How did you do it? How did you convince
all those lovely women of yours...
that they were the ones
that couldn't bear children?
When all the while it was you
and your little immortal pecker...
that really didn't do the pecking.
Ohh. I know.
You must've been very disappointed.
All those nice years thinking
you were the only one left.
But, you see, the prize was never yours.
And now, it never will be. Amen.
Nice little speech, Kane,
but it's not gonna save your head.
Where's John?
Oh. Well, come with me.
Come. Where's Johnny?
Here's Johnny.
Ahh.
Ooh.
MacLeod.
- What are you doing here?
- I followed you.
L... I just thought I could help.
Aah!
Aw, shit!
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Ooh, MacLeod.
You're such a lady-killer.
I can't kill an unarmed man.
Take it.
But then again, life isn't fair, is it?
I'll see you... in hell.
I'll be the judge of that.
There can be only one.
Dad?
Oh, John.
Will ya do somethin'for me, Connor?
In the years to come, will ya light
a candle and remember me on my birthday?
Aye, love. I will.
There's
a fresh breeze blowing off the loch.
The glen is snowy and cold.
It's the most glorious sight on Earth.
I've found no place
to match it in 400 years.
I'm back now... with a woman I love
and a son I've taken as my own.
I'm at peace.
It's fýnally over.
O bonny Portmore
I am sorry to see
Such a woeful destruction
Of your ornament tree
For it stood on your shore
For many's the long day
Till the long boats from Antrim
Came to float it away
O bonny Portmore
You shine where you stand
And the more I think on you
The more I think long
If I had you now
As I had once before
All the Lords in Old England
Would not purchase Portmore
All the birds in the forest
They bitterly weep
Saying, Where shall we shelter
Where shall we sleep
For the Oak and the Ash
They are all cutten down
And the walls of bonny Portmore
Are all down to the ground
O bonny Portmore
You shine where you stand
And the more I think on you
The more I think long
If I had you now
As I had once before
All the Lords of Old England
Would not purchase Portmore
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org