Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
What are you doing down here? I thought
you usually had lunch with Coma Guy.
This is Vegetative State Guy.
Better company.
Tell him about those Sherpas you dropped
acid with in St. Patrick's Cathedral.
You stole my prescription pad,
and you forged my name.
What did you tell the cop?
I lied. They'd have
put you away for ten years.
After they took your
license to practice medicine.
- So everything's good, then.
- I lied to the cops.
There is no case unless they can prove
that either I got the drugs illegally
or I sold them illegally.
I didn't do the second.
You lied about the first. Game over.
Yeah. Tritter's just playing.
He's gonna see how clever
you are and then just walk away.
The important thing is that
you keep prescribing
the same amount of drugs to me,
or it'll look suspicious.
Here's another way to look at it.
Having forced me to lie to the police,
your first concern is
securing your drug connection.
Joining my father for lunch?
I should've called ahead for a table.
- Dr. House was just--
- Enjoying a Reuben.
It's okay.
After ten years, anything that'll
get doctors in the same room as--
What are you doing?
Nothing. What are you doing?
Chips?
Wanna see something really cool?
I saw you leaving last Tuesday.
Practically tripped over
two guys on your way out,
but you had no problem opening doors.
It's called akinetopsia.
You can't see things when they move.
And since you haven't been hit by a bus,
I assume that it's intermittent.
It's probably accompanied by seizures,
which made me think that I
could set one off by flashing the--
God, I love this family!
Transcript: FRM - Synchro: jh26
I can see fine now.
I've had seizures before.
Most of the time, they're small.
Doctors ran me through all the tests.
Couldn't find anything.
Any history of epilepsy in your family?
The only things I know
that run in my family are
a lot of chutzpah and the
ability to sleep for ten years.
Although I'm not really an expert.
Dad never really liked
my mother's side of the family,
and after she died and he came here,
I was raised by a guardian.
I wouldn't even know
how to get in touch with him.
How 'bout your father's
side of the family?
Any relatives we could speak with?
My father was an only child.
And my grandparents are dead.
Who did you put down as the person the
hospital should contact in an emergency?
I left it blank.
There's gotta be someone. A friend?
Oh, plenty of friends. Just...
no one that would care if I was here.
Say, do you mind passing me my backpack?
Hair of the dog.
- Could be infection.
- Or a brain tumor.
Says he had a CT.
What's wrong with
the simplest explanation?
Trauma.
He didn't report any injuries.
He didn't report being
an alcoholic, either.
Drinking equals falling down,
equals trauma, equals--
Maybe it's inherited.
How would you jump
to genetics from his EEG?
All you've got are some
vaguely epileptiform waves.
It's not his EEG.
It's his father's.
When it comes to cortical seizures,
like father, like son.
Small seizures aren't unheard
of in a patient in a vegetative state.
Similarities are interesting, though.
What caused the vegetative state?
His house burned down.
Went back in to get his wife.
Firefighters found him unconscious three
feet from the bedroom, asphyxiated.
Not an inherited condition.
Test his DNA.
Start with adrenomyeloneuropathy.
Check out the home.
- He has a single bed.
- They still make single beds?
Could mean he just doesn't have sex--
though there were
condoms in the apartment.
House asked you to check
out the home for toxins.
No mold, no leaks, no pets.
MRI and LP are both inconclusive.
Infection's still possible.
- Tumor's less likely, but--
- DNA?
Adrenomyeloneuropathy test was negative.
DNA test again. Try Unverricht-Lundborg
and late-onset Lafora's.
Genetic tests take forever.
You can't just keep testing
for every inherited condition
you think it might be.
Well, not me.
I'll be leaving early. But you guys can.
You said no one's been sick, but
what about delivery people, repair guy?
I wouldn't know.
I work from home.
Haven't been to the
office in over a month.
- Visitors?
- Haven't had any.
The only person I've seen in the
last week was the pizza delivery guy.
And he looked pretty healthy.
There's gotta be
someone you're close to.
Actually,
the person I see
most often is my father.
He's asleep, so he can't stop me.
What is it?
Just feeling a little nauseous. I--
I think his liver's failing.
Oh, God. Does--does that mean that I'm--
I need a central line kit. Two units of
packed red blood cells, type O negative.
He's unconscious and heading for a coma.
He's at a four on the RLAS scale.
Stop all treatment.
You think this is
a reaction to our meds?
Well, they're obviously not helping.
Given the fact that he's an alcoholic,
there's a good chance his liver wasn't
so hot when he came in.
Anti-seizure drugs could
have just pushed him over the edge.
We take him off those meds,
what do we put him on?
I was hoping you'd know.
May be academic,
but I just started him on dialysis.
Kidney and liver failure.
Not too many people come back from that.
Trauma's out of the picture.
It could still be infection.
- Or neurological.
- Or genetic.
We need a better history.
Did you miss the part where
the patient lost consciousness?
L-dopa?
You're not waking Kyle.
You're waking his father.
I commend your observational skills.
You have no reason to think any amount
of drugs will wake a man from a coma.
Vegetative state. Much easier.
This guy's no Terry Schiavo.
His brain's all there. He moves around.
His muscles have barely atrophied.
Just waiting for a fairytale kiss.
After I do that, stick a needle in him.
The amount of amphetamines
alone would be dangerous,
besides whatever the
hell else you've got in there.
There are reports out of South Africa
about a pill that would temporarily
revive someone in a vegetative state.
We've all seen Awakenings.
Made me cry. I wanna cry.
Put the syringe down.
I can out-draw you, mysterious stranger.
We don't experiment
on helpless patients.
Be reasonable.
There's no way this is gonna work.
Even if you woke him,
it would only be for a few hours.
A day, two at the most.
You're risking his life.
I'm risking getting sued.
That's the only objection here.
You'll be torturing him. And his family.
Good news for legal. The only
family he's got is upstairs dying.
I want this patient monitored
for the next 24 hours.
I want someone with him at all
times to make sure you didn't kill him.
I want your ass in my office--
God. I'm starving.
I could really go for a steak.
Do you know your name?
You know where you are?
Gabriel Wozniak.
I don't know the name of this hospital.
How much are three and five?
Eight.
Also known as 1/2 of 16,
1/4 of 32, two to the third power.
Coolest thing ever.
Any history of seizure in your family?
No.
- Liver disease?
- No.
How long have I been here?
I got the feeling it's,
um, been a long time.
Interesting.
If your internal clock kept ticking,
how deep does that awareness go?
Pick up scraps of conversations?
You have the vague sense
that the hospital administrator
dresses like a trollop?
Or that the new Star Wars
movies were a disappointment?
I know my wife is dead.
I don't know how long it's been.
Ten years.
What's the last thing you remember?
The fire.
My wife was in the bedroom.
She had taken a sleeping pill. I got...
Kyle out.
Went back in for her.
I knew I didn't make it.
I'm sorry.
What about your wife's side of the
family? Any history of seizures there?
Your son Kyle is a patient here.
I'm afraid his condition is serious.
He may be dying.
No seizure issues on
my wife's side, either.
What about that steak?
Nobody ever answered me.
Rumor in the cafeteria was
Caustic Guy was waking up Coma Guy.
Technically,
Vegetative State Guy was woken by...
- yeah, Caustic Guy.
- So what happened?
Gotta get him a steak before
I can ask him any more questions.
He doesn't want to talk about his son?
Didn't seem to emotionally
register that his son is sick.
Brain issue? He was asphyxiated,
spent ten years as asparagus.
Who knows what damage is in there?
It's possible. 'Course,
there's always the simple explanation.
Maybe he just doesn't like his son.
Only in your world would that be simple.
The delusion
that fathering a child installs a
permanent geyser of unconditional love--
Maybe your father's feelings
were conditional. Not everyone's--
Yes, well, of course, that would play
into your romantic vision of human--
In terms you would understand,
we have an evolutionary incentive
to sacrifice for our offspring.
Our tribe, our friends.
Keep them safe.
Except for all the people who don't.
Everything is conditional.
You just can't always
anticipate the conditions.
Mind if we talk for a few minutes?
How many pills would you say Dr.
House takes a day?
I'm uncomfortable setting a number.
Try.
Six.
A day.
Has he ever had you...
write prescriptions for him?
No. What is it you want me to say?
That he takes too many pills
and is a danger to the hospital?
Or he takes too few because
he's selling them on the side?
Either one is ridiculous.
I meant the former.
You're wrong.
Can I ask what Dr.
House has done to deserve your loyalty?
He's not known as a great boss.
He's not even much of a friend.
I mean, look how he left Dr.
Wilson holding the bag.
It's odd.
You don't know about that.
You defend him, and
he won't even tell you
what's happening in his life.
I was paged.
Saw you with a cop.
- What'd he want?
- How many pills does House take,
did I ever write him a prescription,
that sort of stuff.
- I told him six.
- A day, or in a mouthful?
I was just hoping you guys
would stay consistent with--
- He wants to talk to us, too?
- You're next.
We've gotta tell House what's going on.
- Tritter says no.
- Then no it is.
Cops have a thousand ways
to make life difficult for you.
Quick, what's the kid's status?
I gotta get back to our sleeper before
he goes looking for the orgasmatron.
See, if that were rhetorical,
it would mean that I could just
turn around and leave now. Which I'm
not doing. From which you should deduce.
He's off all drugs
except the antibiotics.
His liver's just managing
to hang in there.
He's still sliding into coma.
Your barber sucks.
Coma diet. I could make a fortune.
Vegetative state diet.
- Who gave you your clothes?
- Dr. Cuddy.
I guess I'll need all new ones anyway.
Everything went in the fire.
Ah, don't worry about it.
We use recyclable clothes now.
Wear them once, then eat them.
Your son's measles vaccination.
Do you remember if he
had it and what type it was?
Man, you're a piece of work,
you know that?
You weren't gonna tell me, were you?
I don't need new clothes. Dr. Cuddy
says my body will adjust to the drugs.
That I'll be a vegetable again
by tomorrow. If I'm really lucky,
the day after.
Yeah.
If I got a day to live,
I'm not gonna spend it
in a hospital room being grilled.
Come on, where you gonna go?
Your house burned down.
Your wife's dead.
Business was sold off.
The only thing you have left
is down the hall heading
for a liver biopsy.
Used to be this little,
um, hole in the wall.
Run by a guy named Giancarlo.
Made the best hoagies in the world.
Real Italian rolls.
Prosciutto. Provolone.
How far is Atlantic City from here?
You have one day to live.
And you want a sandwich.
People on Death Row get a last meal.
State provides it.
Who's providing for you?
You got a car? Money?
You're negotiating with me.
Take out another hundred for me.
And I need your car.
- I'm not doing you any favors.
- You'll get it back tomorrow.
Two days, max. Road trip.
This is like trying to control
the weather, but I'd prefer it
if you didn't eat in the car.
I just had it detailed.
- I drive.
- Oh, the hell he does.
Sure.
Aside from the fact he just
woke up from a vegetative state,
the guy doesn't have a license.
How 'bout this? Cops stop us, we lie.
You know how to do that.
Chips.
It's all the drugs
pumping through his system.
Right now, his reflexes are
better than Dale Earnhardt Jr.'s.
Hey, what's this?
It says, "Ipp-odd."
I'm coming.
So let's talk about toxic exposure.
What was wrong with the old colors?
I trusted brown.
Do the purple ones
have chocolate inside?
Raspberry cocaine.
This house that burned down.
Where was it?
Moorestown, New Jersey.
Listen, I really need to know about the
candy because I'm allergic to berries.
You didn't mention that.
- Is it significant?
- No.
So where else did you live?
List everywhere, including vacations.
Start with when your wife got pregnant.
We lived in Jersey. Then we
moved to Jersey. From there, Jersey.
What are you waiting to hear?
About the little cottage in the Amazon
with the mosquitoes and
the lead paint all over the walls?
Yes.
You know what?
I didn't let you come along
so you could suck all the
fun out of my one day of life.
Well, you're outta luck,
'cause that's totally why I'm here.
O kay.
Rule change.
Person with the money makes the rules.
Or in this case,
the person who's friends with the
person with the money makes the rules.
Well, you want answers
more than I want money.
All right, so here's the game.
Ask whatever you want.
But for every question I answer,
you have to answer one first.
And why would you care
about anything I have to say?
The day before I died,
I was a successful man.
I had a factory with over 200 employees.
People listened when I talked.
I liked power.
Now the only power I have left
is the power to annoy you.
Took Wilson's assistant for coffee.
- Why?
- Something Tritter said.
She told me the police think that House
stole Wilson's prescription
pad and forged his name.
You... believe it?
Do you?
Oh, absolutely. I do.
I'm just checking how naive you are.
He's not gonna steal his best
friend's pad, jeopardize his career.
Until his best friend says no to him.
House is a junkie. Junkies do whatever
they have to do to get what they need.
Kyle's down to a
three on the RLAS scale.
He's only showing localized response.
I'll call House. Tell him
we're gonna need an answer soon.
Get in your right lane for 295.
And pass me the Twizzlers.
- I'm curious.
- No, you're not.
Why would a man's first instinct
be to drive away from
the only family he's got?
No! This is no time
for you to do your thing.
We don't care about his state of mind.
We don't care if he's happy. This
factory of yours. What did you make?
So ask me a question.
I'm thinking.
Only six left, by the way.
So sign my name.
You don't need a doctor. You need a pen.
What is up with you two?
Wilson lied to the bulls
to keep me out of the big house.
- Are you out of your mind?
- Well, who's he gonna tell?
By tomorrow night, he's gonna
be a mindless stalk of celery.
Since I answered that one,
by the way, my turn.
What did you make in your factory?
Luxury boats.
Have you ever been in love?
Going right for the closets with
the embarrassing stuff. Good move. Yes.
Describe the boats.
35- to 65-foot hulls. Twin engines,
parquet floors in the galleys,
staterooms with queen beds.
How'd you meet?
She shot me.
These boats. I assume you used
mildew-resistant paint on the hulls?
Naturally.
Shot you?
Paintball.
Doctors versus lawyers.
You ever take your son to the factory?
Sure. He used to run all over the place,
but it was perfectly safe.
Ever love anybody else?
No more questions. I got my answer.
While Dad's in the office,
son's watching them spray-paint.
And what kid wears a mask?
Mercury specifically targets
the central nervous system.
Are you saying this was my fault?
Mercury poisoning explains the seizures.
The liver is like a big soup strainer.
Soup runs through.
Chicken dumplings stay. For soup,
read blood. For chicken dumplings--
I get it, I get it. Mercury.
Sits more or less idle until your kid
pours tequila shooters into his liver.
When the liver goes, takes
out the kidneys. Explains everything.
Yeah, it's me.
Foreman, draw blood.
Test for mercury poisoning.
Chase. Start heavy metal chelation
while we're waiting for results.
Chase isn't here. I'll start the--
Where is he?
The lab.
How many pills does he take a day?
It's hard to say.
Pain levels vary over time.
Could be six, eight, ten.
Ever write any prescriptions for him?
- Yes.
- Why?
Did he tell you to?
He asked me to.
Medicine...
attracts people who
are attracted to power.
I know how he hates when
he is defied by a patient.
I doubt he handles defiance
from his staff any better.
Now, you correct me if I'm wrong.
But I don't think Dr.
House asks for anything.
I think he takes it.
And I think that you
are stuck lying to the police
to cover up something...
you didn't want to do.
We have been up and down St.
James like a Monopoly car.
It's not here.
Giancarlo has left the building.
We could still turn around
and go back to Princeton.
No! We've come this far.
I'm getting the hoagie.
If your son does have mercury poisoning,
there's a good chance
he'll respond to the chelation.
You might be able to have a
few min with him before you lapse.
Why are you so concerned about me?
Deep inside,
Wilson believes that if he cares enough,
he'll never have to die.
Your behavior isn't normal.
And you would know normal.
What could he have done that
you won't forgive after ten years,
when this is your last chance?
My son is what he is.
His mother's side?
All drunken losers.
He's gone the same way.
House told you that drinking
had damaged your son's liver.
I just said that.
But you didn't hear him say
that till after we left the hospital.
So why did you leave?
Maybe your son takes after your side.
Seizures and an allergy
to emotional connections.
Okay, okay, okay. Enough.
We're in Atlantic City,
and my time's not up yet.
We'll find a hotel with a casino.
BP's starting to drop.
O2-sat's down to 70.
0.3 milligrams of epi in.
What are you trying to do?
Make him bleed faster?
Check the pulse.
It's not his liver.
It's the heart.
I understand he's a French chef,
but I'm sure he can handle this.
We need a 12-inch Italian roll,
oregano vinegar--
No. Not balsamic vinegar.
Oregano vinegar.
Quid pro quo, Clarice.
Game's still on.
I thought the answer
was mercury poisoning.
What other questions
would you care about?
If you each had one day to live,
you'd look for one last meal,
and House would look
for one last answer.
No, can you just send the ingredients
up here? And I'll make it myself.
Last ten years.
- How much awareness did you have?
- I don't know.
I knew it wasn't the next day.
I knew that--
I recognized your voice.
How often were you in my room?
No. You're wasting a question.
I have a better one.
- Why steal my pad?
- Oh, my God. You're right.
I'm an addict.
Thanks for opening my eyes.
No, I mean, why my pad?
Foreman, Cameron,
and Chase's pads are just as convenient.
But their association with
you is involuntary. They're employees.
I associate with you through choice.
And any relationship
that involves choice
you have to see how far
you can push before it breaks.
This is easy.
You ask the questions,
answer them, and make tasty snacks.
Let's go try the casino.
And one day, our friendship will break.
And that'll just prove your theory
that relationships are conditional,
and you don't need human connection,
or deserve it,
or whatever goes on in
that rat maze of your brain.
Sorry. If I'd known he
was gonna be this annoying,
I would've stolen Dr.
Cameron's pad and Dr. Foreman's car.
At least she appreciates
my brooding melancholy.
House's House of Whining.
State your complaint.
Patient's BP just dropped like a stone.
Do an echo.
Mercury isn't likely to damage--
It didn't. Mercury test was negative.
Do an echo.
I was wrong. Your son's still dying.
I need to go over every
relative you ever had again.
This time, forget their diseases.
Just tell me how they died.
We don't have time to take turns.
Gimme the answers.
You get a big one at the end.
You go for whatever you want.
Destroy my privacy, my dignity.
Your grandmother?
Heat exhaustion.
Fourth of July picnic. The woman was 92.
Does anyone in the kitchen
know the hoagie shop
that used to be on St. James Place?
Your sister-in-law with the diabetes.
As far as you know, is she still alive?
She's not. Killed in a traffic accident
driving home from a Phillies game.
I'm sure a lot of beer was consumed.
Phillies lost.
Your father?
Old age. Heart finally gave out.
Your wife's father?
Hit-and-run.
Walking the incontinent dog.
Uh, hi. Do you guys deliver?
Let me put it this way. If you deliver,
there'll be a $100 tip in it for you.
Excellent!
Victory.
Ha, ha, the night
is finally going my way.
Wilson, toss me a soda.
Shall we go somewhere to talk?
House is an ass.
But he obviously needs pain medication.
How much pain one person feels is not
a call the government should be making.
So you think I'm a bureaucrat
with a badge following some
arbitrary guideline.
Yeah. I do.
So you're saying I should...
just trust him.
Do you?
- You're not qualified to make that--
- I'm not sure you are, either.
I've been a cop for 20 years,
and not a day goes by
that someone doesn't try to
sell me some self-serving story.
If you had my job, you'd know.
Everybody lies.
Think you've run out of relatives.
So. It's my turn.
- Why did you become a doctor?
- That's the big question?
I gave you complete license to humiliate
me, and that's the best you can do?
Well, okay. Let's discuss
the wonder of the human body.
No, no, no.
You're a curious guy.
You like to figure things out.
Why not go into research?
Why work with people when you...
obviously hate people?
Oedipal fixation.
I was seeking my mother's love,
and she thought that Ben
Casey was just the dreamiest--
Okay, fine. You don't think
you'll need any more answers from me?
Give me a hard time.
When I was 14,
my father was stationed in Japan.
I went rock climbing with this kid
from school. He fell, he got injured,
and I had to bring him to the hospital.
We came in through the wrong entrance
and passed this guy in the hall.
It was a janitor.
My friend came down
with an infection and
the doctors didn't know what to do.
So they brought in...
the janitor.
He was a doctor.
And a Buraku.
One of Japan's untouchables.
His ancestors had been
slaughterers, gravediggers.
And this guy,
he knew that he wasn't accepted
by the staff. Didn't even try.
He didn't dress well.
He didn't pretend to be one of them.
The people that ran that place,
they didn't think that
he had anything they wanted.
Except when they needed him.
Because he was right.
Which meant that nothing else mattered.
And they had to listen to him.
Thank you.
Need 20 milligrams
of diazepam in a syringe.
Heartbeat's irregular and accelerating.
- It's at 200.
- He's gonna crash.
- Allergic reaction to the diazepam?
- Better hope so.
It's either that, or his heart's done.
What happened on the night of the fire?
Yeah, I'm sure it's a
stressful emotional question.
Suck it up.
My wife had taken a sleeping
pill and gone to bed.
It was Christmas Eve. I let Kyle
pop corn in the fireplace. He
managed to...
knock loose some tinder.
Wrapping paper caught on fire.
Spread. So fast.
I got Kyle out.
And when I went back in for--
You're a disappointment.
You act as though you
don't need anybody. You--
You just blame your
son for what happened.
I don't blame him.
He was a 12-year-old boy.
You don't blame a kid for an accident.
Then what are we doing here?
Why aren't you with him?
Because it wouldn't matter!
I failed to keep my family safe!
I couldn't stop the fire.
I couldn't save my wife!
Now you want me to stick around
watching while I fail to save my son.
Thank you so much for waking me up.
How did your son dislodge the tinder?
He dropped the popcorn tray.
He had been complaining it
was too heavy. I should've listened.
And the hit-and-run.
Walking the pissy dog.
That happen at night?
I think so, yeah. Why?
Car accident after the Phillies lost.
Night game?
Ragged red fiber.
It's an inherited condition.
Dropping things, muscle weakness.
Poor night vision.
Makes people seem uncoordinated,
accident-prone, careless.
It's transmitted in mitochondrial DNA.
So it only passes through the mother.
Your wife's family weren't drunks.
They were sick.
It wouldn't have affected his liver.
The kid is a drunk.
He thinks that he killed his mother
and turned his father into a vegetable.
You know,
I might have a few shots myself.
Foreman.
Test his DNA for ragged red fiber.
- It's not gonna--
- Here's a thought.
Why don't we not assume that the test
is negative until we actually do it?
House.
The kid has severe cardiomyopathy.
Alcoholic. No shot at a transplant.
So yeah, maybe you figured out why.
Good for you, but...
he's gonna die anyway.
I want to give Kyle my heart.
This thing--
whatever it is--
you said he gets it from the mother.
My heart's fine.
And it could go on being
fine for the rest of your life.
Yeah.
It's not like he's
gonna do anything with it.
Well, you woke him up once.
Maybe someone will come
up with some other answer.
We've both seen breakthroughs
no one expected.
And ragged red fiber's treatable,
but not curable.
Even if he gets your heart,
there's no guarantee.
He's my kid.
No. Did you really
expect a different answer?
We have arranged transplants
before when a patient is near death.
Except he isn't near death. He's saying,
"Kill me and cut out my heart."
Are you out of your mind?
Fine. I'll think of something else.
I'm sorry.
Wilson.
Get out.
No.
You've lied to the cops enough for me.
Maybe I don't wanna
push this till it breaks.
Pills are the simplest.
Hanging has less chance
of damaging the heart.
I'm okay with pain.
Strangulation is better
than breaking your neck.
Which means this'll be slow.
I wouldn't get to see him
even if we got in the car right now
and broke the speed
limit driving back, would I?
No.
Tell him--
I don't know what to tell him.
Think it's my turn to ask a question,
isn't it?
I don't think so.
'Cause you just asked me
that thing about the speed limit.
What do you wanna know?
If you could hear one thing
from your father, what would it be?
It wouldn't help you.
Try me.
I'd want him to say...
"You were right.
"You did the right thing."
Yeah.
It doesn't help.
I'm Dr. Wilson.
I'm Mrs. Schaeffer.
I'm from Princeton.
My husband and I and our
three children live in Philadelphia.
So, uh...
do you like to swing?
No.
Well, if you change your mind,
I'm in--
House. House!
Is it room 622? 642?
622.
Yeah.
Alibi.
I figured.
They found an open bottle
of aspirin by the body.
Lucky he had a headache.
Reduced trauma to the heart in transit.
Lucky.
That can't be all.
Well, you got a heart out of it.
How many organs do
you want from the guy?
I mean, my father
must have said something.
He couldn't just--
He must have given you
some kind of a message for me.
He said you were right.
You did the right thing.
Right about what?
What does that mean?
How would I know?
He's your dad.
You know what I found
interesting about this case?
That it proved that people
can love unconditionally,
and you can tell yourself
it's not true, but
you'll just end up in a hotel
room in Atlantic City asking someone
- to cut your heart out?
- The hoagie.
You thought this guy was emotionally
confused and that the hoagie
was just a mask to hide
his real feelings towards his son.
It was.
Did you know Tritter was talking
to your team while we were away?
Yeah.
And yet you moved heaven
and earth to get him that mask
with mustard and prosciutto.
Which one of them told you?
All of them.
Which means that none
of them said anything
I have to worry about.
Back to the hoagie.
You think that my
addiction's out of hand.
Your need to be needed is so strong
that you'll give people what they want,
what they need,
what they think they need.
I don't think my enabling is anything
you should be complaining about.
Yes, my name is Dr. James Wilson.
Account number 835687.
The ATM says I've got zero--
What does that mean-- a hold?
Yeah, okay. Thanks.
My accounts have been frozen
as part of a police investigation.
They can't keep your money forever.
No, they can keep it till I agree to
help send you to prison for ten years.
You're getting dinner.
Transcript: FRM - Synchro: jh26
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org