Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
[ Iolaus ]
dd Golden sandals
pulsing around dd
dd Came the ethereal Muses
Filling the hills
of the Centaurs dd
Whoo!
dd The echoing woods dddd
[ Laughs ]
[ Chuckles ]
You're not excited about
this festival, are you?
What's not to get excited about?
Beautiful women--
Yeah.
games, wine-tasting,
beautiful women,
great food,
beautiful women.
[ Laughs ]
Yeah.
Will Electra be there?
Maybe.
Maybe that's
why you're singing.
Off-key, I might add.
Wait a second.
I was not sing--
[ Man ]
Hand over your money!
We have no money!
We're poor travelers!
They're everywhere we go!
It's amazing, isn't it?
Can't fight back, huh?
[ Laughs ]
Is there a problem here?
No, we're just having
a little discussion.
Oh. See,
we love discussions.
What do ya
wanna try next?
Thermopylae.
Oh, no.
One!
Two!
Three!
Let's get outta here!
Come on! Run!
- They're like a two-man army!
- It still works.
Yeah, if you're 18.
[ Laughs ]
Don't worry. They won't
bother you anymore.
Lahti and I
can't thank you enough.
We're on our way to Kastus.
If we'd known the road
was full of bandits,
we would have
paid for escorts.
W-Well, how about if I
escort you there?
Yeah, we'll do it for free.
We? I thought you were
in a hurry to get
to the festival.
Well, yeah, but--
No, Iolaus, I can
walk 'em both there--
Okay!
Hey!
Uh-- I'll catch up
with you later.
You-- Sure.
Yeah. Okay.
He loves festivals.
Shall we go?
Great Hera, as your
special day approaches,
I appeal to you.
The people of Kastus and I
have served you well.
But since my son's death,
we have lost our
former honor and glory.
Help restore us
to our previous power...
that we may serve you better.
Please, show us a sign,
that we may know
what you have in store for us.
[ Laughs ]
Queen Parnassa?
Lonius, our prayers
are answered.
Hera's sending someone
to restore our kingdom
to its former glories.
Who, my lady?
A warrior without equal--
one who will make
our kingdom invincible.
Please, my lady,
his name.
Hercules.
It's awfully nice
of you to accompany
Styros and me to Kastus.
My pleasure.
We've worked
too long and hard...
to give up our
life savings to bandits.
You know, we've thanked you,
but we haven't even
learned your name.
Whoa!
Look out!
[ Grunts, Groans ]
Oh!
It's stone!
That's quite a knock
you took there.
You all right?
I'm-- I'm fine,
once my head stops pounding.
Thanks for your help.
That's twice
you've saved our lives.
And we still don't
know your name.
Neither do I.
[ Man Narrating ]
This is the story
of a time long ago,
a time of myth and legend,
when the ancient gods
were petty and cruel,
and they plagued mankind
with suffering.
Only one man dared
to challenge their power--
Hercules.
Hercules possessed a strength
the world had never seen,
a strength surpassed
only by the power of his heart.
He journeyed the earth,
battling the minions
of his wicked stepmother, Hera,
the all-powerful
queen of the gods.
But wherever
there was evil,
wherever an innocent
would suffer,
there would be... Hercules.
- [ Screeching ]
- [ Roaring ]
Hail!
[ Grunts ]
This may not help you
remember your name,
but it should keep
the swelling down.
We better get going, Lahti.
We must make Kastus by sundown.
Kastus?
Ring a bell?
No.
[ Chattering ]
My lady, I can't see how
this can possibly work.
Doesn't Hera want Hercules dead?
This is better than dead.
To lose his memory--
his identity--
and spend the rest of his days
serving his stepmother?
But even if she does rob
Hercules of his memory,
the people of Kastus
still have theirs.
They won't believe
he's their long lost prince.
Why not?
Prince Milius has been
gone from us for five years.
We've kept his death from them
for half that time.
They want to believe he's alive.
Don't you see?
These people don't care
who leads them,
they just want to be led.
Perhaps.
But there's always a few.
Well, it'll be your job to keep
the streets free of doubters.
All we need is three days.
If we can convince Hercules
that he is Prince Milius,
get him to pledge his loyalty
to Hera on Equinox Day,
he'll be hers,
and ours, forever.
Now, that's insane.
We'll never get away with it.
The soldiers know
what Milius looks like.
Soldiers follow orders.
And the townspeople?
Live in fear
of the soldiers.
How often did they ever get
to see their prince anyway?
Yeah, but this Hercules,
I-I can't see how--
Well, you'd better see!
Unless you want to incur
the wrath of your queen,
or Hera, it would be
smart to cooperate.
Sir, travelers approaching.
Just as Parnassa said.
Garas, get ready
to meet your new prince.
You don't remember
any of your past?
All I can see
are blank faces.
Styros, who was
that cute little man
he was traveling with?
I was traveling
with a cute little man?
Blond, blue-eyed.
Said he was
going to a festival.
Don't you
remember his name?
No.
Milius!
Prince Milius!
By the gods!
You're alive!
Our prince
has come back to us!
- E-Excuse me?
- My lord.
[ Chuckles ]
My friend!
I can't believe that you've
survived all these years!
Welcome back, Sire.
You know this man?
Fool! This is Prince Milius.
Returned to us from the war...
by the mercy of the gods.
No, no.
Please. Please.
I'm sorry, but I don't know
what you're talking about.
Oh, Garas,
he doesn't remember us.
Must be shock
or a war wound.
Oh, come, my prince.
You're in safe hands now.
Where are we going?
Your castle.
Your kingdom.
Huh?
I--
So I'm a prince.
This way, Sire.
Come along now.
I knew he was royalty.
I could tell by the way
he handled himself.
Mm. Hmm!
Sire.
Milius!
[ Laughs ]
My son!
Thank Hera!
You're... my mother?
He's lost
his memory, my queen.
Undoubtedly from the war.
Well, that doesn't matter.
The important thing is
you're safe!
Your memory
will return in time,
and your wife can help
in that area.
Wife?
Milius.
Oh! I thought
you'd never return.
I'm-- I'm sorry, I--
Is something wrong?
He can't remember
anything, Kirin. Something
to do with the war.
He'll need your help.
Yes. We have a lot
of catching up to do then.
Your sons
can't wait to see you.
Sons?
Boys, go give
your father a hug.
They... seem
a little uncomfortable.
They don't remember you.
Macareus was only two
when you left,
and I was carrying Protos.
Why don't you two guys
show me your toys.
Okay.
That broke the ice.
[ Chuckling ]
[ Chattering, Laughing ]
[ Man ]
I've got it. Thanks.
[ Woman ]
I wanna see the archers.
[ Man ]
How about a small wager?
[ Man #2 ]
Ten dinars for the archer
on the left.
Iolaus!
Juris!
Good to see you!
Where's Hercules?
Oh, you know,
off being heroic.
Creating the stuff
that legends are made of.
He'll be along soon.
I hope so.
The festival wouldn't be
the same without him.
Looking for Electra?
No.
She here?
Yeah, and she's
looking for you.
Really?
She wants you
to meet her cousin.
Whoa! Ah--
Two against one?
Okay. Oh!
I give up! I give up!
Hey! Hey! Watch it!
Hey! You little--
Boys, it's time for bed.
Oh.
Aw!
Now kiss your father
good night and go wash up.
Good night, Father.
Good night.
Good night, boys.
Sweet dreams.
Good night, Mom.
I'll be in in a minute.
Okay.
Along with everything else,
I'd forgotten how much
I miss my family.
You're very good with them.
They're good kids.
Well, they should be.
They're your sons.
Yeah.
[ Chuckles ]
Is anything coming back?
You know, I--
I won't lie to you.
You know, I have--
I have this sense,
you know?
This feels...
good and warm and natural,
but every time
I think back,
all I can see
are blank faces.
There's no rush.
It'll all come back.
We have plenty of time.
Yeah.
Your move.
Thank you, my queen.
It's working, Lonius.
I can feel it.
When the sun strikes
the Hera stone
on Equinox Day...
and Hercules
pledges his loyalty,
he'll do
whatever we want.
With a leader like Hercules,
Gorgos would be ours
for the taking.
Forget Gorgos! We'd rule
the peninsula within a year.
[ Groans ]
My lady,
may I have a word?
In private.
What is it?
You look troubled.
I can't go through with this.
Why? Does Hercules
suspect something?
No, nothing.
It's just that he's...
nice, decent.
It's not fair.
And was it fair that Milius
was taken from us...
on the eve of
Kastus's greatest victory?
No, but I sense
in Hercules a--
a longing
for his own family.
To make him live this lie--
I'd worry about
your own children.
What are you saying?
You wouldn't--
It's a big castle, Kirin.
Accidents can happen.
Lonius, I appreciate your
arranging this tour for me,
but do we really need
all these bodyguards?
Uh, one can never be
too cautious, my lord.
You have many enemies
in the neighboring
kingdom of Gorgos.
Why is that?
It's very complicated.
Welcome home,
Prince Milius.
Uh, betrayal, revenge.
Goes back generations.
Sire.
I'm still not comfortable
with these... clothes,
or people
bowing down to me.
I'm sure it'll grow on you,
my lord, as your memory
comes back.
- Hey, I know that man.
- Come, my lord.
And he's not our prince!
I saw him in Corinth once--
Shut up!
Why did he say that?
Ah! Five years
is a long time, my lord.
You know,
you look different now.
So don't we all, huh?
[ Chuckles ]
You! You remember
Prince Milius, don't you?
- Uh, I'm not sure.
- You're not?
O-O-Oh, I mean, uh,
o-of course I do.
It's just that, uh,
without his beard--
My lord!
No, no. Please,
please. Stand.
This way, my lord.
[ Chattering ]
I think we can
get through here.
Ah! Damn. These alleys
all look the same.
Just like old times, huh?
After them!
Don't let 'em get away!
Yes, sir!
What was that all about?
Come on.
I recognized one of 'em.
They were sent from Gorgos
to assassinate you.
Let's get back to the palace.
Why so glum, Iolaus?
You should be enjoying yourself.
Hercules should have
been here by now.
[ Chuckles ]
You're worried about Hercules?
If he can't take care
of himself, who can?
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah.
Come on. You're judging
the grape-picking race.
No, I don't think so.
Electra's in it.
Okay, uh--
When I start banging
the drum, you all start
picking the grapes!
[ Women ] All right!
First one
to the end, wins!
Everybody ready?
[ Woman ]
I'm ready.
You ready?
[ Giggles ]
Go!
[ Cheering ]
[ Man ]
Come on, Electra!
Show 'em how it's done!
Go, woman!
My money's on you!
A kiss for the winner!
[ Woman ]
Faster! Faster!
[ Iolaus ]
You're gonna win!
[ Laughs ]
And the winner is--
[ Giggles ]
So how did
our little ruse work?
It almost didn't.
This Hercules, he's better
than they say he is.
We're lucky we didn't
lose anyone.
But now he considers
Gorgos his enemy.
Oh, yes.
Good.
With a prince who can lead
his soldiers by example,
the other provinces
will fall like dominoes.
Okay!
Everybody ready for
the grape-crushing competition?
[ Cheering ]
On your marks. Get set.
Crush!
[ Chattering ]
Come here, sweetie!
[ Giggles ]
Tell me something.
How did we meet?
It might
help me to remember.
Well, um--
One day I was in a field
picking flowers,
and, uh--
I looked up
and there you were,
staring down at me.
Hm.
You said
that there was, um--
that you had never seen
anything more beautiful
than those flowers.
[ Laughs ]
I was-- I was shocked
that a prince could talk
to a commoner like that.
There's nothing
common about you.
[ Laughs ]
You sent me flowers
every day during
our courtship.
Dozens of them.
You even scattered
flower petals on our bed
on our wedding night.
Is any of this
coming back to you?
I get these
glimpses, but--
I still can't see any faces.
Maybe this will help.
Kirin,
you're very attractive--
and I-I-I feel
you're a good person, but--
See, I'd rather wait,
see, until I get
my memory back.
Can you understand that?
Of course.
[ Labored Breaths ]
And, uh, the winner
of the grape-crushing
competition--
Iolaus! You'll never
believe what this
crazy old coot told me!
He said he saw Hercules
dressed as a prince.
I'm telling you it was him.
Plain as day.
I met him in Corinth years ago,
and I know Hercules
when I see him.
Wait, wait, wait.
You saw Hercules?
Yeah.
Where?
In Kastus!
In royal robes, no less.
And not enjoying it very much,
if you ask my opinion.
They tried to shut me up,
but, ah, they don't scare me.
[ Hercules, Children Laughing ]
[ Hercules's Voice ]
Aeson, come here!
Hey, Ilea!
Oh, no. Let's find
your mother first.
[ Deianeira's Voice ]
I love you.
Are you okay?
Shh.
What a strange dream.
Dream about what?
I--
Nothing, nothing.
I think...
I'll take a walk.
Maybe it'll clear my head.
[ Man ] Sire?
[ Hercules ] Oh, no. Please.
Get up.
Sire.
No. Don't.
[ Man ]
Did you see that?
[ Man #2 ]
Yes. The prince himself.
[ Chattering ]
Excuse me.
No, don't.
Do you--
Do you recognize me?
No, my lord. But I really
didn't see much of you
before you went off to the wars.
[ Man ]
It's not our place to mix
with the likes of royalty.
But you do remember
seeing me before the war.
Do I look the same?
No, but you had a beard then.
Prince Milius!
[ Sighs ]
[ Chuckles ]
We were looking
all over for you, my lord.
You had the queen
and your wife worried.
Well, I thought I might
take a little unguided tour.
Not a wise choice
without a bodyguard.
You never know when
your enemies may strike again.
Let's have a drink.
There's a tavern up ahead.
You really must be more careful.
Man!
Excuse me.
Have you seen
a guy, big guy?
Out of the way!
Yes, sir.
This is the place,
my lord.
Ah.
Hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey!
You told me you saw Hercules
dressed like a prince.
I have been searching
for him everywhere,
and I still can't find him!
Have you tried the palace?
[ Mimicking Man ]
"Have you tried the palace?"
Palace! Come on, Iolaus.
Get a brain.
Off limits.
Royalty inside.
That's no royalty!
That's Hercules!
I met him in Corinth once--
Oh!
Hey, what's
going on here?
Stay out of this!
Yeah, but--
Oh! About time
you show--
What's... with
the c-clothes?
I-- I think
the little guy knows him.
I was afraid
of this, my lord. I think
we have another assassin.
Why is he purple?
Insanity?
Birth defect?
Who knows?
But I think...
you should get rid of him,
once and for all.
Kill him, my lord.
He's your enemy.
This doesn't feel right.
Escort this man
to the border unharmed
as a gesture of peace.
But, my lord--
He was sent from Gorgos
to assassinate you!
You heard my wishes.
Do as your prince commands!
Yes, sir!
Have them take him
down an alley,
and when he's out of sight,
have them kill him.
Mm.
The streets are empty here.
This is as good a place as any.
What is it now, Lonius?
I'm not so sure your prince will
lead us into battle after all.
If you're still worried about
the people of Kastus accepting
him as their prince, then don't.
After the ceremony,
it won't make any difference.
Oh, we have bigger
problems than that.
What?
He regained his memory?
Ha! Worse.
Instead of invading Gorgos,
your Prince Hercules
wants to make peace.
We just need one more day.
Once Hercules vows
his allegiance to Hera,
it won't matter what he thinks.
He'll be under her spell
and do whatever she commands.
Thin firing slots
in the armor...
make it almost impossible for
spears and arrows to penetrate.
Who thinks up these things?
Ingenious, isn't it?
A combination of levers
and pulleys can fire
a spear through a house.
[ Man ]
Fire!
[ Laughs ]
Impressive, huh?
Uh, I--
I still don't understand
why you'd wanna do this.
[ Horses Galloping ]
[ Man ]
Something's wrong
with the horses!
[ Man #2 ]
Rein them in
before we lose them!
What are you idiots doing?
Get back here!
Psst!
What are you doing here?
I'm trying to figure out
what's going on.
- Why did you hit me before?
- Well, you were trying
to hurt my friend.
- I'm your friend!
- Why are you purple?
What does it matter?
You really can't remember
who you are?
[ Sighs ]
No, it's nothing.
That's crazy!
Y-You're Hercules!
Son of Zeus.
The slayer of the Minotaur,
the Hydra, the--
I'm sorry, but that...
doesn't ring a bell.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Uh, don't panic.
Uh, we gotta jog
your memory. Um--
You remember the Cyclops?
No.
The Stymphalian bird?
Stymph--
Mm-mmm, sorry.
[ Sighs ]
Uh, Typhon, Echidna.
Uh, Salmoneus.
Yeah?
No.
[ Man ]
Easy. Easy. Easy.
Come on. Come on.
Get out of there.
Help get this fixed.
Hurry up
and be careful.
We were all Argonauts.
Remember?
[ Sighing ]
I thought he was dead.
Get him!
Come on! Let's go!
Yeah, so you were
swallowed by a sea monster,
then you were spat out!
And then you rescued
a girl from a kitten
that sounded like a monster!
And what about the time
I got struck by lightning?
And you, you fell in love.
And I could see the future.
And then you fought
yourself when Proteus
was disguised as you!
Only it wasn't you.
It was it was this
ugly, ugly... thing!
Because your mother
taught you to be polite
no matter what.
And so what happened--
Thanis had to come in and--
Oh, not again!
He's quite a storyteller.
Storytellers
don't look like grapes.
This guy's crazier
than a Harpy.
Oh, we should probably
lock him up for his own good.
[ Man Screaming ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Man ]
Get him out of there!
[ Clamoring ]
Go on. Get back.
Get him out of there.
[ Man ]
It's amazing.
You--
You always were
uncommonly strong, my lord.
I was?
Just one more night, my dear.
That's all.
What about the purple man
who says he knows him?
He won't live
to see the morning.
My dear Kirin,
after the sun strikes
the Hera stone tomorrow,
you'll be joined to one
of the world's living legends.
And one day,
after I'm gone,
you'll rule
as king and queen,
a throne that eventually
will go to one of your sons.
If you can't do this
for me or yourself,
do it for them.
The same sons
you threatened to kill?
These have been stressful times
and sometimes I say things
I come to regret, but--
you must know
I would never ever
harm my grandchildren.
Now, go.
Do what you must.
You've done wonders
for the children.
They've really missed
having a father.
I feel like there's
been a lot missing
out of my life too.
These are for you.
Oh, that's very sweet.
You say it as if
I've never done anything
like this before.
No, it's just that he--
I-I mean, you--
Y-You were never s-so--
so kind and gentle
before the war.
The war must have
changed you.
How could I have ever
treated you differently?
I think I'm falling
in love with you...
all over again.
I still can't
recall our past.
But the way
I feel about you--
I don't think
I can wait until I do.
Then don't. Don't wait.
I could get in
a lot of trouble
for this, my lady.
Don't be insolent.
[ Gasps ]
Who are you?
I'm Princess Kirin.
Milius's wife.
Why are you purple?
I like it.
What do you want?
I wanna know
about your friend.
Hercules? Why?
Because I'm in love
with him, and I think
he's in love with me.
Oh, great.
[ Kirin Screams ]
Guard! Please come!
Put down your sword
and open the door. Huh?
Okay, back.
Back, back, back, back.
Now, don't make a sound,
or I'll kill her.
What is going on here?
You behave
or your princess dies.
- Who cares?
- You pig!
You swine!
Come on!
He's gone. They must
already be preparing him
for the vows of allegiance.
Will Hera's priests
be attending the ceremony?
Of course.
Okay. Here's what
we're gonna do.
I'm proud of you, my son.
You've memorized
your pledge?
Yes, Mother.
My queen,
the purple man has escaped.
Let's not take any chances.
Close off the ceremony
to all outsiders.
Mm-hmm.
Let the ceremony begin.
We gather once more...
to pledge our loyalty
to Hera, our patron goddess,
and to thank her
for delivering
our Prince Milius back to us.
Today, my son
will show his gratitude...
by vowing his
allegiance to Hera,
asking for her guidance
as he leads us in battle,
that we may
vanquish our enemies.
My prince?
On this,
the first day
of the autumnal equinox,
I vow my allegiance... to--
I vow my allegiance to--
Hercules, don't.
Remember Deianeira.
Deianeira?
Your real wife.
And Aeson, Klonus,
and Ilea, your children.
My children.
[ Parnassa ]
You see? It's too late.
Hera!
Kill them!
Kill them all!
[ Man ]
Get him!
Over here!
Thermopylae!
What?
One! Two!
Three!
That still works!
This is for the tavern.
And this is for the field.
And this is just
on principle, friend.
You betrayed me!
[ Screaming ]
[ Lonius ]
Queen!
Come on! With me!
All right!
No!
The queen is dead!
Put down your weapons!
As your prince,
I command you.
Come on.
Very well.
Hercules,
are you really back?
Yes, I am, Iolaus.
And you know what?
You look good in purple.
[ Chattering ]
Hercules, wait!
Wait for us!
Now, you two,
you listen to your mother.
She's the new queen,
and good princes
obey their queen, don't they?
Mm-hmm.
Come on.
Give me a hug.
Bye, Hercules.
I don't want you to go.
I'll miss you.
Good-bye.
Bye.
And we'll miss you.
I'm sorry this can't
end differently.
It could
if you wanted it to.
No.
You know what I do,
what my life is about.
No, I know.
And I could never keep you
from your destiny.
The world needs you too much.
Will you come back
this way again?
I'll come back this way again.
I'll think of you always.
And I you.
Good-bye.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org