Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I couldn't help wondering why you'd
risk your life to save such a man.
You have such a strange job. I can't
decide if it's heroic or absurd.
Why would you risk your life
to kill a man like that?
- Read my psychological profile.
- I don't believe in them.
Nor do I. A man's actions don't equal
the sum of his psychological parts.
- It doesn't work that way.
- Just how does it work?
It doesn't work. God doesn't punish
the wicked and reward the righteous.
Everyone dies.
Some die because they deserve to.
Others die because they come
from Minneapolis. It's meaningless.
If none of this means anything,
why kill the President?
- To punctuate the dreariness.
- You need to get yourself laid.
You're the same. Name one thing
in your life that has any meaning.
- I play the piano.
- That's not enough.
How do you know? Do you play?
I've seen you in your bar alone.
There's no cause worth fighting for.
All we have is the game.
- I'm on offence. You're on defense.
- When do we start playing the game?
The clock's ticking, Frank.
Take care.
He scrambled it. I missed him.
Fuck!
Jesus, Frank.
I called for hours.
I thought something happened to you.
I'm sick, I'm tired
and I'm armed, too. So be careful.
- You're also maybe a genius.
- Not to be recognized in this lifetime.
- Did you listen to the call?
- Yeah, remember...?
Call the field office in Minneapolis.
See what you can find
about the accidental deaths.
Frank!
Will you listen to me, please?
- Spit it out, damn it!
- We spoke to some model builders.
There is a professor at Pasadena
College. I think we've got something.
I met him at a design conference
in New Orleans a year ago.
We ordered a few rounds of drinks.
He seemed like a nice enough guy.
But when we talked politics
he got a nasty edge.
He said the government betrayed him
and he was out for revenge.
The way he said it scared me.
I said, "Nice talking to you. "
And I got the hell out of there.
For the life of me
I cannot remember his name.
But I'm pretty sure
he said he was from Phoenix.
You ought to talk to a guy
in Phoenix named Walter Wickland.
- We're going to Phoenix.
- Let's get a police artist.
- Have a sketch faxed to us.
- You figured that out by yourself?
- Kiss my ass, Frank.
- I told you you'd make a good agent.
That doesn't look much like him,
but it's got to be Mitch Leary.
- I haven't seen him in over a year.
- What do you know about the guy?
You see this wheelchair?
Mitch bought it for me.
It cost over $1,000.
- You see this?
- Take it easy now.
This is in case he ever comes back.
He accused me
of ripping off his design.
He said my penalty for disloyalty
was death.
If you put him away,
I'll sleep better.
- Where can we find him?
- I've got his address somewhere.
Don't move.
Drop it!
- Let him go, Horrigan.
- I got him.
It's okay. We're on the same team.
- Hands, motherfucker!
- I'm getting my identification!
- Give it to me.
- David Coppinger. CIA.
- And who's this asshole?
- He's with me.
- God dammit!
- Are you here for Leary or me?
Mr. Leary used to be
one of our operatives.
- He's threatened to kill the President.
- We didn't think he was serious.
- But you knew. You and the FBI.
- I understand your frustration.
You understand my frustration?
You pompous son of a bitch!
What did Leary do for you?
Run drugs? Sell arms to Iran?
It's a C-12 matter,
so this is off the record.
If asked, I'm going to deny it.
- Leary's what we call a wet boy.
- What's a wet boy, Frank?
- Leary's an assassin.
- He's more like a predator.
- Was that you shooting?
- Yes.
- What kind of gun is that?
- Something I made.
You made it?
That beats paying for it.
- Can I see it?
- Yeah.
- It's light. What's it made of?
- It's composite. Like plastic.
Pretty neat!
Mind if I give her a little dance?
- Not at all.
- Go for it.
That is great! That is really great!
- Would you sell it?
- No, I need it.
- For what?
- To assassinate the President.
- Why would you want to do that for?
- Why did you kill that bird?
Leary was one of our most effective
contractors, but times changed.
Cutbacks had to be made.
Leary didn't take it too well.
- We've not been able to locate him.
- We can work together on this.
- Wouldn't that be refreshing?
- We have fingerprints and photos.
- These are at least 15 years old.
- He's camera-shy.
He'll be in disguise, anyway.
We need photo alterations, Sam.
What I'm about to show you
is highly classified.
This is a former colleague
of Leary's. A close friend.
He went by Leary's home to try
and get him to accept counseling.
This is how Leary
treats his friends.
We need every possible variable.
Facial hair, glasses, weight change.
Keep in mind
he's 15 years older now.
As good as they are, they aren't
much good. The eyes are dead.
You can always tell a man
by his eyes.
- Tomorrow morning I'd like you to...
- I'm resigning tomorrow.
What?
What for? Because you were scared
down in Phoenix? I was scared too.
I have nightmares about that
boat with the bag over my head.
I can't breathe.
Phoenix clinched it.
- The service has counselors.
- I've been to counselors.
- We can get this guy.
- I can't do it!
Stop this cockamamie shit.
Come on, pal, I need you.
Please.
Okay, Frank.
Cockamamie. That's a word
your generation hasn't embraced yet.
You ought to use it once in a while
to keep it alive.
- Cockamamie!
- Yeah.
- Oh, God!
- Well, it made you laugh.
You kill me, Frank.
Hello, Frank. And let me welcome
all of you joining our programme.
I know who you are, Leary.
I'm glad. Friends should be able
to call each other by name.
- We're not friends.
- Sure, we are.
I've seen what you do to friends.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- You slit your friend's throat.
- You talked to Coppinger?
- Yeah.
Did you de-louse?
The man's a professional liar.
- I saw the photos.
- No, you saw what he wanted you to see.
I saw a picture of your friend
with his throat cut.
What you don't know
is that they sent my best friend...
...to my home to kill me!
- Your voice is shaking.
- I haven't lied to you, Frank!
Everyone who ever knew you
says you're sick.
- Your colleagues. Your wife.
- What does your wife say about you?
Frank, I want you to understand.
We both used to think that this
country was a very special place.
Do you have any idea
what I've done for God and country?
Some horrible things!
I don't even remember who I was
before they got their claws into me.
- They made you into a real monster.
- And now they want to destroy me.
What do you see when you're in
the dark and the demons come?
I see you standing over the grave
of another dead President.
- That's not gonna happen.
- Fuck you, Frank.
I'm willing to trade my life
for his and that's all it takes.
That President is coming home
from California in a box.
- Where in California?
- The address?
I'll keep you in the game,
but I won't throw it for you.
- I want you to give yourself up.
- To live a long and fruitful life?
Don't lie to me.
I have a rendezvous with death.
So does the President.
And so do you, if you get too close.
- You have a rendezvous with my ass!
- You know how easily I could kill you?
I've watched you go home.
You are alive because
I have allowed you to live.
Show me some damn respect!
St. Francis Hotel!
Frank.
Take my hand, Frank.
Take it. If you don't, you'll die.
Take it.
You're gonna shoot me
after I saved your life?
The only way to save the President
is to shoot me.
Are you willing
to trade your life for his...
...or is life too precious?
Leary, don't move!
I got him!
Al?
There's nothing here.
Frank, you've got a phone call.
Frank, you looked so sad on the bus.
I'm sorry, it was self-defense.
- Tell me about Skellum.
- Skellum is worthless.
- Are you gonna meet him in L.A.?
- You're way behind in the game.
I'm way ahead. I know what you
look like. I've seen your eyes.
- They might look different next time.
- Not what's behind them.
- You better pray I never find you.
- You want to kill me, Frank?
That's right.
- The irony's so thick here.
- There is no irony!
The same government that trained
me to kill, trained you to protect.
Now you want to kill me.
Up on that roof I protected you.
They'll write books about us.
- I'm tired of your bullshit!
- Don't be a poor sport.
You could have taken me out,
but you chose to save your ass.
It does make me wonder about Dallas.
Did you really do all you could,
or did you make a choice there too?
Do you really have the guts
to take a bullet?
I'll be thinking about that
when I'm pissing on your grave.
There's no one named Skellum
in all of Los Angeles?
- What about Louisiana?
- Hang on.
No Skellums. Sorry.
Damn it!
- The election's in three weeks.
- Just stay out of California.
If this guy's so smart, he's not gonna
tell you where he'll do it.
I don't think he'd lie to me.
You've become that close?
California is the key
to the whole race.
- We can't let up now.
- We have to change our procedure.
- Frisk people within 50 yards.
- At $10,000 dinners?
- You're overreacting.
- Lf I don't, the President's dead.
- Why is he even here?
- He's heading this investigation.
Then let him investigate,
but keep him out of sight.
If you'll excuse me,
I'm in the middle of a campaign.
Frank. Hi.
- Up late?
- L.A. Will be a lot of work.
- What's up?
- I've got a request.
I'd like you to talk to Watts.
Get me on your team.
- He thinks you'll overreact.
- What do you think?
- You're too close to all this.
- That's why I've got to be there.
- I can spot him. Anticipate him.
- You think he'll be in California?
- Why would he tip you off?
- He wants to keep the game close.
This has nothing to do with
you and me. Strictly professional.
But that son of a bitch
killed my partner. My friend.
I know. I'm sorry.
You're looking at a living legend.
The only active agent
who ever lost a President.
Please.
Mr. Horrigan, welcome to Los Angeles.
Can the President close the gap
in the little time he has left?
Today he's in California for a rally
at the Bonaventure Hotel.
Field office, the advance team
is at the Bonaventure.
- Any problems?
- No.
We've swept the motorcade route.
Manholes are secured. Mailboxes
removed. Abandoned vehicles towed.
We'll need sharpshooters
on both those towers.
We need sharpshooters
to cover those restricted areas.
Other polls today had the President
three points behind.
He'll have to close that margin
in California.
Welcome to Los Angeles
International Airport.
- Raines, double-checking those exits?
- Yes, this is the third time now.
Alert, section five.
Secret Service.
- Robert Stermer.
- He's a bellboy. He's cleared.
- Robert, have a nice day.
- No questions.
Come on, pack it up and move.
Mr. Carney, all set.
Finally we meet!
You are James Carney?
- You must be Sandy Riggs.
- So you really do exist.
- I'm very much human.
- Let's go up to the bar.
- When does the President arrive?
- Tomorrow, before dinner.
Here's an invitation. Don't lose it.
The Secret Service is acting crazy.
You've got a great seat,
just across from the President.
So what is Microspan Corporation
all about?
I just came to meet the President.
I won't bore you with business.
I don't blame you.
I don't understand high-tech.
I can't wait to introduce you.
Look at this beautiful view.
Yes, very pretty.
Give me the list of dinner guests.
Who was the organizer?
Sanford Riggs
of the California Victory Fund.
Call LAPD and make sure
they have no uniforms missing.
- It's been taken care of.
- Call the hospital about blood.
Your average American businessman
who looks at product marketing...
...sees the length and width of it.
The Japanese see the depth.
We plan the next fiscal quarter.
They plan the next quarter century.
- Our people don't understand that.
- Mr. Riggs, can I talk to you?
- Who's that?
- Secret Service agent.
- Do you know all these people?
- I sure do.
- How about these pictures here?
- I went through all this yesterday.
I'll cooperate, but this is
bordering on harassment.
I'm a harassing kind of guy.
No, no, no, no.
I'll be right back, Mr. Carney.
He did what anyone of us would.
He beat up a bellboy on television.
I'd say he was overwrought.
We're all overwrought.
Leary's out there someplace.
- You don't think he's a liability?
- No.
Well, you're in the minority.
I want him gone.
- Send him on to San Diego.
- By whose order?
Traveler.
Do you want to tell him or should I?
Miss Raines, somebody's
approaching Traveler’s suite.
- Hi.
- What are you doing up here?
- Seeing what I could do.
Between the LAPD,
the FBI and the rest of us...
...there are 229 people
protecting Traveler tomorrow.
A lot of guns.
If Leary gets off a shot,
we could be killed in the crossfire.
Frank.
- Bill Watts just called.
- Heard about the bellman?
So did Traveler.
They want you to go to San Diego
and assist in the advance.
Just like that.
It's not just you against Leary.
Have some faith in the rest of us.
You know something?
For years I've been listening
to all these idiots...
...with their pet theories on Dallas.
It was the Cubans, or the CIA.
The white supremacists, or the mob.
Whether it was one weapon
or whether it was five.
None of that meant too much to me.
But Leary...
He questioned whether I had the guts
to take that fatal bullet.
God, that was a beautiful day.
The sun was out.
It had been raining all morning.
The first shot
sounded like a firecracker.
I looked over and saw him.
I could tell he was hit.
I don't know why I didn't react.
I should've reacted.
I should've been running.
I just couldn't believe it.
If only I'd reacted,
I could've taken that shot.
It would've been all right with me.
- What's the number in San Diego?
- 619 ukulele.
- Ukulele?
- That's how I remember it.
You just push U-K-E-L-E-L-E.
- Ukulele? Isn't that U-K-U?
- I don't know.
But the phone number is U-K-E-L-E-L-E.
U- K-E-L. Wait a second.
Jesus.
We have an arrival.
Chopper standing by.
- Southwest Savings, may I help you?
- Southwest?
- Yes. May I help you? Hello?
- What's your address?
Taxi!
- Post check. Post 3?
- In place.
- Post 6?
- Post 12?
- In place.
Wait right here.
There's no Leary in our accounts.
Try to imagine him in disguise.
A hat, wigs, that sort of thing.
- I haven't been here long.
- Who was here before you?
- Pam Magnus.
- Where can I find her?
She's dead. She was murdered.
- She was murdered.
- They won't cancel.
- Then make the arrival underground.
- They want a big show.
- We need proof.
- How about a dead president?
I'm pulling up all the accounts
Pam made, but it'll take time.
Fax me the list
as soon as you get them.
All agents in position.
- Please step back.
- Empty your pockets.
Thank you.
You're from Texas, right?
I'm sorry.
Frank! Watts is gonna shit
if he sees you!
- Have you got a fax for me?
- Yeah, what is it? What's this about?
What the hell is going on, Frank?
James Carney.
Carney, James.
- What the hell is he doing here?
- I don't know.
- Who gave you permission...
- He's here. His name is Carney.
- I want the seating chart.
- Give him the chart.
Gun!
Stop! Put the gun down!
Get down!
Don't shoot!
Get him in the car!
Hold your fire!
Get out of his way!
He's got a hostage!
Raines to shooters.
If you have a shot, take it.
Nice view.
- What's the plan, Captain?
- It's your man. You tell me.
Get me sharpshooters
on the north and west towers.
Take the subject out.
You had the guts.
You took the bullet.
- I broke my damn ribs.
- Sorry, I wasn't aiming at you.
Where the hell are the shooters?
- West tower in place. No lights.
- No shot from the north.
A bulletproof vest
is a bit of a cheat.
- Otherwise, you played a good game.
- It's no game, Leary.
I was doing my job.
What do we do now?
Do you believe
in the nobility of suicide?
No.
But if you want to blow your head off,
be my guest.
Nicely put, but I don't want
to leave this world alone.
- West tower, do you have a shot?
- Negative, too dark. Target unclear.
- It's better to die with a friend.
- Friend? You're a damn killer!
I saved your life. You owe me.
- I don't owe you shit.
- I was always honest with you.
- Go ahead and shoot.
- It's Frank. Quiet!
- Come on.
- Are you talking to me?
- What are you waiting for?
- Waiting for?
I'm waiting for some gratitude.
Without me, you're a sad-eyed,
piano-playing drunk.
I brought you into this game.
I let you keep up with me.
- I made you a hero today.
- You didn't make me anything.
I redeemed your pathetic life.
I just did my job.
You're the one with a pathetic life.
- Go ahead and shoot!
- Lf they fire you'll be hit.
- I want you to thank me first.
- Shut up and shoot.
- All right, Frank.
- Stand by to fire on my command.
- Sleep well, my friend.
- Just one thing, aim high.
- What?
- Aim high!
- Now!
- You bastard!
Take my hand.
If you don't, you'll die.
- You want to save me, Frank?
- To be honest, no. But it's my job.
Take it.
Are you okay?
We've worked with Agent Horrigan
for some time.
He exemplifies
courage and self-sacrifice. Frank!
I guess I overreacted again, Harry.
Agent Horrigan, why are you
retiring from the Secret Service?
Well, I hate desk work and I'm
too old for running around.
And thanks to all this press,
I'm no good for undercover work.
How are you, Frank?
The President sent his limo for you.
- That's the least he could do.
- Good. I love public transportation.
Come on in.
Make yourself at home.
- So, what do you think?
- I like it.
Hello, Frank. By the time
you hear this, it'll be over.
The President is most likely dead
and so am I.
Frank, did you kill me? Who won
our game? Not that it matters.
Among friends, like you and me, it's
how you play the game. The game's done.
It's time to get on with your life.
I worry that
you have no life to get on with.
You're a good man.
Good men, like you and me,
are destined to travel a lonely road.
Goodbye and good luck.
I bet you that brown pigeon
flies off before the white one.
How do you know?
I know things about pigeons, Lilly.
Subtitles by
GelulaISDI
Ripped by:
SkyFury
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org